♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 18=
Lin Xiangyuan?
What are you doing here?
Fanlv,
this is for you.
What's this for?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
You've been avoiding me in the company.
You see me now.
You can leave.
Fanlv.
Let me do it.
OK.
I really like you.
Please believe me.
I'll be good to you.
Give me a chance, Ok?
I'll prove it to you.
Ok,
then give it to me.
Fanlv.
Dad, what's the matter?
What is Lin Xiangyuan here for?
For nothing, dad.
Stop lying to me.
I saw everything upstairs just now.
Dad,
there is nothing going on between us.
So, you won't tell me, right?
I'll ask him.
Please don't.
It's Lin Xiangyuan.
He always pesters me.
I'm out, Mr. Lei.
I am not good at fencing.
How can I compete with you?
I'm not Shao Zhenrong.
Right.
You're not Zhenrong.
No one can be him.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lei.
Never mind.
By the way,
I heard Du Xiaosu's not doing well
with her studio.
I'm wondering how
she dares to
start up a studio
without connections or background.
Not that surprising
since she even dares to stop my car
to argue with me.
By the way,
you can go back to the company first.
Ok.
I have other plans.
Need a ride?
What did I tell you?
Being drunk is not a big deal,
but doing stupid things like that is.
Dad,
Yuzheng turned me down that day.
I was upset and drank a lot.
That's why Lin Xiangyuan and I...
I'm not blaming you.
I care about you.
But no matter how upset you were,
you should not have been with
Lin Xiangyuan.
The less you love yourself,
the farther away
Lei Yuzheng will be from you.
Man would never
love a woman more
because she abandoned herself.
It is such a simple truth.
Why can't you get it?
Dad.
Client's coming, client's coming...
Client's coming...
Flower means client.
Flower!
But no client.
It doesn't count this time.
One more time.
Client's coming, client's coming...
Client!
Welcome to Du Xiaosu...
Lei Yuzheng, why are you here?
I just stop by.
Why? Am I not expected?
It is not like that.
Your studio is quiet.
No people here.
Is it going out of business?
Lei Yuzheng,
what are you talking about?
Are you expecting my studio
to close down every day?
What a capitalist you are!
You have no sympathy at all.
I'll talk to Ning Weicheng.
You can come back to Boyuan.
Back to Boyuan?
Are you losing your mind?
Do you think I open this studio
just for fun?
I'm just concerned that
you can't make it,
and might be starving to death.
It's not that far yet.
How do you know that?
I'll hang in there.
Mr. Lin,
to be honest,
I feel unsettled
as I owe money to you.
So, I wanna pay the money
back to you.
Qunfei,
no rush.
You can return that money
anytime you want.
I didn't push you.
I know,
you don't want to owe me.
But in this society,
anyone might
suffer from a very difficult time.
We are friends.
Take me as your sponsor.
I'll give it back to you
as long as I have the money.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
You are welcome.
See you later.
You're so late!
Three drinks to start, Ok?
All right.
A piece of cake.
One toast
to you.
You're so easy today.
I don't know what to say.
One toast to each of you.
Stop it.
I dare not to take it.
You gave him a toast last year.
The final price was lowered
by two percent.
He couldn't do anything about it.
Don't listen to him.
I heard you recently acquired a company,
and want renovation.
Do you need a designer?
A friend of mine is a designer.
Come on, what do you mean?
You don't wanna make
such a little money, do you?
This is not you.
What do you have in your mind?
Ye Shenkuan,
you take your little money back
as soon as possible.
I wanna introduce you
a designer friend.
A man or a woman?
A woman.
It's a woman for sure.
I knew it!
It is a woman. So what?
Yuzheng,
we've known each other
for so many years.
You are on your own.
You never ask for favors.
Why did you do that this time?
Are you in love?
Anyway, this is the deal.
I'll give you her number.
Call her.
But remember
not to tell her that you know me.
Miss Jiang, are you expecting Mr. Lei?
Mr. Lei told me that...
Fanlv.
What are you doing here?
Why? Am I not allowed to be here?
You are.
But next time before you come in,
please knock at the door.
Ok, I'm sorry.
Yuzheng.
I have something to tell you.
Hold on one second.
I have to approve
this contract right now.
I'm getting engaged.
Getting engaged?
Don't you congratulate me?
Are you surprised or
reluctant to let me marry somebody else?
Fanlv.
Congratulations!
You mean it?
We grew up together.
You have your beloved one now,
and are getting engaged.
Of course I'm happy for you.
Don't forget
to give me the invitation.
I'll definitely give you
a big red packet.
Great.
This is it.
Lei Yuzheng,
I've got the best seat for you.
Please be there on time.
(Wedding Invitation to Lei Yuzheng,
from Lin Xiangyuan and Jiang Fanlv)
Wait.
Are you getting engaged
with Lin Xiangyuan?
Why?
Can't I?
Fanlv.
Ok, fine.
He is your fiance now.
It might not be proper for me
to tell you this.
But Lin Xiangyuan
may not be as simple as you think.
Even I can't see him through.
Think about it again.
Lin Xiangyuan
is really not the one for you.
Love is the foundation of marriage.
We grew up together,
so I know you.
You won't be so naive to
take your marriage lightly.
Think about it.
I just want you to be happy.
Happy?
I think I'll be happy.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to
take my marriage lightly.
The clothes are too expensive here.
Let's go somewhere else.
Du Xiaosu.
Can you learn from me?
Look at yourself! Not fashionable!
Look!
Not fashionable?
Does this one look nice?
Is it nice?
(Price: 5280 yuan)
More than 5,000 yuan for this?
Are you nuts?
Who would buy such an expensive coat?
It is expensive. So what?
No input, no output.
Xiaosu,
I think
this coat looks good on you, too.
I don't have the money for
such an expensive coat.
No business yet
since the opening of the studio.
If it goes on like this,
I have to shut it down.
That's why I called you silly.
Give up the work in Boyuan.
Have to live on your own.
You are meant to be poor.
Why did you talk like this?
Hello.
Yes, it is my studio.
I'll take it.
I'll take it for sure!
When are we going to sign the contract?
Great! Brilliant! Thank you!
Ok. Bye.
Siqi!
What happened?
Somebody just called me
and asked me to
decorate an office building
at this price.
It can't be timelier!
I finally don't have to be starving!
I finally can keep the studio!
Renovation of an office building?
At this price?
Xiaosu.
Calm down.
How did he know you?
I didn't ask about this.
Whatever.
Now, we have eggs,
what's the point to know
where they come from?
I'll treat you to dinner!
Not today.
Why?
Shangguan is going on a business trip
to Guangzhou tomorrow.
I have to be with him.
Siqi.
Where are you, you and Shangguan?
Where are we?
We just proceed without a plan.
I support He Qunfei.
Forever.
Xiaosu,
let me tell you the truth.
I'm not like you.
You can be on your own,
begging every day
for a big contract out of nowhere,
and living an unsettled life.
But I can't. Really.
Do you think
I'm so sick and realistic?
Fine.
Then take care of yourself.
Sushi!
So much delicious food!
Zou Siqi,
you care dates much more than mates.
This wine is all for me.
Come on!
Fill the glass!
I, Du Xiaosu,
finally settled in Shanghai!
I have my own studio.
And I just signed a big contract!
Dad! Mom!
You should be happy for me.
I'll try my best.
I'll work hard.
Besides,
I'll become
a real architect.
Cheers!
I'm so happy!
Come on!
Cheers!
Great. Thank you, Shenkuan.
I'll treat you to dinner.
(Du Xiaosu)
(Calling Du Xiaosu)
(Lei Yuzheng)
Lei Yuzheng?
Hello,
this is Du Xiaosu's studio.
What can I do for you?
Du Xiaosu, where are you?
I'm in the botanical garden.
Ok, wait for me.
Another contract!
Du Xiaosu,
your luck in fortune is coming!
You can't even stop it!
Cheers.
I screwed up.
Miss Du.
You look so happy.
What made you so happy?
You didn't even
share it with me.
Are you also offering me a big contract?
I just arrived.
Good for you. Du Xiaosu.
I heard you've got a big contract.
You don't even think about
treating me to dinner,
but come here to enjoy foods alone?
Who told you I was eating alone?
Didn't you see that
Zou Siqi just left?
Du Xiaosu,
you have signed a big contract
as soon as the company is open.
So lucky for you.
Of course. Don't you know who I am?
I, Du Xiaosu,
graduated from a famous
university after all.
When working in Boyuan,
you know my talent was just wasted.
What's so funny?
Fine.
Seems that I didn't value you.
When I go back,
I'll have a serious talk with
Ning Weicheng.
Ok!
To retain the talent like you,
we must offer well-paid job.
How can we have such a talent
drained away to the society?
Isn't this
developing competitors for Boyuan?
You regret it?
But it's not too late yet.
We can join force together.
Well, Miss Du,
how are you going to make it?
Well,
I have to think about it.
Ok.
Miss Du, take your time.
Contact us whenever you're ready.
Yutian
is always waiting for you.
By the way,
when are you going to start to implement
the contract you just signed?
Tomorrow.
To be honest,
I didn't expect that
I'm so valuable.
I'm wondering why the guy is so silly
that he spent that much money
on a designer like me…
What?
Nothing.
I'm happy for you.
Xiaosu, you shouldn't have said that.
He offers you work,
but you're speaking ill of him.
Don't you have a conscience?
I'm not speaking ill of him.
I'm telling you. Don't worry.
This contract,
I'll take it seriously.
I know exactly
what I'm capable of.
Absolutely no problem for this contract.
All right.
Wish you all the best
for your first contract!
Cheers!
Xiangyuan.
Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang, have tea.
You and Fanlv
are getting engaged.
Do you have anything to say to me?
Mr. Jiang, please trust me.
I'll be good to Fanlv.
If she asks me to go east,
I'll never go west.
I promise that
I'll favor her and love her
for my whole life.
From now on,
you can regard me as your son.
I'll be willing to risk any danger
to do whatever you want me to do.
Xiangyuan,
we're gonna be a family soon.
I want to be honest with you.
Frankly speaking,
you're not the son-in-law
I was expecting.
And
you knew it yourself.
Fanlv is the apple of my eye.
As long as you're good to her,
I'll be good to you.
Got it.
Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
From now on,
whatever you ask me to do, I'll do it.
Wait.
I've already given the invitation
to Lei Yuzheng.
Now there is a person
for you to invite.
No problem.
(Wedding Invitation to Du Xiaosu,
from Lin Xiangyuan and Jiang Fanlv)
Miss Du, take a look.
Here it is.
Mr. Ye,
you have a very good location here.
Enough for an office.
By the way,
are you satisfied
with the last design?
Miss Du,
I'm very satisfied with the design.
How about this?
Since we've signed the contract,
you can start anytime.
I'll check as soon as
the renovation completes.
Ok, Mr. Ye.
I’ll do my best!
So, he likes this type.
What?
Nothing. I was kidding.
You're in charge now.
I shall go now.
Ok.
Bye-bye.
See you.
Hello, who is that?
(Wedding Invitation to Du Xiaosu,
from Lin Xiangyuan and Jiang Fanlv)
Are you getting engaged?
Yes.
Congratulations!
Miss Jiang has always been
the one you've been dreaming of.
You should cherish her.
And I wish you all the best.
You have Jiang Fanlv,
and I have someone I loved.
Shao Zhenrong?
But he's...
As long as he is in my heart,
he's always been around me.
Don't worry.
I will be there on time.
-Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
Upstairs, please.
-Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Upstairs, please.
Mr. Huang is here.
Congratulations!
Hello, Mr. Huang.
Come over here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Huang from Ruiyuan Group,
and also one of our shareholders.
This is my son-in-law, Lin Xiangyuan.
He's working in Yutian.
Your support is highly expected.
It's my pleasure.
Kindly give me more advice, Mr. Huang.
Mr. Jiang's son-in-law
must be outstanding.
I‘ll do my best.
-It's very kind of you.
-Upstairs, please.
Why does Fanlv
get engaged so soon?
It was really a shock to me.
As a spectator, I can see that
Fanlv has been having a big crush on
our Yuzheng for years.
Why did she get engaged
to Lin Xiangyuan all of a sudden?
What's the point?
Fanlv did have a big crush on him,
but he
just ignored that.
She is a girl after all,
and she has the dignity.
So,
Yuzheng let Fanlv down, right?
Aunt Shao,
it's Fanlv's freedom to marry
anyone she wants.
It's none of my business.
How dare you?
A good marriage is screwed up.
Jiang even sent me the invitation.
I have to pretend smiling
to attend the ceremony.
You've made me so embarrassed.
Dad, the problem is...
Come on.
You two, just stop.
But Yuzheng,
you're not young anymore.
You should settle down with a girl.
If you don't like Fanlv, that's ok.
But you need to be careful.
Don't be like our Zhenrong.
Such an awful relationship he was in.
Aunt Shao, I'm not in hurry.
I'll take care of you when you're older.
Mr. Jiang. Congratulations!
Kaixuan,
it's more than enough
while you are here.
Don't be so kind.
Uncle Jiang,
congratulations.
This is a little regard
from my dad and me.
Jiang,
congratulations.
Let me see
who's so lucky
to win the heart of our Fanlv.
Kaixuan,
you're flattering Fanlv.
Actually, everyone has
their own preference.
Our Fanlv is worthless
in someone's eyes.
Uncle Jiang,
don't you accept the red packet?
My God, I just saw it.
Thank you.
Yuzheng,
Fanlv used to annoy you a lot.
I apologize for her.
Don't worry. From now on,
I promise she won't annoy you anymore.
It's so kind of you, Uncle Jiang.
Today is the big day for Fanlv.
Why let the past ruin today?
Dad and Aunt Shao,
I will come inside.
Ok. Upstairs please.
Ok. We will go upstairs first.
Please. Thank you.
Du Xiaosu,
why are you here?
Mr. Lei?
Fanlv invited you?
Today I'm the guest of groom.
Why?
Are you coming here to kidnap the bride?
Fanlv is not my type.
Then what's your type?
I can help you.
Let me guess.
First,
she has to be a good-looking,
like the Hollywood actress at least.
Second,
she must come from a well-bred family.
Third, she has to have a good character.
Only the one who is gentle and obedient
can stand your bad temper.
Du Xiaosu,
are you insane?
You make fun of me!
I guess the ceremony will begin soon.
I should go for it now.
From now on, the Leis and the Jiangs
have contradiction with each other.
Pathetic parents' heart.
Jiang is just worrying about Fanlv.
It's normal to make some complaints.
He'll be fine in few days.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
So beautiful.
Aunt Shao.
Dad.
Look,
you won't marry Fanlv,
and Jiang's getting mad at your dad.
And now, your dad is getting mad at you.
Are you gonna eat it?
Today…
Forgive me.
I'm a little excited.
Thank you very much
for coming to my daughter‘s
engagement ceremony.
My daughter Fanlv and Lin Xiangyuan
are in love with each other,
and pledge to marry each other.
I've been thankful for this.
Here,
I kindly hope that everyone here
can help my son-in-law Xiangyuan.
I thank you all here.
It seems Jiang Jin is
pretty satisfied with this son-in-law.
Sure.
Let's raise our glass.
Lin Xiangyuan is not like you.
You are so proud.
Lin Xiangyuan has been
determined to marry Jiang.
He just gets what he wants.
You…
Let's
cheers.
I've heard that this groom
is working for Jiang Jin.
He is not in the high position.
He is just a vice president.
He's already bonded with Mr. Jiang.
Promotion is for sure.
Thank you again
for coming to my daughter's
engagement ceremony.
Thank you.
Du Xiaosu, I don't get you.
It's not your engagement ceremony.
Why were you so excited?
I'm sorry.
I don't know why.
I kind of lost my cool today.
Don't tell me you were touched.
Also,
are you always so sentimental?
I know you don't believe in fate.
But I believe fate is meant to be.
I believe,
everyone has his own love.
It's said that the fate is marvelous.
If two people in the world
can get together in the end,
that would be the best thing
in this world.
What are you thinking?
You have such a special way of thinking.
Du Xiaosu,
you are so naive.
Can you live on fate and love?
Don't you think
there is only love in life?
You have to love deeply
while being laughed by others?
That's what you want?
What do you mean?
Don't you understand?
Understand what?
I do feel like that anyway.
You are so stubborn.
Forget it, and just be naive.
You are really weird.
Why do you have to eat cakes
in the engagement ceremony of others?
Did you see it?
How come I didn't see it
since you were eating like that.
I was so starving.
I saw that cake was pretty good.
I just took several.
It turned out to be really tasty.
I'm telling you,
in that ceremony,
the cake
is the only highlight.
What is that?
Fireworks!
So many of them!
Look over there!
It's so beautiful with all colors.
It's really beautiful!
What a pity.
Just one moment.
Like the happiness.
The more dazzling,
the less possible to keep it.
So what?
At least it was dazzling.
But I'm telling you that
the details are particularly important.
Be sure to focus on details.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪