[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 31]
The great rose of Sharon
♫Grew in the northwest♫
grew in the northwest,
♫Lived on miasma♫
lived on miasma,
grew by rivers,
and flourished to the River Gu.
What does that mean?
I think Four Season Clan is very likely
using miasma as a natural barrier.
So, for all these years,
no one has ever located them.
Where does miasma form?
It's recorded on my waterway map
that miasma tends to form
in the forest north of the River Gu.
Here.
That can't be right.
How can the Clan people get in if there's miasma?
[River Gu]
People are most likely to get lost
near the River Gu where there's miasma.
The great rose of Sharon lived on miasma.
There must be a rose of Sharon wood
on the north bank
and it must be the Clan that planted them.
These trees can absorb miasma
and guide the way.
That must be it.
Finding that forest
means finding their location.
Sounds reasonable.
You're not going, are you?
What do you mean?
You're being so generous.
Run a small business with the money.
Stop selling fake wines
and getting beaten up all the time.
You're not that young anymore.
It's time to think about getting married.
Find a girl
and live a good life together.
I believe in destiny.
How about introducing someone to me?
I'm off.
Let me know if you need such help again.
What a lucky day!
Why did it sound like his last words?
Everyone that gets in or out
is being investigated.
Gates and roads are all blocked off.
Everything is in chaos.
[Mo Wubing, Xu Shiqin, Interior Guards]
Sir Li is so suspicious,
but she only asked us to bring him back
rather than arrest him.
She is so biased.
She even hides this from Sir Wu.
It's not about being biased.
It's a cover-up!
Exactly.
If you've got a problem, say it to my face.
Madam Wu.
You think I'm covering up for Li Beiqi?
Okay.
Then tell me,
what crime did Li commit?
Is there a conviction?
Have you got evidence?
It's been just one day.
You've started to speak ill of him.
Li Beiqi is your comrade,
your buddy who goes through
fire and water with you.
You talk behind his back now.
Then, you'll do the same to others in the future.
If you're ever in danger,
do you still think others will help you?
Madam Wu, Sir Wu wants to see you.
Recite Interior Guards' Motto
100 times before you leave.
Yes, Madam.
Keep order for Her Majesty.
Louder!
Guard Luoyang!
With fortitude and loyalty!
Resoluteness and bravery!
Keep order for Her Majesty!
Guard Luoyang!
With fortitude and loyalty!
The forest to the northwest
of the River Gu is vast
and rarely visited.
Finding the wood of rose of Sharon out of it
is like finding a needle in a haystack.
We've searched the forest.
This is the most suspicious place.
Okay.
Now that the location is clear,
I'll set off.
The Intelligence Services only supervises.
This is all we can do.
We can't support you with more people.
I know.
Whatever happens,
stay safe first.
Retreat immediately if there's any danger.
I won't act recklessly.
If I find anything,
I'll try my best to send a message back.
Baitan,
get a carriage.
I'm going to the Palace to meet Her Majesty.
Why did you not tell me?
We agreed that during your recovery,
I'll carry out your duty.
This is such a big matter.
Can't you tell how serious it is?
It is our own man who's done wrong.
-Li Beiqi has done no wrong!
-No one can live if Her Majesty knows!
He's done no wrong?
How can you make sure of that?
I have absolute trust in him.
There must be something we don't know.
We just need to ask him when he's back.
When he's back?
What if he doesn't come back?
What if he's never coming back?
Do you think that's something
an interior guard should say?
Wu Siyue,
you should be very clear
that Li Beiqi is whom I myself trained.
The last thing I want
is for him to get into trouble.
However, it's because of this
that we cannot cover things up for him.
I am not covering up for him.
Li Beiqi has just gone missing for one day.
How come he is a suspect now?
Because
he is the closest person to us!
I tell you,
I don't want us to be the last to know
if Li Beiqi really has done wrong.
Do you hear me?
I'll go find out the truth now.
The ring puzzle is so hard.
I tried my best,
but they're still just some iron rings.
I can't make a loop out of them.
If I have an extra finger
like you,
I can probably make it.
I've told you a million times.
Do not mention my fingers!
Lord Kuanren.
Brother.
[Baili Kuanren, the eldest son in the Baili family]
Sit down.
Hongyi,
I just scolded you in the study.
It is my fault.
Don't hate me.
You can't work this out, right?
Let me teach you.
Look.
To figure out the ring puzzle
is not about how many fingers you have,
but about finding the trigger in it.
You did work out the second ring,
but you ignored
how the first and the third are related.
Now,
put on the first ring and try again.
I solved it!
Great!
Hongyi,
don't be obsessed with what you've achieved.
Sometimes,
letting things go
can get you some pleasant surprises.
Baili Kuanren lived in fear
after he pleaded guilty
and eventually died of illness at home.
I, Wu Youjue, took Your Majesty's order
and examined the body in the Baili Mansion.
The deceased has six fingers on the right hand.
It can be confirmed that he was Baili Kuanren.
You failed?
My lady,
we were about to succeed,
but...
but arrows came out of nowhere.
We had to leave.
It was you who sent people
to rescue Baili Hongyi, right?
You have no proof,
so you'd better not slander me.
Lord Six-Finger,
I didn't expect that
it's been years after you joined the Clan,
but you're still thinking about
your damn brother.
I tell you,
even though Baili Hongyi is your brother,
he has figured out the secret of the Thunder,
so he must die.
You don't want the great plan
that the Clan has been working on for so long
to fail, do you?
Still,
don't accuse me
until you get evidence.
Baili Kuanren,
do not forget
what you swore
to His Lordship.
I, Baili Kuanren,
shall join Four Season Clan now.
From now on,
I have no parents,
relatives or friends.
All people in the Clan
are my siblings.
Those outside our Clan
are all weeds!
The weeds are all over the fields.
[Lord Freedom, Leader of Four Season Clan]
Set fire to them.
The weeds are all over the fields.
Set fire to them!
My lady,
this suits you the best.
Look at the color.
Believe me. It will look nice.
Look at them.
Am I right?
Don't go.
Look at this.
Bingzhu!
What are the odds?
You're going out of the city, too?
I'm also...
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
Go back now.
It's too dangerous for you to go alone.
You haven't got a child
to pass on your family name to.
The Gao family won't have future generations.
Let's go back, plan carefully,
and get some help before going.
Cut the crap.
This is my own business.
Go back now.
If you keep following me,
I'll break your legs.
Even so, I have to follow you.
Bingzhu, I'm serious.
Go back with me
or bring me with you.
In case anything happens,
I can send your message back.
Then listen,
if there's any danger,
protect yourself first.
If I ask you to leave, you must go.
Don't worry. I'll be the first to run.
If you die,
I can at least bring your body back.
Madam Wu,
the attendance registers
don't seem to have any problem.
Madam Wu,
I've asked everyone
and it can be confirmed
that Sir Li would leave the Services
for unknown places
every one or two days.
Li Beiqi normally reports
before he leaves.
But for the last few days,
there's no record of him on the registers.
How could that be?
Madam Wu,
Sir Li is also my good friend.
I don't want to doubt him,
but now that it's come to this...
I know what you're going to say,
but all I trust is evidence.
Let's go. Check his room.
Siyue,
if it weren't for you today,
that guy would've gotten out of the city.
How did you know he was fishy?
He did try so hard
and darkened himself with paint,
but unfortunately,
he forgot to paint the small part behind his ears.
Who else could it be?
You finally turned the tables around.
I bet no one
would dare to say you relied on Sir Wu
to join the Interior Guard Services.
Interior guards don't drink!
Shh!
This case
is worth an exception.
This is Feng's rice wine.
I saved six months' salary for this.
We must have a taste of it.
Come on.
Then I won't say no.
Madam Wu, something's wrong here.
[Kang Zhanbi, Kang Jin, Li Ji, Dai Zhou]
And this.
Wasp stinger?
The Thunder?
Yes.
It is a weapon that
Four Season Clan has been working hard on.
We can't estimate its power now.
The Clan has been working on such a weapon.
Why was the Intelligence Services
not aware of it at all?
Then, have you figured out
where Four Season Clan is going to use it?
I did not do my job well.
It was all my fault.
-No more confession.
-I...
You're here to see me.
I believe you have got an idea.
I'm afraid the Ceremony of Light
will be full of danger
because of the Thunder.
I beg Your Majesty
to postpone the Ceremony.
You mean that
Four Season Clan plans to ruin the Ceremony
with this weapon.
Are they going to create chaos
or...
They want to kill me.
A merchant from the outlands called Kang Zhanbi
[Kang Zhanbi, Kang Jin, Li Ji, Dai Zhou]
died of Shachi Venom.
He lived here when he was alive.
[Guanglin Inn]
He went missing
after Kang Zhanbi died.
They must be avoiding someone.
To escort Li Ji
was Sir Wu's last-minute decision.
How could one
know it so quickly?
Why are you behind me?
I was working on a case near Xing Jiao Fang.
I saw your horse
tethered at the end of the alley,
so I came to find you.
He died of wasp venom.
Wasp stinger.
Didn't I tell you to keep him safe?
I never left here.
You were still outside.
I was worried, so I waited by the door.
I didn't know he'd...
I don't dare to say so.
I am just worried.
But
I have sent the Halberdier of our Services
to find the hideout
of Four Season Clan on his own.
On his own?
Yes.
On his own.
Then,
I will wait for the good news
from the Halberdier.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will report to Your Majesty
as long as there's any news.
I know what you are thinking about.
You want reinforcements
to stand a better chance.
If he really finds the Clan's hideout,
I can lend troops to you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Kang Zhanbi, Kang Jin, Li Ji, Dai Zhou]
What do you think?
Li Ji and Kang Jin died mysteriously.
Now this name list appeared.
All the evidence seems to point to Li Beiqi.
But now I'm more worried about Beiqi.
He went missing suddenly.
Then we found the evidence in his room.
Is it possible someone set him up?
If so,
he can be in great danger now.
Then how do you explain
the license of the refugees?
Sometimes, it's not easy to let go.
It is hard to accept that Li Beiqi is suspicious.
Siyue,
I will ask someone else
to investigate Li Beiqi.
You're afraid I'll get irrational
and biased towards Li Beiqi.
We are humans.
It's normal to be influenced by emotions.
No more discussion about this.
The top priority now
is the Thunder.
I've asked Baili Hongyi to help you.
He knows it very well.
You know each other, too.
I can feel more relieved this way.
The Ceremony of Light is approaching.
We have to make sure
all the interior guards are loyal.
Even if it's not for Beiqi,
I'm still going to investigate the whole Services.
All right.
[Forest by River Gu, the outskirts of Luoyang]
Don't make a fuss.
Bingzhu,
are we heading in the right direction?
Look at the sun.
We are heading to the northwest.
A rose of Sharon.
That is a rose of Sharon?
It is here then.
You can still leave if you want to.
I...
I'm not scared at all!
[Four]
The Ceremony of Light is approaching.
Our Services must fully support
other ministries' work,
especially the deployment of the Palace Guard
of the Interior Guard Services.
If you find anything suspicious,
report immediately!
Yes, sir!
Be careful.
Yes, sir.
Madam An.
Li Beiqi holds the title of Sir Li.
He is a core interior guard.
Report to me if you've got news about him
for the past three days.
Yes, madam.
[Field Agents]
At 7:20 am,
[Dun Hua Fang]
trouble was stirred up in Dun Hua Fang.
All offenders have pleaded guilty.
[Middlemen]
No relation to the ceremony is found.
By 7:30 am,
the Palace Guard had searched Dun Hua Fang.
[South Market of Luoyang]
By 7:40 am,
all participants of the Ceremony
had collected tokens
from the Interior Guard Services.
[Xiuye, Gong'an]
The interior guards
will only allow the access
of token holders to the Ceremony.
[Wenrou, Sishun]
Violators will be taken as rebels.
The interior guards have checked
the route Her Majesty will take.
Everything's normal.
At 7:40 am,
all gates in Luoyang were temporarily shut.
some stores in Ji Shan Fang
opened, violating the ban.
They now have been shut down.
The violators have been
brought back by the Grant Court.
[Interior Guard Services]
On the day of the Ceremony,
Her Majesty will set off
from the Palace of Origins
and take a tour in the city to show her grace.
The last destination is the Heavenly Temple,
where Her Majesty will light candles and pray.
Here,
here,
and all these places
will be heavily guarded by the imperial guards.
The interior guards should particularly watch
the route Her Majesty will take.
For you,
the most pressing task
is to find where Four Season Clan
[Map of Luoyang]
might have placed the Thunder
as soon as possible.
I think the key is to prevent
the Clan from entering Luoyang.
How would you like to do that?
From now on,
close all city gates.
Before the Ceremony ends,
no citizens in Luoyang can go on the streets.
This way,
we will be able to find
the Clan's whereabouts in the city.
You want to lock down the whole capital?
If it's not feasible,
we can allow citizens to go on the streets,
but merchants from outside can't get in.
It is still a lockdown.
What's wrong?
Luoyang is our capital.
It's the world's center and collects taxes and tributes from all countries.
Regardless of the weather,
we receive numerous ambassadors.
This is exactly why
there can't be any trouble in Luoyang.
The best way is to block the enemy's way in.
If Luoyang is locked down,
we'll be sniffed at by the world.
No more discussion on this.
Luoyang can't be locked down.
In that case,
let me oversee the security work
of the Interior Guard Services.
Okay.
Li Chun.
Sir Wu.
Where's Li Chun?
He's with us. Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Li Chun and others
are being interrogated by Madam Wu.
It's said it is for clearing
the Interior Guard Services of suspicion.
The Thunder searching
needs people.
If the interior guards can't be trusted,
I can get help from others.
Who are you to say that?
Or why did you mention
clearing up your suspicion?
You're not one of us...
Stop it.
Don't worry.
I will arrange trustworthy people for you.
I want those screened by Madam Wu.
Wang Junqing.
Here.
Wang Zhaoyang.
Sui Xin.
Here.
Li Chun.
Madam Wu, you're...
Chen Wu.
Here.
Xu Shiqin.
Fan Changling.
Here.
You and Li Beiqi
joined our Services in the same year
and have been partners.
[Wang Zhaoyang, Interior Guard]
Yes.
But off work,
we are not close.
Do you know Li Beiqi's whereabouts or not?
Madam Wu,
I've never colluded with Li Beiqi.
Why are you interrogating me like I'm a criminal?
Just answer the question truthfully.
I'll have my own judgment.
I really don't know where he is.
Three days before Li Beiqi went missing,
you drank with him in Shang Lin Fang.
What do you mean, madam?
Li Beiqi is not only my comrade
but also my superior.
It was not proper for me
to refuse his invitation for a drink.
Bingzhu,
we have been walking
around the roses of Sharon.
Why don't we go through the forest?
Have you ever heard
any sound made by birds or insects?
Oh, right.
Why is such a big forest so quiet?
There is no living thing in this forest
because it's full of miasma.
It's because the roses of Sharon absorbed miasma
that we don't smell anything.
If we weren't going around them,
we would've died from toxins.
Thank you, rose of Sharon.
So we...
Stop!
Stop there!
You said there's no living thing here.
Here! Right ahead!
Stop!
Stop there!
Catch her!
-Hurry up!
Stop!
Stop running! Catch her!
Stop there! Stop!
Stop!
Stop running!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Stop there!
Stop running!
I...
I really didn't know anything.
I got in by accident.
You wanted to run, huh?
Did you?
I really know nothing!
Why...
Why did they run away?
Whoever has had relations with Li Beiqi
will be interrogated.
That's tricky.
Whoever offended him
can get into trouble.
Li Beiqi is missing
and he's suspected
to have colluded with Four Season Clan.
The Ceremony of Light is approaching.
Perhaps
Madam Wu has her reasons.
It makes no sense.
We have to bring it up to Sir Wu.
Sir Wu is probably the one
who feels the worst because of Li Beiqi.
I'm worried this can affect his health.
Let's not bother him with this.
But Li Beiqi
has nothing to do with us.
The one who trusted him the most
is Madam Wu herself.
But now she interrogates us as if we're criminals.
That will only disappoint us!
True.
Madam Wu.
This is what you just said.
I checked your schedules.
It seems that
someone wasn't telling the truth.
I do believe
you didn't mean to deceive me.
Madam Wu,
this is Sir Wu's order.
When you finish,
ask them to go to the Baili Mansion.
Okay. You can go now.
Yes, Madam.
Sui Xin,
stay here.
Here.
Slow down.
Are you okay?
Don't touch me.
We saved you.
You didn't even thank us.
Who knows if you're on their side?
Would we save you if that's the case?
Take a look.
Do you want to add anything?
Madam Wu,
I have answered all your questions.
If you don't trust me,
you can simply arrest me.
Three days ago,
it was your time off.
Yes.
That night, the Grand Court
sent someone to do a handover.
It should've been Li Beiqi who handled it,
but your stamp
was on the handover register.
The same night,
Li Beiqi let a group of refugees
get into Luoyang.
His stamp
was on the license.
What happened?
I did cover his shift for once,
but
when he asked me
to cover his shift,
he said Sir Wu asked him
to go out of the city for work.
Sir Wu.
She looks suspicious.
Don't touch me!
It should be fine now.
Who were those two guys?
Why were they after you?
I don't know.
Probably they're from the academy.
The academy?
I was picking herbs
and got into an academy by accident.
I looked around
and found nothing special,
but after I got out, they tried to kill me.
Where is the academy?
That way.
Walk around for a while,
turn right, and you'll see a cliff.
Then go down.
It's far away, anyway.
Could you take us there?
I don't want to get myself killed.
The two assassins
must be waiting for you somewhere.
I don't think you should walk around.
Sui Xin mentioned me.
You must have a lot of questions for me.
Go ahead.
Don't think of me as Sir Wu
or even your brother.
Just see me as a stranger.
Do it the way you normally do.
Sir Wu,
Sui Xin said
it was you who sent Li Beiqi
outside the city for work.
Is that true?
No.
But this doesn't make for proof.
I'm only a witness.
Besides, every interior guard knows
Li Beiqi is close to me.
No one can order him
other than me.
Do you believe me?
Let's say Li Beiqi lied.
He used you as an excuse
and let a group of refugees enter Luoyang
before he went missing.
Then we found a name list
in his room.
All the names
are targets of Four Season Clan.
All of this suggests that Li Beiqi
has something to do with the Clan.
The next one who will die...
[Kang Zhanbi, Kang Jin, Li Ji, Dai Zhou]
Dai Zhou.
Dai Zhou is alive!
We can interrogate Dai Zhou!
Perhaps he can prove Li Beiqi is not involved!
That is what I came for.
I received news from the Eastern Palace.
Dai Zhou died in a well
the next day after he was sent back to the Palace.
If Dai Zhou's death
was related to Li Beiqi,
he must have had something
to do with Four Season Clan.
No way.
The Li Beiqi I know
is not like that.
Impossible.
I must have missed some clues.
Li Beiqi and I
grew up together.
-He is not like that.
-Siyue...
Siyue!
I must have neglected some clues.
Siyue, stop it.
He won't betray us!
Even if he did,
I will arrest him by myself.
Wu Siyue.
Wu Siyue!
Brother.
Where do you want to look for him now?
What matters now is not Li Beiqi,
but the Ceremony of Light.