=City of Streamer=
=Episode 24=
I want to talk to you.
Wait a minute.
Let go.
How are things going?
Rong Jiashang appeased
the residents of Wenchunli with money.
That's settled down for now.
But the weird thing is
who leaked the news to the press.
I can't find a clue about it.
What about Rong Dingkun?
Rong Dingkun
is shrewd and suspicious.
He must know
that I'm not that stupid
to go against him in such a way.
My aunt told me
that she needs to plan your wedding
with Jiashang as soon as possible.
I guess so.
Rong Dingkun
has been close with my father recently.
What about Rong Jiashang?
He doesn't have any response?
His relationship is a mess.
How would he have time to care about me?
What about you?
Do you still want to marry him?
Otherwise?
It's a deal.
It's not like I can break it as I want.
The thought of
the fact that you're going to marry him
and bear children for him
makes me feel...
Your brother
doesn't talk much
and barely comes back these days.
He always said he was on duty.
I'm afraid he is mad at us.
Mother.
Don't think too much about it.
Probably he's too busy.
No matter how busy he is,
he still should go home.
In fact,
I know that your brother
has been stubborn since he was a kid.
He is a man of principle.
He just wants
the Rong family to apologize.
But you
signed a deal with them
and took the gold bars.
Did that
hurt his feelings?
Mother.
Think about this,
since Shixun bought the tickets
and agreed to accompany me
to visit the grave,
it means he still cares about me.
When I get to Bailiu Town,
I'll explain it to him.
This weekend is the anniversary
of your birth mother's death.
Have you got
everything ready?
It's the 20th anniversary of her death.
I want to do a ritual for her.
She gave me my life,
but I can't even remember her face.
I'm an unfilial child.
Have you remembered
anything over these years?
I dreamed about it sometimes,
but it was about the same pieces
over and over again.
I only remember
that my little brother was crying,
and my mother shouted to me
and asked me to run.
It was more than 20 years ago.
I don't know
if my little brother's still alive.
I hope
there was a nice family
that took him in.
Mr. Jiashang.
Mrs. Feng took the gold bars.
She exchanged the gold bars
for money on the same day
and put the money in the bank.
I think Miss Feng and her brother
won't cause any more trouble.
Did Miss Feng say anything
when you sent them the gold bars?
Miss Feng hadn't come back
when I arrived.
I stayed near the gate as you ordered.
About two hours later,
Miss Feng came back.
But she hasn't been out
since she came back.
It's Mrs. Feng who has been
doing the grocery shopping these days.
Okay, I see.
You can leave.
Yes.
Hello?
Mr. Rong.
This is
Wang Chunhua from Red House Hospital.
Nurse Wang.
How is it going
with what I asked you to do?
Dr. Feng bought two tickets
for three days from now
to visit a grave with his younger sister
in the countryside.
It's a place called Bailiu Town.
But Dr. Feng didn't say
whose grave it is.
It's inconvenient for me to ask.
Okay, I see.
I'll contact you later.
Okay.
Hello.
Is this Red House Hospital?
Put me through to Director Joseph.
Shixun.
You just finished the night shift.
Are you not going back to get some rest?
I'll go to the countryside
with my sister this afternoon.
I'm going to be late. I'll go straight
to the train station.
Dr. Feng!
Thank God you haven't left.
There is a major surgery
and you're needed as an assistant.
Hurry up and get ready.
- So sudden?
- Ah.
Can't Wenpei do it?
I applied for switching my shift.
He has a plan.
I can do it.
You can't.
Director Joseph ordered it himself.
He designated you.
Moreover,
Liu Yingchun
will perform the operation in person.
There are a lot of people
fighting to be his assistant.
Dr. Feng.
You mustn't miss such an opportunity.
Well, you better get going.
- Nurse Wang.
- Mm.
Please go to the train station later
and make sure
to give this to my sister.
Okay.
Rest assured, Dr. Feng.
Thank you.
(Waiting Room)
(Shanghai Red House Hospital)
Mr. Rong.
Mm.
(Shizhen, something came up.
I can't go with you. Shixun.)
You've gone through a lot
for your sweetheart.
Ever since it happened,
she hasn't been out for days.
My men can't find anything about her.
I have to start with her brother.
What will you do when you find her?
What if she still blames you?
Let's play it by ear.
Keep your stuff well.
Be careful on the road.
Write to me.
(TELEPHONE)
Do you want me to buy some for you?
Boss.
I was about to send people
to look for you,
and then you called me.
I heard
that the affected households
in Wenchunli
all signed the contracts
and took the gold bars
from the Rong family.
Did you also sign it?
Yes.
I didn't expect
that Rong Jiashang would break in
with gold bars during the negotiation.
The neighbors in Wenchunli
suffered heavy losses from the fire.
It was hard not to be tempted
in the face of such a huge compensation.
If I didn't go along with them
and sign the contract,
Rong Dingkun would suspect me
with his nature.
Please show your ticket.
The railway station?
Are you going somewhere far away?
Yes.
I'm going to Bailiu Town
with my older brother
to commemorate my birth mother.
Okay.
Have a safe trip.
Goodbye.
Get on board!
Hurry! Get on board!
The train to Nanjing!
The train to Nanjing will leave soon!
Go back, go back.
The train will leave soon!
Go back, go back!
Get on board! Get on board!
The passengers to Nanjing, hurry!
The train will leave soon!
This is your compartment, Miss.
Thank you.
Little sister, you're traveling alone.
Doesn't your family worry about you?
My older brother will be here soon.
(Shanghai Railway Station)
Little sister.
I think your older brother
won't come.
That's the way men are.
They can be really sweet
when they make a promise.
But by the time...
Sorry, I'm late.
Excuse me.
Dr. Feng asked me to give this to you.
(Shizhen, something came up at
the hospital. I can't go with you.)
(Be careful on the road, Shixun.)
Little sister.
I haven't met anyone
who is as good-looking
as this gentleman.
Dear, look at his manner,
and the quality of his suit.
Your watch is beautiful indeed.
Are these diamonds on it?
One diamond would cost
hundreds of silver dollars.
May I ask where you are working at?
Pardon me, you must be a young master.
Oh, right.
I booked a spare room next door.
Sir.
Why don't you take your wife there
and have some quiet time?
Okay.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Sorry.
You've lost weight.
Haven't you rested well lately?
I don't mean anything else.
I just want to spend more time with you.
You don't want to see me,
so I come to see you.
Miss Feng.
Just think of me as a friend.
I'll try to like you
a little less every day.
Maybe I won't bother you
after a while.
Miss Feng.
Be patient with me like you were
when you tamed me before.
Bear with me for a while.
I will abide by the rules of etiquette
and never do anything you don't like.
Miss Feng.
This is the Brazilian coffee
from an import and export company.
Have a try.
And this.
I had someone find a French chef
to make the dessert.
I was thinking that you got up early
to catch the train
and you must have eaten nothing.
Have some.
Miss Feng.
I just want to create
some good memories that belong to us.
I don't want it to only be hatred
when you remember me.
I don't hate you.
Really?
It was all my fault.
Can we just put it aside for a second?
Just think of me as a student, a friend,
or an errand boy for a few days.
As long as you let me stay by your side,
I'll be good and listen to you.
Okay?
I'll take your silence
as a yes.
Try some.
(Bailiu Town Exit)
Hold the umbrella.
Rickshaw! Rickshaw!
- Rickshaw!
Get in the rickshaw!
Be careful.
- Rickshaw!
- Need a ride?
Rickshaw!
My car is over there.
Let me give you a ride.
Need a ride, sir?
No need.
- Rickshaw!
(Bailiu Town Exit)
Rickshaw!
- Need a ride?
Let's go.
Where do you want to go, Miss?
Let me take it.
Come on.
Be careful.
Rickshaw!
Need a ride, sir?
To Dongfenglai Inn.
Okay.
Sit well!
Miss Feng.
Let me take it for you.
Sir.
Are you hungry?
I'll treat you to a meal.
Mm.
(Mrs. Wang's Beef Noodles)
Ma'am.
Yes.
Two bowls of beef noodles, please.
One large bowl and one small bowl.
More chilies
for the large bowl.
No problem.
Did you come here a lot before?
No.
Only once a year
on the death anniversary.
Bailiu Town is crappy and small.
I'm just afraid
that you're not used to this.
I'm not that squeamish.
When I was in military school,
I had field survival training
for a month every semester.
I needed to live in the wilderness,
and make fire and cook on my own.
Oh, right.
I remember going hunting
in the wild at that time.
I gutted the wild rabbit,
rubbed it with salt,
put honey on it,
and roasted it over a fire.
When it was done,
I just took a bite.
It was really delicious.
Oh, right.
I'll take you to the Cao River
to shoot ducks.
The wild ducks there are fat and stupid.
A young lady like you
who has never used a gun
can still shoot one or two.
Only if we can meet again
in the spring...
Thank you.
I remember
the noodles you made for me earlier.
I've never had
such delicious noodles again.
I'm glad you still remember my taste.
Miss Feng.
Thank you.
For what?
Anyway, thank you.
It feels
nice.
Hurry up and eat.
Mm.
Are you all right, Miss Feng?
Sit well.
Sorry.
The road is bumpy.
Miss Feng, you should sit still.
Are you all right?
Hey.
Drive slowly.
I'm sorry, Mr. Jiashang.
Don't you know that
this would help you sit securely?
Didn't you study physics before?
If you want to be secure,
why don't you get off and walk?
Hands off.
Look.
It's not that I don't want
to put my hands off you.
(Lanruo Monastery)
Benefactor, benefactress.
(The Spirit Tablet of Mother Bai)
Mom!
(Lanruo Monastery)
The meal is not ready yet.
Let's take a walk.
Okay.
Who is that Bai person to you?
She was my birth mother.
Your birth mother?
Well,
what about Mrs. Feng...?
I thought Yang Xiucheng
did a thorough
background check on me.
It turns out you didn't know
I'm an orphan
adopted by the Feng family.
I didn't know it.
I thought you were born
in the Feng family.
When I was a child,
my mother took my little brother
and me to visit relatives.
We met bandits on our way.
My mother was killed
and my little brother was lost.
The Feng family saved me
and raised me.
They treat me like their own.
In my heart,
Mr. Feng and Mrs. Feng
are my real parents,
and Shixun is my real big brother.
Do you have any other
family members at home?
What was your original last name?
I don't remember.
I was two or three years old.
I only remember
that my name was Zhenzhen.
My mother's last name was Bai.
And the daughter
in the Feng family
who died young was also named Zhenzhen.
I'm surprised that the Feng family
didn't lie about who you are.
When they saved me,
I was almost three years old.
I can vaguely remember something.
Over these years,
I still dream about that day
all the time.
My mother used her body
to block the blade
so I could get away.
She died miserably.
I come here every year
to commemorate her.
Have you ever looked for
other family members?
Look for them?
How?
We're not locals.
My mother died
in the middle of our trip.
I don't know anyone.
I'm actually very lucky.
The Feng family treats me
like one of their own
and they sent me to college.
But my little brother
was only a few months old.
I don't know if he is alive or dead.
I'm sure he's still alive.
I'm sure he found a nice family
and grew up safely.
When the time comes,
he will come to see you.
Don't move.
I just want to hug you.
Let's go.
The meal is almost ready.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I guess I have to do this.
Come on.
I'm okay.
Hurry up.
Hold me tight.
When I was in college,
I read a geology book.
It said that where we're standing
right now
was a vast expanse of water
billions of years ago.
I don't know if it will
turn into the sea again
billions of years later.
Perhaps it will turn into the sea again.
Everything in the world
has a reincarnation.
When the water comes,
there will be nothing left.
If Shanghai is flooded,
I'll row a boat and escape with you.
I just don't know
if you will come with me.
If there is nothing left,
where can we escape to?
To the end of the world.
Oh, right,
I should fly a plane to pick you up.
At that time,
we will fly to plateaus with mountains,
getting through the clouds
with the ocean under us.
Just the two of us.
We will fly all the way ahead
to the end of the world.
Fool.
You'll need to take care
of your wife and your children.
I'll need to take care
of my husband, too.
How can I get on your plane?
Yeah.
It's a bummer.
The train will leave at 2:30 PM.
I'm gonna go upstairs and pack.
Okay.
I'll wait for you here.
- Sir.
- Yes.
I want to ask you about something.
Okay.
I heard a mother and two kids
were mugged here.
Bailiu Town is a small place,
but it had been peaceful.
There wasn't even a thief before.
What happened at that time
really freaked out everyone in the town.
Think about it,
the place where it happened
is less than a mile from here.
No one ever saw the bandits?
No.
The bandits killed them all.
That was
a slash on the neck.
They couldn't even scream.
Did no one in this town
see the mother and the children?
(Dongfenglai Inn)
I think they came from the south
and were heading for the northeast.
You can go to the tea house
by the South Bridge
and ask them.
The passersby like
to take a break there and have some tea.
Okay.
Thanks!
Miss Feng!
Why did you ask about that?
Don't you want to find your family?
Maybe your father
is also looking for you.
Looking for me?
It has been 20 years.
If he wants to find me,
he should be here by now
even he crawls here.
It's not 2:00 PM yet.
This is not a big town.
We can make it to the South Bridge.
Why are you so interested in it?
If you like solving crimes,
why don't you work
at the police station?
I'm trying to help you.
I don't want to pry into your privacy.
Miss Feng.
You got separated from your real family.
Maybe they're looking for you, too.
My family is the Feng family.
My parents are kind to me.
They treat me like I was their own.
Well,
the Feng family is on the ropes,
so I should be in a hurry
to find my birth father
and turn to him
if he is rich?
Of course not.
That's not who you are.
I know you're close
with the Feng family.
Even you don't want to see them,
don't you want
to find your little brother?
Don't you want to find the killer?
Since we are here,
let's go.
(I feel grief and joy to meet you again.
The snow stops and the geese fly away.)
How much do you remember
about your childhood?
I was too little.
I have some vague memories.
I remember
that my mother took me
and my little brother
and we were sitting on a cart.
When we met the bandit,
my mother asked me to run.
Did you see the bandit?
Only a shadow.
Sometimes he is a big black dog
in my dream
coming at me and trying to bite me.
Sometimes,
he is a big rock
falling on me
from the sky.
Do you remember
when you were three years old?
I remember playing in the garden
when I was little.
I got stung by a bee
cried in pain.
Later, I asked my nanny
and she said it happened
when I was three years old.
There was another time
when Mrs. Rong
gave birth to Fanglin and Jiaxin.
I went to rock their cradle,
but I rocked it too hard,
and they started to cry.
Mrs. Rong rushed over
and pushed me to the ground.
I was either three
or four years old at that time.
All right.
Now it's my turn to feel sorry for you.
We are both motherless children.
My father only exists in name.
We are in the same boat.
We are not in the same boat.
My parents are good to me.
Yeah.
I'm quite envious of you.
(Tea)
Here, have some tea.
Thanks.
(Tea)
Sir, go on.
I remember
they took a break here
when they passed by.
How could I not remember them?
The three of them were in a donkey cart.
They came from the southwest.
The baby's diaper was wet
and she changed the diaper on my table.
There was also a little girl
about three or four years old.
Look.
How good your little brother is.
He doesn't cry at all.
Sir.
Do you remember anything else?
That little girl you just mentioned
is me.
You are still alive!
What a blessing!
Do you remember
where my mother came from?
They sat here for a while and then left.
Your mother's accent
sounded like she was from Guojia Town.
Are you sure it's Guojia Town?
Well...
What's wrong with Guojia Town?
Nothing.
Go on, please.
I'm not sure if they were
from Guojia Town.
There are Guojia Town,
Futian Village
and Wanjin Village over there.
The accents are similar.
Well, I think
it was all fate.
How is that?
The sun was falling down
when the three of them came here.
My wife advised her
to stay over at the inn
and leave tomorrow.
But
she said someone was waiting ahead.
Then
she left.
If she hadn't left that day,
such a tragedy wouldn't have happened.
Sir.
Do you remember
what that driver looked like?
He was a young man.
He called the woman sister-in-law.
I guess he was her husband's brother.
But...
But what?
But the man had a northern accent
and he was tall.
He was not a local.
Did he die, too?
No.
There was only the woman's body
at the scene.
I talked to the neighbors about it.
How weird
was it?
The man driving the cart
is most suspicious.
Even if he's not the killer,
he should know who your father is.
If we find him,
maybe we can find some clues.
You seemed surprised
when the owner mentioned Guojia Town.
Not surprised.
I just found it coincidental.
My family
also came from Guojia Town.
Really?
Mm.
That is coincidental indeed.
But our relatives there all passed away.
My father left home to work
when he was young.
There was a plague back home
at that time
and our close relatives almost all died.
My father avoided it
because he was out there.
If my mother also came from Guojia Town,
maybe
we are relatives.
Maybe you are my cousin.
Shizhen.
I'll stop right now
if you don't want to look into it.
But if you want to find the murderer
and your little brother,
I'll find out the truth for you.
Shizhen.
Use me.
I can do a lot of things you can't.
I knew.
I knew it long ago.
(Exit)
Shizhen.
Shixun.
Let me take the suitcase.
Okay.
Be careful.
How was it going?
It went well.
Sorry.
Something came up
and I couldn't leave.
I know you are busy.
It's okay.
Just treat me to something delicious.
Okay.
I'll buy you whatever you want.
Let's go to Wangfu Restaurant.
Wangfu Restaurant? Okay.
We can have a late night snack.
But it's a little expensive there.
For my little sister,
nothing is expensive for me.
Well,
Mr. Jiashang, you're back.
Miss Du is here.
She is playing Mahjong
with Master and madams.
Okay.
Great.
Thank you, Aunt.
You ate it.
Father.
Mm.
Jiashang.
Lanxin sent over
two cases of fine wine her father
brought back from Europe.
I know you are busy,
but no matter how busy you are,
you should save some time
for your fiancée.
Men should be busy with their careers.
Since Jiashang is back,
I won't play anymore.
Aunt Wang.
Please take it for me.
Yes.
I'll go with you to grab a late snack.
Okay.
Character five.
A complete sequence.
I've been playing Mahjong with them
since this afternoon.
My waist is gonna break
if you don't come back.
Why is Yang Xiucheng here?
He followed your father here.
It has nothing to do with me.
Well,
Young Master Rong,
you can't even stand
his presence anymore?
After all,
the Rong family hurt him first.
I have no problem with him.
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪