=Please Don't Spoil Me=
=Episode 17=
(Lan Xin Palace)
After eating hotpot, let's have
a cup of tea to wash it down.
Your Highness, you're really
enjoying the food!
Oh, it's Eunuch Niu.
Have a seat.
Come and sit.
Your Highness,
although you left
the Cold Palace not long ago,
you're suffering
this bad luck again.
I feel so sad for you,
so, so sad.
Entering the Cold Palace is
a very happy thing for me.
Look how free it is here,
with the wine and meat
you're sending me.
Life is good here!
Your Highness,
I can't speak for others,
but on the aspect of food,
if there's anything you want,
just let me know.
I'll get it for you.
I do in fact have a few special dishes
that I want you to get for me.
Sure!
Come here.
Aortas and tripe.
Tripe?
Aortas?
You know, from the cow's stomach.
Your Highness,
this...
I don't dare to bring
such dirty things to the Palace!
If the nobles find out,
I...
Upon my return to the Cold Palace,
I don't feel so good.
I wanted to write a few poems
with these emotions.
- But unfortunately...
- Your Highness,
I am in charge of the Cold Palace.
It is my duty to
improve the living conditions
in the Cold Palace,
and that includes the diet.
Your Highness,
if there's anything you need,
just let me know.
I'll get it done.
But...
All I ask is that you don't
stop your passion for poetry.
Fu Ling, ready my brush and ink.
Have a look.
A mountain range from the front
looks like peaks from the side.
Its physique changes when
viewed from various angles.
Your Highness, have some tea.
No one can see
the true face of Lu Mountain,
for they are in the mountain themselves.
Your Highness,
this poem seems to be about scenery,
but it actually has a profound meaning.
Your Highness,
you can simply write anything
without hesitation.
You're truly a genius poet!
You flatter me.
Your Highness,
there's something I don't understand.
(Su Shi)
Why do you sign it with "Su Shi"?
The author is Su Shi.
It's natural that I sign it
with "Su Shi".
I remember that you've used "Li Bai",
"Du Fu",
and also "Meng Hao Ran".
Why did you change
the name again this time?
Well, different poems
naturally have different authors.
Oh, you won't understand.
Yes, I don't understand.
Um, Your Highness,
I feel like you're very inspired today.
Can you write a couple more
poems for me?
To be honest,
after reading your poems,
everyone else's are
boring and plain to me.
Sure.
That's great.
Your Majesty.
How is Concubine Rong doing
in the Cold Palace?
Is she feeling restless,
like she's missing someone very much?
No, no, Your Majesty.
Not at all.
Concubine Rong
took out the hotpot
that she asked someone to make,
and is having a good meal.
She's also reciting poetry
with the Cold Palace's
General Officer Niu De Yi.
She looks very happy.
Zhao Xiao Wu!
Stop talking!
She's very happy?
That's not right.
Your Majesty,
Concubine Rong has only been
in the Cold Palace for a day.
It's only normal that
she hasn't started to miss anyone.
Is it normal?
But why do I...
Fine.
I want to see
how long Concubine Rong can last.
Good poem. Good poem!
But, Eunuch,
why is Her Highness's signature
different every time?
Throughout history, literati have always
used pseudonyms when writing poems.
Every name has a different meaning.
A scholar like Her Highness
is not someone that you and I...
She is not someone that
people like you can try to fathom.
Eunuch, you're brilliant.
I wonder,
Her Highness has given me so many poems,
how should I repay her?
♪Listen to the sound of tides♪
♪They are saying I do♪
♪The setting sun is listening
to your whispers♪
♪I have told you too many of my secrets♪
♪I am being too sweet♪
♪The whole galaxy is shining for you♪