....thing like this when i was your age.
Walk a different partn of the property every day.
He said it gave him a feel for
what kind of day it was gonna be.
Was the "first thing" so early back then?
It was even earlier,you little rat.
Remember the song he used to sing me?
Mm.
[Together]
♪ You are my sunshine ♪
♪ My only sunshine ♪
[Hershel]
♪ You make me happy ♪
♪ When skies are gray ♪
"Morning, Barbara"
♪ You'll never know, dear ♪
"Morning, Maggie"
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ Please don't take my sunshine away ♪
♪♪
[Hammer pounding]
[Negan]
Hey, I just wanted to thank you
for getting me the hell out of Dodge.
I mean, uh, you may have noticed
things with Maggie and I
are a little bit tense.
I don't mind being lay-low Negan for a bit,
but, hell, there's only so far
I can go to get out of her way.
♪♪
You know, I was thinking,
maybe, uh...
Maybe you'd put in a word for me?
Smooth things over, at least
kind of get the ball rollin'.
Given our recent history,
uh, I kind of figured
you owe me that much, right?
♪♪
You know this place?
Mm-hmm.
♪♪
[Door opens]
[Door creaks]
[Birds calling]
[Door creaks and closes]
I see you went ahead and moved me in.
Daryl helped. I'm sorry.
The Council's voted to banish you.
What you want just isn't gonna happen.
It's not possible.
I know it's not what I promised,
but given our less-recent history,
it's better than you deserve.
It is what it is, I guess.
And if you don't mind me asking
did the Council really banish me?
Or is this more of a "Carol seizing the reins"
kind of situation?
[Chuckles softly]
This rabbit's for you.
[ Door opens and closes ]
♪♪
Improved By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
[Fire crackling]
♪♪
[Savior Negan]
Little pig, little pig.
[Bat thudding]
Let me in.
♪♪
[Chuckles]
It's all right.
I know you can hear me loud and clear.
I know that nobody likes an "I told you so."
What can I say?
I must be a bit of a masochist,
'cause, uh...
[Laughs]
You know what the sad part is?
The sad part isn't where we ended up here,
'cause, I mean...[Scoffs]
Let's face it.
It could have beenn a hell of a lot worse.
No, see, the sad part is that
you thought for even a second
that those folks would see you for anything
but who you truly are...
♪♪
Which is me.
You're a clown.
A cult of personality with no cult.
You go ahead and you call me
whatever little names
you want to call me,
but you gotta admit...
We got a hell of a lot further
with a kind word and good ol' Lucille here
than we ever got with just a kind word.
It's time to face the facts,
old man.
You are nothin' without her.
[Glass shatters]
♪♪
[Chains creaking]
[Rick]
Carl said it doesn't have to be...
It doesn't have to be a fight anymore.
He was wrong.
[Grunts]
[Gurgling]
[Thud]
[Negan]
Look what you did.
I want to see her.
I need to see her.
No.
Negan
we don't have your bat.
Where is she?
What did you do with her?
She's still out there.
♪♪
[Crow caws]
[Walker snarling]
♪♪
[Panting]
[Snarling continues]
♪♪
[Thudding]
[Scraping]
♪♪
[Panting]
Y-You gotta let me go.
♪♪
My wife... she has cancer.
She needs it.
Gotta keep it safe, okay?
I told you.
I know. No, it...
Shh. You keeping me here...
[Shushing]
I know.It kills me and her.
Please, I told you.
Shh. Hey. I know you did.
I know.
Hey, and I told you...
My heart, it goes out to you.
Can't imagine what you must
be going through right now.
God.
[Scoffs]
Just wondering
if she's ever gonna get her next treatment.
[Chuckles]
We drove out to where you told us
those doctors gave you this stuff,
but, um, they weren't there.
That's not my fault.
I told you. I told you.
They move around.
They were never there.
I mean, that road,
it was so overgrown,
we couldn't even get the pickup down it.
So, now...
I know you can't get this stuff
just anywhere.
It needs to be refrigerated.
Somebody, they took care
of this for a long time,
and if they've got something
as rare as this...
[Chuckles]
They probably got a lot
of other stuff, too.
So, now
you tell me where you got it,
I am going to let you
take this to your wife.
Otherwise, I'm gonna pour it down the toilet
and make you watch.
Hm?
[Groans]
[Spits]
[Panting]
All right.
Just please put that back in the cooler.
I will tell you
whatever you want to know.
Just, please, keep that safe.
[Sighs]
The part about the medical
clinic, that's all true.
And, yeah, you're right...
They have a medical stockpile somewhere.
They keep equipment, drugs.
I don't know where, but that
is where that came from.
I've been tracking 'em for weeks.
I found 'em... I don't know...
Two or three days ago.
♪♪
[Engine rumbling]
[Groans]
Drop your guns! Drop your guns!
I don't want to shoot him,
but I will!
Okay. Take it easy.
[Groans]
[Panting]
No, don't!
[Body thuds]
Shit. You didn't have to do that.
Better safe than sorry.
[Breathing heavily]
♪♪
[Rattling]
Take it easy, Capone.
My name is Negan.
[Microwave beeping]
Negan. All right.
I'm Franklin.
[Microwave humming]
[Jingling]
We gonna have any problems?
No, sir. No problems.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
[Microwave beeps]
Exposure
exhaustion
dehydration.
And I think I can add
malnutrition to the list.
Uh, I gotta wonder,
with a guy like you
the state you're in
trying to rob a bunch of doctors
with an empty gun.
My wife has cancer.
She was in the middle of treatments
when the world went to shit,
and I have just been
trying to keep her going.
So you're a doctor?
I'm a high-school gym teacher.
High school. Mm.
So, what'd you mean by "keep her going"?
The doctors had given us
a calendar of what she needed
and when she needed it,
so all I had to do
was find the drugs and figure
out how to do infusions.
Wait a minute.
So... you taught yourself
how to give someone chemotherapy?
The pumps aren't that complicated.
Unless something goes wrong.
Well, did something go wrong?
Yeah. You could say that.
[Walker snarling]
[Dishes clatter]
[Refrigerator door creaks]
[Sighs]
[Refrigerator door closes]
Trying to figure out what James
Bond movie I want to watch.
Well, baby, I think we're gonna
have to skip the movie just for now.
Generator's making too much noise.
Hey. We're gonna have to kill it.
Why bother, right?
I turn the generator off
for a little bit,
and they lose interest.
They always do.
[Walker snarling]
[Freezer humming]
[Door creaks and closes]
[Walker snarling]
[Generator rumbling]
[Generator slows and stops]
[Walker snarling]
[Fence rattling]
"'I see what you are feeling, '
replied Charlotte.
'You must be surprised,
very much surprised...
So lately as Mr. Collins
was wishing to marry you.
But when you have...'"
[Sighs]
Mama.
Hmm?
This book sucks.
It's killing me.
I-I-I can't... I can't do it.
You're the one that won't
let me watch James Bond.
Read.
[Walker snarling,fence rattling]
You gotta take care of it.
[Walker snarling]
♪♪
Come on. Seriously?
[Gunshot]
[Thud]
[Crows cawing]
♪♪
That was our last bullet.
Hey.
Are you all right? Uh-huh.
Turn the generator back on.
I want to watch a movie.
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
[Spits]
♪♪
How you doing?
I'm good.
I got something for you.
I found someone's stash.
[Chuckles]
Now, it's a little bit dried out,
but this is gonna help with your nausea.
You're having to go further
and further every time.
Well, generator needs gas,
and this place has been picked over.
But the bright side is...
that I reckon
that's exactly what's keeping us safe.
There is nothing here  that anybody wants.
You can't keep it up.
We need to move.
We need other people.
It's just too dangerous out there.
That's my point.
Baby, you have three treatments left.
That's it, okay?
So we are gonna get your strength up,
and then I will put you on my motorcycle
and I will take you
wherever you want to go...
Wherever you can dream up.
I promise.
Okay. Okay.
[Generator thumping]
[Shivering]
♪ You are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
[Chuckles]
♪ Can't you see ♪
♪ You're everything I hope for ♪
♪ You're everything I need ♪
♪ 'Cause you are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
♪♪
♪ To me ♪
[Walker snarling]
Ugh. Damn it.
[Lucille]
It's not like killing a person, babe.
It's not even like killing an animal.
You can't let it keep bothering you.
It doesn't bother me.
I...
I'm just worried that
I'm gonna get used to it.
[Snarling continues]
Okay.
Go turn the generator off.
How, um...
How's your dinner?
It was really good.
If I had known
that dog food could taste like this...
I would have been eating
that shit all along.
[Both laughing]
Oh, God.
[Laughs]
Hey.
Hmm?
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniver...
Wait. You actually know what day it is?
[Laughs]
No. I just want you to have it. Open it.
[Paper rustling]
[Laughs]
Oh, my God.
Holy... shit!
Where did you get this?
Okay, it was in the crawlspace
this whole time.
'Cause I was mad.
I was so mad that
I couldn't return it,
so I just hid it,
and I told you I returned it.
So, there you go.
You're awesome.
[Both laughing]
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry I made
a big deal out of it.
If I'd known
[Inhales deeply]
like, all this was gonna happen,
I wouldn't have cared about
a stupid credit-card bill.
[Laughs]
No. No, no, no, no.
See, I, um...
I don't deserve anything from you.
And you shouldn't be apologizing to me.
Uh, it should be me apologizing to you.
The man that I was
the pain that I put you through...
♪♪
You know, uh... You know,
I lie awake at night
just wondering how I got so lucky
that you have stuck with me.
[Laughs]
Come here.
♪♪
Listen to me.
I stuck with you 'cause
I could always see
the man you are right now.
Even when you weren't.
♪♪
And that asshole really had it comin'.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's smoke the pot. No way.
Yeah. I got that for you. No.
What, we gotta go to work tomorrow?
Let's pretend it's, like, Saturday.
[Laughs]
Oh. Hmm?
Are you sure?
You feel okay?
I feel good enough.
Can I wear my jacket?
You better.
[Laughs]
♪♪
[Water dripping]
[Birds chirping]
No. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
♪♪
Remember that guy and his family
came through here a while back?
The kid had leukemia, uh,
and they were looking
for this group of doctors that
traveled around in a mobile clinic?
Well, I remember. I sat down
with him. He showed me his map.
These doctors, they take
the same route every time,
and they make the same stops.
I think that I know
where they are,
and if I leave right now, I can
catch them before they move on.
They could be dead by now if
they even existed to begin with.
And then what do you do
when you find them?
You have nothing to
barter with, so just stop.
I will figure it out.
Stop... Negan! I said stop!
I have something to tell you.
[AC/DC's "Back in Black" plays]
[Children chattering]
[Laughter]
[Dog barks]
[Negan]
Well, I hope you got your shittin' pants on, boy,
'cause you are about to shit your pants!
[Teenager]
Come on, dude.Stop being a D-bag and let me play.
Don't be such a pussy! This is
how you get better! You gotta take it!
Are you playing with children?
Uh, teenagers. I think. Mostly.
[Teenager #2]
Yeah, you were pretty harsh, dude.
All right, yeah. Chu... Chumpo,
this is how you get better.
Please tell me that you did not spend $600
on this "Happy Days" bullshit.
Calm down. Don't worry.
I got two leads.
One's a lock, but the other one pays better,
and I am just celebrating
a little early, is all.
Really?
Yeah.
Tell me about these two leads.
'Cause you can't be
a gym teacher anymore.
You have a misdemeanor
assault on your record,
and you refuse to go back to school.
So, please, oh, I would love it
if you would tell me
all about this job that you got
that's gonna pay for this.
Right.
I'm returning it.
I threw the receipt away!
Ugh!
[Door slams]
[Janine]
Well, I'd like to tell you he's not the dude
you married anymore,
but he was always like this.
It was cute when we were younger,
but it's gotten old and out of control.
I know. I know, Janine.I just...
[Sighs]
It just feels unfair
to give up on him, you know?
He really was in such a good
space, and he loved that job.
He loved working with those kids.
Yeah, and then he beat a guy
up and he put him in the hospital.
Janine, I told you...
That asshole had it comin'.
How's the food?
It's good.
Did you do somethin' different?
Yeah, I, uh...
I tried a little rosemary instead of oregano,
and there's a little white-wine reduction
in with the chicken stock.
My appointment's tomorrow at 2:15.
What appointment?
I'm getting an MRI.
I need you to drive me home.
Uh, I can't. Tomorrow at 2:15?
I-I have a meeting
with the probation officer.
Besides, you know how the doctors can be.
They have you sit around
for three hours with your ass
hanging out, and then they
tell you everything's fine.
[Doctor] [Echoing]
The good news is that we caught it early on.
A lot of times,with this one, we don't.
In your case...
[Voice fades]
[Fluorescent lights humming]
Do you have someone to drive you home?
[Sighs]
[Phone line ringing]
[Voicemail beeps]
[Negan]
Hey. It's me, Negan.I'm Probably out riding the bike.
So leave a message.
Shit.
[Phone line ringing][Cries softly]
[Voicemail beeps] [Janine]
Hi. You've got Janine.
If I don't pick up...
Uh, he should be there.
He said he was going...
Um, he was gonna see you at 3:00,
so he should have been there 20 minutes ago.
[Probation officer]
I'm sorry.I don't know what to tell you.
I don't have him in my calendar
for another two weeks.
♪♪
Sh...
[Keys jingling]
[Engine starts]
[Man on radio]
Cumberland have concluded that in all cases,
the killers are eating the
flesh of the people they kill.
Shut up and play some goddamn music!
♪ I like to do it ♪
[Tires squealing]
[Muffled rock music continues]
[Engine revs]
[Motorcycle engine approaches]
[Engine shuts off]
[Footsteps approach]
[Door opens]
What's going on?
What is it?
♪♪
I've got cancer.
[Negan]
You knew.
You...
You knew about Janine.
Uh, about me and her?
You knew this whole time?
Mm-hmm.
It's just, you know, I... I...
I broke it up with her as soon
as we got your diagnosis.
Uh, I never saw her or
even talked to her again.
I know that, too. I know.
Jesus, Lucille.
I don't understand.
Why are you telling me this now?
'Cause...
I want you to know that you made up for it,
and you can stop.
And if you really want to help me
then just stay.
Stay.
Baby, we... we were so close.
You know?
This...This... This can work.
The doctors said that this could work.
No, they didn't.
We went down swingin'.
Now it's time for you
to go on without me.
I need you to do my fightingfor me, okay?
Stay.
No.
No. We are not giving up.
[Sighs]
You know,we have made it this far,
so we are gonna see this through.
I'm gonna find these doctors,
and I am gonna bring you back
the drugs that you need,
and we are gonna kick
this cancer out of you.
[Inhales shakily]
We are not giving up.
Do you hear me?
We are not giving up. Not ever.
♪♪
That was about six weeks ago.
You know, I figured I would...
I would scavenge along the way,
but it was worse out there
than I thought.
And then I ran into some
problems with the dead, and...
[Sighs]
Here I am.
[Franklin]
I found that note you wrote.
My daughter went out
to the warehouse to see
if we have what you need.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
We had it all.
Everything on your list.
I don't know what to say here. Um...
We have a lot.
We just want to help.
You know, I came here threatening your life,
and you've patched me up and
gave me the first decent meal
I've had in weeks.
You gave me everything that I asked for,
and you haven't asked
for anything in return.
Well, we're good.
What goes around comes around.
There's a gang that owns the roads at night.
Is that empty gun your only weapon?
Yeah, I broke my hammer on the way here.
Here. Take this.
This the bat you hit me with?
Damn, girl. You pack a wallop.
[Craven]
Enough.
Enough! Enough! Enough!
I ask you where you got the drugs,
and all you've done is tell me
one stupid, pointless story
after another.
First, you wouldn't talk. Now...
I'm begging you to shut up.
[Gun clicks]
Well, story time is over, bitch.
Now... either you tell me
where you got 'em,
or I pull this trigger
and your wife dies
thinking you ran out on her.
I'm not even gonna count.
If you don't start talking
by the time I stop,
I swear to God...
Wait, wait, wait.
Just bring me my map.
[Sighs]
Bring me my map.
[Paper rustling] Okay.
♪♪
What about security?
Security is light.
It is a guy and his daughter.
[Sighs]
There are guards on top
of the RVs. They're decoys.
There could be a couple of
others, and they have no guns.
♪♪
And if they're not there
for literally any reason,
I'm gonna come back here and kill you.
All right?
No questions asked.
Lock him in the storage room.
♪♪
[Chuckles]
Good to go, my man.
♪♪
[Banging]
[Woman screaming]
Hey! Get away from that!
[Man]   Shut up!
[Woman] No!
[Objects clattering and slamming]
[Man]   Hey!
[Woman] Stop!
No!
[Engine starts]
♪♪
[Woman screams]
[Click]
[Creaking]
Lucille?
[Sighs]
[Walker snarling]
[Plastic rustling]
[Snarling]
[Sobs]
[Snarling continues]
[Snarling]
[Joe Cocker's"You Are So Beautiful" plays]
♪♪
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
[Snarling]
♪♪
♪ To me ♪
[Snarling]
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ Can't you see ♪
[Snarling continues]
♪ You're everything I hoped for ♪
♪♪
♪ You're everything I need ♪
[Insects chirping]
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪♪
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪♪
[Snarling continues]
♪ To me ♪
♪ Can't you see? ♪
♪ Ohhh ♪
♪ You're everything I hoped for ♪
♪♪
♪ Everything I need ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ So beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
[Fire crackling]
[Motorcycle departs]
[Thud]
[Grunts]
[Craven]
All right.Okay. That's enough.
[Chuckles]
You know, it's been a long day.
I... I did not get much sleep last night,
so this is gonna be the last time I ask.
Tell me where you keep the good stuff,
or I'm gonna bring out the girl.
Hmm?
[Chuckles]
She's a little young for you,
don't you think?
[Generator rumbling]
[Blow lands]
[Man grunts]
♪♪
[ Footsteps approach ]
[Gunshot]
What the hell's going on out there?
[Man on radio]
Stay there.We're checking it out.
Eh. Go take a look.
[Man] Over here!
He's over here!
[Gunfire]
[Glass shatters]
[Wood snaps]
Can one of you idiots
tell me what the hell
is going on out there?!
[Gunfire, man screams]
[Man]
I'm dropping my gun!
Please!
[Gunshot, man grunts,body thuds]
♪♪
[Footsteps approach slowly]
[Rhythmic knocking on door]
♪♪
[Glass shatters]
[Gunshots]
♪♪
[Groaning]
[Gun cocks]
♪♪
[Groans]
Are there any more of them?
I think I got all of 'em.
[Groaning]
You take this.
You go find your daughter,
make sure she's okay.
[Craven groaning]
Okay.
♪♪
[Craven groans]
[Sighs]
Well. Look at us.
Here we are again.
You know, last time we did this,
you said that I talk too much.
Bad news is, I got some stuff
to get off my chest this time, as well.
[Groans]
But, see, this time...
This time, you'd best hope
I never stop talking
because when I do...
When I do, something very
terrible is gonna happen to you.
You know I never killed a man
before tonight?
It's the truth. Came close once.
See, there was this... this bar
my wife and I used to go to.
It was our favorite bar.
It was our favorite bar 'cause
it had our favorite jukebox.
Favorite jukebox because, well,
it had our favorite song.
"You Are So Beautiful"
by the one and only Joe Cocker.
Probably the greatest
love ballad ever written.
I'm sure you agree.
But, see, there was
there was this guy.
This guy, he had, uh...
He had one of those voices you can't unhear.
Yeah, it was like, um,
my brain had been hijacked,
and I can't...
I can't think anymore.
Anyway, he is talking and laughing
while the song is playing,
being completely obnoxious.
So my beautiful wife, Lucille,
she gets up,goes over to where he is,
and politely asks him
if he could keep it down
so she could hear her song.
Well, let's just say he chose poorly.
So now I gotta get up.
And I go over, and I tell him
that he owes me 50 cents
so I can play the song again
and he can shut the hell up
and my wife can enjoy her song.
♪♪
Now, here's the important part,
and I really want you
to pay attention to this.
You know when people get
so angry they say they see red?
That shit is actually true.
When this asshole comes at me,
all I see is red.
It's like I am looking
at the world through blood.
So I wail on him.
I wail on this son of a bitch
until he's not moving.
And then I reach down,
I grab his wallet,
and I take out one dollar,
and I play her song again.
Twice.
Turns out that this prick
has kids that go to the school
that I teach gym at.
Needless to say, the school was
unthrilled.
I get fired. This guy sues me.
I don't have a job,so now my wife
has to pay his medical bills.
So, t-the point of this is,
there were consequences to me seeing red.
Seeing red was a bad thing then.
I was a bad man... then.
But, see, now,nobody's suing anybody.
Nobody's gettin' fired.
Hell, nobody's keeping score.
Now when I see red,
it's just a question of what I am capable of.
And, well, man,I hate to break it to ya.
See, I am startin' to think
that I am capable of damn near anything.
♪♪
So this
this is for not killing me.
[Blow lands, Craven grunts]
[Walker snarling]
♪♪
I am sorry that I left you.
I was a coward.
I couldn't face the pain
of losing you, so I ran away.
And then I made myself not feel anything
because I didn't want to feel the shame.
The problem is that
shame is the one thing that I still feel.
♪♪
Uh, I'm sorry that you went out like that.
I should have been there.
I am sorry that I named a stupid
baseball bat after you.
♪♪
I am sorry for all the pain
that I put you through.
♪♪
I hope that you found someone in the afterlife
and you are screwing your brains out.
Well
not really, but
fair is fair.
♪♪
I miss you.
I love the shit out of you.
♪♪
And I am gonna do your fighting for you.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[Leaves rustling]
♪♪
Where's the A-Team off to?
Looking for food in an Army base Daryl found.
We find anything,I'll bring some by your cabin.
Nah, that won't be necessary.
In fact, that whole situation
isn't gonna work out.
I came by here hoping that maybe
you could requisition a cart for me.
I can bring back my stuff.
Yeah, I'll ask Gabriel to approve that.
♪♪
If you stay here,she will kill you.
I just didn't want your death
on my conscience, and
now it's not.
Fair enough.
♪♪