Previously on
"The Walking Dead."
We found one
of their masks today.
- They're on alert. Someone found a skin.
- A skin?
AARON: So, at least one of 'em
has been on our side of border.
- Are they back?
- We do not need to start a panic.
[EXPLOSION IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
If we get caught on their side
of the border,
that's it, that's war.
Why are we still respecting
borders,
when Alpha
isn't even here?
♪♪
[CAR HORN BLARING]
[HISSING]
[BLARING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[BLARING STOPS]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Open.
♪♪
- [GROWLS]
- No!
[GRUNTS] Aah!
[WHIMPERS, CRIES]
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[CRIES]
Aah!
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[GROWLS]
[ALL GROWLING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Mama!
♪♪
Hurry, Mama!
[POUNDING ON DOOR,
GROWLING CONTINUES]
Mama!
Mama, hurry!
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [VOICE BREAKING] I'm so sorry, Mama.
- [COUGHING]
You almost got us killed
again.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mama, there's a man.
♪♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
It is time that
the pack returns.
There is more gathering
to be done,
Guardians to be found.
We are far from the enemy.
Their fear will subside.
They will fear us
no matter where we are.
They fill fear us
because of what we did.
Do you doubt me?
Our mission?
Never.
Take the sisters
when you depart.
They have a real gift,
a scent for the dead.
♪♪
We don't mean harm.
[BANGING ON DOOR,
GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
Can you talk?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
- [METAL CLANGS]
- [GASPS]
Mama, I don't like this.
Please...
Go on and try to kill us.
But know two things...
One, I do not die easily,
and, two, you must also
kill my daughter
because I will not leave
this Earth without her.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
One night.
Thank you.
Do not leave this hallway.
Do you think
I could wash up?
- Sorry, Mama, but the smell...
- Is there water?
[BANGING, GROWLING CONTINUES]
Is he a monster?
[WHISPERING]
We're all monsters now.
♪♪
BETA: Be on alert.
Buildings could be full.
MALE WHISPERER #1:
Gather all of them?
Every last one
we can find.
[GROWLING]
Split up.
We track better apart.
Did you hear me?
[ALL GROWLING]
♪♪
He's watching you.
FRANCES: The sun feels...
different today.
[CHUCKLES]
Can you feel that,
sister?
Like it's burning
right into our skin.
Stop it.
Your head's in the clouds again.
He'll see that you're not
committed to the cause...
to her.
♪♪
Don't say that.
I should've left you behind
when I had the chance.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
I hear them.
Over there.
♪♪
- [GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
- [WHIMPERS]
Shh.
[HUMMING]
- [HUMMING STOPS]
- Were you singing?
Wouldn't call it that.
Don't do it again.
[PILL BOTTLE RATTLES]
You have a name?
The dead
don't have names.
And we shouldn't,
either.
Without names or a past,
those of us strong enough
to still be alive out here
can know each other
on a primal level.
[GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
They fear nothing.
They want only to feed.
They are free.
How'd you end up
in here?
Got into a tussle
with the dead,
ran me out of my camp
a few months ago.
Is that why
you wear that?
LYDIA: Mama, come back!
[SNIFFS]
I like it...
...the sound
of the dead.
It's the only song
I never want to end.
♪♪
[ALL GROWLING]
[GATE RATTLES]
[GROWLS]
♪♪
[GATE RATTLING]
[GATE WHIRRING]
[GATE THUDS]
[ALL GROWLING]
♪♪
Sister, focus.
[BABY CRYING]
♪♪
[SOBBING]
What is wrong with you?
♪♪
You will pay.
[CRYING] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel...
he's better there.
I love him, and he's gone.
[CRYING]
♪♪
He's with them
in a better place!
ALPHA: Stop!
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
[CRYING]
[SOBBING]
♪♪
BETA:
She is an uncommitted now.
Her actions threatened
the entire pack.
Leaving her child
broke her.
You will never understand how
it feels to abandon your child.
You still think
of Lydia.
She was dead to me
long before I ended her.
Bring her to me
in the deeper place.
I'll be waiting.
[SCOFFS]
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
You're gonna sleep
in here.
I'll be right outside.
It'll be quiet.
Why are there big pillows
all over the walls?
So the people put in here
wouldn't hurt themselves.
[ZIPPER UNZIPS]
People like that man
out there?
These walls could never control
someone like that.
You like him?
Uh-huh.
I don't want it.
You've never slept
without her...
I don't want it.
I'm not a baby anymore.
I don't want
that stupid bunny.
to be scared.
I want to be more like you,
Mama.
♪♪
[GASPS]
I've waited so long
to hear that.
[CHUCKLES]
And I hope
that you will...
because if you can't,
I'll have no choice
but to leave you behind.
Please, Mama,
don't ever leave me.
I promise I'll do better
out there. I will.
You'll see.
♪♪
I love you, Mama.
Stop calling me that.
♪♪
[SHUDDERS]
[CRYING]
♪♪
Alpha, I'm sorry.
Please.
I won't talk about him
again.
Please.
Remove your mask.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
Kneel.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
[CRIES]
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[CRYING]
Shh.
♪♪
Thank you.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
♪♪
Alpha showed you
her grace?
I'll never stray again,
sister.
We keep thinking about
that place, too.
It looked so safe.
There was livestock.
We can all go back.
We can get...
♪♪
Why?
Do not question me.
But if she strays again, I will
skin her alive for all to see.
She unsettles the pack.
Then we keep a close eye, make sure her
moment of weakness doesn't infect the others.
The others have already spoken
of the enemy, the life they saw.
It is not a life.
It is a fantasy.
And the pack
must learn that again.
They must see it
up close.
- They will.
- When?
Soon.
♪♪
Are you content?
I have seen you wander away
from the camp alone at night.
♪♪
I am right here...
as I've always been.
[HUMMING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[HUMS]
[GROWLS]
[BODY THUDS]
[GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
[ALL GROWLING]
[KNIFE CLATTERS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[BODY THUDS]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
I like killing
with you.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[SNIFFS]
Oh, you're different.
People who knew me
before all this
would probably say
the same thing.
Never trusted
those people, anyway.
I don't hardly
trust anyone.
Neither do I.
[GRUNTS]
[BONES CRACKING]
Well done, Big Man.
- "Big Man"?
- Okay.
"Mr. B."
I thought
we didn't have names.
It's not a name.
It's a letter.
So, if I'm "B,"
what does that make you?
"A."
[SNIFFS]
[SLOSHING]
So, you can move with them
when you're covered?
It's not just about
moving with them.
You got to become them,
feel what they feel.
And what do they feel?
Nothing.
There are only two kinds
of people left in this world...
the ones brave enough
to walk with the dead
and everybody else.
So, tell me, B,
which one are you?
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SHAKILY] Leave.
At sunrise.
Don't come back.
[BUCKET SLIDES]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
♪♪
[HUMMING]
[BLOOD SPLATTERS]
♪♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
What was it like,
To be alone with her?
Just as you'd imagine.
♪♪
She's powerful,
so calm.
My head finally feels right
again.
So, you are no longer
thinking of him?
I'm glad
I made that sacrifice.
As Alpha sacrificed
her daughter.
She said
when she watched her die,
she didn't shed one tear.
♪♪
She is Alpha.
She doesn't cry.
I'm so sorry...
for risking
what we have here.
I know.
♪♪
Don't do it again...
ever.
♪♪
Did you mean what you said
before,
you wish
you'd left me behind?
♪♪
Go to sleep, sis.
[ALL GROWLING]
♪♪
[EXPLOSION]
ALPHA: Pull them back.
BETA: Steady.
Do not break.
♪♪
There's too many.
Stay the course.
I want them.
[ALL GROWLING]
♪♪
[BABY CRYING]
Bring him.
You brought a baby
out here?
[CRYING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[CRYING]
No!
[ALL GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
[SCREAMING]
Aah!
♪♪
Do you regret
what you did?
She was an uncommitted.
She no longer
belonged with us.
I had to protect
the Alpha.
And you did.
It was your destiny.
As the lion who smothers
her wailing cub,
we're strongest
when we kill our own blood.
It is the purest,
most honest way
to bring order to chaos.
Your purity
will never be forgotten.
Yes, Alpha.
I see greatness in you.
♪♪
There's a tear.
Should I repair it?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
BETA: Leave us.
♪♪
Are you hurt?
I never felt more calm.
Calm?
♪♪
We lost three of our own,
and many more of the dead,
and you are calm?
It was mayhem.
♪♪
There is clarity
amid the chaos.
♪♪
She fears nothing.
Hmm.
[DOOR CREAKING]
♪♪
[SQUISHING]
LYDIA:
We're all monsters now.
♪♪
We're all... monsters now.
For your bravery
and sacrifice
and for putting the needs
of the pack above your own,
I anoint you Gamma.
♪♪
To Gamma.
- To Gamma.
ALL: To Gamma.
To Gamma.
To Gamma. To Gamma.
♪♪
You've been gone
for hours.
Are you angry with me?
I feel nothing for you.
I am also empty,
as Alpha wants.
Where is she?
I saw her moving toward
the old camp a while ago.
♪♪
LYDIA:
We're all monsters now.
We're all... monsters... now.
[GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
[SHUDDERS]
We're all monsters now.
♪♪
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[GROWLING, BANGING ON DOOR]
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS, GROWLING]
ALPHA: Lydia?
♪♪
Lydia?
Have you
lost your way?
Have you?
I told you
never to come over here.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I-I need to
find my daughter.
I don't care.
You kept that?
This is for Lydia.
♪♪
You said she was dead,
that you killed her.
You want her back.
♪♪
You shouldn't have
come here.
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
She is never coming back,
no matter how much
you wish for it
or how hard you try to
replace her with someone else.
She is gone, Alpha!
[GROWLING]
♪♪
No!
She's my daughter.
She's my baby.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I could not kill her.
♪♪
[WHISPERING]
They can't know.
They cannot know
Lydia's alive.
They cannot know.
[SNIFFLES]
They won't.
[VOICE BREAKING]
Lydia is dead.
Lydia is dead to me.
She was dead the moment
she was born...
'cause she was not
like me.
[CRIES]
Because she was not like me.
She was not like me.
She was not like me!
She was not... like... me!
She was not like me!!
[GRUNTS]
[WHIMPERS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [CLATTERING]
♪♪
I know you better
than you know yourself.
You've got demons,
yeah, just like me.
But you are not broken!
- You were made for this.
- Aah!
No! Stop! No!
She's trying to save you!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
My baby.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Mama, I was strong.
- You were, baby.
And I'm so proud
of you.
But don't you dare,
dare ever leave me again!
You hear me?!
[SNIFFLES]
♪♪
The world, it went dark
so that we could
see a new path.
So come.
Come on.
Walk with me
in the darkness.
Walk with me,
and you will never
be alone again.
My "B."
I am the end
of the world.
I am the end of the world.
I am the end
of the world.
We are the end
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
♪♪
[CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFLES]
Come with us.
I can't leave him.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
You won't have to.
♪♪
[CRIES]
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I saw smoke
by the border.
♪♪
The enemy
may have crossed.
♪♪
We must teach them
a lesson.
And the pack will watch.
We're going back.
♪♪
BOTH:
We walk in darkness.
We are free.
We bathe in blood.
We love nothing.
We are free.
We fear nothing.
We need no words.
We are free.
We embrace all death.
[ALL GROWLING]
This is the end of the world.
♪♪
Now is the end of the world.
We are the end of the world.
♪♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪♪