[FLY BUZZES]
[CHAINS CLINKING]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING]
Shit.
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Aah! Aah!
♪♪
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
You couldn't have done
that five hours ago?
Why would I do that?
[GRUNTING]
Come on. Family's inland.
And the munitions?
Everything's inland.
♪♪
I need to get back.
We headed in?
Well, I can't show up empty-handed.
Wife wouldn't like that.
Oh, my God.
This garden's her baby.
Got herbs and teas for everything...
pain, nerves, sleep.
How 'bout focus and speed?
Well, those Whisper folk
really got you percolatin', huh?
There's a lot of lives at stake.
Where are these munition
depots you spoke of?
Is this one of them?
Nah, that's just an old lab...
some structural damage.
Wild animals get in there sometimes.
Best to stay away.
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
My kids would run riot in here.
My boy seems to think
maybe the sailors must've left
a buried treasure in the grain silos.
I can barely get him not
to claw his way up the thing
and jump inside.
♪♪
Kid's 5.
[CHUCKLES]
He's just like his mom.
♪♪
Once they decide to do somethin',
ain't a damn thing
you can do to stop 'em.
I remember one time I...
Stop the bullshit.
Now, where the hell is your family?
♪♪
When I said I had to
come home to my family,
I meant it.
I promised her when we got married.
Flowers every day.
How are you gonna wait
till now to tell me this?
[SCOFFS]
Those words don't come easy.
I don't like to bring people here.
Don't trust 'em.
I was scared.
Are there any weapons here at all?
I promised I would help you check,
and I will, but...
- Ugh, I'm gonna find 'em myself.
- The island's not clear.
No shit it's not clear!
It was until the others came.
They brought violence.
The sickness came with it.
Killed my family.
We never had a lotta Rippers.
So I never really got good at...
doing [SIGHS] what it is you do.
You're good with a sword.
What are you askin' me?
My family's still in there.
My wife.
My babies.
That's why I asked you to come.
Needed you to come.
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[METAL CLINKS]
♪♪
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[FLESH TEARS, GROWLING STOPS]
[THUD]
[GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
[GROWLING STOPS]
[GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[METAL CLANGING]
Shit. Sorry.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
What do we do?
♪♪
Follow me. Stay close.
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Get behind that... now.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GROWLING STOPS]
Thank you.
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
VIRGIL: I wanted to give
them somethin' they loved
to take with 'em.
And Jasmine loved that book.
Look, I know that this
is hard, and I am sorry,
but I have got to get back.
My wife, whenever I had a hard time,
she'd talk me through it.
Without her, I don't know who I am.
It's not too late to find out. Look...
I wanted to ask you...
It's been a long time
since I had a reason to
say thank you to someone.
Don't thank me.
Just show me what I came here for,
and I'll go.
No, it's gettin' late.
- Tide's low.
- Oh, God.
I'm not sure the boat'll
make it through the channel.
Might wanna stay here
tonight and not risk it.
Virgil, I need you to hold
up your end of the bargain.
Yeah. But...
[GRUNTS]
It's gettin' dark,
and some of the buildings aren't safe.
Could we do this in the morning?
We can do it first thing.
[WALKIE-TALKIE CLICKS, STATIC]
[WALKIE-TALKIE TURNS OFF, THUDS]
[OWL HOOTING, CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DOOR CLANKS, CREAKS]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[DOOR CLANKS]
[SIGHS]
MAN: [WHISPERING]
Stay still. Everyone quiet.
Is it him?
WOMAN: I don't know.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
What is that?
I don't know. Quiet. Stop moving.
It might not be him.
Shh.
- No, I don't know.
- Be calm.
Stop moving.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
Virgil!
VIRGIL: Why couldn't you
just wait until morning?
I told you it wasn't safe.
Virgil, open the damn door.
I trusted you, and you ruined it.
Open the damn door, Virgil!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Virgil!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[WATER DRIPPING]
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, shit!
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Damn it.
MAN: Calm down.
Hello?
WOMAN: We've been trying to talk to you.
How long have I been in here?
A day maybe?
[SIGHS] A day?
Why didn't you answer me
when I called out to you the first time?
He blows up at us sometimes.
Gets in one of his moods.
When he's angry like that,
it's best to be quiet.
You guys know this building, right?
What's the layout?
Don't bother trying to escape.
Whole place is booby-trapped.
What's his routine? How
often does he come around?
As little as possible.
He doesn't like to see us.
[SIGHS]
Celeste and I were
researchers with Virgil.
We wrote the papers.
- Yeah, and I swept the floors.
- She assisted us.
So you had a life here.
You knew each other.
Yeah, we were friends with Virgil.
Tell me what went wrong.
Stragglers used to come by boat,
stumble on us, and we took 'em in.
We took 'em all in.
One night, it got really bad.
Food supplies were gettin' low,
and a fight broke out
over the rations and...
And somebody pulled a
knife, and this newbie died.
Virgil was late gettin' there,
panicked.
Said we need to lock all the doors.
He didn't know.
Virgil didn't know.
Know what?
His wife and kids were inside.
[SIGHS]
He snapped.
He was never the same.
We've been in here ever since.
You okay?
I will be.
I'm not stayin' here long.
You need some rest. Eat something.
The food should be okay.
Save your strength.
You can't kill him if you
don't have your strength.
CELESTE: You haven't told us your name.
It's Michonne.
[CLANK]
[PANTING]
I'm glad you ate.
Open the damn door!
I can't do that.
Why the hell not?!
Because you'll kill me.
I know you will.
Well, we reap what we sow, asshole.
[ECHOING] I don't wanna fight.
I want you to understand.
♪♪
[GRUNTING, WHIMPERING]
The island has a gift.
It can help you the way it helped me.
♪♪
[ECHOING] Aah!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
What the hell did you do?
[WATER DRIPPING ECHOES]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What did you... what did you...
[ECHOING] Jimsonweed.
Makes a nice tea.
Calming.
I want you to see.
You don't think I see it, but I do.
You're in pain, like me.
You need peace, like me.
Like you? No.
I don't drug people
and toss them in cells.
"Toss them in cells"? Yes, you've said.
We've had that conversation three times.
I need you to hear me.
I need you to think about
my daughter and my son.
"Think you about my
daughter and my son."
Yes, I said those words, too,
but no one listened.
♪♪
Everything I did was
to protect my family.
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho, I'm sure
they're real proud of you now.
SIDDIQ: [ECHOING] What about my child?
My family?
♪♪
You're no angel.
[WALKER GROWLS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm so cold.
It's cold. It's cold.
So picture the sun.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Let the medicine do its work.
♪♪
Siddiq.
You were supposed to protect us.
I did my best.
You let me die.
- No!
- And Rick and Carl.
What happens to Coco?
What happens to my family?
[CRYING] You are my family.
Well, this is how it
feels to be your family!
♪♪
[GROWLS]
Stop! Stop it! Stop!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
Siddiq?
[CHAINS CLINKING]
♪♪
VIRGIL'S VOICE: Stop fighting it.
[ECHOING] She's waiting.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
MICHONNE: [ECHOING] Hey!
Help!
Help! Please!
- Help me! Please!
- Come on. Let's go!
[SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
Please!
♪♪
[WALKER GROWLING]
- [GROWLING STOPS]
- [GRUNTING]
♪♪
Well, looky what we have here.
[GRUNTING]
Goddamn.
This chick has some cojones.
[NORMAL VOICE] I don't want any trouble.
Well, then, you probably shouldn't have
taken a swing at me.
Or I probably shouldn't have missed.
[CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
You know, I'm not much on
savin' people on the road,
especially those that
try to take my head off,
but I gotta say, I like you
and your big, ol' massive lady nuts.
Besides, be a waste
to have such a nice sword
and no strength to use it.
♪♪
[ECHOING] Name's Negan.
[FLESH TEARS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
♪♪
[ALARM BLARING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[NEGAN WHISTLING]
♪♪
NEGAN: Eenie...
meenie...
miney...
Nah.
Just kiddin', assholes.
See, I was gonna do
this next part myself,
but, see, my right-hand
gal, [ECHOING] Michonne,
is on a wicked-ass tear these days,
and who the hell am
I to stand in her way?
♪♪
[NORMAL VOICE] Mm.
You wish 'em a happy new
year from us, will ya?
♪♪
[SCOFFS]
You didn't know who they were...
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
...or where they were from.
♪♪
[ECHOING] You didn't
know shit about them.
But you came in the dead of night
and slaughtered them
anyway in their sleep.
♪♪
Like cowards.
Ah.
♪♪
And you remember...
you did this.
What happens next...
it's your fault.
♪♪
Welcome to the new world.
Ha!
♪♪
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GUN COCKS]
[GUNSHOT]
[RETCHING, COUGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[KEYS JINGLE]
You feel better?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You will.
Aah!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪♪
[BLADE CLANGS]
- LUCY: Michonne.
- JEREMIAH: Don't leave us.
CELESTE: Let us out. Please.
Michonne.
♪♪
[FIRE CRACKLING]
Oh, shit.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
I was gonna ask you to help me.
I wanted to let them go.
I wanted you to be there
so they wouldn't kill me.
Then you found 'em first,
and I knew you were gonna kill me, too.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? "Sorry" doesn't cut it.
[SCREAMS]
She always told me
the right thing to do,
and then she was gone
and I didn't know what to do.
And I couldn't let you leave,
and I didn't wanna kill you.
Move, Michonne.
You have as much reason to
kill this asshole as we do.
I do.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[SIGHS]
CELESTE: Do it or move.
♪♪
Look at him.
He owes you more than
he can ever make right.
Taking his life...
you'll lose more of yourself.
It doesn't settle it.
But your mercy gives you something.
You get something.
What?
Peace.
♪♪
[LUCY AND VIRGIL GRUNT]
[SIGHS]
MICHONNE: There's nothing here.
I checked every building,
even the ones you said
had structural damage.
Not a Goddamn thing anywhere.
I know you don't have
any reason to believe me,
but I never lied to
you about the weapons.
You said you'd seen them.
I told you I could show you the spots.
I got no reason to go in them.
You have got to do better than that.
I'm sorry. I can't.
Sometimes we find a stray shell,
but never any more than...
I... I find a stray shell.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm not going back empty-handed.
Take whatever you want.
Clear my debt with Oceanside.
- [KEYS JINGLE]
- [SIGHS]
You took the risk.
Didn't have a choice.
I had to find out.
And there's no tea, so don't even ask.
What do you see when
you're trippin', anyway?
Lisa with that damn
camera pointed at everyone.
My babies.
[CHUCKLES]
Jasmine sittin' by the
fire with that book,
askin' a million questions
about a world she'll never know.
♪♪
Bobby and me lyin' on
the roof of that Annex,
lookin' up at the stars.
Heaven.
♪♪
I wanted...
hoped that you would see that, too.
♪♪
It took my family from me.
I saw hell.
I'm sorry.
Only world I ever wanted
was one they were in.
I don't know how to
do this without them.
You try, like the rest of us.
Now, how 'bout you try to find my stuff?
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Where the hell did you get these?
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
VIRGIL: It washed up. [GRUNTS]
It washed up during the big storm.
I don't know where
the hell it came from.
[GRUNTING] Wait.
♪♪
No! Michonne.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Holy shit.
That's you.
And the kid?
♪♪
You knew.
You came to find us at Oceanside.
No. [SCOFFS]
What?
Uh, uh, why would I do that?
Because of this.
I have never seen that
before in my life. I swear.
But why are his things
here? What was he doing here?
How the hell would I know?
You knew that this boat
was here this whole time.
VIRGIL: The world ended.
Boats wash up. What
do you want me to say?
[GRUNTS]
You knew that there were no munitions.
Were you setting up a trap for us?
Did you lay a trap for him?
What did you do? What did you do to him?
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
Who are you talking about?
♪♪
[SNIFFLES]
VIRGIL: I don't know what
it is you think I have
or who you're looking for, but...
maybe it wasn't an accident that we met.
If the others will help me,
I think we can mod the engine
and get it workin' again.
♪♪
If this person was on this boat,
then maybe you can find them again.
♪♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Gonna take some time.
We're out of time.
They're willing to let you come.
They say that?
There's only one boat left.
You leave now or you don't leave.
After everything,
I can't believe they would do that.
Sometimes the most injured
are the most forgiving.
They're good people,
Virgil, and they're trying,
giving you a chance, a
way off of this island.
I promised her flowers every day.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[MICHONNE CRYING]
[SNIFFLES]
Shoto.
Shoto, are you there?
It's Daito.
Shoto?
Are you out there?
Anyone?
JUDITH: I'm here, Daito.
I've been trying you.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I'm sorry. I'm here now.
Are you still with Virgil?
No, but I found three
people on the island,
and I'm helping them get back home.
I've missed you and
your brother so much.
Mama.
JUDITH: No, no.
Call signs for safety.
Daito.
You're Daito.
Hey, baby.
And who are you?
I'm Little Brave Man.
Oh.
I love "Little Brave Man."
He picked it all by himself.
How long have you been with
your sister, Little Brave Man?
Tia Rosita brought me.
Judith...
how are Tia Rosita and Coco doing?
Okay, I guess.
Better.
How's home?
Anything with the Whisperers?
We got 'em, Mom.
We got most of the horde.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Alpha can't hurt us anymore.
You're doing it again.
You always make that
sound when you're worried.
Do not.
Do, too.
[SNIFFLES]
Um...
I found something.
Not what I was looking
for on the island,
but something else, something that...
could be really important to all of us.
What do you mean?
I found something that
belonged to the Brave Man
in a place that he
might've been recently.
I don't know what any of it means yet
or... or if it means anything at all.
Mom...
is he alive?
I-I don't know, [SNIFFLES] baby.
That's what I'm saying.
I-I-I don't know.
But if you think he's alive,
then you have to go find him.
No. No. Not now.
You and your brother need me,
and everything going on in Alexandria...
Mom, you have to go.
You have to.
♪♪
We're okay.
What if he needs you more?
♪♪
What if he's trying to come home, too,
but no one will help?
Ah, God.
♪♪
[SNIFFLES] If I go...
When you go and when you find him.
Okay, okay.
When I go...
and find the Brave Man...
[POUNDING]
- JEREMIAH: We're at the coast.
- I have to go.
Listen to Uncle Daryl.
I know.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay.
Okay, baby girl, I'm gonna try.
♪♪
I'm gonna head north.
And I'll try you every
morning on this walkie
for as long as I can.
I'll take it everywhere.
[SNIFFLES]
I love you and your brother so much.
Love you, too, Mom.
Go get him.
Shoto, out.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Wait, wait, wait.
♪♪
Wait.
Can you help us?
They'll leave without us.
Who?
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING]
Please.
♪♪
They won't wait for us.
CARL: Should we help her?
♪♪
RICK: You wanna tell us your name?
Who are you?
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWL]
Come on.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --