There's people in there.
Previously on "The Walking Dead"...
I lost my Kingdom.
And Carol.
I don't even know how
to talk to her anymore.
_
This is my home.
Negan killed her!
You know, the people out there
are talkin' about puttin' you down,
It was an accident.
What?
He's gone.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Gotcha.
Don't try anything.
Man.
The look on your face.
Dude, seriously, I'm...
I'm just messin' with you.
You're fast.
Took me forever to catch up.
Over there.
Normally, my chief concern
would be the hidden beauty of the grain,
but with quantity being of the essence,
rift and quarter sawing it'll be.
Happy to recapitulate.
Oh, no, no, just
checking in. Y'all good?
Eugene's come up with a zero-waste plan.
Claims he can use every cubic
inch of the tree, even the bark.
Seems as good a time as any
to master the Pueblo
art of basket weaving.
Hey, uh, before you head off,
Earl and I were talking.
Instead of using the extra
wood for the addition,
what if we made some weapons?
You know, big ones, defensive,
couple... couple of
catapults for the north wall.
Yeah, no, look, I think
it's a good idea, honestly,
just not right now,
not with half the
Kingdom still in tents.
Okay. I get it.
So, the Whisperers smash
a giant hole in our wall...
Yeah, well, we don't
know it was them for sure.
...and now they're
throwin' walkers at us
every couple hours, and
we're just gonna sit here,
twiddlin' our damn thumbs?
It happened again.
Root cellar. Middle of the night.
Well, who the hell was on watch?
♪ You're hard of hearin'
when I'm whisperin' ♪
♪ Love songs late at night ♪
♪ I'm used to dinner 'n drinks ♪
♪ But now all we ever do is fight ♪
♪ Leavin' liquor in the laundry ♪
♪ 'Cause ya love watching
me play hide-and-seek ♪
I'm not sure if you heard,
but someone stole a crate of fish,
the one from Oceanside.
Third theft this week, so...
♪ It's sad but true ♪
Brianna said
that you were guarding
the root cellar last night.
The sickos showed up at the breach.
♪ Oh, we used to stay up late ♪
You know how strained
everything is at the moment.
It would really help
if we all just stuck to
the jobs we were given.
♪ ...call you up and apologize ♪
♪ And, oh, oh ♪
♪ It's a cold, hard fact ♪
♪ We've said a lot of
things you know now ♪
♪ We can't take back ♪
♪ And, oh, oh, we used
to hold each other tight ♪
♪ Under sparkling trees ♪
_
No sign of Negan?
Searched all day and
night, but no sign of him.
Keep thinkin' about
what he took from us,
what we didn't take from him.
Alexandria deserved better.
Hey, you've had your trouble, too.
Actually, we could use
a hand in the infirmary.
Much of the Kingdom's still in recovery
from the tree fall.
We were plannin' on leavin' tomorrow,
but, uh... but yeah.
Of course. Whatever you need.
You ask about Carol?
Open the gate!
Nah.
_
She's not here?
She was tracking something,
said she'd meet us back here.
Should've been back by now.
Was that it?
Did I get it?
Nah. You woulda totally
whistled back, right?
My dad, he used to tell me how, like,
you and the Saviors would, like,
whistle back and forth
like that before...
You, uh... you say you had
some granola or some shit?
Sorry about the raisins
and the busted knife.
Was kinda in a rush
when I packed it all.
So, you're really not gonna tell me
how you got outta that cell?
Alright, well, at least tell
me what we're lookin' for.
Someplace safe.
I get it. A new Sanctuary.
Damn, how badass was that place?
And then Rick Grimes comes along,
talk about hypocrisy, kills our parents,
drags us to Alexandria,
lectures us about community.
Eh. Can't argue that. It ain't bullshit.
Man, I heard you made him
cut his own kid's hand off,
then you killed them.
Carl Grimes... I heard you shot him.
I never did that.
And I never did that to Carl.
Carl was...
I would never kill a kid.
Yeah, no, definitely.
I'm with you, obviously.
We're both Negan.
Who would do this?
The skin freaks.
Damn.
Should we cross?
"The enemy of my enemy is my friend"?
No.
Thanks for your help.
Sorry. I just needed a
second to wrap your gift.
There's more.
I swiped it all from Alexandria.
Was waiting for the right
time to surprise you.
Took me forever to find this.
Found it in the back of
an old storage garage.
My dad said he never saw you without it.
Listen, uh...
why don't you just put
that in your backpack?
I don't wanna be recognized.
You like it, though, right?
Does pig shit stink?
I'm gonna say...
she's a seven.
What?
Isn't this the kind of stuff
you and the Saviors
used to do to kill time?
I can't say that I remember
rating walkers on hotness.
Besides, she's clearly a three.
Spot's not half bad, right?
New Sanctuary.
You gotta be kidding me.
Damn! Classic Negan.
It's not your fault.
_
Hey.
Did I ever tell you
about my brother, Merle?
Uh...
Merle.
Okay, this one time,
he takes me fishing.
Right?
Fishing, right, on this big lake, right,
which is, uh...
private property...
right?
In this boat, which is, uh, stolen.
Stolen boat, right?
And he's drinking, right?
So he's fishing, he's drinking.
He falls in the lake.
Like, ka-pssh!
Right?
I have to take him, uh, like this...
...swim him all the way back.
I save his life, right?
You know what he says to me?
"Dummy, go get the beer."
Idiot, right?
Yeah.
It's gonna be alright.
Come on.
Good dog. Good dog.
What?
So, uh, the roofing and
the gutters should be fine,
but the plumbing's
making me kinda nervous.
I have to scavenge for more copper.
I should really be out there with them.
You know, if I was lost in the woods,
it's the three of them I'd
want to come looking for me.
Somebody's gotta hang back,
deal with the plumbing.
I'll... I'll ask Oscar about the copper.
You really think Kelly's okay?
I hope so.
What about us?
That tree didn't fall on its own.
Wasn't leaning or dying.
The roots were healthy.
If you don't think they're
coming back for worse, son,
you're not thinking at all.
I haven't forgotten
about them, you know?
Think about 'em every day.
Well, good. Don't stop.
We've had some thefts lately.
Took a quarter of our medical supplies.
Sorry. I...
No, no. It's, uh...
Henry forged it during
his apprenticeship.
Found it wrapped among his things.
A gift intended for me but never...
You okay?
Sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
Uh-huh.
That doesn't sound good.
It's nothing.
Just the regular slings and arrows.
Or smoke inhalation from the
fire might've triggered it.
Let me just...
I said I was fine.
Okay.
How long have you...
A month.
It's grown since then.
Look.
It could be a lot of
things, yeah? Infection.
- You know you might've injured yourself.
- I know what it is.
Listen, without tests,
you can't be sure.
Siddiq, I know what it is.
Growing up, my grandmother
went through it,
then my father.
The pain, the coughing, the swelling.
I watched them fight it and win.
Did you know thyroid cancer
had a 98% survival rate?
Different times.
Times of sorcery and witchcraft.
Chemo, iodine radiation therapy,
thyroidectomies.
Now?
Now we both know what it means.
No, you can manage it.
Acupuncture, uh, hypnosis.
There's... You...
You know, I've been struggling
with my own condition...
...ever since the barn.
That's why I had to leave Alexandria.
I just... I can't stand
how everyone looks to
me for some kinda...
So, you know, maybe we
can't get away from it.
But we can talk about it.
I mean, what are we here for
if not for each other?
It was just Milo and me.
We'd been walking for days, weeks,
until the hissers ran through our camp,
scattered everyone to the winds.
After that, we went back
to what it was before,
what it always is in the end...
Milo and me,
moving from place to place, surviving.
I get it.
I've been there.
I better stay on my feet.
Milo, you wanna come on a walk?
Yeah.
Be safe.
So, what are you thinkin'?
We follow 'em, see
where they're hiding it?
Hiding what?
They've got a stash somewhere,
probably full of weapons, too.
It's a chick and a kid, Brandon.
People are a resource.
Yeah. Not them.
Alright, look.
I appreciate everything
you've done since Alexandria,
but it's only gonna get
more dangerous from here.
I think it's best I go on alone
and you go home.
Okay.
It's just, if I go back,
everyone's gonna wanna
know where I've been.
What am I supposed to say?
I've never been a great liar.
New plan, then.
You go wherever the hell you want.
You go back to Alexandria,
you tell the whole
world exactly where I am.
You see, I don't give a shit.
Just as long as I don't have to see
that pasty, creepy-ass
face of yours ever again.
You're just like all the others.
Careful, now.
Ears are the trickiest.
You have something for me?
I've been damming up the
creek, like you wanted.
I've just come back
for one more guardian.
A guardian taken is another lost.
Patience.
Shifts in strategy take time.
The creek, the water, the tree...
it will crush them.
Or we could release
an army of thousands.
Go ahead.
Say your piece.
Instead of these little nicks,
getting our guardians
killed at their walls,
why don't we...
cut the enemy down all at once?
Let us vote.
Anyone agree?
That's democracy for you.
The human body...
...is fragile.
All it takes for it to collapse
is a few nicks in the right spots.
Just like the enemy.
When their world collapses,
the smart ones will know
where to come to stay safe.
We'll be waiting.
You said you wanted another guardian.
Oh, no! We're gonna crash!
Ah.
Hey.
Don't worry, kid. I don't bite.
Your mom, she's inside, packin',
so we got a little bit of time to kill.
Where'd Brandon go?
Brandon... he went looking for supplies.
You know what?
I'm gonna be real with you.
Uh, I told Brandon to get lost.
You see, uh, it turns out,
not the best co-pilot,
if you catch my dri...
You don't catch my drift at all, do ya?
You've never been on a plane.
Aw, man, it's alright.
It's not your fault that
God turned this world
into an asspit before you were born.
Alright.
Picture this, alright?
Sitting on a plane,
really nice, comfy seats,
but it feels like you've
been sitting on the runway
for Goddamn ever.
Suddenly, there's this kinda rumbling,
a groan, alright?
The plane finally starts
to creep along, right,
and now we're moving faster and faster.
And you look out that window,
and everything's turning into a blur.
And then, "Whew."
Wheels come up off the ground.
You are flying.
It is like voodoo magic, man, alright?
Up and up and up, higher and higher,
until it feels like you are floating
on top of the frickin' world.
And you're looking out that little
window, and you can see houses.
They look like little toy
houses and little toy cars.
Oh.
But the food?
Unh-unh. No way.
They served us something.
They called it beef stroganoff.
Let me tell you something.
It looked like baby shit.
And my Lucille she
wouldn't even touch it.
Ah, kid, there is so
much you're gonna miss
growing up in this... screwed-up world.
You know, driving your
first set of wheels,
video games,
nut-tapping.
What, you've never heard of nut-tapping?
Seriously? With big ol'
sausage fingers like those?
Alright, man, the whole
point of nut-tapping...
catching the other guy off guard, right,
embarrassing him,
getting even for him
calling your mom a slut
or whatever.
Wanna keep your wrist loose, like this.
Lean in all casual like.
And then... thwack!
Snap your fingers right on his nuts.
Now, you gotta remember, you go low.
You go too high, you
get nothing but dick.
Alright, let's see what you got.
You're a natural.
See, if nut-tapping were a sport,
you wouldn't have to 'roid up,
and you would still
be in the hall of fame.
Ahh.
Alright, kid, dinner.
Not gonna happen without fire.
Fire's not gonna happen without wood.
Tell me something.
You get all packed up?
Yeah.
Hey, you know, I know that moving sucks.
You know, it's like I was
telling your mom, though,
I know a place that I'm pretty
sure they're gonna take you in.
It's got really high walls, farmland,
even has a mansion sitting
in the middle of it.
You just can't tell 'em
who brought ya, alright?
But I will get you as close as I can.
One condition, though.
Keep those meaty fingers holstered up
when my nuts are around.
Okay.
- Deal?
- Yeah.
My man.
I anoint you Gamma.
Oh!
Shit. Shit!
It's okay.
That's for you.
I had it in my bag.
Take it.
It's okay.
My name is Aaron.
What...
That's right. You guys
don't do names anymore.
But you're from somewhere, right?
I'm from Vermont. Where...
You're welcome!
Hey.
_
We've gotta get her back to Hilltop.
Nah, I think we gotta
find somewhere closer.
_
Tell them what?
Did you know about this?
Hey. What's she saying?
I said I don't trust you.
What's your problem?
Huh?
Hilltop takes you in.
They got sick children
and mouths to feed,
and you steal from 'em?
All you're good for is talking shit.
_
That's it, right?
You almost had me.
Back on the bus, when you kicked me out.
Then I remembered, "This is Negan.
He's always messing with
people, keeping 'em in line."
So I realized there's a test.
"It's gonna get a lot more
dangerous from here on out."
That's what you said to me.
You wanted to make sure
that I had the balls
to do what had to be done.
What do you think?
I passed, right?
I am Neg...
_
I had to pop a couple blisters.
Bill's still freaking
out about that rash.
What else?
I mean, the universe
is basically on pause
till God gets back.
I'm assuming your mic's out,
or else I'd hear you
laughing your balls off.
Nope, still here.
How's Rosita?
She, uh, didn't want me to tell you,
but she caught a little bug.
She okay? Gabe back?
Not yet. But she'll be fine.
I'll leave for home tonight.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
One other thing.
Is Carol around?
She's just outside. Let me grab her.
Hey, Carol. Siddiq's
on the radio for ya.
You know, it's scary to think, but...
Kelly probably wouldn't have made it
if you guys hadn't
have found that stash.
Sounds like it was pretty
far off the main road.
Just say it.
You think I stole everything
and hid it out there.
Yeah, well, it wouldn't
have been the first time.
Then... it would've been smart.
Yeah, or it would've been a mis...
Selfish, stupid.
I was gonna say a mistake.
No, but you were thinking it.
For 13 years, that's
how you've looked at me.
That is not true.
Since the day you showed up
in your... your fancy
suit, with all your fancy...
Do you really wanna know
what I thought that day?
I thought, "Here is a
person, an innocent person
who's been locked up for
a crime they didn't commit,
someone who's never trusted anybody
because no one's ever trusted her,
someone who's good.
And, yeah, mad.
Mad at everyone.
Mad at the world for
being so messed up."
My cousin, she was a little girl,
and he gets to go on living his life?
No way.
But nobody came for him.
So I came for him.
And there it is.
Now that we've both killed...
how many people have we killed, Miko?
And still, that look right there.
I think you should find
another place to sleep.
The... man with the
metal arm gave it to me.
I don't know what that...
Sit.
We've all had to wear different masks
at different times.
Call it a kinda sacrifice.
Like your sister.
Your sacrifice was... much greater.
The man with the metal arm...
could prove useful.
You might just have to wear a new mask.
_
Uh, yeah.
Uh, Siddiq has to go back.
Is, um...
Kelly okay?
Mm.
_
No, no, no.
I get it. Um...
Family.
Right?
Alright.
Oh, you sorry, rotten sacks of shit.
What's a fella gotta do
to get eaten around here?
What's the matter? Huh?
Y'all scared of the Big Bad Wolf?
Little pig, little pig!
Uh-oh.
Let me in.
And there you are!
Oh, I am gonna huff.
I am gonna puff.
I am gonna blow...
...your...
...house...
Ahh.
...all the way in.
Alright, you big-ass freak.
Let's do this.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --