The ones that watch the horde are loyal.
She gives them no choice.
Previously, on "The Walking Dead"...
People that I love died
right in front of me,
and now I get to watch it over and over.
No more games.
Let him go.
No. No. No.
Your mother told her
people that she killed you.
You used me.
♪♪
[BOTH GRUNTING]
I don't care if you're new to us.
♪♪
I don't care what your past was.
We all have a past.
None of that matters now.
♪♪
You did well at the barn.
Now I need something more.
♪♪
Eyes and ears inside their walls.
You are the kind of man they'll trust.
Practical, loyal, smart.
♪♪
And my daughter doesn't know you.
Where should I start?
Ugh!
Find some strangers and join them.
♪♪
[HERD GROWLING]
Help!
- Come on! Let's move!
- Help me!
- Walkers!
- Walkers! Move!
Help me!
- He's over here!
- Help me!
[GRUNTS]
Help me!
[GROWLING]
[WOMAN SHOUTS]
- [GROWLS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [MAN SHOUTING]
- [KNIFE PLUNGING, THUDDING]
[WALKER GROWLS]
♪♪
ALPHA: Go to their gate.
They won't turn you away.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
How you doing?
Hey, roll your sleeve up for me, please.
Oh, yeah, sure.
There we go.
♪♪
Make them think you're at home...
...but never forget your real one.
♪♪
Push quietly against their
weaknesses until they crumble.
♪♪
- [CREAKING]
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
♪♪
- [CREAKING]
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
♪♪
- [GRUNTING]
- [MUFFLED GRUNTING]
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
♪♪
ALPHA: Do all this,
and we will welcome
you home when they fall.
You'll have a special place among us.
♪♪
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKS LIGHTLY]
♪♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[COCO FUSSING]
♪♪
Siddiq, are you awake?
[DOOR CREAKS]
[COCO FUSSING]
Hola.
Bueno.
_
♪♪
Siddiq and I were talking about
how he's not sleeping much.
♪♪
_
We're having a hot romance.
Didn't you know?
[CHUCKLES]
Nah, we were just hanging,
and he got called out.
Something about, uh,
Andy and Donna's kid throwing up.
I didn't ask for details.
Okay.
Lo siento, pero you just missed him.
♪♪
Mm.
_
♪♪
[WHEEZING]
No.
Rosita.
[COCO CRYING]
♪♪
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
- There you go.
- [CRYING]
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
[COCO CRYING]
♪♪
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [CRYING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- Alright. It's okay.
- No.
- It's okay.
In nature, sometimes
parents eat their young.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
♪♪
Ahh!
No!
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[GROWLING]
No!
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
Oh!
[THUDS]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
It's okay. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- [CRYING CONTINUES]
[GASPING] I know.
I know.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[RUSTLING FOOTSTEPS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
You alright?
Is the baby still alive?
The baby that was rescued at Hilltop?
Y-Yes.
He's my nephew.
Oh.
I didn't know that.
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
Did you ever name him?
My sister didn't.
She couldn't.
The family raising him named him Adam.
Can I see him?
Your people left him to die.
Why would we ever agree to that?
Because we can trade.
I have information for you.
What is it?
Promise me I can see him.
I can't promise you anything.
I'll listen to what you
have, see if it's true,
and then we can talk.
He's the only family I have left.
Well, then, you better tell the truth.
Without your mask.
[SIGHS LIGHTLY]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
Before all this, my name was Mary.
Hi, Mary.
What do you wanna tell me?
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Hope that hurts.
It doesn't matter.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
None of this matters.
Watch enough people get
incinerated, devoured alive,
you see how ridiculous it is
getting attached to ourselves.
But knowing that sets you free.
Is that what you're doing?
Setting us free?
If you learn that lesson,
it'll only help you.
- What, so we can be more like you?
- [LIGHTER CLICKS]
- Accept the future.
- GABRIEL: Siddiq depended on you.
Why put him through all
that hell in the barn
just to kill him months later?
I-I can't see an ideology behind that.
I liked Siddiq.
Oh, you liked him?
♪♪
He wasn't part of the plan.
But he found out who I
was, so I had no choice.
What plan?
Encourage your paranoia about us...
which will push you into bad decisions.
Places like this
are cruel promises to their people,
and they crumble at the smallest nick.
♪♪
Hell, I'm gonna enjoy watching
you rip each other apart
over what to do with me.
Just like with Negan.
Is that what you want?
A public reckoning?
A chance to be heard?
That's what you'll give me.
Because it's right.
♪♪
- We helped you.
- Why?
'Cause you wanted another doctor around?
You got something from me, too.
Don't pretend you didn't.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
No one is actually kind.
We are selfish.
We are brutal.
Come on.
Even seeing all those heads on spikes
didn't teach you what people are?
- [GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
He's been here four months.
How didn't I know?
None of us did.
We all ate together.
[SIGHS] Talked about training the militia.
[BREATHES SHARPLY] He treated Gracie.
You can't do that to yourself.
Yeah. Especially now.
We gotta keep our heads straight,
try to figure out what's going on.
[SIGHS LIGHTLY]
Mary, the Whisperer
I've been talking to, um,
told me where Alpha is keeping the herd.
Just over the border, on their side.
It's this sunken field
on the edge of the national forest.
We can leave right after the funeral.
We're gonna trust a Whisperer now?
- You wanna do nothing?
- Lydia's still gone.
We don't even know what that means yet.
Alpha doesn't know that.
With Dante locked up in
a cell, she never has to.
We ain't gonna talk about how
this is probably an ambush?
Well, the baby that Connie rescued...
apparently that's Mary's nephew.
She wants to see him.
I don't think she's lying.
Alright.
Get a group from Hilltop
and meet us there.
Second we're done, we're
going looking for the girl.
Yeah. I'll radio them.
Maybe they can get the
news to Michonne, too.
Alright.
- [DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- Hey.
Why don't you stay here? I'll go.
Why?
You gonna tell me what
really happened out there?
I told you. Lydia
didn't want to come back.
I couldn't make her.
Her being here protects
us. You know that.
So, that's it for her
now, to be our shield?
Just lock her up again?
I showed one of Alpha's people
that their leader lied to them,
and that's good for us.
We can push on their wounds, too.
You still should have told me.
I'll help you look for her,
but I don't think she wants to be found.
Are we talking about her,
or are we talking about you?
♪♪
[WHISTLING]
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [WHISTLING STOPS]
- [HORSE NEIGHS]
♪♪
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[HORSE SNORTING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
What do you see?
I'm not as good a tracker as Daryl,
but those prints look recent and clean,
not dragging like a walker.
Whisperers don't travel alone,
so it's gotta be somebody else.
Could be one of their scouts.
The longer we spend out here,
the more likely we
are to bump into them.
If it's just one scout,
I like our chances.
But we have to be as quiet as possible.
Right?
- Yup, that was meant for me.
- Let's go.
I take no offense.
I am here as a representative of Hilltop
as a soldier of peace and justice.
Or you wanna see Jules.
What?
Stop it.
What were you whistling before?
I'm glad you asked me that.
I'm whistling one of
the most whistle-able...
is that even a word? It is now...
whistle-able sections
of Rachmaninoff's variations
on a theme of Paganini.
It's like one of the
greatest pieces of music ever.
It's my favorite.
And I can only hear
it in my head nowadays.
I wanna write that down, but
you've gotta spell it, please.
I got you. What do you got here?
A record of everything
that happens to us.
Our stories for the future.
Really?
Oh.
Well, maybe I can help you out.
If you wanna do a
great personal history,
you've gotta read a little.
And this road leads right
through Waterford, right?
And I remember they had a
really excellent library there.
Maybe we want to stop and
pick up some inspiration.
What do you say, Ma?
We really shouldn't.
Come on, please, Mom?
I've read almost every
book in Alexandria.
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪
Russian-English dictionary for Eugene.
Satellite parts.
Okay, smart one.
I'm gonna go check out
their music section.
Just 'cause, you know, we're here.
I'll go see if there's
anything worth taking.
Mm.
♪♪
I always wanted to read this.
[PAGES FLIPPING]
Maybe we can read it together?
MAGNA: Hilltop to Michonne.
Are you there?
[CLICKS]
This is Michonne.
It's Magna.
I'm relaying a message
to you from Alexandria.
Michonne and Judith are listening.
What happened?
[WHISTLING]
[WHISTLING CONTINUES]
Aha, yes!
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Yo.
Here we go.
Ahh!
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
- [GROWLS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
♪♪
Ohh!
[GRUNTS]
[WALKER GROWLING]
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
Oh!
Damn it!
[WALKERS GROWLING]
- Help!
- [BREATHES SHARPLY]
♪♪
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
Hey! W-What's your name, man?
Huh? What's your name?
What... Wait!
- Thank you! Ah!
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[WALKER GROWLING]
♪♪
[GROWLING STOPS]
- [THUDS]
- Hey!
- What's your name, man?!
- What happened?
This guy just came in out of nowhere.
He saved my life. He just ran out!
Who the hell does that?!
Maybe you can catch him. Ohh!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS]
Who in the hell does that, man?
And leave all his stuff here?
Just runs off?
What the hell?
That's a good book.
You should keep that one.
We'll take all of it.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Is everything alright?
[SIGHS]
♪♪
Siddiq is dead.
So, no, not everything is okay.
We have to get to Oceanside
and get back home now.
♪♪
I remember this passage from my studies.
Written by a scholar centuries ago
who was trying to
understand the impossible...
"Let me live if life is better for me
and take my life if
death is better for me."
He had surrendered himself to fate
because his world defied logic.
Defied justice.
♪♪
We created you from it...
...and return you into it...
♪♪
...and from it we will
raise you a second time.
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hi.
It's good to see you.
You too.
I can't believe he's gone.
I don't know why, but...
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Never mind.
What?
He was one of those people
I thought would live forever.
Not really, but you know.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Too many things are changing.
How long are you staying?
Maybe a day or two.
I'm sorry. I wish I had more time.
It's okay.
I hear you might have
found Alpha's herd.
You need help?
No, we have enough people.
Everything else okay?
Good luck.
Thanks.
♪♪
[HORSE WHINNIES IN DISTANCE]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪♪
[THUMPING]
[HERD GROWLING]
[THUMPING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
- [CRYING]
- No!
♪♪
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
- [GROWLS]
- [GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
♪♪
Ohh!
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH PANTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Thanks.
No expressions of gratitude required.
I was only relieved I
happened to be crossing through
on my way ho...
On my way back to my domicile.
You almost said "home."
No.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Yes.
♪♪
My deepest condolences, Rosita.
Siddiq's passing was an
incomprehensible tragedy.
♪♪
I only wish there was more I could offer
than to pay my respects
and to bash
a few vexatious walkers
in their flame-blistered crania.
♪♪
Well...
travel safe.
I mean, I'm... I'm the one
who's gonna be traveling.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
MAN: Who were you before?
I was a doctor, a father.
I was trying to get by.
How long did you know the
people you came in with?
Months, I don't know.
I lost track of time.
They saved my life.
I was dying out in the woods.
Who was your leader?
- We didn't...
- [VIDEO FAST-FORWARDS]
How many people have you killed?
Only man I ever killed
tried to hurt my son.
But walkers got Jimmy
in the end, anyway.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[BREATHING QUICKLY]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
What happened?
I was helping Eugene with
some walkers at the gates.
How's sweet pea?
Fast asleep.
You know, that wasn't the truth.
Um...
I wasn't helping Eugene.
He was helping me.
- Okay.
- I just...
I should be able to
handle walkers like that.
I always could before.
It's been a rough day, Rosita.
No, it's not that.
I could die.
♪♪
I used to think that, if
it happened, it happened.
♪♪
But now that would make Coco an orphan.
And I cannot die.
♪♪
I'm afraid.
And that feeling isn't going away.
Well feelings don't predict the future.
That sounds like a quote
from somewhere else.
We need to focus on the
problem in front of us.
It's my responsibility to...
If I freeze again...
You won't.
You're not listening.
I have to figure out
how this happened to us.
Council members are talking
to Jen and Wayne now,
and I need to get over
there. We need to find Lydia.
We need to find out why
she didn't know Dante.
- We need to find out...
- Did you hear what I said?
You needed help with a walker,
and now you think
you'll keep needing help,
but I'm saying the feeling will pass.
♪♪
Maybe Dante was right about us.
We're not as strong as we think we are.
♪♪
Alright. If you get
two more right, you win.
- Pick easy ones.
- No way, Jose.
[CHUCKLES] Okay, let's see. Uh.
Capital of Missouri.
Jefferson City.
Amazing.
Uh...
capital of South Dakota.
Pierre.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a winner.
- That's amazing.
- [LAUGHS]
It's good.
Okay. Choose.
I want a story about California.
Capital, Sacramento.
[CHUCKLES] California.
Okay.
Let's see.
Okay, um, summer after college,
I was hiking near Eureka
with this man I was in love with.
And we were way high up in the forest.
We found these old ruins
from a Native American village
from hundreds of years ago.
And we stood there in
the middle of the village
and just listened to the
sound of the ocean waves
crashing on the beach from far away.
And we tried to imagine, you know,
what those people were like
who were now, um, um, lost to time.
These were people who had
their own laws and beliefs
and hopes for the future
of their own village.
♪♪
You know, I was one of
the very first people
here in Alexandria,
back when it started, back when we...
we thought we knew
what it was going to be.
♪♪
And recently, I've been
thinking more and more
about that village.
What happened to those people?
I don't know.
♪♪
[GATE OPENS]
MICHONNE: When was the last
time you had new people in here?
RACHEL: Since way before the fire.
Dante showed up in Alexandria
way before the fire.
We can't use that as a marker
of Alpha's return anymore.
Whatever process you were using
to vet your newest people here,
you have to put them
through a different one.
MAN: Ahh! No! No!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- What's going on?
- Aah! No! No!
- N-No! No!
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
How did you get in here?
- Come on, come on!
- [GRUNTING]
- Who the hell are you?
- He was trying to steal a sail.
And then probably also a boat.
- Let me go!
- Where did you come from?
Let me go. Don't touch me!
I swear to God, I'm
not gonna ask you again.
♪♪
I'm just trying to get home.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
I just wanna get back to my family.
Michonne... This is the
guy. This is the guy.
He saved my life at the
library. How you doing, pal?
And also the guy that's
been sneaking around,
messing with the security system.
In the past, we've hung
men for less than that.
And he might be a Whisperer.
O-Okay. H-Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
He was taking books.
He... He has a picture of his family.
He's got a bag full of stuff.
Does that seem like a Whisperer?
We don't know what a Whisperer
looks like anymore, Luke.
Come on. Let me go.
You're gonna answer our questions.
Who are your people?
♪♪
[HERD GROWLING]
CYNDIE: They breached the fence!
Hold him!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Watch their hands!
♪♪
[GRUNTING ECHOES]
[GROWLING ECHOES]
♪♪
[GROWLING]
Judith!
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKING]
Did you even have a son?
Why does that matter?
I guess it doesn't.
It was one of the
things I liked about you.
That my son was killed?
That you had a family.
I suppose you'd like me to
never trust anyone ever again.
[CHUCKLES]
It's a meaningless idea.
[SIGHS]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Is that what you're here to show us?
Look around you, Gabriel.
Look what people did to the world.
And you think we can be good?
You think we deserve a second chance?
I loved Siddiq like a brother.
My family will never be the same now.
His daughter will never know him.
Maybe Rosita will blame me,
and maybe she's right to.
I didn't protect them enough.
I...
I haven't always been brave.
Do we deserve a second chance?
I don't know.
But sometimes we get one, anyway.
[KNIFE UNSHEATHES]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
Ahh!
[SHOUTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[SHOUTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[KNIFE CLATTERS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[CRYING]
[RUMBLING CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS] No! No!
[GRUNTS]
[HERD GROWLING]
Ohh!
[GRUNTS]
Don't move.
[GROWLING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Mom!
Over here!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[HERD GROWLING]
♪♪
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HERD GROWLING]
Good girl.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
You will grow tall,
and you will grow strong.
You will know safety...
[RUMBLING CONTINUES]
...and family...
and home.
♪♪
[RUMBLING CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[HORSE SNORTS]
- Hi.
- Hey, D.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
- Mm.
- How's Rosita?
- As expected.
Let's get to it. Screw these freaks.
I say that in Siddiq's honor.
Thanks for helping.
_
♪♪
Hey. Wait.
Coulda lost a foot.
They laid traps. Means
we're getting closer.
I saw something over there.
Will you stop this shit?
Please.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
You want her dead so bad,
you don't even care what happens to you.
That's not true.
You never came off that boat.
It's been like talking
to a goddamn ghost.
I'm doing the best I can.
I'm the one you tell.
Me.
♪♪
[VOICE BREAKING]
I don't... I don't know how.
You gotta try, alright?
♪♪
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Come here.
♪♪
[SIGHING]
She's not worth it.
♪♪
She's not.
Look at me.
♪♪
She's a dead woman, anyway.
We have a future.
Don't let her take that, too.
♪♪
Yes.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
You good?
♪♪
Yeah.
Alright.
I'll get this.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[WALKER GROWLING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[FIRE CRACKLING ECHOES]
♪♪
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[GROANING LIGHTLY]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[GROANS]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
Don't go through my stuff.
That book belongs to my daughter.
I wasn't.
The book fell out, and
I picked it up for you.
And it clearly belongs to the library.
It's for my daughter.
Put it back.
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
Be careful.
You'll rip your stitches.
[PANTING]
You comfortable?
[GROANS LIGHTLY]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
Judith...
give us a minute.
[FOOTSTEPS]
So...
what are you really doing here?
Your daughter's a little
demon with a sword.
Yeah.
Like mother, like daughter.
Only mine wouldn't
leave anything to heal.
Now answer my damn question.
Didn't mean it in a bad way.
No way you make it this long
without being comfortable with violence.
Now, how long have you been watching us?
I'm not watching you.
I don't want to hurt anybody here.
I left home for supplies,
and now I'm just trying to get back.
I swear.
Why'd you help my friend?
Is that a part of the play?
No. No. There is no play.
I don't know. I just did it.
He needed help.
Even with what might happen
to me here, glad I did it.
Mercy's in short supply these days.
♪♪
I don't expect it.
Maybe I don't deserve it.
♪♪
Something wrong?
You just reminded me of something
a friend of mine used to say.
♪♪
What's that?
"My mercy prevails over my wrath."
♪♪
Okay.
So, you're trying to get home.
♪♪
Just tell me where that is.
I can't tell you where I live.
My family's there.
This is how you get back to them.
Or keep them safe.
Your wife and kids
don't know where you are
or whether you're ever gonna come back.
Don't put them through that.
♪♪
I live on Bloodsworth
Island in Tangier Sound.
♪♪
Hard to find...
and fortified.
♪♪
Like I said, I didn't mean
to break in, cause any chaos,
but I needed a boat on your pier.
[SIGHS]
Well, good intentions or not,
you owe them for all that damage,
and you're not going anywhere
until we figure that out.
You have enemies to fight.
♪♪
Maybe we can help each other out.
What do you mean?
♪♪
What'd he tell you?
He lives on a naval base,
an island about two days from here.
♪♪
Could be weapons big
enough to kill a herd.
Take out Alpha once and for all.
And he'd just let you have 'em?
Oh, yeah.
Then I need to find a
way to bring them back.
♪♪
So, what's wrong?
It would have to be me...
just me taking that kind of risk.
♪♪
But also...
I should get back.
With everything happening at
home, we should be together.
Fighting together.
♪♪
But this could end the war.
Right?
Maybe.
♪♪
I have to find out.
It's okay, Mom.
You do.
♪♪
We can't lose anyone else.
[MUSIC FADING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
God damn it!
- Wait.
- For what?
AARON: This doesn't mean
Mary lied to us, alright?
They were protecting this place.
T-They put a trap in
the road as a deterrent.
Yeah, from some hunter a decade ago.
No. That thing was rigged
more recently than
that, and you know it.
You wanna stand around
and figure it out?
Look, the herd could have been
here last week or yesterday.
We had an obligation
to come check this out.
Nah. Time to find Lydia.
Let's go.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
I know everything's
upside down right now,
but I wasn't wrong about this.
♪♪
I negotiated with Rachel.
Whatever weapons you have on your island
will pay off your debt.
I'll take you home,
and I'll bring the boat back to them.
♪♪
Can't be that simple.
Or thank you.
You're welcome.
Up to you.
♪♪
Can I have my stuff back?
[SIGHS LIGHTLY]
♪♪
I'm Virgil.
Michonne.
MAN: Yeah, we're gonna need...
Fill everyone in back home.
I am just a walkie call
away if they need anything.
I'm only a couple days behind you.
I'll make sure the council knows
what you're about to bring home.
We'll have people ready
with wagons, if you need.
Just keep us posted.
Michonne, I don't want you to worry.
We got Judith looking after us.
♪♪
Keep her safe.
I will.
♪♪
Now, it doesn't have to be an emergency
for you to check in, okay?
You can do that every day.
♪♪
Or...
[WALKIE-TALKIE CLICKS]
...every hour.
[CLICKS]
Roger. Over and out.
♪♪
I'll see you soon.
Be good for Uncle Daryl.
♪♪
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
DARYL: Lydia would have
taken this river downstream.
Back to our side.
♪♪
Hey.
Carol, let's go.
You go on. I'll meet you.
Nope. We all stay together.
♪♪
Hey!
Carol!
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[HERD GROWLING]
Go! Get her ass out of there!
[GROWLING]
♪♪
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[WHISPERING] Carol!
[RUMBLING]
♪♪
[GROANING]
[HERD GROWLING]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --