Previously on "The Walking Dead."
You want her dead so
bad, you don't even care
what happens to you.
NEGAN: I'm all in.
Whatever you want, whatever I got,
it's yours.
Hey!
Carol!
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[SNARLING]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Uh...
Hey, guys?
♪♪
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
♪♪
Make sure they don't get out.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Aah!
Damn. You okay?
I almost had it.
DARYL: Nah, it's too high.
You risk breakin' your neck.
We need to find a better way.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
You got something?
Groundwater's deeper in here.
That water's coming from outside.
CAROL: I don't see a way across.
Whoa, whoa. Go back, go back.
We could use those to jump across.
- Nice.
- Wait. For real?
♪♪
All right.
You ready?
Let's go.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
Come on.
Let's go!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
_
♪♪
Do it now!
[GRUNTS]
No! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Come on!
♪♪
Hey, hey!
Come on! Come on!
Come on. I gotcha.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
Hey! Hey!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
Hey, hand me that thing.
Knock yourself out, dude.
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
Alright.
I need you to stay here, all right?
Keep everyone together.
Should I even ask how
we're doing on food?
Not great.
Food?
How long do you think we gonna be here?
Hey, no worries.
Walkers got in here somehow.
We'll get out.
I think we know exactly
how they got here.
Alpha put them here.
These are theirs.
We have to assume we're not alone.
♪♪
I'm fine.
Just a little winded.
She's claustrophobic.
Why didn't you think of that
before you got us all trapped down here?
Hey.
It's not the time for this.
Why not?
Seems like we have plenty of it.
♪♪
What the hell were you thinking, huh?
Running off like that by yourself.
DARYL: Hey!
We ain't got time for this shit.
We got in this mess together.
We're gonna get out of it together.
Now follow me.
I think I found a way out.
♪♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
The enemy are watching us.
A small group crossed the border.
They went straight to the
edge of the national forest.
The horde...
They knew exactly where to look.
Did they find it?
We underestimated them.
We have to assume
they've been sending
spies across the border.
I want more patrols around the camp.
♪♪
I want you to take a message
to our eyes along the border...
they have failed.
♪♪
[WATER DRIPPING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
_
Hey. Can I... Can I get matches?
You should try to take
it easy for a minute.
I can't.
I need to do something.
Thanks.
I never told you I was claustrophobic.
If I only knew what you told me,
I wouldn't know shit.
Look who's talking.
It's like I can't even
turn my back on you anymore.
It's bad enough I got
Aaron running around
with that skin freak.
Now I gotta worry about
you all half-cocked
every time you go outside.
I'm sorry.
I begged you to talk to me.
I wanna be there for you.
I do.
I don't know what to do anymore.
[SIGHS]
I can't stop thinking about it.
I know I have to, but I can't.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪♪
Oh, God.
I don't want to just kill Alpha.
I want to hurt her.
♪♪
I want to make her regret everything.
I want her to beg for forgiveness,
and then I want to kill her.
If I went through
all the shit that you went through...
I'd probably feel the same way.
♪♪
Unless you tried to stop me.
You gotta quit all this.
You gotta.
People you care about
are starting to get hurt.
♪♪
I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
I know I have to...
I know I have to s...
You gotta not bullshit me.
♪♪
Don't bullshit me.
You gotta promise.
I gotta know we're on the same team.
♪♪
We fight for our future.
We don't fight for revenge.
I promise.
♪♪
Alright.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[WIND WHISTLING]
Skins!
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Let's go.
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
If we don't follow
each other in the dark,
we're gonna get split up.
She's right. We stick together.
At least we know there's a way out now.
Yeah, but where?
I think they went this way.
You see where they went?
Not exactly, but...
I know a road sign when I see one.
♪♪
Hey, come on.
[MATCH STRIKES]
♪♪
NEGAN: Sorry to butt in.
No pun intended.
[ZIPPER ZIPS]
The latrine is at the edge
of the camp for hygiene,
not privacy.
Ah, well, actually, I, um...
just wanted to talk.
About?
Well, I hear we're supposed
to be keeping our eyes peeled
for a spy lurkin' in the woods.
I have an alternate
theory to run by you.
The spy you're looking for?
Right here in your camp.
My people know the enemy have
nothing to offer except lies.
Maybe they do. Maybe they don't.
Believe it or not,
I have been where you are right now.
And if you don't want to
end up where I am right now,
I suggest you zig where I zagged.
You and I... very different.
I had people.
I had a system.
I thought they believed in it,
just like you.
See, the thing is,
you stay king or queen long enough,
with people telling
you all day, every day
that your shit don't stink,
eventually, you start to believe it.
The thing is...
it still stinks.
Who?
Well, based on my own
personal experience,
I'd say look closer to home.
And, no, I am not talkin' about
Frankenstein's Hemorrhoid.
That big dude is
clearly a goose stepper.
But the little one...?
You see, she is close enough to you
that she knows exactly
where that horde was.
But she guards the border,
which means she's close
enough to the enemy
that they could've gotten to her.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
I will not have you sowing paranoia.
If you breathe a word of this to anyone,
- I will take these.
- Aah!
[BODY THUDS]
[GROANS]
♪♪
This is it!
Oh, God.
♪♪
Alright, just give me one minute.
I'll be fine.
♪♪
Or not.
Ooh, boy. [SIGHS]
"You are... are...
O-K."
"You are..."
"You are okay."
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
Oh, man.
Hey.
You all right back there?
Yeah, sure.
I'm just a 6'2" dude
that had trouble fitting
into airplane bathrooms.
[GRUNTS] Why wouldn't I be okay?
[GRUNTS]
Fair enough.
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Alright, I'm out.
Follow my voice.
Come on.
That's it.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Alright.
Come on.
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
I'm good.
♪♪
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Carol?
Carol!
[PANTING]
I'm here.
You hurt?
I'm okay.
Can you see my light?
Yes.
Just follow my light.
[PANTING]
♪♪
I can't.
I can't!
Yes, you can.
Come on.
We're gonna get through this together.
Come on. Come on.
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
♪♪
Go ahead.
I gotcha, I gotcha.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey, guys...
AARON: What is it?
- [CRANK WHIRRING]
- What is it?
Just be quiet for a second.
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
Go, go, go! Go!
Go, go, go!
♪♪
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Jerry, come on!
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
Come on! Come on!
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Jerry!
Come on!
You're almost there!
Guys!
I'm... I'm stuck.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Here... take my hand!
[GRUNTING]
Aah!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
My feet!
My feet! They got my feet!
They're biting my feet!
[GRUNTING]
My feet!
Take your gear off!
Take it off!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Come on.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
Aah!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[WALKER GROWLING]
[PANTING]
You good?
It's okay.
They didn't bite through.
You're good. It's alright. It's okay.
[GRUNTING]
[WALKER GROWLING]
♪♪
Hey.
Look!
- Wait!
- [GASPS]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[BOARDS CRACKING]
Why are we standing
around looking at it?
KELLY: We got to be very careful.
We take out the wrong piece,
this whole thing is gonna collapse.
♪♪
Where's Gamma?
She never made it to the border.
I've sent four scouts to find her.
If there are spies among us,
maybe she's been captured.
Or she is the spy.
You believe she has gone over?
I suspect.
♪♪
I want you to track her down.
Bring her to me.
And if she has betrayed
us, I will kill her.
♪♪
I will deal with her.
And the pack will watch.
♪♪
Alright, find something to dig with.
[GRUNTING]
- Hey, Aaron, can you help me with this?
- Yeah, yeah.
[GEAR CLATTERING]
KELLY: Hey, check this out.
Yo.
Somebody left this crate of dynamite.
Yeah, okay, that's really cool.
But maybe somebody left it there
because it's obviously
insanely dangerous.
That thing's sweatier than I am.
I need you to put it back.
Very carefully.
♪♪
Just... Just...
Want to take a break?
I can rest when... when we get home.
- You in a hurry?
- I just don't wanna hang out here
any longer than I have to.
- Do you?
- No, but...
you barely rested,
haven't eaten anything.
You never stop.
I didn't leave things good with Yumiko.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
Me too.
♪♪
You.
Looks like Mom's mad at me.
♪♪
Keep walkin'.
You know, this feels
like some sort of...
fraternity initiation.
Is that what this is?
Huh?
Am I gonna get my skin suit
and finally get to learn the
secret Whisperer handshake?
Eyes front.
Alright.
You don't wanna talk?
I'm down with that.
We just won't talk.
You know, I...
I'm big enough to admit it, alright?
I...
I am not good with long,
uncomfortable silences.
Stop here.
I said...
eyes front.
Shit.
[SIGHS]
Take off your clothes.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You know what? You
were... You were right.
[SIGHS] We are different.
[SIGHS]
I made myself into a monster,
because that is what the world needed.
[SIGHS]
I built something.
I saved people.
My name... it meant something.
Turn around.
Whoa.
You're a crass man.
I reckoned you might appreciate
a crass reward.
A reward?
For what?
The spy.
Gamma.
It took courage to do what you did.
And I want to express my gratitude
in a way that you will understand.
Wait.
Are you just gonna...
leave that mask on?
Does my true skin disturb you?
Not at all.
Weirdly the opposite.
Wait.
This isn't some sort of, uh,
praying mantis situation, is it?
You cut off my head off afterwards?
Yeah, sorry.
I can't help but notice that
you didn't say no to that.
Ah, you know what?
It's been a long time.
I reckon I will take my chances.
♪♪
Stop... talking.
[CRASHING]
Come on, go.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Just a little more!
[COUGHING]
Where's Carol?
♪♪
Damn it!
[GRUNTING]
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[MATCH STRIKES]
Oh.
Aah!
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
DARYL: Take my hand.
Come on.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
What the hell are you doing?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
We can take out half
her horde from here.
You're gonna get yourself killed.
♪♪
[VOICE BREAKING] She killed my boy.
- [CRYING]
- I know.
But you gotta come back with me.
Please.
Come on.
♪♪
Aah!
- [GASPS]
- [CRASHING]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Come on!
Hey! Move!
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
Hey! Hey!
Come on!
What are you doing?!
♪♪
Come on!
Ohh!
♪♪
We got freaks!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[CRASHING]
[COUGHING]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[RUMBLING]
♪♪
MAGNA: Come on!
- Come on!
- Hurry!
I can't...
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
AARON: Come on!
Come on, guys!
Come on!
♪♪
[WOOD CREAKING]
Give me your hand! I'll pull her up!
Come on!
Give me your hand.
[RUMBLING]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
We've got more skins!
[SCREAMING]
♪♪
[SHOUTS]
Get outta here!
- Jerry!
- Aah!
- Jerry, give me your hand!
♪♪
Jerry, now!
Come on!
♪♪
[EXPLOSION]
[COUGHING]
No!
[CRYING]
♪♪
AARON: Daryl...
Daryl.
♪♪
It'll take us a week to clear this.
[GROANS] Then help me!
[CRYING] No.
We can't!
♪♪
That blast is gonna call
walkers and Whisperers
from a hundred miles from here.
We don't want our backs
pressed against this mountain
when they come.
We can't save them if we're dead.
[SNIFFLES]
Come on.
♪♪
[CRYING]
[VOICE BREAKING]
Go ahead and say it to me.
I deserve it.
Just say it to me.
You were right about everything.
Just say it.
No, please.
You cared about her.
And now she's gone because of me.
Please, just say it!
Please say it!
[CRYING]
Go home.
Tell the others we found the horde.
Where you gonna be?
They got out before us.
There's gotta be another way in.
♪♪
CAROL: No.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --