Previously on "The Walking Dead."
[CRYING] No. Please.
Go home.
Tell the others we found the horde.
Where are you gonna be?
There's got to be another way in.
The spy you're looking for,
right here in your camp.
The little one, you see,
she is close enough to you
that she knows exactly
where that horde was.
I want you to track her down.
Bring her to me.
And if she has betrayed
us, I will kill her.
[FLIES BUZZING]
♪♪
[HATCH DOOR CLANKS]
[MATCH STRIKES]
♪♪
[LANTERN SQUEAKING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[FUSSING]
ROSITA: It's your turn.
GABRIEL: [GROANS]
[YAWNS]
[GRUNTS]
Hi.
Aw. Okay, okay, okay.
[FUSSING CONTINUES]
[CRYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
No!
[GASPS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
GABRIEL: Rosita, do you copy?
♪♪
[MASK SPLATS]
[SIGHS]
I'm the one that knows Aaron.
We know who you are.
♪♪
The people you sent
out, they're in trouble,
trapped in a cave where
Alpha has placed her horde.
Now, they could still be in there
or they might've gotten out.
- I don't know.
- You said the horde was in a field.
It was.
Now it's in a cave.
She moved it.
The whole thing.
Right before they got there.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
I'm just telling you what happened.
I'm not sure you are.
♪♪
I'm trying to help.
Why?
♪♪
[SIGHS]
The baby that they left at Hilltop,
he's my nephew.
♪♪
And I would do anything
to see him again.
Where's the baby's mother?
♪♪
Dead.
If I give you a map,
can you show us where the cave is?
♪♪
Yes.
[GRUNTS]
You're a liar.
The cell.
♪♪
[GROWLING]
[CLANK]
It's from the last one.
The last Whisperer we had in here.
You killed him?
GABRIEL: No.
I did.
ROSITA: It was the one your
people sent to spy on us.
He killed my baby's father two days ago.
[SIGHS]
I don't know anything about that.
Right. Never heard of him.
- I haven't.
- Mm.
I don't... uh... [SIGHS]
It's amazing how much
you say you don't know.
Let me lay it out for you.
You're gonna work
very hard in this room.
You're gonna have to convince us
that you're different
from the ones who lie
and walk with the dead and eat worms.
And what if I can't?
Then you die.
No torture. No games.
No second chances.
You'd be the third one, by the way.
All's I've done is tell you the truth.
GABRIEL: You haven't.
This is not for show.
I am a servant of God.
I've taken many confessions,
and I can tell when people
are holding things back.
ROSITA: Holding things
back is the same as lying.
Outside at the gate,
the story you had about
being the aunt of the baby...
It's not a story.
...it does tug at all
the right heartstrings,
but you're hiding something,
which makes the whole thing a lie.
Ask God if I'm lying.
I've spoken to God.
He told me to hang you.
I, uh...
[VOICE BREAKING] I killed my sister.
♪♪
I killed my sister.
I killed...
♪♪
I killed her for Alpha.
She didn't even have to ask.
I just did it.
♪♪
You believe me now, Father?
Then you should get me a map.
♪♪
[HORDE GROWLING]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTS, COUGHING]
Aah!
Where are they?!
[SCREAMS]
Tell me!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
GABRIEL: So, 14 miles inland here?
Yes.
SCOTT: Any other way in or out?
There are others in the area.
I'm not sure where.
And they'll be guarded.
Did Earl send those new weapon sets?
Yeah. Enough for all of us.
Good. We're gonna need them.
What about the border?
It's gonna be guarded
all the way down to...
It's clear.
It's too long for Alpha to defend.
Most of the patrols
will be near the cave.
♪♪
Take her back to her cell.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
So, two rescue parties.
Rosita and I will take the first...
We don't know if any of this is real.
Don't we?
You said you were sure she wasn't lying.
I am, and she isn't.
♪♪
You all are hesitating
because you're afraid of them, right?
You shouldn't be.
That's why I brought her in here.
- So you could see.
- LAURA: See what?
That they're cowards.
We broke her.
Completely.
And if we can break
her, we can break others.
If you come across one
of them, keep them alive,
start pulling teeth and taking fingers.
Get information, because we now know
the more pain and fear
you pour over them,
the sooner they drop the act,
which is what it is.
♪♪
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[PANTING]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CLINK]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
[CLANKING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[LID CREAKS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
You okay?
You seemed a little
off in the meeting room.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Look, why don't you stay here
and look over the
defenses at the gate?
Smart thing would be
having me out there.
I don't think it is.
I'm not gonna freeze. I'm good.
But you need to worry about your shit.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Means you're erratic.
Name one thing I've done
that's been erratic.
"Cut off their fingers.
Pull out their teeth."
You're itching for a fight.
So what if I am?
[SIGHS]
♪♪
I can feel that Coco is...
...wondering where he is.
♪♪
And I don't want her...
I know.
♪♪
Right. I'll see you out there.
- You don't have to...
- I'll see you out there.
♪♪
JUDITH: I'll make it really fast.
I'll be right back.
What's your name?
Nobody's asked me since I got here.
It's Mary.
What were you like
before the Whisperers?
I'm from Santa Monica.
That was in California.
My parents' names were John and Alice.
I went to school and...
♪♪
I don't remember.
What do you mean?
♪♪
Alpha has a way of, um...
making you forget.
You really don't remember anything?
♪♪
There are echoes left, feelings.
I was ordinary.
That much I know.
And when it all went down,
my sister and I kept
making bad decisions.
We needed someone to make them for us,
and then we met Alpha.
♪♪
You met the wrong person first.
If you'd met my mom or my dad,
you wouldn't be in that cell.
♪♪
You don't look like a monster to me.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
ROSITA: Judith.
♪♪
We're about to go on lockdown.
You should get inside.
♪♪
Bye.
[SHOTGUN CLANKING]
♪♪
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
Aah!
[PANTING]
♪♪
- How many can you see in the herd?
- MAN: 100 at least.
It's hard to tell, but it looks like
there are Whisperers in it.
It's on its way. What should we...
Echo post, say again. We lost you.
- [STATIC]
- Echo post, respond.
[STATIC]
That watch tower's two miles away.
We can't let this next
wave bunch up at the gate
the way the last one did.
Why would they send a herd now?
We have a defector
giving us information.
They're trying to stop
us before we act on it.
We're gonna have to split up
if we want to cover both gates.
SCOTT: That means less people out there.
We don't have a choice.
Show of hands...
how many people here
have been on gate duty?
MAN: I have.
Alright, how many do we need?
Need or want?
Six, plus you, me, Rosita, and Gabe.
Alright, you seven,
you're gonna be on the main gate.
Hold on. New plan.
Rosita and Laura,
stay back on gate security
with a skeleton crew.
You and I take a squad
out to the outpost,
break up the herd, and
then move on to the cave.
- Good?
- Yeah.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Gonna grab that.
I didn't want... I'm not
trying to speak for you.
No, it's fine. I don't trust
myself out there anyway.
Could get us both killed,
and then Coco would...
It's okay.
I'm having nightmares about them.
Dreams they're killing me.
SCOTT: We're good to go.
♪♪
I'll see you soon.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
♪♪
All I'm saying is we
could make it into a game.
I kill more skins than you,
you take my watch duties for a month.
I don't wanna mess
around out there, man.
Aw. [CHUCKLES] What, are you scared?
Remember Lydia?
My friends and I beat
the shit out of her.
She barely put up a fight.
I'm telling you, man, one on one,
the Whisperers are a joke.
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS, LAUGHTER]
[GRUNTS, CLATTER]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
♪♪
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
MAN: This don't make sense.
What the hell happened?
We'll go back the way we came.
You don't see anything coming?
No, nothing.
No sign of a herd.
No walkers.
What the hell is going on?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪♪
[GROWLING]
They were forced to call.
Must've held the knife to her throat
to make him call us and lie.
Why?
Most of us are out here.
There's hardly anybody...
back home.
[GROWLING]
♪♪
Walkers!
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪♪
They're here.
Check Morgan Street. Come with me.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNT, BODY THUDS]
This place... it isn't
what she said it was.
She lied.
♪♪
These are not your people.
But she lied.
She is your Alpha.
♪♪
You think you're still alive.
You were dead the moment you came to us.
♪♪
Step towards me.
Why?
She wants you.
She said your death would be painless.
If you fight, it will not be.
Step towards me.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
All she wants is me in pain.
♪♪
You're lying for her.
Step towards me.
♪♪
I am not afraid of you.
Yes, you are.
♪♪
Get help.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪
Help!
JUDITH: In here.
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOORKNOB RATTLES]
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪
[DOORKNOB CLICKS, DOOR CREAKS]
Okay, go, go. Fast, fast.
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS IN DISTANCE, CLOSES]
Aah!
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Hey!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[ITEMS CLATTERING]
♪♪
[COUGHING]
MARY: Stop!
♪♪
[PANTING]
Alpha wants me alive.
♪♪
Step towards me.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
You will fall.
You will rise.
You will walk with your sister again.
♪♪
[GUN COCKS]
No, I wasn't...
I-I didn't...
I didn't betray you.
I just... I-I drew him out
here because he was gonna...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Please.
♪♪
I'm telling the truth.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Can you see beyond the darkness
into the light?
No.
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
I'm tingling with joy...
as I see the ones who broke me...
all around us, standing there.
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
Thank you.
Thank you for making me strong.
Pain made me.
Pain made you.
Pain made my Lydia.
You lost her.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You drove her away.
'Cause you didn't love her.
What did you say?
[WHEEZING]
What did you say, boy?
I can't hear you.
I'm all ears.
♪♪
Are you really here?
[VOICE BREAKING] Yes, Mama.
Don't call me that.
You know better.
♪♪
You came home.
I am you, and you are me.
♪♪
[CRYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪ Lydia ♪
♪ Oh, Lydia ♪
♪ Say, have you met Lydia ♪
♪ Lydia the tattooed lady ♪
♪ She has eyes ♪
♪ That folks adore so ♪
♪ And a torso ♪
♪ Even more so ♪
♪ Lydia ♪
♪ Oh, Lydia ♪
♪♪
Mama, I...
- Oh, Lydia.
- Mama.
Lydia, baby, push.
- [CRYING] Mama.
- Push.
- I...
You're ready, baby.
I made sure you're ready.
[CRYING]
♪♪
They're waiting for you to lead.
They're waiting.
♪♪
I'm not here for them.
I'm not here for you.
♪♪
They're human.
Not perfect.
Just human.
♪♪
It's all I ever wanted.
It's what you never gave me.
♪♪
I need you.
I want you to...
stay.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪♪
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[WINCING, EXHALING SHARPLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
_
[LAUGHS]
♪♪
This was Dante.
Scouts in the tunnels are saying
the Whisperers sealed
whole sections off.
Aaron.
♪♪
You're alright.
Yeah. We, uh...
♪♪
What happened?
Aaron, where are the others?
We got separated.
Most of us got out.
Most of you?
♪♪
Not everyone.
You sure you don't want her with you?
It's a short trip.
No, I'll be back as soon as
the doctor at Hilltop clears me.
Besides, they could still be out there.
I want her safe, and safe is with you.
Okay.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Room for three more!
[GRUNTS]
I'm Rosita.
Mary.
I know.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[HORSES WHINNY]
Easy, easy.
DARYL: [BREATHING HEAVILY]
How long I been asleep for?
Most of the day.
And you were just out here?
Yeah.
Just watching you.
Watching them.
Deciding.
Deciding what?
Did you kill her?
If it was your father, could you have?
♪♪
I'm no longer weak.
I'm stronger than ever.
Our horde will butcher and consume them.
Screams will be song to me.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪♪
We bathe in blood.
We are free.
We love no one.
We fear nothing.
We are free.
This is the end of the world.
Now is the end of the world.
We are the end of the world.