[English subtitles are available]
[Oh My Lord]
[Episode 15]
Once upon a time,
there was a little wild cat
who was always alone.
In order not to get bullied by others,
it sharpened
its claws.
Everyone was afraid of it.
But one day,
a girl appeared.
Although the cat was not easy to deal with,
the girl
treated it well.
She gave it the sweetest watermelon,
warm clothes to wear,
and showed it the brightest stars.
Her kindness
made the small cat
happy for the first time.
Gradually,
the little cat
got used to being patted
and hugged.
But one day,
it woke up
and the girl had disappeared.
She stole its heart.
It didn't know why.
But it knew
that without the girl,
its life
would be colorless.
So it looked for her.
Kept looking and looking.
It crossed the forest
and kept looking for her.
Kept looking and looking.
It crossed the hill,
and kept looking and looking for her.
[River]
It crossed the river.
Finally,
it found the little girl.
It told itself
this time,
no matter what,
it would never let her leave.
You stole my heart,
how could you leave me alone?
If this
can save your life,
I'm willing
to give your heart back.
But I have fallen in love with you.
From now on,
my heart will only beat for you.
Do you remember our show for Madam De?
As long as we love each other,
life can mean death,
and death can mean life.
I would rather be dead
if you left me.
But Jiang Bihan...
So what if she knows?
I wouldn't be afraid even if I had to
break my bones and ruin my reputation.
Besides, she has left Bai's Mansion.
She won't bother us.
Youyou.
Since the moment I stopped being Su Wen,
my life has been full of darkness.
But you...
lit up my world.
Would you give me all of you?
No matter what hardships we encounter,
I will protect you
and our family.
Trust me.
I am the famous Lord Qiansui.
Everything can be figured out.
My lord,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
That's it?
You have been
with those pretty boys these days.
I felt really sad.
Stop talking.
Weren't you in the room with Jiang Bihan?
You came back to see me?
If it's not you,
I won't lose control
even if I lose my life.
Does it hurt?
It hurts here.
Lord.
Wait.
Come on. One, two, three.
Welcome home, wish you a long and happy marriage.
Stop!
Let's go, there are too many people.
[Happy Times]
I think I got it right this time.
Lord looks really happy.
Tiao, why are you crying?
Retreat.
Don't cry.
If Lord Bai sees this,
I will get punished again.
What's wrong?
Miss
bought...
She bought a yard in the northern city
and a house in the southern city,
and went back to the shop in the eastern city.
She...
What's your point?
It was really hard for her
to be this happy.
Yes.
I'm so happy.
Tiao.
Actually, this is a good thing.
You…
Wipe,
wipe your tears.
But don't blow your nose.
Alright.
I'll wash it for you, OK?
It's fine, don't worry.
I didn't
give you a perfect wedding before.
From now on,
I will pay you back with my life.
Well...
My lord, you can't go back on your words.
Are you still going to call me "my lord?"
My love.
From now on,
your home
will be by my side.
♫ Moonlight falls on your red lips ♫
♫ The autumn wind brings fragrance ♫
♫ Your beautiful hair is reflected in the pond. Memories fade ♫
♫ If the night breeze makes a difference ♫
♫ In the way you look back ♫
♫ Our fates are intertwined ♫
♫ We can't turn back ♫
♫ The handsome boy puts on a decent suit ♫
♫ Running at full speed on horseback ♫
♫ Sadness and happiness can't be seen ♫
♫ I'll hide all my worries ♫
Give me a hug.
♫ I'll be innocent all my life ♫
♫ And enjoy the colorful world ♫
♫ Together with you ♫
♫ I can wait for thousands of years ♫
♫ Love fills my heart ♫
♫ Time can't tell how bad I miss you ♫
♫ For thousands of years ♫
When you get drunk,
♫ I miss you in the mortal world ♫
you're really cute.
♫ I want to be with you ♫
I'm not only cute...
♫ I can wait for thousands of years ♫
♫ Until the end of the day ♫
♫ We've been in love for years ♫
Gu Tianhe!
Call the imperial physician.
My lord,
I'm just on my period.
Come on. You will feel better after you drink it.
Hurry up. It's getting cold.
It's too bitter.
Then,
do you want me to feed you?
I envy you.
In the next life,
I also want to be a male.
OK.
I'll be your wife in the next life.
And I will
suffer this pain instead of you.
Miss Chen is usually very active.
Why did she suddenly get sick
after she got married?
Tiao,
do you know what's going on?
Me?
How would I know?
I've never been married.
Being married.
Not being married.
Got it.
Here.
Does it still hurt?
Much better.
But
if I eat something sweet,
I think I'll feel much better.
Gu Tianhe!
I got you, lord!
You...
What?
What did you get?
Cakes, snacks, melons, and preserved fruits.
Lord instructed us
on the food you like.
We have them all in the kitchen.
And
iced watermelon.
Who asked you to prepare cold food?
Lord, I
made a mistake again?
Go.
You are here eating dog food
and we're going to get punished.
Tiao.
What are you doing?
Get out of the way.
I asked the best physician in the southern city.
I also went to the eastern city to buy the best cinnamon from the west.
Yes.
And I...
You wouldn't understand even if I told you.
Anyway, this sweet soup
will relieve her pain.
Get out of the way.
Wait.
Well, lord and madam
are busy at the moment.
What are they doing at this critical moment?
Anyway,
if you don't want
to go to the old place to be punished,
don't go in.
Well,
you're going to get punished again?
Can I go and have a look?
General Gu,
are you ready?
Come on.
[Old Place]
Lord, I won't do it again!
What's wrong?
What's so funny?
Thank you, Your Royal Highness,
for bringing the Fortune Shop so many instruments.
I've seen the Fortune Shop
to get on the right track.
So this is my gift.
Youyou,
I have another gift for you.
What's this?
This is my improved friendship cake.
Give it a try.
Your Royal Highness...
From now on,
we are just good friends who make pastries together.
Not bad.
My lord!
What a pity.
You can't eat this anymore.
Does that mean that you're leaving?
I'll travel to all cities and learn to make new pastries.
It's what I've always wished for.
I think
it's time to fulfill my dream.
There are seven cities
near Fuxian City.
They have all types of delicacies and customs.
I believe Your Royal Highness
will get a lot from these trips.
See you.
Although I sent Youyou by your side this time,
don't get too excited.
If you dare to do anything bad to her,
even if I'm far away,
I will take her away from you immediately.
Don't worry.
That won't be necessary.
[Fortune Shop]
I'm leaving.
When I come back from my study,
I'll treat you to a good meal.
[Fortune Shop]
Goodbye.
My lord!
Youyou, no!
What's wrong?
My lord.
Did you have a nightmare?
Youyou.
That day by the river,
you told me you would never leave me again.
And you wouldn't leave no matter what.
Is that right?
Yes.
I'm stuck with you.
You won't get rid of me
for the rest of our lives.
My lord.
In the past,
you've always protected me.
Then let me protect you
in your dreams.
If you encounter something bad
in your dreams,
just think
that I am still by your side
and everything will be fine.
By the way,
the 15th is coming up soon.
It so happens that you are on vacation.
How about
we go to the temple to pray?
OK.
[Bai's Mansion]
Oh, Tiao.
Have you brought the candles?
Lord.
Yes.
You have never believed
in God or Buddha.
I believe in her.
By the way, Madam.
Why are you suddenly going to the Tanmen temple?
Lord has been working so hard recently.
I want to go
so that he can take a break.
Give me the bag.
[Bai's Mansion]
I haven't left the city for a long time.
This landscape is so beautiful.
We depart at 7:00 AM.
We have lunch at 11:00 AM.
We worship Buddha at 3:00 PM.
We go to sleep at 9:00 PM.
Why can't we sleep together?
My lord,
it's a Buddhist temple.
It's inappropriate for men and women to share a room.
But the castellan made us husband and wife.
It's still inappropriate.
We're going to pray for blessings.
Only when we put our whole hearts into it
will our wishes come true.
But
what if I had a nightmare tonight?
I have prepared
some soothing incenses for you.
Tanmen temple is really quiet.
You will sleep great.
My lord,
behave yourself.
No.
Tiao.
Don't look at what you shouldn't look at.
Yah!
[Tanmen temple]
My lord,
the supervisor in the temple
has arranged our rooms.
You should go to bed early tonight
and have a good sleep.
OK.
So cute.
My lord.
What's wrong?
Lord,
is there anything wrong?
Something feels strange.
I feel like I've been here before.
And that man,
I think I've seen him before.
I'll go check it out.
Don't act rashly.
Be careful tonight.
Don't worry.
I will do my best to protect you
and your wife.
Madam, don't worry.
I will protect you
against all dangers.
Tiao.
Is it because you've been spending too much time with General Gu lately?
You talk like him.
No way.
Let's go inside.
Madam, wait for me.
[Tanmen temple]
Buddha,
I, Chen Youyou,
live in Bai's Mansion in the south of Fuxian City.
I came to pay my respects.
I sincerely pray
so that Buddha can bless my husband,
Bai Li.
He helps the castellan uphold justice.
He does good deeds and helps people.
He's a good person.
He's also really nice to me.
For a long time,
he endured a hard life
full of secrets.
Finally he can settle down,
but is still suffering from nightmares.
Buddha,
please protect him
from nightmares.
Or...
Let me share his pain.
I'm willing to share his burden.
I just hope
he lives a happy and peaceful life.
My lord.
How come you're here?
I came to pay my respects.
I'll join you.
Buddha,
she said she would share the burden with me,
please don't take it seriously.
As she said,
for so many years,
I've been living in the darkness.
She is the only light in my life.
I just hope
she'll be by my side
and enjoy a healthy and happy life.
If there is any pain or suffering,
I will bear it all.
My lord,
what wishes are you making?
It takes so long.
Behave yourself
in front of Buddha.
This...
Wait for me here. I'll be back soon.
My lord.
My lord!
Youyou!
Who are you?
You're in a high position, but you're not doing your job.
You're disloyal.
You indulge in childish love and forgot your roots.
This is impious.
You broke your promise and forgot your original intention.
This is unrighteous.
Do you acknowledge your mistake?
Master.