same food
Diners have different moods
taste will be different
I think it's because the cooks don't care
How can you, Your Highness
How dare she
Free at kisskh.me
Your Highness
It's New Year's Eve
The food bureau is really busy
Negligence is inevitable
If you are not satisfied with Yao girl's craftsmanship
The slaves will go to Shangshan Supervisor for you
Pick another cook
Your Highness
Han Wang, the foreign minister of Qianqing Palace, can't afford to kneel
The prince can't persuade
I had to kneel with him
Princess, please come and see
Can you persuade you to come back?
what do you say
do what you do
second uncle
You've been kneeling here for over two hours
Kneel down like this
Can the body eat it?
Yes
I'm not afraid
when the army is fighting
I can go three days and three nights without eating
second uncle
are you all right
you
come
The second uncle knelt down for a long time and passed out
hurry to the hospital
you
quick
you you you
Dad is here
I do not
do it yourself
father
His Royal Highness
Your Highness is really brotherly
Grandpa Huang will be in tears when he sees it
Make sure all the gas is gone
His Majesty
The medicinal properties of Lingji Palace are hot
Very easy to phlegm and dyspnea
I can't take it anymore
roll
Meng Shang food
continue
Yuan Shaoqing's face-to-face technique
Highly trusted by His Majesty
Today he persuaded His Majesty to use less talisman
As a result, His Majesty was furious
The two servants who followed the persuasion did not say anything
And also expelled Mr. Yuan
Your Majesty has been having nightmares recently
The dragon body is not as big as before
I'm afraid there will be no peace in the palace
command the crowd
be careful
Yes
Therefore, the good-nurtured
Hunger before eating
don't eat enough
thirsty to drink
Do not drink too much
less appetite
not wanting to stop
Yam noodles
make up for deficiency
good energy
Six pounds of white noodles
ten white chickens
ginger juice
what are you thinking
You adult
From now on, you don't have to go to the pharmacy every day to borrow books
Adult favor
The slave's heart took it
how
As long as a book passes through my hand
feel dirty?
adults misunderstood
The slave has seen this volume
It's all in my heart, don't look at it again
I do not believe
Jujube Ginger Soup
Eat and drink with the spleen and stomach
Broken gas soup
Treat Yuanzang's Weakness
abdominal pain chest tightness
cinnamon pulp
Dehumidify and drink smoothly
quench thirst
adults walk slowly
do not send
pantry powerhouse
If you have nothing else to do
please don't trespass
today is laba
Free at kisskh.me
also my birthday
What about my longevity noodles?
Today, His Majesty bestowed the ministers Laba noodles
by convention
It was prepared by Guanglu Temple
I don't want laba noodles
is my longevity noodles
Is it tasty
tasty
Daughter
you also have a bite
mother doesn't eat
eat it
Doesn't look good
Zijin
what are you doing
don't listen to his nonsense
I haven't done anything bad lately
It's all slander
Misunderstood
Today is your birthday
He just wants a bowl of longevity noodles
This is Shang Food Bureau
Not Guanglu Temple
Not Shang Shan Supervisor
Meals not provided for guards on duty
be quiet
The King of Hell is knocking on the door
Why don't you hurry and hide away
You are too long
do not talk
It's over if you send it away
you give me an egg
Are you afraid that he can't rely on you?
When I was a kid on my birthday
That's what my mother did for me
Then if I have a birthday
you have to do it for me too
Then I'll lay two eggs for you
How
almost
Everyone, hurry up
Is this the plum for serving?
words of returning adults
It's for making plum porridge
Plum can also make porridge
Plum blossom clears heat and promotes body fluid
Can be used for soup and porridge
What other orders do you have, Mr.
Why is everyone in the food bureau
are so afraid of me
I said what happened last time
just a misunderstanding
I sincerely apologize
You adult
You stepped on my plum branch
Come
come over
Give
get me one
be careful
Be careful it's hot
tasty
Yuehua hasn't come back yet?
Yuehua
correct
none of you
Prepare Longevity Noodles for Mr. Yu
no no no no no
no
I was busy preparing laba porridge yesterday
I forgot to tell you
If you come today
try to avoid him
why
since his tenure
Laba Festival will come to the restaurant on this day
one who cooks for him
Death or injury within three months
very evil
Everyone in the Shangshan Supervisor said it.
Laba Festival Tour Hell
dodge anyway
Then why did you say it now?
how
You wouldn't have prepared meals for him already, would you?
After Laba is the New Year
be careful
i am not afraid of you
not afraid of you
I am the real dragon
grandfather
it's me
Your Majesty is still Imperial Physician Xuan Sheng.
Need not
i am healthy
No need to declare imperial doctor
Need not
grandfather
Today is Laba Festival
child
you have grown up
From now on, this heavy burden will fall on your shoulders
don't worry grandpa
And my father is there
nothing like me
don't let me down
grandfather
When did your grandson let you down?
do that thing
don't let anyone know
do you understand
Yes
go
prince
The lord has something important to report
News from the Prince's Palace
Plum can also make porridge
Plum blossom clears heat and promotes body fluid
Can be used for soup and porridge
emperor
Pepsi Box
Yao girl
His Royal Highness admiring plums in Qiongyuan
please take a trip
Deliver the food box in person
Yes
Yao girl is here
then you wait here for a while
I'm going to inform you
Your Highness
You hear that my piano sound can be improved
Your Highness, what do you see?
Wu Cairen forgives his sins
The servant made a mistake
stained your clothes
It's okay, it's okay
I'll go back and get another one.
you rest
I'll be back in a while
Your Highness, the people from the Food Bureau are here
Yes
Your maidservant, please go now
Miss Yao, let's go
Your Highness
let you wait
can't you speak
Are you going to freeze to death
make me feel guilty
I tell you
even if you freeze to death
I won't feel bad
Your Highness
the dish is cold
The slaves go back and redo
Don't get angry
it's too cold
Vegetables will be cold
Your Highness, rest your anger
maid, go back
Yao Zijin
Your Highness without orders
The slave is really going back
Okay, then I'll take you out
See if you can still be a slave
to treat the master
Your Highness
slave yesterday
He has been officially promoted to the head chef of Shang Food Bureau.
A humble palm meal
Is it really what you asked for?
Lady Wang
Known for his moral knowledge
The sage wants to recruit a concubine
Concubine Quan even invited her to accompany her
so glorious
Free at kisskh.me
She also politely declined
insist on returning home
Not only did the saint not force her
Still give a lot of money on the day of returning home
Slaves dare not compare themselves to wise men
But His Royal Highness always takes the saint as an example
The Holy One is so broad-minded
Your Highness is also a young man
How can you force a maid?
You said the word "heart" with your own mouth
Did you forget it all?
how to forget
How dare you forget
I just wish your heart was like mine
will live up to love
But the heart of the king
do you really know me
Even if the slaves are humble
I dare not give my heart
you stop
Chen Wu
take her back
Yes
to get the twenty rods
Your Highness, your servant is wronged
It's really snowing
How wrong is the slave?
The slave is to vent your anger
forty
show us
i want to see too i want to see too
very nice
That's awesome, yeah
so much
see what dishes
Let me see
Ziping
It's so cold outside
It's freezing
don't you bring an umbrella
I've been told
you are so weak
Why are you still running around?
it's okay no problem
much better
What's up
Look at our specialty dish
Just deal with him
Yeah, definitely beat them
what happened to them
I heard that every New Year's Eve banquet
The Shang Food Bureau and the Shang Shan Supervisor have to compete
winner
Get the right to enter the imperial meal next year
But this year's dishes for the opponent to challenge
She heard it all
strange to say
Supervisor of Shang Shan is trying to surpass Shang Food Bureau
How can you expose your food list?
where did she come from
I'll see what's in the back
It's not that Caozhou suffered.
The peony that arrived in Beijing after the Mid-Autumn Festival
Are they all from Henan?
tell them early
Don't send peonies again this year
But the florists heard
The empress in the palace is for disaster relief
Even donated his own hairpin jewelry.
I personally picked the best flower seeds and sent them
The palace moved them into the warm cave
It's been a while
How to be grateful for the little help
Makes me feel very sad
when my mother was there
In winter, I am afraid that the heavy snow will overwhelm the houses
When the heat is hot, I worry that the sun will burn the crops
Don't worry when you leave
Thinking about the wives and children of soldiers who died in the fight against the rebellion
Ask the father to give them rewards and pensions
This is the true virtue of women
Now we're in the harem
do my best
Not to betray her kind heart
princess
You imitate Queen Renxiao everywhere
I really take my mother's world as my responsibility.
Concubine Guo, please be careful
If this is the case, spread the word
How do you call yourself a princess
Founding Heroes
You have such an immoral virtue
unscrupulous woman
I'm not afraid of losing the reputation of the Guo family.
The dignified mansion of the Han Dynasty
To be jealous
Dishonorable
how
Are you worthy of talking about women's virtue?
Concubine Zhuang
This Qiongyuan is very windy
I feel dizzy after enjoying the flowers for a while
Pardon my apologies
one step ahead
Second sister-in-law, don't care about her
She's a notorious scumbag
it's important that you take care of yourself
After all, this peony is not a festival thing
It's not good in the warm house
I see that the plum blossoms in front of me are blooming very well
let's go see
Concubine Guo is too domineering
Father is always humble and kind
How could she be so lawless
Concubine Guo is his father's favorite concubine
also our elders
How can the younger generation discuss the gains and losses of the elders?
Look at this little talk
I'm so pissed
Wu Cairen
This is the holy year
Specially prepared for the queen
What about the best peony?
Miao Xian
I'm coming
let's go
The fish you sent
fish scales dull
The scales have fallen off
And this shrimp
Shrimp heads and tails have loosened
Shrimp shells are black
And it feels smooth and sticky
It's not like you said you just died
these foods
You dare to send it to the palace
how did you check
Si Shan relieves his anger
Today, His Majesty bestows a banquet on the ministers
Guanglu Temple is busy up and down
Perhaps it was a momentary negligence
Let's talk about this fish and shrimp delivery
Long Trip
Inevitably
Food is to be eaten
The taste can be masked by heavy oil and heavy salt
But is the food fresh?
How is the quality
can you deceive yourself
with this stale food
Not only will it damage the body of the eater
It will also destroy the conscience of the cook
Heart is corrupted
What qualifications do you have?
Return all these ingredients to me
Yes
move quickly
Meng Shang food
The ingredients used in the palace are all carefully selected
Such a mistake happened today
It is nothing more than the fact that Guanglu Temple favors Supervisor Shangshan
deliberately let us lose
It's okay to make things difficult on weekdays
Now that he has used such a despicable method
move them all up
Adult Hideaki
I have plans
These are the ingredients I have stocked up in advance
Check it out, don't go wrong
Yes
go up and bite
bite it
bite bite bite
bite
Free at kisskh.me
Go on, touch its eyes
bite it
yes yes yes you throw it
you bite it
Bite it, get on it, get on it
bite it
yes
Kaijou
bite
bite it
good right right
That's it
bite, bite
bite it
Your Highness
don't you want to watch a cockfight?
up up up
everything is ready
one big one small
Which do you think will win?
small
Then this time
The slave dared to gamble with His Royal Highness
I think big wins
You take your men to receive the twenty rods
Your Highness
yes yes bite it
unsatisfactory thing
just bite
up up up
go on
good bite
I lost my money and wasted my money
small wins
Su girl
what's the matter with you
Sir Siqing asked me to send me a new food list
Meng Shangshi personally checked this food list
just add six more dishes
I don't know what's wrong
no
we'll get it done
Ojizen
you see
But here it can be made thinner
Okay
Su girl
Shangshan Supervisor adjusted the food list
The first one is still a double shot
Then we still use green onions to burn sea cucumbers
last course
It is the three things of Fushouquan
Fu Shou Quan Three Events brings together abalone and sea cucumber
Fish lips and other ingredients
Three things about Fushouquan with authentic taste
It takes about ten hours to boil the thick soup
People just come prepared
I want to discredit the Shangshi Bureau
Unprepared
Shang Food Bureau is disgraced
what coke do you have
The order of serving is also important
Three things about Fushouquan once eaten
The next dishes are tasteless
last course
Originally Zijin
Don't waste time
Let's get started
Yes
adult
come with me
New Year's Eve banquet in Qianqing Palace tonight
The humble office bears the responsibility of guarding the palace
Don't dare to leave the office easily
The security guards of the palace are temporarily handed over to Liu Yanshi
You and I have other business
let's go
Let Grandpa Huang drink less wine tonight
emperor
Your Royal Highness advises you to drink less
Why don't you eat it
Hidden set
The scallion grilled sea cucumber
His Majesty just glanced at
never touched again
I said earlier that this year's sea cucumbers are not in good condition
I want you to change ginseng
you don't listen
The second-class ingredients are naturally inferior in taste
Where can you get sea cucumber from black ginseng?
Is Meng Shangshi very angry?
go explore
Yes
quick
Then prepare for the next
let's go
A pot of umami
Can you hold back the three things of Fushouquan?
Steamed sea cucumber and fish maw are hard to resist
Thick soup that has been boiled for more than ten hours
What's more, it's too late now
That
what about mutton?
That doesn't work either, that doesn't work either
Is that so
Losing the game
let me think again
Zijin
what are you looking for
it's interesting
Don't underestimate this dish
It's just the work of removing the bones without hurting the flesh
just fine
grandfather
This pigeon meat was steamed very badly
And the soup is very nourishing
you try
Meng Shang Food has given up
This clear soup of cabbage is not really clear soup
There should be
Free at kisskh.me
Duck Chicken Ham
as His Highness said
It is a meal specially prepared for the Prince by the Food Bureau
There is a folk saying
No ham is not beautiful, no chicken is not fresh
No duck, no fragrant, no elbow, no thick
That's right
is a connoisseur