♪You crossed the sea of ​​stars
and came with light♪
♪My heart is like the dust, and I
couldn't bear to stain the hemline♪
♪To love in a different way,
the fireworks are in the stars' good graces♪
♪I turn around and realize that
my heart is empty ♪
♪I miss the overflowing galaxy
surging into the sea♪
♪Even the fireworks desire
to give the stars a future♪
♪As long as you are around♪
♪Even the fireworks fear to bloom♪
♪Looking at you,
the light in your eyes dimmed♪
♪I laughed at myself
and that I deserve it ♪
♪My heart skips a beat, but I'm afraid
I'm not worthy of the future that you desire♪
=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 9=
Let's order more dishes.
If we can't finish them,
just pack some for So Panicky.
I want to try
some of the dishes.
Jingjing.
I need your help.
For what?
I bumped into
my professor and his wife.
They are waiting at the entrance
and there are
more than ten customers ahead of them.
So,
can we
let them take this room?
I'll bring you to somewhere else.
I don't mind
but why can't we
invite them over?
You don't mind?
Why would I?
I'll bring them over.
Here, sir, madam.
Hello.
This is my high school classmate,
Qiao Jingjing.
Jingjing,
this is my professor, Mr. Zhang,
and his wife, Mrs. Wang.
Hi, Mr. Zhang.
Hi, Mrs. Wang.
Hello.
Come, have a seat.
Here.
You can put this here.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Yu,
when did you find
such a beautiful
high school friend?
I feel like
I've seen you somewhere.
Is today your birthday, Mrs. Wang?
No.
Today is actually
our
wedding anniversary.
We will have dinner here
every year to celebrate it.
We actually
booked a table
but for some reason,
they couldn't
find
the record.
They must have a lot of customers.
Mr. Zhang,
if today is your
wedding anniversary,
then we...
It's no bother!
You know very well that
both of us
like companies.
Having a meal
with you two,
one of which is a pretty girl,
it can't possibly be better
than this, can it?
Okay.
I'll order food then.
No need.
We are its patrons for several decades.
I know very well which dish is the best.
Just enjoy
the free meal today.
You take their room first.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Ready to order?
Yes.
For the cold dish,
one smoked fish,
drunken chicken,
candied lotus root,
and the Four-Treasures-In-Huadiao-Wine.
That's all.
As for the hot dish,
red braised pork belly is a must-have.
Then, one stir-fried prawn.
And then...
Mr. Zhang,
wouldn't it be too oily?
We should have something light.
This is a rare occasion.
Also,
you guys are still young.
Sautéed peas.
Fish noodle.
Those will do.
Okay.
You're staying in Shanghai?
No travel plan?
Yes,
I have some business here.
I was looking for you.
Yu Tu,
I have dealt with
your problem.
I know that
Guan Zai and you
have reached a bottleneck
in the model research project.
The school
has always played safe.
You have to understand that
that's how
we survive thus far.
Safety
is the most important part.
More redundancies are always good
because
the stake is too high.
However,
the time has changed.
Our nation has become stronger
so we need to change our mindset too.
We ought to encourage the young
to innovate.
I can understand why you suddenly said
you wanted to quit.
That's why
I gave you a break.
Let you take your mind off.
During this month,
I was busy as well.
I discussed
with Mr. Hu many times.
The school's attitude
has now softened.
Your project represents the future.
The higher-up
have their eyes on Guan Zai and you,
the future leaders.
We don't want you
to follow the old mindset,
and refuse to change.
Your break is almost over.
When you return,
revise
the proposal
with Guan Zai
and try to get
the school's support.
Did you hear me?
You still wish to quit?
Let's not talk about business.
Relax.
Come.
Let him speak.
Do you have other reasons?
Mr. Zhang,
I left
for money.
I understand.
Many people
have left over the years.
I can sympathize
with them.
I'm just a bit disappointed.
Yu Tu,
you really let me down.
You're my proudest student.
I thought...
Let's not talk about how my generation
started everything from zero.
Look at your colleague,
Guan Zai.
He gave up his high-paying job
and came back from the US.
I thought
you're like him,
that
you have your own belief.
Yu Tu gave up
his high-paying job too.
Yu Tu and his colleague
are talented people.
They deserve the best.
But
asking them to do what they are told
for the sake of their dream,
isn't this...
isn't this guilt-tripping?
Jingjing!
Sorry.
I apologize,
Mr. Zhang.
We should leave now.
Enjoy your anniversary dinner.
You're
the biggest benefactor
of our current system,
so you shouldn't
say those things to my professor.
What do you mean?
If I'm not Qiao Jingjing,
if I'm not a celebrity,
I'll be able to say it?
I just wanted to defend you.
I want you to be
an aerospace engineer
more than anyone else.
Why?
Jingjing.
Mr. Yu.
Why are you guys out here?
Can you
delete the photo you took just now?
Thank you.
(I'm sorry.)
(Don't take what
Mr. Zhang said to heart.)
(He was just a bit upset.)
(We respect your decision.)
(Also, don't be mad at your friend.)
(What she said was true.)
(Thanks, Mrs. Wang.)
(Qiao Jingjing. Sorry.)
(Qiao Jingjing. But you're the rabbit
who has seen the most stars.)
(Good luck, Rabbit God!)
(Thanks. You should sleep now.)
(Let's start a ranking match tomorrow.)
(Goodnight)
(I'll leave then. Wait for my return.)
(Okay.)
(Sorry.)
(Northwest Satellite Control Center)
(Data Transfer Subsystem,
Satellite JX-1)
(Treatment Value)
What's happening?
Why haven't we received
the telemetry signal?
(Data Transfer Subsystem,
Satellite JX-1)
(Unknown ID)
Yu Tu,
Satellite JX
has some emergency issue.
The attitude is out of control.
I don't care where you are.
Your break is terminated
and get to
Northwest Satellite Control Center
immediately.
The boot.
What happened?
Mr. Hu summoned you
with one phone call?
I grabbed some documents
from the institute
and took the last flight
to Xi'an.
Why are you here?
I flew over from Beijing.
I just arrived.
Mr. Hu said you'd be here
so I was waiting for you.
What exactly happened?
They didn't tell me anything.
Let's go in first.
Are you two the staff from Base 158?
ID, please.
These are your passes.
Follow me.
Okay.
Here.
JX was working properly.
But last night,
after it finished its first rotation,
the ground station did not receive
any telemetry signal.
The center
informed us
straight away.
Fixed channels transmission
from the ground station,
RF module from the transponder,
issuing commands to the back-up.
They did it thrice
but they still couldn't
receive the telemetry signal
from the satellite.
MIA straight away?
No response even from the backup?
Yes.
The backup
transponder on Satellite JX
is heterogeneous.
The possibility of a simultaneous
error is extremely low.
But it happened.
We are the first to arrive.
Others who worked on JX
are occupied.
They'll be here by tomorrow.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Han. Mr. Yang.
Our colleagues from
Base 158 are here.
Hi.
Hello.
Allow me
to introduce,
Mr. Li, Head of the Technical Department
in this center.
These two are
Mr. Yang and Mr. Han,
also from the Technical Department.
I'm Guan Zai from Base 158,
Satellite JX Head Engineer.
I'm Yu Tu from Base 158,
Satellite JX Engineer.
Mr. Hu is in Taiyuan now.
He has some business to attend to.
He'll be here tomorrow afternoon
at the latest.
Wonderful.
Thank you, Lv.
No problem.
Have you prepared for their reception?
The receptionists have done it.
Don't worry.
This is not urgent.
Mr. Li,
please brief us
the latest news of JX.
Last night,
after you transmitted
the commands during the second
and third rotation,
any downlink signal?
So,
when it entered our range,
we sent the command straight away.
However, we still haven't received
the downlink signal.
We switched to the backup and sent
the command via fixed channels
but there's no response.
I have with me its documents
and blueprint.
Do you have
any recent telemetry data
of the satellite?
It's all in our
system.
Let's figure out the problem then.
Once we find it,
we can devise a solution.
(Real-time fault diagnosis system
for on-orbit spacecraft)
(Two hours later)
Are you okay?
I'm getting old.
One white night
and I'm all dizzy already.
Back then,
a few hours of sleep
for a few nights? No problem.
I'll head to bed now.
I received
another call from the ministry.
The government
invested a lot
to launch this satellite.
Now that it's not working out,
the ministry wants an explanation.
Should we explore other options
instead of focusing on the transponder?
It could be the power supply.
Besides,
is it possible that its orbit
has changed?
The fixed channels
might not be able to reach it.
The power subsystem
and the recent orbital data,
I've read them all.
The telemetry data
is within
the normal threshold.
I've also checked the orbital data.
It matches quite well with the
predetermined orbit.
However, Mr. Guan and I
designed the model.
To reach a conclusion,
we need to wait for the
electrical and orbital engineers'
input.
(Space environment Solar wind)
(Pluto's interaction
with its space environment: Solar)
(Real-time Solar Wind
NOAA/NWS Space Weather)
(Heliospheric Weather Expert
Service Center, H-ESC)
(Earthward coronal mass ejection)
(CWE Propagation Example)
Guan.
We found the satellite?
No,
but I might have found an explanation.
All right. Let's have a meeting.
(Four hours later)
Solar energetic particle
is already a rare phenomenon.
But to have one whose energy
affects two machines at the same time?
This is
too unlikely.
Previously,
we've
been focusing on the satellite itself
and we couldn't locate the problem.
I was exploring the possibility
of external factors
and I suddenly thought of
the solar wind forecast I saw earlier.
I consulted
the International Space Environment Web
and I did find some relevant info.
While we were waiting for you,
Mr. Guan and I
did a rough calculation.
This possibility cannot be ruled out
but to reach the final conclusion,
we still need
a lot of calculations and simulations.
The backup is a dynamic backup.
Did we really hit the jackpot this time?
This year is also
the year of peak solar activity
according to the 11-year solar cycle.
Contact the Space Department of
the Chinese Academy of Science.
Ask them to provide us the details
regarding
Satellite JX in its trajectory
yesterday.
On it.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Hu of the Base 158
and others who worked on JX
have arrived.
Li.
Mr. Hu.
You arrived earlier.
Time is of the essence.
I traveled through the night via car.
Let's not waste time chatting.
Any update on JX?
Look at me. So anxious that
I got sick.
Satellite JX
is my last work before
I retire into administration.
If it's gone like that,
I will regret it
for the rest of my life.
Take a break first, Mr. Hu.
We might have found
the reason.
We're waiting for the confirmation.
(Two hours later)
The Chinese Academy of Sciences replied.
They confirmed that
the malfunction of the satellite
coincided with the solar storm.
(Xi'an Satellite Control Center)
Run the simulation now.
Cross-check the satellite's position,
the time of the malfunction,
and the range
of the energetic electron storm
triggered by the solar storm.
See if they match.
(Northwest Satellite Control Center)
How long will it take?
No longer than two hours.
We can still salvage it today.
The one in charge of orbit monitoring,
calculate its orbit
and surmise its
precise trajectory and travel time.
Transponder
and satellite coordinator,
write the command script now.
Power supply,
copy the previous energy level
on the satellite and evaluate
if there's any breach
in the power supply.
Besides,
the solar storm
is only the most
probable explanation so far.
We need to wait for the result.
Think
if there are any other
latent factors.
Guan Zai.
Since you're the head engineer,
stay in the loop.
Report to me every hour.
Noted.
(Two and a half hours later)
According to the simulation,
we can confirm that
before the Satellite JX
rotated to within our range
last night, it was hit
by the energetic electron storm
that happens once
every 11 years.
The massive energy released
might have affected
both transponders.
Single-event upset took place
simultaneously
and damaged the satellite's
communication system.
We have already devised
a contingency plan
for this.
The reception part
of the transponder
uses analog electronics.
It won't be affected
by the single-event upset.
Therefore,
when the satellite
rotates into our range again,
transmit reboot command
to the two transponders
via fixed channels.
If the satellite
receives the command successfully,
its telecommunication system
should come back online.
(Real-time fault diagnosis system
for on-orbit spacecraft)
(Chinese Spacecraft Management
Visual Panel)
Attention, everyone.
Reporting in from Jiamusi post.
Target will appear
in T-minus one minute.
K35 Satellite Transponder.
Launching module.
Reboot command for both machines.
Command sent by Jiamusi post.
The signal is in.
Telemetry signal received.
No interference.
Please check every system now.
How's the satellite?
Stabilization subsystem malfunction.
Three-axis
earth-oriented stabilization failed.
Power system normal.
Excessive power supply.
It uses less power
than expected.
We did take into account
the damage
to the stabilization subsystem
due to the solar storm.
We have a plan
for this exact scenario.
The power supply malfunction
must be the side product
of the damaged
stabilization subsystem.
I think it is
because of the solar sails,
that we can't establish
solar orientation properly,
so the power demand increased.
Our utmost priority now
is to reduce the workload
on the satellite.
Contain its energy consumption
and correct its attitude
as soon as possible.
Follow the protocol
and launch the commands.
Shut down all unnecessary systems
to reduce power consumption.
Meanwhile,
launch commands to request
solar sails to be solar-oriented.
The satellite is now
out of the monitoring range.
The next rotation will be at
8:03 PM.
Attention, everyone.
Reporting in from Kunming post.
Target is in range.
Telemetry data reports
malfunction
in the stabilization subsystem.
The satellite has not entered
a solar-oriented stable state.
Another white night.
Send the amended contract
to my e-mail.
The latest one, okay?
Xiao Zhu.
Come here.
Yes?
What happened to Jingjing recently?
She came to the office
three days in a row now.
She's in an argument with Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu has been absent these few days.
Really?
Aren't they get along well?
Jingjing.
I have good news.
Mr. Li sent us the contract
back.
I quite like the conditions.
Also,
if we announce this news now,
we'll have a higher offer
for the upcoming drama.
Am I worth the money?
I mean,
shooting for a drama usually
lasts for five months.
Am I worth the money?
Of course, you do!
Just think about it.
When you star in a show,
TV channels and streaming platforms
all want it.
Advertisers want to
place their products in it.
That's how the TV channels
and the streaming platforms make money.
Of course, you're worth the money.
Other B-listers
would ask for this price,
not to mention
you're an A-Lister yourself.
I don't want to be compared to them.
To who then?
Am I too
sentimental now?
Well,
it's not about
being sentimental or not.
I've thought about
this question too.
But you see,
that's how the market works.
If you don't grab it, someone else will.
Besides,
if you don't take the money,
the main investors
will still sell the copyright
at the same price.
So where will the price difference go?
Into the pocket
of the investors, of course.
It has
nothing to do with sentimentality.
Dwelling it in will serve no purpose.
Let me ask you then.
If someone offers you
several million yuan
for a drama,
would you say,
"No, I just want
several hundred thousand yuan?"
I wouldn't.
See?
There's no point in dwelling in this.
Just do your job properly.
Act well.
Stay out of trouble.
Respect their work.
Respect their money.
Donate to charity
like we're supposed to.
Is that not enough?
Look at you.
Sulking.
Why this all of a sudden?
Where's Mr. Yu?
All right.
I'll leave now.
Cheer up.
See you then.
Call me if anything.
Check on her.
If something happens,
call me.
See you then.
Will do. Don't worry.
(Yu Tu)
♪I dreamed of starlight
pulling the sleeves♪
♪A white top
covering the thin shoulders♪
♪I have seen the wounds healed
with each passing year♪
♪There will always be people
running towards eternity♪
♪The bustling intersection♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden
under the dim light♪
♪I loved your eyes
looking at the starry sky♪
♪And I loved the universe in your heart♪
♪Time does not stop, remember the time
that we failed to treasure♪
♪The wind passes by the tall buildings
with no one awaiting it♪
♪I've dreamed of traveling
around the planet♪
♪Seeing the galaxy
pass through the clouds♪
♪I looked at the hills with sorrow♪
♪Will the exit of the dream lead
to the end of the starry sky?♪
♪Looking back all of a sudden♪
♪Which galaxy am I drifting on?♪
♪Looking into the distance,
which of the stars are your eyes?♪
♪It's out of reach,
so dazzling and hard to get♪
♪Time does not hold back, the spring
and autumn in the passing time♪
♪The wind sings the song of freedom
as I listen to the tenderness of time♪