[English subtitles are available]
Please bless me with
a wonderful marriage.
Look after my best friends
Zeng Li and Wu Ying.
Please.
Pass it to me.
Thanks.
I apologise.
My colleagues were unctuous.
You're known to be most
popular around here.
No, they were fooling around.
Not many young women
work at the library anyway.
Initially, Wu Wan Xia and
I were unmarried.
They started promoting us
and gave us the title.
Last year, unexpectedly,
Wu Wan Xia got married as well.
Your colleagues told me
you've never dated anyone.
Would what happened today
hamper your prospects?
My apologies.
Not at all.
I should be apologising.
They just wanted to
find me a boyfriend.
There were several candidates.
After a few days,
they'd forget all about this.
It seems like
you've many rumoured
boyfriends as well.
You're right.
I've only met most of them once.
I don't even remember
what they look like.
Well, I guess I'm the one
that left the deepest impression.
Xiao Chu.
Auntie, you're here.
I heard you spent the night together.
Auntie, don't be ridiculous.
She's right there. You shouldn't...
I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant.
Don't take it personally.
It's alright.
Xiao Chu.
She must be the friend
you told me about.
You should introduce us.
This is Zeng Li.
She's a patient of mine.
This is my aunt.
Hello, auntie.
You look adorably bright.
You look really young too, auntie.
You look like Mr. Ai's sister instead.
Not at all.
Guess how old I am.
[-How do I do that?]
-Auntie.
You can't ask this
each time you meet someone.
I'm just asking.
I was talking to Xiao Zeng.
28.
I'm 35 years old.
You're such a sweet talker.
You're one pretty charmer.
That's enough, auntie.
Grandpa is waiting for us.
Let's go.
We're leaving.
-Xiao Zeng.
-Let's go.
Come by to have dinner with us soon.
Xiao Chu will make the arrangements.
Okay. Bye.
That girl was gorgeous.
-Let's hurry up.
-What does she do?
How old is she?
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 5]
Hold on.
[Goodness gracious.]
[My prayer worked immediately?]
[Abstinence.]
Did you drop this?
[His voice is so gentle.]
I got it for my dad.
Thanks.
I'm thanking you
for the second time today.
I came to pray for
my grandmother's safety as well.
She underwent a major
surgery recently.
Well,
I hope our prayers were answered.
I shall get going then. Bye.
[He's leaving already?]
[Power off]
Wait up.
My phone ran out of battery.
Can I use your phone
to text a friend?
Sure.
There's no need to thank me again.
[Zeng Li, I'm Ma Yi Yi. My phone ran out
of battery. The road up hill is blocked.]
[I'll meet you at the
hotel a little later.]
Thank...
I shall get going then.
Would you like to watch
the sunset in the evening?
There's nothing much
to do here in Dongshan.
The sunset is mesmerising though.
Perhaps,
you're going on a date with Mr. Ai.
Hold up.
Please take it easy on me.
The entire world has been
pestering me about Ai Jing Chu.
Give me a break.
How pitiful.
I'll let it slide
because I need to
head to the restroom.
I'll wait for you.
[Dou Dou]
[Sister Zeng.]
[I heard you went to Dongshan.]
[Can you do me a favour?]
[Last month, my ex-boyfriend and I]
[left a love lock]
[at Yue Lao's temple.]
[It's blue in colour.]
[Can you remove it for me?]
[I came to my senses.]
[I'm going to]
[end it completely before Yue Lao.]
[By the way, the password is 1314.]
You should go home.
When he ignores me,
I can't sleep nor eat.
No matter what I do,
he's all I think about.
Ai Jing Chu.
What kind of a person are you?
I'm finally here.
There are so many.
How am I going to find it?
It's blue.
[Wishing Terrace]
It might be there.
Which one is it?
[Dou Dou.]
[You broke up with Ai Jing Chu.]
[Why are you punishing me?]
Hello.
Mr. Ai, what are you up to?
I'm visiting Dongshan with my family.
The sunset here is mesmerising
so I came by alone.
What's the matter?
I...
I fell in love with a girl.
She's Chinese,
[but she's ignoring me.]
I'm not great with
relationship issues.
I might not be of help.
I'm just feeling dejected.
Just need someone to talk to.
Mr. Ai.
I've never intended to annoy her.
I noticed
she can't seem to
take care of herself
so I wanted to treat her better.
Am I being annoying?
No.
I think you're very sincere
and polite.
[Mr. Ai.]
[Are you comforting me?]
I really think these are
some qualities of yours.
Well, I'm not the best
in socialising.
[That's why I admire how initiative]
[and warm you are.]
Really?
After listening to you,
I feel much better.
I don't know
how to encourage you either.
Well,
[all the best.]
All right.
Thanks, Mr. Ai.
Which one is it?
Look at this one.
This colour is so pretty.
Actually,
I brought one along.
Let me take a look.
It's freezing.
My hip.
Look at the snow.
Let's hang ours here.
Sure.
If only
Ai Jing Chu is here right now.
[That'd save me from this tragedy.]
Zeng Li.
[Am I hallucinating?]
[No, he's real.]
[Why did he show up
just as I thought of him?]
Saviour?
You came.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for your love lock.
Hurry up and tell me where it is.
Help me out?
What are you talking about?
The blue lock.
The one you hung it up here
with Dou Dou.
Dou Dou?
Don't you remember her?
Did you hang
more than one lock here?
I think I get it.
Do you recall?
Hurry up and tell me.
I've been looking for a long time.
I finally understood
why you'd behave
so baffling previously.
Honestly,
about what happened
between you and Dou Dou,
I was pretty mad at you.
However, Dou Dou is fine now.
She has decided to
cut all ties with you.
Removing this lock
and everything will be fine.
The blue one?
I'll help you look.
[Help me look?]
Let's get this straight.
It's the other way round.
[You're acting so calm?]
Also,
I searched that area already.
Look for it over there.
Okay.
You'll know once you find it.
He's smiling?
The blue one.
I found it.
Let me take a look.
Let's see what's written on it.
We will always be together.
Dou Dou and Xu...
Xu Heng Heng.
Xu Heng Heng?
Isn't he a...
Yes.
He's a doctor of our faculty.
Like Dou Dou,
he was a student of mine.
What?
That means Dou Dou's ex-boyfriend
wasn't you.
I just found out
I shared such a past
with her today.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know...
I didn't know you weren't
Dou Dou's ex-boyfriend.
I was really mean to you
in the past.
What's the password?
Wait.
I was really rude
and offensive in the past.
I'm apologising this instance.
I'm sorry.
The password.
1314.
It's done.
I'm sorry.
You're forgiven.
Xu Heng Heng?
He looks nice.
He didn't look like a player.
Do I look like one?
[Do...]
[Think carefully before you answer.]
[I can only]
[fill the grave I dug for myself.]
Mr. Ai, you're understanding
and considerate.
Don't hold a grudge against me.
Fine.
Let's
forget this incident completely.
However, Mr. Ai,
you just recovered not long ago.
Why did you come up the hill
instead of resting in your hotel?
I heard the sunsets at
Dongshan is mesmerising
so I wanted to check it out.
Well...
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
It's fine.
I couldn't make it anyway.
I'm taking a move.
I know a shortcut.
If we're fast enough,
we might be able to
catch the sunset.
Let's go.
[Wishing Terrace]
It's over there.
Stop talking.
Your throat is sore.
These are some lozenges.
This is
the dinner I made for you.
There's a kitchen at our dorm.
It's really clean.
Don't worry.
I'm worried it'd not suit your taste,
so I made the flavours strong.
Remember to enjoy it.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
By the way,
do not consume
too many lozenges at once.
You should stay hydrated
and drink warm water,
not cold water.
I'm leaving. Goodbye.
This is the sincerest
one I've ever met.
Drink warm water instead.
[To: Wu Ying]
Mr. Ai, wait up.
I can't go on.
You should go ahead.
Watching the sunset alone
is pretty boring.
Let's go together.
I can't. My legs are failing.
Let me take a breather.
Shall I
help you up there?
All right.
We're almost there.
What do you think?
Thankfully I insist
to complete the hike.
It's breath taking.
What's the matter?
I was reminded
of a rumour I read
on the Tieba.
What was it about?
Your side profile was claimed
to have killed many.
It seems like
the rumours were pretty accurate.
What do you mean by my side profile?
Are you implying
that your entire face
is good looking too?
Mr. Ai.
Your skin is probably made of
titanium alloy.
The quality sounds good.
By the way,
do you know how to
determine if one's side profile
is good looking or not?
Are there standards for that?
According to the Asian
beauty standards,
if the tips of the
nose, mouth and chin
could be connected
in a straight line,
that'd create
a perfect silhouette.
The tips of the nose, mouth and chin
connected in a straight line.
Well, you didn't have to
straighten your teeth.
You were already
pretty to begin with.
Your cheeks are flushed.
No.
It was the sunset.
Look at yourself if
you don't believe me.
You're flushed too.
Zeng Li.
Since the misunderstanding
was clarified,
does that mean
you no longer despise me as much?
You're
looking
more like a kind person.
I am a kind person to begin with.
Yes, you are.
Anyway,
Donghu University is over there.
Really?
My house
is around
that area.
You could see that far away?
Of course.
My house is over there.
Your house is here?
Dear bed.
Who are you?
Ma Yi Yi.
I was scared to death.
When did you come by?
I arrived an hour ago.
I texted you.
You didn't read it?
Wait.
Sister.
At this day and age,
besides Taobao shop owners
and delivery couriers,
who still texts?
I do.
Wait.
This number doesn't belong to you.
Pass me your phone.
[Search: Sheng Ming]
Sheng Ming.
Does it sound good?
It's a great name.
Who is he?
The man of my fate bestowed upon me
by the Sansheng Stone.
Sounds interesting.
Explain yourself.
I'm not the one who
should be explaining.
You are.
Didn't your boyfriend
return with you?
What are you talking about?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Stop acting secretive.
When I was checking in,
they told me everything.
About your boyfriend's
glorious deeds this morning.
He saved the world.
Is that so?
Is my boyfriend Superman
or Batman?
The doctor, Ai Jing Chu.
Ai?
You can't possibly believe them.
They'd marry me off
to any man that comes by.
They said,
yesterday, you met up
with someone mysterious uphill.
Were you meeting with him?
I was going to meet you.
They said,
last night, you and him
shared a bed together.
No.
Last night, I slept with...
I did not.
They also said,
you were seen
hanging a love lock on
Yuelao Bridge alone.
I was removing the lock for Dou Dou.
Dou Dou? Sure.
Look at it yourself.
I'll take a look.
Xu?
This isn't Ai Jing Chu.
This guy is Xu Heng Heng.
He's a colleague of Ai Jing Chu.
He is Dou Dou's ex-boyfriend.
The mole we planted
was easily
brainwashed by Dr. Ai?
Wait. You don't believe me?
Fine.
Take a look yourself.
[Dou Dou:Thanks, Sister Zeng.
Throw the lock away for me.]
[Dou Dou: I do not want anything
to do with Xu Heng Heng anymore.]
We misunderstood him?
Hurry up and pursue him.
What?
Did you realise something?
Whether he is my boyfriend
should be consented by me.
He confessed
to your colleagues.
What did he say?
Dr. Ai.
When you're not around,
we will take care of
Zeng Li on your behalf.
If anyone
tries to lay a finger on Zeng Li,
we will keep watch for you.
Do you know what he said?
He probably said,
it's a misunderstanding.
You're wrong.
He probably said,
I do not know Zeng Li well.
Wrong again.
What did he say?
He said,
thanks.
Thanks?
Hence,
admit to your crimes.
No.
He must hate
explaining himself.
A withdrawn man like him
would speak
as little as he can.
You know him pretty well.
Not at all.
No matter what it is,
Dongshan Temple really works.
The both of us
met our destined men on the same dy.
Don't you agree?
Meet your destined
man on your own.
I'm taking a shower.
You're running away.
I'm going to bloom if you don't.
Sheng Ming.
The duckling is coming.
I'll push the duckling
back to you.
That young lady had
eyes that look like eyes
and a nose that looks like a nose.
She's much prettier than the
plastic girls on tv.
What are you talking about?
Have you ever seen
anyone with features jumbled up?
You.
Your face resembles a pizza pie.
It's all jumbled together.
What does the lady do?
I was about to ask.
Before I could,
Xiao Chu dragged me out there hastily.
What does she do?
How old is she?
She's just a patient of mine.
Tell us about her.
She's a librarian at
Dongshan University.
She's 26.
Her age is perfect for Xiao Chu.
Exactly.
A librarian is great.
Here, Xiao Xiao.
Have some Mung bean pastry.
A librarian has a stable career.
She could take care of
the home in the future.
Is it yummy?
Yes.
They'd give birth to
beautiful children.
They'd take after Xiao Chu's
eyes and nose.
The kids may take after
either of their lips.
They must take after Xiao Zeng's skin.
Her complexion is soft,
fair and plump.
Xiao Chu.
Are you interested
in that young lady?
Brother.
I want more.
You can't eat anymore, Xiao Xiao.
Come.
Let's go brush our teeth.
Don't leave.
Say something.
Stop asking.
Something's happening.
Look.
Should I opt for invisalign instead?
You said wire braces would
straighten your teeth faster.
If you opt for invisalign,
it might take a longer time.
Are you planning to
spend your youth
as a brace face?
You were already
pretty to begin with.
Yi Yi.
Do you think
men only care about appearances?
Of course.
Did you think they'd
care about your organs instead?
Hold on.
You weren't asking about men,
you were asking if Dr. Ai
cares about one's appearances.
I was not.
I'm looking
for a boyfriend.
I should take care of my appearance.
Before meeting Dr. Ai,
you couldn't be bothered.
Go to bed.
Don't worry.
Who knows? Dr. Ai
may have an unique preference.
He doesn't care about legs, waist,
looks or figure,
he only cares about your organs.
Darling, are you there?
Let me peep at your organs.
-Let me have a peep.
-Pervert!
Pervert.
Let me take a peep at yours.
I'm peeping.
[Optimum users of traditional
braces and invisalign]
The follow-up cycle
of traditional braces
is 28 days.
The follow-up cycle of invisalign
is much longer.
Check the progress of treatment
once every six to
eight weeks suffices.
Besides the price and
orthodontic treatment,
there's another factor.
That is the patients'
dental condition.
It is an important factor to consider
when selecting the optimum
orthodontic treatment.
[Donghu University]
For patients with crowded teeth,
generally,
I'll opt for traditional braces.
Mr. Ai.
What kind of alignment
is considered crowded?
Let me find you a case study.
Hold on.
[Case study]
This patient is pretty.
Mr. Ai.
Is her alignment considered crowded?
Moderate crowding.
Look.
There are no spaces
between her teeth,
but there isn't overlapping
or erupting problems.
Let's take her for an example.
If the condition is
more severe than hers,
opt for traditional braces.
Was she given traditional braces
or the invisalign?
Traditional braces.
Mr. Ai.
Are you looking for
somebody or something?
Zeng Li had an
early shift this morning.
She left already.
No.
I came
to extend the loan period
for the books
I borrowed a few days ago.
Extending the loan period?
You can get it done via
the application.
It's unnecessary to
come all the way here.
Really?
You can also let Zeng Li know.
It'd be done then.
You're mistaken.
Nothing is happening
between Zeng Li and I.
Mr. Ai.
I thought
the both of you were just shy,
but this afternoon, I heard that
Zeng Li's mother made arrangements
again for her tonight.
Mr. Ai.
You let me down.
Arrangements?
A blind date.
Well, I've work to attend to.
Please excuse me.
Mr. Ai.
Would you like to know
where they'd be
having dinner tonight?
It's alright.
It's none of my business.
7pm at Ruger.
That's the most I could do to help.
I'm exhausted.
You played well today.
I did alright today.
-Not bad.
-Brother Yu Cheng.
Have something to drink.
I don't drink iced drinks. Thanks.
I'll get a new one at the store.
Wait for me.
Don't worry about it.
Just leave it.
Thanks.
Are you free tonight?
Let's go watch a movie.
Age of Dinosaurs III
will be off screen soon.
You haven't watched it, right?
I watched it already.
Well,
let's go grab dinner then.
Brother Yu Cheng.
Please say yes.
Mr. Ai.
I had dinner plans with Mr. Ai.
Yes.
We made dinner plans.
Let's go then, Mr. Ai.
Let's go.
Bye.
-Let's go.
-Don't worry. Over there.
There's more over there.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ai.
I used you as an excuse.
It's fine.
I understand.
I shall get going then, Mr. Ai.
See you.
Aren't you going to eat?
Mr. Ai.
Are you asking me out?
Of course I can. Let's go.
I heard about a restaurant
named Ruger.
Have you heard about it?
It's located near the west
gate of the university.
[Ruger Cafe]
I could tell in one glance
that you were forced to
attend the blind date by your family.
[You don't say.]
Was it...
Was it that obvious?
We're on the same boat.
[I couldn't tell.]
Honestly though,
normally,
I would have rejected this.
Well, fortunately I came today.
Otherwise, I would have missed you.
[Can I reject this instead?]
Like the saying goes,
everything just falls into place.
-What do you think?
[-Yes.]
[Everything is laid out for me.]
Don't you find yourself
rather lucky?
[Yes.]
[The luck of forgetting an
umbrella during rainy days.]
Is that how people
compliment themselves nowadays?
I was just kidding.
Honestly,
what do you feel about me?
[The epitome of unctuous.]
You're great.
That's too general.
Can you be a little more specific?
[You're asking me to be specific?]
[It's going to be awkward
if I call him a chatterbox.]
You're rather affable.
[You're a man.]
[You look great too.]
[What else can I come up with?]
You've great prospects.
All right.
If you find me suitable,
let's sign the
marriage certificate right now.
[Marriage certificate?]
[Brother,
are you in a rush to get married?]
I was just making a spontaneous joke.
[Do you have a
misconception about humour?]
Let's do this.
Let's start of as friends.
If you're not hasty,
I'd be able to keep it in.
I'm fine with being just friends.
However, I don't feel
anything else for you.
Feelings can always be
nurtured through time.
At least you don't hate me, right?
I don't.
Don't be in a haste to reject me.
Give me a chance.
We will start off as friends.
Let's see where this
takes us in the future.
[In the future?]
[If your dad wasn't my
stepdad's superior...]
After dinner,
would you like to catch the movie,
Age of Dinosaurs III?
It's just a movie.
[I'm doing this for the sake
of my mother's happiness.]
All right.
Welcome. Come on in.
Let's take this table.
I'm back.
Mr. Ai.
Do you know her?
No.
This restaurant is decent,
but I haven't been here
in a long time.
Is this your first time, Mr. Ai?
Yes.
Take a look.
Call for me when you're ready.
Thanks.
Mr. Ai.
Let's catch a movie after dinner.
Age of Dinosaur III.
I wanted to watch it for a long time.
I can't.
I've matters to attend to tonight.
What is it?
Before 8pm,
I need to head home to workout.
Then, take a shower.
From 9-10pm, I will read
books of the related field.
10pm to 11pm
is my time of relaxation and leisure.
Mr. Ai, your schedule
is pretty great.
I'll make myself one too.
There are times when you
wouldn't be home though.
Just like today.
Normally, I'll arrange a night or two
per week
as a flexible time.
However, I must go to bed before 11pm.
Young people like you
stay up pretty late though.
You should readjust if possible.
I'm not like the others.
I care about health a lot.
Normally, by 11pm,
I would be asleep too.
Are the both of you ready?
Chicken breast salad.
Green apple juice with kale.
Also,
a bowl of vegetable soup.
Feel free to make your order.
I'm heading to the washroom.
Okay.
Two sets of chicken breast salad.
Two glasses of green
apple juice with kale.
Two bowls of vegetable soup.
Hello.
[Aren't you having dinner
with Gu Dong Hai right now?]
[You picked up the phone immediately.]
[Did you run away again?]
Mom, are you monitoring
me from a distance?
I'm at the washroom.
Come and inspect if
you don't believe me.
[Xiao Gu is really hilarious.]
[You'd never be bored around him.]
[Is there a spark?]
No.
I'm not looking for a talk show host.
[I'm warning you.]
[Do not mistreat Xiao Gu.]
[He's in the finance industry.]
[His father is your
Uncle Peng's superior.]
I get it.
You should get some water, mom.
[Don't be in a rush to
come home after dinner.]
[You enjoy watching movies alone.]
[Finally, you found someone to]
[keep you company.]
Mom.
Do you have any idea
how awkward it is
to watch a movie with
someone I don't like?
[Perhaps, after the movie,]
[you would have developed feelings.]
[Am I hallucinating again?]
Mom, I'll talk to you later.
-I'm hanging up.
[-Hey.]
[In a relationship, adults]
[tend to think that]
[the one who takes the
initiative is the loser.]
[It feels like when
a relationship begins,]
[a game begins,]
[a competition begins.]
[Even when one has fallen deep,]
[but would tell oneself stubbornly]
[that he doesn't like you as much.]
[I can always leave any time.]
[Sheng Ming: Awaiting approval.]
Sir, here's your apple juice.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
It tastes great.
[Recipient: Wu Ying.
Items in cart: Apple juice with kale.]
[Place order.]
[The meaning of love]
[lies in sincerity.]
[There are no winners nor losers.]
[It doesn't matter who takes
the first step forward.]
[In the world of adults,]
[sincerity]
[is the most priceless thing.]
[The one everyone should
cherish the most.]
[Isn't that so?]