♪Time once stopped everything♪
♪There's someone special♪
♪I flip the eternity dictionary♪
♪And uncover the suspense
that makes my heart beat fast♪
♪At this special moment
we run into each other♪
♪As unconsciously as we breathe♪
♪Holding hands over a long time♪
♪Means more than any word♪
♪Among a sea of people♪
♪I hold the umbrella for you♪
♪You hold the umbrella for me♪
♪I'll be special for you♪
♪You shelter me from the rain♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪Your love gets me through the haze♪
♪You'll have me♪
♪I'll search and wait♪
♪For the love of our lives♪
♪The future spent with you♪
♪We shall no longer linger♪
♪Is the best arrangement of love♪
♪The best arrangement♪
=The Oath of Love=
♪Is love♪
=Episode 7=
I am going to start a business,
and
I get the start-up capital ready.
I need talent.
What do you say?
Are you interested in
doing something big with me?
What project?
A bar.
A bar?
Do you have a license
to operate alcoholic beverages?
Do you know the high risk
of nightclub business?
Do you know how to run a bar?
I don't, but I can learn.
You? Forget about it.
I knew you were unreliable.
You tell me.
What should I do?
A café.
A café is too boring.
Bars are fun.
Bars are full of pretty women.
I think you want to open a bar,
so you can take advantage of
the opportunity to drink and pick up girls.
Cafés are full of businessmen.
I think you just want to have a place
to be a gold-digger.
Wait…
I have an appointment. I'm leaving now.
Café it is!
You can be the manager, OK?
Bye-bye.
Hello, Dad?
Who…
Who says I can't get a job?
I've already received a lot of offers.
I'm telling you,
I pick the jobs now,
not the other way around.
Don't send me money!
I didn't go to school abroad
for nothing, OK?
I have skills, OK?
Don't worry.
I can take care of myself,
absolutely no problem.
I know what's going on
at home, OK?
I know our business is not doing well.
It's okay. I'm fine.
OK, I have to go.
I'm going to take a shower. Bye.
Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
How do you say it in your hometown?
Say what?
I like you.
I.
Like.
You.
Put them together.
I like you.
I like…
- Slowly.
- You try it.
Let's try it slowly.
- Slower.
- I'll try. I like you.
Who is this? It's late already.
I need to take this call.
Hello, Sansan.
Sansan.
Are you really going to open a café?
Of course!
- I'm ready to hire now,
- Come on, cheers.
I'm reviewing resumes.
Good.
You set a time for an interview.
I will get my resume ready.
No need.
I trust you.
If you come,
you'll be the manager.
OK?
Let's discuss
the cooperation model tomorrow.
I want to be a shareholder
with technology contributed.
And
we need to discuss
the management model and business style.
No problem. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
So unreliable.
Let me ask you something serious.
Do any of your families own a café
or have you done it yourselves?
What's she talking about?
A shareholder
with technology contributed,
management model and business style,
what are these?
Xiao,
café is boring.
You're wrong.
Is he doing this for a café?
You got me. Cheers.
- Come on, cheers.
- Here, here.
Keep an eye on the patient.
- Yes, okay.
- If anything happens,
report it to me immediately.
Okay.
Hi, Dr. Gu.
You're done with your rounds?
Get back to work.
Sure.
Would you like
to join me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Here, Dr. Gu.
To celebrate the success
of Lin Zhixiao's cellist contest,
cheers!
You really like this so much?
You should drink Coke
on such a good day.
It's a ritual.
Do you doctors do not drink this?
Some doctors like to
drink a little Coke
after multiple surgeries
to get a quick sugar boost.
Right?
I owe my success
in the contest to you.
You help Mr. Lin a lot.
I've been saying thank you a lot,
but I want to say thank you again today.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
You're a very uninteresting person.
You're always acting cool.
We've been talking to each other.
We are friends, right?
Dr. Gu sounds strange,
can I call you something else?
Like…
Like what?
Dr. Handsome?
This is…
This name is a bit flirty.
Not good enough. Another one.
Like…
Dr. Old-school.
It suits you.
What? You like it?
What kind of name is it?
You don't like it?
Lin Zhixiao.
Mr. Lin is coming back for chemotherapy.
Does it seem appropriate that
you are offending
his attending physician?
No, not at all.
I'm just kidding.
I'll call you Dr. Gu.
Dr. Gu?
Yes.
Do you think I'm not reliable?
Actually,
I'm not that bad.
I owe you a song. I remember it.
When I get the tickets for the Concert,
I'll give you one,
and invite you to listen to it.
Uh-huh.
I'm looking forward to it.
Want some chips?
It's delicious.
You're so funny!
Why do you do that all the time?
Do you think
this is cool?
Let me tell you something.
It's so lame.
(Doctor's Office 2)
Gu Wei.
Du.
Dr. Gao.
Come here.
Where's Gu Wei?
Did he leave from work?
The family of the patient in bed 9,
Ms. Lin, wanted to see him.
Bed 9? What's wrong with bed 9?
Nothing.
But something is going on with them.
What?
I didn't say anything.
He should be back soon.
Mr. Lin, Ms. Li.
My first step on the road to greatness
is about to begin,
the cellist of the Concert.
Tickets for friends and family.
I just got them.
Let me see.
Am I good?
You are so easily satisfied.
What are you talking about?
I think my daughter is very good.
When is it?
The first of next month.
I don't know how well
your father will recover by then.
Maybe we won't be able to go.
What are you talking about?
I must be there.
Lin Zhixiao.
Don't embarrass me.
Alright, Mr. Lin.
You need more rest.
There will be many opportunities
for me to be a cellist,
I will invite you to be there
every day, okay?
I promise I'll make you proud.
Okay, I'll wait for the grand theater.
Okay.
How's it going?
Dr. Gao
Good. Good.
The wound doesn't seem to hurt so much.
right?
You can try to move around more.
Sure.
Good.
Dr. Gao.
We didn't have time to
thank you
after the operation.
I have a concert next month
and would like to invite you to see it.
Thank you for
taking care of Lin.
Dr. Gao, I'm sorry.
Lin Zhixiao and I need
to talk about work.
You go ahead.
I want to run for the cellist
in our school's concert.
But I haven't practiced for a long time,
so I don't know if I can succeed.
I can help you with that.
See you in the hospital lobby
tomorrow morning.
Dr. Gao.
Dr. Gao?
So, did you invite Gu Wei?
I did.
I'll give him the tickets later.
Why don't you give me the tickets.
I'm on my way to see him.
Sure.
Thank you.
The first of next month?
That's right.
Gu Wei and I have a seminar that day,
so we might not be able to make it.
But we'll try to be there.
Okay, thank you, Dr. Gao.
Rest well.
- Thank you.
Bye, Dr. Gao.
If you don't have a place
to send these tickets,
I'll give them to my colleague.
A lot of people want them, okay,
Ms. Lee?
I'm on fire, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
I can't believe you.
What are you doing?
I'm writing medical records.
The first of next month,
our colleagues are organizing a seminar,
and the participants are professionals,
so I'd like to invite you to join us.
Uh-huh.
If the department doesn't
have any plans,
I'll definitely go.
Then we'll go together.
From the patient's family.
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert
Date: May 1, 2019 at 14:30)
I owe you a song. I remember it.
When I get the tickets for the Concert,
I'll give you one,
and invite you to listen to it.
(Harrison's Gastroenterology
and Hepatology)
Qiuqiu.
Listen to your mother
after you leave the hospital.
I know.
Dr. Gu.
Good boy!
Qiuqiu.
Be careful.
Zhixiao.
I'll be discharged today.
That's great. Congratulations, Qiuqiu.
Try to be happy,
- OK?
- Uh-huh.
Thank you for what've done
for our boy.
I've been wanting to
invite you all to dinner,
but…
In fact, we have always
wanted to hold
a simple send-off party for Qiuqiu.
We all love Qiuqiu very much
The nurses are going to miss you,
you know?
Qiuqiu's birthday is coming up soon.
Right, Qiuqiu?
Great! Can I have some cake?
Yes.
Happy birthday to you.
- ♪Happy birthday to you♪
- Thank you again , Dr. Gu.
It's OK.
- ♪Happy birthday to you♪
- Easy there.
You're one year older.
Qiuqiu,
who do you want to give
your first piece of cake to?
First piece of cake.
Aim.
To me?
Thank you, Qiuqiu.
Let me try.
So good!
Thank you, Qiuqiu.
Qiuqiu's mom,
I need to do rounds,
so I have to go.
Sorry.
Who is the owner of this cake?
Me?
- Thank you, Qiuqiu.
- Dr. Du.
- Wei.
- Thank you.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Who should you give this piece to?
To me?
- Thank you, Qiuqiu.
- Zhixiao.
I like you the most.
Remember to think of me.
I like you the most, too.
I'll miss you.
Good boy.
Who's next, Qiuqiu?
Me?
Dr. Gu.
You take care of me the most.
I will visit you.
Qiuqiu.
My biggest wish
is that you don't come back
after you leave, OK?
Then I won't
be able to see you anymore.
How come?
We just hope that
when we see you again,
you won't be in the hospital.
But if you miss us,
we will visit you, okay?
There's one last piece.
Look who doesn't have one yet.
Give a piece to Dr. Gao.
Dr. Gao.
Would you like a piece of cake?
Thank you, Qiuqiu.
I thought I wouldn't get one.
You have to eat less sweets
and oily things in the future, you know?
Just take one or two bites of this,
don't eat it all.
Dr. Gao is quite right,
but that's for later.
- Today is an exception.
- Gu Wei!
I approved it today.
You can eat. Go.
Come on, Qiuqiu.
- Dr. Gu said you can eat cake now.
- It's OK.
Come on, have some more.
Here. Enjoy the cake.
Cake time.
Use this.
Dr. Gu is still
a neat freak.
I'm exactly the same as Gu Wei.
It's just a professional habit.
Not really.
I can use disposable ones.
Oh, Gu Wei.
This piece it too big.
I can't eat it all. It's a waste.
Let's share it.
I don't want to waste it.
I should share Qiuqiu's piece.
It's not good for him to eat that much.
Sure.
- Come on, Qiuqiu.
- Dr. Gu and Dr. Gao are so close.
I've known him for such a long time.
We know each other's flavor.
Of course.
Alright, let's enjoy the cake.
OK.
Enjoy yourselves.
Qiuqiu, is it good?
Which one is better?
Yours is better.
No way.
Bye-bye.
Gu Wei.
That cake was a bit greasy.
Would you some black tea?
No, thanks.
Dr. Gao.
I have things to do.
Don't wait for me.
OK.
What is it, Qiuqiu?
Dr. Gu.
I know your secret.
Really?
That's big.
What secret? Tell me.
You like Zhixiao.
Nonsense.
Who told you that?
Do you know what it means
to like someone?
Of course I do.
You didn't smile before,
but since Zhixiao came,
you've been smiling at her a lot.
Qiuqiu, we should go.
Dr. Gu, I'm going to get us ready.
We'll leave soon.
I'll walk you out later.
Thank you.
Come with me, Qiuqiu.
Bye.
(In-patient)
Thank you.
Qiuqiu,
Aunt Li
is busy taking care of Grandpa Lin,
so I'm here on behalf of them
to say goodbye to you, OK?
Thank you, Zhixiao.
I don't want to say goodbye to you
and Dr. Gu.
I don't want to leave you either.
Here, this is a gift
from Grandpa
Lin, Aunt Li
and me.
If you miss me,
just look at this, OK?
Zhixiao,
How can I play with a bear doll?
OK, OK, OK.
Would you
take care of this bear
for me?
OK.
Good boy.
Qiuqiu.
After discharge from the hospital,
you should eat less snacks,
rest well and take care of yourself,
understand?
Here, this is for you.
Book of Healthy
and Study.
Uh-huh.
Dr. Gu's gift
is worse than Zhixiao's.
You take it.
Don't be rude.
Say thank you to Dr. Gu.
I have gifts
for Dr. Gu and Zhixiao.
Really? What gifts?
- Help me.
- Let me help you.
Zhixiao, this is for you.
This one?
Thank you, Qiuqiu.
And Dr. Gu.
This is for you.
Thank you, Qiuqiu.
What is it?
Don't open it now.
Wait after I leave.
Don't tell the others.
This is a little secret.
Uh-huh.
OK, we won't open it now.
Dr. Gu.
Thank you.
Sure.
Pay attention to Qiuqiu's health.
Got it.
Zhixiao, goodbye.
Thank your parents for me.
Keep in touch.
Yeah.
- Bye-bye.
The car is leaving.
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
- Be careful.
- Safe trip.
- The bear.
- Thank you.
Save the bear a seat.
- Qiuqiu.
- Goodbye.
- Bye-bye.
Let's go, Dr. Gu.
Uh-huh.
See.
This is Qiuqiu's gift for me.
This is obviously me, the cello.
Who is this one next to me?
Is it Qiuqiu?
How come he's so tall?
What's yours? Let me see it.
No.
I promised Qiuqiu
not to show it to anyone.
You're sneaky.
I've already shown it to you.
Why can't I see yours?
No.
Why can't I see it?
It won't hurt.
Fine, fine.
I don't want to see it.
Let me see it.
Why can't I see it?
Your stitches
will be removed soon.
Don't just like that.
Gu Wei.
Have you prepared
the surgery plan for tomorrow?
Not yet.
I'll let you know when it' ready.
OK.
Don't forget about the seminar
on the first of next month,
you have to prepare in advance,
let's discuss later.
Oh, Gao Xi.
Did you get the tickets
from Lin Zhixiao?
I'm very busy.
I can't remember it.
Uh-huh.
I suppose so.
Isn't she from the music department?
I've been in contact with her
for a while,
she's kind of cute.
She is cute.
Lin Zhixiao.
Let me disinfect your wound first.
Dr. Gu.
Please be gentle.
It won't hurt.
Come here. Don't move.
I promise to be gentle.
Lin Zhixiao, I think,
you misunderstand me and Dr. Gao.
Dr. Gu.
Tell me the truth,
do you want to murder me?
I'm sorry.
Just a little more patience,
it will be done soon.
This is your last chance.
I promise it won't hurt at all.
Can I trust you?
You don't have a trust.
Don't touch it with your hand.
Come here.
There you go.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Is my hair still perfect?
Do I have a high hairline?
It's perfect.
Lin Zhixiao.
Uh-huh.
I think
you really misunderstood me and Dr. Gao
We were
classmates.
And now we're
colleague.
She is not my girlfriend,
nor is she my ex-girlfriend.
In fact,
what I mean is that
Dr. Gao and I
used to be classmates,
but now and in the future
we are just colleagues, understand?
I understand what you mean.
You mean
you're afraid I'll…
Spread rumors!
I'm not that nosy.
Don't worry,
I won't tell anyone about it.
Besides, Lin will be discharged soon,
so I won't have this chance.
Yes,
Lin will be discharged tomorrow.
Uh-huh.
I couldn't be happier!
I was finally able to take off
the heavy responsibility
of VIP's special nursing.
I'm exhausted.
Speaking of that,
you and Ms. Li
are spoiling Li.
I sometimes think,
if only I had someone
to spoil me like this.
Seriously? Dr. Gu,
do you want to get sick?
Who would want to get sick?
Yeah.
Lin Zhixiao,
after you leave the hospital,
what are you going to do?
I'm going back to school
to continue my cello dream.
I'm going to be
the best cellist in the country.
Going back to school.
It sounds like a life
from my previous life.
See, Dr. Gu,
you're acting like an old man again?
Well, if so,
do you feel there's
a generation gap between us?
I do feel that way
in terms of habits
and jargon.
And sometimes,
I feel like you're older than Lin.
I even want to call you Uncle.
Uncle.
Oh, right.
Did you get the tickets for the Concert?
Dr. Gao was supposed
to give them to you.
You must come.
I did.
What? you want me to come?
Of course. It's my concert,
of course I want you to be there.
Ms. Li needs to take care of Mr. Lin,
so she can't come.
If she can't make it,
of course I want you and Dr. Gao
to come and support me.
It occurred to me that I might
have a seminar that afternoon.
You know what?
I'll try to make time,
OK?
Oh.
Let me help.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
This thing of yours,
is it OK?
It's fine.
The stitches are removed.
You can leave now.
I'll clean up.
Uh-huh.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Bye, Dr. Gu.
Hey.
Don't get
any water on that wound.
Be careful.
Remember that.
Bye-bye.
(Treatment Room)
Here.
Zhixiao.
Check things out.
See if there's anything left.
Don't leave it behind.
Don't worry. It's all checked out.
Where are you going?
I'll get a contact number
from Dr. Gu.
If there's a problem after we leave,
I can go to him.
Don't you have the contact information
for the nurse station?
They are too busy.
I'll ask him for a private number.
He's a doctor.
He doesn't have private time for…
Don't ask for his private number.
Ms. Li.
She won't get it.
(Popular Science Books on Cancer
Prevention and Treatment, Gastrointestinal Cancer)
(In-patient)
You're back so soon?
He refused you, right?
I got it.
Dr. Gu.
Why are you here?
Don't you have surgery?
There's a 20-minute window.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Go finish the discharge formalities,
or you're not going home today.
Sure.
Mr. Lin.
Watch your diet.
OK.
Well, I better get back to it.
Bye, Dr. Gu.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
(Points for attention
in postoperative care)
Zhixiao.
Let's go.
Oh.
This is my plan for the café.
What do you think?
(3. Project market positioning
and SWOT analysis)
Gu Xiao.
Are you listening to me?
I am. I am.
I listened to every word
You... You have
a great proposal.
See, who would I hire
if I don't hire you?
Come on, let's get something to eat.
Let's go. Interview's over.
No!
If we're gonna do this right,
we have to do it as soon as possible.
You see, this is the information
(58.com)
I picked up on 58. Com
about the right store
to open a coffee shop.
(58.com)
Some of them are pretty good.
You're so good.
You're so serious.
Let's go on a field trip right now.
Now?
Uh-huh.
You gotta be kidding me.
What are you doing?
Let's go!
OK, go.
(New schedule)
(Lin Jianguo, chemotherapy)
(Points for attention
in postoperative care)
(1. Semi-liquid diet,
eat less at a time…)
(Remember: no spicy food,
no smoking, no alcohol)
(Searching by phone number)
(Add)
(Hint: this user refuses to add anyone)
Oh, dear.
It's finally over.
You haven't slept in, like,
twenty-four hours since
your shift yesterday.
Go take a lunch break.
I'll take it from here.
Don't worry.
So considerate.
Get some rest.
OK.
Hey, Dr. Gu.
The clinic hours have been changed,
and the director wants you
to take the afternoon off.
No need.
I have a patient coming in
this afternoon for chemo.
Chemo?
Isn't that Dr. Gao's job?
I'm just checking for her.
OK.
(In-patient)
Zhixiao.
I'm paying the bill.
When Dr. Gu comes,
you should ask him
about the chemotherapy,
especially how to take care
of your dad, and make him suffer less.
It's very useful.
I got it.
Go pay the bill.
You think I'm nagging you again.
Stop it.
Dr. Gu…
Dr. Gao, it's you.
I'm the attending.
Post-op care
is my job.
Is there a problem.
No, no, it's just,
we've been talking to
Dr. Gu a lot,
and we know him pretty well.
But we're all very impressed
with your abilities.
We're talking about chemotherapy.
Shall we begin?
I have a lot of patients.
Yeah, yeah.
The chemotherapy,
which will take two days,
is based on the XELOX regimen,
which is made up of Oxaliplatin,
but in small doses,
along with liver protective drugs
and prescribed by your doctor.
Any reaction to the chemo?
Well, it depends on the person.
Can you be more specific?
Depends…
It means the patient
may experience nausea,
but vomiting cannot be ruled out.
Lin will have an upset stomach
and won't be able to eat?
Yes.
Well,
is there anything we can do about it?
Well, you can prepare something
nutritious and digestible.
If his appetite is really bad,
I'll give him some nourishment.
Oh.
Any questions?
No, no.
I'll take my leave then.
Sure.
Thank you, Dr. Gao.
What's going on?
Lin.
Big news.
You have
a beautiful woman
in charge of your chemo.
Dr. Gao?
Yes.
What's the fuss?
Dr. Gao has been my attending physician.
It's normal for her to be in charge.
You didn't look happy.
What were you doing?
I wasn't upset.
What's going on?
What?
I mean,
Dr. Gao is so beautiful.
Standing next to her
makes me look less pretty.
Right?
Always joking around.
(In-patient)
Dr. Gao, excuse me.
It's just that my dad
used to be able to eat these,
and now he can't eat any of it.
I'm a little worried.
So I want to ask for your opinion.
It's normal after chemo.
I'm sending a text.
Dr. Gu, this is Lin Zhixiao.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but Mr. Lin can't eat
because of the reaction
of chemotherapy.
I don't know
if there is any way to help him.
I like Dr. Gu.
He looks cold on the surface,
but he's very warm-hearted.
(Doctor's Office 2)
How about now?
Would you like some porridge?
(Dr. Gu)
How about now?
Would you like some soup?
Mr. Lin.
This is not going to work.
You have to eat something.
Meat soup smells disgusting.
Vegetable soup it is.
No.
Noodles?
Porridge?
Wonton.
Lin Zhixiao.
There's a wonton restaurant
about a block east of the gate.
Get some vegan wontons for Mr. Lin.
OK, I'm on it.
Go, go.
Be careful on the road.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
It's OK.
It's killing us.
Thanks.
You have to eat something.
OK, Thanks.
Well, I better get back to it.
Sure.
Thank you. Thank you.
You want wontons,
why didn't you say it?
Slow down.
Dr. Du.
Mr. Lin is eating something.
Thanks to Dr. Gu.
Dr. Gu was here?
He came back today?
He really cares about you.
He's really busy today.
He didn't have time to go
to the bathroom today,
and now he's in surgery.
Mr. Lin,
just turn on the news and you'll see.
Here, one more bite.
Easy.
(Serious traffic accident in our city,
101 people injured)
OK, got it.
I'm on my way.
(Doctor's Office 2)
(Breaking news.)
(There was a traffic accident
on Ning'an road this morning.)
(Several cars rear-ended each other)
(and some people were injured.)
(Traffic control has been implemented
on the section of road.)
(Please plan)
(your route well in advance)
(and travel safely.)
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
Gu Wei.
I don't want to say this,
but…
Unbelievable.
No need to write, I'm blind.
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
You just asked me about
=The Oath of Love=
things I pay attention to in life, right?
(Lin & Gu's Sweet Little Theatre)
I try not to use
technical terms
and not to be so old-school.
I don't want to hear you say
me old all the time.
Who says you're old?
Well, it does sound
familiar somehow.
Tell me.
Did you say it the day
I remove your stitches?
I…
You, you, you.
You can't say it.
Say it.
- Confess to me.
- I did?
But I must have said something
like you're young,
you look young, to save myself.
I didn't?
Don't be mad, Dr. Gu.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
OK, how about I call you
Dr. Gu?
Gu Wei, Mr. Hot.
Mr. Hot.
Mr. Hot. Love you.
How about
Mr. Cutie Pie?
Mr. Cutie Pie, love you.
Yeah, it's me.
=The Oath of Love=
(Little theater)
♪Pass by the bustling scenery♪
♪Fascinated by a raindrop♪
♪Watch it glide on my fingertip♪
♪Kind of like
the intersection of pressing strings♪
♪Some small things♪
♪Have been kept in my mind♪
♪Later I smiled and remembered,
leaning on you♪
♪I couldn't help myself then♪
♪One likes another♪
♪They show love
by slowly getting closer♪
♪Secretly glad how incredible it is♪
♪One likes another♪
♪Leave all care♪
♪Without a trace, without reservation♪
♪All myself to you♪