♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 2=
Mengmeng.
Is that golden powder on your eyelids?
Sister queen,
this is girl-group style makeup.
Using shiny powder
to make your eyes look bright.
Is that ash on your face?
This is shading powder.
Using light and shade
to modify the face shape.
See. Is my face V shaped?
Such nonsense.
Yes.
Mengmeng.
Aren't you cold,
Mengmeng?
Sister queen,
this is the way
I try to be cool.
The marriage competition
is going to start.
Princes, please enter the palace.
Such vulgar makeup.
The Wu Ze prince is so good looking.
He is so handsome.
Exactly.
(How come there's such a
pretty guy in this world.)
It's you?
You two knew each other?
No.
(I thought he was just
a non-player character.)
I didn't know that he had
so many parts to play.
(Don't tell me he is the one.)
(Mr. System.)
(Don't make a fool out of me.)
The marriage competition
consists of four rounds
in which you will compete on
beauty, wisdom,
talent, and courage respectively.
The first round
is on beauty.
Each maid can give the flowers
to the top 3 good-looking princes
in their thought.
The more flowers get,
the higher points scored.
Starting now.
Why?
Give it to him.
That one, that one.
Yes, yes, yes.
To Wu Ze, to Wu Ze.
Give it to him, give it to him.
Give to Wu Ze.
Yes, yes, yes.
I announce that the top 3 winners
in the first round are
the 5th prince of Cang Yun Kingdom,
the 7th prince of Wu Ze Kingdom,
and the 2nd son of Assistant Minister
of the Ministry of Revenue.
Princes with no flower shall leave now.
The second round is on wisdom.
The test is the mechanism
box in front of everyone.
The person who opens it
faster can win higher points.
He can do it. He can do it.
This...
(Song Che,)
(the son of the general
of Ruo Shui Kingdom,)
(the fighter's descendant.)
(He has a pure heart
but acts impulsively.)
(He's the typical straight guy
who thinks straightforwardly.)
It's open.
This is against the rules.
It's the young general Song.
But Your Majesty,
this way of opening...
This setting of sudden spotlight.
Does it mean...
Maidservant Hai,
you only said to open it.
But you didn't say how.
Then...
The winner of the second round
is the young general Song.
Why is it him?
It doesn't make any sense.
Did he do it on purpose?
Xiao Ai,
who is he?
Song Che, the son of general Song.
He has been the childhood
sweetheart with you
since young.
The, why didn't he show up until now?
Princess,
Song Che has been practicing
martial art since young.
When he was 12,
he went to the wars with general Song.
He went to Nan Cang to settle
down rebellion one year ago.
Maybe,
he heard that you brought
forward the marriage competition.
So, he hurried back.
I heard that
it took him 4 horses
to hurry back here.
I knew that
you are very good at digging things out.
But this is very detailed.
It's okay.
This setting
is powerful,
affectionate,
with entrepreneur spirit,
ability to protect me
and decent mindset.
He is also kind of stupid.
My white horse prince.
(It seems that she won't
compete with me now.)
The third round is on talent.
Please draw two princesses.
Sister,
if you push a little more,
I will be out of the picture.
Aren't you trying to gain attention
by wearing like this today?
I'm trying to gain attention?
If you want,
you can show your legs off.
No, I won't.
Ignorant.
Drawing time is over.
Please show your works.
I...
I didn't do it on purpose.
It's good that
my clothes didn't get dirty.
Such a squeamish person.
What's this?
In this round,
the 5th prince of Cang Yun Kingdom
scores 0 point.
The winner is the 7th
prince of Wu Ze Kingdom.
It shouldn't be.
Xiao Ai,
does it have to be like this?
The rule is like that.
Please bear with it.
But this it too...
Princess,
you think this is too loose, right?
Wait a second, no.
It's ok now, princess.
Please take care.
I will leave for now.
Leave?
Is this actually my close maid?
(Jiang Mengmeng's Route)
Based on the scoring of
the first three rounds,
there are 8 princes in total
who might enter the last round.
This round is on courage,
in which the hero shall save the beauty.
Princes must move
forward from all the traps in the forest
and save the princess before darkness.
the 4th princess is on your left
and the 9th princess
is on your right.
You can decide on your own
which princess you want to save.
The competition starts now.
Go away.
Quickly, this way.
This way, that way, this way, that way.
Ride a horse and go to a war.
Where should I go?
Well, I will choose this way.
It's good that I prepared early.
Mengmeng, wait for me.
I'm coming.
Are you scaring me?
Let me tell you.
Don't blame me for cheating.
What kind of garbage game is this?
So hard to find the hero.
I finally determined
who my true love is.
I won't let him run away.
How come these are all the same?
How is it?
Soon.
Why are my shoes dirty?
My hairstyle is messed up.
It's been five times already.
Five times.
It's still early anyway.
I'm starving.
Time for a snack.
He's been so lucky along the way here.
Such a pity.
Giving up right before the success.
He has no sense of direction,
and he is so lazy.
(Your highness, how about that
marriage competition?)
(I cannot win that competition.)
(But I must lose with dignity.)
- Let's go.
- Go.
It's so good.
(Jiang Sisi's Route)
Murong Chen.
It must be Murong Chen.
How come it's you?
Of course it's me.
My beautiful princess.
I'm here to save you.
How come you are still so clean
after going through all those traps?
This is not important.
Don't worry, my princess.
I will save you right now.
Please.
I have been liking you for a while.
Today, I come to Ruo Shui Kingdom
also for you.
I didn't expect that
you are even prettier
than what the hearsay says.
We are really a heaven-made match.
We are meant to be together.
But,
since we are husband and wife now,
there are some things that
I would like to discuss first.
After we get married,
I hope that during each new year,
you can follow me
to Wu Ze Kingdom on January 1st.
I will then come bake to
Ruo Shui Kingdom with you on the 3rd.
How do you like that?
You can't even talk clearly
and you wish to marry me?
Where is Murong Chen?
How come there's no man?
Am I so unattractive?
Song Che.
Who is it?
I heard someone calling me just now.
It must be Mengmeng.
Mengmeng,
I'm coming.
Mengmeng.
Am I still late after all?
Sisi,
why are you back by yourself?
Where are the princes?
Mr. System,
why do I have to be tortured by the game
without fighting back a little?
Are you trying to kill me
with such a huge pit?
Ah right, Song Che.
Song Che, I'm here
in the pit!
Help!
Help...
Is somebody here?
Anybody here?
Help.
I'm the 9th princess of
Ruo Shui Kingdom.
I'm in danger.
It's me.
You kept such a low
voice calling for help.
If my hearing is not as clear as it is,
I would've just gone.
Since you are here now,
help me.
Why would I help you?
Never mind then.
When you go out
and see sister queen,
she will ask you that,
the 5th prince,
why are you by yourself?
Where is the 9th princess?
And you will tell her like this.
The 9th princess?
I saw that she was lying
under the pit.
I just ignored her
and came back on my own.
Say that.
Good point.
Try harder.
Up.
What?
You are too heavy.
I can't pull you out.
You didn't try hard.
How about this.
Step on that wall
and climb up hard.
Try to climb up.
Don't go down.
How come this cirrus was broken?
I'm also wondering.
Is it because you are too heavy?
Am I heavy?
Why are you so bad
at making a conversation?
You didn't even say sorry last time.
Why don't you tell me you're sorry?
I…
You…
Forget it.
I'm not angry. I'm not angry
Think about how to get out.
Come here.
Do you know lightness skill?
Why didn't you say it earlier?
You didn't ask.
Ok.
We go our separate ways.
What happened to your leg?
Twist in the pit.
Is it funny to you?
Get on my back.
You don't even say sorry.
What are you doing?
- You put me down!
- Mengmeng.
Mengmeng, Mengmeng!
Where's Mengmeng?
Isn't Mengmeng saved?
Isn't Mengmeng saved by you?
Me?
We've been waiting here.
We didn't see the 9th princess.
Seven noble sons
have made their way out.
Then, in the woods are
- The 9th princess and Murong Chen?
- Mengmeng and Murong Chen?
Sister queen.
You're so heavy.
Put me down.
- Mengmeng.
- What are you doing?
Mengmeng, are you hurt?
Kind of. It's okay.
Congratulations to the 5th
prince for passing the final test
and becoming
the emperor's 9th son-in-law.
(Ling Xi Palace)
Your Highness, Xiao AI has been with you
for seven years.
I didn't expect you
to get married so soon.
I'll take you with me
if I get married.
But if you
marry the 5th prince,
your long-cherished wish to
leave the palace will be dashed.
Leave the palace?
Before,
you always wanted to
live outside the palace.
You also said that one day
you would make a living
wandering from place to place with me.
I didn't expect that
I was a princess with a story.
By the way, Xiao Ai.
Do you know why I yearned
for the outside world so much?
Is it because
something happened to me before?
I don't know.
She even has anti spoiler function.
Mr. System,
you are so clever!
Now there are two love storylines
for me to choose.
One is with Song Che,
my childhood sweetheart.
The other one is with Murong Chen,
whom I may fall in love with
after we get married, I guess.
I can't make a choice
between the two.
I want to list their
strengths and weaknesses,
and make a comparison.
I will go with the
strengths of Song Che first.
You have to tell me his weaknesses.
General Song goes to the wars
quite often.
No wonder there will be few days
for him to be at home in the future.
And general Song is only good at
fighting and practicing martial arts.
He has no other hobbies.
He is old-fashioned and boring,
and lacks a sense of romance.
Straight man.
Murong Chen.
He has many weaknesses.
I'll go with his weaknesses first.
About the 5th prince,
I heard that
he seldomly attended school
or practiced martial arts
since he was 13.
So, he knows nothing about
poetry and prose,
and his martial arts are mediocre.
He never cares about the national life
or shares political affairs.
Instead, he is proficient in
eating, drinking and playing.
He lives
a luxurious and dissipated life,
spends money like water,
and does each luxury imaginable.
He is narcissistic
and has got this fixation
with cleanliness.
He focuses on
wear and dress every day.
He has little ability to
take care of himself.
He also has no sense of direction.
If there is no entourage around,
he can't even find his way home.
He always talks in an unpleasant way.
He is so mean that,
from the elderly aged 80
to babies aged 8 months,
anybody can be made cry by him.
That's right.
Does he have any strengths?
Good looking.
Good family background.
Nothing else?
Nothing else.
That's all?
Is he really that bad?
(Murong Yi.)
(Semi-paralysed prince, Murong Yi)
(Prince of Cang Yun Kingdom,)
(Murong Chen's favorite)
(and trusted elder brother)
(who was poisoned by Jing Yue Sect
nine years ago)
and thus became partly paralyzed.
(The 3rd prince became the fiance
of the 9th princess, Jiang Mengmeng)
Chen
has become the emperor's 9th son-in-law
of the Ruo Shui Kingdom.
Chen, you disguise yourself as
(Eastern Palace of Cang Yun Kingdom)
an ignorant dandy.
It's all for me
and for this country.
But these responsibilities should
not have been borne by you.
Your natural freedom
should not be bound by responsibility.
Chen.
You promise me.
If there is any chance that
you can find a life you like outside,
just take it
and never come back.
Bro.
You are my world.
All I want is
to make you stand up again.
It has been nine years.
I have no hope for myself.
Bro.
I won't give up.
I won't stay in the Ruo Shui Kingdom.
As soon as I find
the blood night-blooming cereus
and the medical supplement,
I will try my best to come back.
Wait for me.
(Liu Guang Palace)
You found him?
Yes, I did.
He changed his name and identity.
Now, he is named Zhao Qian.
He often mingles in Baiji Tavern
on Jinxiu street.
Keep an eye on him.
Do not act rashly
and alert him.
Your Highness.
About the engagement
what's your plan?
Whether I can find
the blood night-blooming cereus
in Ruo Shui Kingdom or not,
I will definitely find a way to
break off the engagement.
(The General's Mansion)
I'm afraid I will be away
for a year or two.
It will be the time
for you to choose a worthy husband then.
Two years later,
I will be eighteen years old.
It is almost the time.
Why don't you choose me
as your husband then?
Haven't you always wanted
to leave the palace
and live a free life?
My mother died early.
My dad spends his life
defending the frontier.
I'm the only child.
And I don't have any relatives.
So, after we get married,
you can do whatever you want.
No one can stop you.
That is true.
- So, is it a deal?
- Yes.
I will for sure come back for
your marriage competition.
Wait for me.
Okay.
(Song Che, young, handsome
and enterprising)
Your Highness,
are you sure to do this?
Now the only person who
can stop this marriage
is Song Che.
He almost fell out with his dad
in order to catch the marriage
competition for the 9th princess.
He even shortened the 10-day trip
to 3 days.
He hurried all the way back to
the town without food or drink.
With such affection,
I don't believe that he would
let any other man marry her.
If I tell him the fact that
the 9th princess lost her memory,
it for sure will stimulate him
to damage this marriage.
Let's go.
(Murong Chen, indifferent to
national life and government affairs)
Since it's decided,
let's not think too much.
Why did she come here?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Didn't she lose all her memory
and forget about everything?
Look at that flirting face.
Her mouth water almost came out.
Your Highness,
this is good.
For what?
Think about it.
Since the 9th princess came on her own,
we don't have to show up.
Dong Kui,
let's go.
Mengmeng,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
Mengmeng,
I'm sorry.
I failed
to keep my promise to you.
What promise?
You don't remember?
I injured my head a while ago
when I sneaked out from the palace.
I forgot everything.
I see.
But I heard from Xiao Ai
that we grew up together,
and that you struggled really hard to
come to the marriage competition for me.
But I broke the promise.
I promised you to
win the marriage competition.
Then, I can take you out of the palace
and live a free life.
It's not your fault.
On the day...
On the day of the marriage competition,
I untied the rope
to look for you…
Seriously? Mengmeng?
You actually went to look for me?
Yes, I did.
I...
But I fell in a pit.
Don't worry.
I will break off the engagement
for sure.
I'm not going to be with Murong Chen.
Let's go live our free life together.
Xiao Ai.
Tell me.
If I want to break off the engagement,
what should I do?
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪