Previously on AMC's The Walking Dead....
Everyone! Get into your houses!
Go!
My friend's
are in there.
My pregnant wife.
No!
Argh!
Ugh!
No!
You're not gonna
make it out there.
We'll see.
We're gonna
gut these things.
It'll mask our smell.
Make 'em think we're like them.
Stay calm.
Don't draw attention.
- We can move right through 'em.
- Mom.
Why don't you come on out,
join us in the road?
That's great.
It's going well
right out of the gate.
Now, step two,
hand over your weapons.
- Why should we?
- Well, they're not yours.
Whose are they?
Your property
now belongs to Negan.
And if you can get your
hands on a tanker,
you're people our person
wants to know.
So let's get those
sidearms, shall we?
Right now.
Thank you.
If you have to eat shit,
best not to nibble.
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.
It goes quicker.
Thank you.
Who are you people?
I get the curiosity,
but we have questions ourselves.
And we'll be
the ones asking them
while we drive you back to
wherever it is you call home.
Take a gander at where
you hang your hats.
First, though, your shit.
What have you got for us?
Yeah, you just took it.
Come on.
I mean, can we not, okay?
There's more.
There is always more.
T...
take my man to the back
of the truck,
start inside the back bumper,
work your way to the front.
Go.
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.
Who's Negan?
♪ Ding, dong ♪
♪ Hell's bells. ♪
You see, usually
we introduce ourselves
by just popping one of you
right off the bat.
But you seem like
reasonable people.
I mean, you're sportin' dress
blues, for Christ's sake.
And, like I said, we're gonna
drive you back to where you were.
I mean, do you know
how awkward it is
carpooling with someone whose friend
or friends you've just killed?
Oof.
But I told you
not to ask any questions.
And then what does
this ginger do?
So that's that.
I don't want you to get
the wrong impression of me.
Wait.
You don't have to do this.
Shut up.
I am talking to the man.
No, you're not.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Wait, wait.
You know what?
Yes, I am.
Son of a bitch
was tougher than he looked.
- Did he cut you?
- A little.
What a bunch of assholes.
Let's get you fixed up at home.
Yes, ma'am.
Nibble on that.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
All right, new plan.
Flares from a few guns
aren't enough.
Too many walkers,
too spread out.
We're not going to the armory.
We need our vehicles
back at the quarry.
All of us drive.
We'll need to round 'em up.
We leave, we come back.
Okay.
But Judith...
to the quarry and back, I...
I'll take her.
Keep her safe in my church
until you all lead
the walkers away.
Can you do this?
I'm supposed to.
I have to.
I will.
All right.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh...
- Take Sam.
- No.
Yes, Sam, it'll be safer.
I'm not leaving you.
- Sam--
- Mom, I'm not.
I can keep going.
- Sam--
- I can keep going.
Please.
Let's just go.
Okay.
I'm going to keep her safe.
Thank you.
Shh, shh, shh...
Hey.
He's gonna make it.
Okay?
I know it.
Sam.
We have to try.
We cannot go out there.
There are too many of them.
Rosita, he's gonna kill her.
We won't get to her.
She needs us.
We'll die.
That is what will happen.
We have one gun,
and the streets are filled
with those things.
That man needs her.
Okay?
She's a doctor. He is sick.
And I think we've seen
that he knows how to survive.
But we need to make sure
that Carol and Morgan are okay
and then we make a plan.
We cannot just go.
Okay.
Oh, God.
Rosita, gonna need your gun.
Gonna do a sweep
of the brownstone.
I want to see what other
surprises are in here.
Hey, he's waking up.
Easy.
Where is he?
Where's Denise?
He took her, didn't he?
Let's get you up.
Maybe when they searched this
place, they missed something.
Depends if it was Aiden or Heath's
group who went through it.
Easy.
Look in the Bibles, too.
Could've hollowed out the pages.
Are you serious?
We have two bullets.
People holed up in here--
people hide guns, ammo.
Maybe something to start a fire.
It's getting dark out soon.
Maybe we can distract them.
We need sheets,
ropes, towels--
anything Maggie can use
to climb down the other side.
How things turn.
Enid.
When I wanted to run...
you said, "That's
how you lose people...
even after they're gone."
What the hell does that mean?
People you love...
they made you who you are.
They're still part of you.
If you stop being you,
that last bit of them that's still
around inside, who you are...
it's gone.
Who are those people to you?
My parents.
A man named Dale.
Maggie's father, Hershel.
A woman named Andrea.
A man named Tyreese.
Who are they to you?
My parents.
Then they're still here...
'cause you're still here.
When there's an opening, we'll
make a break for that tower.
Hmm?
No, I'll just slow you down.
Denise.
Denise, you're here...
with me.
I need you.
Maybe I want you to stay
'cause I'm enjoying
your company so much.
I want you to stay put.
What?
I wanted you to come back.
I can handle myself.
You said you wanted help.
No, I didn't want you
to give up on this place,
on these people, to be afraid.
You were right.
So I'm here now.
And I'm going out there
and I'm helping you.
We have to get her
off that platform.
She's hurt.
She needs help getting over the wall.
I can climb up the gate.
You can distract them.
We do it together.
I'm just gonna follow you, anyway.
You keep looking
for the Bible Glock...
I'll make her something
to climb down.
Okay.
I like what you said before.
That I wasn't born this way.
You're right.
I changed.
And now I want
to help you change.
Hey.
You were right.
Let's get Maggie.
Can't you just stay here?
Nope.
You've been given
a gift, Denise.
You'll see that one day.
Or maybe you won't.
The monsters will come,
and you won't be able to run
away when they come for you.
The ones out there.
And they will tear you apart
and eat you up
all while you're still alive.
Sam?
Come on, come on.
- Sweetheart? Sam?
- You can do it.
- Yes, you can.
Sam.
Sam, come on.
- Come on, Sam.
- Sam.
- Sam?
- Sam...
hey, you can do this.
Sam, just look at Mom.
Honey, you can do it.
Sam, you're gonna get--
Sam, honey, I need you to come with me.
- Sam.
- I need you to come with me.
- I want to.
- I need you to be strong.
Sam--
Mom!
- Jessie?
- Jessie. Jessie.
- No.
Come with us.
Come on.
We have to go.
No.
Dad.
Come on.
You.
Dad?
Carl.
No.
Sooner or later,
we're fighting our way out.
I know that you're
fully aware that we will.
Yeah...
we will.
Not you.
- Well, by my reckoning--
- Eugene.
Come on.
They're moving
towards the gunfire.
That shout.
I suppose someone thought
they could put up a fight.
I guess you all thought that.
We did put up a fight.
That's why
your friends are dead.
Yeah.
We should've waited
and watched a little longer.
I was selfish.
But maybe if I
wasn't so selfish,
I wouldn't have got that IV.
We're gonna find a gap and go.
Up that guard tower
and over the wall.
You don't need to be afraid.
Go to hell.
You need to know
it's safer out there
than it is in here.
Start moving.
Now, straight up that guard post
and do not stop.
Go.
Shit!
Let's go.
Come with me, now.
You get me to the infirmary,
I save your life.
I'll save your life.
You had a child.
Right?
A husband?
I didn't want to hurt you,
I just had to stop you.
You saved him for you, not us.
If it was for us,
you would've...
I should've killed you.
I should've.
You can't.
The infirmary's
right across the alley.
We need to get you there now.
Hey!
The ladder was clear.
Could've made it.
You turned back for me.
Maybe it was because
you needed a doctor,
or maybe you changed.
You ready?
Come on!
Go! Go!
Go!
Come on, come on.
You okay?
I'm fine.
How are my patients?
They're doing well.
We moved them upstairs just in case.
Oh, my God.
It's the kid.
Is he bit?
Nope.
What?
I need bandages.
Top shelf, next to the sink.
Two IVs from the fridge and all
the clean towels you can find.
Aaron, grab the gurney.
This is a gunshot?
Handgun. Close range.
Please save him.
Please.
That's gonna draw them here.
I need light.
Michonne, towel.
Hold it here.
Okay, we need to keep
pressure on the wound.
I'll go in and sew up
any lacerations.
Just like that, right here.
Now, Spencer, I need that pan.
That one on the tray.
Good.
I'm going to clean
and close this.
Michonne, keep following me
with the towel.
What-- what are you doing?
Rick!
- Rick's out there.
- Hold on.
- He needs my help.
- Just one more suture.
But he's out there.
This is his son.
Give me a second.
He's taking them all on.
- We have to go get him.
- What?
We have to.
- This is it.
- Okay, got it.
Knock 'em away.
Drive 'em down.
We can beat 'em.
We can beat 'em!
Drive 'em back. That's it.
We can do this together!
Will you take her?
Of course.
Come with me.
Okay, okay.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
Gabriel.
What are you doing?
We've been praying...
together.
Praying that God
will save our town.
Well, our prayers
have been answered.
God will save Alexandria...
because God has given us the
courage to save it ourselves.
Guys, it's thinning
out there in front.
We need to get out there.
Rick's making a stand.
How's that?
He's out there fighting them
with Michonne and some others.
It's time.
Up the alley.
I'm going.
Denise is safe.
Did you see her?
Yeah, she made it
to the infirmary.
- I'm gonna go help Rick.
- I'm going, too.
- I'm with you.
- All right, me, too.
- Right behind you.
- Eugene, you don't have to.
That's incorrect.
I do.
No one gets to clock out today.
And, hell, this is a story
people are gonna tell.
This way!
Come on!
I'm sorry.
No.
Go get her!
Hey!
Over here!
Come on, here!
- Over here!
- Glenn!
No! Glenn!
- Come on! Over here, come on!
Maggie!
Enid!
Over here!
Over here, come on.
Come on!
Just go!
Just get over!
- Go!
- No!
Go!
Come on!
Shit.
- No, Glenn!
- Go!
Over here!
Glenn!
Can you get the gate?
Appreciate it, pal.
Come on, we got you.
What the hell happened?
I don't know.
I just got back.
Listen...
we can-- we can lead
some of them away,
but they're scattered.
No, we get 'em all together.
Won't have to lead 'em away.
Move it!
Back up!
All right, that's it!
Don't let up!
I was wrong.
I thought after living behind
these walls for so long that...
maybe they couldn't learn.
But today...
I saw what they could do,
what we could do,
if we work together.
We'll rebuild the walls.
We'll expand the walls.
There will be more.
There's gotta be more.
Everything Deanna
was talking about...
is possible.
It's all possible.
I see that now.
When I was out there...
with them...
when it was over...
when I knew
we had this place again...
I had this feeling.
It took me a while
to remember what it was...
because I haven't felt it
since before I woke up
in that hospital bed.
I want to show you the new world, Carl.
I want to make it
a reality for you.
Please, Carl...
let me show you.
Plea-- please, son,
don't die.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com