Previously on
AMC's "The Walking Dead..."
You're well-equipped,
but your provisions are low.
I'm from a place that's
a lot like this one.
We might be in a position
to help each other.
This is Gregory.
I'm the boss.
They still have Craig.
Negan?
They said they'd
return him to us,
if I delivered a message to you.
You give us supplies,
we'll save Craig and take care
of Negan and the Saviors.
Done.
We need to know what you
know about Negan's compound.
We need you to come.
It's gonna be a fight.
We'll win. We have to.
- Hey, Carol.
- Tobin.
You deserve some cookies.
Oh, no, not with
the kids as hungry--
No, there's plenty.
I foraged a lot of acorns.
- They're pink.
- Beets.
- Beets?
- It's what makes them sweet.
Oh.
I never was much
of a beet kind of guy.
Will you just put it
in your mouth, jerk.
They're the best beet and acorn
cookies I've ever eaten.
Are you screwing with me?
No.
Seriously.
They're amazing.
They're back!
- Get Olivia.
She should inventory
what we have.
We'll meet her at the pantry.
- You have food?
- Yeah.
Enough for another month.
I need everybody in
the church in an hour.
What is it?
We'll talk about it.
Rick, what's going on?
We're gonna have to fight.
It's been a while.
Weeks.
- Since what?
- Since we talked.
That's what we did in that cell?
We talked.
Why didn't you tell Rick?
Tara, Rosita, Eugene?
- Why didn't they...?
- I told them to keep quiet about it.
Why?
Can we just forget it,
move past it?
You don't have to carry that.
Carry what?
You know what I did.
You don't want
to tell anyone, it--
it's kind of like
you did it, too.
No, it's not.
Just go.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
And we can work
with the Hilltop.
Maggie hammered out a deal.
We're getting food--
eggs, butter, fresh vegetables.
But they're not
just giving it away.
These Saviors,
they almost killed Sasha,
Daryl, and Abraham on the road.
Now, sooner or later,
they would've found us,
just like those Wolves did,
just like Jesus did.
They woulda killed someone
or some of us.
And then they
would try to own us.
And we would try to stop them.
But by then,
in that kind of fight,
low on food, we could lose.
This is the only way to be sure,
as sure as we can get,
that we win.
And we have to win.
We do this for the Hilltop,
it's how we keep this place.
It's how we feed this place.
This needs to be
a group decision.
If anybody objects, here's
your chance to say your piece.
You're sure we can do it?
We can beat them?
What this group has done,
what we've learned,
what we've become,
all of us--
yes, I'm sure.
Then all we have to do
is just tell them that.
Well, they don't compromise.
This isn't a compromise.
It's a choice you give them.
It's a way out,
for them and for us.
We try and
talk to the Saviors,
we give up our advantage,
our safety.
No, we have to come for them
before they come for us.
We can't leave them alive.
Where there's life,
there's possibility.
Of them hitting us.
We're not trapped in this.
None of you are trapped in this.
Morgan...
they always come back.
Come back
when they're dead, too.
Yeah, we'll stop them.
We have before.
I'm not talking
about the walkers.
Morgan wants
to talk to them first.
I think that would be a mistake,
but it's not up to me.
I'll talk to the people
still at home.
I'll discuss it
with the people on guard now, too,
but who else wants to approach
the Saviors, talk to them first?
What happened here,
we won't let that happen again.
I won't.
Looks like it's settled.
We know exactly what this is.
We don't shy from it, we live.
We kill them all.
We don't all have to kill.
But if people
are gonna stay here...
they do have to accept it.
We need someone on the
perimeter keeping watch.
That could be me.
That would be safe.
Safer.
Whatever safer looks like now.
Yeah.
I made that deal.
It wasn't my idea,
but I led us into this.
I have to come.
Those things'll kill you.
You got another one?
Not for you.
And why is that?
'Cause, asshole.
Okay.
Couldn't sleep either?
I never could sleep.
Worried about tomorrow.
You going?
No.
You are.
You can
do things that--
that just terrify me.
How?
How do you think
I do those things?
You're a mom.
I was.
You are.
It-- it--
it's not the cookies
or the smiles.
It's--
it's the hard stuff.
The scary stuff.
It's how you can do it.
It's strength.
You're a mom to most
of the people here.
To you, too?
No.
You're something else to me.
Well, it's not tomorrow yet.
Packing your stilettos?
We'll only be gone a night.
I'm going.
I am, too, but tomorrow.
I'm leaving.
Why?
It happens.
Are you serious?
This is how I want it.
- Why?
- Why are dingleberries brown?
It's just the way shit is.
No, no. After everything
we've been through,
you are not walking out that
door unless you can tell me why.
Tell me!
Tell me why!
When I first met you,
I thought you were
the last woman on Earth.
You're not.
You try one of these?
They're chewy.
They, uh...
got some fight in them.
Describe it.
Rectangular building,
big satellites on it.
- Rick: Any windows?
- I don't remember any.
I think they made it
so there's only one way in.
Guards outside?
Yeah, two of them, at least.
And you don't know
how many people they have?
No.
Uh, I mean, no. I saw a place
where they stored food.
It wasn't that big, so...
- Rick: You've been inside?
- Yeah.
They had us load in
supplies one time.
Hmm.
What do you remember?
Are you worried?
No.
No, it's just...
I love you, and I just
wanted to say it before--
you don't have to say it back.
It's--
I'll say it when you come back.
Heath and I are still
going on that two-weeker.
We're gonna leave from there.
Do you want to come?
I mean, I can change it so we
don't leave from the compound.
We could come back and we
could leave from here.
- You know, we're gonna get meds, so...
- I can't.
- No, I didn't-- I'm-- I just-- I need to be here.
- Yeah.
I'm the only doctor now.
So I can't.
Yeah.
But I want to.
I'll tell you
when you come back.
Yeah.
And you didn't
see any other rooms?
No, it's a big place.
This is the hallway I saw.
There is more.
And every time, they had you
bring things into here?
Jesus.
We brought a couple
spears for them.
Two of the Saviors took
them down this hallway.
Now, they must've
done something with them
because they didn't
come back with them.
Maybe a weapons
locker, an armory.
Okay.
We get in there,
secure the armory,
that's how we end it.
That's how Carol ended it here.
But we don't know if they have
an armory or where it even is.
Well, we've got
a lot of good guesses.
We've done more with less.
We go in at night
while they're sleeping.
The guards won't be sleeping.
Like I said, I think
there's only one way in
and there's no way
to bust through that door
without waking up
the rest of them.
We don't need to.
They're going to open it for
us, let us walk right in.
They want Gregory's head, right?
We're gonna give it to them.
Aaron, Rosita.
You start here.
We'll peel off
every quarter mile,
meet back here
in a couple of hours.
See what we got.
There's no turning back now.
I could walk.
Maybe run a little, maybe a lot.
I'm not going anywhere.
I wanted to learn and you
taught me for a reason.
Why are you still wearing that?
It's still who I was.
I think.
And it'll be harder for
them to see me in the dark.
I almost told everyone
at the meeting.
We're not telling them.
Morgan stood up in that church and
tried to talk us out of this.
What's wrong with that?
Maybe that he didn't know what
the hell he's talking about?
That he should take the win
that we didn't kick his ass out
for hiding that psychopath.
If we told everyone, they'd find
out about Denise, you know that.
That hijo de puta
tried to stand there
and act like we didn't
know what we were--
He doesn't want to kill.
We don't want to kill.
We don't like it.
It happens.
I'm not telling anyone.
What do you think?
Maybe.
If we, um, cut the hair...
trim the beard.
If it's dark.
We're gonna kill those people.
Tonight.
Look, I've been lucky.
I haven't had to do it before.
Have you?
I've been lucky, too.
You nervous?
Have you ever seen
something that, um...
afterwards, you--
you didn't want to sleep
and you weren't hungry because
when you close your eyes
you could see it?
- And when you try to eat--
- Yeah.
Me, too.
Killing somebody has gotta
be worse than that.
It has to be.
So, yeah...
I'm nervous.
For the whole thing, man.
For the whole thing.
We're gonna
take a look around,
try to get a feel for how
many people are in there.
We like how it looks, we go in.
A couple of hours before dawn.
The guards outside'll be tired.
Everyone inside'll be sleeping.
We don't like what we see, we
head back, make a new plan.
They don't know who we are.
We'll keep Jesus in the shadows.
This is how we eat.
We roll out at midnight.
Why is Maggie here?
She's guarding the perimeter.
Yeah, but why is she here?
'Cause it's her choice.
I want to stay
out there with her.
Well, this whole thing's
a race to the armory.
We need as many people
inside as we can get.
She shouldn't
be out there alone.
She shouldn't be out here
in the first place.
Okay.
Good.
She's done with the hair?
What've we got?
- That one.
- Yeah, that's it.
All right.
Though, it's probably good
we're doing this at night.
Something wrong with it?
The nose. Gregory's
is a different shape.
He fought back.
He broke your hand, right?
Guess there's no reason
to be subtle about it.
What?
The Saviors, they're scary,
but those pricks
got nothing on you.
Stop right there!
Announce yourself, asshole!
It's Eddie from Hilltop!
It's done!
Step out!
Is that it?
Yeah!
Bring it here, shit brain!
I don't want the bag,
needle dick.
Will you look at this shit?
He broke my hand.
I broke his nose.
That's why he looks that way.
Little bitch broke my nose.
- - Wah.
Okay, looks like you learned.
I'll get your guy,
you'll go home,
and you bring us more
stuff next week, hmm?
Well, well, well.
Look who it is.
- Ahh!
- It's okay, it's okay.
We're bringing you back.
Check the doors.
Find the arsenal.
We take them out.
You still a priest?
Rick and Carl
taught me about guns,
other weapons.
How to contribute.
I'm still a priest.
I lied to my girlfriend
this morning.
I, um-- she caught me
thinking about something,
so I told her that I loved her.
For the first time.
That's how I told her,
covering something up.
What were you covering?
That I'd done something
like this before.
That I didn't like it.
Do you?
Do you love her?
Yeah.
So, you know what
you're fighting for.
Hmm.
Honeypot.
They're in trouble.
Stay here.
- I'm going with you.
- I said stay here.
No.
Damn it, Maggie.
- I have to.
- No, you don't. You don't have to.
Yes, I do.
What the hell
are you doing here?
What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed
to be someone else.
They need our help.
You are staying here.
We need to go. Get them
back to the Hilltop.
What? Your people
could be in trouble.
If you get them back,
the deal's still on, right?
Right?
If they get themselves back.
Andy, drive him
back to the Hilltop.
Look, if they see you
and we don't make it--
We're gonna make it. And
they're not gonna see me.
Are you kidding?
Go!
Ah!
If it wasn't us,
it was gonna be you.
The hell?
That's one of the locked ones.
I'm gonna cover you. Do it.
Come on!
So, this is the next world.
Drop it.
You, uh--
you gonna kill me, Padre?
Padre?
"Let not your heart
be troubled."
You're just as dead as me.
"In my father's house
are many mansions.
If it were not so,
I would've told you."
You're all dead.
- "I go prepare a place for you."
- Blood's coming.
Amen.
Hey, you want to just
come back with us?
Take a couple days before
you and Tara go out again?
No, man. I just want
to get out of here.
What is it?
Just--
just want to know which
one of them was Negan.
Son of a bitch!
Where'd you get the bike?
Just do it!
Like you did
everyone else, right?
Lower your gun, prick.
You, with the Colt Python.
All of you, lower your
weapons right now.
Come on out.
Let's talk.
We're not coming
out, but we will talk.
We've got a
Carol and a Maggie.
I'm thinking that's something
you want to chat about.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com