Previously on
AMC's The Walking Dead
I know you're scared.
The wall's going
to hold together.
Can you?
I don't get to
know what will happen.
I have to live with that.
The others,
they're gonna be back.
They're gonna be back.
So you wanna just
leave her out there?
She's your friend.
My girlfriend.
I mean 'cause she
was anyway, right?
You have to protect everyone...
...to create peace.
Thank you.
Hey, heads up!
Shit.
I said heads up.
Enid?
Enid.
What are you doing out here?
There's another water
bottle in the corner.
Take it and go.
You're not gonna answer me?
No.
What happened in Alexandria?
We heard that sound.
The gunfire.
Enid.
What happened is
what always happens.
People died.
The herd broke
through the walls?
What herd?
The walkers.
They broke out
of the quarry early.
We got on them, but that
sound, the air horn,
what was that?
It was people.
You should go.
My wife,
Maggie,
she okay?
Enid?
Is Maggie okay?
Answer me!
Enid.
Enid!
Hey, Enid!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Morgan.
Morning.
We haven't talked.
We should.
A little later, okay?
Okay.
You don't have to be
up here so much.
I won't be.
This is the direction
he'd come in.
If he sends up a signal,
it'll be from out there.
Yeah.
Or it-- it won't be.
When we go out there,
it's never easy,
it's never simple.
It's always a fight.
But we've come back
from harder things.
From further away.
Glenn, Daryl, Abraham, and
Sasha, they will, too.
Maybe we don't wait
for them to be back.
We should start figuring out
how to draw the walkers away.
We have some food and
water to last us a while
and the walls are holding.
We can take our time.
Really think this through.
Do it right.
Clear it so they can--
they can walk right in.
I saw Judith in the house
the other day.
She's starting to--
she's starting
to look like Lori.
- Yeah.
- Made me happy.
Me, too.
Dad.
Handguns will be a little
better for your first go.
Magazine release.
Slide release.
Thumb safety.
That stuff's easy, right, Dad?
Yeah.
Empty magazine.
- Empty chamber. See it?
- Yeah.
Someone's in front of you,
they have a gun.
You're gonna be scared.
You will be.
Your body's gonna tense,
you won't have time to think.
You're just gonna want to pull the
trigger when you get it in front of you.
But you'll miss
and you'll be dead.
You have to get it
up to your eye.
You've got to be strong enough
to wait for your moment.
Can I, uh...?
Hey, your finger doesn't
touch the trigger
until you're ready to shoot.
Keep that one with you.
Get a feel of what it's
like to carry one around.
Can I shoot it?
Maybe like down at the walkers?
No, with things how they are,
the walls are strong,
but we're lucky the
walkers are spread out.
We don't want to pull
them all to one spot.
Well, what about, like, target
practice in the center of town?
'Cause then the sound will
spread out in each direction.
Or maybe we could use, like,
silencers or something like that.
But, uh...
I mean, we probably don't want
to waste bullets right now, huh?
Just want to learn more.
You will.
Hey.
Sorry.
I was making--
you want some oatmeal?
Thank you.
I'm-- I'm okay.
You were coming to the door.
What's up?
Want me to take
a look at your arm?
No, I'm not here for--
I'm fine.
You can tell me if you're not.
Morgan.
Can we talk now?
Uh-huh.
What's going on?
When I was coming back...
I tried to cut off
the herd with the RV.
Lead the walkers away.
But five of those people with
the Ws in their foreheads,
they stopped me.
They tried to kill me,
shot up the RV.
Now, Carol says she saw you.
That you wouldn't
kill those people.
Did you let any of them go?
Yes, I did.
I didn't want to kill five
people I didn't have to kill.
They burned people alive.
Yeah.
Why didn't you kill me, Rick,
back in King County?
Pulled a knife on you.
I stabbed you.
So why didn't you kill me?
Was it 'cause I saved you
after the hospital?
'Cause I knew who you were.
Back there I would have killed
you as soon as look at you.
And I tried.
But you, you let me live
and then I was there
to help Aaron and Daryl.
See, if I--
if I wasn't there...
if they died...
maybe those wolves wouldn't have
been able to come back here.
I don't know
what's right anymore.
'Cause I did want
to kill those men.
I seen what they did,
what they keep doing.
I knew I could end it.
But I also know
that people can change.
'Cause everyone
sitting here has.
All life is precious.
And that idea--
that idea changed me.
It brought me back
and it keeps me living.
I just don't think
it can be that easy.
- It's not easy.
- I wasn't saying--
I-- I know.
And I've thought about
letting that idea go.
But I don't want to.
You may have to.
Things aren't as simple
as four words.
I don't think they ever were.
Do you think
I don't belong here?
Making it now,
do you really think
you can do that
without getting blood
on your hands?
I don't know.
If we can somehow
get outside the walls,
get back to our cars
at the quarry,
we could use them
to draw them away.
We'll set up more watch points.
Coordinate the shooting
of guns and flares
so we could pull them out
in even directions.
We'd need to get
all our people on it.
Carl, Tara, Rosita, Carol.
What about everybody else?
Well, let's just keep
this to our own for now.
Really?
Look, if we had the time to
bring the people along, sure.
But we haven't had
a chance to catch our breath.
Really?
We're in here together.
We're catching
our breath right now.
Anything else is just excuses.
Deanna.
Rick.
What's that?
Plans for the expansion.
We got a few other things
on our plate right now.
I know.
These are for what Alexandria
can be after this.
Because one way or another,
there's gonna be an after this.
Now, when the blade connects,
don't jerk it right back.
- You'll get stuck.
- Stuck?
Like an ax cutting into a tree.
It's easier to get a blade
into bone than out.
So what should we do?
You should slide the machete
down through the wound.
One fluid motion.
Okay, you ease it through
the bone like this.
All right?
Hey!
I'm a weapons novice holding
a significant blade here
and there are people in my
proximity with open-toed shoes.
That's right.
So get a grip.
What are you so scared of?
That would be dying.
Dying is simple.
It all just stops.
You're dead.
The people around you dying,
that's the hard part.
Okay? 'Cause you keep living
knowing that they're gone
and you're still here.
What you should
be scared of is living
knowing that you didn't do everything
you could to keep them here.
Too upset to keep going?
Are the noises scaring you
or can I get back to my lesson?
Let's try this again.
Shh!
The hell are you doing?
Shh.
I'm taking you home.
I don't know you.
Why did you give me water?
I had it, you needed it.
That doesn't make us friends.
We're not friends.
I'm doing this for Maggie.
Your wife?
She wouldn't leave you behind.
She wouldn't want me
to leave you behind.
So we're going.
I'm not friends
with your wife either.
I'm not having
this conversation.
I'm not leaving you out here.
We're going now.
No.
Give me the gun, Enid.
Turn around and walk away.
You're not gonna
pull the trigger.
I will if you make me.
Let go.
Asshole.
You point a gun at me
and I'm the asshole?
Let's go.
Out the back down the alley.
We're taking the road.
We need visibility.
Why?
Because half the herd broke off
and they're headed towards home.
I guess you missed that.
Lead the way.
You look like
you could use some help.
You know, I think we could build
up a brace on this thing.
What?
Think your wife wouldn't
have wanted me to kill it?
We can use them
to distract them.
There's a helium tank
in those shrubs.
More balloons, more string.
It don't mean anything
as long as we keep this up.
You know, you scared the hell out
of people when we first saw you.
I know.
You scared the hell out of me.
With that beard.
The way you looked around
like you were seeing
things we weren't...
hiding around corners.
Turns out you were.
Things moved slow here.
And then things
just started moving fast.
Too fast.
But don't give up on us.
Who did you stay with back home?
It's not my home.
I lived in Olivia's place.
But I was on my own.
Orphaned by walkers.
Me, too.
Probably.
It's just what happens.
I get that you're scared.
I'm not scared.
Yeah, you are.
You don't want
to lose anything again,
so you give up and you say,
"That's just what happens."
- I don't need a lecture.
-  Yeah, I think you do.
You honor the dead by going on.
Even when you're scared.
You live because
they don't get to.
You think your parents
wanted you
waving around a gun
because you're afraid?
We don't have to talk.
Crap.
My God.
Stop.
I said stop.
What's the point?
The world is trying to die.
We're supposed to just let it.
No.
You're wrong.
We're not supposed
to let the world die.
And I sure as hell
am not gonna let you die.
I'm sure your wife
will forgive you.
It's not for her anymore.
Look, the walls are still up.
The houses are still up.
We'll find out the rest.
Okay?
What the hell?
Spencer.
Hey, Spencer, get back here!
Tara.
Spencer.
Spencer, get back here now.
Spencer, move!
Go! Keep moving!
-  Hurry!
- Eugene...
have Maggie and Rosita fire their
guns out from their posts.
- Why?
- Just do it!
- Tara, I cannot in good conscience--
Spencer, come on!
Grab on!
Tara! You almost died
once for these people.
What?
What the hell were you doing?
Lost a damn shoe.
Crap.
What was that?
I was trying to help. I wanted
to get to a car, draw them away.
You ever make a climb
like that before?
You want to help? Don't make
us come running to save you.
You got an idea, you come to me.
Would you have listened to me?
Everything okay now?
It's handled.
Everything's fine.
Cheat sheets.
Yeah.
Probably doesn't
give you a lot of faith.
I have faith.
Well, you have to, right?
You don't have to.
I choose to.
You should, too.
So are you gonna tell me
why you're here this time?
How well is the community
stocked with antibiotics?
We're good.
I need to dress a wound,
but I don't know
if it's infected.
I don't want to waste
medicine if I don't have to.
FWoPP'RS.
Fever, warmth, pus,
pain, redness...
um...
Tell me what it is.
Swelling.
Let's take a look at your arm.
I didn't come in this morning
because I didn't want to get
you involved in something
that you may not want
to be involved in.
In a secret.
It's not my wound.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I know you just took care
of Judith this morning,
but they want some help
with the watch points
after that thing with Spencer.
Could you...?
Oh, yeah, no problem.
Unless you want me
to take your shift.
No, I like being up there.
Even with all them outside?
You can see everything.
Even inside.
Um, let me just lock these up.
- Can you give me a second?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you want to come in?
- Yeah.
Carol?
Carol.
What, Sam?
Sam?
What happens if you
can't live with it?
I told you, it eats you up.
Can you come down here?
I can barely hear you.
The people who came,
were they the monsters?
Did my dad turn into one?
What?
If you kill people,
do you turn into
one of the monsters?
The only thing that keeps you from
becoming a monster is killing.
- Thank you for this.
- Oh, yeah, no problem.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
Who the hell do you
have in that cell?
Hey, you seen Denise?
No.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
Look, I'm sorry about before.
- I was just--
- He was stupid. That we know.
I just meant what you did for
him, you didn't have to.
I know.
You could have died.
I mean, I'd like to say
I was thinking about it,
but I wasn't.
Is that why you did it?
You weren't thinking about it?
No, that's how it works with us.
We're stuck with
each other, right?
Rick, you saved my son.
Thank you.
Thank Tara.
I already did.
Now I'm thanking you.
What Spencer did was stupid.
I can't argue that.
- At least he tried.
- That's not the point.
I could have tried.
There was a chance.
How's that?
When the walkers were going
for him, it made a gap.
I could have jumped down,
ran, made it out.
I could have got in a car,
used it to lead
the walkers away.
I could have done that
and Spencer would be dead.
But you didn't do that.
Why?
I helped save him
because he's your son.
Wrong answer.
That's Glenn.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com