=City of Streamer=
=Episode 18=
You kicked Qingzhi out of the house.
Wasn't it for the sake of Jiaxin,
I'd fallen out with you.
And what about now?
Are you destroying the Rongs' name?
I... I... I'm not.
I... I...
Don't say one more word!
From now on,
we two families don't know each other!
Hi, Zhihui.
Mrs. Rong yelled at Mother
on the phone just now
and threatened to cut all ties with you.
What were you thinking
seducing her husband?
Your aunt
is the only rich person we know.
I meant to get a job
at her husband's company through her.
That's never going to happen now.
Look what you've done.
Who in their right mind
would marry a slut like you?
Don't listen to him, Zhihui.
I've checked with that loan shark.
That hillbilly
doesn't mind.
You can still be his wife.
I'm not going to marry him.
You...
Here's five thousand
to pay off your debts.
From now on,
we're even.
Zhihui,
Mr. Rong gave you
more than that, didn't he?
You're young and naive.
Men out there
are coveting your money.
Once they get it,
they'll go back to marry virgins.
It's not safe to keep such a fortune.
Let me handle it for you.
Yes. Give it to me.
I'll keep it for you
in case you get scammed.
It's all I've got.
Should I give it to you
or your wife?
Give it to me. I'm your elder brother.
Over my dead body!
You're a loser!
How much have we lost because of you?
How dare you call me a loser!
I'm warning you!
I can kick you out!
Kick me out?
Sure, if you don't want your baby.
Without me,
who'd cook for you
and look after your children?
I'm sick of you
gussying yourself up every day.
Who is it for?
What?
All I've had is the cheapest clothes
since we got married.
What could I do with them?
Say it!
Now, you're silent.
I should keep the money.
Give it to me!
It's too much
for a girl her age.
(To Mother)
That girl is really something.
She's bold
and hard-hearted.
After such a huge scandal,
even if it weren't her fault,
it'd be impossible
to marry a decent man in the city.
The best option would be
to take shelter in another city
and marry a stranger quickly.
In terms of women,
nothing is more important than
marrying a good man and having a son
when we're still young and pretty.
Things like ambition
and love
are young girls' privilege.
The older
and wrinklier we get,
the less
men care about us.
At the end of the day,
sons are our only hope,
don't you agree, Miss Feng?
You're young,
attractive
and well-respected
as a governess.
You have nothing to worry about,
especially
when your brother is unmarried himself.
Is Dr. Feng seeing anyone at the moment?
Not that I know of.
Nurses, patients and their family
at the hospital
all seem to like him, though.
He's always popular among girls.
So no worries there.
Still, he needs to be careful
so that he won't be fooled.
Miss Feng, you're unsophisticated.
Some women
would do anything to get married.
They'd act all kind
and understanding before marriage.
After getting married,
they'd call their husbands useless
and unmarried sisters-in-law a burden
or not want to pay for their dowries.
Is that you, Concubine Sun?
I just heard Jiakang crying.
Go take care of your son.
Yes.
Ma'am.
Mm.
Miss Feng,
see you.
Sit back.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Clearly, she's Rong Dingkun's type.
Why would he rather take Yu Zhihui
than take a glance at Feng Shizhen?
Did he not make any move
because he already saw her
as his son's woman?
Ma'am.
I'd like to ask you something
You know what happened
at the party, don't you?
I can't say I don't.
Everyone is talking about it.
It's impossible
to shut them all up.
Is it true
that you were with Zhihui
the whole time
before that thing happened?
I was.
Miss Yu was drunk.
When I was about to go get Mr. Yang,
my brother said
he'd like to go home,
so I walked him out first.
Ma'am,
I'm to blame
for all that mess.
Had I...
It's not your fault.
She chose that path.
Are you leaving, Mr. Jiashang?
Yes.
Ma'am,
if there's nothing else,
I'm going upstairs.
Sure.
Mm.
Miss Feng...
(Shanghai-Nanjing)
Xiucheng,
I'm not going to marry anyone else.
Let me go!
He's becoming more and more
like his father.
Morning, Miss Feng.
Morning, Mr. Jiashang.
I almost forgot Fanglin had gone out.
The class was canceled.
Wait!
We're still friends,
aren't we?
Are you interested in my calligraphy?
(Gentlemen)
It's got strength and style.
(Gentlemen should think...)
I bet Meng Xu'an didn't get to
see Rong Jiashang's penmanship.
If he were that spoiled brat
like everyone said,
he couldn't write so well.
(Gentlemen should think thoroughly.)
You want to try it?
Why not?
(All rivers)
(Gentlemen should think thoroughly.
All rivers run into the sea.)
That's unique.
You've got perseverance
and talent.
If you were a man,
you'd make a difference.
I am what I am.
There are no ifs.
We'd better not
aim too high.
Live the life we have
to the fullest is all that matters.
If we can't even put food on the table,
the rest is just empty talk.
I hated it when you lectured me.
But now that
I can no longer hear you preaching,
I'll miss it.
You...
You aren't coming to class anymore?
My father asks me to
focus on our business.
So my study
has to give way to that.
But that doesn't mean
I'll give up my dream.
That sextant you gave me
is sitting next to my model plane.
I can see it every day.
Good.
It pains me to see
a talented and ambitions young man
let go of his dream
for money.
You're born rich,
nothing should hold you back
from fighting for your dream.
Shizhen,
have you ever been in love?
Of course.
If not,
that wouldn't make sense
at my age.
What kind of man was he?
Why should I tell you?
We've found everything we can about you.
Nothing indicates
you've ever been involved with any man.
Did you lie to me?
Why would I?
Besides,
you've never shared
your love life with me.
You mean Hashimoto?
Yeah.
That was a mistake years back.
A mistake?
That's hurtful.
I mean it.
Her mother was a retired harlot.
When I first met her,
she was named after her
as Lin Shizhi.
All I know was
her mother was some rich man's mistress.
After that man's wife kicked her mother,
her brother and her out,
they had to depend on
their remote relatives in Chongqing.
So you stayed there
for another year for her?
Who told you that?
Fanglin and Fanghua.
According to them,
you two were childhood sweethearts
and forced to break up.
Now she's found you again,
but you've already been engaged.
How unfortunate
and sad your story is.
Those girls don't know anything.
Back then,
when Whampoa Military Academy
first opened to students,
I applied behind my father's back
and got admitted.
He wouldn't let me go
and insisted I go to business school.
So I refused to come back
to protest against his decision.
Of course,
I didn't win.
In the end, I yielded to
his persuasion and pressure.
A plane has to
battle against gravity and the drag
to take off.
If anything goes wrong,
it'll crash
and kill everyone aboard.
Independence
is more complicated than you think.
I know.
Sometimes, I think I've grown up.
At other times, however, I'm still young
and weak.
Growth takes time.
You know,
I'm looking forward
to being flown by you
someday.
Really?
Yeah.
You want to be on my plane?
Of course,
if my student is a pilot.
It's not like
I can afford a ticket.
Deal!
Shizhen,
once I become
a pilot,
you'll be my first passenger.
Just because you no longer take my class
doesn't mean you can call me by my name.
You're cunning.
We were talking about your love life,
yet you circled it back to me.
Oh?
I never meant to tell you anyway.
Are you going out?
Yeah. To run errands.
(Rong)
Mr. Yang isn't a nobody now.
How could he let it go
that his uncle took his woman?
I know, right?
He has to
as long as he still wants his job.
I heard
Mr. Rong paid him a lot for this.
Money can't buy his dignity back.
Mr. Rong is his uncle
and boss.
He'll have to see him every day.
I feel bad for him!
Hey, would they
fall out with each other?
If you ask me,
I'd say yes.
He's here. Stop. Let's go.
- Mr. Yang.
Mr. Rong is waiting for you upstairs.
He wants to see you once you arrive.
They will be fine. He wouldn't dare.
Right?
I don't think so.
Enough.
Come in.
Xiucheng.
Have a seat.
I heard you were sick.
You look terrible.
I can get you a doctor.
It was just a cold
and could be contagious.
Thank you for your concern.
I see.
Have a seat.
Xiucheng,
I know you're mad at me,
and you can't get it off your chest,
can you?
I'm sorry
for putting you through all this.
I'm not just
your boss,
but also your uncle.
Although you're unrelated to me
but my wife,
I've been treating you as family,
cultivating and promoting you
over the past years.
Have I ever
mistreated you
prior to this incident?
I'm forever in debt to you
for all that you've done for me.
I'm not asking you for any return.
I just want you to know
that you've come this far
because you deserve it.
I don't want some stupid mistake
to drive a wedge between us.
You were there
when Yu Zhihui made a scene.
She wasn't innocent.
As you know,
I wouldn't
take women by force.
Well,
let bygones be bygones.
We should move on.
That said,
I feel bad
for what happened.
I understand
it's still awkward
for us to work together.
So,
why don't you take a vacation
to relax yourself
and think about your future plan?
If you still want to work here,
as Manager Guo is about to retire
and Jiashang is still young,
you can be the General Manager.
If you have other plans,
we'll find a way to work things out.
I remember you said
that women are
unimportant.
I could never repay you for your help
and I'd never
betray you for such a trifle.
It's just that
we can't stop the staff
from gossiping around.
I can come back once things blow over.
Sure.
You may leave.
Xiucheng.
Father.
Mm.
What did you say to Yang Xiucheng?
I gave him a vacation.
This deal in Tianjin is well done.
It kept dragging on
until you made it work.
My friends are
speaking highly of you.
Are you letting Yang Xiucheng go?
Let me ask you.
If it were you,
what would you do?
I only work with
people I trust.
If you had little trust in him before,
now,
it's even less, isn't it?
That ship has sailed.
Look,
learn from my mistake.
Don't let any woman get in your way.
What about you and Miss Hashimoto?
I didn't know
she was your girlfriend.
She wasn't.
She was just a girl I met in Chongqing
who
you thought was too poor
to be with me.
That was her?
So she's admitted by her family?
Why didn't you tell me
she's a Hashimoto?
If I had,
you would've had me
sign the prenup with her,
no?
I know
you hate me telling you what to do,
such as to marry Miss Du
and work in our company.
You don't want any of that.
But you're too young
to know what's best for yourself.
Hadn't I intervened,
you would've still been wasting time
on your stupid dream.
Father,
a pilot is well-respected.
It's what I want to be.
How is that respectable?
It's the same as a driver.
Do you respect your driver?
All professions deserve
equal respect.
Father,
you're too conservative
and stubborn.
I know you wish to join the army
and prove yourself on the battlefield,
but the military is divided.
Generals fight against each other
for money and fame
just like those in the outside world.
Back in the day, Hua'an and I
went to deliver goods with guns
at the risk of our lives.
We'd fight to the death
against robbers.
When our business expanded,
we had to protect what we earned,
pay those along land and shipping routes
and take precautions against enemies.
We wouldn't go anywhere without guns.
Even at night,
we had to put them under the pillow.
After what I went through,
I'd never allow my son to follow suit.
Given our family condition,
you could enjoy a comfortable life
and go to college.
Why play with fire?
Now, back to business.
You'll fill in for Xiucheng
while he's away.
These are his files.
Read from cover to cover
to familiarize yourself with everything.
Is that all?
I'm off.
Hey...
(Wenchunli Title Deed)
(Seller: Shanghai Dasheng Company
Buyer: Shanghai Rong Company)
Miss Feng,
I was told
your family once owned
a pharmacy at Wenchunli
which was later destroyed in a fire.
My family and I survived
except that my father got injured.
Well, a full recovery can be expected.
Secretary Zhao,
come to my office now.
Come in.
Mr. Jiashang,
what do you need?
I'm asked to
take over Mr. Yang's projects
and I have questions
regarding things in his files.
You've been with him for so long.
What do you know
about the Wenchunli Project?
Mr. Yang
was in charge of it.
Dasheng sold that large piece of land
to us
at an unusually low price.
Why was that?
Mr. Rong had his eyes
on that land long ago.
Mr. Yang and I went to negotiate
with shop owners
and residents there many times
but couldn't reach an agreement
as they all had their own demands.
Hearing that Mr. Yang failed,
Mr. Rong gave him a tongue-lashing.
Unexpectedly, that place
got burned down overnight
and became worthless later.
Dasheng took the chance
and got hold of it.
As for why they didn't charge us
for more,
I have no idea.
Mr. Yang handled
the transaction himself.
That didn't make sense.
If we wanted that land for so long,
how come veterans like
my father and Yang Xiucheng
didn't make any move
when its price plummeted
and let Dasheng get it?
And I'm not seeing anything
about that company in the files.
I know.
Mr. Jiashang,
the thing is,
Mr. Yang finished this project
all by himself
after the fire.
He only gave me paperwork.
I don't know anything
about Dasheng.
I see.
You may leave.
Yes.
One more thing.
I need newspapers
and anything you can find
about the Wenchunli Fire.
Yes.
(Shanghai Station)
(Shanghai-Hangzhou)
Occupied.
I know.
What are you doing here?
I'm invited to a schoolmate's wedding
in Hangzhou.
I spotted you all depressed
and came to say hi.
Pull yourself together.
She cheated on you, so what?
Didn't you already know
what kind of woman she was?
Leave me alone.
That's none of your business.
Like I care about you.
You're incorrigible.
You could've been a boss,
but you went to be Rong Dingkun's slave,
and let Rong Jiashang reap
you've sowed all these years.
What's worse,
you know Rong Dingkun's secrets.
I don't need to tell you
how he ties up loose ends.
What do you think will happen to you?
Drowned in the water,
or buried in the wild?
You don't have family anyway.
No one
will even go to your tomb.
You're too soft.
If you want to rise to the top,
you should do everything to win.
Had you dumped Yu Zhihui
to be with Rong Fanglin,
you would've got your share
of the Rongs' property.
And what did you do?
You stayed faithful
only to be played by Yu Zhihui.
Miss Du,
if you're here to taunt me,
that's enough.
Please go back to your compartment.
I'm here to wake you up.
Yang Xiucheng,
I believe
a man with your talent and experience
deserves
a better boss
and a better woman.
If you still don't realize that
and don't know what you want,
then you're the dumbest
and cheapest clown in the world.
(Fire Broke out at Wenchunli)
- Mr. Jiashang.
Sir.
To Wenchunli.
(Rong)
Here.
What's this about?
Hey,
are you aware
of the Wenchunli Fire last year?
Of course.
Those flames
lit up the entire city.
Our newspaper broke the story first.
Didn't that piece of land
end up in your hands?
After the fire,
Dasheng Company
bought it
and then sacrificed it to us
in a financial strait.
You have all kinds of connections.
I need you
to look into that company.
Why don't you
ask your father about it?
He traded with them
and must know a thing or two.
Yunchi,
honestly,
I think that fire
wasn't an accident.
What do you mean?
I believe
someone set that place on fire
to get the land at the cheapest price.
My family
could be behind it.
I need to know the truth.
Yunchi,
please do me this favor.
Finally!
How rude!
We're going to the Rong's
with Father tonight.
How are you going to
impress them like this?
No worries.
Brother can't leave the house.
I'm the only son left.
If the Rongs intend to work with us,
I'm their only option.
You fool!
We're siblings
and twins.
If you show up as a good-for-nothing,
what will they think of me?
By "they", do you mean your ex?
You want him back, don't you?
If it's yours, it's yours.
If it's not, it's not.
It has nothing to do with me.
When Father
had us back
as his children,
you thought Jiashang was too poor
for our family.
Then what?
Turns out
he's Rong Dingkun's eldest son,
the first heir to their family business.
If you and Mother hadn't interfered,
we would've got married long ago.
Come on!
Don't blame us.
Who dumped him
for him lacking money?
It wasn't us.
Too bad,
he's already engaged.
But you can
still be his concubine.
Be his concubine?
No way!
You forgot how Mother had to
grovel to Father's wife
like a slave
with no dignity and died in depression.
You forgot how others looked at us
and humiliated us?
Father wouldn't have gotten us back
if Brother had been healthy.
I cannot live like Mother.
I'll marry Rong Jiashang
as his wife
and take over
his entire family.
He's taken.
What else can you do?
Jiashang is soft-hearted.
We had a history after all.
Now,
if playing well,
I can use that to my advantage.
Mr. Jiashang,
did you just come back?
Yes.
Is Miss Feng in?
Sorry, Mr. Jiashang.
Mrs. Rong gave her permission
to go home for the festival.
She'll be back in the evening.
I see.
Mr. Jiashang.
Who is that, Mother?
It doesn't ring a bell.
Mrs. Zhao's niece.
You went to the same school.
It's her!
Now, I remember.
Mrs. Zhao has asked me a few times,
but Shixun doesn't cooperate.
At this rate,
when will I have grandchildren?
Mother!
Here we go!
Again with the grandchildren.
I'm on Mother's side.
When will I have a sister-in-law?
Just worry about yourself.
Mother is working on your marriage, too.
You're older and unmarried.
It's not my turn yet.
You're wrong.
You're 23 already.
Wait any longer,
and you'll end up
as someone's stepmother.
Mother,
there's still time.
Relax, Mother.
She's my sister.
If she decides to remain single,
I'll support her forever.
Poppycock!
Shixun.
Yes?
Is this a new scarf?
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪