♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 8=
Chang Kong,
you slept outside last night.
I...
A top-fighter like you
should notice if
someone kidnapped Xiao Ai,
even if it was midnight.
That is where it is strange.
I asked the people who slept beside her.
They said no one came close.
That does not make sense.
Neither from the roof,
nor from the door.
How did the criminal take her away?
We missed an important point,
which is
how he knows Xiao Ai is a girl.
Mengmeng,
you are a genius.
Yes.
Xiao Ai dressed like a man.
And she was among a bunch of males.
How did he discover that?
If a male-dressed girl is recognized,
she must have exposed something
unconsciously,
like when taking a shower,
or...
I got it.
These are the beads
from Xiao Ai's purse.
I got it.
Xiao Ai must have been kidnapped
in the toilet by someone ambushed here.
It is evident Xiao Ai struggled here.
That makes sense.
What a dirty criminal!
He hid out here to take the victim.
Damn!
We must rescue Xiao Ai.
Why are you all looking at me?
Chang Kong,
Xiao Ai stays with me more.
Why are you more worried about her?
I...
I don't.
I just...
I understand...
We can tell that from your look.
Let's think about how to save her.
(Yi Chun Tavern)
It seems
I have to take all the responsibilities.
Lure the criminal.
Set him up.
Eliminate him.
Make peace.
No.
Last time in Bai Hua Village,
you nearly lost your life.
This time
I will never put you in danger.
No worries.
Last time I was alone.
Stuck there.
This time we will collaborate.
I will attract their attention.
You divide and close in upon.
It will be fine.
Mengmeng,
the thing with battles
is to know yourself and your enemy.
Look,
we don't even know who is the enemy.
Besides, you can't fight.
You are putting yourself in danger.
True.
You are like
a lamb in the mouth of the tiger.
Only if there is one more girl among us,
I don't have to do it by myself.
It would be better if
two of us can operate
with and for each other.
Where can we find another girl?
Actually,
it doesn't have to be a girl.
What do you mean?
You and Xiao Ai can dress like men,
and vice versa.
You mean, a female-dressed boy?
No, no, no.
(This boy looks pretty.)
(Then it's you.)
Why are you all looking at me?
What a hustle and bustle!
Will this lure the criminal?
Yes, for sure.
Can't you see they are all watching us?
At this time, only you and me
dare to be on the street.
No wander they will watch us.
Rongrong,
let's buy some rouge.
Go.
My guests, want some rouge?
Wow, there is eyebrow powder.
Yes, take a look.
They are all new arrivals.
Mengmeng, look up.
What are you doing?
We are sisters.
I'll make you up.
Song Che,
what are you doing?
Murong Chen is taking advantage of her.
I need to warn him.
Now the criminal may be near.
You might make him notice.
I...
Let's make a full one.
You are so close.
Of course.
She is the best.
Are you from the outside?
Then you have to go back.
It's not safe here recently.
Not safe?
We got it.
We will go back soon.
One day passed and
no sign of the criminal.
I think he will appear tonight.
Tonight?
Let's go, sis.
Let's hang out.
In front of me,
he acts indecently.
Murong Chen,
- I'll kill you.
- Song Che.
I'll kill... kill you.
Well, Song Che.
Easy!
The cup will be broken.
They stick together in the daytime.
Now at night,
they are still in the same room.
It is a trap for the criminal.
We guard here.
Once he appears,
we bust him alive,
and force him to let Xiao Ai go.
You all care about Xiao Ai only.
No one cares about me.
Sis Mengmeng,
are you going to wear
so much and go to sleep?
Don't you feel hot?
I am not.
Even a little cold.
Did he come?
A cat.
Kind of hot.
Hot?
Yes, a little hot.
They put out the light.
I'll kill...
- I kill...
- Stop.
- Easy.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
If we sleep with lights on,
he will never come.
It makes sense.
Why don't they come?
Wait for a moment.
Maybe soon.
Song Che and Chang Kong
might have caught the criminal already.
We are here waiting for nothing.
Mengmeng,
sometimes do you feel...
Mengmeng?
Not good.
Toxic smoke.
Mengmeng!
Mengmeng, wake up.
Mengmeng, Mengmeng.
We lost him.
But
why did he run away alone?
Mengmeng...
Go.
Mengmeng!
Murong Chen, you are useless.
We are tricked away.
I am useless.
I didn't take care of Mengmeng.
Now there is no time to blame.
How about this?
We split up.
You inform the officials.
I ask around.
Come, come.
Itchy.
So itchy.
Look at my skin.
Your skin looks great.
Look, her skin is very good.
My head aches.
Mengmeng,
look around.
Are we in the Spiders' Cave?
I don't know.
What are they doing?
It is so strange.
The newcomers wake up.
Come.
- What are you doing?
- Don't be shy.
Come on, take it off.
Sis,
why are you wearing so much?
Xiao Mei,
come and help.
what a familiar name.
I remember it.
The daughter of the old couple.
Why doesn't this one take it off?
She can't.
She is sick.
My sister has sensitive skin.
She can't touch hot water.
You are sisters?
Yes, she is Rongrong.
I'm Mengmeng.
We are biological sisters.
But you don't look like each other.
Really?
Your sister is more beautiful than you.
Yes.
Well,
I have sensitive skin.
So I can't enjoy the spring with you.
What a shame! It is a nice spring.
It seems you can't enjoy it.
Then I'll just have a rest over there.
Sisters,
enjoy yourselves.
You go alone.
Sisters,
let's sit and talk, come.
I'm new here.
I want to ask
if there are any rules here.
Nothing special.
Every day we just
smooth our skin in the water.
Make ourselves look beautiful.
It has this function?
Oh, sis.
Do you remember how you got here?
I don't remember.
Strange, me neither.
Do you miss your home?
Why?
Girls are supposed to be beautiful.
What about parents?
Well,
are you Xiao Mei?
How old are you, Xiao Mei?
(How do girls flirt with girls?)
Your nails are so beautiful.
You do feel so?
I made it by myself.
It looks so good.
I want the same.
But I can't do it.
Xiao Mei,
can you tell me how to do it?
Alright.
Really?
Great.
Well,
I want to ask you about something.
Do you still remember
where is your home?
No, I don't.
Sis, what about you?
- Me neither.
- You?
Do you remember?
Yes, I do.
My home is...
Where?
Where is my home?
Well, girls like you...
No, girls like us,
how many of us are here?
Eighteen, including you two.
It can't be right. One is missing.
Yesterday, there was one
who kept crying.
She was kept in a small room.
(She must be Xiao Ai.)
Where is my home?
What's wrong with you?
Mengmeng!
Mengmeng! Mengmeng!
Sis, what's wrong with you?
- What happened?
- Don't know.
Mengmeng,
you are up.
You...
I...
Murong Chen, you...
- Don't thank me.
- I...
Don't thank me, for real.
We are caught here together.
It is normal I helped you.
I need to take care of you.
We help each other, right?
Well, you put me here?
Yes.
Then my clothes...
No.
The girls helped with your clothes.
They did it for you.
Oh, they did it.
Jiang Mengmeng,
are you thinking I...
No.
I thought...
I thought they helped me.
Fine.
(Well, well, Jiang Mengmeng,)
(what is on your mind?)
(In the spring, you must have)
(lost your sanity.)
Right, the spring.
Murong Chen,
do you think something is wrong with it?
It seems the spring can surely wash out
one's memory.
Like you,
even if you just
touched it a little bit,
you lost your memory.
If I make it right,
the girls are the same as you.
They kept retrospecting.
Yet the more they did it,
the more the headache.
They may pass out just like you.
So they give up trying now.
They choose to forget
their past and families.
So that's why
they want to stay here.
And their mind keeps saying
girls are supposed to be beautiful.
Oh, what about Xiao Mei?
I talked with her.
Anything about Xiao Ai?
Close.
And then you passed out,
and the conversation broke.
Pity.
But I got another idea.
(Sang's house)
Your idea is
to search the rooms one by one?
What if we pick the wrong room?
Don't you cry.
You'll ruin the spring.
Madam will punish me.
I put some food here.
I will not eat it. Take it away.
Whatever.
Quick!
Go!
Let go!
Let's get in.
Yes.
Get in.
Xiao Ai.
I said I don't...
I'm having illusion now.
The 5th prince is a girl now.
Xiao Ai, it's not an illusion.
It's us.
Your Highness.
It's OK now.
You keep it down.
Someone will notice.
But your tears are worthy.
Without them,
you might have forgotten me.
Your Highness.
I heard from the servant,
some Madam?
Do you know who it is?
I never met this person.
It's called Luo Bo,
Bo Luo, or Sang Luo.
I don't know.
Sang Luo?
Someone is coming.
Quick, hide.
It's me.
Xiao Mei?
I know where Sang Luo is.
You met my parents?
How are they?
No worries.
They are fine.
They're just worried about you.
Oh, Xiao Mei,
why is your memory
not washed out like others?
Actually, there is not much memory left.
I can't remember the look of my parents.
How come you...
Because every day back in the room,
I can recognize
the characters at my bedside.
Characters?
Every day before sleep,
I can feel the characters at my bedside.
It says "stay away from the spring".
I think I carved it long before
I forgot everything.
Right.
The characters.
You are so clever, Xiao Mei.
No wonder you didn't
go to the spring like others.
The characters kept me
away from the spring.
But as the time passes,
the spring affects me as well.
Then why didn't you run away?
I tried.
At some nights, I sneaked out.
But this place is well-guarded.
I couldn't get out.
But last night,
I found Sang Luo's room.
I eavesdropped beside the window
the conversation
between Sang Luo and two servants.
One servant said
two girls were conspicuous.
It may be a trap
set up by the officials.
But Sang Luo said
they only need two more girls.
It would be another month
if they missed the chance.
So Sang Luo sent one of the two servants
to attract the guards,
and the other one
to catch the two girls.
That makes sense.
Song Che is easy to
fall into the trap.
But besides Song Che,
Chang Kong fell into the trap as well.
Chang Kong
was affected by Song Che,
like I was affected by you.
Coo like a crow, and you like a...
I like what?
You like a... meow.
Lady, please behave yourself.
Oh, Xiao Mei,
Sang Luo talked about two girls
and one month.
Do you know the details?
Xiao Ai, do you know?
Xiao Ai did nothing but cry.
What is the whole thing?
You can stop thinking.
We can just poke around.
Someone is coming.
Quick, quick.
Mengmeng.
- What?
- Look!
Am I looking green?
To hide better, I put
a bunch of leaves on my head.
- Looks good?
- Green.
Xiao Mei, am I good?
Good, good.
You are the best in this house.
There, there.
Xiao Mei, later in there,
please cover us with Xiao Ai.
Take care of yourselves.
I am leaving.
Go.
Quick.
Let me see.
Wait, wait.
You are so annoying.
Poke another hole.
Sleep now.
Stop crying.
Sleep early.
(Sang Luo)
All the skin care recipes
do not work at all.
Of course.
Dozens of ingredients on the face,
they will damage your skin.
My face looks bad.
Yes,
you clean others' memory.
How good can your face be?
Small wrinkles appear.
Only a facelift can help ones
in your age.
And a little inflammation.
An angry middle-aged woman!
You are sure to be inflamed.
It seems someone is talking to me.
Madam,
no one talks.
It must be an illusion.
Oh, where is my honey?
Honey?
Where is it?
- Take a look.
- Yes.
The servant.
What now?
Room check.
We are on bed now.
Something's wrong?
The two newcomers are obedient.
Why are you so slow?
Madam is impatient.
The night is dark.
I tripped.
Go.
I'm good at bondage.
Well, I don't want to eat.
Greasy and useless.
She has the blood night-blooming cereus.
Stupid.
The cereus seduced him.
What is on your mind?
My beautiful madam,
I just remembered
I have seen a skincare recipe.
I want to recommend it to you.
Shoot.
Use boiled aloe juice
mixed with honey
to make an Aloe Honey Mask.
Put it on your face.
It helps refresh your skin.
Dietetic invigoration
for facial treatment.
Wonderful ideas.
But I don't need it anymore.
Tomorrow night is the fifteenth.
The full moon will help me summon
the Blood Moon Tactics.
Blood of 18 young girls
will dip into the
blood night-blooming cereus.
Then I will never get older.
Never ever.
Oh god.
So evil.
What a new version of the plot!
(Information about the
blood night-blooming cereus)
On the fifth of last month,
someone in Qing Luo Town
sold a fake blood night-blooming cereus.
The buyer was
Sang Luo.
I can't imagine
Sang Luo is planning something horrible.
Xiao Ai doesn't want to die.
Don't cry.
We still have one day.
You seem calm
at this moment.
I should be calm.
I play the leading role. I fear not.
Why are your hands shaking?
My hands have their own thoughts.
What are you doing?
Listen,
don't be afraid.
In the world, your owner is
the smartest
and the bravest girl.
She will surely keep you safe.
And she is not alone.
There is me
as a mate.
Childish.
Yes, let's pull together.
We still have one day.
Everything will be fine, right?
Good.
But
we have to deal with this guy now.
If he talks,
we can't make it tonight.
Indeed.
Wait.
Easy, easy.
I've got an idea.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪