A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 15
Hey, can you be more punctual?
You're always late for our dates.
Is your watch using local US time?
I was late by just ten minutes.
-Don't be so irritated.
-I'm irritated?
You're the one who's late,
but you're complaining about me?
It's not nice to shout at a girl.
You're such an embarrassment to us men.
Where did this brat come from?
I'm not a brat. My name is Xiao Long.
He's the kid my neighbor
asked me to care of.
He's alone so I brought him here
or else he'd feel so sad.
Him? He looks like a gangster.
How can he be sad?
-It hurts.
-How can you be sad?
It hurts. Let go.
-Hey.
-You're a bad guy.
Don't bully a kid, okay?
Shancai, you're the best.
Can we go play?
Hey, you're putting on an act
and pretending to be cute.
Shancai, don't be fooled by him.
Why are you fighting with a kid?
Xiao Long. Where would you like to go?
I don't know.
I remember you told me
that you haven't been to the zoo.
-Do you want to go there?
-Sure.
Zoo? We just got here
and now you're going to the zoo.
-Do you know how far that is?
-No.
Let's go.
Are you having fun?
Is that a monkey?
Let's go and see the monkeys.
She's even more childish than the kid.
Have you seen that before?
I've never seen a real monkey before.
Yes, it's been awhile
since I saw a real monkey.
What's that monkey doing?
Guess what?
That monkey looks so ugly.
As ugly as you.
Who are you calling ugly, stupid boy?
Go slowly.
I'm way more handsome than you guys.
Shancai, is this a goat?
Yes.
Goat's milk is similar to cow's milk.
You can drink it.
And it's even more nutritious.
Really?
Then I want to have him as a pet.
That way, I can ride him
and go to you so we can play.
No. That's too dangerous.
Then can I feed him?
Can we go down now?
Do you see the tiger?
I don't see it.
You don't? He's over there.
No. I don't see it.
-You still can't see it?
-No.
Come on. Can you see it, little midget?
I see it.
Shancai, the tiger is so beautiful.
Xiao Long, do you know
that feline animals would produce
a sound when they're happy?
Really? I didn't know that.
Of course not.
Because you're a canine.
He really is a kid.
He can fall asleep just like that.
Yes.
Let me hold that for him.
There's no need for that.
-Daoming Si.
-What?
-Why?
-What do you mean "why"?
You said that out of the blue.
How could I understand that?
Why did you lend me money?
Why did you support me to join
the competition?
-Why are you spending the day with me?
-Because you're stupid.
What did I do to infuriate you again?
Don't you know the answer to that?
Can't you use your brain
to think about it?
I...
If I can figure it out,
why would I ask you?
You're a bipolar, manic-depressive guy who
can't talk normally and likes to shout!
-I don't want to talk to you!
-Then don't!
It's really tiring to talk
with someone dumb like you.
-Why did this brat pee on me?
-Hey!
-You'll wake him up!
-So what?
-Why are you so annoying?
-Who's annoying?
-You!
-I'm annoying, right?
-I'll show you what's even more annoying.
-Hey! You'll hurt him.
Since I'm so annoying,
don't ever see me again.
Fine! I won't see you again!
Xiao Long, it's okay.
Don't cry anymore, okay?
I peed in my pants.
It's so embarrassing!
Xiao Long. Look.
Do you want some strawberry cake?
I want to eat the strawberries.
Okay, sure.
Shancai, this one's for you.
That's nice. You know how to share.
Shancai.
Is there any problem?
I must have messed up that guy's clothes.
You mean Daoming Si?
Forget about him.
Let me give you some advice.
Don't be like him when you grow up.
But when he lifted me on his shoulders,
it felt like he was my dad.
Anyway,
I think he's quite nice.
I know.
That guy is nice at times.
But I always want to fight with him
when I see him.
Shancai, I want to come
and play with you again.
You're welcome here anytime.
Remember you have to keep
that thing a secret.
What thing?
You mean peeing in your pants?
Xiao Long.
You peed in your pants again?
How old are you?
I told you to keep it a secret.
I'm so mad.
All right. I'm not going to tell
anybody else.
Tell that guy,
after I get more practice on that game,
I'll seek him out for revenge.
All right. Let's go home then.
Say goodbye to Shancai.
-Shancai, bye.
-Bye.
Thank you.
Bye.
Why did you lend me money?
Why did you support me to join
the competition?
-Why are you spending the day with me?
-Because you're stupid.
What did I do to infuriate you again?
Don't you know the answer to that?
Can't you use your brain
to think about it?
This is our restaurant's signature dish,
Lobster Thermidor.
I made that sauce using my own recipe.
It contains a lot of ingredients.
And it needs to be cooked for three hours
in order to create this flavorful dish.
If the timing is not precise,
the flavor would be wrong.
As for this steak, it's also
one of our restaurant's specialties.
The sauce is very unique.
Hello?
Dad.
I've thought about it already.
Tian Ye is not the man I want.
What's the matter?
You don't like him anymore?
No, it's not that.
Then what happened?
He wants to live a certain way.
But I don't want
that kind of life.
Thank you.
Wait.
How do I know this is yours?
Isn't it obvious?
I think it's better to give
a lost item to the police.
You're quite interesting.
What do you want?
Buy me a drink.
Turns out the famous F4 is so cheap.
Turns out the cooking competition
champion is so stingy.
That Hong Kong style fried crab you made
with garlic was really interesting.
I know, right? When I was overseas,
I cooked it every day
because I missed the taste of home.
Honestly, you really cooked that dish
so well that day.
Stop it.
I know you guys were there
to cheer for Shancai.
I'm an exception.
When you won, I clapped so hard.
It's a pity you didn't hear it.
Is that so?
Then why were you cheering for me?
You're all Shancai's friends, right?
That's true,
but after the cooking competition started,
I also wanted you to be my friend.
Are you interested in me?
You think too much.
We're not that close.
I just want to be your friend.
Aren't you buying me a drink?
Sure.
What do you want? Order it. It's my treat.
Wei Xun.
What can I do for you?
The bartender here is my friend.
He has a special talent.
He can make any drink you want.
Is that so?
Then I have to test him.
I want to order a drink
that would prevent me
from ever meeting someone who asks
for favors after finding up a lost item.
Well...
I guess you two didn't expect that.
We have that, of course.
A drink that would not ask favors
after picking up a lost item, right?
Then I want one too.
A drink that would let me meet
a cute but arrogant girl again.
Do you have that too?
Well...
We have that, of course.
A drink that would let you meet
a cute but arrogant girl again.
Just those two, right?
Yes, thank you.
Here you go.
This drink is so sour.
I think he wants that person
who picked up a lost item
and asked for favors to suffer.
All right.
Now it's your turn.
You're wasting time.
Are you scared of drinking it?
Of course not.
I'm afraid that I'll meet
a cute but arrogant girl
daily after I drink it.
What should I do?
I get it.
You don't want to drink it.
I'm not afraid of drinking it.
I'm afraid that
you'll fall in love with me.
It's bitter.
It tells you that falling in love with
a cute but arrogant girl is going to be
a very bitter experience.
Meizuo, who did you go
on a date with yesterday?
You weren't answering your phone.
It's a secret.
Why are you being so mysterious?
Didn't you mention the other day
that you're going out with an older woman?
Where did you guys go during the holiday?
Lei, what did you do?
I slept and played games at home.
Never mind.
How about you, Si?
You must have been happy
on your date with Shancai.
What's there to be happy about?
Did you two fight again?
No way.
Is Shancai that hard to figure out?
Who says Shancai is the problem?
Si.
You have a bad temper.
You're wrong.
How could Si be the problem?
Si has always been
straightforward and honest.
His temper is just a little bit bad.
But is that a crime?
That's right.
It's all Shancai's fault.
-Who knew Shancai's IQ would be so low?
-That's right.
Falling in love with a person with low IQ
-will also make your IQ low.
-Are you done talking?
You're babbling! Aren't you tired?
Lei. Did we say anything wrong?
The point is that you didn't say
anything wrong.
That's why Si walked out.
Si doesn't have the capability
to date girls.
The problem is right in front of us.
We all see it very clearly.
The problem is how do we solve it?
Indeed.
Si will end up dying alone
if he stays this way.
At that time, if nobody will push
his wheelchair to let him get some sun,
we'd all be sad when we see that, right?
So what should we do?
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
COME IN AND RECEIVE A GIFT
Shancai. How was your holiday?
Don't even mention it.
I really hope I can go back in time.
Why?
Nothing.
I'm not in the mood to think about it.
Let's just sell milk tea.
Yes. If we don't sell enough of them,
we won't receive
our bonus again this month.
We haven't received our bonus
for three months already.
There's nothing we can do.
The weather's so cold.
Nobody wants to go out and buy tea.
Shancai.
That "different" guy is here.
Lei.
Why are you guys here?
Hi, Ximen.
Long time no see. Welcome to our store.
Hi, Xiaoyou.
How are you doing?
Long time no see.
You're still so cute.
Don't look directly at this guy.
It's very dangerous.
Shancai, you're so busy.
It's the holidays
but you're still working.
How can I rest when I have
a part-time job?
How can I earn a lot of money
if I don't work hard?
That's Dong Shancai.
Why exactly are you guys here?
You're not buying milk tea.
You're just getting in the way of our job.
If our sales don't increase
by the end of the year,
we won't get any bonus for this year.
Leave it all up to us.
Hey, pretty girl, come and taste
our store's new milk tea flavors.
Try the White Jasmine Dew.
The tea is very refreshing.
This is Peach Red Royale.
It's sweet with a fruity fragrance.
There are many flavors to choose from.
-Do you want to try this?
-Yes.
-He's so handsome!
-Hey, handsome.
-Can I have your Weibo ID?
-And...
This is yours.
-I like this.
-This latte and cheese are good.
-I like it too.
-And it's not fattening.
-If you order...
-Don't push me.
-Bye, handsome.
-Which tea do you want?
-This is your Peach Red Royale.
-Thank you.
-Welcome to our store. What's your order?
-I want what she's having.
-Do you want ice on it?
-No.
Do you want to try it?
That's right. I really recommend this.
They're so handsome.
-It smells really good.
-Do you want to try it?
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
It's so amazing!
Today's sales are even higher
than the past three months altogether.
Mission accomplished.
I'm giving you extra on your bonuses.
Here. These are for you.
-Thank you, ma'am!
You're welcome.
Keep up the good work!
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Thank you for what you guys did today.
I've never gotten a bonus this big.
No.
I can't accept this bonus.
You were the ones who sold
those milk teas.
Take this.
We sold them outside.
You prepared them inside.
It was teamwork.
How can you say that you don't deserve it?
Do you want to return that to your boss?
Then all our efforts this afternoon
would be wasted.
Just accept it, Shancai.
We helped out just for you.
All right.
I'll treat you guys for dinner
as a reward for your efforts.
That's right. We can all eat together.
Shancai, if you really want
to treat us for dinner,
how about using this money
to have fun with us instead?
Have fun?
Where?
We're going to Canada
during the New Year holidays.
And we'll do the countdown there.
What?
Canada?
Join us, Xiaoyou.
Really? Can I really go with you?
I've never been out of the country before.
But...
Is this enough to go to Canada?
Don't worry.
Si's family has a chalet mansion
with a very nice view in Canada.
Food and lodging would not be a problem.
Shancai, let's go with them.
I really want to go.
I want to go too.
But...
Daoming Si would probably be there too.
We had such a big fight.
How can I pretend like nothing happened
and stay at his mansion?
-I'm home.
-You're back?
Shancai.
I heard that you're going to Canada
in a couple of days.
Remember to buy smoked salmon for me.
Yes. And maple syrup.
Buy a few bottles.
I heard the stewed chicken leg
is delicious there.
How did you know?
Ximen called and told us about it.
Ximen?
I haven't even agreed yet.
I'm still thinking about it.
What's there to think about?
I think it's good to go out
and see the world.
I'm usually busy with school.
I need to accompany Mom to the market
to buy ingredients during the holidays.
Don't worry about that.
We only have a few days
of holiday vacation.
It's the New Year.
You must be really busy with cooking.
I have to help you with the deliveries.
Don't worry. I'm here.
My working hours are quite flexible.
That's right.
Don't worry about these things.
Your dad and I will take care of it.
You rarely have a chance to go out
and have fun. Enjoy yourself.
Your friends can take care of you
and you won't be alone. Isn't that great?
It's good. Just go.
Remember to buy smoked salmon for me.
Shancai, are you still thinking about it?
I'm still worried about my family's
food business.
Do you really want to go?
Yes. I want to go to Canada with you.
But...
I haven't made up my mind yet.
DAOMING SI CALLING FROM QQ
I heard you're going to Canada.
So what?
What has that got to do with you?
Of course!
If you're going, I'm staying behind.
What do you mean?
Let me make it even clearer.
You can't go to Canada.
Daoming Si, who are you to stop me
from going to Canada?
It's too luxurious
for a stupid girl like you.
You don't know how to ski
and you're afraid of the cold.
You won't enjoy it there.
I think you shouldn't go.
Who says so?
I'm not afraid of the cold.
I'll enjoy it even if I fall while skiing!
I'm definitely going!
And I'll go there happily.
I didn't invite you to go.
And I don't want to see you.
You weren't the one who invited me there.
If you don't want to see me,
then don't go!
I don't need your approval for my actions!
Fine, I'm not going!
I'll tell them all not to go.
Just go alone.
When you encounter wild animals
in the wilderness,
don't call and cry to me!
Cry?
You think too little of me.
It's better to encounter wild animals
than beasts like you!
-Bye!
-Goodbye!
Si, why did you think we sold milk tea
in such a cold weather?
You guys like to sell milk tea.
What does that have to do with me?
In life, it's very lucky
to have good friends.
It's also very unlucky to meet Daoming Si.
Lei.
You can freely court Shancai now.
Si and Shancai are now enemies.
He wouldn't care
about what happens with you and Shancai.
Really? I'll do that then.
Don't regret it.
Don't play tricks with me!
I said I'm not going so I'm not going!
Then don't go.
That's right. Nobody's forcing you to go.
Let's go and pack.
We'll leave you all alone
in Shanghai then.
We'll go.
-Si.
-Bye.
We're leaving.
Si. Have a happy holiday!
Really? You've decided to go to Canada?
My parents encouraged me to go.
Your parents are so nice.
Yes.
Daoming Si is not going anyway.
Then I don't have any reason not to go.
Honestly, I really wanted to go.
Yes. Let's go together.
Shancai, you're so nice.
I love you to death!
What should we wear in Canada?
Let's take a selfie and post it in QQ
to celebrate our trip to Canada, okay?
Sure.
DONG SHANCAI: GOING TO CANADA
WITH MY BESTIE, I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT!
IT'S A GOOD THING THAT
ANNOYING PEOPLE ARE NOT COMING!
GOING TO CANADA WITH MY BESTIE,
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT!
Xinhui.
-What? I'm not done trying yet.
-Come here and see this.
Shancai is going to Canada.
Shancai?
Is she going with Daoming Si?
F4.
I want to go too.
Can I go?
It's impossible.
How about we call Shancai?
Let's ask if we can go with them.
F4.
I was too excited to sleep all night
thinking about going to Canada with you.
I searched online
for the places we can go.
Canada's snow is so pretty.
Shancai. I saw your post in QQ.
Are you going to Canada for the New Year?
You said you're going with your bestie.
Who's that?
My friend from senior high school.
Xiaoyou.
We're all classmates.
Let us go with you.
But it was Ximen who invited me.
Then I'll call Ximen
and tell him that you invited us.
Shancai.
Don't you consider us your close friends?
Could it be that you were referring
to Xinhui and me on QQ when you said,
"It's a good thing that
annoying people are not coming"?
No, I wasn't talking about you.
Good. It's settled then.
I'll tell Ximen later
that you invited us to go to Canada.
Thanks, Shancai.
It's so beautiful.
Yes. What a beautiful mansion!
Let's go.
-We finally arrived.
-Yes.
Why is the fireplace burning?
Did the attendant come
and prepare the fire first?
Daoming Si.
You're so late.
What kind of plane can be that slow?
Si, how did you arrive before us?
Yes. I even had time to go
around the city and eat ice cream.
I bought yours too.
It's good that you're here.
Lei, aren't you cold?
Eating ice cream in front
of the fireplace sounds interesting.
-Hi, Daoming Si.
Stupid girl, you came anyway.
I should be the one saying that.
Somebody said he's not coming
but he has come secretly?
Whose words cannot be trusted?
Get your facts straight. This is my house.
I can come anytime I want.
If you're not happy about it,
you can go home now.
-Daoming Si, you--
-That's enough.
We came all the way here.
Just get along.
Si, can you mellow out a bit?
Stop flirting with each other.
-Who's flirting with whom?
This is so comfortable.
I've always wanted to just
lie down here like this.
I never thought the handsome Daoming Si
would be so scary when he's mad.
He's handsome?
Which part?
You don't think he's handsome
because you're mad right now.
But this vacation house is really great.
I'm able to come here because of you.
Not really.
Isn't this our first trip together after
we graduated from senior high school?
This is so nice.
I'm so happy!
Xiaoyou.
Let's have a snowball fight!
Okay!
Jiang Xiaoyou.
You hit me.
I'm dying from so many hits.
Come on.
Can't you and Shancai get along?
How long will you be fighting like this?
Who's fighting with her?
I'm so angry with her.
I'm the victim.
It's no use being nice
to that stupid girl.
Is that so?
Isn't that so?
Are you all right?
Daoming Si.
Why are you so childish?
You deserved it.
Look where you're going.
Are you stupid?
-Daoming Si, you jerk!
-Hey!
What are you doing?
Daoming Si!
Calm down. Hey!
Calm down!
I'll really get my revenge on him.
Xiaoyou, you can shower now.
Shancai, the picture of the snow
you sent earlier was so nice.
Just enjoy yourself.
I'm with you in spirit.
Don't forget to bring back some
smoked salmon and maple syrup.
I know.
I won't forget to bring them back to you.
Xiaoyou, I already showered.
Come back now.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU!
LOG IN
I MAKE THE DECISIONS
Shancai, this lousy teammate.
She's still playing this?
What happened to Xiaoyou?
She's still not back yet.
Lei, have you seen Xiaoyou?
Which one is Xiaoyou?
I'll just find her myself.
Excuse me.
Have you seen Xiaoyou?
Xiaoyou?
-The one from the snowball fight?
-Yes.
Have you seen her?
Oh, that's Xiaoyou.
Let me think.
It looked like she went out
to see the night view.
Yes.
About ten minutes ago,
I saw her walk out the door
with her coat on.
See the night view?
But it's snowing outside.
She insisted on going
for a walk around the area.
We forgot to remind her.
She might not find her way back
if she walks all alone in the snow.
Could she have gotten lost?
Shancai, where are you going?
I'm going to find Xiaoyou.
She went out to see the night view.
But it's a blizzard out there.
I'll search for her around the area.
I'll be right back.
What should we do?
They really went out.
Lei went with her anyway.
They should be back soon
if they can't find her.
Let's go.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene