A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 29
Look.
To preserve the history of the house,
I suggest not breaking
its entire structure.
Let's keep some old structures
and add new elements.
What do you think?
I'm not an expert in this field.
You two can decide.
Then let's do it soon.
After Mr. Ye goes out of the country,
it might be a few years
before he comes back again.
You're going overseas?
Where?
Well...
Talk to Mr. Ye.
Don't worry.
I'll complete the design for your house.
I'll take care of it until it's finished.
How long will you be away?
Aren't you coming back anymore?
Why?
I accepted the offer
from Mr. Brown, a Cambridge seismologist.
I'm joining his team
to go all over the world
to help construct earthquake-proof
houses for earthquake victims.
When are you leaving?
Soon.
All right.
Are you mad?
What right do I have to be mad?
With such a great plan,
you should forge ahead without hesitation.
You don't have a house and family.
There's nothing to keep you here.
You can go wherever you want.
But I'm not like you.
This is my work.
It's also my dream.
This is what I do.
Then we have nothing to talk about, right?
We shouldn't have started
in the first place.
Don't you have any feelings for me?
No.
Then why did you keep
that coconut in your house?
You saw it?
Yes.
After I saw you again,
I don't want to travel alone anymore.
I want to see the world with you.
And live in different tents.
Sing,
dance,
drink and chat.
That's the life I dream of.
Why me?
Fate.
Fate?
You want me to believe in fate?
I believe in it.
I believe that fate let us
meet each other.
I've never been happier than that day.
But that won't last forever.
You can decide if will or won't.
Are you willing to come with me, Caina?
I...
You don't have to answer me now.
Because your answer
is very important to me.
Tell me after thinking about it.
Mr. Lu, what's the matter?
The robot vacuum got stuck on something
while it was cleaning.
I'm trying to get it out.
It's a coconut.
I wonder when it fell on the floor.
Why did I bring you home with me?
I believe in it.
I believe that fate let us
meet each other.
I've never been happier than that day.
But that won't last forever.
You can decide if will or won't.
My dear Caina.
I miss you.
What are you doing now?
Meizuo.
Let's meet at the bar in an hour.
I have something important to tell you.
What should I do?
Why am I leaving?
Caina?
It's late. Why are you here?
Were you looking for me?
You said I can decide on everything.
You'll do whatever I want.
But I think the answer lies with you.
This is the answer I'm giving you.
What happened, Caina?
I should be the one asking that!
You like to travel
and see different women.
Don't get me involved!
-Why do you say that?
-I saw it.
-Ding Qi? Listen to me, Caina.
-You don't need to explain.
I don't want to hear it.
-Listen.
-It's none of my business!
I came to tell you
that I hope you'll leave.
Regardless if it's three or five years,
I never want to see you again
in this lifetime.
What do you think?
The green color is quite interesting.
I know, right? That's my latest cocktail.
Try it and see if you like it.
You're here.
I know I asked you to come here.
Why did you arrive
ten minutes earlier than me?
Miss Caina.
Because I want to let girls
who admire me know
that I'm waiting for her.
Meizuo.
You're a really good man.
But don't girls like bad men?
I left that bad man in the end.
Is something bothering you?
No.
Nothing is bothering me.
I have such a cute
and thoughtful little boyfriend.
Others would be so envious of me.
Waiter, I want to drink.
Give me a double red dynamite.
All right.
You're drinking so much.
Are you trying to get drunk?
I can hold my liquor now.
Your red dynamite.
Don't just...
Caina, are you all right?
I just feel
that I'm so lucky not to fall in love
with a bad man.
Let's drink.
Don't drink anymore.
Be careful.
Ms. Zhou, why are you so drunk?
-Take her upstairs.
-All right.
Hi, Mr. Lu.
Go on.
-You...
-I'm home.
Lie down and rest for a while.
But I still want to drink.
-I'm not drunk.
-Yes, you are.
Give me more.
Lie down and rest for a while.
-Okay?
-Give me more.
-Mr. Lu.
-Here.
Yes. You can drink more.
Have some warm water first.
-Is it alcohol?
-Yes, it is.
Liar!
What is that?
It's so annoying.
I don't want to see it. Mr. Lu.
Throw it away!
Throw this lousy coconut away!
But Ms. Zhou this is your...
Throw it away!
-Get it out of my sight!
-Okay.
I'll throw it away.
I will.
Are you all right?
Come on.
The coconut.
Take it away.
Why?
The coconut.
I don't want to see it.
Why?
The coconut has a smile
carved by Ye Mingchuan.
I don't want to see
that annoying guy anymore.
Don't just...
You're awake?
Meizuo?
Good morning.
Here you go, Ms. Zhou.
-Drink orange juice for your hangover.
-Okay.
Meizuo.
Didn't you go home last night?
Ms. Zhou, have you forgotten?
You were so drunk last night.
Meizuo brought you home.
And he took care of you all night.
Sorry, Meizuo.
I must have been a sight yesterday, right?
It's fine.
I've seen worse.
Ms. Zhou.
You vomited and made a fuss
the whole night.
And you kept on talking.
You insisted on throwing
that coconut away.
And you insisted you were not drunk
and you wanted to drink more.
What? Say it again.
And you insisted you were not drunk
and you wanted to drink more.
-Before that.
-Before...
You asked me to throw that coconut away.
Where did you throw it?
In the trash can outside.
I don't want to see it.
Why?
The coconut has a smile
carved by Ye Mingchuan.
I don't want to see
that annoying guy anymore.
-It smells so good.
-Yes.
-It's delicious.
-I'm so hungry.
Hello to the viewers of Tengxun broadcast.
We're broadcasting now.
I'm Ms. Fang, your foodie host.
Welcome to one of the food streets
in the fishing village.
The trending Dong's King of Squid
in Weibo created a squid fever here
and attracted many tourists,
making this place a hot spot.
Look. This girl wearing a cute hat
is the creator of Dong's King of Squid.
Mom, these are ready.
Here.
Be careful. It's hot.
-Hi, how many do you want?
-Two.
Okay, two.
Here.
-Hi, how many do you want?
-Two.
Two. I have two here.
Here you go.
Come on. Cheers.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mom, it's for that table over there.
Be careful. It's hot.
Here. These are yours.
Enjoy.
HIGHLY RECOMMENDED
Mom, these are ready.
Hi, how many do you want?
-Two.
-Okay. Two.
DAOMING SI
Hello? Daoming Si.
Are you free right now?
Hey.
Are you listening to me?
Shancai's in the fishing village nearby.
You found her?
I thought she was kidnapped
for hard labor.
She was.
She looks tired.
Do you know what she's doing?
She's grilling squid.
She's all sweaty.
She can't speak properly
from all the smoke.
And she's creating a new flavor.
She's really great.
She's so creative.
Why are you still sitting there?
Go pick her up.
I'm not going.
You go.
But what does it have to do with me?
If it's none of your business,
it's even more so with me.
You're her friend. You can go.
Let's go together.
Don't be silly.
She left me.
Why should I go?
Go if you want to.
You don't need my permission.
That song earlier was really good.
Right?
My makeup is all messed up.
My eyes are swollen.
I think you're especially cute today.
Are you teasing me?
I'm serious.
Meizuo.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because you're worth it.
Next time, I'll bring you
to a jazz concert.
What's your favorite song?
I like Casablanca.
Have you seen that movie?
It's a story about Rick
sending his lover and rival away.
-Who are you looking for?
-I'm Zhou Caina's boyfriend.
I'm here to see Mr. Ye Mingchuan.
If you don't let him see me,
I'll stand here
until he gets off from work.
-You--
-It's simple and straightforward.
I'm here to end our rivalry
once and for all.
Please tell him that.
You're not here to discuss
architectural design with me, are you?
Ye Mingchuan.
What exactly did you do to Caina?
What do you mean?
Caina seems so unhappy.
I know it's because of you.
You should ask her.
Why are you asking me?
Because I care about her.
I don't want her to be sad.
Is that so?
What are your feelings towards Caina?
You shouldn't be the one asking me.
Do you want to go on like this?
Flirt with girls, dump them,
not take any responsibility,
and continue making them miserable?
What have you done for her?
I worked hard to make her happy.
I make her laugh every day.
I give her little gifts every day
to show her how I feel.
How about you?
Yes.
Every time I see her,
I can see the uneasiness in her eyes.
I want to tell you something.
I'm in a hurry. Maybe next time.
Meizuo's waiting for me.
You don't have to.
Just don't avoid me in the future.
I...
I'm not avoiding you.
I thought I could do it.
But no matter how hard I try,
I can't make her happy.
I can only make her sad.
-Ding Qi? Listen to me, Caina.
-You don't need to explain.
I don't want to hear it.
-Listen.
-It's none of my business!
I came to tell you
that I hope you'll leave.
Regardless if it's three or five years,
I never want to see you again
in this lifetime.
Even now,
she thinks I'm seeing different women.
She's so disappointed in me.
James is seeing another woman.
What should I do?
It'll be all right.
Fine.
Just treat me as a womanizing scumbag.
Then she'd get over me quickly
and be happy again.
What do you mean?
I won't bother her again.
I've accepted an offer overseas.
I've made the preparations.
I'll be leaving in a few days.
But before I go,
I hope you can give something to her.
Please give this to her on my behalf.
I hope you can always make her happy.
DONG'S KING OF SQUID
-It's taking so long.
-I'm craving this.
-How much longer?
-Here.
We've lined up for two hours.
I'm so hungry.
How many are we getting?
-My legs are killing me.
-It's numb.
-Is two enough?
-Almost done.
There are so many people.
Never mind. Let's go.
It smells so good.
We're almost there.
Why is your hat so ugly?
Why are you here?
I'm here to bring you home.
Huaze Lei. Make sure to eat a lot.
Don't be shy.
Thank you.
Here.
Is this the legendary
Eight Treasure Squid?
-It's really good.
-All right.
Do you want some Yakult with it?
It will taste even better.
Here.
By the way, Shancai.
You've stayed here for so long.
When are you going back to school?
I don't want to go back yet.
Is your seafood survey assignment
that difficult?
You're not done yet?
No, I'm not.
Shancai.
I remember your professor said
that you can go back
if you're almost done with it.
Yes. Why are you staying here?
You can ask your professors
if you have any questions.
Right? Here.
Here. Huaze Lei.
-Try this flavor.
-Shancai has never cut any class before.
She does well in school.
We don't need to worry about her.
-Of course. Whose daughter is she?
-Yes.
I also believe Shancai
would not disappoint you.
Right, Shancai?
I'll go back to school
as soon as possible.
Have some more.
They don't have this in school.
Your Yakult.
It's quite nice here.
How did you know I'm here?
I saw the trending video online.
Your outfit was really nice.
You were grilling squid.
You looked really cool cooking it.
You're the special prize winner
of the culinary competition indeed.
You didn't disappoint.
You can survive anywhere.
Thanks for coming here.
Don't thank me.
How is he doing?
You can see him
when you go back to school.
If you like him that much,
why won't you tell him?
It's because I like him,
that's why I can't let him know.
-Hi, how many do you want?
-Three.
Three. All right.
Do you want extra or less chili?
-Extra.
-All right.
-Yes.
-Here.
How many do you want?
-Two.
-Two. All right.
-Do you want extra chili?
-No. Put less.
All right.
Is two enough?
-Dine-in.
-Almost done.
Please wait a moment.
There are so many people. Let's go.
Three sticks with extra chili.
-Okay, thanks.
-Be careful.
-Thank you.
-Look at that girl.
-She's quite efficient.
-Yes.
Hi, how many do you want?
-Five.
-Give me five.
All right.
-It's good.
-I'm craving this.
It's delicious.
-Yes.
-Two sticks. Be careful.
-We've lined up for two hours.
-Thanks.
-It's numb.
Hi, how many do you want?
-I want five.
-Five.
There are so many people.
-Do you want extra or less chili?
-Less.
All right.
-It smells so good.
-Two for me.
-Sure. Two, right?
-Yes.
Do you want extra or less chili?
Extra.
-Sure. Please wait.
-I'm so hungry.
What are you looking for?
A place to rent in Airbnb.
There's no need.
We already took care of it.
What?
Shancai, we're here.
Ta-da!
Look.
It's so nice.
Is this really where I lived?
Let me tell you.
This sofa.
I bought it.
Xiaoyou bought this chair.
And this knife.
Li Zhen brought it from home.
-Nice, right?
-It's not just nice.
It's a dreamland.
This table is so pretty too.
-Is it from the online second-hand store?
-Yes.
I was afraid you'll be mad
if it's too expensive.
The quality might be bad
if it's too cheap.
So I chose carefully
from the online second-hand store.
This is brand new.
I bought it when I saw
that it's 40 percent off.
They'll deliver more furniture later.
Thank you, Qinghe. I really like it.
Why do you need to thank me?
I also picked that pillow for you.
Hugging it is like hugging me.
Let's all welcome Shancai back.
-Cheers!
By the way, Shancai,
Meizuo wants me
to welcome you back on his behalf.
He'll come when he's free.
You know he's pursuing Caina right now.
And kept asking us to listen
to their love story.
Really?
I want to know too.
How did they get together?
Someone's willing to listen to it.
Great! We're finally off the hook.
Xiaozi, you can ask Meizuo anytime.
You have to listen to him yourself.
I think you guys are trying to trick me.
How come? Why would we do that to you?
-Hey, Shancai. I want to try your squid.
-Me too.
-Shancai, we all want to try it.
-No.
There are so many of you.
If I grill them now,
then won't all of you suffocate
from the smoke?
I'll get it.
What...
What's this?
Hi, I'm ZZ Bear.
We're delivering the furniture you bought
from the online second-hand store.
You deliver so fast!
Thank you for choosing
our online second-hand store.
Our items are varied and practical.
We hope you'll continue supporting us.
By the way, this is for you.
It's so cute! Thank you.
I just ordered it yesterday.
It's here today.
ZZ Bear, you're so great!
I want to give you a big hug!
Dong Shancai, you're so lucky.
There are so many good friends
who care about you.
Come on.
Even though...
-I want to take a picture too.
-I'll do it.
Move over a bit.
I can't be that greedy.
I already have so much.
FRIEND ACTIVITY
DONG SHANCAI
Thank you, Huaze Lei,
for bringing me back to Shanghai
and renting my old place.
Thanks to all my good friends
who prepared such a nice surprise.
Thank you, everyone. I'm back!
Am I a fool?
I know perfectly well that Ye Mingchuan
is just playing around.
That night in Yunan,
he said he won't settle down.
Now,
I saw him flirting with his assistant.
I should have realized
that he's not serious with me.
Why am I still keeping this lousy coconut?
I must be crazy.
What should I do?
Is there a cocktail called,
"I'll surely regret what I'll do today"?
Yes.
Then I want one.
And add a little "sacrifice" in it.
All right.
No matter what,
meeting me is the start of your happiness.
To your future.
Cheers.
I like it.
Meeting you is the start of my happiness.
Let's toast to our future.
Your "sacrifice."
I'll surely regret
what I'll do today.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene