A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 31
Lei.
Why did you bring me here?
After experiencing so many things,
I think you haven't let out the feelings
that you have bottled up inside.
Don't underestimate me.
I'm Shancai, the weed in the garden.
Shancai.
You have to learn to express your emotions
in order to face reality
and make the right decisions.
So that you'll see things clearly.
I wasn't being emotional.
I was just--
When you're with me,
you don't need to hide your emotions.
I didn't--
Release your emotions.
Release all your sadness,
grievance, and pain.
Do you feel better?
Thank you.
Relax.
You can rest.
You should rest.
I'll always be by your side.
Just be yourself.
Lei, you've always avoided
getting involved before.
Why is it different this time?
Lei, do you know what you're doing?
I really don't understand you anymore.
Meizuo, it's not that
you don't understand me.
The circumstances are different this time.
Do you think Daoming Si and Shancai
can be together again?
We're not sure.
But since you got involved,
this matter has gotten worse.
There's no more room for negotiation.
Maybe.
What does Si think?
You're even smiling.
Do you know Si got so drunk last night?
He said he was celebrating
for you and Shancai.
What celebration?
Ximen and I knew
that he just wanted to escape the pain.
You know we're not siding with Si.
But do you really need to do this?
Must Shancai be Jing's replacement?
Don't say things like that.
Shancai is not Jing's replacement.
They're different individuals.
No person can replace another.
You even asked for a fair competition.
You're just adding insult to injury!
Ximen.
Lei is not like that.
Don't say those things to him.
Lei, explain yourself.
Instead of arguing with me,
you should remind Si
not to escape reality
and be honest with himself.
I'm so tired.
Only a few of these youngsters
are good at doing their job.
Why are they not like Shancai?
Speaking of which,
how long has she been back
from the fishing village?
Has she forgotten about me?
Shancai.
Mrs. Yu?
Why did you call me?
You even dare to ask me why I'm calling.
How long have you been back?
You didn't even tell me.
You didn't come to see me.
Have you forgotten about me?
Mrs. Yu, I didn't do it on purpose.
I was busy moving into my new place.
And catching up with school.
-I'm--
-Why are you still babbling?
Seven o'clock tonight
at Suzhehui Restaurant.
-See you there.
-Hey.
Hello?
Mrs. Yu is so energetic.
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
Shancai.
Tell me the truth.
To you youngsters,
am I old and useless?
Is that why you didn't bother
to come see me after coming back
from the fishing village?
Mrs. Yu, why would you think that?
I missed you.
Why wouldn't I want to see you?
I was just afraid I'd cause you trouble.
You won't cause me any trouble.
But can you tell
that I wanted to trouble you
with something?
All right.
Tell me, Mrs. Yu.
If you need my help,
I'll be there anytime.
All right.
But what can I help you with?
You can help me with a lot of things.
Among them,
you should always visit me
and see if I'm still alive.
Mrs. Yu, don't say that.
They say that good people don't live long.
You'd probably live to be a hundred.
You're mocking me.
That means you still have a strong
fighting spirit.
Here.
Eat some vegetables.
I ordered all this.
-Finish it or you're not going home.
-Okay.
Eat some more.
How's your new home?
It's quite nice.
It's a good thing Huaze Lei helped me.
And my friends decorated the place for me.
How is everything with you and Si?
Daoming Si and I
have broken up.
You broke up?
Yes.
He and I
have nothing to do
with each other anymore.
What?
So,
you've given up?
Mrs. Yu.
I can't win over Daoming Si's mom.
I'm powerless
when it comes to her.
A person like me
wouldn't make Daoming Si happy.
Actually,
logically,
I should stay as far away as possible.
You're good for nothing.
You're so irresponsible.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Yu.
I really did my best.
"Might as well not start a journey
if you're going to stop in the middle."
Do you think I'd say that?
It's never easy to survive
in this world.
You'll encounter a lot of hardships.
There's no guaranteed outcome.
Shancai.
You chose to give up,
to extinguish your passionate feelings
by throwing them to the wind.
You chose others' happiness
over yours.
I know
these things
are even harder to do.
At your age,
you can completely ignore
your friends' problems.
But you didn't.
You're a good kid.
I know better than others
that sometimes,
reality is very cruel.
And hard to overcome.
However,
you have to make a decision.
You already did your best.
If you want to stop now,
then stop and rest.
It's not your fault.
Don't feel hopeless.
Don't blame yourself.
Stop crying.
Remember.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I should make a decision.
What I can do right now
is to eat a good meal.
I can only start fresh on a full stomach.
That's a must.
-Eat.
-Okay.
Eat more.
Here.
Mrs. Yu.
Take care.
Let me know when you get home.
How fussy.
Are you the housekeeper or am I?
Little Miss Housekeeper.
I'm so happy to see you today.
We have to do this again next time.
Of course.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Mrs. Yu.
Mrs. Yu!
Look behind you, ma'am.
-Mrs. Yu.
-What is it?
I...
I want to tell you how I really feel.
I hope at least one person
can know how I really feel.
Mrs. Yu.
Actually, I...
I really like Daoming Si.
I know I won't be able to forget
everything he did for me.
But I can't be selfish
and hurt everyone around me
because of my love for him.
So I...
I can't keep going back and forth
with him anymore.
I had to end it.
Daoming Si.
I wonder what you're doing now.
I miss you.
I really miss you.
But our worlds are completely different.
Maybe our time together
has come to an end.
Let's go back to being friends.
And treat each other casually.
Si's here.
I thought you're not coming today.
It's not good to cut class.
Cut the crap.
Why should I cut classes?
What time is it now?
-Why are you late?
-Who knows?
I think so too.
Good morning, everyone.
-Morning.
-Morning, guys.
Morning, Shancai.
Shancai.
Are you all right?
Why are you asking that?
Of course I'm all right.
I'm going to class.
The professor is really strict.
We're doomed if we're late.
I'll go now.
Shancai.
Our classroom is here.
Yes. Where are you going?
Don't you think Shancai
is really strange today?
She's not just strange,
but it seems like she's possessed.
She's forcing her smile,
pretending like nothing happened,
and acting so unlike her.
Si, what's going on with you two?
If she showed me any affection at all,
I'd be willing to do anything for her.
Elope.
Or even fight with my mom.
But that never happened.
So...
I'll leave it as that.
Is it really over between them?
Who knows what kind of tricks
they are playing now?
Hey, Daoming Si's ex-fiancée.
Can you stop following me?
I want you to take me to Shancai.
You can just call her.
That won't be any fun.
I want to catch her off guard
and surprise her.
By the way, I got her a small gift.
She'll surely like it.
What is it?
What is it...
Take it out and see.
Wait.
Like Daoming Si, would you
place a toy inside to prank me?
Of course I won't.
What's that?
A cactus.
You lied.
You didn't let me finish.
I mean of course I won't miss
-the chance to prank you.
-You...
Xiaozi.
Meizuo, Ximen.
Have you seen Shancai?
I'm not sure where she is.
She's always with Huaze Lei lately.
Does that mean
Si and Shancai are really over?
What do you mean?
Are they still avoiding each other?
No, not anymore.
Si said he doesn't want
anything to do with Shancai.
And Lei said he'll pursue Shancai.
Wait.
That means they didn't make up
after Shancai came back.
Instead, she became closer to Lei?
I think so.
Then Si...
Is Si broken-hearted?
He deserves it.
Where are you going?
Let's rest a bit.
Your legs are so long.
Your stride is so wide.
I can't catch up with you.
I'm not saying my legs are short.
My shoes today...
Why did you suddenly stop?
Go home. Stop following me.
I'll call you a cab.
-Then I'll leave.
-No.
When will you stop walking around?
Si.
If you're unhappy, just say it.
Why are you pretending?
Hey.
Daoming Si.
Daoming Si!
Why are you so annoying?
Si.
Since when did you become so gentle?
I remember the first time that I met you,
you really left me alone, barefooted.
You're different this time.
It must be because of Shancai.
People say that a good woman
can change a man.
I think it's true.
Between me and Lei, who would you choose?
You and Lei?
Based on gentleness, you lose.
-Never mind. Go home.
-No.
I was kidding.
If Shancai didn't choose you,
she must have her own reasons.
Reasons?
What an excuse.
I've had enough of the same excuse!
Whatever it is,
regardless if it's wrong or right,
is it always forgivable
because she has her own reasons?
Why are girls like that?
It's just an excuse
for not being firm enough!
Si...
I'm not sure what I'm saying.
I can't think straight now.
Go home.
I said go home!
You still have me!
I was kidding!
See? You got scared, right?
Were you scared?
Did you get scared? Did you?
Seeing your serious face,
I just wanted to tease you.
It's so much fun, you know?
-Xiaozi.
-All right.
I'm leaving.
You should also go home early.
Daoming Si.
That brow of yours.
Don't keep it wrinkled like that, okay?
When you do that,
you look like an old man.
Okay?
Shancai.
I'm sorry.
I'm such a bad friend.
But...
I really can't bear
seeing Si in so much pain.
SHANGHAI MINGDE UNIVERSITY
19TH GRADUATION CEREMONY
You played really well today.
-Yes.
-It was superb.
What can I do for you?
Huaze Lei, happy graduation.
You're not here to congratulate me.
Do you really like Shancai?
Tell me. What do you want?
If you really like Shancai,
I hope you can let Si give up.
I'm not responsible for that.
If Si really gives up,
a part of F4 would die too.
Then you're just going to let him suffer?
I know Si said he already gave up
on Shancai.
But he didn't.
And I think it's better
if we don't make it worse.
I can't keep on seeing him like this.
You'll help me, right?
Sorry, I can't.
Hey, wait.
I admit...
I have my own motives.
If you and Shancai are together,
maybe
Si would accept me too.
I know I'm a very bad and selfish friend.
But they want to give up
on each other already.
I'm just fighting for my feelings.
Maybe we'd both be happy
after this.
Huaze Lei.
I'm begging you.
Can't you help me?
All right.
What do you want me to do?
Let's take a picture here.
This is for you.
Take care after graduation.
If you go to Sanya, go to our banana farm.
Our bananas are golden yellow,
soft, and sweet.
I sent a box to Professor Ma once.
He said nothing but compliments.
When I think about not seeing
F4 anymore next year,
the campus seems less attractive.
That's right.
My motivation to come to school decreased.
-There.
-Let's take a picture.
-One, two, three.
-Say cheese.
-Happy graduation.
-Let's take a picture later.
-Come here.
Over here.
-Let's take a picture?
-Okay.
Come on.
You woke up late.
You're teasing me.
Hello, Xiaozi?
Now?
At the Math building courtyard?
You're at my school?
Hey.
-Come here.
-Okay.
One more.
Didn't Xiaozi ask me to come here?
Why don't I see her?
-What's that sound?
-It's the violin.
It sounds so nice.
He's so handsome.
What's Huaze Lei doing?
-He's so good.
-What's he doing?
-Who is he playing for?
-I'm not sure.
Why is Lei playing here?
He said he'll just play
at the ceremony, right?
Isn't that Shancai?
Is Lei playing the violin for Shancai?
It's been a while since I saw
Lei play the violin.
The last time I saw him play,
he's still the same person
who always said,
"I really have no interest
in other people's business."
Without realizing it,
a lot of time has passed.
F4's graduating already.
A lot has happened in the past year.
That will be the last song
I play for you in Mingde University.
Shancai, I dedicated it to you.
What are you doing?
No way.
Huaze Lei and Shancai?
What's going on with them?
Huaze Lei is playing the violin
for Shancai?
Wow.
I really envy Dong Shancai.
-Don't--
-Don't push me away yet.
Before I go, please give me some time.
Lei.
I'll be happy...
if you're happy.
Si?
Hello?
You want to see me?
Sure.
I'll wait for you at the coffee shop
near your school.
Okay.
Xiaozi?
Shancai.
Sorry.
What happened today
was planned by Huaze Lei and myself.
You know already, right?
Yes.
So what exactly is going on?
Isn't it obvious?
A low-key person like Huaze Lei
played the violin for you
in front of everyone
and he even hugged you.
He's making a love confession.
A love confession?
Aren't you going to accept him?
You really liked him before.
I'm not sure.
Before,
I'd feel nervous for no reason
when I'm with him.
I'm not sure when it started,
but seeing him now
makes me feel very safe and secure.
He's being so nice to you.
Aren't you the least bit affected?
Right now,
there is no other place in my heart
to love anyone.
Is it because of Si?
Shancai, if...
I mean,
if there's someone
who can comfort Si's pain,
would...
Would you mind?
If there's such a person,
I'd be really happy.
I hope
that his suffering will end with me.
Do you really mean it?
It can be anyone?
Yes.
It can be anyone.
When Si's with me,
he suffers as much as me.
So if there is someone
who can make him happy,
I'd be happy for him too.
Xiaozi, are you waiting for someone?
I...
Yes.
-Why is this so hot?
-Are you hurt?
Shancai, isn't it time
for you to go to work?
Don't be late.
Yes, I have to go to work.
I'll go now.
Shancai.
I really like being your friend.
Me too.
Today, Xiaozi looked really nervous.
She seemed like
she wanted to say something.
And she was speaking hesitantly.
And why would she be helping Lei?
Sorry I asked you to come so suddenly.
It's fine. I'm free anyway.
Turns out Xiaozi was waiting
for Daoming Si.
Sir, what are you having?
-I'll order later.
-Sure.
Xiaozi.
Find a nice guy.
It's not possible for us.
For the longest time,
Shancai is all I can think of.
You finally said it.
I thought you'd say something else.
I'm so relieved, you know?
I thought you're here
because you wanted to forget Shancai
and be with me again.
I'm so relieved that you said that.
How can I go through that again?
That's right.
I wasn't wrong about you.
I'll always treat you as a good friend.
You consider me as a friend
but you consider Shancai as a woman?
Daoming Si.
In our next life,
consider me as a woman too.
Stupid girl.
He's smiling.
I haven't seen his smile for a long time.
I'm not sure why I'm happy for him.
If he's with Xiaozi,
Daoming Si would definitely be happier.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene