A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 48
I know you did it so Daoming Si
and I can be together.
Stay and wait with me
until he wakes up.
We'll wait for him to wake up.
With you around,
I'll feel brave and more confident.
It's been raining for days.
Is God trying to help Si and Shancai,
or keep them from being together?
Xiaozi?
Meizuo, I've made my decision.
No matter what,
I'm on Shancai's side.
Okay.
Let's meet at Si's house in a bit.
Shancai, stay strong.
You have to make it to the end.
You're the luckiest girl
because you have Daoming Si
who loves you with all his life.
Shancai's been standing there for days.
Your son is about to starve to death.
When are you going to give in?
They're being very naive.
They think that by doing this,
they can force me to give in.
I'm telling you,
that's not going to happen.
Mom, can you wake up?
Don't tell me to wake up.
I know precisely what I'm doing.
I'm begging you.
Someone is going to die.
Have you ever thought
about what caused this situation?
It's because they were disobedient.
This is the price they have to pay.
This is the result.
Do you think
they're the only ones who are dying?
Let me tell you something.
I'm dying too.
I'm dying of anger
because my children are disobedient.
Xiaozi?
I've talked to my parents.
I'll never, ever marry Daoming Si.
Because
I really want Shancai to be with Si.
Mrs. Daoming,
give up already.
Is this your decision?
It's my decision.
And it's my dad's decision too.
My dad will talk to you soon.
Mrs. Daoming,
apart from being here with Xiaozi,
we have something very important
you and Zhuang should look at.
Shancai, it's over now.
Shancai, Mrs. Daoming gave in.
She won't try to separate
you and Si anymore.
Daoming Si.
I'm here.
Wait for me.
Why are my feet so heavy?
You're so close to me now.
Why can't I walk over to you?
I'm fine.
I can do this.
If I can't walk to you,
where else would I go?
What is the principle of Schumpeter theory
of creative destruction?
In an entrepreneurial life cycle,
one doesn't always remain an entrepreneur.
Unless he continues to evolve
and create new formations,
which means to destroy the old,
creating the new.
Because with every depression,
there's a possibility to gain new skills.
It becomes a new product, skill,
or business model
to bring the most benefit.
That day, I was studying with Shancai.
She asked me about
a theory I had memorized.
I gave her the answer fluently,
but I suddenly felt that
remembering the theory
and understanding it
were two totally different things.
And Shancai's expression at that moment...
You're incredible.
She was so cute that day.
I had never seen
that expression on her face before.
It was true admiration.
I hope that
I will always be the person she admires.
So, when I do my job in the future,
I'll have more than memorized theories
or an affluent family background.
I want to become a talented person.
I want to find out
how we can truly realize
the creative destruction theory.
I started looking for ways
to think out of the box
and create something new.
So I decided to launch
a startup incubator platform project.
In this project,
I've collected ideas and creative thoughts
from different fields,
places, and products.
This might allow us
to break free of our old ways.
Also, this project is able
to bring about market miracles.
It includes artificial intelligence
technology development
and business strategies
that are applicable to every field.
Practical products that everyone uses
in their daily life will also be included.
Something as small as a sauce packet
can become an international product.
I've done preliminary research
on all these aspects.
Currently, nobody knows about my research.
But I'll announce it soon
because we need the help of many people.
Hey, what is Si's email password?
F4's friendship anniversary.
LOG IN
It's not it.
It must be Shancai's birthday.
That would be too easy.
LOG IN
I guess Si is a simple person.
EMBRACE YOUR DREAMS
Of course, I didn't have enough time,
so I haven't contacted anyone yet.
But I truly believe that
this project is feasible.
I'm very confident.
Also,
I have some very talented friends.
I'm sure when they find out
about this project,
they'll do their best to help me out.
Don't you think this tea is special?
Yes, it's very fragrant.
It's a new kind
that has never been on the market.
Are you willing to incorporate it
-into your pastries?
-Yes.
DONG'S KING OF SQUID
From the first day I met them,
they've always been kind
and sincere to me.
My worries, my immaturity,
my emotions...
They accepted me for who I am.
I'm very happy because my project
can bring hope to people.
Do you really think that
Shancai's Eight Treasure Spicy Sauce
can be sold across China?
Here, nothing is impossible.
My name is Daoming Si.
My family owns an international
enterprise, Daoming Group.
Even though I don't know
whether our group can always be on top,
I hope that when I join the group,
I can instill new energy
into the business empire my dad built.
So that my mom
and my sister can be proud of me.
We're not throwing away our past.
We're using new methods
to bring glory to our past.
The boy that has always got
on their nerves
is all grown up now.
Because he met a girl, Dong Shancai.
This girl taught him a lot.
He realized that the world
doesn't revolve around him.
He learned how to let go of his pride
and accomplish things.
Because her love gave him strength.
I want to remember that moment.
And I want to remind myself
to remember that moment.
Therefore, I'm going to name
this project Embrace Your Dreams.
We all have dreams
and we should all bravely
embrace our dreams.
Mom.
Lei, I can see your face.
You probably think this is so sentimental.
That's exactly what I want.
Why are you here?
After watching Si's project,
you passed out.
The doctor said you were too tired.
We thought you passed out
because you were so mad at him.
But I think you saw
how grown-up and mature he is now.
So you're finally able to let go and rest.
How long did I sleep for?
Seven days.
I tried to wake you up.
You would open your eyes and say,
"The sun isn't out yet."
Just like a child.
I was too exhausted.
I know.
You should rest.
SAFE AND HEALTHY, FRIED KING OF SQUID
UNLIMITED CREATIVITY, SPICY KING OF SQUID
MARKETING POSITION OF KING OF SQUID
EMBRACE YOUR DREAMS
Daoming Group had faced
some financial troubles
because of over-expansion
and management issues,
but now there is hope.
Daoming Feng's only son, Daoming Si,
has launched an incubator platform
for young people to embrace their dreams.
It has won the support
of many domestic financial companies.
They have joined the strategic alliance
and some even plan to invest.
The Shenzhen Tencent Technology Platform
has provided a building
for all the entrepreneurs,
which will become the future
dream incubator headquarters.
It's closed today?
How is that possible?
Hello, Ximen?
I'm here.
Yeah, it's weird.
It says that it's closed today.
Where are you?
What are you talking about?
Aren't we sending off Lei today?
That was yesterday.
We already sent him off.
You didn't show up.
And you weren't answering your phone.
Yesterday?
I didn't show up?
What's going on?
-Where's Si?
-Si went to London with Lei.
To London?
How is that possible?
Why would he ditch me
and go to London himself?
Shancai, did you forget everything?
What's going on?
You and Si broke up.
Broke up?
That's impossible.
Si was held captive
by his mom and stopped eating.
I stood outside his house
and didn't eat too.
Everything was taken care of.
We got back together.
What are you talking about?
That never happened.
You rejected Si.
So he married Xiaozi.
His mom took him to London today.
That can't be.
Where is Si? I need to go see him.
He's probably at the airport.
I have to go there.
Daoming Si.
Where is this?
London.
London?
Why are you in London?
No.
This is a dream.
You know what?
If you listen to me,
I'll let you be my girlfriend.
Wait.
I remember that.
I do.
You know what?
If you listen to me,
I'll let you be my girlfriend.
Gosh, it is a dream.
This dream brought me back
to the arrogant and annoying Si.
No. Wake up!
Wake up!
Shancai.
Listen to me.
No matter where I go, you can be
with me within a one-meter radius.
When I eat, you can sit with me.
Even better,
you can find me anytime you want
and be with me immediately.
Of course,
I can take you to and from school
once a week.
I can give you good snacks at school.
I can help you with homework
if you need it.
We can go to the best restaurant
in Shanghai on your birthday.
When we play games, I'll let you beat me.
You can also enjoy the meteor garden
I designed for you.
Also,
I can get you a new phone
to replace the broken one.
The content is different,
but why does it still make me mad?
What?
You must feel really happy now.
You must be kidding me!
Who do you think I am?
Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?
Daoming Si.
I'm not sure if you're crazy
or if you're dumb.
I don't know
why you said all of that to me.
I don't need your charity
or some special treatment.
I also don't need your money
or a new phone.
I want to go home!
Hey, listen to me.
You'd better not come back crying.
There's nothing in this world
that I can't have.
Who do you think you are?
I don't give a damn.
Well?
You can't have me even
if you give me everything in the world.
Listen.
I, Dong Shancai, simply won't
date a narcissist like you.
What you just said is as stupid
as your pineapple head.
Goodbye!
Fine.
I guess you don't like those things.
Listen to me.
There's nothing in this world
that I can't have.
You're a handful.
You'll be a difficult wife.
I'm leaving.
Don't regret this.
Daoming Si, don't go!
Don't go!
Daoming Si! Stop! Don't go!
If apologies worked,
why would we need the police?
Come back here!
She didn't mean to do it.
She apologized to you, didn't she?
Why do you have to be so mean?
You've got guts.
Daoming Si!
Hey!
You're a bad girl.
Why are you so mean?
It's all your fault!
Si...
Stop crying.
I won't hurt you anymore.
Sorry, I'm late.
If you say you didn't do it,
I believe you.
If you dare kick her,
you'll regret it
for the rest of your life.
Stupid boy.
Why did you come here?
Don't look at me with your filthy face.
Close your eyes.
Idiot.
Didn't I tell you before?
Even if you went to Mars,
I'd still go after you.
You wouldn't be able
to get rid of me in this life.
Stop struggling for no reason.
Shancai.
I just want to be with you.
I, Dong Shancai,
will be with you no matter what.
Can you not leave me?
To the end of the world,
to hell or heaven,
I'll be with him.
Daoming Si!
I'm very happy.
Because you're the only one I'm willing
to trade all the meteors in the sky for.
Shancai.
Do you know what the lyrics mean?
I do.
Do you love Daoming Si?
Do you want me to bring him out?
Yes, please, Zhuang.
I ask of the world, what is love?
People live and die for it.
People live and die for it!
Why isn't the spell working?
Shancai, you're not devoted enough.
All right.
If we can only conjure F3,
just pick one of them
to be your husband then.
What?
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Sophie Chang
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene