A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 30
Miss Caina.
How are you doing?
I'm doing fine.
Actually...
Stop if you're not fine.
Here.
I'll order a cocktail for you today.
Wei Xun.
I want to order
"Goodbye Old Place."
I want it sour, sweet, bitter and spicy.
Everything in it.
One for each of us.
All right.
"Goodbye Old Place"?
What does that mean?
Are we not coming here again?
No, we're not.
Caina.
Do you remember what I told you?
Meeting me
is the beginning of your happiness.
Today,
I want to officially start this happiness.
If you're not coming back,
it'd be
my treat today.
All right. Cheers.
Here.
The taste is horrible.
If we had this the first time,
maybe we wouldn't have met
the second time.
Sometimes,
we cannot tell the outcome beforehand.
Because if we did,
then we'd have no courage to do it.
But if we don't,
how would we know the outcome?
Since we got to know each other,
this is the first time
you didn't get drunk
after having one glass.
Because you said
we won't go to that old place again.
I don't want to face you
in a confused state.
Love is confusing.
I don't want to be too sober today.
Or else, I won't be able
to tell you what I want.
You have something to tell me?
-What a coincidence. I--
-Don't say it yet.
Follow me.
Today will also be
a very,
very good day.
Why are we in my backyard?
I have a gift for you.
What?
A gift for me again?
Let's keep walking. You'll see it.
Meizuo, wait.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because you're worth it.
I'm not as perfect as you think.
I never thought that you are.
Because you're you,
you deserve to be loved.
Just keep walking
and you'll see
where your happiness lies.
No, Meizuo.
I really can't.
I'm moved by everything you do.
But if I go forward,
I'd really hurt you.
You won't.
Every single day will be precious.
Every single day,
I'd make you smile.
This is my promise to you.
Trust me.
Follow me.
This is...
This is Ye Mingchuan's gift for you.
He said
what you wanted
is not an ordinary house.
You wanted a dream.
He spent all his time with Ding Qi
so that he can give you this surprise
on your birthday.
He said this would make you really happy.
You've always been
his most cherished person.
I'm really such a bad person.
Caina.
You should be honest with yourself.
Even though you've been resisting it,
but you've always loved
Ye Mingchuan.
Yes.
I wasn't confident.
I was insecure.
It's all my fault.
I'm a fool who doesn't know how to love.
Meizuo.
Why are you telling me this?
Don't you hate him?
I do.
But
I like you.
I always thought that...
to make someone fall in love with you,
you have to make her smile.
But I've learned
that when you really love someone,
you'd unconsciously
cry because of her.
Meizuo.
You've done so much for me.
I don't want you to feel miserable.
Don't worry.
Youngsters like us fall in love
and move on.
We're honest with how we feel.
But that guy
really likes you.
He just couldn't tell you.
Stop wasting time.
When he leaves,
you might not see him anymore.
Caina.
This tree house is here.
But Mr. Coconut is leaving.
Aren't you going after him?
Thank you, Meizuo.
Thank you.
But before I go,
I hope you can give something to her.
TREE HOUSE DESIGN
I spent a lot of time preparing
this tree house for her.
It's located in her backyard.
She told me
that she doesn't like to stay
in a house like a cage.
She likes tree houses.
When I'm in the house,
I'm a like a bird
in a cage.
Is that so?
You feel that way too?
That's how I've always felt.
It turns out I'm not the only one
who feels that way.
I really like the tree houses
in fairy tales.
I know this is insignificant.
Initially,
I wanted to give it to her as a surprise.
The two must overlap.
The living room in front,
bedroom at the back.
-Overlap.
-Yes.
Then a French window in the middle.
The living room in front,
bedroom at the back.
This tree here...
It has an oval shape.
It's a tree house with two eggs
overlapping together.
-Overlapping together.
-Yes.
Please give this to her on my behalf.
I hope you can always make her happy.
Where is he?
He already left.
He left?
Where did he go?
He confirmed his next project.
He went to the States.
How can you leave?
You're leaving
without finishing the renovation.
If my dad doesn't like it,
I have to go back to the States.
But I want to stay in Shanghai.
How can you be so irresponsible?
I'm not leaving.
But why are you here at the airport?
I'm waiting for someone
to travel with me.
How did you know I'd be here?
I don't know.
Just like before.
I thought you liked me,
but you disappeared.
I really don't know what you'll do.
I'm just doing whatever I can.
Then I can only wait.
How long will you keep waiting for me?
Until that one day
you'll feel that being with me
would make you happy.
Today is the day.
It has been a while.
Caina.
Hi, it has been a while.
Can you do it?
Maybe I should just call the plumber.
Thanks.
You must check all the pipes
in this house.
It's raining so heavily. Go inside.
I'll be done soon. Go back inside.
Did you make it?
Hello.
Are you on a date?
I have a bet with Lei.
I said you're at a concert.
Lei said you're at a bookstore.
What's the matter?
Is it going well?
Yes.
We...
ended it.
Are you feeling okay?
How come?
I'm too cool
to be understood
by regular people.
That's great.
I met a lot of beautiful girls
in my group report recently.
I was worried I have no one
to share them with.
We have a group discussion tomorrow.
Don't be late.
All right.
I'll be there.
It's been a few days.
Haven't you recovered?
Here.
This is for you.
Seven days.
In a blink of an eye,
it's been seven days
since Caina and Ye Mingchuan left.
And I've made a personal record.
I still couldn't move on after seven days.
From the perspective of psychology,
you will go through four stages
after you got dumped.
Shock, conflict, anger
and acceptance.
But a heartless person like you
should already be in the acceptance stage.
So much for acceptance!
I'm shocked, conflicted and pissed.
Why did I accept a heartless person
like you as my friend?
How could you laugh at my handsome face?
That's rude.
Because the dark circles around your eyes
exude the beauty and sadness
of a broken heart.
Hey, Lei.
Didn't you bring Shancai back
from the village?
Why didn't you bring her to see Si?
Si should be the one to ask me
where Shancai is.
You don't need to overreact.
Hey, Si.
I wasn't overreacting.
Si, Shan--
Shanshan is late.
Why are you late?
I didn't have class any earlier.
All right. Let's begin.
Hey.
-I'll take the attendance.
-Tell me. When will that guy move on?
-Feng Meizuo.
-Present.
-Yan Qian.
-Lian Zuo.
-Present.
-Liu Panpan.
-Zheng Han.
-Present.
-Cao Zhen.
-Liu Zhengbo.
-Present.
Shancai, you were gone for two weeks.
What did the teachers say?
I apologized to them and filed my leave.
They made an exception this time.
But the finals are coming up.
-I'm afraid I couldn't catch up.
-It'll be all right.
I can lend you my notes.
You're amazing.
I feel so stupid for always asking you.
You can ask me if you have any questions.
You'll be fine.
However,
a lot of things happened recently.
Don't think too much.
Just move on.
You have a new future ahead of you.
Shancai.
Did I see Shancai earlier?
If it wasn't her,
then I might be hallucinating too.
Shancai, why are you hiding here?
It's nothing.
Is it because of Daoming Si?
Maybe.
I don't want to face him yet.
Shancai,
if you want to draw the line
with Daoming Si,
then tell him directly.
You can't hide all the time.
I have nothing to do with him anymore.
We should go to class.
Why did you ask me to come here?
Si.
What do you plan to do with Shancai?
I've nothing to do with her anymore.
Isn't that obvious?
Shancai's feelings,
her life
and her future
have nothing to do with you anymore?
How many times do I need to say it?
It's over between us.
Do you really believe that?
Lei,
since when are you interested
in other people's business?
All right.
Because it's Shancai, right?
That's why you're so interested.
I told Ximen and Meizuo before
that I won't get
in between you and Shancai,
unless you have nothing to do
with each other anymore.
I'll ask you one last time.
Do you want to be with Shancai?
Stop talking nonsense.
I don't want to repeat
what I already said.
All right.
Then let me officially tell you.
I'm pursuing Shancai.
Do whatever you want.
Listen to me carefully.
I love Shancai.
I've always felt
that we're more than friends.
I backed off before
and wished you both well.
Now I'm not sure
whether I've done the right thing.
Lei.
These words you're saying
are very hard for me to take.
The words "backing off"
piss you off, right?
Then let me say it again
This time, I want to compete
with you in pursuing Shancai.
I don't want to see her cry
because of you.
If you've already given up on her,
then please wish me well,
just like what I did before.
Are you threatening me?
Or are you purposely challenging me?
You don't have to tell me what you'll do.
There's no need for that.
Si.
Even if it's not necessary,
I still think I should tell you.
I value F4's friendship.
So please wish me well.
Or would you rather have a fight with me?
Then let's fight.
Let me tell you again.
You don't have to tell me
what you want to do.
Do whatever you want.
Si!
Let me take care of Shancai.
Your mom said
that if I continue seeing you,
she'll make Qinghe and Xiaoyou's
dads lose their jobs.
I'll talk to her now.
Don't!
I've already decided.
I don't want to have anything to do
with the Daoming family.
I've decided not to contact you.
I can't accept it.
Shancai.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I eat and sleep well.
I'm full of energy and my mind is clear.
Stop pretending.
Don't give up on Daoming Si.
Look at you.
You seem distracted.
I'm really worried about you.
I've really thought
things through this time.
Why?
Can't two people who love each other
be together against all odds?
It's not that easy.
If it's because of me, don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
It's not just because of you.
Maybe I'm just exhausted.
When I was with him,
it felt like things always went wrong.
Can you really forget him?
How do I put it?
There were many times
when I realized I fell in love with him.
Then, get back together.
Falling in love is the best gift
in this world.
Many people want to, but they can't.
But when I first knew him,
I definitely, completely
didn't like him at all.
-I even hated him.
-That was before.
Then I'll go back to the way it was.
I definitely, completely
don't like him at all!
Now I'm back to square one.
As if nothing happened.
-What are you doing?
-I want to tell you something. Follow me.
Let go of me.
Don't you have something to tell me?
If you have nothing to say,
then I'll leave.
Can't you stay with me for a while?
Do you hate it when I'm around?
That's not what I meant.
You suddenly disappeared
and hid in the fishing village
to sell squid. What were you thinking?
The fishing village was nice.
It was relaxing there.
I had squid and went
to the beach every day.
It was like a vacation.
-You don't know how happy--
-Shancai.
You're so disappointing.
Every time I want to have a serious talk,
you either talk nonsense
or hide or sleep.
Do you know how to be honest?
Daoming Si.
-It's not that I don't know--
-If you can honestly face your feelings,
I don't need to be like a clown
getting played by you!
I can't only think about my own happiness
and not care about others.
If Qinghe and Xiaoyou were not in trouble,
I wouldn't have had to go
to the fishing village.
That's just an excuse.
You always have a lot of excuses!
I think I really am that stupid.
I've had enough!
Do you think I want
to wander around
and struggle like this?
Daoming Si.
-Actually, I--
-Don't cry.
Even if you cry,
I won't do anything for you anymore.
Also,
you don't need to run away
when you see me in school anymore.
We have nothing to do
with each other anymore.
Just like strangers.
Let's end it today.
Goodbye.
Daoming Si!
Since that's the case...
Here's the meteor necklace
you gave me.
Daoming Si, I like you.
I really like you.
There was a moment earlier
when I almost told you that.
I almost destroyed my friends' families.
I almost threw away my pride
and self-respect!
I almost threw everything away
and confessed to you.
I really...
almost confessed my feelings.
Shancai, what are you doing?
Shancai, come up here.
Lei.
I'm begging you. Help me find it.
Please come here and help me
find it, okay?
What are you looking for?
Stop it.
Even if it's something very meaningful,
it's gone now.
No! I want to find it!
I have to find it!
Why can't I find it?
I want to find it!
Where is it?
Is this the one?
Is this what you're looking for?
Now, I know how it feels like
to love someone.
Whatever you do,
you can't turn away from your feelings.
You can't stop yourself from loving him.
Si, why are you drinking so much?
What's wrong?
I'm happy. Can't I drink to celebrate?
Celebrate?
What are you celebrating?
To celebrate that Lei and Shancai
are officially dating.
How is that possible?
Are you drunk?
No.
I'm very sober.
After all this time,
I'm the most sober now.
How could that happen?
Has Lei already decided?
What's your plan?
What do you mean?
I wish them well, of course.
Don't you think this is great?
Si, cut it out.
How can you not care at all?
Do you want to kick Lei
out of F4 like before?
No. Why would I do that?
Lei said
I should wish him well,
just like he did before.
Si, this is not you.
Listen carefully.
If you really give her up this time,
you might not have a chance anymore.
And that's Lei.
It'll be more complicated now.
If you regret it later,
you'll lose both friendship and love.
Have you thought it out?
Shancai and I are done.
Are you saying you don't care
who Shancai will be seeing?
Of course!
Come on. Let's toast for Lei!
Si, you...
Even if it's not necessary,
I still think I should tell you.
I value F4's friendship.
So please wish me well.
Or would you rather have a fight with me?
Then let's fight.
Let me tell you again.
You don't have to tell me
what you want to do.
Do whatever you want.
Si.
Let me take care of Shancai.
Don't you think
they're actually quite a match?
A stupid girl...
and a sleepyhead who sleeps all the time.
Si.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene