A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 20
All right. Done. Take a look.
This one won't do. I look so ugly here.
The cookie looks so ugly in this one.
This one won't do either.
Both the cookie and I look so ugly.
Help me take more photos later.
What's so good about this cookie?
Has it been blessed?
Shancai gave it to him.
The most precious happy face
was eaten by you, you jerk.
Damn it.
Look at this. Does it look like me?
Look at this one.
And this one.
I like this one the most.
Look. Does it look like me?
Yes, it does.
I think Shancai is following
the flow of abstract consciousness.
She pursues a close resemblance,
not an accurate representation.
How were things with you two yesterday?
Did anything groundbreaking happen?
We just broke thin ground.
How thin?
We watched the stars together.
And we even kissed.
-What?
It's really thin.
Si, are you really a man?
Hey.
I like it. So what?
I didn't ask you to do the same.
Ma'am, what can I do for you?
I thought it was still too early
to implement that plan.
But I think it's time.
Do it.
All right. Si's graduating soon anyway.
It's good for him
to choose his path sooner.
Yes. Contact them immediately.
All right.
Five million dollars?
Daoming Si's mom wants to give
you five million yuan?
That's a big dowry.
What are you talking about?
She gave me five million yuan
to stay away from Daoming Si.
She's gone too far.
-Who gave her the right to do that?
-That's right.
I'm not her employee.
So refusing this money
means you're refusing to break up
with Daoming Si?
Yes.
No.
I don't know.
Shancai.
Actually, regardless of who you choose,
I just hope you're happy.
You have no idea how infuriating
Daoming Si's mom was.
There are really people who you'd want
to kick when they open their mouths.
Welcome to our store.
Hi, Shancai.
The president asked me
to give this to you.
"Miss Shancai, you're cordially invited
to Maple Hotel
Jingan Temple Main Branch,
VIP Room at 2:00 p.m.
From Daoming Feng."
What does she want this time?
If she wants to see Shancai,
she can come here.
She would like to discuss
yours and Si's future there.
The car is waiting outside.
Shancai.
You can do it.
This way, please.
Dong Shancai, don't embarrass yourself.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Let go of me!
Why did you bastards bring me here?
You told me my sister's back
for a blind date with this annoying girl?
Hey, who's annoying?
You think I want to be here? I was brought
here and I didn't even bring my phone.
For your information,
Mr. Tony from the salon downstairs
is more handsome than you.
Well, young people nowadays
are very outspoken.
They're impatient. That's understandable.
I asked them both to come here today
to introduce them
so that they can slowly
get to know each other.
Then we can prepare for the wedding.
Who's marrying her?
That's what I wanted to say.
Who wants to marry you?
Excuse me.
Please come in.
Shancai, why are you here?
I asked Miss Shancai to join us.
Miss Shancai is Si's good friend.
I want her to be a witness
to Si's future marriage.
Shancai.
Look at Xiaozi.
She's beautiful
and talented.
Isn't she and Si a perfect match?
You should be happy for Si, right?
I am.
I'm happy that Daoming Si
can marry such a nice girl.
Shancai, what are you talking about?
I won't marry this girl
no matter what happens.
What are you saying?
You want me to marry him?
You guys have fun. I'm leaving.
-Wait.
-Bye.
Nobody can leave.
Look at yourselves.
Do you look like future successors?
Let me tell you.
Your lives aren't all about
following your instinct.
Let's go.
This kid.
Don't say anything. Don't look back.
-We're dead if they catch us.
-Who?
Hey, stop.
Are you crazy? Are you running a marathon?
Why is it you?
What do you mean? You dragged me here.
Where's Shancai?
Who's "Suancai"?
Hey, stop right there.
The weather is so cold.
I lost my shoes.
-Stop.
-Let go.
Let me tell you.
Wearing these prison clothes
already irritates me.
You even dragged me here this way.
I don't have my phone and money with me.
I'm even barefoot.
Are you crazy?
If I had any money,
I would've taken a cab.
How can my mom fix me
with someone like you?
My mom's the crazy one
to let me marry you.
You...
You can't leave.
Leave your money or take me home.
Are you a thief?
Or do you think I'm a cab driver?
Don't think you can leave.
Hey, what are you doing?
-I...
-Get off me.
-No.
-Did you grow up with monkeys?
If you don't get off me,
I'll throw you down.
Hey.
Shancai, get out a pineapple for me.
-"Eight Treasure Spicy Noodles" again?
-That's right.
Don't you know?
Your signature dish
is quite famous online.
DAOMING SI CALLING FROM QQ
Why is he calling me?
Does he want me to be a witness
to his wedding again?
DAOMING SI
Si.
Why did you leave by yourself after class?
You didn't call us.
By the way,
how's the financial report
that Professor Luo asked us to do?
No problem, right?
Yes.
It's very easy for me.
Then why are you in a bad mood?
It looks like you and Shancai
had a fight again.
It's a long story.
It doesn't matter.
We have the whole lunch period anyway.
You can take your time to tell us.
Ximen, my brother.
Shancai, let's go over there.
Sure.
I can congratulate Daoming Si too.
Daoming Si.
Congratulations
on your upcoming engagement.
Engagement?
This is your long story?
Hey, I didn't know about it either.
My mom decided on her own.
Is that so?
Weren't you passionately holding hands
-while running to elope?
-Am I crazy?
-Why would I elope with that crazy woman?
-I'm the one who's crazy.
I was dragged by your mom
to witness your romantic moment
with Miss Xiaozi.
I can't explain it to you.
Then don't.
Just talk to your perfect match, Xiaozi.
You ran off together anyway.
That's what you should do.
I'm telling you again.
I made a mistake. I thought it was you.
Our height, hairstyle, and clothes
are completely different.
Are you blind?
Why are you so unreasonable?
I called you all night yesterday.
You didn't give me a chance to explain.
What's there to explain?
You're the perfect pair.
Why drag me into this?
You even played me like a fool.
Who's the unreasonable one?
If you like tall, slim,
sexy and beautiful girls,
why don't you just tell me?
Hey! Shancai, where are you going?
What were they talking about?
I'm so furious.
It was so obvious.
He even tried to deny it.
Dong Shancai. Look at yourself.
You know they're the perfect pair.
Yet you're still not avoiding him.
Now, look what happened.
You're a laughingstock.
What's there to be sad about?
She's tall and slim, just like a model.
That's what Daoming Si's mom
wants for her son.
Wait...
You're...
He Yuanzi?
Isn't that the daughter
of He Group's president?
The one who's in oil and mining business?
The only business lacking
in our family is oil.
A commercial marriage to expand territory.
That's something she would do.
By the way,
how's Xiaozi?
What's she like?
Si likes the hot-headed type,
like Shancai.
This kind of spoiled heiress
should be sweet and silly.
Sweet and silly?
She's a monkey.
A monkey?
She climbs anything that resembles a tree.
And she even bites people's ears.
Bites people's ears?
What kind of interesting games
were you playing?
Cut it out.
I'll go first.
Si's face is even redder
than a monkey's butt.
Aren't you that...
We met at Maple Hotel yesterday, right?
What's your name? I'm Xiaozi.
Why is she here?
Is she here to find Daoming Si?
I'm Shancai.
Shancai.
All right. I'll remember that.
Are you looking for Daoming Si?
Yes.
He's in the cafeteria. Just go over there.
Cafeteria?
Okay.
I happened to drive past
Mingde University.
So I came to visit.
Exactly what kind of school
can produce such a weirdo?
Weirdo?
Yes. Don't you think he's strange?
I think
he might be from Mars.
Yesterday,
I didn't have any money.
I lost my shoes due to running.
I was barefoot.
Tell me. What kind of guy
would leave a girl
all alone on the street?
You mean he left you all alone
on the street yesterday?
Yes, I was so furious.
I walked an hour to get home.
Shancai.
Tell me.
-Does he like...
-Si.
-Shancai's over there.
-men?
I don't think so.
No?
Hey, Monkey. Why are you here?
Speaking so rudely would reduce
your lifespan, you know?
-My name is Xiaozi.
-I don't care what your name is.
What are you doing here?
Thanks to you,
I was in pain all day yesterday.
Don't you care about me at all?
In pain all day?
You were that intense
the first time you met?
What does that have to do with me?
Listen, my mom can't decide who I'd marry.
Then you listen.
My mom can't decide who I'd marry too.
But I like you.
Monkey, what are you talking about?
Okay.
You can't fool me.
Your ears got all red
after I bit them, right?
-Now he's still putting on an act now.
-Bit his ear?
I'll beat you up if you don't shut up.
Daoming Si, from now on,
I'll train you properly
as your fiancée.
We'll get married anyway.
Let's date first.
Si, how can you hit a girl?
Why would I hit a girl? Let me go.
Nonsense. You already did before.
I'm not hitting a girl.
I'm hitting a monkey.
Why can't you be nice?
But the more naughty you are,
the more I want to be with you.
Let go of me.
I'm not playing along anymore.
Whatever you do has nothing to do with me.
Shancai.
Wait for me.
Why did you run away so fast?
What is it?
What are you doing later?
Why?
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's have coffee if you're free.
I didn't say that I'm free.
Let's go. My treat.
Why are you guys all so unreasonable?
I remember now.
You seem so familiar.
Do you know me?
Aren't you the special prize winner of
Chinese Cuisine Culinary Competition?
I remember Caina told me
so many nice things about you
after the competition.
I just got lucky.
Even though I didn't expect you to win,
congratulations anyway.
Seriously,
what do you think
of Si?
How would I know?
I have nothing to do with him.
I'm not talking about that.
I mean,
his face got all red after I bit his ear.
Is he a virgin?
Excuse me, miss.
What are you thinking asking me
such a question in public?
It's very important.
We'll get married in the future.
I have to know.
Since you'll be married to him,
then just ask him. Why are you asking me?
I'm leaving after I finish my coffee.
Actually, I've never actually
dated anyone before.
The guys I know
are either too stupid for me to like
or they feel that my temper is bad
and won't dare to approach me.
I know my parents
would surely find someone for me.
I thought they would find someone ugly,
spoiled and full of shit.
But after seeing Daoming Si,
I think he's quite nice.
Even though he has a bad temper,
but he's very cute.
So I've decided to officially date him.
That's good.
You can do whatever you want.
What does that have to do with me?
Sorry.
Maybe because I'm an only child,
I've been too sheltered
and self-righteous.
That's why I couldn't
make any good friends.
Sorry.
No, sorry about that.
I was too emotional.
You're very nice.
You're lively, cute, and generous.
Is that so?
Let's be good friends.
As friends,
we have to be honest
with each other, right?
Let me ask you.
Have you ever...
liked anyone before?
Not now.
Not now?
That means you did like someone.
Tell me about him.
Well...
Previously...
There was someone who seems dull,
doesn't talk much
and likes to sleep a lot.
What? Your taste is that poor?
Your taste is not that good either, okay?
Then let me ask you another question.
Has Daoming Si ever liked you before?
Shouldn't you ask him that yourself?
I think he must have liked you before.
Even though he told you he liked you,
but has he ever told you
that he only liked you?
No.
No, right?
Then what if he likes someone else too?
Is that so?
Yes.
Help me pursue him.
If he's unmoved,
then that means he really likes you.
If he falls in love with me,
then he's a playboy.
Let's dump him together. Okay?
You have a point.
Of course.
Then you'll help me, right?
It's a deal then.
Here. Try this.
It seems really good.
No, you can have it.
This is the only place
I can be at peace.
But why do I feel so sad?
When I close my eyes,
all I see if Daoming Feng's arrogant face
and Xiaozi's excited face.
It's so annoying.
It's getting more and more annoying!
Why do you find me annoying?
No.
I don't.
I'm happy to see you every day.
Is that so?
I don't mean it that way.
Why are you spouting nonsense?
Your face is so red.
-Do you have a fever?
-Hey.
Because the sun is too strong.
Shancai.
Instead of chatting with me,
shouldn't you resolve
your problem with Si?
I'm not sure what to do either.
His mom feels that I'm a stumbling block
and she introduced
a perfect girlfriend to him.
That girl likes him too.
I feel that I'm the odd one out.
You're not the Shancai I know at all.
After everything that happened,
don't you know how strong
Si's feelings are for you?
You should be confident with yourself
and your feelings for each other.
Really think about it.
You don't know how much pressure I feel.
I want to be confident
with our feelings for each other.
But what should I do?
We're all powerless
in front of Daoming Feng.
Daoming Si.
Why did you come
to my house to look for me?
How dare you ask me that.
Where did you go this afternoon?
You won't answer your phone.
Do you know how long I've waited for you?
What did you do?
Is it fun to pretend to be missing?
You came here because of that?
Do my whereabouts have
anything to do with you?
Then let me tell you.
I had tea with your fiancée
in the afternoon.
That's it.
That crazy, overbearing girl?
Why did you go out with her?
What did she want?
Initially,
I thought
she's a spoiled
and an arrogant heiress.
I realized...
that she's actually quite nice
and straightforward.
She's a thoughtful girl.
She has a good figure too.
-Her upbringing--
-Why are you telling me this?
I wanted to tell you
that I think you're quite a match.
It would be good
if you two end up together.
How about following your mom's advice
and staying by her side?
This way, everybody is happy.
Do you understand?
I was wrong about you.
Dong Shancai.
You idiot.
You hurt Daoming Si again.
You know you'd hurt him this way.
And you've made it even worse.
Lei, I'm so envious
that you're studying music.
Unlike Ximen and I,
who has a lot of reports to turn in.
I have to practice the piano daily.
My hands have a lot of callouses.
It would be easier if I'm incredibly
business-minded like Si.
The stumbling block in Si's life is love.
He has to do better in that subject.
Or else his life would be a mess.
Si.
Why are you drenched?
What happened to Si?
Why do you look so pale?
It seems like he's struggling
in the love subject again.
I think you're quite a match.
Si's situation seems
even worse than before.
Should we try to understand it more?
Understand what?
Isn't He Yuanzi
the fiancée Si's mom found
to make Shancai stay away from Si
after she met her?
What kind of girl
is He Yuanzi?
This is what we'll do.
After submitting our reports tomorrow,
let's deal with He Yuanzi.
Then she wouldn't bother Si.
Then Si and Shancai
won't have anything to worry about.
Lei, what do you think?
What do you mean?
You have to participate too.
This is Si's business.
We'd only complicate things
if we get ourselves involved.
Complicating things
is precisely what we want to do.
Sir, you spent a huge amount today.
We can give you a VIP card.
Can you please fill out your information?
No, thanks.
I, Ximen,
ended up fighting...
over dolls from claw toy-grabber machines
with some brats.
It's the same for me.
I ended up becoming an assistant.
Hey.
Why is there no Durian King doll?
Go and get me one.
Hey, aren't these enough?
You asked me to come out
when I was so comfortable at home.
And now I'm not enjoying myself.
Why are you doing this?
I'll buy all of them for you, okay?
No. You have to get it
from the claw machine.
It's more meaningful.
All right. I'll do it now.
Have you completed your mission?
Miss, all their C cup bras are here.
Don't ask me to exchange them anymore.
No limited edition style?
Then I don't want them.
Are you kidding me?
Let's get things clear, okay?
You guys asked me to come out.
If you can't fulfill my expectations,
then I'll go to Daoming Si.
Don't.
Which style do you want? I'll buy it.
Really?
Then wear it for me.
Quit playing around.
I'm not asking you to strip.
Just try wearing it.
Is this enough?
Why is there no smiling Durian King doll?
I remember there was one in there.
Smile.
Is there such a thing?
You two are so boring.
I'm going to find Daoming Si.
Hi, this is your White Jasmine Dew.
This isn't White Jasmine Dew, is it?
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Shancai, what's the matter?
You look so pale.
And you're so absent-minded.
It's nothing.
I stayed up late
doing homework last night.
Xiaozi suits Si better than me.
His mom would be all quiet now.
This is a good thing.
Dong Shancai.
You should be happy for them.
Shancai.
Xiaozi.
I brought my two assistants along
to see you.
-Ximen.
-Shancai, Xiaoyou.
Finally, there's a cute girl.
What are you three doing?
What else? Dating.
Dating?
I don't know why they asked me
to come out.
This is a bad decision.
We stayed at the arcade all afternoon.
Then we watched a movie.
Then we went around Nanjing West Road.
She hasn't had enough.
She asked me to buy her bras.
Shancai, do you want them?
There are many styles to choose from.
There's no need.
I would rather shop
with Xiaoyou for a year
than see this terrible girl again.
Then when do you plan to date me?
But why are you doing this?
Listen.
At first, I thought I was too charming,
they couldn't help themselves.
Then I realized
they wanted me to give up on Si.
How did you know?
Actually, you did well.
But I don't like you.
No matter what you do,
I won't like you.
Let me tell you.
He gets tired easily.
He doesn't know how to enjoy himself.
But both of them
are especially great to hang out with.
How boring.
I don't think it's fun at all.
Never mind. I'll go ahead.
I'll leave the best supporting actors
to you.
See you next time. Bye.
Hey, who's a supporting actor?
In my world, I'm always the main actor.
Why do you all look so sad?
What can I get you?
-Alcohol.
-Sure. Please wait.
Shancai, you can't drink.
Hey, we can't act this way.
Our plan just failed.
Why are we so down?
What's the matter?
Is it because of that pretty girl?
Pretty?
She looks like E.T.
Didn't you see how Monkey
played us today?
But...
why are you doing something
you don't like for Daoming Si?
Because of you.
Are you stupid?
You know how Si is.
He might even back out of his marriage.
We're doing everything to help you,
yet you just want to give up.
Do you know how sad Si is?
By the way,
on that rainy night,
why did Si come home all drenched?
What happened?
I told him
to date Xiaozi
and said that they're a good match.
How can you say that?
Have you ever considered
how Si would feel?
Have you ever considered how I feel?
I can't change their family.
His mom even went to my house
with five million yuan
so that I'll break up with him.
Have you ever been insulted that way?
Five million yuan?
Did you take it?
Of course not.
You should tell Si.
How else would he know?
Stop it.
Daoming Feng is his mom.
What else can I do?
What can I do to satisfy all of you?
All right.
We'll stop, okay?
I know you have your reasons.
Come on. Let's toast
to the invincible Dong Shancai.
-Here.
-Hey.
-Cheers.
-Meizuo can drink.
But why are you toasting
-when you can't drink?
-Cut the crap. Here.
-Cheers.
The president is waiting for you.
Lei.
Some unfortunate things
happened on Si's birthday.
I wasn't able to contact you afterward.
-Well--
-That's fine, Mrs. Daoming.
Why did you ask me to come here?
I watched you and Si grow up together.
I contacted Jing's family earlier.
They said
that Jing would not
come back anymore, right?
Why are you asking me this?
Actually,
I heard about you and Shancai.
Shancai used to like you.
Because she couldn't get your affections,
she accepted Si.
Is that what happened?
Mrs. Daoming,
I think you've misunderstood.
Si is the one Shancai likes.
Don't you understand Si's personality?
He likes to take other people's things.
Do you remember that Spiderman toy
when you were young?
He got tired of it
after he stole it from you.
I'm worried
that Shancai is just like your toy.
After Si gets her,
he'll dump her.
If that happens,
Shancai would end up getting hurt.
Si was naughty before.
But he's all grown up now.
He wouldn't do that.
Si has been fickle-minded
ever since he was little.
I'm worried that Shancai will get hurt.
By the way,
I heard that your dad's company
is having some financial trouble lately.
I'm not sure about that.
I really don't want
to see your family business
get into trouble.
I'm thinking that maybe
I can help you.
As long as you and Shancai
can start over again.
Mrs. Daoming.
Don't you think
what you're doing is not right?
You're still young.
You'll understand better in the future.
There are some things
that the end is more important
than the means.
My dad would handle our business matters.
Then aren't you worried
that Si would dump Shancai one day?
For that, I trust your son more than you.
Toys and lovers are different.
Regarding Shancai,
I'd protect her as a friend
for the rest of my life.
I'll tell you something else.
We all know Si's personality.
The more you want to break them up,
the stronger their bond will be.
I hope you won't outsmart yourself
and hurt your relationship with Si.
That's all.
I'll get going.
Mrs. Daoming,
let me say again.
Regarding Shancai,
I'd protect her as a friend
for the rest of my life.
I won't let her get hurt.
Miss Heiress.
Why are you here?
What happened?
You...
You're crying.
Sorry.
I'm too emotional.
I'm not sure what to say.
Si...
Did he bully you?
I know him.
You don't have to worry about him. Listen.
I'll help you beat him up.
-I once beat him until--
-Daoming Si agreed to date me.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene