A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 44
This is a day
that's worthy of a celebration.
Even the King of Hell hates Daoming Si,
the immortal monster.
So the monster kicked Daoming Si out
and made him return.
Let's celebrate.
Bottoms up.
Wait a minute.
Daoming Si hasn't fully recovered yet.
Are you guys really his friends?
I think you're a bunch of scoundrels.
A shot of alcohol is nothing
to the undefeatable Daoming Si.
We need to confirm
if he has really recovered.
If he finishes this shot
and he's still completely fine,
then we don't need to worry.
I'll drink this then.
This is
so bitter, spicy, and salty.
How can you drink this?
You're an idiot.
That's not how you do it.
Watch and learn.
Hey.
Don't cause us any trouble.
I think you're the troublemaker.
If you get admitted again,
I won't take care of you anymore.
Hey.
Have you forgotten
how you should treat your boyfriend?
That's enough. Can you not be
so openly affectionate here?
All right.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll live well to repay you all.
Even though we've already graduated,
I believe our friendship wouldn't change.
Let's toast to our friendship.
To friendship.
-Cheers.
Drink this. It's good.
Okay. Thanks.
Sorry about the last time.
You went to the Way of Tea Museum.
And I was busy.
Sorry that I couldn't go there with you.
No. I went there without notice.
I should apologize to you.
Then, we're still friends.
Yes. It's good to be friends.
I suddenly realized
how cute you still are.
I wonder what Ximen
is talking about with Xiaoyou.
It's none of our business.
How come?
I don't want to meddle
in other people's business.
Shancai.
I just want to be with you.
Let's leave.
Leave?
This is a party
to celebrate your recovery.
How can you leave?
Since it's my party,
I can call it a day and leave
whenever I want.
Are we really leaving?
Where are we going?
Somewhere where
there will just be the two of us.
This is where you belong.
An exclusive place for my girlfriend.
Dong Shancai's Love Corner.
From now on,
this is where you shield yourself
from the storm.
No need to worry
and don't handle everything by yourself.
Hearing your heartbeat like this
is so nice.
To know that you're alive
Daoming Si.
I was really,
really scared.
I'm really the biggest idiot
in the whole universe.
Why did I only realize how much I love you
when you almost died?
I don't want to lose you anymore.
You think too highly of yourself.
I mean
I'm the only one worthy of the title,
"The Biggest Idiot
in the Whole Universe."
You are only
-in the minor category of a stupid girl.
-Stop teasing me.
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
Does it hurt? Did you tear your wound?
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
Are you really all right?
It won't be all right
if you keep touching me.
Can you be more serious?
Can't you stay and let me hug you
a little longer?
I'm not sure why,
but I feel like I owe you something.
Really? You don't.
You told me before
that you've climbed more stairs
than I could imagine.
Actually, I knew
even if you didn't tell me.
You climbed
so many flights of stairs
in the middle of the night
just to find the answer for me.
I'm really moved.
I wanted to know the answer myself.
Don't feel like you owe me anything.
All right then.
To show my gratitude,
tell me what I can do for you.
The full package?
What?
Just kidding.
All right.
I joined my school's Way of Tea Club.
Originally, I joined
to understand you better.
But now, I realized
the world of tea is quite interesting.
So can you do me a favor?
It's great for you
to come and teach this class.
Everyone is excited
about the new instructor for the club.
By the way,
the girls in our club are very friendly.
They'll be really happy to see you.
This way.
That's strange.
Where did everybody go?
It's all right.
Even if all the girls in your club
are invisible,
I can still teach the class.
Yifen, can we finish all these junk food?
Everyone takes these junk food
all the time.
Sometimes they're not even enough.
Girls always have room
for junk food and sweets.
-Hi.
We're back.
Xiaoyou.
Who's this handsome guy?
He's the instructor I told you about.
He's also my friend. His name is Ximen.
Is he the boyfriend you said
you were going to introduce to Yifen?
-What's going on?
-I'm not sure.
Xiaogeng.
It has been a while.
Xiaogeng?
Yes.
It has been a while.
So Yifen already knows
this handsome guy
who knows about the Way of Tea.
That's why she couldn't
fall for other guys.
Over 1,000 years ago, the Japanese
people loved the Tang Dynasty culture.
So they sent envoys to learn the culture
of supplying and serving tea
and bring it back to Japan.
Turns out Yifen is Xiaogeng.
Supplying and serving tea mean
providing tea leaves in pavilions
on the side of the road
for passersby to quench their thirst
and make friends.
It symbolizes
sharing good tea with strangers.
It can be considered a state of mind.
Okay. Now I'm going to demonstrate
how to make tea.
Who wants to be my assistant?
-Me.
Let me do it. I'm sitting closest to you.
She's considerate and funny.
And cute too.
No wonder Ximen can't forget her.
Me. Pick me.
-Pick me.
-Me.
I brought Ximen
back to Xiaogeng.
Did I already have
some sort of premonition?
Geng Yifen, take a deep breath.
Learn how to let go and turn away.
Don't think about someone
who doesn't love you.
After all these years,
you've already moved on.
After all these years...
Why?
Why do I still like you so much?
The Chinese tea culture
is broad and profound.
Instead of understanding it,
just try and taste a cup of good tea.
Everyone, please enjoy.
-Thank you.
What do you think? Is it good?
-So handsome.
He's asking if it's good.
What do you mean "handsome"?
These three people.
-He's really handsome.
-That's right.
Yifen.
It turns out you're Xiaogeng.
I heard about you from Ximen.
He must have been laughing
at my ugly past.
No, actually Ximen--
Xiaogeng, I'm really glad to see you.
Yes.
It has been a while.
Do you still have class later?
Let's go out and talk.
Xiaoyou should come with us too.
Xiaoyou too?
I still have class. You two go ahead.
Are you really not coming?
Yes. I want to, but maybe next time.
We'll go ahead then.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
It's been a while
since we walked together on this street.
Now, I can walk by myself.
There were no street lamps before.
Every time we finished late at school,
you'd always go home with me.
And you even told me that
you were trying to protect me.
You were afraid of the dark yourself.
Are we talking about our ugly past now?
I remember someone wanted
to pick fruits from the rooftop
and fell from so high up...
But didn't even get a scratch.
Actually, I know.
The reason why I was miraculously safe
was because you were protecting me.
I really regretted
asking you to go to that rooftop.
And saying goodbye
to you when you didn't go.
I was such a coward,
but I was greedy.
I couldn't bear to hear your answer.
I'm the one who should apologize.
If I went there
that day,
things between us...
wouldn't have turned out like this.
Xiaogeng.
Can you give me a chance
to make up for it?
Let's go to that rooftop again.
Can we start over again?
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Is something on your mind?
Yes.
I think I did something really bizarre.
I helped Ximen find his first love.
And I helped them reunite.
Does your foot hurt?
Didn't you just drop a rock
on your own feet?
I'm already miserable. Stop teasing me.
All right.
Don't be sad.
You'll surely find someone better,
more outstanding
and someone who's perfect in the future.
No.
Ximen is the perfect one.
Mrs. Yu.
How is Si doing?
Yes, ma'am.
Si is recovering at the hospital.
But he still needs more time.
Don't worry.
He's recovering quickly.
The doctor said
he'll be in good health soon.
This child
has always been healthy
ever since he was little.
Okay.
All right then.
Can you give me a chance
to make up for it?
Xiaoyou, what time
will you be working today?
Do you have time to meet me?
Xiaogeng, why did you
suddenly come and see me?
Ximen asked me to go
to that rooftop with him today.
That's great.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I can tell
that you like Ximen too.
So I feel that I have to tell you this.
Is that so?
Xiaoyou.
Thank you.
I'll work hard to make up
for what Ximen and I have missed.
Do you still have to work later?
I won't disturb you then.
I'll get going.
-Okay.
-Bye.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Xiaoyou.
What's the matter?
Why did Xiaogeng come to see you?
Shancai.
Remember that time we went shopping
and the saleslady told me
my eyebrows look sad
and I should draw a different shape?
What are you talking about?
My eyebrows do make me look sad.
This eyebrow shape is not good.
Even though I'm happy,
I still look sad.
Your eyebrows don't look sad.
What happened?
Xiaogeng told me
that she'll go with Ximen
to that building tomorrow.
Ximen has always been the man of my dream.
A dream I don't want to wake up from.
So Shancai,
if I look really sad,
it must be because of my sad eyebrows.
Please don't worry about me.
It's fine.
Hey.
-You scared me.
-What is it?
You told me to come here so urgently.
Do you want to see my singing talent?
It's Xiaoyou.
She's already inside.
This is about Ximen again?
When will she ever learn?
Let's go.
So, you're joining us for real?
You're so worried about her.
That means she's not doing very well.
So I should support you and stay with her.
What are you doing?
Daoming Si.
You're so reliable
when I need you the most.
Nonsense.
I'm the successor of a business empire.
Being reliable is a basic requirement.
You're such a good guy.
You're better than a best female friend.
And you just realized that now?
Wait a minute.
You called me your best female friend?
Shancai, why did you call me
your best female friend?
Hey.
Are you sure she's broken-hearted?
I'm not really sure now.
Are you really not singing?
Is it okay to keep the mic to myself?
It's fine. Just sing your heart out.
Xiaoyou.
You already sang that song
so many times in one hour.
Aren't you tired?
I'm not.
I'm very excited.
Can you help me choose more songs?
I'm glad you guys came with me today.
I don't think I can sleep at home.
Xiaoyou.
Just let her get it all out.
Then she can sleep when she's tired.
She'll get over it soon.
Go and choose some songs for her.
Okay.
I think Xiaoyou will be fine.
The night will be over soon.
A new day will come.
Good morning.
Why are you so early?
You're early too.
You couldn't sleep
so you came here this early?
You're talking about yourself.
Busted.
Let's go.
I'm running out of energy.
Well, that went on for quite a while.
I wish I had that energy too.
Tell me. Do you think they've already met?
Do you regret it?
No, I don't.
My heart is just aching.
I'm not sure when the pain would stop.
Stop thinking about things
you're not sure about.
Hey, you don't have to say anything.
That's how I did it.
No one knows what'll happen in the future
no matter how much we think about t.
Just treasure each moment.
Your heart is aching.
That means you're still alive.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
Probably because
I didn't sleep well last night.
You've always been weak
since you were little.
Yes.
When you were little,
you kept playing nonstop.
You know your body couldn't take it.
But you still kept going.
You slept when you were tired.
You ate when you woke up.
Then your stomach hurt when you were full.
Why do you make me
sound like an animal?
In my loneliest, saddest time,
your innocence saved me.
Thank you.
Ximen.
Do you know I've always loved you?
Yes.
You knew?
You're so easy to read.
And you're so difficult
for me to figure out.
Ximen.
Have you realized
after we met again
that we've always...
Always what?
Nothing.
It's almost time. Let's go.
Okay.
The sun is so bright.
It's 8:00 a.m. It should be bright.
Shancai, Daoming Si, thank you.
It's good that it's the weekend.
We can catch up on some sleep.
Xiaoyou, will you be able to sleep?
Yes.
Hello? Xiaogeng?
Can you come to the rooftop?
What? Now?
Okay.
It's so strange.
Isn't Xiaogeng supposed to be with Ximen?
Why did she ask me to come?
Are you going to see Ximen?
Do you want me to drive you?
I...
But...
But what?
You'll find out if it's good or bad
once you get there.
It's nearby. I'll go there myself.
Shancai, Daoming Si, thank you.
Xiaoyou.
You can do it.
Ximen.
You're here.
Why is the sign gone?
Where's Xiaogeng?
She left.
Did she leave because the sign is gone?
But that sign no longer matters.
-What's important is that you're here.
-Xiaoyou.
It's over between me and Xiaogeng.
Over?
What does that mean?
We still missed it.
Ximen.
Don't you think that this is a sign
that nothing
would remain?
Did you realize it?
After we met again,
everything we talked about
was our past.
And it can only stay in the past.
We think of the past
because we can't go back to it anymore.
Is that what you're trying to say?
I'm sorry.
Five years ago,
that day you asked me to come here
was our "Once in a Lifetime" moment.
I missed it.
It's fine.
Some things
are only meaningful if they happen
right there and then.
If you missed it,
just move on.
Actually, I can tell
that your "Once in a Lifetime" moment
doesn't belong to me anymore.
It belongs to another girl.
Girls' intuition can be very accurate.
Xiaogeng.
I owe you a confession nevertheless.
The old me
really liked you.
Back then, you were
more important to me than anything else.
Ximen.
Me too.
I used to really like you so much.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene