A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 38
Goodbye.
To me,
the "Once in a Lifetime"
for me and Xiaogeng
was the moment she turned around and left.
You're hurting yourself this way.
Until now,
I still can't resist thinking
that if I went over
and hugged Xiaogeng tightly then,
what would happen to us
right now?
Xiaogeng.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have stood you up.
Would I be able to find it
without knowing what it is?
Should I give up now?
I've been to almost
all the buildings in Lujiazui.
Only a few are left
with a view of the Oriental Pearl Tower
and are accessible at 5:00 a.m.
What did she want me to see?
I'm still not sure at this point.
Is that the one?
No way, right?
It's so unimaginable.
Ximen.
I think I found it.
I found it.
Ximen.
I have something important to tell you.
You have to see me today, okay?
I'll wait for you at the third stop
of Lujiazui Metro Station.
You have to be there.
Okay?
Someone's inside.
Is it a thief?
Or Daoming Si's bodyguards?
No.
Ms. Zhuang already took care
of the bodyguards.
No matter who it is,
I have to make a move first.
Go away!
Get out of here!
What are you doing?
Why are you waving that around?
Mom.
Thank goodness, it's you.
I thought it was a thief. I was so scared.
It's a good thing
that I have a strong heart.
Or you'd have scared me to death.
Mom, why are you here?
I called you last night,
but you didn't answer.
I wasn't home last night.
You weren't home?
Where did you go?
I spent the night
at Daoming Si's house last night.
Daoming Si's house?
You two were all alone
and full of passion.
No.
Not that.
It's not what you think.
Tell me.
Last night, did you and Daoming Si...
I mean, did you two seal the deal?
No.
Mom.
Don't you trust your daughter?
Yes, I spent the night
at his house last night.
-But I--
-But you're still
pure and innocent, right?
Mom.
Actually, he and I
are dating secretly.
We can't let his mom know.
What?
That wench still doesn't know?
How much more does she want you to suffer?
Daoming Feng is really crazy.
There must be something wrong in her head.
Where is she? Tell her to come out.
I want to talk to her.
Mom, stop it. She's not in Shanghai.
That's good.
Or else, I'd give her a piece of my mind.
Mom, how did you find time to visit me?
You know, that idea of yours
is really great.
Our squid business is doing really well.
Business is booming. We're so busy.
Your dad and I both have
high hopes for our future.
I initially didn't have time to come here.
But I really missed you.
I was curious how you're doing all alone.
So I came here today just to see you.
-Mom, wait here.
-Okay.
-This is for you.
-What is it?
Mom.
I know it's hard to do business.
But skin care is also very important.
Look at you.
There are fine lines around your eyes.
Are you saying that I look old?
All right. I know
you're concerned about me.
Mom.
I'm fine here.
-Really?
-Yes.
Is Daoming Si being nice to you?
Did he do anything bad to you?
No. He's quite nice to me.
That's good. I don't need to worry then.
This time, you seem different from before.
You're all grown up. You've matured.
Come on.
This is so nice.
And now for our weather report,
starting on Wednesday,
due to strong winds from the north,
most of the East China region
will experience cold waves.
EAST CHINA REGION TO EXPERIENCE
COLD WAVES. PLEASE KEEP WARM.
When the cold waves come,
and the weather continues to be this bad,
it would be impossible for him to come.
So...
today might be our only chance.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is not accessible at this time.
Please try again later.
Hello, Xiaoyou?
You haven't come
to the milk tea shop lately.
Did something happen?
Shancai, did you see Ximen?
I need to talk to him.
It's Ximen again.
Xiaoyou, you...
I haven't seen F4 the whole day.
Then can you ask Daoming Si
if Ximen is with him?
What's the matter?
Why do you sound so anxious?
I have to see him today.
Why?
Just help me look for him first.
Xiaoyou.
For the past few weeks, you've been
keeping a lot of things from me.
I'm really worried, you know?
Shancai.
I know what I'm doing.
Today
is a very important day for me.
If "Once in a Lifetime" really exists,
I don't want to miss it.
Shancai...
I know you're worried.
I won't let myself get hurt.
Trust me.
All right.
I'll help you look for him.
Really?
Where should we meet?
I heard from Daoming Si
that they're going
to an art gallery here in Shanghai
for a symposium.
Let's meet there.
I think we'd find them there.
Okay. See you later.
Bye.
Any progress?
Still no news from him.
Xiaoyou.
Do you really need to see Ximen tonight?
We're going out the day after tomorrow.
Do you want to go with us then?
If possible, I want to see him tonight.
Why must it be tonight?
Because the cold waves are coming.
Cold waves?
Do you want Ximen to keep you warm?
Meizuo.
Stop teasing Xiaoyou.
All right.
I just want Xiaoyou to relax.
Look at her knitted brows.
Ximen is not here yet,
but you'll have gone old
from waiting like this.
Thank you, Meizuo.
I'm fine.
Actually, you can go home first.
I can wait for him by myself.
All right.
I mean all right.
We'll wait with you until Ximen arrives.
Xiaoyou.
It's all right.
We'll wait with you.
It's only 8:00 p.m. anyway.
This stupid girl
can't even fix her own problems.
Yet she's worried about other people.
Hey.
You three.
It's past midnight now.
Ximen is still not here.
Call and tell him to hurry up.
Lei, you call him.
Meizuo, you call him.
See if he's at the bar.
I called the bar earlier. He's not there.
What are you doing?
Help me look for him.
Okay, fine. Don't be mad.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is not accessible at this time.
Please try again later.
Ximen, it's past midnight.
You're still not here.
What's going on?
Listen.
We won't leave until you get here.
And if you don't arrive soon,
we can't be friends anymore.
Because Shancai will kill us all.
We will all be dead.
See you in the next life.
Is that good enough?
Xiaoyou.
It'll be all right.
Please.
Thank you for the lesson.
I'll practice it when I get home.
Ximen.
When we last saw each other,
you were still in high school.
You're all grown up now.
How have you been?
Thank you for your concern.
I'm fine.
Well, despite all challenges in life.
Life is full of ups and downs indeed.
You should be happy about it.
If life only goes smoothly,
that means you'll never grow up.
Thanks for your concern.
Ximen, where have you been the whole day?
Ximen, if you don't come now...
Never mind. I'll just sleep
in the coffee shop.
I regret not bringing
my sleeping bag with me.
Ximen, it's past midnight.
You're still not here.
What's going on?
We won't leave until you get here.
And if you don't arrive soon,
we can't be friends anymore.
Because Shancai will kill us all.
We will all be dead.
See you in the next life.
Ximen.
I have something important to tell you.
You have to see me today, okay?
Hey.
Based on our height difference,
isn't it uncomfortable
for you to sleep like this?
It is.
But I like it.
Xiaoyou.
We'll just find Ximen tomorrow, okay?
That's right.
When we find him tomorrow,
I'll surely beat him up for you.
And I'll force him to call you.
Sorry, everyone.
I made you wait with me until now.
Because I...
I'm too impulsive.
Let's go.
It's all right, Xiaoyou.
I'll surely find Ximen with you tomorrow.
Ximen.
Who do you think you are?
We've waited for you all night.
You were gone the whole day.
Where did you go?
We were all just waiting for you.
Do you think you're that important?
Am I not important?
Then I'll get going.
Get back here.
-What are you doing?
-I want to beat you up.
-Cut it out.
-Where did you go? Tell us.
Let Xiaoyou speak to him.
Even though I told you
I won't bother you again,
I think you have a right to know.
Even if you treat me
like a stranger starting tomorrow,
today, you have to do what I tell you.
What do you want?
Give me a chance
to show you what Xiaogeng
wanted you to see then.
It seems like the problem is solved.
I'm leaving.
I'm going with you.
That's great. It's still dark.
We still have a chance.
The elevators are not working
at this hour.
We can only take the stairs
to the rooftop.
What?
There's no time to waste.
Do you want to have more regrets?
We have to hurry.
There are about ten more floors to go.
Are you all right?
Can you still go on?
I'm fine.
There's no time.
Why don't you go ahead?
I think it's almost time.
I searched all over
before I found this building.
I remember you told me
that Xiaogeng asked you to come
during this season, at this specific time.
At first, I didn't get it.
It was until yesterday morning
when I saw the news about the cold waves.
Then I knew
that if you miss the timing,
she would never have a chance to tell you
what she wanted to say.
Look over there.
XIMEN BUILDING, MY BELOVED
The words on the building in front
will disappear temporarily
for three minutes
due to the sun's refraction.
XIMEN, MY BELOVED
What an idiot.
She asked me to come so early
in the morning just for this.
She's so silly.
She's really silly.
XIMEN, MY BELOVED
Hey.
After waiting for Ximen,
we're now waiting for Xiaoyou.
We had dinner and now breakfast.
How long do we have to wait?
Go home if you're tired.
Xiaoyou is my best friend.
I won't leave until I hear back from her.
You only care about your best friend.
I wish you had the same concern for us.
What's there to be concerned about?
You think I don't notice
how uncomfortable you are
staying at my house?
What else can I do?
What does this mean?
I've been wanting to tell you this.
I don't want to sneak around anymore.
How long do you think
my sister can help keep this a secret?
So,
you want me to live with you in London?
But...
But my English is very bad.
And the only thing I know about London
is that London Bridge is falling down.
-It's dangerous--
-Shancai.
I want to make our relationship public.
I don't want to sneak around.
I'm not happy about this.
And neither are you.
-But your mom--
-So before anything happens,
we must convince my mom.
How is that possible?
How is that impossible?
Even though she's hard to convince,
she's still my mom.
I think I just need to tell her how I feel
and she'd understand me sooner or later.
Trust me. Just follow my lead.
That's all. Give me an answer tomorrow.
I'll go and get some sleep.
It's not that simple.
You don't know the things
your mom did to me.
Can I trust you?
Si and Dong Shancai are dating.
What happened to the bodyguards I sent?
They've been paid off.
Paid off?
By Zhuang?
And Si rented the place next door
to Dong Shancai.
They're living closely together.
Your White Jasmine Dew.
Thank you.
Please come again.
Can we resolve this
if we go to London?
Xiaoyou?
Thank you for helping me
look for Ximen that day.
I wasn't even able to thank you then.
Thank you very much.
Your hair...
I just had a haircut.
Do I look like a boy?
Does it look strange?
No. It's nice.
-Really?
-Yes.
But why did you cut your hair?
Did something happen?
No.
I just wanted a change.
And I've had long hair for so long.
I've grown tired of it.
Suddenly cutting her hair short,
suddenly wanting some changes,
those seem to be things
a broken-hearted person would do.
I'll go get changed then.
Hey, Xiaoyou.
Did you and Ximen...
Shancai.
I want to date again.
This time,
I really want to have
a happy relationship.
Sorry.
I made you so worried
this time around.
But I already did my best.
I feel at peace now.
You did your best?
What does that mean?
Did something happen with Ximen again?
Just give me a little more time.
I'd tell you everything when I'm ready.
You'd listen to me, right?
Yes.
The gentle Xiaoyou
recklessly did everything
for the person she loves.
I suddenly feel like
Xiaoyou has matured a lot.
She looks especially brilliant
and attractive.
And I
haven't listened to my heart
like she does for such a long time.
Even though she's hard to convince,
she's still my mom.
I think I just need to tell her how I feel
and she'd understand me sooner or later.
Trust me. Just follow my lead.
This time,
I should also be ready
to fight for my future.
I have to trust Daoming Si.
-Where are we eating?
-At a western restaurant.
We'll be there soon.
Let's go.
This is the new smart jewelry from Italy.
It's a hot trend right now.
The most important thing is it lets lovers
stay connected with one another.
What do you mean by that?
These bracelets are connected
with the mobile app.
Every time you think of each other
or need each other,
just lightly tap on it like this.
No matter how far you are from each other,
you'll receive the thought automatically
as it lights up and vibrates.
That's amazing.
So every time it lights up,
it means he's thinking of you.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene