A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 27
Shancai has arrived, ma'am.
-Ask her to come in.
-Yes.
Please come in.
Bag.
You're all sweaty from running.
Have some tea.
I brought them from London.
There's no need.
I'll leave after I speak my piece.
I like your style.
Then let's get straight to the point.
I'll agree to all your conditions.
Please stop destroying my friends' lives.
Mr. Fang? It's me.
Cancel all of my instructions.
What will you do for me?
I'll leave immediately.
I'll cut my ties
with Daoming Si from now on.
Satisfied?
Then why are you still standing there?
Maybe you're a successful businesswoman.
A person in the Forbes' billionaire list.
But you use people as tools
to achieve your goals
with the power you possess
and destroy life's precious things.
You're even more despicable
than a criminal.
Life's precious things?
Don't tell me you're talking about
love and family.
Kid.
You're wasting my time.
Do you know
that the time I spent listening
to your joke
is enough to close a business deal
that your family
cannot even earn in three generations?
No matter how nice your make-up is,
it cannot hide your ugly face.
Do you know the price you'll pay
for saying that?
Do whatever you want.
But I'm telling you.
No matter how you break me,
I will continue to pick myself up.
But if you dare to hurt my friends,
I won't let you off easily.
You bitch.
Why is Shancai not back yet?
It's already eight o'clock.
At this time,
she should have already started working.
Mrs. Yu.
Shancai came back earlier.
She came and left?
Yes, she seemed to be in a hurry.
Why would she be in a hurry?
Where's the president?
She left and went back to London.
TO MRS. YU
Mrs. Yu,
my parents suddenly asked me
to go back to the province.
So I have to leave today.
I hope you understand
how much I miss my family
and want to be with them.
I'm very sorry for being so selfish.
Thank you for taking care of me.
You treated me like my own grandma.
I will never forget you.
I'm really grateful.
Shancai.
Why are you standing here?
Why are you all drenched? Let's go home.
I want to tell you something.
What's the matter?
I...
I can't see you anymore.
What are you talking about?
I'm leaving your house tonight.
Why are you acting like this?
Didn't we go to the Rabbit Hole together?
So sweet.
How do you eat these things?
Cakes are supposed to be sweet.
You even said you want us to be balanced.
And told me not to move out.
We're lovers.
The effort we put in the relationship
should be balanced.
If I'm too reliant on you,
we'll lose this balance.
Have you forgotten already?
I didn't forget.
Then what's going on?
Turns out you didn't want me
to protect you
because you wanted to break up with me?
No.
I meant everything I said.
I meant it when I told you
I wanted to be your girlfriend.
Then why?
Tell me what's wrong.
You're saying this out of the blue.
I can't accept it!
Your mom said
that if I continue seeing you,
she'll make Qinghe and Xiaoyou's
dads lose their jobs.
I'll talk to her now.
Don't!
I've already decided
to have nothing to do
with the Daoming family.
I've decided not to contact you.
I can't accept it.
You're leaving me because
of such a lousy reason.
That's nonsense!
Shancai.
Do you really think I'm a useless guy?
Forget about my family, my mom,
and everything else.
Have you ever thought of me
as a worthy guy?
Yes.
Since a long time ago.
Stop!
Stop it!
At that time,
to me,
you're not the successor
of the Daoming Group
or Daoming Feng's son.
Stupid girl.
Good thing I came here early.
Or else what would you do?
You stupid boy!
Why didn't you fight back?
If I fought back,
then I would really lose.
You're just an overbearing,
innocent, kind and gentle man.
I'll put it on for you.
No. It's too expensive.
I can't accept this.
Don't move.
Shancai.
Be my girlfriend.
I was naive
thinking that I can forget everything
and just be with you.
However...
No.
Not even once.
If I really like you,
I wouldn't leave you.
I should go now.
Bye.
Shancai.
I can't stop walking.
I can't turn back.
If I hesitate,
I'd run into Daoming Si's arms.
If that happens,
the harsh words I tried so hard
to tell him would be in vain.
I'm getting numb.
Aside from the pain of my heart
being torn apart,
I can't feel
anything else.
Mr. Lu, why don't we have water?
That's right.
This house's pipes are old.
There's nothing we can do.
The pipes burst from the heavy rain.
But don't worry.
Well...
Terence said that he'll take care of it
by wrapping the pipes.
He's outside right now.
He should be done soon.
He's here again?
Yes.
It's good that he's here.
I can go and rest.
It's raining so heavily. Go inside.
I'll be done soon. Go back inside.
Go back inside.
No.
Have some ginger tea.
Did you make it?
It's good.
Let me guess.
You added brown sugar,
lemon, and a little cola.
And a special flavor.
Is it sesame?
Am I right?
You're good.
I'll give you some more.
My heart is already warm.
You got drenched because of me
and fixed our pipes.
I think anyone with that much compassion
would do something seeing you this way.
So you're taking pity on me?
Yes.
I guess so.
Caina.
Actually,
I've always wanted to tell you...
Tell me what?
-Sorry.
-It's fine.
Do you want to take a shower?
There's no need.
Hello? Meizuo.
There's a visitor in your house?
Yes. It's Terence.
Terence is in your house?
He's taking a shower?
No. I asked him to, but he refused.
No.
That's not what I meant.
Why am I...
I can't explain now.
I'll hang up now. Bye.
I'll get going.
Good night, Caina.
MINGDE UNIVERSITY
Sorry. The subscriber you called
does not answer.
Please try again later.
Si, why did Shancai disappear?
Wasn't she staying with you all this time?
Isn't your relationship going well?
Why would she disappear?
Did you make her mad again?
Daoming Si.
Where's Shancai?
She has no home and no money.
How would she survive?
Is it because of what happened
a few days ago?
Shancai sacrificed herself
to protect them, right?
It looks like what happened
to Xiaoyou's family and mine
-is all because of your mom?
-Shut up.
Shut up? Daoming Si.
Why did you let your mom
do such a thing to us?
Why did she do such a thing to Shancai?
What did Shancai sacrifice?
Where exactly is she?
Why can't you protect her?
I said shut up! Don't you get that?
-Si.
Did you see the look on Si's face?
It's the same as before.
The old Si is back again.
Didn't Shancai contact you?
No. I'm also very worried.
I can't reach her.
Why did she suddenly disappear?
Actually,
I heard
that Shancai left because of us.
I knew it was strange.
My dad was sued.
After Shancai disappeared,
the lawsuit was withdrawn.
That's right.
After Shancai left my house,
my dad received a call saying he doesn't
need to work in Qinghai anymore.
It must be because of Daoming Si's mom.
How can she do that?
She used us to deal with Shancai.
Because of us, Shancai...
But she never said a word.
That's what she always does.
She silently helps us.
She never complains even when
she's carrying such a heavy burden.
Actually, I don't think it's our fault.
Daoming Si's mom knows that Shancai
values her friends.
That's why she used it to her advantage.
Isn't Daoming Si going to do
anything about it?
Don't mention that scumbag.
Shancai left.
Daoming Si didn't say anything
and wouldn't let us look for her.
She didn't file a leave with the school.
What if she gets expelled?
But did Daoming Si really act that way?
Yes. I'm so furious!
I shouldn't have entrusted Shancai
to that guy.
You're Shancai's best friends.
Tell me. I'm more suitable
for Shancai than Daoming Si
and I can make her happier, right?
Qinghe.
We can see that you really like Shancai.
That's right.
I like Shancai the most.
I wonder where Shancai is.
Is she out crying because of that bastard?
Yes. I wonder how she's doing,
whether she's cold or hungry.
I wish she'd contact us soon.
I'm really worried about her.
Goodbye, Daoming Si.
Goodbye, Mingde University.
Dad.
It's late. What's the matter?
Caina.
When are you coming back to California?
Something came up.
I'm busy.
You're busy?
What are you busy with?
Your marriage with Tian Ye
was cancelled all of a sudden.
Our relatives keep asking me about it.
Well...
I feel so humiliated.
I have my own thoughts regarding marriage.
All right.
Since you're not planning to get married,
come back immediately.
Our company needs your help.
Dad.
I don't want to work in our own company.
I want to stay in Shanghai.
Stay in Shanghai?
What do you plan to do in Shanghai?
There are lots of things I can do.
For example,
our ancestral house is so old.
You've always wanted
to renovate it, right?
Caina.
This house was your great grandfather's.
Your mom kept trying to hire
that famous designer.
But she couldn't get him to work on it.
How can you do that?
Dad.
Can I stay in Shanghai
if I can get that famous designer?
That's impossible.
Miss, who are you looking for?
Hi, I'm looking for Mr. Ye.
May I know your name?
I'm Zhou's Development--
Don't construction companies
like you ever get tired?
There's no one by that name here.
Just leave.
Wait.
I'm not representing any company.
I must see Mr. Ye today.
You people come here
without setting an appointment.
Either you're a nouveau riche
who wants your mansion designed
or a construction company
who wants to use Mr. Ye's name
to sell your properties.
I've seen a lot of people.
Don't come again.
Mr. Ye would not see you.
Terence?
Why are you here?
Are you stalking me?
Mr. Ye.
Do you know her?
She's my friend, Ms. Zhou Caina.
She's my assistant, Ding Qi.
She's very good.
Ding Qi, coffee for me please.
Your assistant is so fierce.
Actually, not a lot of strangers
come here,
especially beautiful girls like you.
How did you find me?
Or should I say,
how did you find out about me?
I didn't.
I just met you by chance earlier.
I don't even know your real name.
I just know your English name is Terence.
Who knew you're the famous Ye Mingchuan?
Are you mad?
Why should I be mad?
Actually, I didn't mean
to hide it from you.
I wanted to tell you so many times.
However, you didn't seem to be interested.
Indeed.
I'm not interested in you.
-I came for Ye Mingchuan to--
-Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye. You have an important phone call.
Excuse me for a while.
Help me entertain her.
Thank you. Sorry to bother you.
Never mind.
If you're not here,
I wouldn't be bothered.
Are you...
Mr. Ye's girlfriend?
No.
I came here to ask Mr. Ye
to do an interior design project.
You want Mr. Ye
to design an ordinary house?
It's not ordinary.
Ours is an ancestral victorian house.
We need him to redesign it.
So what?
Do you know how many
large-scale international
cases he rejected?
How can he design your house?
So, it's not possible?
My goodness. Don't you get it?
A famous designer like Mr. Ye
would not accept an ordinary
residential or commercial project
no matter how much your offer is.
Do you understand?
Sorry.
I was too inconsiderate.
Caina.
Where are you going?
What's the matter?
I shouldn't be here.
Then why did you come here?
I wanted to find a master
to do something he wouldn't do.
I can help you.
"Ye Mingchuan."
RENOWNED ARCHITECT
He graduated from
Catalonia Polytechnic University
with an Architectural Doctorate Degree.
He joined the International Architectural
Design Exhibit when he was 28.
With his brilliant design work,
he received the 2011 Florence
Architecture Gold Award.
In 2012,
he received the Notre Dame
Architecture Gold Award.
But on one condition.
The design, construction,
and budget of your house
are all up to me, all right?
Of course.
Is he such a world-class designer?
I even treated him like a plumber.
And I didn't even pay him.
-Well...
-Mr. Lu.
Stop it.
Isn't this embarrassing enough?
But at least I can tell my dad
that I found the designer
he's been looking for.
I can stay in Shanghai.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO LATELY?
ARE YOU FREE?
-Any plans for tonight?
-I don't know.
You haven't dealt with your rival yet?
What rival?
I don't consider him a rival at all.
Sorry. Just saw your message.
I'm fine.
That day with Terence
was a misunderstanding.
He just came to my house to fix the pipes.
I knew it.
With him?
I don't think he's that fast.
When have you ever let a girl
decide your fate?
Never, but...
Caina is different.
I don't want to scare her away
that quickly.
That's why I prolonged my plan.
You haven't used any tricks yet?
Meizuo.
Why are you being so polite?
Are you becoming like Si?
What? This is what you call strategy.
But now,
since that guy is making his moves,
I'll also make mine.
Huaze Lei.
Please take care of it.
You mean you want me
to use that old trick?
But that's a killer move.
Still no news from Shancai?
None.
My phone was on the whole night.
I was afraid I'd miss her message.
But there was none.
Where do you think she went?
Isn't that Ximen?
Ximen.
Ximen, bro!
Who's your bro?
You are. We're so close already.
Ximen.
Any news from Shancai?
I don't know where she is.
So she didn't contact you either.
How about Daoming Si?
Did he try to find her?
Now, Si's who I'm most worried about.
Tell me.
Should I really confess to him?
Go if you like him.
But...
I heard he's dating Shancai.
I heard that he already dumped her.
Really?
Grab the opportunity now.
Daoming Si's coming. Come on.
Go.
Daoming Si.
I made this cake myself for you.
I hope you'll accept it.
He accepted it. She succeeded.
Actually, I started liking you
a long time ago.
I spent all night making this.
If Dong Shancai didn't keep bothering you,
I would have already...
What happened?
Daoming Si went too far.
How can he throw the cake in her face?
Yes. What's wrong with him?
See?
Si completely changed.
If Shancai doesn't come back,
I don't know what'll happen to him.
Hello?
Hello? Caina.
Meizuo.
You can't miss the dinner your boyfriend's
preparing for you tonight.
All right.
Meizuo. Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's all right.
That's specially for you.
This card contains
the fragrance of grass and soil.
It should be the fragrance of a field.
You're the only girl who can tell.
You won't ever be sad when I'm here.
Come on.
Let's have a toast.
I want to know all about you.
Me?
Then should I start from when I was a kid?
Sure.
During springtime,
a lot of girls wore dresses.
They were really cute.
But I can't wear them
because I'm allergic to the catkins.
Then I'll...
I'll sneeze.
So I felt so embarrassed
during springtime.
Because the spring wind also wants
to chase your bright smile.
That's why the catkins
flow with the wind towards you.
Meizuo.
You're really cute.
I'm not that pretty, you know?
When you really like someone,
it's easy to give
such a sincere compliment.
I'm not that pretty, you know?
How am I different from other girls?
Three days is not enough to describe it.
Meizuo.
You're such a cute little boy.
Look.
Your smile is so nice.
That's why the heavens like you so much.
How do you know?
Because they always give you gifts.
They do?
What else will I receive?
You haven't seen the real gift yet.
Where is it?
So where exactly is it?
Count to three.
One.
Two...
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene