A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 28
My goodness.
This gift is a little too...
Why do you need to go home so soon?
I'm meeting a designer.
What designer?
The one my dad chose
to renovate our old house.
Oh, right.
You know him too.
Who is it?
Ye Mingchuan. Terence.
-The old handyman?
-Yes.
So you're Mr. Ye, the designer.
It's good to see you again.
I hope you'll forgive me
if I had been rude.
No worries.
Sorry for making you wait.
Caina and I
were having a wonderful date just now.
Really?
Was it even more wonderful
than one we had that night?
I heard that you often
travel around the world
to find inspiration for your designs.
I bet you have had many girlfriends.
You're too humble.
F4 is a reputable group.
We're well known indeed,
but we never have flings
while being away on vacations.
That one fling
might just be the love of your life.
But there's also a 99 percent possibility
that it'd just be a forgettable chapter.
It's too bad that the 99 percent
isn't in my control.
Then who's controlling it?
I don't care who is controlling it.
What matters is you're in my hands.
Caina.
These are some design plans
I came up with.
Which one do you prefer?
Okay. I'll take a look.
Why don't we post
a search notice on Weibo?
If we do that,
people will know that Shancai is missing.
Do you think Daoming Si's mom
really took her away?
I asked my dad to check on that.
Mrs. Daoming is away
doing business in London.
She's too busy to care about Shancai.
That's because she's taken care of it.
Remember,
Mrs. Daoming is a meticulous person.
Let's calm down.
Shancai must have her own reasons.
Check your phones.
She'll try to contact us if she can.
I'm such a useless friend.
Shancai is always the one protecting me.
Now that she's missing,
I don't know how to help her.
Don't worry, Xiaoyou.
It's okay.
Shancai will be fine.
I'll protect you too.
Why do you need to protect her?
I can do that too.
If you could do that,
Shancai wouldn't be missing.
It's all Daoming Si's fault.
Don't try to stop me.
I'm going to make him pay.
Why isn't anyone stopping me?
Don't be too depressed.
I have a hunch
that she's doing just fine.
Why?
Did you guys forget? She's Shancai.
I can't accept it.
You're leaving me because
of such a lousy reason.
That's nonsense!
Shancai.
Do you really think I'm a useless guy?
Forget about my family, my mom
and everything else.
Have you ever thought of me
as a worthy guy?
I...
am...
sorry.
I'M SORRY
So what if I feel sorry?
It's not like he could read this.
What are you doing here alone?
Let's go home.
Your dad's coming back
with his boat tonight.
I thought Lei suddenly got a face change.
What's wrong with you lately?
Are you becoming like Daoming Si too?
Did Caina go missing too?
Shut up.
It looks like
you gave up fighting with that old dude.
A few days ago,
Caina and I spoke on the phone
for an hour.
I could feel that
she really likes me.
So I'm hiding from her.
I'm playing hard to get.
I think it's Caina
who's hiding from you instead.
Are you my friend or not?
Lei, what do you think?
Can I not be your friend?
Are you kidding me?
And how about you?
That hurts.
A customized perfect carat
diamond meteor necklace?
Did Daoming Si give you this?
Mom, why did you go through my things?
I didn't go through your things.
I wanted to help you unpack.
Don't touch this.
I'm going to give it back.
Give it back?
Did you fight with him?
No, we didn't.
We broke up.
Broke up?
Weren't you two doing well
just a few days ago?
The two of us were totally incompatible.
We weren't going to last.
Tell me.
Did something happen at school?
Nothing happened.
We ended our relationship.
Nothing else happened.
So be it.
Did you decide to come here because of it?
I told you.
I came here to do some field research
for my school assignment.
All right.
I've always liked that boy.
It's too bad.
I'm going to cook lunch then.
-Here, this way.
-Pass the ball.
Here.
-Go.
-Okay. Come on.
Three-pointer.
Pass it to me.
Over here.
Si's been acting weird
since Shancai went missing.
He's not answering calls and messages.
He doesn't even talk to anyone.
Meanwhile, Lei is busy
with his graduation performance.
Is this going to be the end of F4?
Sometimes, growing up
can be problematic too.
You know how Si is.
Nobody can tell him what to do.
But Shancai can.
The problem with you guys
is you are all too emotional.
Be more reasonable.
The problem here is that you're heartless.
You don't know the pain of being in love.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just more mature.
I'm not like you childish people.
Sure, we're childish.
We're all immature.
Should we look for the ultimate kid, Si?
He shouldn't hide at home.
What do you think?
Ask him out yourself.
I'm not the instigator.
It has been a while, Ximen, Meizuo.
Xiaozi.
Wait, why are you here too?
Why can't I be here?
Don't forget.
F4 and I have a long history.
You see,
Daoming Si is my ex-fiancé.
Shancai is my good friend.
These two guys used to be my servants.
They bought my underwear, shopped,
-caught--
-All right.
That's enough. Don't bring that up again.
Are you for real?
Shancai left without a word
and is still missing.
We're supposed to look for Daoming Si
to cheer him up a little.
How could you invite his fiancée too?
Watch your words.
I'm the ex-fiancée.
Shancai and Si
are two very important people in my life.
How can I not be a part of this?
Xiaozi is so loud.
She'll set the mood.
Anyway,
the most important agenda today
is to cheer Si up.
Remember, guys.
Don't bring up Shancai's name, ever.
Si's here.
Daoming Si.
It's been a while.
You're still the same old guy,
always looking pissed off.
But check it out.
His pissed-off face
looks 100 times better
than his normal one.
You're exaggerating.
You're just buttering him up.
All right, I'm just kidding.
It has been a while.
You don't answer our calls
or reply to our messages.
What have you been up to?
There's not much you can do alone.
Probably reading a book,
listening to music and playing games.
Not necessarily.
Si has got all sorts of ideas.
Right?
I know.
He's been doing embroidery with Ms. Yu
and knitting a sweater.
That sounds like fun.
I know.
He was mopping the floors.
Daoming Si's house is huge
so it took him a while.
I don't think so.
Si probably snuggled up under his blanket
and looked at my photos.
I know, Si.
The more you look at my photos,
the prettier I look, right?
I'll be honest here.
It's been a while since we met.
I'm glad to see everyone here.
Si, we should hang out more.
Or maybe just the two of us sometimes.
That's right, Si. What do you say?
You know what this is?
Lame.
What's up with the act?
Pretending to be all close to each other.
It makes me sick.
What's your problem?
What?
You overreacted.
I overreacted?
You called, I came.
Why can't you just let me be?
There's no need to act all friendly.
You got dumped, showed up here
looking pissed, and blew your top.
Who's being lame?
Refusing to be contacted,
taking it out on your friends.
-What kind of a man are you?
-Shut up!
It's none of your business.
This is the reason why Shancai dumped you.
You guys should go.
The situation is out of your hands now.
Let's go.
That crazy bastard.
It's over between us.
Don't laugh.
Listen up.
I'm staying out of that guy's shit.
Okay.
We'll go back for now
and deal with him tomorrow.
Not tomorrow.
Not ever.
All right.
But let's just go back first.
And from today onward,
there is no more F4.
This ends just like this?
You won't deal with him,
but you want F4 to stay intact.
What is it that you want?
I'll tell you when I figure it out.
Isn't Mr. Ye supposed
to handle the finances?
Why are you showing this to me?
This is our company's protocol.
If you're okay with the contract,
please sign it.
We can then proceed.
Is there anything else?
Mr. Ye will be here later to confirm
the details of the renovation.
Ding Qi placed those there.
It doesn't concern me.
I was just looking.
Ding Qi said you're going to go over
the renovation details with me.
That's why I'm still here.
I thought you didn't like renovating.
Because I thought
you didn't like owning a house.
I don't have one.
Impossible. You...
-Every day, you're...
-Designing houses?
Let me put it this way.
I'm an architect.
Not an interior designer.
So you helping to renovate my house is...
It's an exception because of you.
I know how to renovate,
but I've never done it for anyone.
You never did?
Never.
How should I repay you then?
You don't have to.
Just don't avoid me in the future.
I...
I'm not avoiding you.
I'm not.
Really?
I've tried to talk to you a few times,
but you avoided me. Why?
Because I didn't have answers
for your questions.
I didn't know what to say
and didn't want to think about it.
All right then.
From now on,
consider me your interior designer.
A new friend.
No strings attached.
No extra burden.
I won't bring up
what happened that night again.
How about that?
Okay.
The weather is nice today.
I'll take you home.
Hey, Meizuo.
I'm having a meeting at Terence's office.
It's okay.
He'll take me home.
It'd better be a meeting.
-What?
-Meizuo.
You're getting too distracted by Caina.
You think I want to?
It's that old dude.
He's always sticking to her.
Like a Band-Aid.
Who knows
whether it's an actual meeting or not.
Shancai.
Where are you?
I know you won't answer calls,
but at least reply my messages.
Hey.
Are you two my friends or not?
I'm frustrated here.
Shouldn't I get some sort of a response?
A guy and a girl are there together.
You're here being mad.
What can we do?
If only Si is here.
No, this is bad.
I need to throw up again.
It's been two months.
Why does Dad still get seasick?
It's fine. It's nothing serious.
He'll get used to it soon.
To be honest,
your dad isn't that outstanding,
but he's got a good heart.
He came here to help
as soon as he heard your uncle is sick.
I'm so happy that I found such a man.
Not only that,
we get fresh seafood every day.
Mom, the food is done.
That quick?
So much beef.
Here, have one.
-It's pretty good. Try it.
-Okay.
Why is the squid so difficult though?
It's already dead,
but it takes so long to cook.
It's all sticking together.
Go get me some soy sauce.
Okay.
I'll be back.
Mom, look what I found.
Eight Treasure sauce?
Brush it on. I bet it'll taste good.
It smells good.
Let's try it.
-It smells good.
I feel better after vomiting.
Something smells good.
This is our new product,
Eight Treasure Squid.
Here, try one.
Here.
Dad, it's still hot.
-It's good.
-Really?
-It's delicious.
-Let me try.
-Here.
-I'll eat this.
This Eight Treasure sauce
and squid are a perfect match!
-It's delicious.
-Just like Romeo and Juliet.
Like fried tomato and egg.
Me and your mom.
A match made in heaven.
I've got an idea.
We'll set up a stall tomorrow
to sell the Eight Treasure Squid.
"Sell the Eight Treasure Squid."
Sounds good.
-I think it's going to sell well.
-Me too.
All right.
Eat the squid. I'm just kidding.
No, we're going to do it.
Give me two more.
Meizuo, is that old dude
still not giving up?
You can't expect us to help you
without any plan.
I wouldn't be putting in so much effort
if they didn't meet first.
Women.
They're sentimental by nature.
Anticipating the future.
Reminiscing the past.
If that's true,
the present seems the most miserable.
That's right.
That's why I prefer to be
someone from the past.
Why do you think Caina likes you?
I'm tall, handsome, funny,
and full of youthful energy.
I know.
Dating younger men is a thing nowadays.
It helps women maintain
a youthful outlook.
I remember.
When I'm with Caina,
she'd say,
"How nice it is to be young."
She also said,
"I wish I could be young again."
If that's the case,
let us go back
to when Caina is still young.
Us?
Yes.
Us, F4.
Si...
Don't you want to make up with Si?
DONG'S KING OF SQUID
SIGNATURE FLAVOR: EIGHT TREASURE SQUID
-Shancai, hurry up.
-Okay.
-I heard the squid is awesome.
-It's good.
-I've been coming often.
-It's really good.
Done.
-It smells delicious.
-It's good.
Hello. How many skewers?
-Three.
-Here.
Three skewers?
Thanks for waiting.
I want it extra spicy.
I love them spicy.
-Here you go.
-Almost done.
Here, please enjoy.
-Thanks.
-Hi. Your three skewers.
Mom, how are you holding up?
Are you tired?
Not at all. There's no time to be tired.
Your dad needs to work harder
to catch more squid at sea.
-Three skewers?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Thanks for waiting.
No worries.
Mrs. Dong.
Your business is doing well.
Oh, ma'am.
I've been so busy with the stall
that I forgot to pay the rent.
I'll give it to you right away.
Here, have some squid.
I didn't come here today to collect rent.
I wanted to ask
if you'd like me
to be your business partner.
I'll help you sell the squid.
Well, I'd be happy to let you.
But it's just a small village.
If people buy from your shop,
who's going to come here?
I can lower the rent.
And pay you commission.
What do you say?
That sounds pretty good.
But the Eight Treasure sauce
that Shancai created
is a family secret.
We don't plan to sell it.
Sorry about that.
Wait, ma'am.
Hold on.
I just thought of an idea.
I can create a few more flavors.
This way, we won't
get in each other's way.
Will that work?
That's awesome.
Very good.
How is it?
It's good.
I haven't seen you in a while.
I've been busy
with my graduation performance.
And also,
Si hasn't hung out with us much.
Yes.
Since Shancai left,
Si's been keeping to himself.
I'm worried about him.
I hope you guys
will ask him out more often
and get him out of his shell.
I'm not hungry!
It's you.
I don't have any appetite.
Are you still angry?
I'm not.
But you seem so sad.
Isn't that obvious?
Why are you still asking?
It's been going on for too long.
I'm used to seeing you happy and unhappy.
But right now, we need you with us.
I should say that
Meizuo needs us with him.
We agreed, right?
Keeping company is a sign of friendship.
Sometimes, we need to do
things we don't like
for the sake of someone important.
Like right now.
To make Ms. Yu happy,
you should drink this glass of soy milk.
Lame.
What's up with you guys?
Good morning, miss.
Change into these
and come on a picnic with us.
Daoming Si.
Are you in a bad mood?
Why don't you join them?
I know we're not that close.
But I still remember you well.
During the cooking competition,
you cheered for Shancai
through the window.
And she won the special prize.
It was because of your support.
Are you two doing well?
We broke up.
Normally, girls need some time.
Give her some space.
And you?
Do you like Meizuo?
I need some time to think about it too.
She said,
"It's so good
to have you.
So good."
Right?
Didn't she?
She said I'm worth seven stars.
"So, so good."
You've said that 20 times.
It's actually 21 times.
Is that even a sentence?
Not a sentence.
Just a word.
Hey.
Can't you guys share
this happy moment with me?
I know Shancai is missing.
Si's heartbroken.
But I'm still here.
Shancai's missing.
Si's heartbroken.
Meizuo's drunk in love.
Lei.
You're the only one who's normal now.
I couldn't care less.
Can you guys show more concern?
Are you even my friends?
Meizuo.
Hello.
Good.
So good.
-So funny.
-Huaze Lei.
Okay, Meizuo.
You're our pride.
You want to talk about Caina?
We'll do that.
Then again,
Ye Mingchuan was going after
Caina aggressively,
but he suddenly stopped doing that.
I guess he wasn't that serious
about Caina.
He is serious.
Or else you wouldn't be so worried.
Even if he's serious, so what?
He might be serious about her,
but so am I.
The point is, I love her.
Good.
Make your move while you still can.
Just don't regret it in the future.
Hello, Caina.
What are you doing?
I'm with the guys.
Hello, Ms. Caina.
Caina, Li Quan is having
a concert this weekend.
Do you want to go?
Okay.
I'll see you there then.
See you there.
A concert this weekend?
I want to go too.
I'm afraid not this time.
I need to prepare for our perfect date.
It was hard to get tickets
for the best seats.
I won't let them go to waste.
Have you finished your report?
I'm a top student.
I won't let my social life
get in the way of my studies.
Right now,
I'm the world's luckiest guy.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Jay Wong
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene