[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 29]
Chunyu.
Hi there.
Let's have a meeting
an hour later
to reschedule
the plan.
About your plan,
did you discuss it
with Vice-captain Gao?
We make plans and they carry out plans.
It's the working principle.
We don't need to know their opinions.
I think it's not appropriate.
Why is it not appropriate?
Of course it's not appropriate.
As long as my plan changes,
your plan should also change.
My training cannot be delayed.
By the way,
your 8-unit plan
is inappropriate.
You ignored Mt. Guier.
You'd better turn it into a 12-unit plan
and reduce the time
for every unit by one.
Then you'll be able to
ensure the timeliness and the quality of the test.
And there will be three days for you to adjust your plan.
Gao Liang,
you sent someone to hack into my computer?
Your special forces
are in charge of all the
dirty work, right?
Don't be so rude.
How could you know it's not my guess?
Just consider
my suggestion.
Gao Liang,
that's too much.
Chunyu,
Nanzheng,
you washed all the stinky shoes
of my soldiers.
They're all clean and spoiled.
How can they stand Captain Xia's training?
We did that
to make you cooperate
with the work of our contingent.
What's up?
You smell so good!
What? You're crazy.
I mean I smelt soap.
Come on.
Give me a kiss.
OK.
Close your eyes.
I'm sorry.
What are you going?
Throw you in the water.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Gao Liang hit me.
Vice-captain Gao!
Go back and have a politics class now.
Slow down.
It's hot.
Gosh!
It's like the life-saving holy water!
Mosquitoes almost ate me.
Somebody cares about you.
He asked me to give it to you.
Gao Liang?
Who else could it be?
Now you're chuckling.
How's it going?
Did you complete your work?
No.
Xia Lin is like a whip.
He's always rushing me.
I have to hurry.
Even if he doesn't,
I still have to hurry.
The clock's ticking.
Xia Lin
spared no effort on pursuing you.
Every girl would be touched.
Men are all the same.
They enjoy the time when they pursue you.
They show their best side
to you
and make you think
you're everything to them.
We tend to
magnify their best side.
But,
it's not real at all.
Then tell me about the real him.
Xia Lin
is actually like Gao Liang.
He was born in a poor family.
He worked hard to
make all the achievements.
He's studious.
He loves the army sincerely.
Sometimes,
I think he's too strict with himself,
as if he's torturing himself.
As long as it's his task,
he tries his best to complete it.
I feel like he was born
to be a soldier.
His great faith
often touches me.
He's nice to me.
He's sincere
and caring.
According to you, Xia Lin is so good.
Then why did you refuse to marry him?
I didn't refuse.
He retreated.
He retreated?
Why?
Because he's jealous.
You know
I...
I used to tell Gao Liang I like him.
But I was young at that time
and my crush was immature.
It's been a long time.
I've already moved on.
Otherwise, I wouldn't fall in love with Xia Lin.
But now,
he's the one who can't move on.
But I think
the reason why he told you he's jealous
and refuses to be together with you now
due to jealousy
is that he loves you so much.
Otherwise, why would he be like that?
It's not easy for him
to lose his mind.
But if you love someone,
you should trust him
and yourself.
If there's no trust,
how to keep going?
It's true.
But sometimes, when we're in love,
we tend to be suspicious
and lose confidence.
I prefer confident men.
No matter what happens,
they never turn their backs
on their beloved.
Forced love
does not last.
Just go with the flow.
All right. You should get back to work.
I got to go.
Tomorrow, I'm going to
run a test with them.
Go.
Go now!
Here's a mango.
It smells so good.
Thank you.
Nanzheng,
promise me
you'll travel with me
after we complete this test.
Chunyu.
But I think
the reason why he told you he's jealous
and refuses to be together with you now
due to jealousy
is that he loves you so much.
Chunyu.
[Confederate rose]
The earth and the mountains quaked.
Code.
Here's my code.
Fire at me.
Chief,
it's you.
Is there anything I can do for you?
No.
I'm checking
the safety of the cadres' dormitory.
You can go now.
Yes, sir!
Mountain Eagle 3. Mountain Eagle 3.
Tell me your location.
This is Mountain Eagle 2.
This is Mountain Eagle 3. Copy that.
We're about five kilometers away
from your left front side.
This is Mountain Eagle 2. Copy that.
It's a land mine.
It's in Mt. Guier.
There's a test subject today.
Contact Gao Liang now
and find out their location!
Yes, sir.
Mountain Eagle 2! Mountain Eagle 2!
This is Mountain Eagle 1.
This is Mountain Eagle 2. Copy that.
Comrades of People's Liberation Army.
What happened?
The injured is here.
They're family.
Are they okay?
The two adults have no heartbeat.
-The child is still alive. -Send her to the hospital now.
Come on. Hop on.
Come on.
Sir,
what's the name of the child?
Jingjing.
Is the girl that Gao Liang rescued
okay now?
Thanks to the timely rescue,
she's safe now.
Besides Mt. Guier,
Shanwang One's tests in other units
have all been completed.
After you sign this file,
you'll complete the task of the joint contingent.
Why did you exclude Mt. Guier?
It's a key test area of this region.
This is also my question.
Because it's a minefield.
It's very dangerous to take a test there.
It's dangerous so we have to avoid it?
Captain Gao.
Ms. Jiang.
Just now you saw
the risk of the minefield.
If there are more casualties,
our efforts
will be wasted
and we'll be punished.
The loss outweighs the gain.
We disagree with this temporary plan.
It's dangerous
so we have to take a test there.
Its conditions and environment
are close to those in a real battle.
It's a constructive work
of reference to our test.
Besides,
its conditions and environment
can help us find out
our system's problem.
We can run tests anytime.
But what if people die?
Do they have a second chance?
All soldiers of our squadron
are excellent.
But don't you think
dying in a pointless test is cruel?
Captain Xia,
I don't think you get it.
Ms. Jiang wants the system to
be scientific and authentic.
Her goal
is to reduce the casualties
in real battles.
Real battles?
Where are the real battles?
Don't pretend that you don't understand,
okay?
According to the current domestic situation,
everything we do is for economic development.
Will there be wars?
I think when we think about something,
we have to take the big picture into consideration
and stand on the high ground.
We can't just focus only on
our own perspective.
Enough.
You have the right to decide on the test contingent.
I agree with your temporary plan
but I have a request.
You need to report to the military
and all the land mines in Mt. Guier
need to be swept.
Otherwise, the local people
will be affected.
Don't worry.
I've already reported it to the headquarters.
And the headquarters has reported it
to the military district.
The military district will include it in the third batch of
unified border minesweeping plans.
Write in detail
in the test report.
Then I'll sign.
No problem.
I disagree.
I won't sign it.
Well,
you two are
experts.
But I hope you two can understand
the difficulty of our grassroots army.
OK.
I agree to sign it.
[General Hospital of the Military District]
It's all
thanks to Director Wang
that there was no surgical fee
and the surgery was successful.
Now I'm relieved.
Today,
I'm going to buy you food.
You take the check.
Why?
I spent all my savings
to pay her hospitalization fee.
Why do I have to take the check when you say it's your treat?
It's my treat, actually.
And as far as I can recall,
you never bought me lunch before, right?
Are you going to buy me lunch on credit today?
OK. It's your treat.
There's no difference.
By the way,
I heard
Plan 19 of Army B was ruined.
I'd like to suggest
restarting the test on Shanwang One
in Mt. Guier.
Nanzheng,
don't take it too seriously.
Did you forget how Jingjing got injured?
Now I'm tracking
the minesweeping plan of the military.
Start the certification work after
the entire minesweeping operation finishes.
Don't worry. There's still time.
Let's have lunch first.
Let's order
braised pork with pickled mustard.
Sounds good.
Would you like eggplant?
It's like a grease bomb.
What about
spicy frogs?
Just order the food you want to have.
But the performance of Shanwang One
really needs to be tested in such an environment.
If we miss this chance,
I'll get upset.
Let's have lunch first.
Come on. Order some food.
Order whatever you like. Come on.
Dig in. Aren't you hungry?
Let's eat.
While we're eating,
I want to tell you something.
We have to find a home
for Jingjing as soon as possible.
We can't make her feel like
she's an orphan,
right?
She's too young.
If she thinks she's an orphan, she'll feel wretched.
I know what it feels like to be an orphan.
I endowed two
poor relatives.
Their children are going back to school soon.
One is going to be a high school student,
and the other is going to be a middle school student.
They'll need to pay their tuition fees.
I spent all my savings
to pay Jingjing's hospitalization fee.
Can you
lend some money to me?
I'll pay their tuition fees.
When I get paid, I'll pay you back.
Is there anything else?
Yes.
About the
travel plan we made before,
I think
our schedules always overlap each other,
and we both are buried in
works all the time.
Let's avoid being extravagant.
Nanzheng,
if you disagree with it,
just forget what I said.
Go on. Eat.
Check, please.
We haven't finished. What's the rush?
You can take your time.
[Bethune]
How are you feeling?
The nurse told me you're here.
-Hi, Chunyu. -Mom.
Jingjing.
Come on. Sit down.
You're dripping with sweat.
She's getting tired.
Jingjing
calls me mom now.
Chunyu,
you're a nice person.
Stop talking about me.
You want to adopt Jingjing.
Did you discuss it with Nanzheng?
Well,
I brought it up a little.
Jingjing, it's time to give you an injection.
There you go. Be good.
Go.
Good girl.
Chunyu,
Jingjing's eyes...
It's thanks to Tong Bing.
After the expert of the Eye Center of Beijing Tongren Hospital
came here,
she made an appointment with the expert
to give Jingjing the second surgery.
But,
we're not sure about the result now.
If she's still out of condition,
she'll need new corneas.
Cornea transplant?
It's hard to find corneas, actually.
Yes, it's hard.
Anyway,
I want her to be cured.
Nanzheng.
I talked to the Civil Affairs Bureau
and contacted the Welfare House.
You're not qualified to adopt Jingjing.
I asked for my friends' help. They said
according to the policy,
you can only adopt her after you're qualified.
But she can go to the Welfare House.
The government will adopt her.
Here are the number and the address.
Did you receive the money?
Yes, I did.
I've written an IOU.
Sign it.
What?
What's wrong?
Do you want to welsh on the debt?
Well, Nanzheng,
it feels like you've changed.
[IOU. Borrower: Gao Liang]
What was I like before?
Forget
about the past. But now, you're
like...
a saint.
I'm not used to it.
Today, I prepared myself
to be scolded when I came back.
You think I'm so mean?
Not at all.
My dad is home.
So what if your dad's here?
I kissed my girlfriend.
Why should I be afraid? I'm afraid of no one.
Say it again.
Chief,
let me do it.
Where should I put it?
There.
OK.
Is it okay?
Over there.
OK.
Enough. Let me wipe your face.
You're sweating all over.
Listen to me carefully.
Be my ideal son-in-law
or be a part-time worker.
That depends on Zheng's mood.
Yes, sir.
Did you find any intelligence?
Did I have to look for it? Our old rival.
The First Battalion of Regiment 700.
There's a piece of reliable news.
Their Acting Battalion Commander Gu Yiye
was sent to study for a week.
Now their Instructor Zhang Yuejin
whose nickname is Little Wangcheng is leading them.
See,
he's a political cadre.
By convention, our special forces
never lost.
If we want to win,
will there be any cliffhanger?
Seriously,
we can't underestimate this confrontation.
It's very important to you, Niu Mancang
and me.
How come?
After the maneuvers,
there will be a crucial juncture.
If we win,
we'll be promoted.
Higher ranks, man.
We'll be promoted to Battalion Commander.
Our title will no longer contain "Acting".
The promotion has nothing to do with the maneuvers.
There are rules of cadres' promotion.
It's not up to you.
As an Acting Instructor, I'm responsible
for figuring out the promotion rules.
I've already asked them.
My news is reliable.
Anything else?
Mancang will be
promoted from Company Commander to Deputy Battalion Commander.
Why did the army organize
this confrontation?
You have to ask Staff Officer Zhou.
He's Xia Lin's subordinate.
He made the general plan.
The plan is confidential.
I've sent someone to investigate
but he didn't get anything.
Report.
Deputy Section Chief Xia of Military Training Section is here.
How many
plans of attack have you prepared?
One.
Just one?
You're too careless.
We're not careless.
Instead, we're precise.
Their main Commander Gu Yiye is not there.
Now their Instructor
is acting as Main Commander.
They're disorganized.
But, we
are the tank battalion
of the special forces.
To fight such a battle,
do we need a second plan?
Fine.
Tell me about your resolution.
Under the cover of the tank,
we'll send two companies
to attack Highland 791
and Highland 812 at a rapid rate.
We want to attract their attention.
Then,
we'll send the Ninth Company
to go through Heifengkou between cliffs,
destroy Laoye Temple
and occupy their command post.
We'll bring into full play our advantages.
Be fast, precise and cruel.
Decapitation Tactic again?
Yes.
Little Wangcheng and I lived in the same dormitory before.
Thinking of our friendship,
I'll use a sharp knife
when I cut off the head.
What if you meet your old rival
Gu Yiye?
Our friendship is better.
If I capture Gu Yiye,
I'll put the sharp knife aside
and cut off his head with a stone.
Amazing.
Well,
can't you
use some technologies?
For example,
launch an electronic feint attack.
This morning,
we came close to them and scouted them.
We found on their highland,
their defense is disorganized,
so we decided to
finish the battle
at the highest speed
and spend the remaining time
on something meaningful.
Good.
I'll report your plan
to the Chief of Staff.
However,
I want to tell you that
don't be too cocky.
Otherwise, you'll tend to fail.
No matter who you are,
even the future son-in-law of the Army Commander.
Deputy Section Chief Xia,
being cocky or not,
I do know one thing.
Anyone who quarrels with
his fiancée at home
is definitely a jerk.
Still one kilometer away?
The battle starts at dawn.
Only one small position was taken till now.
I sent you the tanks for nothing?
They've set up tank ambush positions.
Our tanks
were out of action within 20 minutes.
Where did that come from?
They are cleverly disguised.
We didn't find them
within 50m distance.
You couldn't fight a battle without tanks?
Go fight anyway!
You have one hour
to take Highland 791!
Niu Mancang.
Yes, sir!
How's it going in Highland 812?
They have a solid fortification.
We're moving forward slowly.
It's been two hours.
According to the plan,
the 4th Company shall attack by now.
Even the periphery of 791 and 812
is not taken yet.
If we send them now,
they'll be the living target.
Without Commander, the 1st Red Battalion
still fight furiously with his spirit.
This is Gao Liang.
Gao Liang?
Yes, sir!
What's wrong with you?
How can you fight a battle like this?
Chief,
I'm reckless this time.
As the tip of the dagger of Army A,
you are defeated like this.
Fighting for
the honor of ace troops,
they spend
200 percent vigor for the battle.
And you?
The maneuvers started two hours ago,
you are still
not fully awake.
How can you not be defeated?
Chief,
please punish me.
Will it work?
Use your brain!
You haven't found the reason for the failure.
Special operations?
More like specially brainless!
This is Gao Liang.
Vice Captain Gao,
I was away for a week to study,
but I took three days off.
The truth is
you can't always focus on
the results.
Otherwise,
you'll lose again.
I'll start my counterattack.
Be prepared.
Gao,
they start the counterattack.
Notify each company.
We are now changing from attack to defense.
Too late now.
Their attack is very furious.
We don't have time to turn to defense.
Chief!
Attention!
The attack turned into a breakout.
Then the breakout turned into a defense.
A crushing defeat!
Each of you has
excellent personal ability
and has won countless medals.
That meant nothing for the maneuvers.
What is the problem?
Report!
This time
the main reason is the battle plan.
I was reckless.
Do you know
what the collective opinion of
the judging panel is?
The overall training level of
the 1st Red Battalion is very high.
They do
match with you.
Their infantry-tank synergy is very skillful.
In anti-tank technology,
they are one of the best in the military district.
They played to their strengths.
Especially, the ability of their commander
is a magnitude higher
than yours.
Got it?
You, Special Operation Battalion,
as the tip of the dagger for the whole Army Group.
In the future war,
you're probably the first batch
being sent to war.
Fortunately, it's only maneuvers.
If this is a real war, and you got defeated
like this in the first battle.
The morale of the Army Group
is completely lost by you.
Wang Yibing.
Yes, sir!
The tip of the dagger should behave as it should be.
The Special Operation Battalion
doesn't keep losers.
Haven't they been trying
the last-place elimination?
The elimination rate of our officers
and soldiers is about 30%.
Special Operation Battalion 2,
as a team in name only,
shall have a last-place elimination, too.
Give away their place
to any of the Infantry Battalions
of the Army Group
who wins
the battle over them.
Yes, sir!
[Opinions on the Actualization of the Military Exercise]
Xia Lin, your proposal is very timely.
An actual combat test for battalion and
company level first-line commanders
responds to the Army Commander's usual standards.
Future warfare is becoming increasingly diverse.
As Special Operations,
they shall keep updating their minds and means.
Gu Yiye used a psychological tactic this time.
He disturbed Gao's judgment
and made him reckless.
That's the reason for his failure.
I can see that a lot of your thoughts
is forward-looking.
I have formally presented you
to the Army Commander as Section Chief.
So now you have two choices.
First,
go directly as the Section Chief of the Training Division.
Second,
Colonel of Regiment 720.
Now the previous Colonel of Regiment 720
Qin Hanyoung is redeployed
as the Colonel Captain
of the Special Operations Battalion.
This position may
be taken by you.
The specifics will be clear
with the opinion of the officer department.
Thank you, sir, for your care and training.
I will cherish the opportunity and work harder.
Too salty!
Heavy flavor.
Have some meat.
Wait.
I'll split the food.
This plate is Xiaofei's.
Xiaofei is growing up now.
You three behaved like stray dogs.
Don't touch it!
He calls you a dog.
What? He meant you.
Just let them have enough.
Come on, try this.
Xiu, don't help them today.
They are not here for food today.
They are here to revenge.
That's right.
Xiu,
fill his cup.
Let's take revenge on him.
I'll have this.
A bit leftover.
Hey, easy.
Sit,
don't stand here.
Niu.
Dig in.
-Let me do this. -I'll do it.
Xiu,
leave it to him.
Let him do the errands. Enjoy the food.
Just sit down as Captain said.
Just sit down as he said.
-Have some. -Just sit.
Leave him alone.
OK.
Are you drunk?
No, I am not.
I can drink definitely.
Good boy.
Have a look.
Comrade Xiaofei,
that's not right
to treat us differently.
Why only give him
not me?
Why give it to you?
Come on, Xiaofei, show us.
Combat Preparation!
Well done! One,
two.
Hit here.
Three.
See?
Harder.
Punch!
That's enough.
Well done!
Nice, Xiaofei!
Well played.
Comrade Gu Xiaofei, come!
It's Zhang Xiaofei, not Gu Xiaofei.
My last name is Zhang.
All right, Comrade Xiao Fei.
Well played.
Your moves are beautiful, stable, and accurate.
You call that beautiful?
I'll show you.
Why compare with a kid?
I'll show you something special.
He's drunk.
Make a fool of himself.
Gu Yiye,
we've been friends and colleagues for years.
Do you have to take it so seriously?
Niu, you even bought the celebration wine.
What Deputy Battalion Commander?
In your dreams! You deserve it!
Jiang Weixing!
Yes, sir!
Don't be a jerk!
Xiu and the kid are here.
Sit down!
Yes, sir!
Gu,
We haven't had a walk like this for a long time.
Yeah.
I'll have a word with you
with the help of alcohol.
Normally,
I won't
be able to say it out loud.
Shoot.
Defeat you
is not my fault
anyway.
But I do feel sorry for making you kicked out
of the Special Operations by Cheng.
But this has nothing to do with the promotion.
Jiang was right.
I don't feel good about it, too.
Get some humanity.
But I don't agree with his point.
You can't mix personal feelings
with training standards,
right?
That's negligence.
I am on your side.
It's right to stick to the rules.
Yeah,
I am glad
to hear this.
I've checked the maneuvers plan.
It's made by Xia Lin.
I know.
He notified me
back then. I didn't take it seriously.
He's going to
hit two birds with one stone.
Why are you still messing with him now?
How long will this last?
I do hate him as a person.
He flings himself at me every day,
right?
But he's not against me.
He used his brain.
He learns something from
the office.
I heard the news
that Qin Dapao
will be back as the new Captain.
It's a pity.
He's back
but I'll leave.
Iron battalion, flowing soldiers.
Maybe you'll
be back someday.
With the alcohol,
I'll tell you something from the heart.
I won't say it when I am sober.
Fine,
go ahead.
I didn't expect this.
Actually, I can't take it.
I haven't figured out what to do yet.
Being in the army for these years,
I am so unsure of what to expect for the first time.
Right now, in front of Weixing and Niu,
I can't say much about it.
Although they are now mentally broken,
I have to hold on.
If I can't hold it,
the team is finished.
Enough.
What's your point?
Jiang Nanzheng
is back finishing her master's study.
We planned to
get married.
But we haven't seen each other since she came back.
Now, I don't want to see her.
We should postpone our marriage.
I am responsible for
all her aggravation.
Right?
In the end, it's because of my incompetence.
I understand
that you don't want your beloved woman
to see you now.
Dad, the meal is ready.
Braised pork with dark soy sauce.
Come on, Dad.
Have a try.
Gao Liang's
recipe.
How's the taste?
-Delicious. -Not bad?
Very nice.
Good, right?
Gao Liang can be replaced.
Indeed.
Nanzheng,
Gao Liang
was defeated by Gu Yiye.
A bad defeat.
His Special Operations Battalion 2
was kicked out of
the Special Operations Battalion.
Unprecedented punishment.
Gao Liang had a great setback.
I don't know if he
could hold on this time.
Sometimes,
being a father-in-law
is quite contradictory.
I don't want
my daughter to suffer.
But I do want my son-in-law
to suffer.
In the beginning,
I watched him try to take my daughter away.
I didn't like him at all.
And then,
I wanted to
give him lessons.
Dad, why?
I am afraid that he has not gone through
enough setbacks to be strong,
and can't do well enough
in your future days.
I want to offer my daughter the best.
All the bitterness
will be suffered by him.
So,
it's quite hard to be my son-in-law,
am I right?
Cheers.
How's you and Xiu?
I am telling you
if I hear that Xiu
suffered a bit,
I'll beat you up.
Want the truth?
Xiu
treats me like another son.
What?
Son?
Back home,
no matter
it's the bookshelf
or the old trunk,
she turned them all upside down.
And get all the books
out to flatten its pages,
saying this makes it neat.
Last time, she almost wore
the distributed pair of leather shoes
by brushing them before my wearing.
She has to try
to see if the water's too hot before I drink.
It seems
she's just about fed me food.
Isn't it good?
She serves you like a king.
How many men are eager for this
while you're not happy about this.
Fine, stop acting.
I'm not that kind of person.
Xiu and I are both
trying to give our best to each other.
But we try too hard.
That is not happy.
I'm very happy with Xiu.
I gave way to her.
I was afraid that she might have the slightest aggravation.
When the accident happened,
we all felt sorry.
Only you
stood out
and took the responsibility.
Xiu
suffered a lot.
You have to treat her well
and give all your love
to her.
That's it, I'm leaving.
Hey, wait.
Whenever
I have a mood swing,
I can't feel this shoulder.
It's even out of action sometimes.