Ow!
What do you want? Money?
I got money.
My dad's got money!
That's the problem with you men.
You always think it's about money.
But it's about power.
And the power I'm looking for,
you can't give me.
Wait...
Busy night, Sergeant Guerrero.
You're telling me. Damn bloodbath.
But only the bodyguards
have their hearts cut out.
And it turns out they're all ex-military,
all from the same unit.
The Skeleton Crew.
We recognize the tattoos, boss.
Used to be deployed down south.
Crazy bunch with an even crazier CO.
Heard he was honorably discharged
after an operation went sideways.
See if your contacts in the military
can track him down for us.
We should pay him a visit.
Copy that, boss.
We'll get the info to you once we get it.
You think the bodyguards were the target?
We'll see.
Can I do it, Papa?
Sa mata ng iba, mga lihim magpapakita.
Our prime suspect.
Does she look familiar?
I can check our files,
but it'll take time.
Bantay, Puti.
Scent's still strong.
We'll track her down.
I think I need a drink.
Colonel Hidalgo.
Are you all right?
Colonel.
We think that someone
is murdering soldiers from your unit.
They're gone.
If your life is in danger...
My wife and family are gone.
People will say they left me,
but I know the truth.
It was Ramona.
You mean this woman?
The face of the devil herself.
Her band of rebels had been murdering
my men for months
before we tracked her to their camp.
But like all rebels,
they had their superstitions.
Believe they could call
on the powers of war itself.
A blood ritual.
A death ritual.
So you made her into a trophy.
A sick prize for men possessed,
possessed by blood, by lust, by war.
We didn't know what we had done until we...
She was a prisoner.
That doesn't make you soldiers.
That makes you cowards.
You don't understand!
The power of the ritual
had poisoned our minds,
taken control of our will.
By the time we came
to our senses, she'd escaped.
Colonel, your men are dead.
Killed by a woman
who wants retribution for your actions.
If she is coming for you...
Then let her come!
I killed her men and she killed mine.
But death comes for all of us.
Eventually, it will come for you.
The both of you.
Papa?
Don't worry, Alex, we're done here.
Watch his head.
Alexandra, thank you for coming.
I'm happy to oblige, Captain.
But a car crash has little to do
with my field of expertise.
Third drag race this month
to end in a car crash.
And it's also the third time
where the winning car
disappears to thin air.
Nothing picked up by checkpoints,
patrol cars, like he just vanished.
I didn't think drag races
were still a thing around here.
I wish they weren't.
And so does my tito.
Alexandra. This is my nephew, Marco.
From the Philippine
Fifth Infantry Division.
He's old friends
with the victim, JP Llorca.
It just doesn't make sense.
JP's been racing cars since he was a kid.
He wouldn't just wipe out like that.
Hoofprints.
Huh?
Looks like he had a passenger, a girl.
JP went everywhere
with his girlfriend, Coreen.
I've tried calling her,
but it's like she vanished, too.
Witnesses placed the victim
with a girl before the race.
Coreen would never leave JP,
especially not before a race.
No trace, no body.
She could have been kidnapped.
Boys, this isn't the time
to be mingling with the locals.
They're not just any locals, bossing.
They're witnesses.
I'm Hannah.
And I'm Amie.
You're wind people.
Yeah.
We're big fans of races.
The faster the car, the better.
We are especially fond
of that bright blue racer.
- You saw the other driver?
- Mm-hm.
Tall, dark, mysterious type,
full of bestial energy.
Had some real horsepower,
if you catch our drift.
I think I know where to start looking
for our missing girl.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
I think you have the wrong floor.
This is reserved for executives.
We're here to see Señor Armanaz.
- Do you have an appointment?
- It's urgent.
All matters of the Señor are urgent.
So unless you have
an appointment, security will be...
Señor Armanaz will see you now.
Thank you.
Only you, ma'am.
Señor Armanaz, Great Stallion,
and Lord of the Tikbalang,
I thank you for granting me an audience.
You are a strong-minded one,
little Trese.
Much like your father.
I only hope that the matter you bring
to me today is worthy of my time...
for your sake.
I beg your forgiveness, Señor,
but I have reason to believe
that one of your tribesmen
may have taken a trophy,
a young girl.
I need only to see her return to safety.
If whom you seek
is truly from my tribe,
then I shall take care of it myself.
If human trophies are indeed being taken,
then it would only upset the balance
between the human world
and the Underworld.
I have ruled
over these lands for millennia past...
...and you dare lecture me?
I meant no offense, Your Greatness,
but just as you watch over
the good of your tribe,
I too watch over mine.
Your father would be proud to see you
walking in his footsteps,
little Alexandra.
It's unfortunate that I cannot say
the same for my son, Maliksi.
He has gone missing these past weeks.
You shall return him to me, yes?
I promise you, Señor,
when I find the girl,
I shall return your son to safety.
Guerrero called again.
Busy night, bossing.
I feel like
the Underworld is testing me.
Captain Guerrero, we weren't expecting
to see you so soon.
Yeah, we got a call about a repairman
getting struck by lightning
while working on an electric pole.
It's nothing out of the ordinary
until you take a look at this.
Four individual incidents
of electrocution.
All accidents, all in four months.
Right here in the same village.
Sounds like too much of a coincidence.
Tabi-tabi po.
I knew you'd be snooping around here
sooner or later, little Trese.
Nuno, the accidents here in Livewell...
Aren't all a case of cross circuits,
if you ask me.
Been hearing ramblings
about the folks here
being extra prayerful lately.
I don't mean church either.
Trying to keep their happy lives
here and live
while still chug-chug-chugging along.
Then who are they praying to?
Let us just say they are still looking
to the heavens for answers.
So you might need a bit of magic
to part the clouds, so to speak.
Don't wander too far, Nuno,
in case I call on you again.
I never do.
Mga dating nakakubli, ngayo'y ibunyag.
Was this on any
of the other victims, Captain?
That wasn't in the coroner's report.
I can ask.
Don't bother.
I've always been meaning to complain
about our electricity bill.
Alexandra Trese,
surprised to see you here so late.
But then again, your line of work
does tend to keep you up at night.
Not any more than you, Bagyon Lektro.
Especially after finding your son's sigil
on a dead body in Livewell Village.
I don't quite like
what you're implying, Ms. Trese.
I know the rules.
Our family does not deal
in the trafficking of souls.
Not even if they were sacrificed
in your name?
I know how your family operates,
Bagyon Lektro.
You don't have free rein
over the lives of this city.
Not while I'm here.
Don't mistake me
for some lived-old horseman, Alexandra.
That balance
you and your father have tried
so desperately to maintain is at its end.
Is that why
you and your son have returned
to soliciting sacrifices
after all these years?
My son, my tribe, my family
is none of your business.
Then stay well away from mine
or the next dead body
with your son's sigil will be his.
You're treading
on very thin ice, little Trese.
Your father would have respected
my authority.
Meanwhile, you're letting
the foal of Armanaz
run wild in the streets of Manila.
- Whoa! Yeah!
- Yeah!
Are you sure
he's gonna be here?
As long as there's a worthy competition...
He'll never miss a race.
Just make sure you don't forget our deal.
Don't worry about us.
Just keep your eye on the road.
And make sure to have our prize
at the finish line.
Eh, you up for a race?
It depends.
You up for a challenge?
Haven't turned one down yet.
Winner gets a trophy.
Haven't heard that in a while.
You'll have to win first.
Ready, set...
Anytime you're ready, girls.
Then you better hold on to your hairdo.
'Cause once we go,
there's no turning back.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Now!
- Yeah!
You cheated!
You use magic, I use magic.
Sounds like a fair race to me.
I do not lose to inferior humans!
But you still lost,
which means you still owe me a trophy.
I am Maliksi, prince of the Tikbalang.
I owe you nothing.
And I was mistaken to think
that a prince of the Tikbalang
would still honor the code of the race.
Your father would be disappointed.
If only for the code of my people.
You may take your trophy.
She's nothing but a trinket to me.
Boys, Lektro called.
He says he wants to make a deal.
We'll pay him a visit
after we drop off Coreen.
You don't remember a thing, do you?
Nothing.
Not after JP agreed to race that blue car.
And then, well, that's when you showed up.
I don't know. It's like...
Someone cast a spell on you?
Something like that, yeah.
Is my boyfriend going to be okay?
The hospital says
he'll recover soon enough.
You can visit him after we take you home.
Find out anything good, bossing?
Yeah, we've been itching
for some action back here.
Bagyon Lektro wasn't there.
If he thinks I'm playing his game,
he's got another thing coming.
Looks like he's already
making his move, bossing.
Oh, not the car.
Alexandra Trese,
you dare challenge my father, my family?
Bagyon Kulimlim.
Still the spoiled brat
you've always been, I see.
The only thing spoiled
will be your burned carcass, Trese.
It's over, Alexandra.
Your father isn't here to protect you.
How are you, little Trese?
Sorry, I'm late. Traffic and all that.
Better late than never, Nuno.
Ground him!
Thanks for the assist, Nuno.
You know me.
I never miss a chance
to stick it to them big boys.
But you got to be careful who you trip up.
Can't be too sure
about the Underworld these days.
Anyone got spare change?
'Cause it looks like
we're taking the train.
Coffee, bossing?
Thanks, Hank.
Good morning, girls.
Did you enjoy your prize?
Um...
- Yeah.
- I guess you could say that.
Wait a minute, we were the prize
for winning the race?
I feel objectified.
Speaking of prizes,
that Marco guy sends his regards.
Wanted to thank you for getting
his friend's girlfriend back.
Even asked for your number
to thank you personally.
Oh, sounds like
he has a crush on you, bossing.
I told you to stay out
of my affairs, Alexandra.
Good morning, Bagyon Lektro.
You could have used the front door.
You extended the courtesy
to the Tikbalang,
but not to me, not to my son?
Courtesy went out the door
when Bagyon Kulimlim
attacked me in the open.
Then you will pay
for your transgressions, Alexandra Trese.
There is a storm coming.
And when it does,
don't expect help from my tribe.
Not counting on it, Lektro.
Whatever the storm,
we'll be ready.
♪ Sometimes at night ♪
♪ I toss and turn ♪
♪ Did I make a mistake? ♪
♪ Regret fills me up inside ♪
♪ I won't waste ♪
♪ The legacy you passed on to me ♪
♪ Be careful ♪
♪ What you promise ♪
♪ I fear no one ♪
♪ When I feel you next to me ♪