- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
GERALT: The Trail will test you.
Force you to move beyond the pain,
the fear,
the failure.
[GASPS]
Until you become one
with the killer itself.
Remember, hesitation
will draw danger to you like fire.
But trust the path you choose...
and it will protect you.
[CIRI PANTING]
Even in darkness.
[GASPS]
As long as you listen.
Always listen.
- [DISTANT ROARING]
- [GASPS]
[BELLOWING]
- [DISTANT SCREECHING]
- [PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[BLADE RINGS]
[LOUD SCREECHING]
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
[GROWLING]
[SIGHS]
- [SIGHS]
- [BRANCH BREAKS]
TRISS: Don't be scared.
I'm not going to hurt you.
You're a girl.
So are you.
I'm going to Kaer Morhen.
Is that where you're headed?
I appreciate the suspicion,
but be reasonable.
Would I have gotten this far
if I didn't know the way?
Let me look.
[BIRD CROAKING]
[SPEAKING IN ELDER]
[CHUCKLES]
Your heart beat faster.
I heard it.
It's nice to meet you.
You... you're a sorceress, like Yennefer.
GERALT: Triss.
And a friend of Geralt's.
You must be quite charitable.
[LAUGHS]
It's good to see you again.
And you.
GERALT: I brought dinner.
More than that.
My child, what a surprise.
Hello, Vesemir.
Oh, hell,
haven't even had me fill of grog yet,
and already, the women are doubling.
- Merigold.
- Lambert.
I see your wounds have improved,
but your manners have not.
[LAUGHING]
I wish you'd come sooner.
We all could have used you.
Hopefully, we still can.
Your turn, boys. Get to it.
I'll go and dress for dinner. I assume
you'll all want to wash up as well?
[COEN SCOFFS]
[CHUCKLING]
Of course not.
So how do you two know each other?
[SIGHS]
[CROWS CAWING]
- [HANDBELL RINGING]
- CRIER: People of Gors Velen,
the end is nigh!
The Wild Hunt walks among us.
- Get in there, you elven pig.
- CRIER: The end is nigh!
The end is nigh!
Nilfgaard are our punishment
from the gods!
GUARD: Keep it moving!
Take your mind off it, Beardell.
I have done. For the past hour.
Stop! That is enough from the two of you!
Stop fidgeting!
[CRIES OUT]
Shut up and get over here!
[PRISONER MUMBLING]
- I need to relieve myself.
- We'll reach our destination by sundown.
- Where are you taking us?
- Shut up!
Please, sir. I can't wait.
Could I be escorted to an alley?
You can restrain me.
Yeah, well, if it can't wait,
it can't wait, can it?
[SIGHS] Thank you, sir.
Go on, then.
Relieve yourself.
You elf scum.
Come on, then!
- Move, you pointies!
- CRIER: The Wild Hunt!
The Wild Hunt walks among us!
Watch for the signs!
The market is too crowded.
Soldiers are everywhere.
Portal us out of here.
I can't. Portals can be tracked.
Then explain to me
how you're not dead weight.
Looked in the mirror lately?
Prison didn't do you any favors.
I have a mission to complete.
We must get back to Cintra.
Sure. The Nilfgaardians
will be thrilled to have me.
We can reminisce
and share fond memories of Sodden.
You'll be entering with their commander
general. They'll make new memories.
They already are. With the elves.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
Oh, you didn't know.
Reclaimed as Xin'trea.
- Under Fringilla's leadership.
- Fringilla?
Funny how quickly people forget about you
when you're no longer of use to them,
isn't it?
[CROWS CAWING]
[SCREECHING]
CAHIR: We're not safe here.
We are not a "we."
[TOWNSPEOPLE WHISPERING]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
Cintra it is.
King Vizimir, the Northern Kingdoms
are united by a common enemy now,
but it is a tenuous alliance.
Opportunists and assassins lurk
where you least expect them.
I will not live in fear.
MAN: Nor would we ask you to.
We only want to serve Redania
as best we can.
- [GRUNTS]
- Ugh.
[CHOKING]
- VIZIMIR: Dijkstra?
- Good afternoon, Your Highness.
[GASPS]
Drink it.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Now.
[GASPS]
- [GULPS]
- [GOBLET FALLS]
Oh!
[GURGLING]
[SIGHS] Apologies for the theatrics,
Your Highness,
but I just had to be sure.
Fuckers.
Do you know,
I've known him since I was 12.
Even traitors speak the truth.
[GRUNTS]
The Northern Kingdoms
have formed an alliance
based on their mutual hatred of elves.
But, and if you'll excuse me
for saying so, Your Highness,
we shouldn't give a shit.
What'll happen
once the elves are rounded up and killed?
Once they've escaped to Cintra?
Why did Nilfgaard go to all the trouble
of taking the Continent's crown jewel
only to fill it with hungry mouths?
Yes, speaking of which,
I'm starving, Dijkstra. Get to the point.
Cintra is the point, Your Highness.
We would never have taken it
from Calanthe.
But now...
Cintra could be ours?
If we're smart.
Leave it with us.
CIRI: I'm starving. Can I start?
TRISS: It's quieter in here
than I remember.
- COEN: More food for the rest of us.
- MAN 1: My belly's cooled down.
MAN 2: Talking of bellies...
Aren't there any herbs
or mushrooms for me today?
In December?
[COUGHS] That windmill
knock your head about, Princess?
- Right.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
[MEN LAUGHING]
So, Geralt said you saved his life.
He found himself in my kingdom a time ago.
Helped me with a...
a princess in trouble.
Nastier than you, even.
- Hm!
- TRISS: He's not joking.
She took a big chunk out of him.
But he saved her anyway.
Well, you healed my cheek.
Seems pretty impressive too.
I like your dress.
Thank you.
Would you like me
to show you around the keep?
I actually know this place pretty well.
When Geralt told me what Triss had done
for him, I invited her here.
I brought her here for you.
To help guide you.
What, like Mousesack did for my mother?
Just like Mousesack.
But now it's time for bed.
I'm not tired.
COEN: All right, come on, you little rat.
I'll play a few rounds of snaps
with you before bed.
Maybe I might even let you win.
[SCOFFS] Yeah, you wish!
Night, everyone.
Good night.
- Good night, Ciri.
- LAMBERT: Night.
- COEN: Night, all.
- GERALT: Good night.
COEN: So, you think
you can beat me, do you?
So how do you two know each other?
[SIGHS]
[DOG BARKING]
CAHIR: We can steal our way
onto a boat at dawn.
- [MAN 1 LAUGHING]
- MAN 2: Oi! What's under the hat?
MAN 1: Look! I knew it. A fucking elf!
[GRUNTING]
- Get down boy. Stay down!
- Pointy fuck!
Come.
You two. Thought you could get away?
[YELLS]
[GASPING]
- I had that covered.
- Course you did.
CAHIR: Down here!
[YENNEFER GROANS]
Oh, shit.
Shit, shit. [SIGHS]
We're safer down here
than we are up there.
- [GRUNTS]
- Make a move and lose your head!
[FLAME GUSTS]
Stay back!
We're not here to hurt you.
- [CAHIR GRUNTS]
- [YELPS]
[YELLS] I'm still thinking it over!
Run, Dermain. Run! Run like hell!
I'm not abandoning you.
I'll stay and fight.
You don't really want to hurt me.
Dermain, was it?
Traitorous elven mage,
from the posters, you're her!
And the wanted Nilfgaardian soldier!
Ba'lian, they're on our side!
No one's on our side, you trusting idiot.
Are you going to the Sandpiper?
Shut up, damn it! Shut up!
The Sandpiper is an angel of refuge
to the persecuted.
- What is he saying?
- All right, all right!
[PANTING]
[SIGHS] Um...
The Sandpiper
helps elves get to Xin'trea.
We get to Oxenfurt,
he puts us on a boat.
It's just the two of us.
If you know a way to Cintra and help us,
I can assure you
your pick of land on our safe return.
If there's no room,
we'll catch the next boat.
I promise.
[SIGHING] Oh, for fuck's sake.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
All right. Come on.
You're very pretty.
It appears you have some use after all.
Thankfully, men remain simple.
[ECHOING CRASH]
[CRASH]
[GURGLING GROWL]
So your surprise was more surprising
than you'd imagined.
And mysterious.
She won't tell me anything
from before the fall of Cintra.
[SIGHS]
Well, if her mother
did have powers, as you say,
if she was a mage
who never properly harnessed,
the child could have inherited
an evolved version of it.
But it's an untested theory.
When did Ciri start
exhibiting signs of Chaos?
That's the issue.
She hasn't exhibited
any typical indicators of Chaos.
- She can't even form witcher signs.
- What do you mean by "typical"?
She might have the power of foresight.
She seems to have visions
of things that have yet to come to pass.
Like what?
She saw me
at the aftermath of Sodden Hill.
Before it happened.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
No one should have to gaze
upon that carnage.
That loss.
There's more.
Ciri felt something else.
A pull.
Toward the leshy that turned Eskel.
Like a compass to a magnet,
she led me straight to it.
And then this...
tore it in half
and charged us.
TRISS: Gods...
- What is it?
- I've never seen anything like it.
But it did try to get her.
Both of them did.
To do what?
I didn't let it live long enough
to find out.
Could a mage have made this?
Theoretically.
But generating monsters
has been outlawed for centuries.
Oh, outlawed.
So definitely not a mage, then.
[LAUGHS]
There is one way to find out.
May I?
[SPEAKING IN ELDER]
If there is any sign of mutagenic alchemy,
if a mage has been involved,
that component will glow.
We'll know by morning.
- But why would a mage want her?
- [SIGHS]
I don't know.
Mages, Nilfgaard,
something dark lies ahead of her.
I can feel it.
That's why I'm training her.
I won't be here forever to protect her.
I'm sorry about Eskel.
I'm sorry about Sodden.
Those who died, I...
I say their names at night
when I lay down, so I don't forget.
Atlan Kerk.
Vanielle of Brugge.
Axel Raby.
- Dagobert...
- Stop.
If it's up to me,
everyone will know their names.
They can live on in our memories.
Perhaps something more.
[SIGHS]
Oh.
You witchers,
you pretend not to have emotions,
but you do.
I know you feel it too.
[WHISPERS] All of it.
Normal love,
normal hatred,
normal pain, fear and regret,
normal joy,
and normal sadness.
[SIGHS]
Stay with me tonight.
- Triss.
- Only stay.
Let's not be alone.
I'm sorry.
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
[ECHOING CROAKING]
What is this place?
Old elven aqueducts.
Humans built their world
on top of our ruins.
Hand me a torch.
Who did this to you?
This is important.
Yeah, all right, all right.
Some villagers came at us
at a tavern, a week back.
We work... well, worked
at the bank in Gors Velen.
It's dwarf-owned,
so the owner...
let us escape
before the guards
came in for a roundup.
Ever since
the elves took refuge in Xin'trea,
the North have been claiming
that we're all sleeper agents
for Nilfgaard.
Sounds familiar.
Oh, I doubt that.
All we can hope for now is to survive.
There's said to be a pregnant elf
in Xin'trea.
Think of it, Bal. A new beginning.
It's a fairy tale.
We don't have the fight left anymore
to start anew.
The North have made sure of that.
Fuck the North!
Yeah, I know. Fuck the North!
No. I'm starting anew.
Get a little patch of land,
raise some chickens.
Find a buxom, raven-haired woman
to boss me around.
[BA'LIAN SCOFFS]
I'll borrow your hope, then.
[LOUD CROAKING]
Come on, help him! Help me!
[YELLS] What the fuck is it?
CAHIR: I can't see a thing!
Help us!
- YENNEFER: Pull!
- [CROAKING]
[SCREECHING]
- No!
- Hey! Come back!
- [BOTH YELLING]
- [CREATURE CROAKING]
- No! No! He's gone!
- [GASPS]
Fuck!
[PANTING]
Shit.
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Got you!
- [CREATURE GROWLING]
[YENNEFER GASPING]
- [CREATURE ROARING]
- [GROANS] Kill it! Use your magic!
[SCREAMS] I can't!
- [YELLS]
- [SCREAMS] Get off!
Move!
Come on! Let's go!
- [CAHIR GASPING]
- YENNEFER: Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Fuck, fuck!
What the fuck is the point?
- Of screaming?
- Of anything!
- [GROANS]
- [SOBBING]
You're born helpless so you find strength.
Then that's all they want you for,
to use you. [SOBS]
- And you find love, but it isn't real.
- [SIGHS]
It's... it's a wish someone made once,
before they even knew who you were.
And you... you find power,
and it turns to ash in your hands!
- Hey!
- [GASPS]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
You were incredible that day in Sodden.
The fire.
- [SOBS]
- [SIGHS]
Oh...
Oh, that's what did you in, isn't it?
It stole your power.
[GASPS]
[CAHIR SIGHS]
[SOBS]
We all have our time in the sun.
[SIGHS]
Your magic has served its purpose.
[SIGHS] Perhaps there's a bigger plan
out there for you now.
Yes, yes, yes, the benevolent White Flame
who brings purpose
and meaning and all that fuckery!
Skip the recruitment speech.
- Fringilla already gave it.
- Fringilla is devoted to the cause.
[YELLS] Oh!
The most important thing
they teach you at Aretuza isn't magic!
It's to make people in power believe
anything you want them to.
Do anything you want them to!
Fringilla's a political animal.
- Trained by the best.
- Yes, I met your best!
She tried to puncture my brain
and extract every one of my thoughts.
- Exactly.
- Yes, and it didn't work.
But what if it had, huh?
What if it had worked?
What would she have found?
Fringilla and I serve Emhyr
because he served us first.
Everyone answers to someone eventually.
Even you, I suspect.
- [RUSTLING]
- [BRANCH BREAKS]
YENNEFER: You little shit.
Oi!
Get here now, you little shit.
- Come on. Find somewhere. Hey!
- [CROWD CHEERING]
Come on!
SINGER: ♪ All those lonely nights... ♪
You left your friend to die
in a fucking sewer.
You ran.
I... I... I took the only option I had.
He would have done the same.
I... I had to save myself.
You're not worth it.
What's going on?
We have to wait for the place to empty.
Then the piper will take us to the boat.
- The Sandpiper?
- That's the one.
He performs here every night.
♪ As I burn all the memories of you ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
you have been the most beautiful audience.
- Remember to toss a coin if you can.
- [GROANING]
If anyone needs me, I'll be at the bar.
♪ What for do you yearn? ♪
- ♪ It's the point of no return... ♪
- [WOMAN GIGGLES] Ooh-hoo-hoo!
♪ After everything we did, we saw ♪
♪ You turned your back on me ♪
♪ What for do you yearn? ♪
♪ Watch that Butcher ♪
♪ Burn! ♪
♪ At the end of my days when I'm through ♪
♪ No word that I've written
Will ring quite as true ♪
♪ As burn ♪
♪ Burn, Butcher, burn! ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn! ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn, burn... ♪
[SIGHS SHAKILY]
♪ Watch me burn ♪
♪ All the memories ♪
♪ Of you ♪
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
Thank you.
Leave it with me.
[ECHOING] Leave it with me.
No, no, no. No.
There's a... religious zeal
to the followers of the White Flame.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe that's our way into Cintra.
The priestess.
Good point.
Holy men are always the most depraved.
Hmm... Hm, hm!
A prostitute.
Emhyr has to like women!
Or men.
[LAUGHS]
That's the problem.
No one knows his proclivities.
No one knows anything about him.
Who he is. What he is.
Where he is. What he wants.
And nothing he does
makes any fucking sense!
We need to get
as much information as possible.
Whoever we use needs to be
inside the city walls for a while.
But that narrows our options considerably.
[CHUCKLES]
Now that is an out of the box idea.
Getting an elf into Cintra
won't be a problem.
But it needs to be the right one.
Someone malleable.
Distrustful.
In all the right ways.
GUARD: You.
Come with me.
- MAN: Things are...
- [LAUGHTER]
Good morning, Ciri.
Morning.
TRISS: You look lovely and refreshed.
Triss, when do you think
we can get started?
Today.
I was hoping you'd help me in the lab.
We can get to know each other.
I can show you a few incantations.
Get a sense for your potential.
COEN:
...and be a great foal to ride, too.
Everard.
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
- Oh, good morning, Your Highness.
- [BOTH CHUCKLING]
Please tell me you lost a bet.
Is that a flower in your hair, girl?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, she's not joking.
You never got my rags that clean.
COEN: Yeah, like you ever wash.
- I don't need to, Coen.
- [LAUGHTER]
Now that's funny.
Thought it suited her, actually.
LAMBERT: Sure, if she's going to a ball.
- [LAUGHS]
- What happened?
Oh, nothing. She just got
her royal knickers in a twist.
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
It's just a bit of fun.
TRISS: For who?
You dress her in rags.
Keep her bruised as an apple.
That is, when she isn't
washing piss-pots or your trousers.
Does she even have a chemise? Or soap?
Or cloth for when she gets her blood?
Though, with those mushrooms
you're feeding her,
you'll ruthlessly deprive her of that
before too long.
You say you're mutants.
That's why you don't understand
what people feel.
But the truth is, you're choosing
to be ignorant arseholes, aren't you?
Triss.
[COEN SIGHS]
[SIGHS]
How long did it take you
to learn to control your powers?
A long time.
Just like it will for you.
It's not ready yet.
I can wait.
They felt bad
you didn't finish your breakfast.
[CHUCKLES]
[TRISS CHUCKLES]
You know,
my grandmother fought battles
and wore dresses.
You can do both.
- [DEVICE RATTLING]
- I know.
TRISS: It's ready.
No glow.
So no evidence of mutagenic alchemy.
But there is something strange.
Stellacite.
Like from a monolith.
I've never seen that before.
This was taken
from the leshy that turned Eskel.
- TRISS: More stellacite.
- [SIGHS]
How did two different monsters wind up
with the same dust on them?
GERALT: They came from the same place.
A monolith? It doesn't make sense.
Tell us what you know about it.
When...
when Nilfgaard attacked Cintra,
just outside the city walls,
I...
I saw a monolith topple.
How?
[GASPS]
[HARSH WHISPER ECHOING]
[ECHOING] Daughter of Chaos belongs to us.
Turn your backs.
Join the procession.
[MULTIPLE VOICES]
There is only death here.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [GASPS]
- GERALT: Cirilla.
- Ciri. Hey.
I'm fine.
[SIGHS]
You are brave.
But let us help.
[WHISPERS] All right.
[SIGHS]
When the Black Knight captured me...
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
...I was scared.
I screamed.
And that's when the monolith
cracked and fell.
I toppled it.
How could that be?
GERALT: I don't know.
I need to see it for myself.
I really didn't mean to do it, Geralt.
And if these monsters are my fault...
It's all right.
I'll fix it.
[CHILDREN PLAYING OUTSIDE]
[SEABIRDS CALLING]
Sleep it off somewhere else, chap.
[MAN GROANS]
[GRUMBLING]
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
YENNEFER: Bard.
Witch.
What are you doing here?
And what fresh hell
did you just crawl out of?
A sewer.
- What's your excuse?
- Oh, a sewer?
I always knew
you were a blood-sucking, joyless...
hugger?
Hugging. We are hugging.
Oh, gods, I miss the days
when my biggest problem
was an ever-present, sing-songy twit.
Uh, drink? I'm gonna drink.
I am not having this conversation
unless I'm drinking.
I heard the song.
Geralt must have left
quite a sour taste in your mouth.
What? He... No one leaves any tastes
in my mouth, thank you very much.
I sing of universal matters,
my dear, generous lady.
Emotions which anybody could experience.
That song could be about anyone.
- Mmm.
- Anyone.
- Mm. Mm-hm.
- Mm...
Fine. Yes, when I wrote it,
it did come from the heart.
Perhaps a broken one.
We're better off without him.
Yes.
- Oh, by the gods, that is awful.
- [GROANS]
And I am going
to find anything else to drink
whilst you tell me
why the hell your sad arse is here.
You're the Sandpiper.
What? No. Yes. No.
How do you know that name?
You pick up a thing or two
when you're in hiding.
You're in hiding?
Because you're part elf...
Yennefer, I completely forgot.
I'm so sorry.
I would not wish that fate
on my worst enemy, and, yes, you are...
firmly lodged in that category,
it has to be said, but...
what they've done to you
and your people is...
unspeakable.
[SOFTLY] But some people are speaking.
There are anonymous benefactors
working behind the scenes,
helping me, helping us,
helping us make this right.
Why help? What's in it for you?
I was at the great oak Bleobheris
when it was raided.
The Seat of Friendship,
the druids called it.
Where every free thinker was welcome,
no matter their race, their creed...
They come for the elves, Yennefer.
They'll come for the dwarves.
And sooner or later,
they will come for everyone.
Anyone that they deem the "other," so...
Eventually...
no artist is safe.
[SIGHS]
Besides, at the end of the day,
if I've learned one thing,
it is that sometimes,
legends can be intoxicating.
Well, Sandpiper,
the man, the myth, the legend,
- I need your help.
- Stand back! Stand back!
He's with me. It's okay.
I need to get to Cintra.
The both of us.
JASKIER: Well, I'll do what I can.
But know this.
You, you both...
smell truly awful.
I mean, it is like
something has crawled up your arses
and died.
So...
We leave Oxenfurt at nightfall.
Plenty of time to take a bath before then.
Just sayin'.
Coen replenished your elixirs.
Thank you.
Last night...
It's all right.
I can't be what you want, Triss.
What you deserve.
- If things were different...
- Except they're not.
And I'm grown enough to understand that.
Last night...
you were what I was looking for.
[WHISPERS] Your pain...
[SIGHS]
...it excited me.
Because I finally felt something again.
You mean after Sodden?
Most of us were cured after the battle.
You can hardly see the marks, but...
Some wounds cannot be healed.
I understand that more than you know.
I hope that in your search to feel again...
- you feel your value.
- To Ciri?
To me.
You are important to me, Triss.
- You always will be.
- VESEMIR: You're going to Cintra?
You said you'd never go back there.
Twice.
No witcher yet has died of old age
lying in bed dictating his will, Vesemir.
I have a girl to protect.
I can't just stay here.
I have a friend who studies monoliths.
I can portal you to him.
[SIGHS]
Portals are no fun.
There you go.
[WHOOSHING]
ISTREDD: Stay back!
[SIGHS]
You must be the mage.
I know who I am.
Who the fuck are you?
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
JASKIER: A group of elves
from Tretogor is on board.
And if the ship is full?
Well... then you're swimming.
Come on.
I'll go first.
Stick close to the wall and stay
out of sight until I give you the signal.
I'm gonna do what I do best.
And what's that?
Oh, I never really know.
Yeah, that's why I'm so good at it.
[DOG BARKING]
[WHISTLES MERRILY]
Excuse me.
- Fuck!
- Excuse me!
Papers for the transit, please.
- Papers? Absolutely. Papers.
- Yeah.
Ah-ha! How silly of me.
[CHUCKLES] I'm just gonna...
One moment.
- A lot of pockets.
- Mm-hm.
♪ The golden one with the golden rules ♪
Ain't that the, uh...
the song with the, uh...
♪ The long-necked warriors ♪
- ♪ With all their tools ♪
- [LAUGHS] You know it!
- Oh, yeah, yeah! [CHUCKLING]
- Oh!
You're him.
Jaskier, the bard?
- Guilty.
- Oh! [LAUGHS]
Not literally, but, you know.
- Don't worry about the papers.
- Oh!
Thanks for the tunes.
My niece, oh! Just loves them.
- Oh, that's lovely.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Well, bless her, bless yourself.
- Oh, yes.
- Have a lovely evening.
- Oh, you take care, good sir! [CHUCKLES]
Uh, although,
if you don't mind me saying so, that one,
it's, uh... it's not your strongest.
Oh, yeah?
It's a bit complicated.
Took me to the fourth verse to understand
there were different timelines.
- Oh, did it? Well...
- [CHUCKLES] That magic kiss?
- That was a bit cheap.
- Yeah?
I spotted the dragon reveal a mile away.
Oh, you're clever. You're a clever one.
I must say, the, uh...
the bit when the lute player ends up
with the warrior ladies...
Lovable, lovable lutanist.
Yeah! [CHUCKLES]
Didn't really ring true for me,
I must say.
All right.
[CHUCKLES]
Am I gonna say it?
Yeah, I'm gonna say it.
You know,
if you could write yourself a little song,
you could sing yourself
whatever you please,
- but you can't, can you?
- [GROANS]
Because you are a dockside scapegrace,
a qualling feculent,
a beef-witted,
hell-hated, addlepated goon...
This is taking too long.
We need to get him away from the ramps.
- ...and a waste of your father's...
- What are you doing?
I'll distract him.
You take them onto the boat.
Like hell! I'm not going
to fucking Cintra without you.
My head will roll
before I step through the gate.
- Listen to me.
- ...in all of my...
None of us will get to Cintra
if I don't do something.
- If you do, you'll get us all killed.
- ...leave it to...
And maybe, just maybe,
you are grateful to be entertained.
- You're an hero to my niece.
- Well...
- Practically worships you.
- Naturally. [CHUCKLES]
She'll be heartbroken to hear
her favorite bard
- is a steaming pile of shit for brains.
- Well...
This ship's not going anywhere
till I check your papers.
Understand?
BA'LIAN: Fuck the North.
What did you say?
Fuck the North.
Come again?
[SHOUTS] Fuck the North!
[LAUGHS]
- [GRUNTING]
- No, don't...
[GROWLS]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [CHUCKLES]
Fuck the elves.
[GROANS]
[GUARD LAUGHING]
Go on, get stuck in.
- MAN: Go on!
- [GROANS]
- [GUARD LAUGHING]
- [MEN SHOUTING]
We need to go. Now.
[BA'LIAN WHIMPERING]
- GUARD: Go on, lads!
- [ALL YELLING]
[CHUCKLING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[BIRD CROAKING]
[BIRD CALLING]
[SIGHS]
Hmm.
[WIND HOWLING]
Ohh...
VESEMIR: According to Geralt,
no one knows the Continent's vegetation
better than you.
Tell me I'm not crazy.
Tell me what I'm looking at here.
- Feainnewedd.
- Mmm.
This only grows
where Elder blood has been spilled.
Where did you find this?
Killer Trail. Training course.
Everywhere that girl got her ass kicked.
Elder blood was wiped
from the Continent generations ago.
There are legends
that Elder blood was one
of the key ingredients
in the creation
of the first witcher mutagens.
Mutagens that were destroyed
in the sacking of Kaer Morhen.
Not another witcher's been created since.
Vesemir, these are new buds.
Exactly.
Destiny has given us a gift.
The key to making more witchers.
Ciri.
It's all right. You're safe. You're safe.
You all right?
Thank you.
We, all of us, would be dead without you.
Ah, well.
I'm Dara.
It's lovely to meet you, Dara.
I expect you
to do great things, all right?
Make this worth it.
Someone should receive you
on the other side.
Thank you. I'll make sure they get
everything they need when we arrive.
[MEN SHOUTING ON DECK]
What?
What happened to you?
I've lived a long life.
You'll have to be more specific.
[SIGHS]
Chaos appears to be done with me.
You've lost your magic?
Is... is that even possible?
Go on. Get your gloating in.
- Time's limited.
- [LAUGHS]
Once upon a time,
I would have used this opportunity
to call you an empty, lonely,
power hungry she-demon, but...
I'm an artist, Yennefer.
It's my job
to put myself in other people's shoes.
Even if they are, in your case,
large, clunky,
and, I don't know,
probably full of snakes or something.
[SHIP CREAKING]
I'm scared too.
I'm scared that one day,
the muses will stop speaking to me.
Because who are we...
when we can no longer do the one thing
we were put on this Continent to do?
We find a new purpose.
A better one.
Hopefully.
Hmm.
Chaos could never be done
with the likes of you,
Yennefer of Vengerberg.
Of that much,
I am certain.
So, if it's all the same to you,
goodbye,
good luck,
good riddance.
[SNORTS]
Same to you.
- [YELLS] Oh, no!
- [LUTE STRINGS JANGLE]
[CREAKING]
[COMMOTION]
Yennefer, what are you doing?
Yennefer!
We have to save ourselves.
JASKIER: ♪ I hear ♪
♪ You're alive ♪
♪ How disappointing ♪
♪ I've also survived ♪
♪ No thanks to you ♪
♪ Did I not bring you some glee ♪
♪ Mister Oh, Look At Me? ♪
♪ Now I'll burn ♪
♪ All the memories of you ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
you have been the most beautiful audience!
Remember to toss a coin if you can.
If anyone needs me, I'll be at the bar.
♪ What for do you yearn? ♪
♪ It's the point of no return ♪
♪ After everything we did, we saw ♪
♪ You turned your back on me ♪
♪ What for do you yearn? ♪
♪ Watch that Butcher ♪
♪ Burn! ♪
♪ At the end of my days when I'm through ♪
♪ No word that I've written
Will ring quite as true ♪
♪ As burn ♪
♪ Burn, Butcher, burn! ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn! ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn, burn, burn... ♪
♪ Burn ♪
[SIGHS SHAKILY]
♪ Watch me burn ♪
♪ All the memories ♪
♪ Of you ♪
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44