[English subtitles are available]
[Crush]
[Episode 7]
As for Xiao Wei,
based on my judgment,
she has the tendency of
avoidant personality disorder.
In that case,
when she loses her parents
or people around her
who are close to her,
she won't react aggressively.
However,
children who seem to be
obedient and sensible
usually don't express
their true feelings.
Therefore,
when they go to a new environment,
building mental resilience is important.
Are you rest assured now?
I didn't know that
you're quite serious in studying.
That's because I have a good brain.
Actually,
I have been holding back
from saying something.
At the Ferris wheel...
You're still owing me a question,
aren't you?
Finally you have something to ask.
Ask away.
What is that question?
Do you like me?
Yes.
Why do you like me?
Well...
You're...
I...
Su Nian Qin.
I'm such a fool!
Nian Qin, you...
Go now.
We've been together
for almost four years now.
You've been witnessing
my development in psychology.
Look.
No doubt I lack hands-on experience,
but I have a good memory.
However, I don't remember
any theory
that can explain Su Nian Qin
and his unstable emotions.
Here, tell me why.
He doesn't know the answer.
It's your turn.
If you ask me,
you can't blame him.
You failed to answer his question.
"Love at first sight".
It's such a short answer
but you couldn't even say it.
No.
I...
At that moment,
I knew that
it's not just love at first sight.
It's also because...
Why am I not an art student?
Why is my ability to express the language
so terrible?
[Third Class of Year Three]
That's all for today.
Stand up.
Thank you, Mr Su.
Thank you, everyone.
It's my honour to be your teacher.
Thank you.
[Third Class of Year Three
for students with visual impairments]
I was right.
You didn't bid them goodbye.
Thank you.
We are the ones who should thank you.
Perhaps
we'll need your help again.
Sure.
Mr Su.
Will I see you again?
Sure.
I'll pay you a visit when I'm free.
This is a goodbye present.
I only have this.
This is...
I got the candy from Ms Sang.
She told me not to tell you.
Otherwise, you'll scold her again.
She lied.
What else did she tell you?
She also told me that
you lied about not fancying sweet food.
Every child loves sweet food.
Mr Su.
I'm going to miss you.
Don't miss me.
Study well.
Wait for me to come back, okay?
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.
It's all here.
Finally we have gathered enough materials.
Finally.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You look so pale.
I stayed up two nights
in a row to work on my thesis.
You just have to tell me.
You didn't have to come here.
I'm quite puzzled.
I can tell that
working at the news department
is taking a toll on you.
I guess you don't really enjoy it either.
What do you still work here?
I want to finish what I start.
I can't leave the job
just because I'm dejected.
I think disliking the job is one thing,
disliking working is another thing.
Look at me.
I don't like psychology
but I still stick to it.
I think
it's impressive
to devote myself to something I hate.
All right.
Let's pack up and leave.
It's getting late.
It's so funny.
One time, I ran into someone in the lift.
The same thing happened.
I think there's a power outage.
Hello.
We're trapped in the lift.
I think we're at level six.
Okay.
The management is getting it fixed.
They told us to be patient.
Fortunately I'm trapped here with you.
If I were with Cheng Yin now,
I would be freaked out.
She has claustrophobia.
I've never seen her use a lift.
Goodness.
You have a one-track mind,
just like Wei Hao.
Do I really have to
make everything clear
so that you can be normal?
I thought things
would go back to normal
after we spent two days together.
Fine, I admit.
Things were brought to a deadlock
due to my fault.
However, as a human being,
it's normal to be block-headed.
Wei Hao was my childhood friend.
He's been following me around since young.
He fell in love with you all of a sudden.
I need some time to get used to it.
Worse, both of you
didn't tell me the truth.
You especially.
I'm so mad at you.
I got so much madder at you than him.
I don't mind losing
that useless childhood friend.
However,
you're my best friend.
How could you do that to me?
Wu Yan, Wei Hao and I...
Enough.
We've resolved the misunderstanding.
He told me
you left the band.
You also had a row with him.
If it's because of me,
it's not necessary at all.
What happened later
was not because of you.
My mum is back.
She came to see me.
She...
I bet she's dumped by her boyfriend again.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone
about it.
Anyway,
I have so much to worry about.
I don't have that time for her.
How about Wei Hao?
What do you plan to do?
I'm going to do nothing.
Just let it be.
We'll listen to the song next time.
Good morning, Mr Qiu. Hello, Mr Wu.
Morning.
Mr Li.
Wu Yan.
Have you done
dealing with your school affair?
I've submitted the draft of my thesis.
Mr Li.
What happened to Mr Su's desk?
Ms Zheng is back.
It's natural that Mr Su has to leave.
When did that happen?
It happened over the past two days
when you were on leave.
You've missed your chance.
You didn't get to
bid him goodbye before he left.
[Sorry.]
[The number you've
dialled is unavailable.]
[Please try again later.]
Ms Sang.
Is Mr Su not coming?
Xiao Wei.
Maybe Mr Su is not good at
saying goodbye.
That's why he decided not to come.
Please understand his feelings, okay?
I'm here for you.
I'll pay you a visit
with Mr Su in the future, okay?
Sure.
He promised to pay me a visit too.
Don't forget it.
Sure.
Here, let's make a pinky promise.
Let's go.
Please take care of her.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ms Sang.
Don't mention it.
Xiao Wei.
Nian Qin, what's wrong?
Why didn't you answer the phone call?
My sister said that she called you.
That's why I switched off the phone.
Nian Qin, you should go home.
Sure.
Do whatever you want.
I've made arrangements
for meals and laundry services.
During this period,
there's no need for you
to leave the house.
I'm leaving. Take care.
Where are you going?
I'm going on a break.
Have a good one.
To be honest,
it's very wise for you
to ignore that lady.
Don't ruin the girl
with your odd temperament.
If you ask me,
I would suggest you
seek help from your former boss
to look for him.
Don't you forget that he's Yi Jin.
I've asked him.
I didn't get any feedback.
[Mum]
What's wrong?
How dare you ask me that question?
It's been so many days
since you last answered my phone call.
You only sent me
a few brief text messages on WeChat.
You're busy?
I don't get it.
Why are you so occupied?
Mr Zhao told me that
you haven't even submitted your thesis.
Goodness, Zhao is calling me out again.
You have the cheeks to blame him.
Listen.
You'd better come home right away
when the semester break starts.
We'll get someone
to guide you
on the postgraduate entrance examination.
If you're unable to register this year,
you'll sit for the examination next year.
I can't let you
fool around.
Did I hear it correctly?
Sit for the examination next year?
Didn't I say that
I want to work?
I've started working at the radio station.
Furthermore,
I plan to continue working there.
Don't tell me about the radio station.
No one listens to radio stations nowadays.
Not even your dad listens to the radio.
Working at a radio station
is not as good as being a professor
in a university.
Not only are the benefits better,
you'll be respected too.
Everyone wants the position so badly.
I'm the exception.
You're talking about success in life
based on conventional belief.
I don't feel like talking with you.
I'll have to work
during the semester break
before I can go home.
We'll talk about it when I'm home.
[Mum]
Hello?
You don't have to worry about money.
Just take care of her.
Got it.
I'll go home early.
If there's nothing else, I have to go.
Thank you.
I just passed by
and saw you by chance.
Are you here for an interview?
I've missed out on
the peak recruiting season.
It's difficult to secure a good job.
Aren't you working
at the radio station with Wu Yan?
You don't want to work there?
Radio station...
It's not up to me.
I need to have a spare plan.
By the way,
don't tell Wu Yan
that I came for an interview.
Students.
As we know,
Chinese Braille
is made of consonants and basic finals.
[Each syllable is written with
up to three Braille cells.]
[A phrase
is formed by two to three syllables.]
♫ I want to see ♫
[A sentence is formed by
combining a few phrases.]
♫ All the possibilities ♫
♫ Make me believe ♫
Ms Sang, what can I help?
♫ You're the only one ♫
♫ Yes I believe ♫
Mr Li wants me to deliver the worksheets.
He'll explain about
the school break later.
♫ All the promises that you gave ♫
Thank you.
♫ No matter how long the journey is ♫
♫ We'll be together ♫
♫ You're the most reliable ♫
♫ Refuge ♫
♫ You're also my deepest ♫
♫ Secret ♫
[Nian Qin]
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
♫ In fact, we're indeed very close ♫
♫ to each other ♫
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
♫ However, it still feel as if
we're separated by glass ♫
♫ You're like the breeze ♫
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
♫ Passed by the heavy shadows ♫
♫ And stopped by my side ♫
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
♫ But you're still beyond the reach ♫
♫ I just can feel ♫
[Sorry.]
[The number you dialled is not available.]
♫ Your heartbeat and breath ♫
♫ Your worries and happiness ♫
[Please try again later.]
♫ No words are needed ♫
♫ I want to see ♫
♫ All the possibilities ♫
♫ Make me believe ♫
♫ You're the only one ♫
♫ Yes I believe ♫
♫ All the promises that you gave ♫
♫ No matter how long the journey is ♫
♫ We'll be together ♫
♫ Be together ♫
♫ Yes I believe ♫
The simplest way to tell them apart is
to take a look at the edge of the leaf.
♫ Love is just like mails ♫
Feel it.
It's smooth.
♫ that come slow ♫
[Ilex leaf]
♫ The more impatient you are ♫
[has a zigzag pattern.]
♫ The slower it comes ♫
♫ The morning is gentle and warm ♫
♫ In the light ♫
♫ I gently kissed your eyes ♫
♫ You're like the breeze ♫
♫ Passed by the heavy shadows ♫
Xiao Lu.
Can you please go to the convenience store
♫ And stopped by my side ♫
and get me a pack of candy?
♫ But you're still beyond the reach ♫
It's given by that lady, is it?
♫ I just can feel ♫
In that case,
why don't you go and see her?
♫ Your heartbeat and breath ♫
Didn't you say that
♫ Your worries and happiness ♫
♫ No words are needed ♫
it's a wise decision?
♫ Do you know that
I want to see? ♫
Nian Qin.
♫ All the possibilities ♫
♫ Make me believe ♫
♫ You're the only one ♫
♫ Yes I believe ♫
So,
she naively brandished the four thorns
and said,
"Stop dilly-dallying."
"You're so annoying."
"Since you've decided
to leave this place,"
"you should leave now."
She didn't want
the Little Prince to see her crying.
She is such a proud flower.
Why did she do that?
That's very odd.
Yes.
She can't be weirder.
[The Little Prince]
He refused to answer my calls again.
Fine.
I'm not going to entertain you anymore.
When I become sober,
I will be my old strong self again.
Am I right?
My dear.
Can we go home after a drink?
I need to catch a train tomorrow.
What did you see?
Xu Qian is at the entrance.
Didn't you see her?
Your eyesight is terrible.
What are you doing?
I'm inviting people to come over.
[Me: Wei Hao, come over now!]
[Me: At the bar street]
What drinks would you like?
Give me the strongest drink.
Okay, orange juice it is. How about you?
What do you want?
It's been a while since we drank together.
I'll get you anything that is available.
I started the one-sided love.
I started it alone.
I made up the story alone.
I experienced happiness and sorrow alone.
Now, I'm going to end it alone.
You won't even sing me a song.
It's a long story.
Pretty lady, please do her a favour.
Please sing for her.
Just one song.
♫ If ears and promises ♫
♫ Hadn't met each other ♫
♫ If wishes and future ♫
♫ Hadn't come into contact ♫
♫ Perhaps ♫
♫ We could pretend that
nothing has happened ♫
♫ And move on easily ♫
♫ When forever is still not too far away ♫
♫ When a hug is still connected to love ♫
♫ Throw everything aside ♫
♫ And bet on the uncertain tomorrow ♫
♫ What's left are lies ♫
♫ That can't come full circle ♫
♫ Who is willing to take the fall ♫
♫ And give up on taking the initiative ♫
♫ Spending all the years ♫
♫ For an exchange of apology ♫
♫ Stubbornness and determination ♫
♫ Refuse to listen to people's advice ♫
♫ Watching the memories ♫
♫ Burn in flames ♫
♫ I'm willing to take the fall ♫
♫ But I can't escape from rising ♫
♫ The hurt along the way
can only be written, not erased ♫
♫ The blue past ♫
♫ Is now covered in snow ♫
♫ How can love melt? ♫
It's okay if you turn me down.
I mean it.
It's really okay.
After all,
you always say "No" to everything.
However, I can't find you anywhere.
I can't find you anywhere.
It's as if you've completely vanished
from the world.
Sometimes, I wonder
if that period
is merely my own imagination.
You're a nutcase.
You turned me into a nutcase too.
Just pretend that he's dead.
Finally you're awake.
I need to leave for the train now.
Clean up the place before you leave.
Where is Wu Yan?
She went out early in the morning.
Fan girls are always the craziest.
Did anyone else
come to visit you?
This one time,
Aunt's mum came here.
She brought lots of snacks.
You're such a foodie.
It seems that everyone loves you.
Ms Sang.
Why didn't you come together
with Mr Su?
He paid me a visit yesterday.
He also bought me
the same kind of candy you gave me.
Hold on.
Did you just say Mr Su paid you a visit?
Did he say anything?
He asked about how I've been.
He also asked about my studies.
He also reminded me
not to tell you that he came to see me.
Then, why did you tell me?
Just pretend that I didn't say anything.
Xiao Wei!
You're becoming more and more like him.
[Today, a listener wrote in]
[to complain that she's sick of]
[arguing with her group members
during group work.]
[It makes her tired.]
[In the beginning, she thought
that she's not articulate.]
[Soon, she realised]
[the toughest part]
[was not speaking out her mind]
[but no matter how hard she tried,]
[the other party
just wouldn't listen to her.]
[I guess]
[many people can relate to that.]
[That's why I love conducting broadcasts.]
[I have a selfish thought]
[and that is
whatever I said in the broadcast,]
[I bet there is at least one listener]
[who listens attentively to me.]
[Does such a listener exist?]
[All right.]
[I dedicate the following
therapeutic song to all of you.]
[I look forward
to receiving more letters from you.]
♫ The warm sunlight idly crawls into
the window ♫
♫ A faint and tipsy scent of
coffee aroma ♫
♫ Suddenly you're by my side again ♫
♫ Smiling as bright as the stars ♫
♫ Turning to the next page
of the storybook ♫
♫ You said the wind
will dry the tears shed by the clouds ♫
♫ I asked you how to console
the sighing wind then ♫
♫ You smiled without replying ♫
♫ Telling me not to be silly  ♫
♫ Oh clear skies outside the window ♫
♫ Oh yeah ♫
♫ I want to hug you from the back
and never let go of you ♫
[Broadcast: Literature and Art in Donghu]
♫ Why do beautiful things
always make people sad? ♫
♫ I'm afraid of you leaving ♫
♫ Hai yeah ♫
I've copied these documents
and sent them to you.
Mr Jiang.
Sang, come here.
Xu Qian is leaving.
These tasks will be passed to you.
After you're done,
just send a copy to me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't inform you earlier.
It's okay.
It's not the first time anyway.
Wu Yan.
I have to think for my own future.
Future?
Are you saying you won't have
a future in the radio station?
Isn't this your dream?
Open your eyes and look around.
We put in so much effort
to produce a news story.
But we get less listeners
than we would followers
on a public WeChat account.
We're going to graduate soon.
It's time to face reality.
Wu Yan, you need to be realistic.
Because of you,
I fell in love with broadcasting.
When you said that
you wanted to be an anchorwoman
to anchor a news program,
I thought that you're really cool.
To be honest,
I'm really envious of you.
As you know,
my parents have mapped out
a plan for me since I was young.
I thought it was fine.
That's because
I didn't have
any ambition back then.
However, now,
I want to be an anchorwoman
and it's no longer because of you.
It's for myself.
Why do I have a feeling that
I was betrayed by my own comrade?
Anyway, thank you.
I found my ambition because of you.
Wu Yan.
Enough, stop talking.
[I received a letter today.]
[Someone threatened me
to read her letter.]
[This lady claims that she needs to]
[answer an important question.]
[The first line of the letter is]
["Let me tell you why I like you."]
[She's so impulsive, isn't she?]
[No doubt
there's nothing special about you.]
-[Besides good looking...]
-[Besides good looking and talented,]
[you're completely different
from my dream guy.]
[However, whenever I think of you,]
[I can't help imagining]
[what I look for]
[in a guy.]
[You're always gentle to children]
[but you're very fierce to me.]
[You never fail]
[to perceive the feelings that
no one else could perceive.]
[You deliberately ignored my feelings]
[but you're actually
very gentle and sensitive.]
[However, when you're in pain,]
[you just silently put up with it.]
[I think because of that]
[you think that]
[I would have the same tolerance]
[when you left me.]
[Just because
I couldn't answer the question,]
[you just disappeared suddenly.]
[You're just a jerk!]
[I still can't answer the question]
[but I want you to scold me
when you hear this.]
[Searching contacts.]
[All contacts.]
[Sang Wu Yan.]
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
Hello.
Say something.
Sang Wu Yan, say something!
How do you know it's me?
Where do you live?
You don't have to come.
I just want to talk.
Give me your address. Now.
[Su Nian Qin]
Sang Wu Yan!
Open the door, Sang Wu Yan!
Sang Wu Yan! Wake up!
Wake up! Sang Wu Yan!
Sang Wu Yan!
Open the door, Sang Wu Yan!
I'm coming.
Sang Wu Yan!