[English subtitles are available]
We're finally back!
Father.
I'm sorry.
I acted rashly
and almost got Yi killed.
I'll accept any punishment.
Father,
If Da hadn't deployed the troops in time,
the Northland's army wouldn't have retreated.
Rise.
Neither of you
let me down.
Bao didn't, either.
You've been helping me
review the memorials.
Thank you for saying this, father.
It's my pleasure
to help you share the responsibility.
I'm not a sentimental person.
I'll try not to upset you.
Father,
you may not know this.
We solved the case
of the missing provisions
and saved our soldiers,
thanks to Xiu's help
from within the East City.
Xiu, you've finally behaved like a prince,
but you still have a long way to go
and work hard.
Not a big deal.
Since the King of Northland
has realized
what princes of the East City can do,
I guess he dares not start any war
in the next ten years.
You should be awarded.
Thank you, father.
The King of East City,
let's see how many good days you've left!
The person behind is watching you.
I'll see how you'll react
when you lose your son.
What did you say?
I mean...
I'll wait till I have my own son!
The King of East City has sons.
I can have many sons as well!
Honey,
what are you waiting for then?
Shall we?
Hua Yan?
Hua Yan.
Hua Yan!
Dismissed.
His Majesty
gave his sword to Prince Da.
Obviously, His Majesty thinks highly of him.
But the jade crown given to Prince Yi
can only be worn by the crowned prince.
Isn't it
obvious?
In my opinion,
the crowned prince
should be Prince Yi.
I agree.
I totally agree.
Congratulations, Si Yan.
It's so beautiful.
I'm really jealous.
Look!
It really suits you.
No more showing off.
I will soon catch up with you.
Let's wait and see.
Here is the order from the First Lady.
The Meditation Chamber
is looking for a makeup maid.
I'll let Si Yan take the job for now.
Why me?
You want me to be Tong Rui's maid?
That's impossible!
No way!
The Beekeeping Site is quite busy today.
They're in short of hands.
Why not...
Si Yan...
Well, it's not a hard no.
Fine.
Serving people
is exactly my strength.
You're here.
Miss Min,
how can I help you?
We're fine for now.
By the way,
father recently sent several pigs
from the Northland.
They didn't eat much these days.
I wonder if you can help me find
delicious pig feed.
This is what you're good at, right?
You...
you're messing with me on purpose!
Didn't we agree that
we never disturb each other
and play our game separately?
I've told you that
I just wanted a makeup maid.
Although your makeup skills
are just average,
you're at least better them.
My god, I almost believed you.
You want me to be your makeup maid?
Just say it out loud
if you think I've improved.
Why hide it?
Glasses.
Don't call me Glasses!
Didn't you ask me to feed pigs first?
Tell me,
what are you planning now?
What's your final task?
Isn't it boring if I just tell you?
Why not
have a guess?
It's getting late.
Go to Prince Yi's palace
and invite him to come here tomorrow.
What do you want?
You're my maid now.
Just follow my order.
Why bother to ask?
You're apparently ordering me about
for personal reasons.
I'm following the story setting.
Now, go!
It has been the third time already.
Indeed.
Look at this.
What General Min sent here
is clearly the dowry.
Dowry?
Whose dowry?
Can Tong Rui be sure that
she will marry Qi Yi?
It hasn't been decided.
He's speaking nonsense.
Don't worry about it.
His Highness won the battle
and was rewarded with the jade crown.
Of course, people want to flatter him.
It will be too late
after he becomes the crowned prince.
He went to the Patrol Squadron.
Do you want to see him?
Not me.
Our wealthy Miss Min wants to see him.
She asked Qi Yi to meet her
in the Meditation Chamber tomorrow.
I just don't understand it.
They live near each other.
Why let me send the message?
Can't she just knock on the wall?
His Highness is in trouble again.
Your Highness.
Where are Commandant Zuo and Minister Liu?
Didn't they say
they want to compete with me while I'm back?
They're ungrateful.
They all went to Prince Yi's palace.
I also heard that...
What?
General Min also went there himself
and brought gifts for Prince Yi.
Your Highness,
does it mean that
we no longer have a chance?
Xiu,
Manager Ruan was caught.
Let's go! Make good use of your strength
and interrogate him.
I asked you to load the provisions.
There's no time for this nonsense!
Move!
I...
I know nothing.
I see.
So this time
we won't ask you anything.
We'll wait.
Wait for what?
You're bluffing.
If you do know something,
you won't be wasting your time here.
You're right.
I'm just a servant.
Observing other's speech and behavior
is just a basic skill.
Such a good servant!
Let's see if your master
deserves your loyalty.
Long!
Dad!
Grandpa, grandma,
and mom all died!
What did you say?
Don't cry!
They were killed by the man in black.
It was too late
when I arrived.
He promised not to hurt my family!
Can you tell me now?
Ten years ago,
I was just an assistant in the grain depot.
They found me
and promised me that
I could be the next manager
if I did what they asked.
We were having a locust attack at that time.
Victims were everywhere.
I worked in the provisions depot
at that time.
Our manager was a sympathetic man,
a great leader.
So I suggested that
we give victims
expired army provisions.
He asked me to write a report
and sent to the Court for approval.
However,
I changed the report
and accused him of taking army provisions
to line his pocket.
That's why many soldiers died
in the battle against the Northland
and we were defeated.
Is the previous manager you mentioned
Lin Xu, or Manager Lin,
who was later put to death?
Yes.
Si Yan,
the seventh daughter
of Manager Lin of Army Depot.
Your father was put to death
for embezzlement of provisions.
You are a criminal's daughter
and you work as a maid in the East Mansion.
What on earth do you want?
They really made you the next manager.
What happened next?
At first,
I was on tenterhooks,
but they never contacted me again.
When did you start to
transfer army provisions to the Northland?
Around...
three years ago.
They contacted me
once in a while.
Then,
the provisions were secretly transferred
to the Northland
through foreign merchants' caravans.
There was nothing left
in the army depot.
I couldn't think of any solution
but let the boats overturn,
hoping that no one would find out.
How do you get in touch?
They sent a spy to reach me.
Then,
we would meet at the Treasure Store
on the edge city.
Treasure Store?
Who's there?
It's me.
What do you want me to do?
Are you suspecting that
they are part of a team?
Director Li was smuggling mica crystals.
Look at the ledgers Si Yan found.
These mica crystals
were sent to Treasure Store
in exchange for metals and jades.
It is worth
several grand every month.
These amounts of money
somehow ended up
being in the Treasure Store again.
So the Treasure Store
is an underground bank.
I sent people
to investigate it a long time ago.
All these years,
the Treasure Store is the only place
that does business with foreign merchants
in the name of
developing trade with the Northland.
So the army provisions
were also transferred
through the Treasure Store.
You once mentioned that
Manager Xue from the Treasure Store
used to serve under General Min.
I suspect that
the Treasure Store
is Min's secret outpost here.
Yi,
do you mean that
General Min is involved with all of these?
Ten years ago,
when our army was trapped in Northland
due to short of provisions,
the Min family's army arrived
and defeated the enemy.
Father bestowed him
the title of Zhenyuan.
After that, the Northland attacked us
once in a while.
General Min happened to
win all the battles.
Normally speaking,
the Northland would have
took our people's money and food
and had conflicts all the time
since they never won once.
However, they didn't do anything.
From what General Min's report said,
we almost lost nothing.
It seemed that
the two of us were just acting.
It's quite possible that
General Min gave
the Northland money and food
to make sure that nobody could replace him.
That's shameless.
He has been fighting for years!
All these years,
father has a good reason
to show his respect
and has feared for him.
That's why we need reliable evidence.
Ask Yun Li to keep an eye on the store.
Go visit the Meditation Chamber these days.
Don't worry about Si Yan getting jealous.
If Min Tongrui knows
what General Min did,
then she is a threat to us
if she stays in the East Mansion.
Your Highness,
this is the special hair growth cream
from the west.
Have a try.
This is good for your health.
Here you are.
I can't even have it with hawthorn cake.
I prefer this.
Your Highness,
you lost five more hairs
this morning.
Please take the medicine.
I'm busy.
You don't know what I saw.
The King's hair
dropped like this.
After he took off the wig,
he actually had no single hair left.
It's so scary.
Does the whole family have hair issues?
The new hair growth recipe
made by the Institute of Medicine
is too smelly.
No one likes it.
Doctors have no solution
and ask if others can come up with
some medicine pairings.
Of course,
the Makeup Service has to show our support.
We have never made
anything like this before.
I'd like to give it a try
on one condition.
If I win,
please transfer me back to the Service.
If you can solve this problem,
I will speak for you
in front of the First Lady.
Deal!
What exactly do we need to make?
Si Yan,
you don't even know what's going on.
How can you just take on the work?
It's still about making makeup products.
Just tell me,
is it hairline powder
or a healthy hair comb?
Neither.
It's...
delicious medicine parings.
Why are you here?
Are you worried about me?
You even bring me gifts.
Yi,
you're here.
Si Yan,
make some tea.
These are...
His Highness was busy with
Patrol Squadron's work
and didn't have time to visit Miss Min.
That's why we bring gifts here.
Fine.
I'll make some tea,
Miss Min.
Yi,
shall we go inside and play chess?
I...
I need to ask you a favor.
If Min Tongrui knows
what General Min did,
then she is a threat to us
if she stays in the East Mansion.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
Prince Yi really cares about Miss Min.
He brought so many gifts
for everyone here.
That's how wealthy people
treat their true love.
Miss Min is lucky.
Those two
are like a dragon and a phoenix.
They will be a happy couple.
Dragon and phoenix?
They're two-timing
cheaters!
I think they're a perfect match.
You only have food in your mind!
I keep meeting you in the kitchen
since you're able to touch the food!
He's so handsome!
So tall!
His eyes are so bright!
You are already
as popular as those princes.
I can't imagine how many girls here
have fallen in love with you?
Are you one of them?
I need to leave.
No need to look there.
Si Yan is not here.
How's it going with General Min?
Although the Northland retreated,
we are not sure
if they will come back again.
I'm worried that General Min
might let his guard down
and give our enemy a chance to attack us.
Don't worry.
Father has been
guarding the border for years
and he never leaves the Northland.
The King of Northland fears him.
This time,
father took the Redbud Pass back
without losing any soldiers.
The Northland will get nothing good
if they ever start the war again.
If they have enough food and money supply,
why would they be afraid of losing?
After all,
the Redbud Pass
is not the only thing that protects them.
You mean...
there are other people
who can benefit from the war.
Checkmate.
So you already had a suspect.
I don't know what to say
to dispel your doubt,
but my father
thought highly of a person.
Who?
Qi Teng.
Father respected him
and felt sorry for his death.
But Father knew that
Qi Teng would die on the battlefield.
Enough.
Father used to tell me that,
as a soldier who guarded the border,
no matter what position he was at,
he should die on the battlefield
to defend every inch of our territory.
You should have a face-to-face talk
with someone who said things like this,
or you may wrong an innocent person
and cause unnecessary trouble.
Don't let the real criminal
get away with it.
Miss Min, you're smart.
I've learned my lesson.
Father will show up at our wedding.
Yi, you put this piece
at the wrong place,
as if you're bringing about
your own destruction.
Miss Min, you have excellent skills.
I lost.
It's late today.
I'll leave for now.
You're not waiting for Si Yan?
You brought so many gifts
to the Meditation Chamber.
Even the maids
working in the Meditation Chamber
can have their portions.
You're so generous.
I should thank you on behalf of them.
Or...
should I thank Si Yan?
Chestnut cakes from the south,
pomegranate flower bonsai,
and a full set of
limited edition lipsticks.
This one is even more amazing.
Golden and silver silk thread from Persia.
I have a question for you, Yi.
Do you want me
to make you a jumper with this?
You want to act friendly.
I totally understand it.
However,
at least show me your efforts next time.
I know you don't have feelings for me,
but please have some boundaries
and let me do what I should do.
I only want a title.
I dare not
ask for anything else.
Miss Min, I'm sorry.
I can promise you anything,
except for
our engagement.
Blockheaded.
Giving me gifts in such a way!
Well done!
Tell me,
what color jumper do you like?
I can make one for you.
I...
I need to go to the Patrol Squadron.
Okay.
I won't keep you any longer.
Be quick.
I'll see you
at the usual spot tonight.
Yi,
why are you resting in my place?
What?
Is there something in your mind?
Manager Lin
is Si Yan's father.
What?
Did she know what happened before?
Are you going to tell her?
I failed to stop Manager Lin
from being killed years ago.
Her family was ruined by me.
How dare a small manager
steal all the provisions from the depot?
Father,
as far as I know,
Maolin is experiencing
severe locust attacks.
Whether Manager Lin
used food to save people
or line his pockets
needs further investigation.
What?
Did anyone make you unhappy?
Brother was besieged by our enemies.
We lost many soldiers
due to the lack of food.
Please don't let these corrupt officials
easily get away with this.
What?
Rise.
If we don't kill
people like Manager Lin,
we won't be able to quell people's anger!
Father.
Take this.
Now
how could I face her?
You didn't know
that her father was framed.
I'm not sure
if I have the right to say this,
but it has been many years
since this happened.
Why mention it to her?
If you tell her the truth,
maybe she will be hurt again.
You two might have more understanding.
How do you get along?
If she is angry with you because of this,
you will end up hurting yourself.
Think more about it.
They're all spoiled.
Does the medicine taste this bad?
Just hold the nose and take it.
You're in the kitchen again.
Such good timing.
Give me some ideas.
Is there anything
I can cook
to make those virtual princes happy?
Let me think.
Shouldn't you add something sweet
to the medicine?
Well...
my mom would give me candy
when I was little.
Sweet and chewy candy.
description
makes me want to have a try.
Good idea!
I can make that.
It will blow their minds.
Jack,
you used to be a cook.
Help me, please.
But I'm an imperial bodyguard.
I'm not allowed to leave.
I see you every day.
Can you just do me a favor?
We need some fruits.
Let's go!
Hurry!
Jack,
I won't try to figure out
whether you are Xiao Li or Jack.
We are the same
as we were before.
No.
It feels more real than before.
I can touch you now.
Actually,
you've always been by my side, right?
I didn't realize this earlier.
I didn't even say
thank you to you.
Don't leave me in the dark.
I can't see anything,
but I can give up everything
for you.
Si Yan,
I'm sorry.
I can't see anything.
Xiao Li, it's alright.
Don't be afraid. It all passed.
Si Yan.
Wake up.
Xiao Li, wake up.
Don't be afraid.
Si Yan.
Can you stay with me?
I need to do something.
I have to leave now.
Prince Da, what brings you here?
Your Highness!
You can't go inside!
Out of my way!
Move!
Leave us alone.
Yes.
Your Highness broke into
my Meditation Chamber
under everyone's eyes.
Don't you think it's inappropriate?
You seem to be quite calm.
You came back days ago,
but you never visited me once.
Instead, you and Yi
got well along with each other
and had a lot of fun.
Tell me,
who am I to you?
Your Highness.
I've made it clear
with you.
I never forgot
what happened between us
while I was still Miss Tong.
But I'm Miss Min now.
I have no choice
but to follow
my destiny.
Your Highness.
Please behave yourself.
Tong Rui,
I'm begging you.
Please?
Your Highness,
do we have the ability
to make decisions for ourselves?
Fine.
Miss Min,
the destiny you're talking about
is not decided yet.
No one knows
who will be the winner.
Your Highness,
what are you going to do?
What happened?
He never arrives late.
You're here!
What happened?
Are you drunk?
Si Yan,
I have something to tell you.
Why are you being weird?
We know each other so well.
You're drunk.
I'll get you home first.
In the end,
we can't force ourselves to be together.
I think we should end our relationship.
We didn't force it.
If we are forced to be together,
how can we make it till today?
What happened?
Is there anything getting in our way?
I don't want to break up with you.
It's too late, Si Yan.
We shouldn't have met
at the beginning.
I don't care
what happened.
Please don't push me away.
You don't know anything.
Many years ago,
Manager Lin,
who was in charge of the provisions,
was framed to death
because I didn't stop them from killing him.
That's why
the system
asked me to kill Qi Yi.
No truth should be kept as secret.
No good man should be wronged.
Si Yan,
you can blame me,
hate me,
or even kill me.
I won't complain.
But I'm afraid.
I don't know
how I should face you.
I can't even imagine
our future.
How can I force you to stay with me?
Thank you for being honest with me
and telling me
the deepest secret in your heart.
I've never seen a man
who can be as honest as you.
Qi Yi,
thank you for your courage.
Thank you for loving me.
I really don't blame you.
I mean it.
I believe that
you didn't know
my father was framed at that time.
That's why you didn't save him.
I know it's an accident.
I don't blame you.
I mean it.
I'll make sure
what you asked will be done.
Where are you from?
It's midnight.
Why are you hanging around?
My lord,
I just joined the Institute of Medicine.
I lost my way.
Please forgive me.
I'll leave now.
Jack didn't make the green one.
I'll do it then.
Where did you go?
Check this out.
I made this green gummy bear.
What do you think?
Green?
Didn't I just make it?
It's fine.
Please forget about
what I said before.
What did you say?
If you want to help me, then be quick.
It's almost dawn.
We'll be running out of time.
Si Yan,
did you finish the medicine paring?
The princes are waiting.
Someone!
Bring the medicine.
Wait.
This one is for Prince Yi.
One reason
you're here today is to
have some tea and chat with me.
Second,
it's time for the Institute of Medicine
to reveal the best dessert.
Mrs. Huang,
bring all the desserts here.
Let the princes have a try
and see if they go with medicine.
The person
whose desserts have been eaten most
will be the winner.
Royal Kitchen.
Dragon beard candy.
Garment Service.
Orange Cake.
Protocol Department.
Red preserves.
Makeup Service.
Spon...gummy bear?
Spongy.
Spongy gummy bear.
Si Yan
treats these princes like little kids.
This is so delicate.
Si Yan,
what's the flavor?
As for the flavor...
You have to
find out yourself.
I won't let you down.
The name is strange.
How can it taste good?
Da,
Si Yan made this herself.
Since you made this,
I'll save it for the last.
Where are you from?
It's midnight.
Why are you hanging around?
I'll leave now.
Check this out.
I made the green gummy bear.
Green?
Didn't I just make it?
What are you doing!
My mistake.
It's my fault.
I accidentally dropped them.
There are a few left.
I'll go get them.
It's fine.
No bother.
You can have mine.
Yi,
please ask Si Yan
to make more of them for us.
Since you had the candy,
finish the medicine then.
Maybe the gummy bear isn't the only poison.
The medicine could be poisonous as well!
Your Highness,
the medicine is cold.
It is bitter.
I'll get you a new one.
You are such a rash man.
You not only hit Prince Yi
but also caused trouble.
Why didn't you get others a new one?
Or is something wrong with the medicine?
What are you doing?
Put it down.
There is nothing wrong with the medicine.
I'll prepare new medicine for all princes.
Jack.
Jack,
are you alright?
Of course,
I'm alright.
They're waiting for you.
Go back.
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Go.
Si Yi.
I won't let anything happen to Qi Yi
and get you involved.
Jack,
this transparent one is for you.
Your Highness.
You are such a professional.
this UNIFON Purifying Clay Face Mask
gives you a deep cleanse
and purifies your skin.
It's just for the royal family's use
and it's a limited edition.
Take all of these
and send them to my palace.
Yes!