Your Highness
Do you think this will make me feel relieved
Events
Your Highness, this turtle cream may be a little fishy
Do you want to use something else
I'm very angry now
Don't you know I'm irritated
Take away
Yes
Add honey and sweet-scented osmanthus
Go quickly
I'm going now
What's the matter? You're not feeling well
It's just a medicine for a woman to recuperate her body
Take it down
It's weird
How come Miaoxian is also drinking medicine. You are also drinking medicine
And you didn't hire a doctor
How
You wrote the prescription
I haven't seen anyone around you
The screen is too young
Mother is afraid that she can't afford it
So I specially chose
Four clever palace maidservants sent it
Empress Empress
This morning, the East Palace sent all the people back
It means Crown Princess
Mother, this is the son's own meaning
Let's all go down
Yes
It doesn't matter if you don't like it
I'll send four more people tomorrow
Mother Queen
I don't mean to be harsh on you
If you are an ordinary person,
I will never interfere indiscriminately
But are you
You are the Prince of the East Palace
One country Chu Jun
If there are no children
Who will bear the heavy responsibility of Jiangshan in the future
The mother's son is still young
There will be children sooner or later
Why are you in such a hurry
I can't bear
I don't bother to embarrass my daughter-in-law
But the whole world is waiting and watching
Looking forward to the birth of Daming's future heir
How about this
Those concubines in the East Palace
If you don't like it
Then choose again
Choose until you are satisfied
Mother, they are all very good
There is nothing dissatisfied with my son
They are all good
But none of them you like
Mother, if you send someone over again
I will send it back as I am
Don't bother about this matter
My son retires
Zhan Ji
This is also your unshirkable responsibility
You come back here
Master
The child
How could he not understand
If I don't embarrass them today,
They will become sinners through the ages
As long as there are children,
They can no longer be blamed by the world
In order to really have a way to live
Empress's painstaking efforts
Your Highness has not yet realized
So what should we do now
Since he doesn't like all the people who send it,
Then pick one he likes
What are you doing now
Meng Shang Shi
His Royal Highness King Wei coughs late at night
I read that it was said in dietotherapy herbal medicine
Make 50 holes with one frozen pear
Fill with pepper
Then wrap the noodles in hot ash and simmer them until cooked
Remove pepper after cooling and eat it
Can relieve cough
So I want to give it a try
Remember when I told you
What is cooking
The so-called cooking
Is to fully consider the needs of diners
Try to preserve the original taste and essence of ingredients
And then make delicious food
Since I choose to specialize in medicated diet,
Remove from paying attention to the physique of the eater
Choosing ingredients is particularly important
Let's talk about it
How did you choose the medicine pear
It is recorded in this sketch
Only the milk pears in Xuancheng
There are also pears in Jingzhou County and Beidu
It is suitable for medicine
But after a couple of trials
I found the perfume pears that were paid tribute this year
It also has excellent results
So this time it was taken out as medicine
It is good to know how to identify pharmacopoeia records
But what
The eaters are children
Pepper tastes too heavy
He won't like it
Why don't you switch to ghee and honey
And
Pear peel clears heart fire, promotes salivation and quenches thirst
It is a medicinal material in itself
Wouldn't the medicine be greatly reduced if the pear skin was removed
You said earlier that you were not good at medicated diet
I almost believed it
As a kitchen
Always be aware of the characteristics of ingredients in the world
Know something
Understand
Xie Mengshang's index finger point
Zi Jin Zi Jin
Meng Shang Shi
Herald of Kunning Palace
Present the midnight snack fruit box with the food bureau
All that's left is these ripe taros
Betel nut taro is not the only good taro in China
The most delicate piedmont taro with taro meat
It is the best ingredient to make taro paste
What about sliced steamed meat
It has to be Fenghua Taro
This little taro
Make sweet-scented osmanthus sweet-scented taro seedlings and scallion oil taro
Isn't it just right
What about this one
Lai Zi Jin
Come and help me
Yes
Meng Shangshi, please stay
Go ahead
Yes
Empress doesn't often eat at night
Meng Shangshi only took cooked taro slices and nuts
Slightly fry almonds in sauce
Serve with parsley Bijian soup
It can strengthen spleen and stomach, tranquilize nerves and help sleep
Please treat the empress to dinner
Remember our stakes
Silly girl, why bother you
Who can fight the royal family
If this stalemate continues,
Who can save you in the world
Crown Princess
Crown princess calms her anger
Wait for me to persuade slowly
She'll change her mind
The world is born as if it were in a cage
If you want to return to nature,
Unless it turns into a piece of loess
You haven't said a word for half a year
Facing this old window all day long
Do you really think
Can I be detached from this world
People who can replace you are like crucian carp crossing the river
It's just that I don't allow resistance
I don't allow anyone to say no to me
Crown Princess
Ali grew up with my own eyes
It's a courtesy
A good girl who knows the rules
Please look at my thin noodles
Give her another chance
Silly child
Refuse to enter the palace
There are only two roads left
Become a monk or die
You are so young
Do you really have to hinge your hair
Have you been with the ancient Buddha with green lanterns all your life
The Crown Princess forced me into the palace
You are not afraid of bringing disaster
Name has been determined
I advise you not to be wishful thinking
Be your great grandwife honestly
But I'm not reconciled
Do you dare to gamble
When you know the prosperity of this supreme and expensive place,
I've seen my son again
All unwillingness will vanish
At that time
I'm waiting for you to beg me
Give you this grace
You have been in the palace for some time
Do you know what is the supreme place in the world
Back to the empress's words
The so-called royal family
Prosperity, splendor and supreme power
There is no one like me in the world
Have you ever seen the prince
His Royal Highness the Prince is wise and wise
Smart decision
There is also a benevolence of loving the people and caring for the people
I will make a decree tomorrow
Make you a prince concubine
The handmaiden thanks the empress for her kindness
Please take back your life
What are you talking about
Handmaiden's blessings are shallow
Shame and dare not accept it
Seeing Imperial Power and Not Admire Imperial Power
Know splendor and don't envy splendor
You are at ease
But between you and him
There is a predestined fate
Are you willing to cut it off together
Handmaiden
When I first entered the palace
Always have grievances in my heart
Can get along with your highness day and night
A cavity of ice and snow is also melted because of him
Empress
Handmaiden sincerely admires your highness
But affection and freedom must finally make a choice
Handmaiden is unwilling to be a princess
Please help the empress
Do you know what you're saying
The empress promised the handmaiden that she would let me go
How dare you speak so presumptuously in front of me
I am the ruler of this harem
As long as I don't let you go
You have to be deferential in this harem
Be your prince's wife
Spread children for the royal family
Handmaiden is naive and foolish
Unknown doctrine
Even more unworthy to serve your highness
How dare you say such a thing so boldly
No matter how hard your bones are
A knife and axe that is hard but sharp
Your will is firm again
Can't shake the supreme imperial power
The reason why you can talk to me like this
Is nothing more than taking advantage of my tolerance and compassion
When you run out of my last patience
Your brother, you are the nine families of Sun Shi
It will overturn in an instant
The world says
Empress is gentle and lenient
But they are all wrong about you
Your will is far more determined than any man
The decision is far from comparable to human beings
But
What the rest of the heart wants
Die nine times without regret
Handmaiden retires
Empress, this maid is so rude
You shouldn't forgive her any more
Sure enough, it is soft, waxy, sweet, crisp and delicious
When I was in trouble,
She can stand by and watch
But she put aside the past and ran for me
Mother is right
She's a good kid
Empress
I just want to see
Does anyone really dare to disobey the imperial power in this world
Even
Resist the arrangement of fate
Wait for me here
Elder sister invited each other late at night
What's so important
What is this
Subcharacter
Machamp Chaos I don't need it
If elder sister asked me to come here for this matter,
Then I'll go back first
The Crown Princess accepted it
I said I don't need
Elder sister
In fact, it doesn't matter whether you have children or not
My sister sincerely prayed to heaven
May you have peace and joy all your life
This wish is enough
Elder sister
Why do you keep saying such strange things tonight
Purple Azolla
Why are you stunned?
Why are you distracted
Nothing
It's really okay
But this tofu practices knife skills
I don't know how long I have to practice
What
Last time I saw Fang Dianshan making Vince tofu
Later, I heard that at the tofu banquet,
There are 158 tofu dishes
She was possessed
Facing that piece of tofu every day
I don't know what I'm doing
Come with me
Your Highness
Although your majesty has spared the golden beads of toes
Buying tea lessons in Shaanxi and Sichuan
However, there are still many places to buy and collect
Wasting people and money
For example, Dan lacquer azurite paid tribute every year
Regardless of whether it is produced locally
Collect it all
Forcing people to sell their property
Buy Dan lacquer azurite at a high price
To complete the apportionment of the government
Profiteers take the opportunity to drive up
As a result, prices have soared dozens of times
The people went bankrupt
Why did you stop me from writing
I don't think you are scolding profiteers
Are you scolding
Eunuchs sent by my father to buy everywhere
Do you know that
Those who my father sent
Most of them are people he values
Some are even confidants who have served for many years
Do you think Father believes in you or them
I can't let someone like you
Be victimized by slanderers
I am now a censor
It is the responsibility of supervising the departments to report illegal activities
You can't sit back and watch eunuchs become misfortunes
It's a mess for me.
Your Highness, you should also be alert to the villains around you
Do not be fooled by them
Your Highness
Reward you
His Royal Highness
Good tea
Good tea. Good tea. Thank you, Your Highness
Gentle water moistens everything
Violent water destroys fields and hurts people
So people fix water trucks
Building dams to prevent floods in Xingyuan
Water is so
So do people
Eunuchs fought with Grandpa Huang for many years
There are indeed many talents around me
Sure enough, it is one
Honest and brave young talents
What
Go
This way this way
Come back
Why are you here
I came to see your sweetheart
Zheng Sanbao fought bravely and fought several times to the West
I also lost my ha and went to work as a slave for many times
Zhaofu local ethnic groups
Of course
There are also private news from the imperial court
Huang Yan who is plotting evil
Eunuch and Water
Even it is no different from officials
There is no distinction between good and evil
It just depends on how to use it
Your Highness is wrong
The sword is in the hand of the chivalrous man
You can be chivalrous
Fall into the hands of bandits and bandits
It is a weapon to kill people
Da Ming Guo Zuo concerns all people
Today, the merciful prince is wise
Can hold this sharp blade firmly
But who can guarantee that
From generation to generation, there are saints and lords in Daming
Bold
Out
Yes
You
Impeach Royal Guards again
Impeach the eunuchs again
How many time have I told you
What are the words in my heart
Just talk to me in private
You swear so openly
Be careful that someone behind you makes a cold arrow
Now that your highness knows it's a villain
Why do you stay around?
When I was young,
Yuan Qi waited on me
I accidentally fell off my horse once
He jumped at the guard
He was seriously injured and lay down for a year
Shaoyuan
Even if it is a villain of humble origin,
It is also flesh and blood
I'll prepare the meal
Isn't this too fragrant
Zi Jin
You said this stinky tofu
It smells so bad
Why does it taste so delicious
Fragrant bar
Zi Jin
The first piece is mine
You are not allowed to rob mine
My my mine
My mine my mine
Give me a bite, too
Eat slowly and be careful of scalding
Zi Jin
Run so fast just now
Ask you and you ignore me
What can I do now
I
Have a quick taste
Meng Shang's food is coming
This year's Shangyuan Festival
Long live Aoshan lamp should be set up in the palace
Pray for peace in the world
Your Majesty will also reward officials with banquets
You all have to cheer up
Deal with it well
Yes
Meng Shang Shi
If I remember correctly
The competition between us
It hasn't been decided yet, has it
Hu Shang Shi
It has come to this point
Aren't you willing to stop
No matter what, I am still eating
On Grade
Not yet
You are presumptuous in front of me
Is this still necessary now
Meng Shang Shi
You are already the master of the food bureau
But the competition is a competition after all
There is no tie between the winner and the loser
How to convince people
This third game
Are you willing to fight
What is a bet
On the Yuan Festival, a banquet was given to officials
Let's try this
If I win by luck
Meng Shangshi should be in front of the world
Admit yourself that you are inferior to others
If I lose
I asked myself to leave the palace
Never step into the Forbidden City again
How
As you wish
If she hadn't been
Crown Princess's own sister
Will she be allowed to linger for so long
Now bring disgrace to oneself
Meng Shangshi hasn't taken the opportunity yet
Get her out of the palace
Are you right, Zihao
Don't talk about it
Can you promise me two things
Two pieces