[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 37]
Your Majesty,
Baili Kuanren, the leader of Four Season Clan
has been sent to the dungeon.
Well done, Youjue.
You've done such a great job.
How shall I reward you?
I dare not ask for any reward.
Your Majesty,
I made a wrong decision back then
and saved Baili Kuanren.
Luoyang was brought into such chaos
because of me.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Everyone knows that
you are the big hero
that destroyed the Clan.
If I punish you now,
those fools
will criticize me for being incompetent.
I am sorry, Your Majesty.
Alright.
Although you made a mistake,
you did earn merit for Luoyang this time.
I'll deduct your salary for a year
as punishment.
Thank you for sparing my life, Your Majesty.
Let me ask you.
Have you found the grain
stolen from Hanjia Granary?
We've found all of it
and sent it to civilians
and shops.
Our people can now buy grain
at the market again.
I would like to invite Your Majesty
to hold an opening ceremony for the granaries
on an auspicious day to boost morale.
Set it up.
As soon as possible.
Your Majesty, our country is blessed by your grace
and will be forever prosperous.
Did you check everywhere?
Yeah.
You can't find them?
No.
Did you find them?
It's...
Sir!
-Sir!
We've checked everywhere.
All the records
on the attack of the King of East River are gone.
I don't know
who took them.
What about records
of the explosion of Hanjia Granary?
Many people saw the explosion.
There should be many testimonies.
Not really.
We asked many people,
but they said they didn't know anything.
Was our Services penetrated by yet another mole?
Sir Wu.
Agent Gao, you came.
Have a seat.
The tea was harvested in autumn in Huzhou.
Southerners like to use boiling water
to brew tea leaves,
so it tastes different from boiling tea directly.
Have a try.
The tea set is not from Qianmu Chamber.
Good eye!
I brought the tea set myself.
I brought them all with me
since I'll be staying here in the near future.
I asked you to see me today
because I know that
there have been bad feelings between us.
However, we're all serving the Court now,
so, I want to solve the problems between us.
I don't understand.
You should, though.
I know all about
you and Siyue.
However, you're now the Halberdier
of the Intelligence Services.
You should know the rule here.
One shall forfeit the right to love.
What should Siyue do in the future?
I am here today to tell you
that rules are made
to be broken.
The rules Lord Chu made
are unnecessary.
He would never
make the Services more powerful.
You should never
hurt Siyue's heart.
There's one more thing.
This time,
the two Services
found the grain stolen from Hanjia Granary.
You should send it to the Unwelcome Well
this afternoon.
The famine is now solved.
Her Majesty is relieved.
She will reward the two Services for sure.
Besides, Her Majesty has issued an order
that she'll visit the south market shortly
to hold an opening ceremony
for the granaries to boost morale.
Her Majesty will be there in person?
Yes.
So, we can't allow anything to go wrong
with the grain we've found.
I want to ask you to
safeguard the grain.
Can you do it?
I work for the Intelligence Services.
I'll do my best.
You can use this token to dispatch interior guards.
[Keep order for Her Majesty]
Gao Bingzhu,
do not
let me down.
[Keep order for Her Majesty]
[Local Office of the Unwelcome Well]
Come, everyone!
Thank you!
Her Majesty sent us grain.
She sent us grain!
Thank you, Your Majesty!
Thank you!
Finally, we've got rice!
Finally!
Thank you, sir!
We're safe now!
Take it!
This is yours, take it!
We've finally got grain!
Okay, next!
Next!
Thank you, sir!
Thank you!
Thank you, Agent Gao!
We're utterly grateful to you.
Here.
Great!
Is there more?
Come on!
Thank you!
Come over here!
Come!
Thank you, Your Majesty!
-Her Majesty sent us grain.
-Thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir!
You and Madam Wu are good people.
You brought grain back in no time.
The folks in the Well
are saved!
What are you upset about?
I just find the whole thing quite strange.
Don't you think
it all went too well?
You...
You always overthink things.
Look!
Luoyang is bathed in peace now.
People have got grain now.
It's wonderful!
I didn't expect that
the man behind Four Season Clan
is Baili Hongyi's brother.
He doesn't value human life at all
and would do anything to achieve his goals.
If his plan had worked,
countless people
in Luoyang would've lost their lives.
Luckily,
you and Siyue's brother
were more capable than
Hongyi's brother.
Think about it! You got him
with no casualties.
You did great!
Cheer up a bit, will you?
I just think that
we got him too effortlessly.
Bingzhu!
Mr. Unsightly!
Thanks to you,
the Unwelcome Well is saved!
It's my pleasure.
We've run out of
all the grain we stocked.
We were too hungry
to have the energy to talk.
We could only
drink water to feel full.
We adults could make do,
but the kids...
If we kept living like this,
our stomachs
would explode.
The grain you sent couldn't have been more timely!
Slow down.
Careful.
Here.
Thank you!
Okay.
[Unwelcome Well]
This is yours.
Thank you!
There's enough for everyone.
Careful.
Thank you!
Don't spill.
Bingzhu,
on behalf of the folks in the Well...
Mr. Unsightly!
Come on.
Get him up.
Mr. Unsightly,
I made you some porridge.
I'll bring you some.
What about them?
Rest assured!
They're all cooking.
Bingzhu!
What?
See for yourself.
Sir, you're our hero!
Thank you, sir, for sending us grain.
Thank you, sir!
Bingzhu,
you're still
Officer Gao of the Well to us.
-Yeah!
Thank you, Officer Gao!
Bingzhu,
the Unwelcome Well
is grateful to you.
We're practically family.
Xiaowu!
Xiaoqi!
Chen Buyi!
You brats, are you seeing this?
Bingzhu
is home now.
Bingzhu!
Bingzhu, let's go!
I can finally come back home!
I am finally home!
[Unwelcome Well]
I tried my first pear when I was eight.
Do you know why?
Why?
There weren't any pear trees in the Well.
Every year, I had to wait
till the pears ripened and fell
by the bridge of Ci Hui Fang to eat some.
When I was a kid,
my friends and I
used to fight intensely
over a pear.
I never thought that
I could ever walk on the street
in the Well freely again,
with a beautiful lady
by my side.
Do you remember that place?
Of course.
When I first came to the Well, I was here to catch you.
♫Lonely footsteps are heartbreaking♫
Back then, you were an officer, and I was a thief.
You chased after me around half the Well.
I am Gao Bingzhu.
♫Everything is as surreal as a dream♫
♫We're not in each other's life anymore♫
♫Looking back after all these years,
how stubborn I was back then♫
♫Smile, there is still a long way to go♫
♫I still expected to know you after drinking♫
♫Life is full of happiness and sorrow♫
♫It would be better not to mention it♫
♫I drink wine while appreciating the view♫
♫We are meant to be apart♫
Back then, I thought,
'That lady is asking for trouble.
♫I miss you a lot♫
How dare she be that reckless in the Well?'
♫I saw the moonlight splashing
on the mountain♫
I've been meaning to ask you.
When I fell off the sluice,
why did you grab me?
I didn't want you to fall
and smash any valuables in the Well.
If I hadn't grabbed you,
I wouldn't have become who I am today.
If I gave you
another chance,
would you grab me?
Take a guess.
I guess...
I would not just grab you.
I'd hold you
and hold you tight.
I'd never let you go.
I used to think that
I'd go and see my friends in the beyond
after I avenged their death.
I won't do it now.
I've got someone I care for.
So, what do you want to do next?
It's August now.
Grapes have ripened.
The grapes at Ming Jiao Fang taste like heaven.
Have you had them before?
Of course.
Do you want to go there again?
Well, I want more than grapes.
The persimmons in September,
the chestnuts in October...
I want them all.
What's in November?
In November...
I have you.
[Unwelcome Well]
[Keep order for Her Majesty]
Your brother is a felon.
Without Her Majesty's permission,
no one is allowed to visit him.
I need to ask him about something.
What's there to ask?
He's now alive
and has become Lord of Spring of Four Season Clan.
We are all complicit.
Sir Wu,
I know the consequences.
[Wu]
You shouldn't have come here.
It doesn't matter.
You should've been dead,
but you're still here, right?
Do you still resent me?
I am not the only one.
All the people in Luoyang resent you.
All of them resent the Clan.
I am here today to ask you a question.
You've plotted
all these things.
What's your ultimate goal?
Hongyi,
we live in this world
because we're driven
by our ambition.
I will die for sure,
but my ambition
won't die with me.
Someone will carry on
and achieve the unfinished greater good.
Go back.
I will meet Father soon.
I will ask for his forgiveness.
Lord Pei, what's this?
It's a search warrant.
We're searching the entire city
[Grand Court]
for Yuwen Peipei, an entertainer at Hong Xiao Fang.
Her sketch is on the poster.
Keep an eye on her
when you're on patrol.
Report to me if you find anyone suspicious.
Listen up, fellas!
She's extremely dangerous!
Do not act on your own!
Yes, sir!
Greetings, sister.
The patrol officers are on a break.
No one will see you.
Hong Xiao Fang was shut down.
I have become a wanted person.
So...
I could only report to you in this way.
His Lordship said you've done a good job.
But I didn't kill the King of East River,
I...
His Lordship said that
it doesn't matter if he dies or not.
What matters is that
the assassination has made the evil Empress
distrust Lord Chu.
Without the King of East River,
the Intelligence Services
will not be able to fulfill its duty to supervise.
His Lordship is wise.
I've learned a lot.
It's just that...
If you need anything, just tell me.
I will pass it to His Lordship.
His Lordship helped me to get a new life,
and for that, I am deeply grateful.
I'm willing to sacrifice my life to repay him.
I'd like to ask His Lordship to show grace.
After I complete my mission,
please, let me leave Luoyang.
You want to leave Luoyang?
Where do you want to go?
I haven't thought about it.
But over the years,
I've been dealing with all kinds of people
in that brothel.
I feel exhausted.
Now,
all I want is to leave Luoyang.
I could travel around the world
or live a reclusive life in the mountains.
I just don't want to come back ever.
It's natural that you want to leave here.
I will pass it to His Lordship.
You've made great contributions, after all.
I don't think
His Lordship will go hard on you.
Thank you, sister.
Sir.
The cleansing mud
is a royal product.
We waited a long time for this new batch.
After your fair lady
uses this product,
she'll look radiant,
beautiful and young forever.
Alright, I'll take three.
Okay.
Go wrap them up.
Liu...
Liu Feng!
Chunhe, don't you know me?
I am Liu Feng!
♫Ignite those colorful dreams♫
What Chunhe?
I don't know anyone with that name.
♫When we bid farewell♫
♫We shall leave silently♫
I don't care if you're an assassin,
or Peipei of Hong Xiao Fang,
to me, you'll always be Chunhe.
♫Falling down♫
I can take you anywhere
♫In the air♫
in this whole wide world.
We'll never come back.
♫Waiting for the wind to bring you here♫
♫Waiting for the wind♫
Liu Feng!
♫Waiting for the light to shine on me♫
He's right ahead.
♫Shine on me♫
♫In the air♫
♫Waiting for the dream to end♫
♫Waiting for it to end♫
Sorry.
♫Stay here♫
Leave.
Yes.
How long has it been
since the last time we played chess together?
Do you remember what it was like back then?
You disobedient son!
You've been talking nonsense
in public all the time.
If I don't teach you a lesson,
you'll get yourself in grave trouble!
Master!
Lord Kuanren is still young and has much to learn.
He knew he made a mistake, right?
I did nothing wrong!
The Empress now
talks about appreciating talents all the time,
-but she misuses cruel officials.
-Lord Kuanren, careful with your words!
They get to decide
who become officials!
who is talented!
Master!
What?
Master,
the interior guards are here
to investigate the article
Lord Kuanren wrote the other day.
Greetings, Sir Wu.
Lord Baili.
I've read Kuanren's article.
It was a bit extreme,
but it was well-written.
My son is a fool.
If he wrote anything inappropriate
or said anything wrong,
it was because I didn't teach him well.
Please, Sir Wu, do not punish him.
Sir Wu,
we didn't find it.
You didn't find it?
So, it must be a rumor, then.
However, since we've been tipped off,
we have to be extra diligent.
Keep looking.
Yes.
Lord Baili,
I want to
talk to Kuanren in private for a minute.
Please, Sir Wu.
Kuanren, you've always been good at chess.
Let's have a game, shall we?
You are good at chess.
On that day, however,
you were completely
defeated by me.
Kuanren,
you were talented back then.
But you were too young.
You didn't know what to do.
So,
you could only write
useless poems and articles.
Weeds are all over the fields.
Set fire to them.
Nature has its order.
Separate the wheat from the chaff.
The nature of the four seasons
lies in Heaven and the Earth.
There was a rebel at North Sea Academy
called Lord Freedom.
He deceived many people,
recruited a lot of disciples,
and established Four Season Clan.
Kuanren,
you're one of his disciples, aren't you?
If you want to arrest me,
why didn't you do it earlier?
You think you can change your fate
by writing articles?
Why can't I?
As long as I can find
enough like-minded people,
even Her Majesty
will be able to hear what I've got to say.
I know what you're thinking.
You've always thought you're talented,
but you were born with an extra finger.
You're regarded as a misfit
and cannot be an official.
You're engulfed in anger.
However, you can't change anything,
because you're insignificant.
If there are weeds all over the fields,
we should set fire to them.
But what is fire?
It's power!
Her Majesty is the most powerful person
in the country.
If you can't overthrow her,
no one will ever
care about how enraged you are.
Now, the fire
is about to burn Her Majesty.
We once swore that
we'd turn this world upside down.
For all these years,
we've been enduring hardships
and taking risks.
Now, the old regime will be burnt down
by the fire we set
and a new one will be born!
Weeds are all over the fields.
Set fire to them.
It's my honor to
see you,
Lord Phoenix!
The conversation
we had years ago
enlightened me.
I've kept your words in mind.
If you want to rule a country,
you need to win over the people.
To win over the people,
you need to win their hearts.
We've gone through
the darkest time in life.
We've endured all the ignorance
and humiliation.
Everything will change
from this moment on.
You promised me that
when you revise historical records,
you'll list me as the top
of all nobles and officials.
All future generations
will read about my struggles, my rage,
my ambition, and my talent!
This day
will come soon.
Chunhe!
[Interior Guard Services]
Brother!
Brother, please don't be like this.
You're suffering.
I don't want to see you like this.
Siyue,
I am fine.
I'm doing this for us.
This is the only way
to prevent others
from bullying us.
Brother!
Leave!
Brother, it's me.
Why are you here?
I want to keep you company.
Water.
Here.
Siyue,
don't worry about me!
I am fine.
Go back and have some rest.
Brother,
do you harbor any resentment?
Resentment?
Towards what?
Me.
You're the only family I've got
in this world.
Why would I harbor resentment towards you?
You got ill
because of me.
I know you became a food-testing officer
so that you could provide for me.
It had nothing to do with you.
Since we were kids,
we've been relying on each other.
I know how hard
it is for us distant relatives of the Wu family
to gain a foothold in the Court.
So,
you took the job as a food-testing officer.
Food-testing officers
need to try food
for Her Majesty to make sure it's safe.
Only by this
could you earn Her Majesty's trust...
Enough.
Stop.
I know that
you care about me.
But you must remember
not to tell anyone
about this ever again.
You have to get rid of this thought.
When everything is back to normal in Luoyang,
you can leave all this behind
and focus on recovery
and getting better.
Didn't you say that
you want to travel to Jiangnan?
I'll go to Jiangnan with you,
alright?
Now,
I need to shoulder the burden
of managing both Services.
I won't be able to get away any time soon.
Didn't I give you the ring puzzle?
Have you worked it out?
Hongyi,
I yelled at you at the study.
Don't be mad at me.
You won't even
greet your own brother?
I remembered that you hadn't reached my shoulder
when I left home.
Hongyi,
do you not think of me as your brother anymore?
Go back.
I will meet Father soon.
I will ask for his forgiveness.
Baili Kuanren, the leader of Four Season Clan,
who calls himself Lord of Spring,
is vile and cruel. He's killed innocent people
and destroyed Hanjia Granary,
bringing Luoyang into grave chaos.
According to Her Majesty,
he is vicious and should be despised by all.
He shall be executed
publicly at the market
[South Market]
today at noon.