♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 36=
I want to apologize that
it wasn't me who was with you
at the hospital that night.
I think, it might be him.
Xiaosu, where are you going?
Lei Yuzheng.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
Xiaosu.
Mr. Lei, what a coincidence!
You also have dinner here?
♪Between us♪
It's ok if you don't answer me.
I will help you.
You are following me.
It seems I am correct.
Is that how you care about someone?
Really special.
I should thank you
for visiting me
when I was in the hospital,
for paying for my bills,
and for all that you have done for me.
Right?
If you really cared about me,
why didn't you reply me on WeChat
or call me?
You keep me waiting for your message.
Don't you think it is
too cruel to me?
Or you just want to see
me in pain?
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
I'm sorry, Mr. Lei.
I can't afford such kind of care.
So please, from now on,
don't follow me.
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪
Thank you for visiting me
when I was in the hospital,
for paying for my bills,
and for all that you have done for me.
If you really cared about me,
why didn't you reply me on WeChat
or call me?
You keep me waiting for your message.
Don't you think it is
too cruel to me?
Or you just want to
see me in pain?
I can't afford such kind of care.
So please, from now on,
don't follow me.
Yuzheng.
Uncle Jiang.
I have something to discuss with you.
Ok.
Sit.
Yuzheng,
you look tired.
It's because of the acquisition.
Since you mentioned the acquisition,
actually, there is a person
I really worry about.
Who is it?
(Mr. Yu)
-Hello
-It sounds like
you are in bad mood.
Mr. Yu, what did you want me for?
I'll come straight to the point.
I just want to know
the current financial situation
of Yutian.
Finance of Yutian
has always been in the charge
of the chairman.
I don't know.
You are the CEO of Yutian.
How come you don't know?
I didn't want to tell you
at the first thought.
But, since things have come to this,
I have to tell you.
The internal information leakage
of Yutian
was related to Lin Xiangyuan.
Are you sure?
Yes.
According to what I know,
the reason why Yutian's stock
suddenly raised during that time
is that
someone disclosed the information that
I would go abroad
to negotiate with S.G.
on jointly building the
Universal Entertainment Center project.
I don't want to lie to you.
This time, I didn't go abroad.
I went to Guizhou.
Why did you go to Guizhou?
To investigate Lin Xiangyuan.
I don't know if you still remember.
On the day I was arrested,
the Financial Times published an article
saying that someone disclosed Yutian's
internal information.
I vaguely remember that.
But,
is it related to Lin Xiangyuan?
The article was quite detailed.
It just happened when
I signed a contract with S.G.
It was on the same day.
Don't you
think that there is anything abnormal?
You mean
it was Lin Xiangyuan
who disclosed the information?
The reporter who wrote this article
is named Li Lu who is in Guizhou.
He was the classmate of Lin Xiangyuan.
Was it arranged by Lin Xiangyuan?
I don't know if it was him.
Because
the reporter who wrote the article
is missing.
Missing?
Kidnapped, to be more precise.
What the hell do you want?
This is not a nice attitude
for cooperation.
I have to remind you that
we are on the same boat.
If anything happens to us,
you won't be fine either.
It
can't be Lin Xiangyuan.
Uncle Jiang.
I also hope it is not him.
But one thing is pretty certain that
the one who is behind
should be Hengshan Fund.
Hengshan Fund?
According to my investigation,
Hengshan Fund has been
secretly buying Yutian's shares.
What is strange is that,
at the high price, they don't
sell the shares.
Instead, they kept buying in.
From then, they have started their plan.
They want to acquire Yutian.
It looks that they really want to win.
I'm telling you,
don't threaten me!
I am very clear about the situation now.
But I have to tell you
it is in the charge of the chairman.
I really don't know anything.
Ok, I trust you.
If anything happens,
please call me as soon as possible.
Fanlv,
how are you and Lin Xiangyuan recently?
We are good.
Really?
Dad, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Dad, what happened?
Dad is just asking.
Dad, are you worried about that,
since Xiangyuan has got the shares,
he will drop his mask
and treat me like before?
He's very nice to me now.
And I can feel that
he is truly repentant.
If he is really nice to you,
why didn't he come back to
have dinner with you today?
He didn't even call.
Dad is really scared now.
I'm afraid that I am wrong again.
It's not only going to destroy you,
but also Yutian.
Yutian?
Dad, Fanlv, I'm back.
Where were you?
Why did you come back so late?
I bought you some food.
You said yesterday that
you like the egg tarts of this shop.
I've been waiting in a long line
to buy it for you.
I just casually said.
Dad, I'm sorry that I'm late.
Hurry up. Eat.
It doesn't taste good when it gets cold.
How is it? Good?
Xiangyuan, sit down.
Let's have dinner together.
Ok.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling cold?
Let me get your jacket.
You have transferred
Lin Xiangyuan and Fanlv's
jointly owned shares
to Lin Xiangyuan.
At that time, I was worried about that,
if Lin Xiangyuan
was really related to Hengshan Fund,
it will make it harder
for us to resist the acquisition.
Dad, I will eat this.
You and Xiangyuan enjoy.
Xiangyuan, I go upstairs.
Don't worry about her.
Come here. Sit.
Dad,
do you have something to talk to me?
Xiangyuan,
do you know what role you are now?
I know.
You're now
not only Fanlv's husband
and my son-in-law,
but also the CEO of Yutian
and a director of Yutian.
At this time,
you should know clearly
what is more important.
Be worthy of your relatives,
people who have helped you
and your role.
It is more important that
you should respect your conscience.
Dad, you can rest assured.
I've got it in my heart.
You are smart.
"A word to the wise is sufficient".
Conduct yourself well.
Tell me,
how is the negotiation with S.G. going?
Not well.
I think
Linton of S.G.
was very polite to us on the surface.
When it came to cooperation,
he passed it to the board of S.G.
I think
they will not
help Yutian,
and they are probably
negotiating with Hengshan Fund
to support the acquisition of Yutian.
That's exactly what I am thinking.
According to what I know of Linton,
maybe S.G.
has cooperated with Hengshan Fund.
For such a business plan of
acquiring Yutian,
only Hengshan Fund is not enough.
So,
we have to think of another way.
By the way,
how is the situation in Guizhou?
Any progress?
Li Lu was found.
But unfortunately,
he has been kidnapped.
It means Hengshan Fund
knows that you are doing investigation
and they start to take action.
Now, we have to wait for
the result from Shangguan.
Hope they can get Xie Li.
Let me open the door.
Why not ring the bell?
Here you are.
At the door just now,
I heard you mentioned my name.
You said something bad about me?
Any information from Ye?
He got Xie Li.
Shall we
pull in the "net"?
No, it is not the right time.
Xie Li is very experienced.
Don't be too hurried.
Otherwise, he may get suspicious.
This is
something really important to him,
and especially
his life and fortune are involved.
He won't confess
easily.
(He Qunfei)
(Hengshan Fund is holding
a press conference)
Hengshan Fund
is holding a press conference.
(Today, Hengshan Fund)
(has officially reported to CSRC)
(and announced its plan for acquisition
of the listed company, Yutian.)
(Yutian is an old listed company.)
(What's Hengshan Fund's)
(purpose)
(for acquiring Yutian?)
(Once the acquisition is successful,)
(will you make any changes)
(to the operation strategy of Yutian?)
(The reason why we put forward
this acquisition plan is that)
(we hope to have
friendly cooperation with Yutian.)
(After the acquisition,)
(we will set up some reform plans.)
(What are your reform plans?)
(Firstly, we will focus on
the development of new energy)
(to accelerate the  transformation
and upgrade of Yutian.)
(Secondly,
we will sell the Global Finance Port)
(to raise fund.)
(Thirdly, we will dispatch a talent team)
(to join Yutian's board.)
(We will reorganize
the current top management of Yutian.)
They called these plans?
It is robbery!
Merger and acquisition
are so common in the business.
(Yutian's
current top management is rigid.)
(The development of Yutian
is also stagnant.)
(But we are confident that,)
(in the following three to five years,)
(we will develop Yutian into)
(one of the world's top 500 companies.)
Lei Yuzheng is in trouble.
Mr. Lin, I have spread the information.
What information?
I have spread that
Lei Yuzheng will not fight any more,
and Yutian will be over very soon.
What do you mean?
Who tells you that Yutian will be over?
Mr. Lin,
you haven't got the picture yet?
How can Yutian fight against
Hengshan Fund?
Mr. Lin, it is a good opportunity
for us
to sell our shares.
We can earn a lot of money.
At that time,
even if Hengshan Fund's
acquisition plan is successful,
it has nothing to do with us.
We are not afraid of that,
as we have money.
At that time, we just make a clean break
and leave Yutian.
We can set up our own company.
Mr. Lin, am I right?
Finished?
I hope you won't say such irresponsible
things in the future.
Besides,
stop doing such stupid things.
Now, I am telling you.
You and I, we are staff of Yutian.
We are paid by Yutian.
Yutian now is fighting with others.
You are one of the top management.
How can you say that?
If there is really a "war",
for such kind of action,
you should be shot.
Mr. Lin, you misunderstood me.
What I have done is all good to you.
I'm warning you again.
No matter what I had
with Lei Yuzheng before,
now, in such a special period,
don't make any trouble for me.
Am I clear?
Yes.
Yes, clear.
Get out.
Good-heartedness is not recompensed.
Xie, what happened?
Why did you ask me out?
Why are you drinking like this?
Anything unhappy?
You can talk about it with me.
See if I can help you.
It's because of my boss.
I
was so kind to give him advices.
He was not only ungrateful,
but also
asked me not to be a sticky beak.
Xie.
Listen.
"Evil people are bad all over the world".
See,
we've known each other for a long time.
I find that
you are
really a royal friend.
You are so right!
I'm telling you that,
one day...
although he seems like
a successful and respectable man,
actually, he is a bumpkin.
A hillbilly. A little redneck.
Right. He is a redneck.
If one day he pisses me off,
I will make the thing about him public
to send him in jail
and let him lose
both fortune and honor.
Go on bragging!
Our boss is so eager
to make his dirty money
that he sent our previous CEO
in jail.
I didn't expect your boss
was such a jerk.
I also got what I wanted.
He made his big money.
I made my pennies.
Pennies?  How?
Stock.
I have a buddy
who is a securities broker.
I provided him the information,
and he paid me for that.
You know what?
You are not a good friend of mine,
because you earned money alone.
Ye, are you also interested in stock?
I am interested in earning money.
You should have told me earlier.
I'll give you my buddy's phone number.
Here it is.
You just tell him that
I recommend him to you.
You just tell him
Just make a call.
You don't
have to worry about anything else.
So simple.
Forget it.
I don't know much about stock.
Come on. Cheers.
Xiangyuan.
Don't get too tired and go to bed early.
Thank you.
Have you been
working very hard recently?
I don't mind working hard,
because I am your man.
I saw the news on TV.
Is Yutian in trouble?
Don't worry.
There's no problem.
It will soon be solved.
Is there something you want to tell me?
There is one thing
I want to discuss with you.
You don't have to discuss anything
with me.
Just tell me what to do.
Recently,
my dad is not in good mood.
He is always sighing.
I think Yutian may be in big trouble.
He is old now.
I don't want him to be too tired.
So, Xiangyuan,
you may need to
share the work load a little bit more.
Fanlv, don't worry.
I will not let him over tire himself.
And...
It's ok. Just say it.
Can you put down
your prejudice to Lei Yuzheng
and work well with him
to help Yutian
overcome the difficulties?
I know.
You don't like Lei Yuzheng.
You've been treating him
like an imaginary enemy.
You've been trying to
compete with him all the time.
But this time, it is quite different.
Yutian is in big trouble.
You have to stop competition
and work together,
in order to save Yutian.
Ok?
Xiangyuan, you just do it for me.
Fanlv,
don't worry about that.
I know what I should do.
I listen to you.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
After I finish all the work,
I will take you abroad to relax.
To be honest, I seldom go abroad.
You have to be my tour guide.
Yutian's share price
has been rapidly raising for three days.
From the current data,
they have acquired 15 percent of
the tradable shares of Yutian.
I believe, in a few days,
they will become a majority shareholder
and request Yutian
to hold a shareholder meeting.
It will be perfect
if we have
some evidences of their illegal behaviors.
We can report it to CSRC
and let them lose all their money!
By the way,
how is the situation of Shangguan?
Maybe
it's time to let them pull in the "net"?
Are you sure Xie Li will tell the truth?
No.
Even if Xie Li says something,
can you be sure that what he says
can be used as a legal evidence?
No.
So,
we cannot pin our hopes on Xie Li.
We cannot put all eggs in one basket.
This is not gambling.
Do we have any other option?
Here is the fried bread stick.
What's wrong? Why don't you eat?
I have little appetite.
Lei Yuzheng's company will be acquired.
What's the big deal?
You have to be like this?
What?
It is not because of that.
You're talking nonsense!
How many years have we known each other?
Ten years.
How come I don't know you?
You are trying to keep it from me?
Halifax
has provided us a definite answer.
Within such a short time, if we want
to seek help from them,
that's impossible.
According to their reply,
it will take one month
to make their decision.
Most of the foreign banks
are not familiar with China
and don't know much about Yutian.
No matter how much effort we make,
they will follow
their own procedure.
How about the other foreign banks?
I need to wait for a while
before I can talk to James.
By the way,
is James your father's old friend?
He should be familiar with Yutian
and has good relationship.
How about this?
I, as your sister,
will go with you to Yutian
after breakfast
to ask about what you want to know.
No.
Lei Yuzheng should be very busy.
He should not want anyone to bother him.
Who says I want to meet Lei Yuzheng?
I will take you to Yutian
to ask He Qunfei.
How is it? Go or not?
No.
Are you sure? Ok, fine by me.
James.
Hello, Mr. Lei.
Long time no see.
Likewise.
Have you had a chance to spot my email?
Look, we made there one assessment.
The assessment is already sent to
Pasadena, our mother company.
Thank you.
But here I have some problems.
How about
calling He Qunfei out and asking him?
I knew that.
You really love Lei Yuzheng.
You are incurable.
What are you talking about?
Stupid.
I will ask He Qunfei out.
So, you can ask him.
But Lei, in this situation,
your mortgage is not of any worth.
But James, that's why I am calling
personally to ask you this favor.
And group board for me,
team board, its will
is my will.
It's grateful for what you've done,
and...
Lei, I am so sorry, not able to help.
Thank you. Next time.
Thank you. Good bye.
I hope the results from domestic banks
are not the same.
Mr. Lei.
I'll be at the club tomorrow
to entertain Mr. Cao from Dafeng Bank
and some other friends from the bank.
Please call the club, and let them not
to have arrangement for other guests.
And, at six o'clock,
pick me up at my house on time.
Sure, Mr. Lei.
Anything else?
No.
Ok. You can rest assured.
Who are you calling?
You scared me!
You check too much, Siqi.
(Lei Yuzheng)
You even care who he calls!
Your slap
made me feel scared.
See, you have made him very scared.
He must have done something bad.
When did your courage get so small?
Why are you so happy that
you two
invite me for meal?
We ask you out to ask
for some information.
Xiaosu wants to know
how Lei Yuzheng and Yutian are.
Is Yutian acquired?
What are you talking about?
The acquisition just starts.
It should not be acquired so soon.
Yes, there is acquisition.
But, don't worry.
Mr. Lei can handle it.
But I can see that
the other side seems so powerful,
aggressive
and confident.
It looks like they just want to
eat Yutian in one bite.
How is he these days?
He is good. He is optimistic.
He also got the way to fight against
Hengshan Fund.
That's good.
Give this to him.
What's this?
It is the amulet Xiaosu got for him.
Wish him well.
Xiaosu, why don't you
give it to him by yourself?
It is better that
you help me to give it to him.
And don't tell him that it is from me.
Just tell him it is from you.
Why?
I am afraid that he will refuse it
if he knows it is from me.
During this period, I can feel that
he has been avoiding me.
I don't know the reason,
but
I believe that he
should have his reason.
So, I don't want to bother him.
I just hope that
he can be healthy and safe
and everything goes smoothly.
Other things don't matter.
Mr. Lei, Mr. Cao has arrived.
Mr. Cao.
Hello.
-Hello.
Where are the other gentlemen?
Mr. Min and Mr. Liao
have something urgent to deal with,
so they can't come.
I come today
because of the good relationship
with your father.
I come here to say hello.
To be honest, our bank
and the other gentlemen
you invited today
know the situation of Yutian.
We are sorry that we can't help.
It's not that we don't want to help you,
but we really
don't have the ability to help.
Mr. Cao. Please listen to me.
You don't need to say anything else.
Indeed,
Yutian's offer is very attractive.
50 percent shares
of the Entertainment Center
as the mortgage!
But we really can't accept that.
Hope you can understand.
I have prepared dinner.
How about we sit down and talk?
No.
I can't join the dinner.
I hope you can understand.
I am really busy.
Maybe next time.
Ok. Next time.
Ok.
Didn't you see the doorbell?
Doorbell?
Why are you so funny?
Why don't you
ask me what I am doing here?
You are really...
Come in.
Buddy.
Look at this.
Shangguan.
What's this?
Treasure.
A treasure that can beat Hengshan.
(Summary of Stock Transaction Details)
Shangguan.
How did you get this?
Ye and I
got Xie Li drunk.
From what he said,
we got
a securities broker's phone number.
I have a buddy
who is a securities broker.
I provided him the information,
and he paid me for that.
You know what?
I'll give you my buddy's phone number.
Then, we went to look for
this securities broker.
Ye and I
tried to use all the tactics.
He didn't tell anything.
At last, there was nothing we could do
but  to deal with him in a tough way.
What have you done to him?
Buddy, don't worry.
We didn't do anything to him.
I just told him that
what he has done
is improperly using internal information
from a listed company
to disrupt the stock market.
He will go to jail for that.
Was he frightened?
Of course he was.
He was frightened to death.
Then, he told us everything,
including how Xie Li gave him the money,
and how he helped Xie Li
to buy and sell the stocks of Yutian.
He told us everything.
Yuzheng.
We have the evidence in our hands.
There is no need to
fight against Hengshan in the stock market.
We should beat them.
Have you ever thought about that,
if we submit it to the regulator,
what kind of result it will be?
What else?
Hengshan Fund
will stop the hostile acquisition.
Then, Yutian can release its crisis.
Lin Xiangyuan
got the information from He Qunfei.
And Xie Li
got the information from Lin Xiangyuan.
So, he started
buying and selling shares of Yutian.
If Xie Li
blamed all the charges
on Lin Xiangyuan,
Lin Xiangyuan may go to jail.
So what?
It's him whom we have to deal with.
Our target is not Lin Xiangyuan.
It is Hengshan.
(Mr. Yu)
If Lin Xiangyuan goes to jail,
have you ever thought about Uncle Jiang
and Fanlv?
What should they do?
Fanlv just recovered.
If this happens, she will get worse.
That's right.
Mr. Jiang can't stand this.
(Summary of Stock Transaction Details)
This cannot be submitted.
What do you want again?
Mr. Lin.
I am now
really doubtful of your sincerity.
What do you mean?
Last evening, Lei Yuzheng
invited the top management
of several banks.
Do you know that?
Lei Yuzheng invited
top management of banks for dinner?
It seems that you don't know anything.
But you are the CEO of Yutian.
Lei Yuzheng invited others for dinner.
Why did he need to tell me?
You're right. I am the CEO of Yutian.
Is a CEO supposed to know everything?
You also know
about my relationship with Lei Yuzheng.
I understand.
But I have to tell you.
The banks will not help Yutian.
I hope you can understand the situation
clearly.
Not irresolute and hesitant any more.
Are you that confident?
Of course.
We'll see if you don't believe me.
You don't submit it?
So, you don't want to save Yutian?
Of course I do.
But not in this way.
It is too harmful.
If two armies engage on the battlefield,
will there be no casualties?
Let's think about another way.
I have to go home.
Ask for help again!
You are?
I'm Yuzheng's friend.
My name is Liu Siyang.
I'm Shao Kaixuan.
Aunt Shao.
I've heard about you from Yu Zheng.
Please come in.
Aunt Shao.
Why are you here?
You haven't slept for a few days.
You knew all?
I knew everything.
I came here
to tell you something important.
But you have to promise that
you'll go to bed after I tell you everything.
I don't want to see you
like this.
Aunt Shao, please have a seat.
Yuzheng,
you must be exhausted these days.
Aunt Shao, to be honest,
I've experienced something before.
But there was no pressure at that time.
Now, it is your hardest time.
I can really feel it.
The time I spent in jail
was better than now.
If Yutian is really acquired,
what I have done
will be all in vain.
Your father worked on Yutian
for all his life.
You and Yutian mean a lot to him.
In other words,
Yutian and you are his two sons.
I really miss him sometimes.
I feel sorry to him.
Since your childhood,
Aunt Shao has never seen you so sad.
I don't want to lose.
What's this?
Your father left it to you.
My dad?
Since you went to university abroad,
your dad had worked on it.
Open it and have a look.
(Group Trust Fund Plan)
Group trust fund?
About how to use this trust fund,
it's up to you,
as long as you're worthy of your father.
Mr. Lin. Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin.
Now, you don't even knock.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lin.
I just got the latest news.
Mr. Jiang and Mr. Lei
are going to hold a press conference
in order to
respond to the acquisition.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪