["THIS HEART'S ON FIRE"
BY WOLF PARADE PLAYING]
♪
♪ Sometimes we rock and roll
♪ Sometimes we stay at home,
and it's just fine ♪
_
♪ This heart's on fire
♪
♪ I am my mother's hen
MAN: Please walk around the other way.
- [PLAYING THROUGH HEADPHONES]
- ♪ And left the body in the bed all day ♪
- What happened?
- Nothing.
They're just getting the lobby
ready for the big party.
[MUSIC CONTINUES THROUGH HEADPHONES]
CLAIRE: It's an annual fundraiser.
Like a carnival?
No, it's a swanky, black-tie ball.
You think a hospital lobby is swanky?
Not yet, but add some lights,
a few decorations,
and, most importantly, alcohol...
It becomes a streamer- and
balloon-infested hospital lobby
with a cash bar.
[SCOFFS] It's for charity.
Better to spend the money for the cause.
Actually, it's worse.
You need to spend money to make money.
I don't like parties.
Doesn't matter.
All residents will be expected to attend
and make a donation.
This is Dr. Alex Park.
He's the last of Coyle's residents
to be reassigned to our team.
Meet doctors Jared Kalu,
Claire Browne, and Shaun Murphy.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome back. How was Costa Rica?
Beaches were awesome.
Monkeys were horrible.
Little bastards stole
my new camera and a pair of...
How old are you?
45.
That's even older than Dr. Melendez.
Dr. Murphy is a talented doctor
who has autism,
which sometimes causes him
to ask inappropriate questions.
No worries. Inappropriate
questions can be very revealing.
I'm a late bloomer.
Park's being modest,
which is very unlike him.
He was a cop for 15 years
before he went to med school.
Now that we all know each other,
Reznick and Browne have dibs
on cases this week.
You make your picks?
- Yes.
- Definitely.
Is there karaoke?
And now, our all-star lineup!
Playing center,
out of Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan.
Whoo!
Spirit, stop it.
They don't have time to fool around.
I'm not fooling around.
I need to document the momentous event.
Then at least get it right.
I'm from Taipei, Taiwan.
Co-o-orrection!
From Taipei, Taiwan...
which is a believe
is a suburb of Moose Jaw...
Dr. Audrey Lim!
♪ Bam, bam-bam, bawr
And assisting Dr. Lim are...
two docs I've never met.
Hello.
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy
from Casper, Wyoming.
And...?
Dr. Morgan Reznick,
Mill Valley, California.
Represent!
- Whoo!
Okay, Spirit, that's enough.
All right, put your phone away,
or it becomes my phone.
Well, folks, looks like
the suits are shuttin' me down.
Thanks for all your support.
- Love you! Bye!
- [CELLPHONE CHIMES]
Sorry, but my friends insist
I keep them up to date.
It's all right. It's a big day.
Spirit was born with
ectopia cordis. She's been...
Why didn't they repair it
when she was an infant?
- They couldn't.
- Her rib cage was too small.
But after 14 years
of slow and steady growth...
It's time to put this baby
where it belongs.
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪
This is an interesting view.
I can see the aortic arch.
- MORGAN: Murphy.
- Oh, it's all right.
I'm used to people being curious.
I'm sure you're looking forward
to when there's nothing
to be curious about.
Mm, what I'm really looking
forward to is... crowds.
You like crowds?
I don't know.
I've never been in one.
I can't go to a normal school,
and my parents barely ever
let me leave our house.
Well, when a small bump could
stop your heart, it makes sense.
But you still have a lot of friends?
Yeah, of course.
I mean, I just can't do
anything fun with them.
If you can't do anything fun,
then how did you get them
to be your friend?
Well, in case you haven't noticed,
I like to talk.
- Mm, yes.
- And, uh...
We all do everything online now anyway.
The first thing I'm gonna do
when I get out of here
is take all my friends to a concert.
Like, general admission, on the floor.
I don't even care who the band is,
just as long as the place is packed.
Oh, and I'm gonna hug everyone.
You've never hugged anyone?
Not even your parents?
Kissed by my parents,
high-fived by my friends,
but, nope, no hugs.
It's just too risky.
Hugs make me feel trapped.
♪
- Agh!
- Sorry.
Almost done.
Pain in the upper-right quadrant.
It's jaundice.
Bilirubin's off the chart.
WALLACE: That doesn't make sense.
He's been doing so well
since the transplant.
Yeah, every check-up this year's
been perfect.
Well, it could just be
a temporary flare-up.
We'll increase his anti-rejection meds
and do a full liver exam.
We'll know more then.
You two, do the work-up.
And you find a new liver.
Shouldn't we wait for the biopsy result?
Not when I already know
what it's gonna say.
He needs a new liver ASAP.
I mean, that's gonna be hard.
He's Blood Type O.
It's gonna be impossible.
He's lucky they were able
to find the first one.
Well, he better get lucky again
because it's our only way
to keep him alive.
♪
We're screwed.
Barbara Boxer got ear barotrauma
scuba-diving in Cozumel
and cannot fly for two weeks,
which means we don't have
a keynote speaker for our gala.
[CHUCKLES]
You think this is funny?
I've just never seen you anxious,
and I seriously doubt
Barbara Boxer scuba-dives.
It's just an excuse.
She sent me a picture
from the hospital.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Anyone can fake a photograph.
What are you doing?
I am doing a search
to see if our esteemed senator
from the great state of California
ever once... once...
talked about scuba-diving
in an interview.
It doesn't matter if it's true.
What matters is that
we find a replacement.
I need you to get me
a meeting with Aiden Coulter.
- Oh, Aiden Coulter?
- Yes.
Oh.
What? I sat next to him once
at an A's game.
And the story I remember is that you two
were talking smack that entire game,
and after he spilled his beer on you
and insisted on buying you a new jacket,
you refused him.
So he owes you.
Just get me a meeting.
I'll handle everything from there.
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
_
Huh.
JARED: You'll be fine.
You've had liver biopsies before.
And they've always hurt a lot.
Please, isn't there another way?
Well, the other way, Eric,
would going through your neck,
and I don't think
you'd like that any more.
Eric, do you know why NBA players
all wear headphones before games?
Don't look at him. Look at me.
I need you to answer me.
Why do NBA players wear
headphones before games?
I don't know.
I guess they like music.
No, they need music.
Music helps them forget
about everything else
and focus on what's important...
the game.
Who's your favorite player?
Curry.
Okay.
This is the song he listens to
before every game.
How do you know?
Because he's my favorite player, too.
I want you to close your eyes
and focus on this.
Just this.
It's cold.
Yeah, now it is, but if you stay focused,
pretty soon, it'll stop feeling cold
and start to feel warm.
When that happens,
I want you to nod your head,
and you'll feel some pressure
and a small pinch.
What if it does...
Then close your eyes and focus.
♪
You ready?
Two minutes and he'll be good to go.
How'd you know he was a basketball fan?
His shoes.
He's not wearing any shoes.
Yeah, they're in a backpack in his room.
You searched his backpack?
Well, it's, um, less invasive
than a rectal,
and most of the time more useful.
Okay, Spirit, just keep still and...
And during a few parts of the exam,
we may ask you to hold your breath,
but it'll only be a few seconds.
You got it.
[WHIRRING]
You gonna buy a tux or rent one?
The fundraiser is black tie.
I have a suit.
It's new.
I bought it for my resident interviews.
It doesn't matter how new it is.
It's not a tux.
Wearing a uniform at work
reassures patients.
Wearing a uniform at a party
does nothing but make you
hot and uncomfortable.
This party is work.
Get a tux.
And not a crappy one
from some outlet store.
Get fitted by a pro and
spend a minimum of two grand.
You're gonna meet rich people
who can help your career,
and they're not gonna want
to help some slob in a...
I'm not a slob.
No, I am very clean
and make sure my clothes
are never wrinkled.
And it's too big.
Her heart.
It's enlarged 53% since her last exam.
Her last exam was only six months ago.
It won't fit.
Too big.
The biopsy confirmed
acute cellular rejection.
We maximized his
immunosuppressives, but, uh...
I found one... a Type-O liver.
Are you sure?
Park and I checked the registry,
and there weren't any.
I found it online.
He, uh... He already tried
to make a direct donation
a few months ago,
but the patient died before the surgery.
I contacted him, which wasn't easy,
but he still wants to be a donor.
That's amazing.
Great job.
What's the catch?
He wants to be a donor,
but he's not on the registry?
I mean, there's got to be a catch.
He, uh... He can't be on the registry
because he is in prison.
For murder.
Actually, um, seven murders.
♪
Boris Tirayan was
a Russian Mafia enforcer
convicted of seven murders.
Who now wants to make amends.
He tried to be a donor a few months ago,
but the patient died before the red
tape could be worked out.
But now that it has...
Are there any laws against
an inmate becoming a donor?
No, but there is a ton of liability.
What if he attacks someone here?
He'll be guarded by state prison guards
on a separate level,
away from patients
and all nonessential staff.
Everyone deserves the chance
to turn their life around.
The guy wants to do something decent,
we should let him.
I don't think we owe a murderer anything.
But maybe he owes us something.
He has a debt to society.
Which he would repay by
donating his inner organs.
Isn't it a slippery slope
between a guy who wants to make amends
and turning our prison system
into a superstore for body parts?
A slippery slope that
saves a child's life.
PARK: It'll never happen.
He's just trying to get a hospital,
where it'll be easier to escape.
You have no idea what his motivation is.
I know he's a lying sociopath
who doesn't care
about anyone but himself.
He's been a model inmate for nine years,
tutors other prisoners in the library...
Yeah, because he's trying
to get someone to trust him,
to give him an inch,
and as soon as they do...
We got approval.
He's gonna stall, make excuses,
and when he sees his chance,
someone's gonna get hurt.
I think it's worth taking that chance.
Anybody who doesn't agree,
feel free to sit this one out.
♪
MORGAN: When you started menstruating,
the increased estrogen
caused pulmonary hypertension,
which isn't a surgical issue in itself,
but along with your
atypical vascular system...
Your heart's grown too big.
LIM: We will control your blood pressure
so that you will keep growing
but your heart won't,
and then, by the time
you're 18. we'll able to...
No.
I'm not waiting any longer.
Spirit, honey, it will be okay.
No, it won't!
I'm sick of being stuck inside
all the time.
I'm sick of this!
I don't ever want to text, call,
or video chat again.
Mom, I want to be touched.
I want to be shoved.
I want to be punched.
I don't even care, just...
Please.
I want this surgery now.
♪
I need it.
I'm sorry. We can't.
♪
We need to get rid of
all the furniture and artwork.
I get removing the paintings,
but the furniture?
Don't want the prison guards
sitting down on the job.
He's gonna be in full restraints,
cuffed to the bed.
Well, that's our plan,
but we also need to be
prepared for his plan.
Okay, we need to get rid of
the window blinds, curtain rods,
jacket hooks, and make sure
there's no metal rivets
or eyelets on the mattress.
Um, what's he gonna do
with a metal eyelet?
Tear it off the mattress and file it down
to cut your jugular,
or bend it into a handcuff key,
or shove it into an electric socket
to create a spark and start a fire.
I've seen knives made out of
toilet paper, soap, and salt
that could amputate a fat guy's femur.
Not quite sure he needed the part
about the guy being fat.
[BOTH LAUGH]
So... I've been thinking.
You want to go to
the fundraiser together?
It's not a prom.
We don't have to bring a date.
Yeah, we don't have to.
But we can, if we want.
Everyone basically knows
we're seeing each other,
but still...
I think it might be a nice opportunity
to take our relationship
out into the open.
Unless you don't want to.
No, it's a good idea.
Are you sure?
Because, you know, we don't have to.
Yeah. Let's do it.
[CELLPHONES CHIME]
Let's go.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
What's wrong?
WALLACE: It's fine. He'll be all right.
No, I won't. I don't
want a murderer's liver!
It's evil!
[SIGHS] Eric, there's no such thing
as a good or bad liver.
It's just a... just an organ.
CLAIRE: Eric, this is your only choice.
If we don't do the transplant,
you will die.
ERIC: I don't want him
to be a part of me,
inside me forever, all right?
I don't care what you
or anybody else says, okay?
It's my body, and I don't want it!
That's ridiculous.
Personality traits aren't
transferred in an organ transplant.
It's also irrelevant.
Children don't consent to surgeries...
their parents do.
But if he doesn't cooperate
with the anti-rejection regimen,
we could be wasting a liver that
could save someone else's life.
PARK: No one's getting saved by Tirayan.
I found a Type-A donor.
It's not a perfect match, but...
His body's already
rejected a perfect match.
There's no way it can tolerate
an incompatible blood type.
No, the only way to save Eric
is to do the transplant
with Tirayan's liver.
That is it.
We have no other option.
Let the O.R. know we're gonna
need more restraints.
Dr. Clinton Ford out of Alberta
developed an experimental
resorbable material.
It would allow us to expand her rib cage
and create room to fit her heart inside.
LIM: An artificial sternum.
That would actually grow along
with the patient.
The surgery isn't reversible.
If it doesn't work,
we can't just move her heart
back to where it was.
It would allow her to have a life.
She has a life, and she'll be healthy
as long as she stays out of crowds,
doesn't hug anyone,
or do anything where she might fall.
I get you're autistic,
but I know even you realize
when a patient cries and throws
her phone against the wall,
they're not happy
with their current health.
There's no reason to make this personal.
There is if his medical
judgment is biased.
I saw she was upset.
You saw it, but you didn't understand it.
You're very competitive.
Are you trying to make
Dr. Lim think I'm biased,
or are you trying
to undermine my confidence?
I'm actually trying
to help you and the patient.
She wants to be able to rub elbows,
and you need to learn
how to trade elbows.
The resorbable plate
is experimental and risky.
But my medical judgment
is that it's worth it.
Make sure she agrees
and then get her prepped.
♪
Why me?
I'm not famous, I don't know
anything about medicine,
and giving the keynote speech
at your fundraiser
is a steep price to pay
for a beer-stained jacket.
You grew up in San Jose.
You went to San Jose State
despite being accepted
by both Princeton and MIT,
and you headquartered your company here,
despite huge tax breaks offered
by Chicago and Minneapolis.
And it was his favorite jacket.
Well, when I offered to have it cleaned,
he said not to bother because
he didn't even like the jacket.
- He was being polite.
- Polite?
I take it you've never been
to a game with him.
You did some homework, but not enough.
I love this city,
but I have giving speeches.
So don't give a speech.
Tell us a story.
Like the one you told at the wrap party
at the Youth Dance company's
fall musical...
the one where you got lost
at the Paris catacombs.
I stand corrected.
Your success is inspiring, Aiden,
as well as your loyalty to this city.
And the fact that you're young,
apparently very funny...
I'm in.
Actually, I was in
as soon as Aaron told me
what you wanted to meet about.
But I was curious what
your attack strategy would be.
So, how was it?
It was very effective.
♪
Now, don't worry.
He's been a model inmate for nine years
and tutors the other prisoners
in the library.
♪
Coke nail come in handy
up at Pelican Bay?
I make jewelry.
Helps me pick up the beads.
Is there a history of cancer
or liver disease in your family?
I went through this
a couple of months ago.
You have my file.
We need to do our own exam.
CLAIRE: And there's nothing
about your family
in previous records.
Are they still alive?
They're dead to me.
Quit stalling, or we'll
send you back right now.
I haven't spoken to anyone in my
family since I was 15 years old.
Last I know, uh, both my parents
were healthy enough
to kick the crap out of me
on a daily basis.
Any other questions?
Why do you want to do this?
Maybe I just like, uh,
cute nurses and bad Jell-o.
- Why do you care?
- We don't.
As long as you do what you're told.
Don't worry.
I'm very good at following orders.
Councilman Burns must be
very happy with his facelift.
He just bought another table
for the fundraiser.
I aim to please,
but you already knew that.
And I need to get into surgery,
so stop being so coy.
What's up?
You and Isabel always seem very happy,
able to manage both your
professional and personal lives.
I'm flattered you think so,
but still a bit coy.
When I met with Aiden Coulter
about being our keynote,
I thought there was a spark.
Okay, so now we're getting somewhere.
Surgery can wait a few minutes.
Is it... unprofessional of me
to explore it?
He's not a hospital employee,
but potentially
a significant donor and...
younger.
Quite a bit.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know, maybe I'm
just imagining something
that doesn't even exist.
Oh, I doubt that.
You're an attractive, smart,
interesting woman.
I'm sure there was a spark.
But you can't date a donor like Coulter.
Sorry.
There's no actual policy against it.
I'm not talking policy,
I'm talking optics.
The last thing you want
is someone thinking
you'd use sex to get a big donation.
It's a double standard, I know,
but it's the world we live in.
I said no! I don't want it!
I thought you gave him
something to calm him.
We did, but he's too agitated.
I'm gonna start him on IV midazolam now.
Eric... Eric, remember what Dr.
Park said earlier about focusing?
I know you can do that.
How about we get those earbuds
you had earlier?
No! Leave me alone!
Eric! Stop it.
Look at me!
Do not move.
♪
SHAUN: You wear very stylish clothes.
Um, thank you.
I assume you mean
when I'm not in surgery.
Yes. Do you think people
believe you're a better doctor
because of that?
Some people.
Others probably just think
I'm a show-off or arrogant, gay.
I don't care. I do it for myself.
You look good, you feel good.
Does it help you make friends?
Feeling good about yourself
helps with everything.
Do you know where I can buy
a stylish tuxedo?
I can pay $2.000.
Okay.
Dr. Reznick says
if I want people who matter
to help my career,
I need to wear a tuxedo that
costs $2.000 to the fundraiser.
Have you talked to Glassman about this?
No. I make my own decisions now.
Murphy, people who matter
will help your career
because they're impressed
with your talent
and potential as a surgeon.
And I could send you to my tailor,
where you'll definitely spend two grand.
But my advice would be just rent one.
Make sure you get fitted by the manager,
and for a couple-hundred bucks,
you'll be fine.
♪
I'm gonna need you to count
backwards from 10.
10. 9. 8...
♪
MELENDEZ: Looks like you were wrong.
PARK: I said he'll do anything
to convince us to trust him,
to let our guard down.
His eyes, they're swelling up.
♪
So is his tongue. He's having
an allergic reaction.
Stop the anaesthesia.
Give me 0.5 MGs epinephrine I.M. now.
I'm on it.
[MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Epi's in.
- He's hypoxic.
We need to intubate. Getting a 5.0 tube.
Now!
♪
[COUGHING]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
You had a severe allergic
reaction to the anaesthesia.
We had to intubate you
and give you steroids.
You didn't do it?
JARED: We can't operate on you
if you can't breathe under anaesthesia.
You did everything you could.
The patient's parents wanted you to know
they're extremely grateful
for everything you did.
Or tried to do.
You can try again.
I'm sorry, we can't.
No, you try again.
Okay? Try again?
[RESTRAINTS CLINK]
You try again.
Try again!
PRISON GUARD: Calm down!
Try again! Try again!
PRISON GUARD #2: He said calm down! Now!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
Same old, same old, yeah?
That's the way it's always been for me.
Nothing I ever...
♪
He's still on the top of the UNOS list,
and we're gonna be calling and rechecking
every registry and database all night.
♪
How long do we have?
Without a new liver, maybe a day.
So, what'd you get... Hugo Boss? Armani?
SHAUN: Dr. Andrews said
I should just rent one.
And you're gonna listen to him?
He's the Chief of Surgery.
And he knows about clothes.
If Andrews had a son,
you think he'd let him
go to an important event
in a cheap rental tux?
He said people who matter
judge people based on their talent.
Yeah, that's what he tells
someone else's kid.
To his own, or someone he actually
respects, he tells the truth.
Cut here.
Do you respect me?
You're smart, able to memorize
a ton of information, but...
no, not really.
Suction the mediastinum.
You've certainly put a lot of thought
into what someone you claim not
to respect wears to a party.
Just because I don't respect him
doesn't mean I don't like him.
Everyone's uncomfortable in fancy clothes
and hates kissing up to bigwigs
at a fundraiser.
But they do it.
They don't cower at home alone.
You use your autism as a crutch.
Okay, I think if you liked him
any more, he'd have a black eye.
Make sure we're clear on that side
and the aorta isn't kinked.
The aorta isn't kinked.
Good.
Now for the moment of truth.
Position the plate.
♪
Perfect fit.
What the hell?
What'd you do?
I don't feel nothing.
No, don't touch him.
If he can't control his bladder...
He can control himself just fine.
Nice try, but the vacation's over.
Stand up.
Re-check his cuffs first.
You're getting changed, and we're going.
Just take him like he is.
I'm not gonna get stuck in the van
for the next three hours
with him like that.
Watch his hands! Watch his hands!
Put the gun down now!
You shoot me, he dies.
Now, no one is shooting anyone.
Everyone stay calm.
Give him space.
You did something good, Boris.
Don't ruin it now.
I did nothing, yeah?
I accomplished nothing!
Whatever happens next
is completely in your control.
You have power, but it's not unlimited.
You're not gonna escape,
you're not just walking out of here.
But there are things, concessions,
that could make your life better.
So let's just take our time and talk.
There's no rush.
What do you want, Boris?
What do you really want?
I don't want anyone to help me.
Whatever you call it,
these life-saving measures.
I... No.
No.
Do not do it.
Don't listen to her. It's your choice.
You do what you want.
Yeah.
Boris, no!
[GUNSHOT]
[RESTRAINTS RATTLE, THUD]
♪
Let's go! Let's go! Move! Move!
Melendez is en route.
♪
All right, ready? Let's go.
3. 2. 1.
Page urology and cardio-thoracic stat.
He's dead and he has a donor card.
We're gonna take everything
he can donate.
♪
["EVERYDAY" BY NVDES PLAYING]
♪ Our love was hard to maintain,
so we broke it ♪
♪ Mmm
♪ But your smile reminds me that
I cannot lose all of you ♪
♪ So can we can we laugh
about being crazy? ♪
Thank you so much.
Your speech was perfect.
And hilarious.
Oh, you're very welcome.
And I appreciate the opportunity
to help change my rep.
You have a rep?
All work and no play.
Something I'm working on changing.
Your rep or your lifestyle?
I need less stress and more fun.
♪
Would you like to play golf sometime?
On a real course with actual grass.
Absolutely.
Would you like to dance?
I'd love to.
All right, let's go.
♪ Like it's true
♪ So can we laugh about being crazy? ♪
We need to get Eric prepped right away.
- What's happening?
- Did you find a new liver donor?
Actually, it's... it's the same one.
The circumstances have changed.
This is incredible.
No, I don't want it.
Eric, when the donor found out
that he couldn't do
the surgery to help you,
he became incredibly sad
because he wanted you to live
more than he wanted to live.
He ended his life so that
you could have his liver.
He... He knew he'd done some bad things,
and I think that this was
the only way he knew
how to make amends.
I think we should try and help him.
Do you think you can do that...
help someone do something good?
♪
Yeah.
Everything looks good good.
Remember to take deep breaths
so you don't develop
any lung complications,
and, obviously, avoid
lifting anything too heavy
for the next few weeks.
I...
What, honey?
I want a hug.
♪
["SMOOTH SAILIN'"
BY LEON BRIDGES PLAYING]
♪
♪ Over the horizon,
she's smooth sailin' ♪
♪ These concrete seas
- JESSICA: Wow.
- ♪ Now she's headed
You look like a million bucks.
No, it cost $2.368.
Well, it was worth every penny.
Good investment.
Glad to see you're treating yourself.
You deserve it.
How much did you dress cost?
I don't remember.
And just so you know,
that's not the best question
for an event like this.
Why not?
I don't know. It just isn't.
Okay.
Can I buy you a drink?
I don't like tequila anymore.
It makes me vomit.
Well, okay. They have other choices.
A glass of wine or a soda?
No, thank you.
Uh, that's a partner at a firm
that did some pro bono work
for us last month,
so I have to go thank him.
Okay. Bye.
♪ I won't wear you down
♪ No, honey, I won't
♪ Wear you down
♪ She's smooth
Hello.
- [CHUCKLES]
- ♪ Smooth sailin'
♪ Smooth sailin'
♪ She's smooth
♪ Smooooth, darling
♪
There you are.
And nicely done.
You got the look.
Now you got to put it to use.
There's work to do.
Mingle.
Okay.
I see you, Dr. Chen.
She runs the Rivington
Fellowship at the Mayo Clinic.
I wonder who brought her here.
I don't know.
Mingle.
You still think people can't change?
He didn't.
He's an assassin who
murdered people for money.
Today was just one more
cold-blooded killing.
You helped him sacrifice his life
so that he could save someone else.
I am not a fan of what you did,
even if it did prove...
He didn't sacrifice anything.
He died a long time ago.
His crew is probably gone.
In prison, he was a nobody.
And now? He lives on as a hero
to Eric's family, to the press, to you.
♪
[SIGHS]
Jaundice is improving.
Edema's resolving, too.
His vitals look good.
It's been great night.
Three other lives were saved, as well.
Does his parents know what he did?
I want to send them a card.
I know they're gonna be sad, but...
I want to tell them I'll take
good care of their son's liver.
I think that's a great idea.
♪
[LAUGHING]
["GOOD TIME" BY EARL ST. CLAIR PLAYING]
Wow.
This is impressive.
It's kind of like prom,
but without the acne.
[CHUCKLES]
And with a DJ that played
the MGM Grand last week.
Would you do me the honor?
♪ On the floor
♪ I bet you think you look cool ♪
Classy.
I brought my A-game.
♪ They don't play no more slow cuts ♪
♪ Everything is turned up
♪ I bet you think you look cool ♪
- ♪ Look cool
- ♪ Unh
♪ I'm not the one to rain on parades ♪
♪ But you in the club in some shades ♪
♪ What is goin' on now, a day
♪ Now a day
[MUFFLED] ♪ This is why
I stay in the house ♪
♪ I'm better off parked on the couch ♪
[MUFFLED CONVERSATIONS, LAUGHTER]
[MUFFLED MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Take a picture.
- Ooh, you look great!
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
♪ When I go out, go out
♪ Put on my Sunday best and show out ♪
♪ Show out
♪ I just wanna have a good time ♪
♪ Good time, good time
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ I just wanna have a good time ♪
The first little while is the hardest,
and then you move on.
You never did.
Well, that's true.
Doesn't mean you don't have to.
Maybe.
Thank you.
Well, what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna sit around and mope?
At least try.
How do I do that?
- I don't know.
- [CHUCKLES]
If I knew, I would have done it.
Let's dance.
Okay. That would be lovely.
♪ This is why I stay in the house ♪
SPIRIT: Don't be shy. You can't hurt me.
Look! I have a bionic sternum!
[LAUGHTER]
Ooh, you smell good, Jenny.
What is that... strawberry?
Strawberry mango.
It comes with a lip gloss.
I got it at the mall.
We can go together!
[LAUGHS] It's a plan!
Let's all go!
WOMAN: You know what,
let's take a selfie.
[YOUNG WOMEN ALL EXCLAIMING "YES!"]
That's a great idea. Bring it in.
Bring it in, guys! Closer!
- Peace sign!
- Cheese!
- [GIGGLING]
- [CELLPHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- Yay!
- Okay.
- That was so funny.
- [GIGGLING]
♪ This ghost of mine,
I hope that it follows you ♪
["TOUCH" BY SHURA PLAYING]
♪
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
- ♪ There's a love between us still ♪
- Remember this?
Should I?
[CHUCKLES]
You really don't remember?
No.
[SCOFFS]
What's wrong?
It's the song that played
during our first overnight
at the hospital.
♪ I wanna touch you, but I'm too late ♪
We had our first kiss to this song.
♪ I wanna touch you,
but there's history ♪
I'm sorry.
It's been a long day.
Yeah.
Jared, it doesn't mean anything.
Yeah, it does.
♪ There's a love between us still ♪
I love you, Claire.
You never loved me.
Now, I thought that maybe someday
that would change, but...
it won't.
♪ But I know I'm out of my mind ♪
Bye, Claire.
♪ There's a love between us still ♪
♪ But something's changed,
and I don't know why ♪
♪ Never felt so close,
but now I know it's over ♪
♪ And all I wanna do
is go home with you ♪
["SURROUND ME" BY LÉON PLAYING]
♪ The lights go down
♪ I want you around me
♪ Oh, oh, oh
♪ Ohh-oh
♪ Don't overthink it
♪ Just finish up your drink
♪ And surround me
DR. LEVY: I have 140
applications for fellows,
not one of them has a clue
how to write an...
Hello.
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
I'm a resident here.
♪ Surround me
I'm Dr. Jake Levy, surgical oncology.
Toby Yang, pathology.
May Curtis, ortho.
♪ Surround me
Okay.
Apparently I was wrong.
I told Dr. Murphy
he'd be fine renting a tuxedo.
Clearly, he chose not to listen.
[CHUCKLES] I'm sorry.
Don't be. You look fantastic.
What is it... Armani?
Yes, it cost...
Well, whatever you paid
for it, it was worth.
How's the golf game, Jake?
- Oh, same as always.
- Mm.
I know how that is.
You play golf, Murphy?
I have, but I don't like it.
[LAUGHTER]
None... None of us do.
You know what they say...
"Golf is a good walk spoiled."
[LAUGHTER]
Yes.
♪ Surround me
♪ So don't let me go
♪ No, don't let me go
♪ Surround me
♪