The timing was good.
I just got a job transfer, Gretchen
will start at a new school.
We're gonna start
a whole new life.
It's very exciting.
In college, my dad
majored in cheerleading.
That was a joke.
Gretchen's got
a great sense of humor.
I'm laughing
on the inside.
Soon you'll be laughing
on the outside, too.
Dr. Park.
Moebius syndrome
is a paralysis of the sixth and
seventh pair of cranial nerves.
The seventh pair
controls facial expression.
Luckily, in Gretchen's case,
we haven't found any
limitation to the sixth pair.
I'm a lucky girl.
We'll be taking two slivers
of muscle from your thighs,
along with their nerves
and blood supply,
and transplanting them
into your cheeks.
There'll be considerable
recovery time
before you'll be able
to smile at will,
maybe three months.
So, what do you say?
Are you up for this?
Can I sleep on it?
See what
I have to live with?
Nobody knows
when I'm joking.
Sorry, Dr. Andrews.
Yes, I am very up for this.
Okay, great. So unless
there are any other questions...
Do you want to be
a comedian?
People getting your jokes
must be very important to you
if you think
it's worth the risk
of dying
during elective surgery.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
I apologize
for Dr. Murphy.
He's still learning that
silence is the right choice
when you have nothing useful
to offer.
We are required to have an
honest risk/benefit discussion
with our patients.
We are giving
a lovely young girl a smile.
That's a simple equation.
Well, it's more than
the smile or the jokes.
She can't express
any emotions at all.
No one can tell
if she's happy or sad
or scared, anything.
She's never had
much of a social life.
Ever since her mother died,
she's been
completely withdrawn.
All I want to do is bring my
baby girl back into the world.
Don't worry, Mr. Milman, we're gonna
take great care of her, all right?
Lucy has a post-op infection
of unknown origin.
Infusing 900 milligrams
of clindamycin.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Have you been changing
your dressing?
Every day.
- Soaking it in clean, warm water?
- Yes.
Taking your antibiotics,
one pill, three times a day?
That's a no.
Lucy, I know I gave you
a scrip for antibiotics,
along with one
for pain meds.
Why haven't you been
taking your antibiotics?
Did you have a bad reaction
to them, or...
I never filled
my prescription.
I didn't think it was necessary
until it got really bad,
and then I was too weak
to go myself,
and I didn't have anyone
to pick it up for me.
Okay. Mystery solved.
I'm sorry.
I know it was stupid.
Very stupid.
Okay.
Hey, Shaun.
Oh. Hello.
I haven't seen you in ages.
What's... What's new?
I'm buying an apple.
I can see that.
Here, I'll get it for you.
No, thank you.
Thank you, Shaun.
What else is new?
You didn't want
to be friends.
Um, yeah, no, I... We... We...
We... We're colleagues.
You know, we're...
Whatever we are,
we can still talk.
We should talk.
I have a new friend.
Kenny.
Here you go.
Thank you, Debbie.
Kenny, huh?
That's, uh, that's great.
Do you have
a new friend?
No.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We can talk.
You know,
we can talk about sports,
we can talk about weather,
we can talk about...
Debbie?
Why would you want
to talk about Debbie?
Debbie was flirting
with you.
She was?
Yes. I noticed her exhibiting
two typical signs.
- Not the trifecta, huh?
- No, not the trifecta,
and one atypical sign.
I think she's just
trying to be friendly.
She gave you
an extra dollar in change.
And the fact that you didn't
notice means you like her, too.
Maybe she's just
bad at math.
My dad said that
you're on the spectrum.
That's why you said that about
people getting my jokes.
People always
get my jokes.
Then you're very lucky.
That was a joke.
I see what you did there.
Yes.
They call me
"Resting Gretch Face."
"Shaun the Moron."
Not very witty.
I'm obviously quite smart.
I drew this
to their attention.
I'm on a spectrum, too.
Somewhere between inscrutable,
unapproachable, and...
Actively scorned.
I don't want to be
more approachable,
and I prefer people
not reading my emotions.
They're mine.
That's what you do
with friends.
You really think
this surgery's too risky?
Possible complications
include embolism,
hemorrhage,
collateral paralysis,
asymmetry, brain damage,
and stroke.
It's also expensive
and medically unnecessary.
Okay,
look straight ahead.
There's a two-hour wait in the
E.R., and what are we doing?
Treating a woman because she
willfully ignored doctors' orders.
I know what a parasite looks
like, and it's not Lucy.
So this is
a Mom thing with you.
Growing up
with a whack mother means
that you can identify any and
all problem personalities.
And that is the sole upside to my
miserable childhood, thank you.
Well, at least
you had a mom.
Mine died
when I was six,
and Dad instantly married
a child-hating bitch
with a butt-load
of debt.
Morgan, I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you
to get sympathy.
Just that I know
parasites, too.
Got you booked first
thing tomorrow morning.
Dad.
What? Too soon?
It's...
You're nervous.
I get it.
If you have any more
questions, feel free.
I've changed my mind.
I'm not having
the surgery.
Murphy.
Hello.
Gretchen's father
is very upset.
It seems you talked her
out of the surgery.
No, I didn't talk her out
of it or talk her anywhere.
I just gave her the list
of potential risks.
Embolism, hemorrhage,
collateral paralysis,
asymmetry, brain damage,
and stroke.
Stroke?
Yes, there was a case
in Brazil in 2004.
and the patient suffer...
It seems
that you don't believe
that restoring this girl's
smile is that important.
Smiles are overvalued.
There are studies
that support that.
And there are studies
that don't.
When we smile,
we produce endorphins.
They make us happy. They
make other people happy.
When we see smiles, our
basotemporal lobes are activated,
and we duplicate
what we see.
Murphy,
smiles are contagious.
You see?
I feel good,
you feel good.
Everybody likes smiles.
I don't.
In any case,
your smile wasn't sincere
since it didn't demonstrate
the Duchenne Marker.
There was no involvement of the orbicularis
oculi muscles around the eyes,
which means you didn't
release endorphins.
You know,
if you can talk her
out of a surgery
she's wanted for years,
I'm pretty sure a conversation
with someone objective
can talk her
back into it.
Get Park, come with,
and keep quiet.
Okay.
Dr. Kalu.
Remember me?
"Fish girl"?
- Uh, hi. Celez. Hi.
- Yeah.
Yes, uh, of course I do.
I hope it's okay
that I requested you.
I'm glad you did.
How are you doing?
Oh, that's what
you're going to tell me.
I've been wearing the, uh,
tilapia skins for five months.
I'm getting really tired of being
followed home by stray cats.
How's the pain?
Compared to
what it was?
Nothing.
Uh, any... any fever,
itchiness, or swelling?
Nope.
Well,
it looks very good.
But?
How much longer?
Um, how do you feel
about tomorrow?
Seriously?
I never joke
about tilapia.
What's the matter?
I-I just wasn't
expecting that.
I...
I'm afraid of how
I'm going to look.
You're going
to look beautiful.
Tomorrow.
I know Dr. Murphy
informed you
about the risks
of this surgery,
and some risks are significant
and some just aren't.
This is as close to risk-free
surgery as we can get.
It'll give you a smile,
it'll let you laugh.
No.
Dr. Murphy didn't
talk me out of it.
He inspired me.
He helped me realize that this
could actually make me stronger.
I don't want
to run from it anymore.
Yeah, she's lying.
She's a smart,
sarcastic young woman,
not exactly someone who's prone
to inspirational stories.
Why would she lie
about changing her mind?
Well,
when I was a cop,
I had a lot of people change their
minds about testifying in court,
and it always came down
to one of three reasons.
Fear, confusion,
or they were paid off.
She doesn't seem confused.
And I don't think
she's afraid.
So Gretchen
was paid off?
I admit the analogy
isn't perfect.
It's close enough.
Guess who's back
in the E.R.
You're happy, so I'm guessing
it's a non-compliant patient.
You misjudged Lucy.
She made an honest mistake
forgetting her prescriptions.
You called her,
didn't you?
She didn't spontaneously
remember, you had to remind her.
Is that
a Mom thing, too?
Gretchen, are you worried that your
dad can't afford this surgery?
The insurance company
is paying for it.
Dad...
I know it isn't.
It's elective.
It's medically unnecessary.
No one can put a value
on your smile.
Not bullies, not an insurance
company, not even Dr. Murphy.
In my opinion, this surgery's
medically necessary.
Gretchen, sweetie...
My first memory
of your mother
was of her smiling at me
from across the room.
And because of that smile,
we ended up with you.
And... And my last
memory of her
is that radiance
lighting up the world
one last time.
I mean,
we never had much money,
but as long
as I had that smile,
it didn't matter.
I love you, Dad.
And that's why I can't let you
give up everything for this.
Lucy Callard?
I'm here.
Um,
Lucille Elizabeth Callard?
Yes, that's me.
A Dr. Browne called me
to pick up my prescriptions?
You're the victim
of identity theft, Lucy.
There's an impostor using your name
and medical ID to get benefits.
Did you have your purse
stolen recently?
Six weeks ago.
And you had your driver's license
and credit cards replaced,
but not your
health-insurance card?
Is this why the pharmacy refuses
to fill my prescriptions?
I'm on pain meds
for post-herpetic neuralgia.
It's getting really bad.
Once the impostor filled her
prescription for pain meds,
the pharmacy
must have thought
you were
overfilling opiates.
Oh!
It always flares up
when I get upset.
Don't worry, Lucy,
we'll get you your meds.
We... We can't.
We're already treating
"Lucy Callard."
Nice game, Tony.
Hi, Jim.
- Marcus, hey. You coming or going?
- Neither.
15-year-old girl
with Moebius Syndrome.
Your company
denied coverage.
No respiratory issues, deformities,
pain, she doesn't even drool.
She's fully functional.
She can't smile.
That's a function.
Marcus,
I think it's wonderful
you want to give
this little girl her smile,
but if we pay for everything
wonderful, we'll go bankrupt, huh?
And then
who are we helping?
We all know doctors cheat
diagnoses to get coverage.
"Deviated septum"
gets you a free nose job,
"migraine"
gets you Botox.
Do you really want me
to play that game?
This isn't a game
for me.
We're a reputable company
with very high standards.
Very high bonuses that get even
higher with your denial rate.
I was gonna
suggest we end this
before we say something
we'll regret,
but I believe
that just happened.
Gretchen's socially isolated,
depressed,
and that's only
gonna get worse.
What if she slashes
her wrists?
You'd prefer
to cover that?
Are you threatening me
with a teenage girl's suicide?
And God forbid
something does happen to her,
'cause I'll make sure that this
conversation's part of the permanent record.
Dr. Andrews said
smiles are contagious,
and I'm testing
that hypothesis.
Well, I'm not sure your study
will prove anything.
It might have
something to do
with the lack
of the Duchenne Marker.
Oh, yes.
But here you go.
That wasn't a smile.
Sure it was.
I want to show you
something.
You need to follow me.
Okay.
The impostor has poisoned the
real Lucy's medical record.
We have to go through
every medication,
every notation, every test
to determine whose is whose.
Doing that with zero tolerance for
errors could take six months.
Well, the paperwork
is our problem, not hers.
Not if the confusion results in a harmful
treatment or incorrect diagnosis.
Well, we have to
do something.
This woman
is in serious pain.
So we treat her.
Just be clever about it.
Shaun.
Shaun, I've already
had two iced coffees...
Debbie. Hello, Debbie.
- Shaun...
- You flirted with Dr. Glassman.
Oh, my God.
'Cause I have a new friend,
and he needs one, too.
- I'm so sorry.
- Okay. Look, Dr. Glassman,
Debbie's facial proportions
are close to optimal, okay,
.38 vertical
and .48 horizontal...
I'm so sorry.
...so you should find her
attractive.
Thank you?
Shaun...
I'm so sorry.
And I think
you're both Jewish.
Tribal commonality is highly
conducive to social bonding.
Shalom?
Bullies can't put a value on
your smile, nor can Dr. Murphy,
but it seems
the insurance company can.
They've agreed to pay
$43.750.
about 85%
of the entire cost.
I can cover
the rest of that.
I swear.
Oh, sweetie, please,
let me do this for you.
Okay.
"Jane Doe"?
That's the only way that we
can treat you right now.
Go home
and get some rest.
The records department will
call you to sort all this out.
A year ago,
I was playing tennis.
And then
the shingles hit,
and I was laid up
for six weeks,
and I've been
on pain meds ever since.
I lost my job, my husband
treats me like I'm an old lady,
and my daughter
thinks I'm too medicated
to be around
the new baby.
Maybe I'll be better off
as "Jane Doe."
The impostor returns.
Lucy? Lucy, can you
squeeze my fingers?
"Lucy"?
She's in septic shock.
Order a lactate level,
blood cultures,
and a broad-spectrum
antibiotic.
I'll tell Melendez we've
initiated Sepsis Protocol.
We should report her.
She's a criminal
and a flight risk.
And very, very sick.
We should put someone
outside her door
and arrest her
when she's stable.
We don't report patients
we find with drugs
or non-violent people
with guns.
We do report people
who steal from us.
What would happen
if people who needed our help
thought they would
be arrested?
If they thought they would be
arrested for stealing an ID,
maybe they wouldn't
steal an ID.
I don't remember anything
in the Hippocratic Oath
about checking payor sources
before treatment.
Strongly suggesting there was no health
insurance in 4th century B.C., Greece.
We have
a duty to treat,
and we have the right
to get paid.
But first things first.
Oh, God, I really
do not want to be sued
by either one
of these women.
Maintain the pretense.
And as soon as she's stabilized,
we're gonna press charges.
Dr. Park,
pull the muscle, please.
We don't want any excess
gathering in the suture line.
Thank you.
Okay,
remove retractors.
Ready?
Are you sure you don't want
something for the pain?
No. No, I'm good, as long
as you keep talking to me.
Especially if you share
something, uh, very painful.
- Painful?
- Mmm.
Okay...
Like the time
I mistook my biology teacher
for my girlfriend and picked
her up in the hallway?
Yeah, twirled her around
three times
before I realized
my mistake.
That kind of painful?
You may have to dig
even deeper than that.
How about
the time I finally found myself
in the perfect situation?
You know, work,
friends, future,
something
I never really had before.
Maybe that's why
I screwed it up.
You're not responding to the
antibiotics like we'd hoped...
Lucy.
You know, don't you?
When the real Lucy Callard
showed up,
it kind of
gave you away.
Is there anyone
we can contact?
Do you have
any children?
A son.
But he'd be
so ashamed of me.
Where is he?
College...
First one in our family.
I had to choose between
premiums and tuition.
Your son is very lucky
to have such a loving mother.
I just wish
you got your antibiotics
when you got
your pain meds.
I didn't get
either medication.
Are you sure?
Because the real Lucy was having
problems with the pharmacy.
I didn't want to risk
using the card again.
Is she okay?
Maybe it's time
to move on,
take the lesson with you,
find new friends.
I went to Denver
for an interview last week.
And?
And... We're done.
Really?
Take a look.
Hey, trust me.
See? Beautiful.
The kid, college, it's just
a convenient sob story.
Why would she lie
if she may be dying?
Here's what we don't know
about fake Lucy,
whether her story
is true.
Here's what
we do know.
She's a liar who just
found out she's busted.
Speaking of lies,
that shingles virus that
the real Lucy had last year?
According to Dr. Spindler
at Santa Clara General,
she had it
the year before, too,
and according to Dr. Millhouse at
SF Muni, the year before that.
She wasn't denied the pain
meds because of our impostor.
She was denied because she
is a garden-variety addict.
Well-played, sir.
Dr. Park says
the surgery went well.
It's been too long.
What has?
She should be breathing
on her own by now.
Even after
prolonged anesthesia,
it should only take
60 to 90 minutes.
Is she okay?
She should have
protective airway reflexes,
motor activity,
and a return of consciousness.
I need to page
Dr. Andrews, STAT.
What's going on?
Something bad.
Gretchen's glucose
is within normal limits
and her electrolytes
are also normal.
And we've ruled out hyper-
and hypothermia.
It doesn't leave much.
What about hypoxia?
Uh, she maintained
normal oxygen,
as well as end tidal CO2
throughout the entire case,
and we've given
reversal agents,
which we will repeat.
Do you feel bad?
It's okay.
You told them
it was close to risk-free.
They knew there were risks,
and I told them, too.
Get a CT. Rule out clots,
hematoma, bleeding, and stroke.
WBCs and lactate
are rising,
O2 sat and MAP
are falling.
The Sepsis Protocol
isn't working.
Multiple Organ Dysfunction Syndrome.
Medications?
Another antibiotic,
ah, continue crystalloids,
- increase her vasopressors?
- Low-dose steroids?
Give 'em all at try, and
intubate her and insert a swan.
And, yes, I understand
this is out of our own pocket.
Um, do anything exciting
for Purim?
Purim. Uh, no.
Yeah, you know, the usual.
Mmm.
Ate a little matzah,
and celebrated
our exodus from slavery,
which I think is Passover
and not Purim.
The truth of the matter is,
I'm only half Jewish,
so only
half the knowledge.
The truth is
I-I'm not Jewish at all.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
Yeah,
my first husband was.
So I guess we have our lack
of Jewishness in common.
You know what, Debbie?
I think I-I should get going.
Okay. Well, it was...
It was nice, uh, finally
meeting you, officially.
Same.
Oh, no,
look at that!
A 1975 300D,
one of the most
perfect Mercedes ever
just got
a little less perfect.
I beg to differ. If you're
looking for perfection,
you look no further
than the 1967 280SE.
Cabriolet or coupe?
The coupe,
an all-time classic.
Well, an owner of a 300SL
Gullwing might argue otherwise.
- A Gullwing?
- Yeah.
Can I get you
another coffee?
Yeah.
Iced, large, black.
- That's it.
- I know.
That's a little bit
unsettling, Murphy.
Okay.
Why are you studying the current
of ions during electrolysis?
Uh, it's not the chemical
kind of transference.
It's the
doctor-patient kind.
I'm dealing with
a personal situation.
I don't think
the Internet is very helpful
for solving
personal situations.
True.
But I can't exactly ask
Claire for her advice,
and I barely know Park,
and Morgan...
Morgan would be bad.
Very bad.
I'm a person.
Yeah. No, no.
Yeah, of course, Shaun.
I'd, uh,
I'd love your advice.
Okay.
Uh, so I think Celez,
my burn patient,
has feelings for me,
and I...
...may have feelings
for her, too.
But there's a good chance
her feelings aren't real,
and if they are real, then
they may not be permanent.
Uh, you know, it's kind of
textbook transference.
She's grateful
and she's vulnerable.
And all I've ever known in my
life is unrequited love...
...from Claire
and from my parents.
And that makes me
vulnerable, too.
You should
call in sick.
Lea says calling in sick
is all you need
to gain superior wisdom
and knowledge.
She was right.
The CT showed
no abnormalities,
and the reversal agents have
been repeated without effect.
So what else
could it be?
Anoxic brain injury, a
complication of anesthesia.
Unfortunately,
we believe...
...your daughter
is brain-dead.
What?
All for a smile.
I made her think she wasn't
good enough the way she was.
I should've listened
to you.
Yes.
There's just no predicting how
individuals will react to anesthesia.
Yeah.
Park! You just walked out
on that man.
The last thing
a grieving family member needs
is to see
their doctor tap out.
Maybe she's still
under anesthesia.
Succinylcholine.
It was one of the anesthetics
Gretchen was administered.
- Yeah.
- Now, what if she has
a Plasma Cholinesterase
Deficiency?
It'd mean her body couldn't
break down that specific drug.
Complete deficiency
is extremely rare.
I've never
personally seen it,
and I don't know anyone
who has.
Yeah, but if she does have it,
she's just gonna wake up.
Should I tell
the father?
No, not yet.
No way we're letting him
grieve twice.
Your labs
are not improving.
Your organs
are shutting down.
You're running
out of time.
I'd like to stop
calling you "Lucy."
You're welcome...
Beatrice.
What are you doing?
Corneal reflex.
It's mediated by the nasociliary
branch of the ophthalmic branch.
What does it mean?
It means we were wrong.
She's gonna be
just fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
Thank you... Oh.
Thank you, Dr. Murphy.
Honey,
you're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be
just fine.
I was drawing a bath, and I
leaned over to turn it off,
and I dropped
the pill bottle,
and before
I could fish it out...
All the pills were ruined.
So you need a refill.
My pain has made me
so clumsy.
Lucy, you're a liar
and a cheat
and an addict.
We know about
the frequent prescriptions,
the multiple doctors, and the
ever-recurring shingles.
You have
a serious medical problem.
Let me help you.
Three months?
Hopefully.
But we might
be able to give you
a pretty good idea of what
you're gonna look like.
Those things by your ears
are neuro-stimulators.
When we activate them,
instant smile.
Sound good?
Dr. Murphy.
It's your mother's smile.
She seemed like
a good template.
There is
no Duchenne Marker.
Her smile is not real.
Thank you. Thank you.
But all the other ones are.
All the other ones are.
I spoke
with Jim Ransler,
who made it very clear that
we owe him big time for this.
Don't worry, Marcus,
I can handle him.
I'm very impressed.
It was all
very presidential of you.
You really went
above and beyond.
Yes, I did.
I thought
I was saving her life.
Instead,
I nearly ended it.
Celez, hi.
This is the brilliant
Dr. Murphy.
He'll be assuming your care
from here on,
though I don't expect
you'll need much.
I understand.
I don't think you do.
You see, doctors aren't allowed
to date their patients.
What are you
doing tomorrow?
Uh, I'm calling in sick.
I think you may still have
some friends here.
I guess there is one upside
to all this.
If she hadn't bought
the stolen insurance card,
the real Lucy wouldn't be
in rehab right now.
Surprisingly nice.
I told her what she needed
to hear to get help.
Trust me, I get it.
Too soft, people take
advantage of you.
But with your
badass upbringing,
no one messes with you.
Upsides everywhere.
You have way more street cred
than, say,
someone whose mom's
a Johns Hopkins cardiologist,
whose dad's
a pathologist,
and whose parents have been
happily married for 37 years.
Coming from privilege,
zero respect.
Must be really hard
to overcome.
- I'll call a code.
- No.
There's nothing left
to save.
Time of death, 8:14 p.m.
I'll notify her son.
Oh, hey.
Um, my homies
decided to pop by
and, uh,
play some Texas Hold'em,
so I'm gonna have to take a
rain check on that pizza night.
You got
a 70-inch flat-screen, too.
Uh, no.
I borrowed yours.
Makes no sense for us both
to have one, right?
Plus homies got to watch
March Madness.
- Okay.
- Oh, um, sorry, amigo.
It's four-player
Texas Hold'em.
I don't like poker anyway.
Hey, Shaun.
Look, you're a great guy,
um, but you got a few,
like, quirks, you know?
And that...
It doesn't really...
...jive with
this kind of face time.
You get what I'm saying,
right?
I love you, man.
I once drove a 300SL...
Thank you.
A 300SL Gullwing.
On the road?
No. For 200 feet
at the Concours d'Elegance.
Oh, in Pebble Beach.
That's just as cool.
The car show,
you know it.
Of course, yeah.
This year, they're featuring
a Rollston Coachwork display.
Including the Mercedes SS?
- I don't know.
- Ah!
But we should find out.
Do you want to go?
I couldn't.
Yeah, no, I...
Why?
No reason.
I just... I just thought
that I should make that my first
response before I accepted.
Can I get you
anything else?
No, thank you. We'll
just take the doorstop.
I'm sorry. Um, well...
Well, you can bring
the doorstop.
Aaron?
Sorry. Um...
The thing...
The thing... The thing...
The thing that... That...
That t-tells you how much
to pay, the... The doorstop.
Could you call a...
Can you call
an ambulance, please?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Thank you.
Subtitles by explosiveskull