♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Continue chasing, who’s glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 39]
I am sorry, Boss. I am not in the right frame of mind lately.
I am the worse in the training progress. I will go into the introspection room for 2 hours to do some soul searching.
I will work harder.
The thing that we are concern about finally occurs.
Not everyone can keep their mindset at their best.
Even If one person is not doing well, the entire team feel bad about it.
Since as a member of the K&K Team, no one will feel better about this.
The closer as we get to the competition,
all the problems and difficulties surfaced.
What comes next is the truly most challenging part.
[K&K ESPORTS CLUB]
Do you want to eat something?
No need. I don't have any appetite.
Your rankings have been released?
The elimination rounds are really scary.
Especially this kind of internal elimination.
You've been eliminated before?
I didn't. But we had over twenty member on our school's S&M Computer competition team, we also went thru this kind of elimination process.
Of course, for us, it was because of the difference between our grades.
But, although at the moment that you win, you feel really happy,
you also really agonize for the classmates that lost.
As to these substitute players,
some tried for their whole life and may not even get into the competition.
It's quite regrettable for them.
This is the beauty of professional league and it's also the brutality of it as well.
A single's general's reputation is made out of ten thousand corpses.
Moreover, if you want to represent Chinese teams to compete,
You need to beat ten thousand other domestic players.
It's about time now.
Then I will go to broadcast studio to watch it, so I wouldn't disturb you.
Right now, in my hands,
is your scores for these past two week's,
also your server's ranking.
These two are the basis of your score.
Actually, following these numbers,
basically we can determine the members who will participate this time.
But I want to give the last three places an opportunity.
One last fight, the last chance.
Boss, what do you want to say? Just say it directly.
I'm about to die from nervousness.
That's right. Give it to us quick.
Do you want to know your own rankings?
Boss, don't say it yet. Save some suspense.
Otherwise it's not interesting while we are competing.
Right, don't tell us just yet.
Alright, then besides Dt,
everyone think of yourselves as the last place.
Let's have a one on one, all against me.
-What?
- No way.
Boss, your the top dog. We will all lose if we go up against you.
-Are you scare?
- We are not scare.
Mainly is because if we all lose, how do we figure it out then?
Then stop the nonsense talk, compete base on reverse engineering, okay?
- I agree.
That works.
I have no objection at all.
Good luck. I won't disturb you guys then.
Alright. One by one. Who wants to go first?
I will go first. The sooner I die the sooner I can be reincarnated.
Come.
[Gun vs Grunt]
Relax.
Who's going next?
[Gun vs 97]
It's all right.
-Next.
-I'll go.
[Gun vs. Buff]
This technique level is comparable to the captain's.
Nonsense. He's top four in rankings after all.
[ACCESS DENIED]
Who's next?
Why don't you go first?
Look how scared you are.
Come on!
[Gun vs One]
[ACCESS DENIED]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Demo.
Boss, If I'm the last place, don't scold me.
[Demo vs Gun]
Wow.
Wow
Congrats, you're second place from the bottom.
[Chosen candidate list. ]
Scared me to death.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
♫ Trying to find the one that is me ♫
♫ Nothing to hide, not be afraid ♫
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
♫ You’re walking away, begging to me ♫
♫ You found another way, I believe ♫
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
Take it easy.
It's fine.
It's all for the team.
Don't worry. It's said already. The team is more important than all else.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
I can understand you the most.
I got pull out in this exact way too.
- I understand.
- The hell you understand.
You think everyone's like you, doing some retiring performance?
Boss.
I am working right now.
Are you willing to resign to this?
No.
Keep working hard.
♫ You found another way, I believe ♫
The people that I bring out are never dumb.
You are only twenty. Bite down and be like Buff and play until thirty one.
There are four big competitions each year, which means there are four international championships.
11 years means that there are fourteen international championships waiting for you.
How does losing one matter?
Buff can play another two years before he has to retire.
If you lose to people who are newer than you then,
wait and see how I will take care of you.
Boss, I know. One year is enough.
In one year, I will take back my position.
-Then why don't go continue training?
-Yes.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
I'll get going.
Don't use your SP's style.
Here at KK, we want passion!
Fine. Passion it is. I'm off.
Hello. Your turn.
Scared me, I thought someone was going to retire.
Not that outrageous.
The children are still young. There are a lot of opportunities.
I've discovered that when you talk, it's like brainwashing.
Once you said it, I immediately accepted it.
That's because you haven't seen Ai Qing's skills yet!
Actually, according to the leaderboard,
you've confirmed the right players right?
And for the substitute players... you have to choose between One and Demo.
You're not foolish.
Then why did you have to hold a competition?
What matters most is not to talk them into it, but to have them convinced.
Everyone is in this field,
a live competition is better than any ranking.
Sister-in-law, did you buy this?
Right! I bought it!
Wait a minute! I'll come down and help!
What is it?
I bought a coffee machine. It's super expensive.
Why did you buy that? Don't we already have one.
That one isn't good. Can't use it for everyone.
Mine is the best! I'm coming!
Petty.
Let you guys see what this is.
What is it?
Let's take it out.
One, two, three!
-Slowly!
-Sister-in-law
The thing you bought is way too heavy!
It's a coffee maker
Bingo, it's a coffee machine.
Move the box over here.
How thoughtful! We needed a coffee machine this good.
Sister-in-law, you are so warm!
It's alright.
How much was this?
This... well, anyway, it's quite a waste of wealth,
but I bought it with my own money.
Where should we put it?
Put it...
This table is a bit small. How about we bring a bigger one?
-Okay!
-Okay.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Wait and see the powerful coffee machine!
Little Han, Did you set a date yet?
This Miss is really good. You got a good catch.
Auntie, in your eyes, do I seem unable to take care of my girlfriend?
Auntie is afraid your temper will scare away Miss.
Hurry and decide okay?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
You've brought all this, what do you want?
You'll know in a bit.
Help me grind some coffee beans.
Enough! Enough It's too much!
Leaving coffee beans out for too long will make it stale.
No worries, these kids can drink a jar.
-We can?!
It won't do.
-When do we drink that much?
-Let's see if this is enough.
It's enough for now.
Okay. Then I'll start grinding the beans.
No problem.
I'm about to show you something cool.
You got scared. This is used to aerate the milk.
Watch closely.
Afterwards is the last step.
Tada! Latte Art.
Cool?
Sister-in-law, can you give that cup of coffee to me?
This cup...?
Okay. Here you go.
Slowly! It's full.
Thanks Sister-in-law
Do you want some brown sugar?
No No, it'll ruin the art.
I'll say, this art is pretty.
You're just going to give it to him?
Yep, you didn't say you wanted it.
He wanted it, so I gave it to him.
-Sister-in-law.
-Sister-in-law!
I want one!
Me too!
I want one too!
Okay.
Sister-in-law, this latte art looks so good.
-You know everything!
-It's okay. Not really.
I want a pretty one!
Pretty one?
Okay, I'll make a few different styles.
Thanks Sister-in-law!
Sister-in-law I'm so jealous.
Wow! Sister-in-law. You got skills!
You're skilled!
So pretty.
-I want this one.
- this one.
- Take whichever you like.
This one is good.
-Thanks Sister-in-law!
-Thanks!
-You're welcome!
Then we'll enjoy it!
Okay. Come back if you want more.
Okay!
-Bye Bye!
-So fragrant.
This taste is good!
Do you want a cup?
If you're not tired, then make one for me.
Okay, then I'll make one for you.
Wait a moment!
It's done
Tong Nian
hello.
Wait! Why did you drink me!
You drank me already?!
WAIT! It's not me. I'm not a pig.
That pig is you. You drank yourself.
Tastes pretty good.
Stop drinking! The pig is deformed now.
What happens when you drink it all? The art will be gone.
After I drink it, you can make another one.
Then I'll make another one.
Don't drink anymore.
Make another one of yourself.
That's you!
Pig is you! Pig is Han Shangyan. Scowling Han Shangyan.
Do you consider this as Sister-in-law's confession?
All I can say is Sister-in-law's skills is too good.
In order to confess, she bought a coffee machine.
Sister-in-law is so romantic.
Do you want some?
-Thanks.
-No problem.
To everyone in our audience, Team SP,
about one minute ago has successfully defeated
Team LP from Australia.
Then, with this match victory, they have successfully advanced into our semifinals.
- Yes.
- Then this Saturday, which is tomorrow afternoon,
in Shanghai the semifinals will be underway.
Yes. Out of four teams, there are two teams from China.
Actually, the draw result we are most afraid of would be a meeting between K&K and SP.
Right, because that way it will lead to a national derby.
For the final seeing SP and K&K would be a fierce match of mighty opponents.
That's to say,
if the result of the draw leads to a match between them in the semifinal,
for us in the audience it would be very hard to take.
- To find out what will happen we still need to watch our follow-up with the situation of the draw.
- Right.
Let us look forward together to the follow-up of this draw result.
[PL 58 Asia Pacific semi-finals]
Look the drawing's started.
[K&K
GEAR]
[SP
VIPO]
[PL 58 Asia Pacific first semi-final]
[1. K&K]
[4. VIPO]
[3. SP]
[K&K v SP, VIPO vs GEAR]
So the drawings for the match ups is revealed.
It is Team SP VS Team K&K, and on this side it is Australia VS Thailand.
My Lord. So it's actually as we were saying before:
our stars will collide first.
It is equivalent to turning this semi-final into a early final.
I believe that the Chinese netizens are surely feeling that it is a great pity,
because both teams are the top strongest teams in China.
This way they'll have to battle first.
No matter which team in the end advances into the finals,
our Chinese netizens will feel it is a great pity for the other team that is eliminated.
If that's the case, anyway, we hope that our Teams SP and K&K
will give our audience a match to make history.
Let's see how it turns out.
Ah, this is too sad.
Semi-finals and it's China vs China.
Okay, enough.
Let's pack up and continue training.
I thought first and second place could be both China's.
Isn't there no show now?
Right?
Everyone just do your best. Don't forget that last time we lost to SP.
We are no longer what we were before.
Our team has new blood now. (T/N: New members who bring fresh ideas/ways of doing things)
Right, Buff?
That's right! Let's eat.
After we eat, we can train.
Then I'm done!
I'm full!
I don't have an appetite anymore.
Let's go!
Any thoughts?
-Yes.
-What thoughts?
Must win.
Don't you know the weather's colder now?
You still wore a shorts.
What is it? Not happy?
Are you feeling unwell or
do you blame me for sending you to Norway with your mom?
I wanted to find her myself.
Not that you gave me away.
Then why the long face?
I just don't understand.
The Chinese Regional Semi-finals are about to begin.
You're clearly busy, yet you're here with me to find Mom.
You're always putting others first.
When is someone going to put you first?
So many years, I haven't noticed
you've also grown.
You know how to take care of others now.
Maybe one day...
you will be so grown that you can take care of yourself
and secretly find a boyfriend.
Then seriously love a person.
You and him holding hands and enter church.
Do you know?
This is a happiness in my life.
Dad hopes that everyone I love
can be happy,
very happy.
I don't want to grow up.
I don't want to find Mom.
Time is merciless.
It never waits for anyone.
Go and accompany your mom.
She needs you more.
Study well there.
After the competition,
I'll go find you.
Dad, promise me.
You have to beat KK and take the championship.
You want to make it hard for Uncle Han?
No.
Only I hope that you can get the championship.
You're the world's best dad.
You're the first place dad.
You can handle and win anything and any situation.
-Take a bite.
I don't want to eat.
-Just one.
-No.
Give me some face.
I don't want to.
You don't want to give me face? Not even a little?
After you eat, Dad will play a game with you okay?
I don't want to play a game.
You don't want to play a game? Then what do you want to do?
I want to ... to find Mom.
You want to find Mom?
Then...after you eat, Dad will look for Mom with you okay?
I don't want to eat.
Then why do you want to find Mom?
I miss her.
Boss, time to eat.
Don't want to.
Boss, it's okay. Don't worry. We can beat SP.
Where did you see my worry?
Uh...I didn't say you were worried Boss.
I was talking about the little kitty! Look, how scared it is.
Kitty. Don't be scared.
How cute. Look Boss.
Time to eat Han Shangyan.
He says he doesn't want to.
Can you guys not all come tell me to eat?
I'm the manager.
I'm not an animal, what is there to worry about?
Go.
Sooner or later, we have to face it. It's the same.
I just didn't think it would be this fast.
Originally, first and second place could have been ours.
Kid, you're so arrogant.
We're finally on.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
[SP Gaming]
Didn't think we'd run into each other that fast.
I had hoped to and not hoped to run into them.
It's unfortunate.
Otherwise first and second place should have been China's teams.
I find the way you speak is more and more like Little Han.
Solo, I have a matter to speak to you about.
Then I'll head out first.
What is it?
There was a call from headquarters earlier.
What did they say?
You are the best captain in China.
You probably wouldn't lose right?
If you lose, then you aren't a good captain.
In other words, if this outcome is true,
you'll be changed for a better captain
to lead China's SP team.
Asia-Pacific Semifinals
Nian Nian are you ready?
I'm here.
What are you doing?
Yaya, my heart is beating so fast. I'm so nervous.
Actually mine is too. I'm really nervous.
- I'm asking you. Are you supporting K&K or SP?
- K&K.
Is your position firm?
Say this together with me.
K&K up in the sky and on the ground as one dragon (i.e. as one in coordination).
Thousands of troops and ten thousand horses rushing forward (i.e. a mighty force rushing forward).
K&K up in the sky and on the ground as one dragon.
A mighty force rushing forward.
Before, I was Team Solo's old fan. I liked Solo the best.
Did you know? Ten years ago, the way he led his team was so handsome!
As for Han Shangyan, he's on his own.
I'm Appledog's fan.
Wherever she is, is what I will support.
Agree.
SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP Fighing!
K&K up in the sky and on the ground as one dragon.
- A mighty force rushing forward. K&K up in the sky...
- SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP Fighing! SP...
K&K up in the sky and on the ground as one dragon. A might force rushing forward.
Let me tell you girls. If SP loses today,
then I will swallow both of your cheering sticks, okay? Thank You!
You're welcome.
She wants to swallow our cheering sticks, why did I say "you're welcome" to her?
Ugh, really.
Yaya. Give me your lipstick for a second.
Today's condition is pretty stable.
Sister-in-law why are you walking backwards?
One, two, three.
KK Fighting!
Tong Nian made me draw it.
We almost rapped in the bathroom in competition.
So we could only draw this.
I'm just happy you guys are here.
Take it off, what if you get allergies?
No way. My lipstick is good, we won't get allergies.
Why are you smiling? Aren't I cool with this?
Hard-core fan at a glance.
Whatever you like.
You're going into the stands and not to the VIP seats?
Of course I'm not going! The atmosphere is good, I want to stay there.
As long as you're happy.
You guys do well too! KK can do it! Fighting!
We'll win for sure! We'll win for sure!
Have to win!
Sister-in-law, if we win, what will you treat us to?
After winning? After winning, you can eat whatever you want.
Can you see? This is 6 year's savings.
Six?! Six?
Wait, we can't spend all her savings. Can't be that greedy.
In two more years, Boss will become an old idle uncle.
Our idle uncle has all grown up, too. (second part to what he said that's not spoken is should get married soon)
He's more anxious then us.
You gang of brats!
See how I will straighten you all up, one by one.
Okay. Come. We'll be playing in five minutes. Fighting! Cheer!
Fighting! Fighting!
Listen to me.
Although before, I once thought your way of celebrating
was very childish.
But today, I hope that I can help you guys.
Come. One, two, three!
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Actually, every time I see them fight, my feelings are especially complicated.
I want K&K to win, but I also want SP to win.
I know that kind of feeling.
Now Ou Qiang is the one of the only ones competing of the founding members of Team Solo.
Say, if he does not get first place,
doesn't that indicate that the former Team Solo lost?
Yeah.
We're about to start today's semi-final competition.
That's right. As the Asia-Pacific host for this competition,
we finally get to welcome the day where both sides are China teams.
I hope that Team SP and Team K&K can bring us
a wonderful match.
Alright, everybody. Give our two clubs some time,
and we will be back soon.
Are you good?
What are you referring to?
Whoever loses in this competition will be a heartache.
SP and K&K are both teams I like,
but only one can go to the finals.
This is practically battle royale.
Let's give them our blessings.
Do you want SP or K&K to win?
No matter who wins
its for the country's glory.
These two brothers, don't be nervous, I've prepared drinks for you guys.
Let the skills of the players decide the match.
-Shut up.
I'm here.
Han Shangyan.
God Gun.
Fighting!
Alright, welcome back, everyone.
Here it is the CTF Asia-Pacific Competition, and we are broadcasting live on site.
We want to thank Eastroc Super Drink for supplying our players with energy supplements.
Half an hour ago, the first semi-finals competition ended.
The winner from the other match was Australia's VIPO.
Now it's time to see who will represent China
Team K&K and Team SP.
Brothers, it's the last game
Let's show them what we got!
Listen to the team captain!
I would like to point out that this time K&K's team has a line up change.
They've added a rank 4 player called Buff.
After Buff joined the team, he gave Team K&K
a huge increase in combat power.
Exactly. So compared to the previous month's
national finals
these are two comparable teams.
Come on!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Husband, what did you go to do? Why are you only here now?
W-Who won?
It hasn't ended yet. Hurry.
I'm telling you, that client was annoying me to death.
If it wasn't for my coworker lending me this bike, I would've been late for sure!
-Quickly!
-Put it here?
It's so difficult to see this competition. Shouldn't have waited for you.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
What are you guys doing?!
-This is a public area!
-I don't care anymore!
The current results of the CTF Semi-final match between KK and SP is 1:1.
This next match will decide the game.
The last four nodes! There is still the last four nodes!
They've lost one! SP lost one node! DT has circumvented Hua Ti!
Beautiful! Lnin has also been blocked.
No, it's a trap! Bug has sacrificed Lnin!
For himself, he has blocked Grunt's seizure!
Bug has entered!
This is dangerous for K&K! Demo has found Bug's infiltration!
Bug is still hiding, he is still looking for vulnerabilities!
He has circumvented Demo too! Bug!
A pity, DT has seized him out!
It's the last node!
Four members of K&K are all defending!
Are they planning to let DT fight one VS five?
He’s passed! Three people were not able to capture DT!
Hua Ti has also been circumvented!
There's only All left! Beautiful! DT has ended the match!
Wow! Congratulations to KK for winning the Semi-finals!
WOW! WOO!
It's already ended.
Bro, bro who won?
K&K! K&K won!
K&K won! K&K won!
I want to see them cheer on the winners!
Wait for me!
Sorry.
-Yay!
-K&K.
♫ It's okay to just follow destiny's vastness together as we please ♫
♫ Now that my dream has fallen to this angle ♫
♫ All right ♫
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. We still have the opportunity to get third place.
Right.
Pull yourselves together.
♫ Your resolute gaze is always looking ahead ♫
♫ Pride, glory ♫
SP!
♫ Let's rush together to everything in this world ♫
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
I willingly admit defeat. Give it your all in the finals.
You too! Let's meet up again at the World's Finals competition.
Don't worry. Third place is definitely ours!
Right brothers?
Go, the audience is waiting for the winners!
Fighting! Fighting
♫ Reclaim your heart
Let us once again congratulate the winners KK!
Yes! Good! Woo!
Congrats KK and hope that they can fulfill China's wish
and expectations. At the Asia-Pacific finals tomorrow,
get a trophy for us!
Let's go! Go!
Let's go. Let's go. Hurry.
Hey Shu!
Han Shangyan, old friend.
On our turf, the trophy is ours.
After the competition, stay for a few days and relax. I'll host.
Still the same. So confident.
-See you at the competition.
You guys know each other?
Over ten years ago, when we hadn't met,
I was already competing against him.
your Boss, me, has never lost to him.
You can't lose face, understood?!
Don't worry Boss.
Let's go.
[Love luck: 1 star. Work luck: 1 star.]
What should I do?
The few people in K&K, in this period of time their horoscopes are all not very good.
Especially Han Shangyan. Looks like we don't have the opportunity of good luck to match.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at horoscopes.
I looked up everyone on KK's team.
Everyone? The five team members, Han Shangyan and my Xiao mi's?
All seven?
What does it say?
I don't know. I was just checking.
I remember my tarot cards came.
Let's see what the cards say.
I don't understand that.
I know a little.
Where are my tarot cards?
Can you not be so anxious?
Oh you don't know.
I saw the news.
K&K's competitor is the favorite team to win the championship.
Can't be relaxed.
I'm so nervous.
Don't be, think of it this way.
The front three can all enter the World Competition.
KK's already gotten the ticket to enter
nothing to worry about.
On the flip side,
SP is going to be on the line.
If they lose, then they won't have the chance to go to Worlds
I hope SP can enter Worlds.
If SP can't enter, Han Shangyan will be unhappy.
Right.
How am I going to sleep tonight?
Right? I can't sleep either.
So nervous.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫