♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 20]
If you're feeling upset, you don't have to reply to me.
I just worry about you because suddenly you disappeared just like Han Shangyan.
You don't need to be so nervous, and you don't need to explain yourself.
There's nothing I can't tell you.
I didn't become successful like Han Shangyan and the others.
In these last few years, I've just been at home.
You can continue competing.
You still have the capability.
I feel like something's wrong.
I feel the same as Han Shangyan.
I feel that once Team Solo is done, there is no point in staying.
That's exactly what I thought.
It seems you really understand me.
Therefore, you came back this time for Solo. Right?
I know Solo's been feeling guilty for the last few years.
Perhaps he'd feel better when I came back.
At the same time, this is for myself.
I wanted to try again.
This is sounding like an interview. Let's talk about something else!
I-I'm still extremely nervous when I talk to you.
Please understand me. It's because I like you too much.
No, no, not that kind of like.
I mean I like you as an adoring fan.
You don't believe me?
Honestly, I never thought I would have fans.
When Han Shangyan told me, I thought you both were trying to play an April Fool's joke on me.
No! I'll show you your fan community.
Your fan community has more than one hundred people.
You're teasing me.
No! These are all your diehard fans.
Although there aren't as many as Han Shangyan's fans, they're all completely loyal to you.
Look. Look.
Look! This fan celebrates your birthday each year by buying a cake and eating it herself.
It's her way of celebrating it for you. Also, she...
She has written you a thousand letters,
but never sent them to you.
And this person, she loves to travel overseas and she brings your photo to every place.
Then, she takes a photo with your photo.
Does that work?
Of course!
When you announced your return, everyone in the group cried.
Why did they cry?
Because we were excited! We finally heard news from you!
You didn't see how active everyone was in the group chat that day.
When we found out, we all cried! I cried, too.
I cried until my eyes got puffy like a peach seed. It was so ugly.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Look.
Do you want to talk to them?
[Mi Shaofei's Global Support Group]
Look. Here.
This one.
Go faster! Faster! Hit him! Hit him!
- Go, my idol! Quickly!
- Hit him!
Step on the gas! Hit him!
- I'm already stepping on it!
- Step on the gas and hit him!
After I clear that curve, you won't even be able to see my tail lights.
Almost at the finish line! Pass him! Pass him!
Good luck! Good luck!
Step on the gas!
So close.
Mi Shaofei, can you even do it?
- I thought you could win one for me.
- You do it then!
Let's go on the picnic. Forget this.
Let's go. Help me get the food.
Let's go, too.
I never thought I would ever see them play games together with my own eyes.
These folks were like gods in my eyes.
And now, they're acting like kids.
Yes, this is how happy they were meant to be.
Let's go.
- What?
- I used to bring my team members here to jog.
This is my first picnic here.
That thing on your neck must be a tumor.
You're such a mood-killer.
Not only can you jog here. You can fly a kite, go fishing, and blow bubbles.
Whoever ends up with you will be bored to death.
Mi Shaofei, is this really the first picnic he's ever been on?
This is his first time after I met him. I'm not sure about before that.
He's always thinking about others, and never thinks about himself.
Haven't you noticed that in K&K, aside from the members, every other person is elderly?
My guess is that he wants to take care of them.
- Start eating, babies!
- Time to eat.
You don't need help?
Almost done. Here, blow some bubbles.
I made it; try it.
I noticed that you eat food extremely quickly.
You don't even look at what you're eating.
You know, when cooking,
we put our hearts into every bite.
There is a lot of work put into it.
What's inside? Your love?
Do you know what I want to do the most?
Travel the world?
Then I don't know. Anyway, my dream is...
To compete and win the world championship, right? I even memorized it.
Actually, I want to tell you to please open your heart.
And to leave more space for yourself... and me.
Actually, what I want to do the most is what we're doing right now.
Try to imagine it.
We're the only two people standing here,
enjoying a relaxing afternoon and feeling the breeze.
Close your eyes, imagine it for a second.
There's a breeze, there are birds chirping,
the sound of the water,
and me holding your hand.
Bye-bye!
Remember, when you're free, we can hang out.
Focus on studying. Don't just think about dating.
Look! In the future, I'll always wear this.
- You like it?
- Of course, I like it.
But it's too long. I have to loop it around my wrist so many times.
It's fine to wear it as a bracelet. Just don't lose it.
How much is it? Was it expensive?
I bought it off a street vendor.
I still love it even if it's from a street vendor.
Get going.
Don't forget to hang out with me. Bye!
Just message me if you need any help.
I was very happy today.
- Bye-bye.
Look how happy you are, Sun Yaya.
Oh my god! I almost twisted my ankle.
It seems like you are more excited than I am.
- You're so bad!
- Are you happy?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Love you!
- So annoying.
I took a picture of the way you looked earlier like a crazy fangirl.
That's enough. Why? You want to make a video clip and put it on the website?
That's right! And show everyone what you look like right now!
Forget you!
- Seriously though, did you add your idol on WeChat?
- Yes.
- How do you feel?
When I was scanning his QR code, my hand was shaking!
Embarrassing!
Thanks, Brother Han!
Thank you!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Let's go! Go up for a look!
Go up and see what? You guys aren't afraid I'll leak out confidential matters?
Leak out what confidential matters? My skill in washing keyboards?
Or the color of my underwear?
Hurry up and go up. Lest Solo will think that I am trying to poach his players.
No, Old Han. In the future, can you stop being such a loner?
Contact us often.
Do you know what "Kill the donkey the moment it leaves the millstone," means?
(T/N: An idiom - getting rid of someone once the job is done.)
Mi Shaofei already finished his task for me. Why would I still contact you two?
The stuff you say! So unpleasant to hear.
You already have a girlfriend. Can you not learn to speak more like a human?
Don't talk to him anymore. Let's go!
Old Han, we're all in Shanghai. Let's get together often. Call us at any time!
Hurry and go up! Dawdling even when saying goodbye.
We're leaving!
- Work hard!
- Do well!
Charge! Whoever loses has to buy drinks!
Do you have them all?
Let's go hand in the exams.
Not missing any?
Nian Nian! It's Zheng Hui.
Zheng Hui!
Tong Nian, I heard your dad is the People's Hospital's authority on liver tumors. Is that right?
Yeah, what's wrong?
My mom's liver is not good.
She got examined at the hospital back at home, and they said she needs a liver transplant.
- So...
- Liver transplant?! A liver transplant means it is really serious.
I think... don't be anxious.
Don't keep your mom at that hospital anymore. Come to Shanghai.
Get her examined a few more times in case it is not like that.
- I'll send a WeChat message to my dad now.
- Okay!
But he might be in surgery right now, so I don't know if he will see it.
When he sees it, he will definitely reply to me. Don't worry!
Tong Nian, thank you!
Don't thank me. You're too polite.
Really, thank you.
Han family's eldest grandson was spoiled by his stepmother.
When I mention him to Uncle Han, Uncle Han gets so angry.
Do you know why?
To be honest, I don't have much contact with his family.
Originally, I also didn't understand,
but Yuejiao had that blind date with him.
But after I saw that child, I thought that he was a bit weird.
After, I thought I would go and ask around about him.
That's how I found out that when he was young, his mom passed away.
His dad remarried and got him a stepmother.
But not long after, his dad also passed away. Say, how pitiful is that?
The good thing is that his stepmother treated him well. She spoiled him like crazy.
But growing up, this child has been especially rebellious. He does whatever you don't want him to do.
No one could control him.
After graduating from university, he was set on starting a business, saying he wanted to start an internet club.
Oh right. Ask Nian Nian to find out more information about him on the side.
Let's not rush to make a decision.
There's no need. They broke up already.
That fast?
Right. This matter... Nian Nian was really hurt.
So, in the future, don't ever mention Little Han in front of her.
Okay.
Really.
Say, I really hope that this child wasn't cheating our Nian Nian of her feelings.
Should we go discuss with Grandpa Han?
No need.
Here, Sir!
Sir, don't take her's!
In here I still have twenty-something yuan, it's enough.
- I have a lot in here. Take mine, Sir!
- Okay!
- Take it!
- I'll use yours then!
It's really too bad.
I hope that this matter doesn't affect the friendship between our two families.
To be honest, Old Tong and I don't hope to find someone of a similar background or status.
We just hope to find someone who is good to Nian Nian, and that's enough.
Mom!
- You're back.
- Oh, Aunt.
Zheng Hui, this is my aunt.
Hello, Auntie. Hello, Auntie.
Zheng Hui, you've come? Quickly sit down!
- Where's Dad?
- Your dad is in the study upstairs!
- Then, I'm going to take him up to see Dad and ask about the situation.
- Go on!
Okay, thank you, Auntie. Then, I'll go up first.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
I'm telling you. Although Zheng Hui is from a poor family,
he is so well-mannered and his temperament is good.
The most crucial point is that he is motivated.
Look at how happy you are.
How come it sounds like you're praising your son-in-law?
Where?
You're not admitting it!
Young man, my recommendation...
It's best that you bring your mom to Shanghai and to our hospital to do further examinations.
Also, we are close by so we can take care of each other.
This way, everyone will be more at ease.
Okay?
[Dad, I forgot to tell you. His family is in a difficult spot financially.]
[His only family member is his mom. He even took loans to go to university.]
[Coming to Shanghai for an examination will definitely take more than a day to settle.]
[Staying at a hotel is too expensive.]
Young man, if your mom comes to Shanghai, I recommend that she comes directly and lives in our home.
- Uncle, that's not good. It's too much.
- Listen to me, youngster.
You and Nian Nian have been college classmates for so long.
Besides, you guys have competed together before.
Your mother is coming here and is unfamiliar with Shanghai; we should help you.
Classmate love, isn't that right, Nian Nian?
Just listen to my day and let Auntie stay with us.
Besides, when she comes, she won't be here for long.
If she really needs surgery, then she will stay at the hospital.
If she doesn't need it, then treat it as our way to thank you
for helping Nian Nian when you went to compete abroad.
Let your mom come to Shanghai as a vacation.
That's right. When I got sick at the ACM competition (International Collegiate Programming Contest), you were the one who looked after me.
This time, I get to help you.
Thank you, Uncle! Thank you, Uncle!
No worries. Then this will be the plan.
Okay. Then sorry to bother you!
No worries.
I have no problem with your wife returning earlier than planned.
But you should at least give me half a month to transfer the work.
There's no problem.
This time your stepmother is getting remarried. Do you have plans to bring your girlfriend with you to attend?
I have no time to worry about this.
Bring her quickly! We want to see Sister-in-Law!
You got married earlier, so you want all men in the world to follow your footsteps?
Boss, we want to see her, too!
Exactly! The few of us here have accompanied you to start a business.
Do we not have the right to see your girlfriend for a bit?
We will prepare a big present for Sister-in-Law.
Come on! Do you not want to show us your girlfriend until you're married?
Come on! Show us! Show us!
We just started not long ago. I'm still not used to it yet.
Stop making a fuss! Once it's settled, I'll definitely bring her over.
Okay, you said it. Remember not to switch her out.
- I said it.
- Then, we'll see you when you come back.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye!
Auntie, this way.
Zheng Hui's mom is here!
- You've arrived!
- Hello!
I've really troubled you guys too much with the examinations and living in your house.
Oh, you're being so courteous. Our children are good friends.
Between us adults, we should help each other. It's fine.
Thank you!
Nian Nian, take them to see their room.
- Okay, come this way, Auntie. I can take this.
- No, I can.
Okay. Auntie, this way.
Go slowly!
Slowly, do you need help?
No worries, I got this.
Nian Nian, what does Zheng Hui's Mom think about the room?
Pretty good. She's resting now.
- Zheng Hui, is he good at studying?
- Yes.
Last year, when you both competed internationally,
I thought he was pretty good.
He is good. The teachers like him, too.
Then, how about this? In the future, invite Zheng Hui over to visit more.
That way, he can take care of his mother and you can both study together.
That's not good. He's a guy.
Oh, Nian Nian, this is normal socializing.
I won't be against it.
That's not okay. What if people misunderstand?
You're quite conservative for someone who's so young.
I am a teacher, and I like these types of good students.
Then, do you like Han Shangyan?
Are you guys still in touch?
Look. You guys broke up already. Stop contacting each other.
Also, I don't like him one bit.
Why? Why don't you like him?
Why? He always has that long face, like people owe him money.
He didn't smile at us, either.
Also, I don't think he's very trustworthy.
You've misunderstood him.
He's actually a really good person. Towards his brothers, he is so loyal and sincere.
You're still a child and don't have life experience.
You're looking at issues with too much bias.
For example, the New Year's Eve dinner.
When he admitted that you were his girlfriend, he looked so forced.
Everyone could tell.
The next day when he came to our house for the first time as your boyfriend,
he didn't prepare anything and randomly bought some fruit from the corner store.
- Is that called sincere? That's called perfunctory!
- Mom, enough.
Good thing you broke up with him. He wouldn't have passed your father and my–
Enough. I said enough already.
He's almost thirty.
What hasn't he seen?
You're too naive. Don't believe everything he says.
In the future, you'll meet more and better people.
Don't be in a rush, okay?
Think about if what I've said is right. Okay?
Yaya, Han Shangyan is so pitiful.
What? How is he pitiful?
Everyone dislikes him. I feel so sorry for him.
Some people would dislike him?
His grandpa, stepmother, and my parents.
Why?
My mom said a lot of bad things about him.
She doesn't like him.
What did she say?
My mom talked about things related to when he was younger.
But... even if that's what he did, somehow it's twisted the way my mom says it.
She says that he's good-for-nothing, says he's full of lies, a man acting too young for his age.
A god has been successfully dragged down the altar by his future mother-in-law.
Don't say that! I'm not joking with you, okay?
I am also serious. In my heart, he is a god.
He has been recorded in the Annals of CTF History.
I must treat him well; treat him better.
I want to buy the whole world for him.
He loves work so much and is a workaholic.
How can I make him happy?
I don't know how I can make him happy.
Let me help you think. I'll help you think.
At most, half a year. Just put in more effort and I'll try to bring you back to Team One.
We can't for this year's national competition.
I know. Everyone speaks with their ranking.
Regarding this decision, I don't have a word of complaint.
Sorry.
What are you sorry for? You've already taken good care of me.
If you keep being biased like this, others are going to lodge a complaint.
I do have a personal stake in you, and I do want to treat you well.
Sorry, I let you down.
Let's talk seriously. When will headquarters change me out?
Next up is the last of the small group competitions.
SP has advanced.
After the next match, you and Team Two's captain will switch.
As long as your scores next year are in the National Top 30 ranking,
I'll move you back to Team One.
Understood.
Can I still fight side by side with Ou Qiang one last time?
Thank you.
Captain, can you hold off on announcing it?
Especially to Ou Qiang. I am afraid it will affect him competing.
Although he's loud and playful on the outside,
his heart's fragile.
Okay.
I will definitely play well in the next match.
- I'm going to a meeting.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Let's go.
I'm telling you! I found the loopholes, forced an attack, and successively broke the opponent's three nodes!
- Really?
- I'm not just boasting!
At the end, when they saw me, it was like a mouse seeing a cat; head down and running away.
- All right! That's impressive.
- You want to learn it?
- I do!
- Just follow me and I'll teach you!
Is it free?
- Why are you bringing up money...
- All right!
You scared me. What are you doing?
- I was listening to you brag.
- And I thought he was something...
Turns out he was just exaggerating.
What exaggeration? Everything I said is true.
Who is it?
Idol, do you know what Han Shangyan likes?
Idol?
Let me search for you.
- Not letting me see, are you?
- Let me ask you a question.
What does Han Shangyan like?
Old Han?
Old Han likes...
scolding people.
Let me see.
Just one look. One look.
Are we brothers or not?
Thank you, my idol. I'll treat you to a meal.
Who is it? Just tell me. What's wrong with telling me?
No!
No fun.
My favor is not important.
What's important is that you want to take your idol out to dinner, don't you?
Yes.
What's going on here?
Dominated!
One week. Take care of all the dorm rooms, the game rooms,
including the meeting room and the front desk.
Sure, I accept defeat.
Challenging me?
No chance before, still no chance now.
That's what you get for challenging Boss. He showed you.
What's up with him? He keeps making a fool of us.
Is his romance sweet? Or is he being beaten?
Why isn't he making nice with the Little Squid, honestly?
- Boss! Boss!
- Say it.
Someone came to find you at the front desk.
Who is it?
- Sister-in-Law.
- Louder.
Sister-in-Law!
Why don't you just go up?
I was waiting for you. I prepared a present for you.
- What is it?
- Wait! You can't look right now.
I'll let you see it when I go up. Let's go.
Why can't I see what you gave me?
You can't look at it here. I can only tell you when we get up there.
I'm not letting you see it.
I don't know what you like so I chose this for you.
I hope you'll like it.
Wait.
Come out.
Hello, I am a little cat.
I've never raised a cat before.
That pet store owner sent me a long list of things to pay attention to when it comes to pet cats.
I couldn't understand it. I'll forward it to you in a bit.
No need.
I... raised a cat before.
What is it? Are you not happy?
Look at him. He is saying hello to you.
Put it in the box.
Then, you'll have to remember to play with it often.
Why haven't you come to see me lately?
You haven't contacted me either.
Aren't I just afraid that you're busy?
I'll definitely be busier now.
Then, I'll give you this little cat.
You'll have to make frequent reports on its condition.
Are you trying to tie me down with a cat?
Look at you. Why are you making it so complicated?
I just wanted the cat to cheer you up. I didn't want you to be bored. Right?
I have a whole house of boys, and you're afraid I'll be bored?
That's different. I gave you this.
What you're doing is adding to my troubles.
What's up with you? Do you not like him?
He's tolerable.
I spent an afternoon choosing him.
It does look like the one I raised before.
Isn't it? Isn't it? I especially asked Mi Shaofei.
Mi Shaofei?
What else did he tell you?
- Anyway, I'm giving him to you. You have to take good care of him, got it?
- Tong Nian...
Tong Nian, that cat of yours...
What are you looking at?
Boss, we did not see anything.
Boss, since Sister-in-Law is here, why don't we go out for dinner?
We haven't eaten together for a long time.
That's all right. I've been dieting lately. Why don't you go?
Are you dumb?
Boss is taking Sister-in-Law to eat a romantic candlelit dinner.
Then... Then, I'll help you close the door.
No need, no need. I'm leaving soon.
Then, we'll not bother you. We're leaving.
We'll leave now.
- Shut the door for a bit.
- Look at you, so awkward.
Oh right. There is a letter in the box.
Remember to open and take a look.
Also, remember to miss me.
Are you still coming back? If not, I'm closing the door.
I'll leave now. Bye-bye.
Hi.
That battle tactic of yours earlier...
Uh, you have to first analyze the attack, you know?
- You have to watch the back door!
- Beef up security!
- That's the battle strategy.
- Right.
That's the battle strategy.
Didn't I tell you?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
The past has passed. In the future, they are all here.
I'm here, too. From Tong Nian.
...I think there is a stray cat. Over there.
You can go and pet him.
Here, here. Let's get up and play for a bit.
The little cat isn't scared of strangers.
Old Han,
I used to think you would like large dogs.
Turns out, you like the type
who sticks to you 25 hours a day, who'll cling to you from time to time,
a little creature who will use its little claws to hook on to you. Huh?
- What class are you going to next?
- The Monster's class.
- Wish you luck. Park it over here.
- Okay.
- Thank you for your bike.
- You're welcome.
It's time to change it. I'm going to class now.
- Bye-bye.
Oh no. My face looks so bad. How can I see my idol like this?
Look where I am.
Why would you suddenly come to look for me?
Wait for a second. Don't run around. Don't go anywhere.
I'll come to find you soon.
This color makes me look more pale.
- Where are you going?
- I'm in a hurry. In a hurry. Bye-bye.
Let me catch my breath.
Take your time. I'll give you three minutes.
Don't need three minutes. Don't need it.
What is it, Idol? Do you not know me anymore? Why that expression?
No, no, no. It just... feels like you look different from last time.
Can't put my finger on it.
I just never thought you would come.
Because someone said she is going to treat me a meal, I came.
Is there something wrong?
Nothing wrong. I just didn't expect it.
Didn't expect what?
No, I... Because in my heart you are still the same as pictures.
I'm a living and breathing man. A picture?
No, no I don't mean that. I just meant to say that I still can't treat you like a regular person.
You get it, right?
Shall we go and eat at the canteen?
Just the canteen?
Because I've been away for so long, I'd like to experience college life again.
Then, okay. Let's go.
Let's go!
Here.
It's enough. These are enough. It's fine.
What is it?
These are enough. These are enough for like ten people. Here. Let's eat.
You said that you've never eaten at a cafeteria before, so I wanted you to try all of it.
My mom has tugged on my ear since I was little and taught me not to waste food.
So let's finish these.
Let's eat!
It looks like... it is a bit too much.
It's fine. If we can't finish, I'll just bring it back to the club.
What do you do in college gym classes?
It's not much different from high school. We all have to go through physical fitness tests.
Once I got into university, I thought that I would never have to do gym again.
I never thought I'd have to do it for the freshman and sophomore years of undergraduate.
- That miserable?
- Yes.
I'm so scared of long-distance running. So scared.
I was first place for long-distance running in high school.
Really? That amazing?
I'm going to put it into the group chat.
What are you doing?
No, I'm just used to it.
In our group, no matter who gets a bit of news about you,
we share it with everybody.
Now that you've met me in person, do you feel like your illusion's been destroyed?
Why would it be destroyed?
Then, do you still do long-distance running?
I stopped running a long time ago. It's all in the past.
When I was in school, I always thought I was so good at P.E.
Then I won the CTF national championship. I was so cool.
But now, it looks like I'm not doing anything with my life.
Right now, you are in SP.
It's the biggest internet club in the nation.
How can you say you aren't doing anything with your life?
♫ Give you everything that is the best ♫
♫ Quietly saying: I love you ♫
The next competition's ticket. It's in Shanghai. Come to it.
I couldn't buy this ticket anywhere! I...
Won't you give it to more important people to you?
I don't have anyone else to give it to.
You have it. This is special seating; it's got a pretty good view.
Take it as thanks for all these years of your support.
Really?
Then... thank you.
I'll have to frame this ticket and hang it on my wall.
If you frame it, how will you come and watch?
You must come.
Yes. I must go, no matter what happens.
♫ Grateful that youth let us ♫
Uncle Han, it's not often you come back to China.
- Stay a little longer this time; don't rush to go back.
- Sure, sure.
Is Little Han not home?
He lives in that club of his all day and doesn't come back.
He's that busy playing with computers?
He wants me to understand it, but how can I?
What about Nian Nian? I haven't seen her in a while. Is she going through exams?
Nian Nian is on vacation; there are no more exams.
It's like this?
These past few days, one of her classmate's mom became sick.
My brother has been treating her.
My sister-in-law said they came from another province.
They didn't want them to spend money at the guest lodgings, so they invited them to stay at home.
My sister-in-law has such a kind heart.
You're all very warm and kind-hearted.
Let me tell you. I've seen Nian Nian's boy classmate.
He's a good person and very hard-working. I've heard he's pursuing his doctorate.
My brother and my sister-in-law like him very much.
They say that his future is bright.
They have high hopes for his future.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫