♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 17]
Do you want to know about Han Shangyan's past?
I do. Especially what's not on the web.
Let me think...
When we were on Team Solo, we raised a cat.
The cat was always taken care of by Han Shangyan.
Then, the cat passed away.
He wouldn't let us mention it, so Solo and I deduced that in terms of his feelings,
he definitely has a first-love complex.
He has a really strong sense of possession and gets jealous often.
But also, because of something small, he'll get happy like a child.
But in love, because of some things,
he'll become very confused and unsure.
He has a first-love complex?
Hard to imagine, right?
Then, who was his first love?
His first love?
I'm guessing...
It is you.
- Me?
- Right.
Because there's never been news about him having a girlfriend.
Also, the way he looks at you is like looking at that cherished cat.
Are you serious?
I think it's 90% true. You can ask him for the last 10%.
These two beauties are chatting?
We should chat together.
Ou Qiang, what're you doing?
Usually, Old Han watches you too closely.
I've never dared to carefully look at Sister-in-Law.
You're scaring her.
Right, Solo is asking for you. Go and talk to him.
Okay, got it. Let's go.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Ai Qing, thanks for telling me about this today.
Actually, I should thank you.
Han Shangyan doesn't have his family's support,
and he's in China alone all because he wanted to help China get the gold medal.
He doesn't have a family or a girlfriend.
He only wanted to win, to continue winning on and on, to use his Chinese citizenship to bring the grand slam.
So, we were really worried that no one would be able to take his bad temper and dedication towards CTF.
But look now. How great it is.
Let's go.
Your work badge.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
So, is this why Grandpa always dislikes him?
He's so successful at his job, has won so many championships, and has suffered so many hardships.
Can his family still not understand him?
It has been very hard for you, right?
It's too hot, and you have a heat stroke?
Wait for me!
Han Sh–
Shangyan...
- Oh my god?
- Jeez!
- Train!
- Train, guys!
I didn't mean to call you loudly on purpose.
When I called you earlier, you didn't hear, so I had to yell.
What were you gesturing down there? I didn't understand at all.
I was saying, "It has been very hard for you and to wait for me up here."
Look!
Listen to me.
I don't mind any private affection, but in public, you have to be careful of our influence.
What if people see and laugh?
I understand. Taste some.
Hey, let me finish.
I'm a man, so I'm not scared of suffering losses. In the end, you're the one at a disadvantage, understand?
Yes, yes. Open up!
Is it good?
- It's okay.
- Have some more.
What in the world?
I let the little kid out for ten minutes and she's back like this?
Little Mi, come with me. Ai Qing, keep practicing with everyone.
Lost my footing.
What are you doing?
Will you be bored?
No, it's very fun here.
Actually, if you go out the back door from the lobby, there's a beach. You can go stroll around.
If you want to eat or drink anything, just put it on the tab for your room.
The beach is connected to a few hotels, don't get lost.
I won't.
- Does your phone still have power?
- Yes, a lot.
If you lose your phone, then–
Why're you nagging like a monk? Talking so much.
I'm not a little kid, I won't get lost. Don't worry.
I brought some fruit for everyone; bring it inside.
I only bought one coconut water for you.
- Bye-bye.
- I'm going.
I'll find you later.
Well, someone bought you all some fruit.
Who is "someone"?
"Someone"? It's Sister-in-Law!
Pass the ball!
Pass the ball! Here!
- Hello.
Why're you here yourself? You aren't playing with them?
I didn't bring a bikini.
- Hello, I'm Mi Shaofei.
- Hello, hello.
- Old Han's good friend.
- I know you.
You read CTF Weekly?
No. After I met him, I collected a lot of information on him.
So, I know both of you.
Wow, so thoughtful.
- I'll go buy some beverages.
- Sure, let's have some.
- No need!
- It's fine, you're one of us.
- Hurry and come back.
- Okay!
- Thanks.
He's too polite.
- Chat a bit?
- Okay.
That day, I listened to you sing "Little Donkey" very sorrowfully.
Did something happen with Old Han?
Sorry, I have no intention to probe into your privacy.
I used to be a team captain. Now, I'm in charge of competing teams.
I'm very good at reading people, so I was able to tell.
Han Shangyan used to live in Norway. How did you meet him?
I just knew you were going to ask about him. We met each other through online chatting.
Then, what year did you know each other?
About 2005? We were close through online chatting.
So, he came to find me from Norway.
Just because you were close online, he came to find you?
Old Han has a weird personality.
You can't use a normal person's logic to think about him.
Aquariuses are indeed kind of weird.
He's weird and you still like him?
I'm back!
Thanks.
- Can you have cold drinks?
- I can, I can. No problem.
Here, this is for you.
Oh, thank you.
Welcome!
You're done? Have some.
What's in the cup?
Mi Shaofei gave it to me.
This is alcohol. Why is a child drinking alcohol?
Old Han, it's fine. This isn't much.
It's peach flavored. Add a bit of ice to the drink and it's so refreshing.
Thanks for taking care of my kid.
We're brothers; you're welcome.
If you're free later on, I need to talk to you.
You are welcome, too!
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
Cheers.
I cannot annoy him or always find him to come and play.
He's too busy; I can't bother him.
I can be by myself!
Tong Nian? You're alone?
I guess that's right. They're all training and are very busy.
How about I hang out with you?
- It's fine. I can–
- Don't worry, I've got nothing to do.
Also, I haven't eaten. I'll take you to have a seafood feast.
No need, really.
We have to eat anyway.
I'll take you to Sanya's fun places and have some delicious seafood.
We're here.
Thanks.
Careful.
I'm very close to the boss here. The seafood is amazing.
- Do you have anything you really want to eat?
- No, I'm fine with anything.
- Okay.
- Then, I'll order what's most popular here.
[Little Mi: 101, 97]
There are only ten minutes before practice, what is it?
The last time we met, it was quite rushed. I had no time to catch up with you.
Between us brothers, what need is there to catch up on?
The relationship is always here.
Little Mi, come join K&K.
Han Shangyan...
I don't have that worth.
Why would you repeatedly scout over a person like me?
You all are priceless in my heart.
I know you take feelings and friends very seriously,
but the worth of a player can be calculated.
My scores are really bad.
If I join, won't I be dragging you down?
Solo works for other people.
No matter how well he's doing, he can't take care of you.
You're finally back. I don't wish you to leave like this.
If there wasn't training, I would've had a few drinks with you.
Changing the topic?
Spare me, Bro.
Because of this last time, I almost had a huge fight with you.
I can't convince you. Whatever.
Scram! Go back to training.
I'm leaving.
[Haitang North Road]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
- Hello.
How do I get to the location on the map?
Walk this way and you'll be there in about three kilometers; it's a seafood restaurant.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Do you need an umbrella? It seems it's about to rain.
- No, I'm fine. Thanks.
- You're welcome.
You ordered so much, I'm kind of embarrassed.
Don't worry. I'm close with the boss here. Eat a lot; the pricing is good.
Thanks.
This one is good. Here.
- It's fine. I can do it myself.
- Have a lot.
- And this.
- Thank you.
Why aren't you eating?
Don't worry. I eat here often.
You've been staring at me a lot. It's kind of weird.
I'm embarrassed to eat by myself. Shouldn't we eat together?
No, you eat.
Is there something you have to ask me?
No, nothing special.
I just rarely see
someone walking with my Shangyan.
I'm just slightly curious.
Oh, that's it?
- Are you his girlfriend?
- Yep.
Right, I am his girlfriend.
Our parents have eaten together and met already.
It was during the new year, they had dinner together.
Eating New Year's Eve dinner isn't much.
I think you're just too young.
You aren't too clear about some things.
You may not be compatible with someone like Shangyan.
When Han Shangyan just joined CTF, I was his fan.
Back then, I didn't understand it, either.
But my older brother liked coding, so I learned along with him. Then, I got into CTF.
Later, I started watching him. I liked our Shangyan so much.
Then, he suddenly retired.
But did you know? Tong Nian. Tong Nian!
Did you know? I took this career because of Shangyan!
I know. Earlier, Ai Qing told me he has a lot of fans, so I can understand your feelings–
I'm not just some fan!
If I had joined Shangyan earlier,
he wouldn't have retired so early.
And with my skills, in less than three years,
he would have been the world's number one, China's top.
You seem young.
There is quite a difference between your age and Shangyan's age, right?
Have you graduated from college?
I'm graduating from postgraduate this year.
You don't seem like it at all!
I'm not going to tell you I took junior classes.
What's wrong with being young? Old lady.
A successful man always has an important woman behind him.
I know. I understand him a lot and support him, so you don't have to worry.
That isn't enough. Men care a lot about their careers.
A woman who can help him succeed in his career is the one who can stay by his side in the end.
But those young and pretty people who interfere with his career...
That is just a short-lived fate; like a fleeting, glimmering boat floating across the water.
Why're there so many flies? Flying here and there.
They're buzzing and buzzing, so annoying.
Don't move, there's one. I'll hit it.
So, what's the purpose of you telling me all this?
Nothing, no other purpose.
I saw that you're young, so I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
You might not understand someone like Shangyan.
He might not suit you.
If she doesn't suit me, then who does?
- Shangyan!
How'd you know I was here?
If I want to know, I'll know naturally.
Shangyan, we were just talking about you.
Here! Have some, too.
Here.
I just thought you were busy.
And it's a pity she was alone, so I brought her here to have some fun.
At the same time, I got her to try Sanya's delicacies. You try some, too.
- Is it good?
No one would enjoy eating this kind of feast.
If you eat in this direction, you should feel happier.
Here.
Can you reach?
Oh right, Grandpa just called saying he misses you.
Really? Then, I'll call him back. I also miss him.
Okay.
You two seem pretty happy.
I have something to do, so I'll be going.
Go ahead.
I'm really leaving.
Bye-bye. We won't see you out.
Okay.
Is Grandpa home? I'll call him now.
- No need. He didn't ask for you.
- What?
Weren't you jealous of her earlier?
I was going along with you to make you happy.
Look at your sad expression. What did she say?
She said she is your fan.
Did you know her in the past?
She's just a fanatic fan who just wants to enter the CTF circle.
She said she joined CTF a long time ago.
So amazing, unlike me.
What use is that? I don't like her, right?
Why's your shirt wet?
The sky was all clear, but it suddenly started raining.
Why didn't you bring an umbrella?
I was worried and came in a rush.
Is it good?
It's pretty good.
She's not a great person, but her choice in restaurants and food is pretty good.
Eat more.
She kept talking earlier, so I ate a lot.
This is really good. Open up!
- Does it taste good?
- It's not bad.
Do you have something to say?
I don't have anything to say.
You have to start a new life.
With a child around, it'll be hard to even get married.
I didn't plan on marrying. She's enough.
Solo, I really miss my daughter.
She's also my daughter.
What's going on between them?
Did you know that you are my first love?
The first person I loved.
I don't regret being with you.
If I could redo everything, I wouldn't have given birth to her behind your back.
I loved you too much after breaking up, so I gave birth to her.
What's in the past is in the past. No need to talk too much about it.
Solo, I want my daughter.
Give me a chance.
Seeing that I bore her for ten months,
give me a chance.
You know that there are many things where you can't interfere, right?
For example, I remember when I graduated from elementary school,
when I first started my menstrual cycle, I freaked out.
It was my mom who looked after me.
If you asked me to talk to my dad, I wouldn't have done it.
This is just a small thing. There are more.
Girls have all sorts of bodily experiences during puberty.
You can't say anything about it.
Have you not experienced it yourself?
Are you done talking?
Let me carefully consider it.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
- What are you doing? You scared me.
- What's up with you?
I'm perfectly fine. If you have something to say, say it.
Old Han and I met today.
What did he say?
He wanted me to join K&K.
Join K&K...
He still hasn't changed. Still so blinded by emotions.
What did you say?
Joining K&K at a crucial time, isn't that like escaping?
You know I'm not someone who flees.
Although I'm unsatisfied about many things, I...
What? We are brothers; I understand you.
Even if I'm unsatisfied, I need to recognize reality.
I will work harder.
If I can't increase my scores, I will give you an answer.
You're the most awesome.
Little white whale. So cute.
These days, when I'm really tired from training,
I will come here to look around.
I wish that I can be like a forgetful fish.
Forget about all the troubles in life.
Yeah! They seem so happy, swimming around freely.
I haven't asked you yet. What happened with Little Ai's parents?
I pity her.
They were first-loves, but they broke up later on.
Then... Little Ai is...
Born after breaking up, so Solo didn't know about her.
Solo didn't know about Little Ai?
That time, Su Cheng couldn't afford to raise her, so she went to find Solo.
Then they got married on paper,
got Little Ai her birth certificate and citizenship, and then divorced.
From then on, Solo raised Little Ai by himself.
They even got married?
At the time, it was just to get Little Ai's birth certificate and citizenship. They divorced very soon after.
Then... Little Ai...
You're a child, stop inquiring about other people's matters.
What's wrong? Do you not feel well?
My head hurts a bit. It could be because Zhou Shan has been annoying me.
Do you want to go back and rest a bit?
It's nothing.
It's not easy to find time to spend with you. Let's walk a bit more.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
♫ I think I see you in my dreams ♫
♫ Your eyes are like twinkling little stars ♫
♫ Drawing me in and capturing all my attention ♫
♫ I don't want to wake up ♫
♫ Getting ready to breathe deep breaths in ♫
♫ I want to climb to the top with you ♫
♫ Watching the beautiful scenery with you ♫
♫ I just want to make you happy ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
You're really going to ask?
I think he really is her boyfriend.
[I thought about it and something's not right. Little Squid, did you go to Sanya with your boyfriend?]
Come look.
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, I'll stay by your side ♫
I thought about it and something's not right.
Little Squid, did you go to Sanya with your boyfriend?
Yes.
You were right!
You just started! Idiot, what time is it already?
Sleep in separated rooms.
Also, don't be together past 9:00 p.m.
Go back to your room and watch your cartoons!
Do you think they are living in one room?
No way!
You should go back and rest.
You're awake?
How is it? Does your head still hurt?
I'll be out the whole day tomorrow for training.
Will you be okay by yourself?
No problem. Of course, it's no problem.
Then, you rest first.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
This is my room card. Take it.
Do not secretly come in while I'm asleep.
I-I'm not a pervert.
Whatever you want to eat, order it yourself.
-  I'll pay.
- No need. I have money.
I called you here to play. Of course, I have to pay.
Then, I'll leave first.
- Go ahead.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
[Sanya Haitang Bay Atlantis Hotel]
97.
Boss?
If a child is in Sanya, but she's in her room all day, what would she be doing?
What child? It's Sister-in-Law, right?
Answer the question, got it?
Got it.
Playing games?
She doesn't play games.
Sleeping?
From last night until tonight?
She's not sick, right?
Then, she didn't even go to the beach?
Boss, we are almost done. If you're in a hurry, you can leave first.
Don't worry, Boss. Go.
Bye, Boss!
Boss is gone!
- Play whatever you want!
- Quiet!
- Hello, how are you?
- Hello!
I wanted to let you know I've returned to my room.
You're back. Why are you back so early today?
There wasn't much going on in training, so I'm back.
Since you're back, I'll go look for you.
- Okay, I'll stroll around with you.
- Okay.
I'll see you in a bit.
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
Look at this fish, it's so ugly.
It looks like this, look.
Let's imitate it and see who's most alike. I'll go first.
- Your turn.
- No way, it's so immature.
We just agreed on imitating it together!
Didn't we come here to forget our troubles? Cheer up.
Look! A fish's memory lasts for only seven seconds. I actually admire that.
You can forget all your troubles, right?
Why did you roll your eyes?
You have to swim along.
I'll be your tail.
Look at this; the one on top. It's even uglier than the previous one!
Isn't it? Its face is like this.
What'd you do today?
I didn't go out today. I stayed in the hotel.
I made you a present.
Present?
A present for us being together.
Then, do I have to give you a present, too?
No, I don't need anything. Don't give me anything.
The present I prepared for you is very special.
I can't tell you right now, it has to be kept mysterious.
What are you doing tonight?
In the daytime, I'm busy with what's happening in China.
In the nighttime, I'm busy with headquarters.
Are you disappointed?
No, no! I know that you're busy.
You stay at the hotel all day anyway.
How about you come to the internet cafe where we train tomorrow?
Can I? Sure, sure.
Go back and rest.
Don't work too hard and take care of your health.
You haven't slept yet?
We're at such a beautiful beach, but you don't seem to be relaxed at all.
We are here to train not to relax.
You talked to Little Mi?
You really want to sign on someone in the second team? Little Mi's current ranking...
We can stop talking about this topic.
He won't join our team. He rejected my offer.
Honestly, I've always wanted to ask you something.
Say it.
The final champion...
Do you wish we take it, or for Team SP, too?
There's only one champion. Everyone wants it.
I hope all your decisions consider K&K's ranking,
and not your past friendships.
When did you start giving advice to me?
Also, do you not know me?
Go to sleep.
I'm sleeping.
One two, one two, K&K champion!
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
One two, one two, K&K champion!
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
Do they do this every day?
Pretty much.
Then, what about in the past? Did you all do this, too?
Us?
We weren't as professional. We trained day and night.
Stomach aches and sleep deprivation; we were all used to it.
Indeed. When I was younger, I didn't like gym class.
When I was tired, I avoided it, but my body wasn't very healthy.
Later, I realized that exercise is very important to a person.
Look. Am I healthy?
Also, I used to be really short.
Thanks to exercise, I grew a bit.
How long does it take you to run 800 meters?
Two minutes and thirty seconds.
Is that good or bad?
Better than a full score!
Hurry up!
K&K champion! One two, one two, K&K champion! One two, one two,
- K&K champion!
- K&K champion! One two, one two, K&K champion!
K&K champion! One two, one two, K&K champion!
Demo! Demo! Give me a sip.
- This is pretty amazing, it doesn't spill!
- Neat, right?
Pretty neat. Advancement in technology and times have developed.
Wow, even water has evolved.
It seems that it's just you guys who haven't evolved.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫