♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 23]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
It's here. The third last row from the back.
Why haven't they entered the stage yet?
Calm down, calm down.
Generally, they enter 10 minutes before it starts.
I-I-I was just a bit nervous, okay?
Okay then. I'll take a picture
and send it to Uncle Mi Shaofei!
Don't take a picture of me, this kid.
Don't be sad.
No, I'm not sad. Don't worry, I'm very happy.
[China Regional Qualifier - Eighth Finals
Pro League Season 8]
Ladies and gentlemen, good afternoon.
You are now watching the CTF Pro League Season 8 Regional Finals Qualifier for the Chinese Region.
While we're waiting for the competition to start, let's introduce the current standing of the players.
Okay, first let's talk about SP's Mi Shaofei.
We can say that Mi Shaofei is a veteran.
His comeback to CTF was really unexpected.
- Mi Shaofei is way past his prime time and he's been retired for many years.
- Get ready to enter the stage.
- It's really surprising for SP to let him play.
- Good luck!
Good luck!
Don't feel pressured. Just perform as usual. I believe in you.
Just think of it as an exciting performance.
Don't coax me like a little girl. Do I need it?
Okay, our warm-up has finished.
Let's give our warmest welcome to the two teams that are competing today.
Team SP and Team Taotao.
[Pro League Season 8: Team Taotao vs Team SP]
Yeah!
My idol!
1, 2, 3, SP!
All right, the competition is officially starting. The first round is the attack and defend model that we're familiar with.
Okay, SP started off by reinforcing their server.
Team Taotao's captain is attacking a node straightaway.
Okay, we can see that with both teams starting, Team Taotao is using all their players for an all-out attack.
Starting off with the wolf pack tactic, while SP is completely the opposite.
The whole team is on defense,  with the strategy to wear Team Taotao out.
Team SP is riding the momentum and has gained their sixth battle point.
They're only one step away from victory.
Team Taotao's server right now is not very optimistic. They can only hope for a miracle to happen for this round.
Hope is minuscule.
SP's chance is very big.
Mi Shaofei's condition today is excellent.
- This is his best performance in a match since he made a comeback. He should win this match easily.
- Strengthen defense. Hurry!
That's right! He's basically carrying the whole team by himself.
Looks like Team Taotao has bypassed Ou Qiang's trap. Three people have now attacked at the middle.
Don't worry about over there. Don't worry about it.
All right! Protected one, seize it... Beautiful!
One more, and one more! Two, beautiful!
Just the final one now, let's see if they can hold on to it.
Beautiful, that was a perfect attack. It was a very nice attack for Mi Shaofei.
Okay, we can see that it is now five defending one.
SP has a good chance at winning this match point.
They are still capturing the final node.
The final node, will they be able to take it?!
[IP Traced]
Yes!
Beautiful! Congratulations to SP on their victory in this match!
Congratulations to SP for winning the Eighth CTF Finals Qualifier for the Chinese Region.
Today was an exciting competition. Veteran players are indeed stronger.
Exactly!
All right, now let our audience please give a round of applause to the winners today,
- Team SP!
- Yes!
I am sure that Team SP's members must also be very excited and have something to say to the audience here today.
Then, on behalf of the team, let us invite Hua Ti, the team captain, to say a few words. Let's give him a round of applause!
I think the one who has the most to say is definitely our team's hero,
Little Mi!
Little Mi! Little Mi! Little Mi!
Thank you, everyone, for coming to see the competition.
Today, we have won. I have already made an all-out effort.
Today,
is my life's last professional competition.
What are you saying, Little Mi?
I believe many of those sitting here were there ten years ago, supporting Team Solo's Little Mi, Mi Shaofei.
My past ten years
have been filled with ups and downs,
but I have always believed that as long as I work hard and put in more effort,
I will obtain a good result.
But the truth is not like that.
But, speaking honestly, in my heart I feel very... calm.
There are many things I am grateful for.
It's like... like a firework that was launched in the sky.
Brief. Brilliant.
The same!
I want to thank you all who have been supporting me.
Thank you all so much for accompanying me on this road. You all have worked hard.
Accompanying me in the most beautiful, brightest fireworks.
Thank you all.
There are still some things I want to say to everyone here.
And that is Team Solo's only player who is continuing to compete, Ou Qiang.
Maybe it was destiny, because his CTF username is called "All."
Thus, he will represent the five of us from Team Solo.
Improving together, working hard together on our behalf.
Becoming a national champion on our behalf.
Becoming a world champion on our behalf.
Having you guys, I am blessed.
Little Mi... Mi Shaofei...
is now signing off.
Solo!
Solo, slow down.
I want to ask Little Mi what on earth he is thinking.
- Don't be anxious, can't you just wait until they're off the stage to ask? Solo!
- Solo!
Who let Mi Shaofei retire? Who made the decision?
Han Shangyan! Don't be impulsive.
Solo also didn't know before it happened!
What did you promise me at the beginning?
Han Shangyan, let go first.
Get out of the way!
What did you promise me at the beginning?
Let go. The audience hasn't left yet.
Wang Hao! I am asking you one last time.
What did you promise me at the beginning?
Ai Qing. Stand further away.
Han Shangyan, don't be impulsive. Let go first.
- Even yelling at you won't make you go away, will it?
- You're not allowed to talk to Ai Qing like that!
Who are you trying to intimidate? I am not your team member now.
That's right.
In this lifetime,
I won't have team members that belong to me anymore.
Before you retired, that was the first thing I promised you.
That if I leave the team, then I will not participate in any team events again.
So even up until today,
I have always been fighting alone.
I fulfilled the first promise.
The second thing, at Sanya, I promised you to take care of them.
Little Mi and Ou Qiang.
I apologize.
I did not fulfill the second promise.
Go on. Hit me however you want, I won't retaliate. Go on!
Han Shangyan!
What are you doing over here?
Your jacket.
It looks like we're just missing Ou Qiang.
Little Mi,
come with me. I'll bring you to K&K.
Wait.
Don't do anything more than three times.
I'll feel really sorry if I have to reject you again.
Good that you feel sorry. Come with me!
But, Gun God,
the worst ranking on your team is 71.
And I am tossed beyond 100.
Why would I go to your club?
Wipe the screens? Wash the keyboards?
Is that it? Do you want to see me like that?
Give me some face, please.
On stage just now, I had such glory. You all saw.
I need to give my family a call.
I don't want you guys to argue again.
Little Mi!
Let's meet and drink sometime!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
What's wrong. What's with the long faces?
Isn't it just retirement?
How can you be like this?
What do you mean isn't it just retirement? Did you discuss it with us?
How could I discuss it with you if you're so impulsive?
Just who is the impulsive one?
I can't win an argument with you. Let's stop talking about it.
Little Mi, I don't have time to joke around with you.
You announced to everyone onstage that you decided to retire.
Now, we can't even help you redeem yourself, Mi Shaofei!
You've disappointed all of us.
Disappointed about what?
Just how old are you?
- Don't be rash. Don't fight.
- Look at me!
What are you going to do once you retire? Have you thought about it?
Are you satisfied?
I confess that I'm not satisfied.
I still have a championship dream in my heart.
So back when Solo asked me to join SP, I did it without hesitation.
However, facts have proved that I don't have the skills anymore.
I don't have the skills anymore.
My tempo and endurance can't keep up with the younger ones. I don't have a choice.
I did my best.
Bro,
give me a perfect curtain call. Okay?
Come on.
Only you are left from Team Solo.
You have to persevere.
As long as you're here,
everyone is here.
Old Han!
Calm down first. Don't be mad!
Little Mi deliberately hid this from everyone.
Solo and Ai Qing didn't know either.
It's not as dirty as you think.
I understand.
Han Shangyan!
I came to watch the competition today. How are you?
Is your mood okay?
Where do you want to go?
Wherever you go, I'll go.
Tong Nian!
Little Mi's retirement was a really heavy blow for him.
I ask of you to help comfort him for the next few days.
I will.
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Wang Hao!
Dad, where are you? Dad!
Wang Hao!
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad, why are you here? Dad.
Dad, what are you doing?
Dad? Dad, just talk to me.
Dad! Dad, don't... don't...
Can you talk to me?
Dad, don't... Don't ignore me, Dad.
Dad-Dad, don't be sad.
Dad! Dad.
Dad!
Dad, don't be like this. Dad!
My life is such a failure.
It's not, Dad!
Dad, don't be sad.
It's okay.
I can't do anything right.
It's not like that.
My dad is the best.
Dad...
Dad!
♫ Among the lights of a city’s dawn ♫
♫ There’s always splendor falling ♫
♫ Imitators one after another ♫
Idol, there are a lot of fans outside.
You suddenly announced retirement, and they've liked you for so long, so there are definitely ones that are upset.
What if they're too agitated? Will you be able to deal with them?
I know! I can use my clothes to help you
- cover your head, and then we can run out.
- All right, all right.
Don't make it seem like we're eloping or something.
I didn't mean it like that.
I was afraid that you wouldn't be able to stand it.
I'm a man. What's there to not be able to stand?
When you need to say goodbye, you just... say goodbye.
Maybe, just like you said, there'll be some old fans out there. Right?
There are, there are!  There are some outside.
Idol, you have to remember. No matter what decision you make,
us old fans will always believe in you, support you, and accompany you.
Let's go.
Mi Shaofei, I...
[Little Mi- Little Mi: Come and Fight]
I've liked you from 2009, Mi Shaofei.
Keep fighting! We'll always support you.
Mi Shaofei, you can live stream when you get back home.
Just don't be like before and disappear. We'll always love you.
That's right!  You have a lot of fans online.
If you start live streaming, we'll all support you.
Why did you retire? Didn't you say that you would accompany us for a long time?
- Why did you retire?
- Don't retire.
- Yeah, don't retire.
- Stay here.
- We will always support you.
- That's right.
- Stay here.
- We will always support you.
Don't leave. Stay here and accompany us.
I would really like to
thank all of you for your support in the past. Thank you.
Little Mi, we can't be without you.
We can't give you up.
We will always support you.
[K&K]
You're back, Boss. Sister-in-Law.
Take care of the guest. Don't follow me.
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
- Wh-What's going on?
- What's this situation?
How come Sister-in-Law you're now a guest?
He's not in a good mood today.
Just now, Mi Shaofei announced his retirement.
What!?
No way...
Boss! Boss!
Where's Boss? Have you guys seen Boss?
- Boss!
- What's wrong, Demo?
Manager, where's Boss? My mom is here.
- What?
- She's blocking the doorway.
She says that she has to see Boss.
What? No way. Why are we so unlucky today?
Manager, you help me.
I'll go handle it.
Hi, Auntie, I'm the Team Manager for K&K, as well as their daily life manager.
I'm looking for your supervisor.
Our boss has to deal with some personal matters these two days and won't be back.
How about you talk to me about it first?
Let me ask you. How much authority do you have?
Are you able to talk about terminating a contract?
What should I do now?
Go in and find him?
I feel like I'm useless right now.
I feel like such an outsider right now.
Demo. One.
You guys take care of yourselves. I'm going to get going. I won't bother you all anymore.
- How about I call Boss right now.
- Please don't. Let him work.
I'll talk to him later. I'll get going for now, all right? Take care of yourselves. Bye-bye.
Okay. Bye-bye...
I have heard everything you said.
But let me tell you, it doesn't matter at all.
Today, I am here to help him terminate his contract!
Although our family has no money, for Dai Feng,
I can still bring out the necessary money to terminate the contract!
Don't you worry!
What should I do? His pressure has become even greater.
[SP Gaming]
- Hello, Brother Solo.
Hello, Brother Solo.
Boss... the contract termination agreement.
Double the compensation. Take it out of my bonus for the next quarter.
In the company's name, put it on Mi Shaofei's card.
Also, don't let anyone know about this.
Okay.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
What are you spacing out for?
Take a look. The company's termination contract.
I have no choice. This is the regular procedure we have to go through.
I know.
I've caused trouble for you.
What are you saying?
There is no such thing as "trouble" between bros.
I just never would have thought that...
things would turn out this way.
I'm pretty sad.
What are you sad about?
I played and got those results myself. It has nothing to do with you.
Besides, Han Shangyan, Ai Qing, and you have already retired.
I should retire, too.
It's exactly because of this
that my heart feels uncomfortable.
We were all too selfish.
Why did we impose our unfulfilled dreams on you and Ou Qiang?
I was the one who led you on this road.
I was the one who sparked new hope in you.
But how come things have come to this today?
Honestly, I've thought it through. No matter how great a hero is,
there is a time that he must step down from his peak.
Ou Qiang is playing really well, judging from these past few days.
I believe he will continue to fight.
I believe in him.
Right.
You're only bringing this little luggage?
Yes, only... only these.
Let's hang out tonight.
I still have something to do tonight.
Come on! How do I sign this, Team Captain?
Just... I can't understand the contract.
What are you doing?
Our relationship as bros can't be expressed by a cold contract like this.
Other than compensation, no matter what happens in the future...
your matters are still my matters.
Thank you.
You're done?
Yes.
You've worked hard.
You're okay now; it's all done.
[K&K E-Sports Club]
Later on, what will we do if they come to blows?
I don't think so.
I'm just repairing the house before it rains!
(T/N: Taking precautions)
Don't scare me! Mi Shaofei is so tiny, how is he going to fight with Han Shangyan?
- Who is tiny? He's just slightly thinner compared to your guy.
- Little Mi, Little Mi! Will you please sign an autograph for me?
You can't talk about my idol like that!
I saw your match and your retirement announcement yesterday and I cried!
- Can you write down my name, too. It's Jiahao.
- Sure.
Sister-in-Law, I'll call Boss for you.
Go! Go talk to him.
Okay. Then I'll go.
Little Mi, thank you.
- Take a seat, take a seat. Sit.
- Okay.
Sit. Do you want water?
Sorry about that. I came to see you without your permission.
I know these two days you are in a bad mood.
Mi Shaofei wanted me to tell you that he wanted to meet with you.
Also, he is at the front desk right now.
Are you going to see him?
Don't be impulsive.
Looking for me?
They won't actually come to blows, will they?
I don't think so.
Didn't we say we were going to go meet and have a drink?
Hey.
- What are they going to do?
- I don't know.
What are you two doing?
First, let's sweat it out, then drink.
Come on!
Wait for us here. We'll come back within two hours.
We'll accompany you guys and go together!
Let's go! Hurry!
No, Nian Nian. Your 800-meter time is good, but I can't meet that time requirement.
Plus, I'm really not feeling well today.
Okay then. Let's wait here for them.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
They're coming from there!
Are you guys okay?
Nothing's wrong, right?
I'm dead.
You started running without a warmup. Aren't you afraid your heart can't take it?
We K&K run every morning.
We care more about our health than your SP.
I'm not even part of SP anymore.
Why do you still have to fight with me like it's life and death?
I am just mad that you have so little ambition!
I'm telling you. Ambition and strength should be proportional; otherwise, you are a joke!
You're very great; you've always been.
You're only old now.
Old?!
I'm still young! Unlike someone who's 30!
Right.
The cruelest tragedy is when a hero meets his end.
Yes. Yes, yes.
Why are you smiling? What are you guys smiling about?
You guys didn't run!
- Come on, come on! Let's run, run!
- No! No, no, no!
- No!
- We don't feel well!
- Run even if you don't feel well.
- Come come! Let's run!
- Nian Nian, save me! Nian Nian!
- Save me!
- Let's run.
Yaya really can't run today.
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person ♫
Are you cold? Do you want to wear this jacket?
Let's go.
I can carry that for him.
Have some.
It's not like you don't know.
Where are you going?
What do you want?!
Maybe just skip her.
Yesterday's death was a moment ago...
Today, a reunion, a revival of a moment again. Cheers.
What do you plan to do next? Go home?
Before I came, I fought with my mom, and I promised that I would bring a gold medal home.
If I go back now, my mom will really criticize me.
To be honest, it's different now than it was before.
There are many job opportunities in the internet industry. You don't have to go home.
Let's not talk about it.
Did you already move out of the Team SP dormitories?
Where are you staying?
I'll see. I'll find a motel and stay for a few days.
Stay at my place.
I'm not married to you, why would I stay at your home?
My grandpa is heading back to Norway next month. While he's here, Wu Bai and I go see him.
Once he's gone, the house will be empty.
Hold on. Even brothers need to keep their debts straight.
Go for the big bowl.
Again.
Okay.
- Here, together.
- Yes.
Are you okay?
Do you want to throw up?
Yes or no?
I'm fine!
From when I was young until now, I've never thrown up!
No, I actually prepared two solutions, so please don't worry.
Besides, in my family, all my cousins from my mom and dad's side like to drink.
And every time they throw up, I take care of them. So, you...
Don't hold it in and don't worry about your idol image.
What idol image!? I really don't want to throw up!
But... just throw up. You look like you need to. Go ahead.
I really don't want to.
Thank you. Mi Shaofei is now signing off.
On that day when you retired, you were so handsome!
Under the attention of many,
you won the match and even announced your retirement on the spot.
There are some people who have endured for decades
and don't have that type of opportunity.
Really?
Just like that year when Han Shangyan retired.
Of all people, you have the best relationship with him. Right?
I'm mad at him,
but I really love him more.
Our relationship back then was so good.
What about now? What about now!
I know.
So that year, it was only you and him that retired.
Yeah. He was heartbroken, and I acted on impulse.
I regret it. I regret it now!
What now?
If I could keep playing now, and I hadn't have retired back then, my scores would definitely be better than before.
But what can I do? What now?
Now? Now, I... I...
That's enough.
Don't think about the past.
You-You need to think about the future.
Think about tomorrow. Tomorrow... Tomorrow let's go eat spiced chicken with chili sauce, okay?
Spiced chicken...
Did you break your phone in Norway?
Is there anything you want to say to me?
I think that today, you and Mi Shaofei–
Didn't I tell you before that I am not reliable?
I think you are pretty reliable.
I didn't tell you I went to Norway,
and I turned off my phone and left it in China before leaving. Is that called reliable?
When I came back, I also didn't tell you.
If we didn't happen to run into each other at the stadium, you wouldn't have even seen me. Is that called reliable?
I know you traveled overseas for work.
Today, you're not in a good mood. I won't fight you.
You drank so much earlier. Eat something first.
What if it wasn't for work?
Then why?
Matchmaking.
Introduced through the family. She's pretty well-off and rather good-looking.
Aren't you dating me?
I just said that we would get to know each other.
After getting to know me, do you think there is something not good about me?
You're all right.
How do I say it?
Do you understand the saying, "Chicken speaking with a duck?" (T/N: people not understanding each other)
The feeling you give me is like that.
Maybe because our age gap is too wide.
I'm almost 30, I should marry soon.
I shouldn't just hang myself on one tree, right?
(T/N: put all your eggs in one basket)
You... should also see other people.
I don't want to see other people.
- This kid, why are you so stubborn? Don't you understand the subtext?
- I don't understand.
I think...
You can't go out with me and see other people behind my back.
If you don't like me–
I don't like you.
Am I really that untrustworthy in your eyes?
I promise you. I won't bother Nian Nian again.
I won't find her anymore.
I won't let her have any more expectations towards me in terms of love.
There's no point if we have to force it.
Right?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫