♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 10]
Han Shangyan, where are you?
- Come on!
- Hi.
- What are you doing?
- Come here and drink!
- Let me go!
- Have a drink!
- Come drink!
- What are you doing? Let go of me!
No! No! Han Shangyan!
Han Shangyan, help me! Han Shangyan!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Han Shangyan! Let go of me!
Han Shangyan! Han Shangyan! Let go of him!
Han Shangyan! Put that down!
Do you only know how to solve problems by using violence?
You say that I only know how to solve problems by using violence?
I didn't mean that!
Maybe, they just wanted to get me to have a drink with them but we couldn't communicate with words.
We can try talking to them nicely.
- Okay? Put that down first.
- Han Shangyan! Han Shangyan!
Stop. Stop. Stop.
We're just kidding, come on!
Han Shangyan!
Let him calm down first.
Sorry! Sorry, sorry.
- Are you okay?
♫ I'll wrap my name up for the past that's dead and gone ♫
♫ While the sun is out, I'll seal it in a frame ♫
♫ I'll thoroughly forget the memories that are hard to let go of ♫
♫ And let tomorrow return to my hand ♫
♫ Whether the clouds in the sky are good or bad, I'll treat them as the view ♫
♫ If there is a storm, I'll treat the rainbow as my reward ♫
♫ Remember all the places where my tears fell ♫
♫ I'll wait for the day when the fragrance of flowers will bloom ♫
♫ When the color of night becomes a dark web ♫
You know that Han Shangyan's personality is like this.
It's been ten years, and it has never changed.
Let him cool down for a few days. I'll go and talk to him again, okay? Don't worry.
Excuse me, Miss!
You forgot your cake and coffee.
Oh! Thank you.
You're welcome.
I just wanted to celebrate with him earlier,
so I secretly ordered this cake.
I didn't think, I messed everything up.
It's okay.
Here, I'll give it to him for you.
Rest early.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
My mood is not good right now. It's best you don't bother me.
I have never understood.
How come between me and Solo,
you chose him?
You want to hear the truth?
Yes.
Of the five, the two of us are most similar.
We've only been on Team Solo.
And we only recognize Solo as the team captain.
We also retired together.
To me, Solo is not just a person.
He represents a spirit, a symbol.
He is the beginning of my dream.
Han Shangyan, you should understand what I mean the most.
I know that the team disbanded because of Solo and Ai Qing.
But Han Shangyan, just because they did one thing wrong doesn't mean you can take the two of them and crucify them,
and have them repent to you forever!
This coffee
and this cake
are things Ai Qing wanted me to give you.
She bought it earlier.
You're still the same; love playing strong.
Clean your hands.
The three of us all have one thing we want to say to you.
Happy birthday, Han Shangyan.
Are you in a meeting? Or are you training?
I don't dare to call you, so I'll just leave you a voice mail.
Happy Valentine's Day! Happy Birthday!
Aren't I really smart? I remembered your birthday!
I hope that your work in Norway goes smoothly.
It's your birthday so be happy!
Oh, right! This is the last one! I wanted to say goodnight.
Remember when eating cake you need to make a wish!
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
My wish is...
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
Coming.
Are you busy?
What's up?
Celebrate my birthday with me.
Judy!
Alice!
Hello!
My brother.
Hello, I am Little Mi.
Hello, Judy.
Did you come back to Norway again?
No, I've settled down in China.
Such a pity. It's hard to find men who love cats.
You guys play. I'll go clean up.
I'll let you borrow Alice to play with. I don't let anyone else borrow her.
Thanks.
She likes you.
You haven't changed; you still like cats.
♫ I'd never dreamed that I'd meet somebody like you ♫
Come, come.
So? After disbanding you came here?
First to study.
Then after I graduated, I started a business and established K&K.
I do admire you.
I like CTF, but at best I play in my spare time at the convenience store.
But you're not the same. You had the courage to start a business.
You're the one who truly likes CTF.
But from the expression in your eyes, I can see that you are not content.
You want to achieve something big.
That longing expression can't lie.
Are you used to SP?
In that kind of established company, is there competition among personnel? Do they exclude you, Uncle Mi?
Oh, stop making things up. The atmosphere is great at SP.
Just like Team Solo back in the day.
Besides, Solo is the boss.
The club that he leads will not be that bad.
Okay.
Then you keep fighting.
As a newcomer, you have to have some achievements to account for your boss.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
Tomorrow, I will do well for sure.
Happy Birthday!
What an old tactic.
What do you mean "old tactic"?
No joy in life.
After we are born, we have to deal with these unhappy things every day. Why?
If you don't face these unhappy things in life, how would you know what happiness is?
Listen to me.
After people are born, they need to experience things for themselves, really walk through life, and be happy.
♫ I'd never dreamed that I'd meet somebody like you ♫
The time is almost up. Time to head on stage.
- Let's go.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Youngsters, stay relaxed.
No big deal.
I'm not nervous. My goal is third but I can definitely get fifth. Easy.
Just this little bit of ambition?
Listen. This is the first time you guys are representing China.
At the arena, you can lose to our opponents because your skills are inferior to them.
But you can not give up before the competition is over. Understand?
Understood, Boss.
Wu Bai, as the team captain, do you have anything to say?
This time we aren't competing for ourselves, it's for China.
We're competing to let the whole world know the reputation of the CTF circle.
Come. Let's cheer.
Go!
Team China. Let's go!
As network security is developing by leaps and bounds at the moment,
the matter of cybersecurity is becoming increasingly serious.
Today, top players in cybersecurity competitions coming from all over the world
representing their own countries,
will contend for the title of National Cyberpower.
Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome to the CTF All-Star One-on-One Invitational Live Show in downtown Norway.
Today, the 50 best players from 34 countries will compete for the superstar in a CTF World Hall of Fame.
- Good to see you again.
- Nice to meet you, Archie.
Welcome everyone to our CTF All-Star Individual Invitational Competition.
I'm your commentator, KK.
At our right side is our English fluent commentator, Archie.
On our left is the beautiful commentator you guys are familiar with. Let's hear her introduction!
Hello, everyone. I am the commentator for today, Grace.
Yes. Today, there will be 50 contestants from the top 34 countries in the world.
They're competing in this arena for individual wins.
The winner will immediately enter our CTF World Hall of Fame.
We will first begin the random selection match. Competitors, please pick up your phones.
Press the start key to choose your opponent.
And over here on the screen we can see the competitors are being shuffled.
This side, I also want to ask one of our co-workers, our English fluent, Archie.
Which players are you projecting to do well?
It's hard to say. We've got great competitions every year.
We've got DT from China. We've got Naya from Norway.
Two of the best players in the world as well. Let's see what happens.
We see that Archie is watching DT from China.
But to DT, today's competition might be very difficult for him.
That's right. Whoever they match up with will not be an easy match.
[All-Star Invitational Match-Up]
[VDMT (Germany) vs DT (China)]
[Norway All-Star Invitational]
[ICER (Sweden) vs 97 (China)]
[ICER (France) vs LNIN (China)]
Little Mi's opponent is pretty strong.
[ALL (China) vs PLAY (Columbia)]
Little Mi might be in trouble.
[Little Mi (China) vs NAYA (Norway)]
Okay.
Little Mi vs Naya?
- Relax.
- Stay calm.
I'm telling you to relax! It hurts!
What are you two doing? Be quiet.
Look.
Meeting your opponent, you must not take it lightly. Your opponent is quite strong.
Am I not strong? I'll beat him for sure.
What's happening?
Who's up for Team China? Who else?
K&K has completed the first round.
Now, Wu Bai and Grunt have won.
As predicted. What about our guys?
Lnin won. Next is Ou Qiang.
[ALL (China) vs PLAY (Columbia)]
Okay. So for this match, it will be China's All versus Columbia's Play.
On this side, All force-attacking an eternal defense player is a complete surprise.
Yes. 1-0 and the second round will start.
They immediately found another loophole; on this side, Play noticed that the opponent might've changed attack nodes.
Congrats to All who directly took the win for this round!
Yes! All won!
The old warrior is as strong as ever!
All these years, Ou Qiang's been working as a penetration tester.
He stopped for a few years but he was still able to keep his condition at its peak.
His professional age is even higher than I imagined.
Based on the results from the first round,
China has a very big chance of winning first place in the afternoon's finals!
- Guess: who is the most projected to win?
- Of course, it will be...
What? Think I'll blame you if you say KK's players? I won't!
On the world stage, we are all representing China.
As long as Team China wins, we will all be proud!
Then I'll be honest. The most projected (to win) is definitely DT.
In CTF's competitions, he is always the first individually.
I think, if there are no surprises this time, it will still be him.
What's wrong? Laughing so happily. Are you his fangirl, too?
You don't say, Han Shangyan's little brother is a genius.
Same as him back then.
[Little Mi (China) vs NAYA (Norway)]
How is Little Mi's condition?
This side... Whoa! Unexpectedly, there's an obvious loophole.
Really full of loopholes, Little Mi!
Right now, he is behind by three points.
This competition is divided into three modes: Jeopardy (problem-solving), attack and defense, and mixed-mode.
Contestants are required to attack and defend around the server, mining and exploiting vulnerabilities,
and multiple categories of cybersecurity issues are all part of the competition.
Naya got a complete victory over Little Mi, on this side.
Congratulations to the contestant from Norway,
Naya that won this match.
But that's not to say Little Mi didn't show us a very interesting battle.
But I personally still think that during the middle phase, his mindset was a little blown.
Although he worked hard, a loss is still a loss.
Anyway, I still have one saying for Little Mi: he's an old general still willing to fight for his country.
Let's congratulate Norway's Naya once again.
- Let's also give a round of applause to our Chinese contestant, Little Mi.
- It's okay.
You're unused to this place.
All right! So far, the first round of the competition in the All-Stars Invitational has come to an end.
Yes. I noticed that during the first round, the Chinese contestants had very eye-catching performances!
Yes. Now, other than Little Mi, who unfortunately went up against the Norwegian CTF expert, Naya, and has been eliminated;
the five remaining Chinese contestants have successfully made it into the second round.
Wu Bai has always been first in the CTF world rankings.
Naya is also a very strong contestant.
I believe that he will be able to take down DT in the next match.
[World's First Place DT (China) vs World's Second Place Naya (Norway)]
Actually, we are all looking forward to the duel between those two.
For the audience and us commentators, it will be visual enjoyment.
Yes. Fellow audience, please continue watching this All-Star Individual Invitational Competition.
We will begin the second round soon.
Eat more. Good luck this afternoon.
Ou Qiang, where's Little Mi?
He said he didn't want to eat and went out for some air by himself.
[Little Mi (China) vs NAYA (Norway) - win]
What? Can't accept the loss?
I can't be mentally weak?
It's just a competition.
I'm a bit regretful. It's my first time competing abroad.
I thought I could receive the people's applause on stage.
There are still a lot of opportunities.
I'm old now.
I'm older than you and you're telling me you're old?
Your younger cousin Wu Bai isn't bad. He has your past demeanor.
Compared to me, he's still a bit unskilled. Right?
Little Mi, no matter who wins or loses,
we will be fighting for China.
Good luck!
I just knew you would be here.
This is your unique way of preparing. I have long heard of it.
You... like to sit in silence by yourself.
Especially before a big competition like this.
Some people like it lively.
I like it quiet.
Then am I bothering you?
To be honest, a little bit.
Sorry. Then I'll keep it short.
I actually came to tell you, "Good luck!"
These years, I've seen your exceptional talent and perseverance.
So, I believe that you will help China win the championship today.
Truthfully, I don't only want to prove to the world that China can do it.
I more so want to, in front of you, win the championship on the international stage.
Thank you...
for liking me so much back then.
Did you know? Back when your Team Solo won the championship,
I was still a high school student.
But after seeing you shining so brightly on stage,
I secretly swore that I will one day be like you,
shining brightly on the stage.
In front of you, I will win a championship for China.
No matter if it was the Singapore Invitationals Competition or the International Tour Competition,
I paid close attention to your achievements.
Your performance really was exceptional.
That is different.
It was because of you that I chose CTF.
So whether or not I can take the championship today is very important to me.
Just wait and see.
Truthfully in my eyes,
you are already that shining star.
Good luck!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Summer! Summer! Do you see?
This is Han Shangyan's team. Let's cheer for him, okay?
Fighting, Han Shangyan! Fighting, Han Shangyan!
Isn't he handsome?
Next up is today's finals competition!
This will be between China's DT and Norway's Naya!
Now, although Wu Bai is globally ranked First Place,
coincidentally, Norway's Naya is globally ranked Second Place.
Furthermore, these two have never competed against each other before.
But from their individual achievements this year,
Naya has actually won three more times than Wu Bai.
Moreover, I heard Naya especially went into seclusion to analyze Wu Bai's tactics for over a month.
If it's like this, then I am concerned that Wu Bai's competition might not be so easy.
That's true. Let us warmly welcome the two contestants into the arena!
[World's First Place DT (China) vs World's Second Place Naya (Norway)]
All right, let's count down! Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
This round will be mixed-mode.
Yes. Mixed-mode has incorporated jeopardy (problem-solving) with attack and defense.
Ten problems. Ten nodes.
The contestant wins if they break through their opponent's nodes, or has solved ten problems.
DT. Naya. Which one will you choose?
DT has chosen the mode that Asian contestants excel in: problem-solving mode.
Nice. DT has already solved the first problem.
The second and third problems have appeared simultaneously on DT's screen!
DT has stopped! What is he thinking?
Is he giving Naya an opportunity?
What is the situation? Could it be he wants to solve both at the same time?
Nice! He solved them all! Now what do we see?
The fourth, fifth, and sixth problems!
Three problems! There are three problems!
I've been commentating CTF for many years, but I've never seen a contestant like this!
Solved! DT has solved it!
He's like a monster! Did you guys see that?
These are the skills of the one who is ranked first in the world for CTF!
What's wrong? An error has occurred in Problem #7 for DT.
It's Naya! He's forcefully attacking DT's server!
He has completely ignored the problem-solving!
This is the style of Vikings!
Plunder, plunder, and still plunder.
Naya has taken down three nodes in one go!
DT is being forced to stop solving the problems.
He has been firmly gripped by the Viking!
I will one day be like you,
shining brightly on the stage.
In front of you, I will win a championship for China.
It was because of you that I chose CTF.
So whether or not I can take the championship today is very important to me.
Just wait and see.
There is not much time left for DT. There is not much hope.
The ninth node! Looks like we will have to congratulate Naya in advance.
Wait a minute. Naya has suddenly lost five nodes. What's going on?
Nice!
Naya's security vulnerabilities have all been infiltrated at once!
DT has perfectly tricked Naya into thinking he was solving problems!
DT has perfectly brought Naya down to his own pace.
He made Naya think he was just going to focus on solving problems and not fighting!
In truth, he had already dug a trap for Naya.
Naya is now forced to defend.
He is now using all his energy on stopping the encroaching DT!
But he obviously cannot block it!
It is now 9 - 9.
DT is only one step away from being the champion!
Now, Naya is really on the brink of exhaustion.
This attack from all sides really is too fierce!
Now let’s look at DT’s screen.
What?
Beside this high-frequency attack, he still had the energy to keep solving the problems?
Four problems... three problems...
It’s the last problem!
DT has stopped! His hands are now on the enter key, he's pressed on it!
[ACCESS GRANTED]
YES!
[DT CHAMPION]
♫ Get ready for the crosstown rivals ♫
♫ Be ready when I take the floor ♫
♫ Get ready to defend the title ♫
♫ Give everything so let's go ♫
To our live audience and our live stream audience,
the champion of this year's CTF One-on-One Invitational Competition has already emerged:
He is the Chinese contestant, DT!
Second place goes to the Norwegian contestant, Naya!
And Lnin from China...
He has won third place in this competition!
In the One-on-One Invitational Competition, China obtained first and third place.
Congratulations, China!
Yes! Let's give these three contestants another round of applause!
Summer, they won!
Meat jerky! Meat jerky!
Summer! Summer!
Hello?
Hello? It's really loud over here, can you hear me?
Han Shangyan!
It's me! It's Tong Nian!
I just saw your competition!
Congratulations to you all!
Thank you!
Do you want to hear the cheers for China on-site?
Okay, okay!
Hello? I will be going to the interview soon. I'll talk to you later!
Han Shangyan. Uh... I...
Congrats!
- Mom!!! K&K...
- What are you doing so early in the morning?
World champions!!
You scared me to death! It's so early in the morning, what do you want? What KKK?
"KK" what? You want me to spank you?
Han Shangyan's Club, K&K, is number one in the world.
Third place was also China's, but it was the other club.
In short, Han Shangyan is the best!!
Wait, wait. Come here, come here!
Han Shangyan's company won the world championship?
Look at my daughter! She really does have foresight!
- Where are you going?
- There's still the award ceremony!
This child really does have good foresight. You see...
Let's eat. Let's eat.
Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome back to the 2019 CTF All-Stars Invitational!
We are on-site at the CTF All-Stars Invitational.
The champions have already been chosen.
Let's invite the organizers of our CTF All-Star Individual Invitational Competition to come here and present the awards.
And now, in third place,
hailing from the People's Republic of China, Lnin!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
In second place...
Congratulations.
And now, the champion of the 2019 CTF All-Stars Invitational is....
DT, Wu Bai!
Not bad.
- Congrats!
- Thanks.
♫ There’s always splendor falling ♫
♫ Imitators one after another ♫
♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
Thank you.
Congratulations.
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
Wu Bai!
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
Old Han, you even prepared the national flag?
Little Bai was the most projected to win.
If I don't prepare it, who would? SP will prepare it?
We can prepare it, too!
Yeah!
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
In the past, you also had the chance to stand on the highest podium.
Han Shangyan...
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
- Hi.
- Okay. Come on.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Hi. Can I... interview you?
You don't need to interview me.
They are the main characters for today.
Let's do one more.
Ta-da!
Come, come!
Drink!
Cheers!
Congratulations! It was a good beginning.
Yes. I finally have something to present to headquarters.
But I really need to especially thank you.
Back then, you chose to stand on my side and start the China branch one year earlier.
Why so formal? Aren't we bros?
This is your wish, and I helped you fulfill it. Isn't that great?
But... I'll discuss one matter with you.
That friend of yours. His skills are not that great.
Mi Shaofei?
I watched the entire competition,
the Chinese competitors were all top-level, but he was just average.
Perhaps he was distracted?
Does he have a lot of pressure?
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Hurry what?
I only finished doing half of my hair.
What is it?
Let's go. Taking you guys to have fun.
- I'm still not unrestrained enough?
- You're unrestrained enough.
- Where are we going?
- Wherever you want to go, we will go.
Great! Then, let's go!
Ou Qiang, I just drank some wine with Nan Wei. You drive.
Hello! My name is Ou Qiang!
Get on the car!
Hurry up!
Try out your car!
Let's depart!
This song!
♪ Today, I saw snow drifting through the cold night ♪
♪ With a cold heart, I drift off to faraway places ♪
♪ Chasing in the storm and fog, I can’t tell the shadows apart ♪
- Han Shangyan! Come up and look!
- Too stupid!
Hurry up, come up and look!
Did you hear me? Come up and look!
♫ How many times met with cold shoulders and ridicule ♫
♫ Never giving up the dream inside my heart ♫
♫ In an instant that sudden feeling of losing something ♫
Be careful, you two!
♪ Unconsciously became indifferent ♪
♪ Who understands what I love ♪
♪ Forgive my whole life’s uninhibited indulgement to love freedom ♪
♪ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♪
♪ Abandoning their dreams, anyone can do so ♪
♪ I’m afraid one day it’ll just be you and me ♪
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫