♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid]
[Episode 37]
Concentrate! Lose no time, the match is about to start!
All right. Go! Go! Go!
What's the matter?
What were you guys talking about upstairs? You guys seemed so happy.
Upstairs we were saying... you're handsome!
Knock it off.
No. We all saw you and Solo were chatting so happily, we were happy too,
so we gave you space and didn't come to bother you both.
You're quite sensible.
Of course!
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
Yaya. Look.
You must go watch the match from the audience seats.
Shout for me until your throat splits!
- Remember to shout until your throat splits.
- Yeah.
- They're here! They're here!
- Gun God's here!
- Gun God, we've been waiting a lot for you.
- We root for you!
Gun God, we came from the North-East, we've been waiting for you for a long time. We had a long ride by train.
- Thank you, you worked hard.
- Gun  God, keep fighting! We'll back you forever! Keep fighting!
- Keep fighting!
- I remember you! 2009 in Guangzhou, right?
- Right! It was me! It was me! Keep fighting!
- Thank you.
- Keep fighting!
- Keep fighting.
Gun God, I came especially from Shenyang, I was on the train for over 20 hours, to come root for you.
- I will always root for you!
- Thank you.
- We, too! Gun God!
- Keep fighting!
- Keep fighting, Gun God!
The path we treaded before will not disappear.
- These are all known faces.
- Keep fighting!
I remember you all. Thank you.
You're still staying here to encourage us.
All along, you've never left.
You have never doubted us.
Such an unforsaking feeling will support us,
forever going forward, holding on until the end.
You all will be our strongest back-up,
that mightiest strength supporting us from behind.
Han Shangyan! Han Shangyan! Han Shangyan!
♫ Today, I saw snow drifting through the cold night ♫
♫ With a cold heart, I drift off to faraway places ♫
♫ Chasing in the storm and fog, I can’t tell the shadows apart ♫
♫ You and I in the vast sky ♫
there have been wins and losses,
laughter and crying,
we've been questioned and gossiped about,
we've been criticized and blacklisted.
We never gave explanations, there was no need to explain.
Solo! Solo! Solo! Solo! Solo! Solo! Solo!
Thank you to all the friends who came here today.
Do you still remember us?!
Yes!
We, Team Solo, have returned again!
Thank you for supporting us having a dream.
Clinging to us, rooting for us to keep fighting, thank you!
We all have the dream to win a championship.
To stand on the world stage wearing the national flag.
But in this life I can only be like this.
This is my only regret in life. I have no way to make up for it.
Saying it the nice way, huh?
We're considered like characters of myth, gods immortalized.
Saying it the unpleasant way,
we retired, we decommissioned, can't play anymore.
But China's CTF enterprise will never halt!
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
In this circle, there will always be new people who step forward.
We, Team Solo, is still in this circle.
At SP! At K&K!
We just changed an identity.
We just became that light that helps them succeed!
Good. The Championship!
Is China's! The Championship is China's!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
♫ Still free with myself, I'll sing my song out loud forever ♫
Han Shangyan!
♫ Forgive my whole life’s uninhibited indulgement to love freedom ♫
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
♫ Abandoning their dreams, anyone can do so ♫
♫ I’m afraid one day it’ll just be you and me ♫
Han Shangyan!
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
Han Shangyan, you're too great! Do you know how excited I was?!
A moment ago I was crying! You're terrific! Great great! Great great!
"Great great! Great great! Great great! Great great!"
I finally realized you have so many fans, you're just so outstanding, Han Shangyan!
You're still in public, aren't you embarassed?
I'm not embarassed.
Hurry up, get down, if we have anything to say we can talk back at the hotel.
No! I have a lot more words to say.
Do you know how terrific you are, Han Shangyan? You're too great!
I think you're terrific too! Terrific!
Go do what you got to do.
- Don't stand there.
- You're too stingy, Han Shangyan, what is it that can't be seen?
Right! We're not asking for money.
Sister-in-Law, is it that you think Han Shangyan was too handsome, so you mean to claim sovereignty?
Or else, how could it be all right?
When we go out in a bit, you'll see Han Shangyan's fans in a crazy crowd.
Enough, enough, guys, let's cut it off. Let's give Old Han some dignity.
Old Han... for once has a girl he likes.
Don't get it wrecked!
That's right!
Hurry and get down.
- Hurry and get down.
- No.
If you don't get down, I'll kiss you in front of everyone.
Didn't see anything! Didn't see anything!
You're really bad!
I have to scare you to make you obey, is that it?
They are not strangers!
Right! We are not strangers!
We're family! No fear!
Let him kiss you! Give a kiss! Give a kiss!
- Give a kiss! Give a kiss! Give a kiss! Give a kiss!
- Don't be afraid! Don't be afraid!
- Give a kiss! Give a kiss!
- Stop it! Stop it! The little girl is bashful. Stop it.
Enough, enough, enough. So, it's like this: tonight everyone come to my place.
We'll have a huge crazy party!
Dance! Dance! Dance! Really great!
Solo! You all go first, I'll be there in a little while.
What's going on?
I'll tell you later.
Waiting for you!
Let's go!
What is it?
- Go to a place with me.
- Where?
Beijing Station! It's the first time I come here!
The first time I came to Beijing, it was just to join Solo and the others.
Since then, my life was turned upside down.
That day I sat in the train for over 10 hours.
When I got to Beijing, I was dead tired and dead sleepy.
But when I saw Solo and the others, I came fully awake.
At that time, the 5 of us had very simple ideas.
It was just: make up a team, compete, win the championship.
But people were enough and money wasn't.
I took a trip back home specifically
to take the money my father had left me as education funds before he passed away, and made it into a contribution.
- I know that.
- Let me finish.
All right, I'm listening to you.
The day we disbanded... Solo wanted to give the captain position to me. I refused.
Why?
How to say...
When the captain changes, it feels like it's not the same team as before.
At the time I... was very mad, very pained.
I left everything to Solo and then I just went back to Norway.
Later on I founded K&K.
My original intent was very simple.
I only wanted to make up for my decision back then.
I wanted to establish a formidable club and get all our ex-teammates to come back.
And we can all start over.
Three years ago, when the headquarter was just starting to take off, I couldn't wait to form the China division.
Do you know why?
You're worried that they couldn't wait that long.
You're worried that they would retire.
That's right. I couldn't wait.
I was afraid that they couldn't wait for me.
But no one expected that all 4 of them went to SP.
So you were left all alone, and became the Boss of KK.
Are you bored by the story?
Not at all! I like to hear you tell me these things.
When the 5 of us won the championship,
I felt like the sky belongs to us, the world belongs to us!
As long as the 5 of us work together, there's nothing that we can't do.
Do you know why the Earth spins?
Because of the sun's gravitational pull.
Wrong. It's because the Earth doesn't want everyone to stay in the same spot.
Whether happy or sad,
it hopes everyone can look forward.
After so many years, your dreams have all came true, right?
All that you went through only served to make you better.
But I have one more dream that hasn't come true yet.
What's that?
This is the championship ring that I got when I won my first championship.
It's a little big. You may not be able to wear it.
Who says I can't wear it?
I can wear it on my bracelet. Or I can get another bracelet for it too!
You can figure out a way to wear it.
Tong Nian.
Let's get married.
Married.
Okay?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
My parents...
How would we talk to my parents about this?
If we get married now, what happens if they hate you?
I already spoke with them about it.
I'm not lying to you.
When my step-mom came last time, she came to meet your parents.
So our parents have already met each other.
And I've also promised them that I'm going to take good care of you.
♫ Attempt to use unfamiliarity to explain the distance between us ♫
Are you... not ready yet?
♫ I start to portray an unfamiliar me ♫
♫ Fathoming the untrue distance behind the words ♫
It's not that...
This is the first time someone's proposed to me.
Give me a second. I'm a bit...
I'm especially nervous. I feel like I'm seeing double everywhere!
I'm sorry. Give me some time.
Let me—
I'm not going to eat you!
Feel my hands! My hands are ice cold.
I didn't expect... I didn't expect you to...
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It's fine.
It's fine. Don't worry.
Why did you take it back?
I...
- I was too impulsive.
- What?
Next time.
When will the next time be?
Didn't you propose to me today?
We can talk about it later.
Let's go eat first.
Then when will you propose next time?
When you no longer have any doubts and hesitations towards me,
and you sincerely want to say yes.
Let's go eat.
I didn't agree to his proposal. Is he going to be okay?
You didn't eat, are you hungry?
I'm not hungry.
Did you think back to the days when you first came to Beijing?
Why did she reject me?
Between the two of us, could it be that there is still a problem that cannot be resolved?
Why did I reject him at that time?
I don't know.
Could it be because it was too sudden?
Or is it that in my heart, I am scared of something?
Later on, I have to go hang out with my bros. We might go out for the entire night.
I won't be able to stay with you.
If you want to sleep here or go back to your room and sleep, that's fine.
I'm going.
Han Shangyan.
Are you... afraid of sleeping alone in the dark?
Your mood right now, it's... okay?
It's great.
That's good.
I'm going to go now.
Go ahead.
- Bye.
What? Han Shangyan proposed to you and you... you rejected him?
No! I didn't reject him! At the time...
My head was just buzzing...
So I... I-I... I... I was just stunned, you know?
If you didn't say yes, isn't that still rejection?
No, I...
What do I do... Hurry and help me think of something.
Nian Nian. Tonight, your boyfriend only just returned to the competition circuit.
He finished a true farewell match and beat the top 5 hottest players right now.
Do you know the fans all cried so much, they were so touched that they almost went crazy!
And at this time, he proposed to you, Tong Nian.
He brought his championship ring to propose to you.
Do you know how precious that thing is?
The championship ring from Gun God's first win.
There's only one in the entire world.
And on top, it has G-U-N engraved on it.
Do you know what this means?
At the time my mind was just blank.
I just kept feeling like there was something missing in the middle.
Or... how about this?
So that he doesn't feel sad, I'll go and say I want the ring?
Are... are you stupid?
No one asks for the ring beforehand!
Then what should I do?
Can you not scold me anymore, I already feel really bad.
I also don't know what to do.
Bye Bye.
What should I do?
Gun God is finally here.
You're here?
What big things did you go do? So secretive.
Sure you can?
If you'd come any later, I'd be drunk already!
- Yeah!
- Where did you go? Punish yourself with three cups!
- Get three cups!
- Punish yourself with three cups! Hurry!
Old rules.
Pretending to be in deep thought.
You went to propose?
- Propose?
Propose?
You really intend to marry?
Stop messing around.
You got rejected?
Look at his deflated expression, it's probably true.
You have a lot to say!
Don't be anxious!
- We're all bros.
- Yeah!
- Tell us the truth.
Han Shangyan, you really got rejected?
Didn't she pursue you?
A girl and she backward pursued?
Yep. He's got all the luck with women.
How did you fail?
Tell the bros. We'll work it out for you!
Who said I failed?
I just... suddenly didn't want to propose.
So you proposed halfway and then stopped?
Why? You regretted it?
Han Shangyan, a proposal is a major thing. It's not a trifling matter.
Who said I was treating it like a trifling matter?
She was way too nervous!
She was sweating all over, her face was pale. If it was you, would you keep proposing?
Are you stupid or something?
- That girl, that's the sweat of happiness, right?
- Yeah!
What girl who is being proposed to wouldn't be nervous?
You guys don't understand.
I'm just afraid that she hasn't thought it through and if she impulsively agrees, that in the future she will regret it.
It hasn't been a smooth path for us.
Tell us! We're anxious to death.
Once she was nervous, I thought, was I too impulsive?
After all, today was the farewell match. I'm not very calm.
Besides, there's no other people in my heart anyways.
Let's just take it slow.
Why do you guys keep staring at me?
I'm done talking.
You're just going to leave like that?
If you're not willing to talk about it, we won't ask anymore.
Say, bro. Let's stop pretending to be deep.
This little heart, was already thumping nonstop early on, wasn't it?
Perturbed.
You're afraid the girl will run?
This guy...
Han Shangyan, you're a woman. You're even scared to court a girl!
I am talking about you! You don't even dare to pursue a girl!
Wing Chun martial arts, right?
It hurts.
If I don't teach you a lesson, you won't know who's the boss here, is that it?
- Han Shangyan, what you said is wrong!
- That hurts!
In this house, who is the boss?
Bros. Make him know who the team captain is! Get him!
Who's the boss?
You're the boss?
Keep acting out, huh? Keep acting up!
You're brokenhearted and you vent your anger on your bros, is that it?
Keep acting up, then.
This little face, this beauty!
You're a woman. Give me a kiss!
Give me a kiss!
Say it, say it! What do you want? What do you want?
Let's go gaming all night. What do you think?
- Let's go!
♫ Get ready to defend the title ♫
♫ Get ready for ♫
Wish you prosperity and wealth, may I have my red envelopes.
♪ Love is like the blue sky with white clouds floating by ♪
♪ Under the clouds, the horses race ♪
I'm so bored. Pink, pink, up! Pink, pink, up!
Wu Bai, sorry for bothering you.
I wanted to ask you a few things regarding Han Shangyan. Is it convenient for you?
It's convenient.
I actually wanted to ask you
your brother, in the past has he been rejected by someone before?
I mean in terms of love.
No.
You're his first love. He never took a liking to anyone else.
Then... all these years, he's never had a girl he liked?
Why would he like me?
Maybe... you're the first one who liked him not because of his achievements in CTF.
When the average person sees his scowling face or his bad temper they would've run away long ago.
Why do you like him?
Me? I fell in love with him at first sight.
When you hear that, it might be a bit hard to understand.
But when I first saw him,
I felt that he was the most special person on this planet.
I wasn't simply attracted by his handsomeness.
I really think that he is charming, different from everyone else.
Besides, I really idolize him.
The more I got to know him, I realized that
he has become very awkward and doesn't know how to love
because he lacked a lot of love when he was young.
Thinking about it, he is pretty pitiful.
So it's fortunate that you appeared.
In this period of time, I find that he has become a lot softer.
Telling you honestly, I also really like him like this.
Then he... for example, if someone rejected him for something... afterwards, would he bear a grudge?
Or would he become really fragile, sensitive, or something like that?
Solo disbanded the team... and he remembers that until now.
That's true.
Whatever question you have, just ask directly.
Beating around the bush wastes too much time.
He proposed to me, but I rejected him.
At the time he proposed so suddenly, and in that moment I was stunned and didn't think it through at all.
Do you think he's angry?
That's pretty good too.
Let him have a sense of crisis of losing you.
Perhaps, that's not a bad thing.
I'm guessing that he still doesn't really understand how to love you.
44, 45.
46.
Scram. Count properly!
You're a little too weak, aren't you?
We just did 200, and we didn't even shout.
-Continue.
-47.
48, 49.
50.
Little Mi!
You had to do 200 because you lost to us four times!
- It sounds like you're unsatisfied.
- Unsatisfied.
- Then, let's battle again!
- Come!
Come! Who is afraid of who?
Continue.
So just now, in the end how many did you guys do?
Not that many less than you.
I think it was 200 or 300.
It was 300!
Instant noodles are coming!
- Instant noodles are coming!
- Instant noodles are coming.
Sorry, only three are left. Please make do with it.
Thank you! Keep the change.
No need, no need. You guys are Team Solo, right?
I just finished watching your competition. It was so impressive.
- Did your blood boil with passion?
- Yes!
Awesome!
Give it your all! My treat.
- Thank you!
- Bye!
Old rules.
Girls, and the youngest ones eat first.
I'm already an old man now, team captain.
- We can't break the rules.
- We're letting you eat first so eat. Stop talking nonsense.
That's right! Come. The rest, we'll divide among everyone.
These few days, it's like I was dreaming.
I especially want to return to when I was twenty in the days when we were hanging out together.
For people, a lifetime goes by so fast.
It ends just like that.
Say something nicer to hear!
Yi Qian. I remember in the earlier years you didn't wear glasses.
What have you been doing recently?
My work is selling medical equipment.
That's a good job. You don't have to worry about your salary.
- It's a good job.
- Just doing it for the money.
Why are you sighing? What do you do?
I also sell machines.
Anyway, my life isn't as dynamic as yours.
It's just work. All the same.
Of course there's a difference!
At least in your hearts you guys still have this!
Thirty years old and you guys can still have a heart just like a twenty year old. That's so hard to come by!
When you first brought Mi Shaofei and the others back,
didn't you post on Weibo on behalf of the club?
I still remember that quote!
Listen up.
"Our dream has been sleeping for a long time.
All of our past effort and honor
have been renewed,
- starting from this moment."
- Starting from this moment.
So great!
Yes!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
We're leaving.
You guys can do it!
This time coming back, I'm most happy to see that you and Old Han are back to how you used to be.
Once our team captain, always our team captain.
If you guys are free, you need to come back more often, you know?
SP Club will always be Team Solo's home.
Of course.
Go!
Okay.
GOod luck.
I will miss you guys.
Safe travels.
Have a safe trip.
Give it your all!
We're going!
Good luck, you two!
Good luck!
There's no banquet in this world that doesn't end.
It's not like you'll never see them again.
We'll meet again.
You're back.
You must be tired.
I'm okay, not tired.
Do you want to go eat breakfast?
Okay. I'll go wash up a bit.
Nian Nian, just pretend like nothing happened!
Treat him so well that he can't help but propose to you again!
To be honest, although they say men cannot be spoiled,
but on his farewell match you rejected him.
Then emotionally, you do need to make it up to him!
That's right just treat him super well.
Sis, I think that men always want to save face.
You broke him, you need to give him a way to back out gracefully! Are you stupid?
I'll be done soon! I'm brushing my teeth.
No need to hurry.
That... I-I am going to change.
Going to change. Not in a hurry.
But this door is translucent... I can still see you.
What do you want to eat? I'll go get it for you.
No, no! Sit. I'll go get it for you.
If I go get it for you, isn't it right and proper?
No. Last night you didn't sleep at all, I was afraid that you were too tired.
What do you want to eat? Are fried eggs okay?
If I was tired, I wouldn't have come down to eat.
I was afraid that you just wanted to accompany me and that's why you came down.
I do not wish to make you feel that I came down here to eat just to accompany you.
I hope that you can have your own ideas and make your own choices.
I can eat anything.
Do you want to drink coffee?
Milk? Or milk
I have hands and feet, so why do you have to help me?
I heard that yesterday Boss' marriage proposal was rejected.
- No way! What kind of situation is this?
- Oh my God!
So right now they are performing ex's battle of defense.
You guys believe what he says? It's definitely that Sister-in-law wanted to get married,
Boss loves to chatter. Probably set a whole bunch of stipulations.
Sister-in-law told me! Manager, you be my witness!
Love is not something that us outsiders can understand!
Boss is so pitiful.
It's time someone teach him a lesson.
And it can vent frustrations for those of us who are usually bullied by him.
I feel that saying it like that is going too far, isn't it?
Okay. Eat, eat, eat!
It's really tasty!
Hello, would you like to drink anything?
No need.
I was afraid you would be cold, and I don't know how to adjust this so I covered you with a blanket.
Thank you.
- You're not going to sleep a little?
- I'm not going to sleep, you sleep!
Tong Nian, let's get married.
Get married.
Okay?
My dad and mom... how do we tell my dad and mom?
If we get married now,
if they don't like you, what do we do?
You... still aren't ready?
It's the first time someone has proposed to me.
Just wait a minute, my mood right now...
I'm especially nervous. I feel like everything I see right now is double.
I was too impulsive.
Next time.
When is next time?
In your eyes, am I especially useless?
No personality, lots of shortcomings.
And...
Is it that because I didn't accept your proposal, you are still angry about it now?
I'm not angry.
I'm just a bit... disappointed?
♫ I carefully covered up ♫
On the contrary, I don't feel that you have shortcomings.
The one with shortcomings is actually me.
It's just that in the time that we have been together,
you've always been accommodating to things that make me happy or angry, sad or joyous.
But instead, you lost your own personality... didn't you?
♫ I attempted to cherish this experience ♫
Because... because I feel that you are really good.
I'm afraid I‘m not worthy of you.
So I just wanted... wanted to be able to silently support you,
I didn't want to be a useless person.
How could you be useless? You've helped me a lot.
You've taught me how to love someone, did you not realize?
I have been trying hard, trying hard to become a better me.
So, I need to thank you.
And I also hope that you can wait for me, okay?
♫ ...to deceive everything ♫
Okay.
♫ But no matter how much... ♫
Sleep a little, it's still early.
Then, I'm going to sleep.
♫ ...doesn't care about you ♫
- Aren't you cold?
- I'm fine.
Are your dad and mom home?
No, they're still not off work.
Then, I won't go in. Later on, go take a shower and rest earlier.
Do you want to go in for a little bit?
What I mean is... do you want to eat dinner before you leave?
After the Asian Championships, I'll spend more time with you.
Okay.
Why did you come back?
Passing the door and not entering, it's shameful.
Let's go in first, I'll eat dinner and then go!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫