♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 38]
Are your parents really haven't come home yet?
Didn't I tell you?
Okay.
Her parents are all not home, then should I...
Do you want to go upstairs to rest,
or in the living room?
If he said to go to the bedroom, then what should I do?
Just pretend here is your own home.
You don't have to be nervous or tensed. Just do as you please.
You don't have to be so tensed either.
This is my home, I'm— I'm very relaxed.
Why do you keep squirming?
Nothing. I just felt like...
it's a bit weird.
What weird? It's not the first time coming here.
It's different. The first time you came to our house is to have a blind date with my older cousin.
Blind date.
The second time you came to our house to mislead my parents.
Only this time are you actually sincerely coming to our house for real.
Do you want to watch TV? If you want to, watch it yourself.
I'll go pour a cup of water for you.
- Come back.
- It's fine. You are the guest. Should be like this.
Wait here for me, I'll come back very quickly.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Tea is done. What are you looking at?
You look good when you were little. It's a pity that you weren't a child star.
- How would you know whether I was a child star or not?
- Getting proud of yourself, huh?
I am not lying.
When I was little, I really on TV before.
When I was little, I was famous around the region, okay?
I can tell. You had quite a good childhood when you were little.
Of course. When I was little, my parents love me so much. They would always let me do whatever I want.
Then are you happy being with me?
Yes. Of course, I'm happy.
I still haven't asked you. That day when your stepmom met my parents, what did they talk about?
Which day?
That time! Before your competition, your stepmom came.
She said she wanted to talk to my parents, that time.
It's that time when you lied to me, saying that you guys are meeting at home, but you actually went to a restaurant.
And so I rushed to get back here but no one was home, that time.
- That day?
- Yes.
Let me think about it.
What are you still thinking? Hurry and say it.
What did you guys talk about?
I said...
I
was immature before I was 30.
And hope that Auntie and Uncle would please forgive me.
But towards Tong Nian, my love and feelings are real.
But it's useless with just words from my mouth.
I want to get married. I want to prove with my action.
I also wish you can sincerely nod your head and agree.
Then... what did my parents say?
If I were your parents, I wouldn't happy either.
Look at you. Good looking, good temper, filial, not spoiled,
and you're also a top student.
The most important point is that your family is not short of money.
The only thing that I might be able to show is worse than yours.
Then what happened? What did my parents say?
Your Dad asked me,
what are you taking out to marry my precious daughter?
So I thought it over. And it seems like I really have nothing to take out.
If we talk about age, I am at a disadvantage. If we talk about education, I am also at a disadvantage.
Then I can only talk about dreams.
I said that for the sake of the path of China winning championship, I would sacrifice my body and shed my blood.
but your parents still don't agree.
I got flustered, both of my eyes got red and I knelt in front of them.
I said that if you don't let me marry Nian Nian, I will stay single forever.
You think I'm a fool?
You think I don't know that you lied to me? Why did you make up those lies? Is it that you—
You are so used to using your hands and feet on me now. Taking advantage of me, huh?
Who is taking advantage of who? It's you that's holding my hands, okay?
What?
Hug for a bit.
Me this kind of person
doesn't like to tell the truth.
Other than "I love you", It's better if you not think of other things.
I am just teasing you.
Let me ask you.
After retiring, have you ever regretted it?
Life is a one way street.
Even if one Han Shangyan is gone, there are still a team of K&K behind him.
Behind Han Shangyan, there are still countless Chinese teenagers
who would for the sake of the path to championship, sacrifice their bodies and shed their blood.
Nian Nian! I'm back!
Look what food I bought you.
Dad!
- Uncle.
- Little— Little Han came?
Yes. He came.
- You guys talk. Later it's lunch, let's eat together.
- Dad.
It's the evening. Right now is the evening.
I am old and forgetful. You guys keep chatting.
Okay.
That scared me!
Little Han, is the food I made good?
- Yes.
- If it's good then eat more.
- I'll get you a shrimp. Men should eat more shrimp.
- Thank you, Uncle.
Don't be so tensed. Just relax.
After grandpa went back, most of the time, I would eat box meal at the club.
So I'm used to it.
Eat what? Eat box meal?
Eat less box meal. Box meal is very bad for the body.
When you have time, come here often.
I'll make some good food for you, okay?
Thank you, Uncle.
Eat, eat.
Yesterday's champion, eat more.
Your club won yesterday?
No we didn't. We lost. We got second place.
Second place is not bad either. It's equivalent to getting second place on a national exam.
It's a good results. Continue to work hard.
That's not it. He told his teammates, in his dictionary,
there are only championship and failure.
You have ambition.
Why give yourself so much pressure?
Here, give it to me. I'll help you get another bowl of rice.
Thank you, Auntie.
Here, get me a bowl of soup.
Eat, eat.
What did I say wrong? Why did you kick me?
Speak less. The more you speak, the worse it gets.
What if they don't like hearing that?
I understand.
Little Han. What are you doing?
Hurry, put it down! Put it down!
- Why are you washing the dishes?
- It's fine. Put it down, let me do it.
You are the guest, I can't let you was the dishes.
Uncle, it's fine. It's fine.
Little Han, listen to me. We have an excellent tradition in this home. Men handle the outside and women the inside.
This kind of thing is always Nian Nian's mother doing it.
- I never do any of it. You can't be doing this.
- It's fine. It's fine.
Put it down. Put it down, okay?
Old Tong, what's wrong with you? How could you let Little Han do the dishes?
I saw him doing dishes as soon as I came in. I couldn't persuade him.
Don't you feel bad? These are things that are normally done by you. Don't you feel bad?
- Enough. don't wash it anymore. Little Han.
- It's fine. It should be.
What it should be? It's the first time that you came to our house to eat dinner. It shouldn't be.
- That's right.
- Nian Nian, hurry and get him out.
It's fine. He normally does this. He is a model worker.
I almost finish washing it. Uncle, Auntie, you guys can go watch TV. I'll come later.
Go, go. It's fine.
Let's go.
Model worker. Do you want me to help you?
No need. Just watch beside me, that'll be fine.
Okay then. I'll accompany you here.
- Do you know what your dad told me earlier?
- What did he say?
He said in your home,  the women handle the inside and men the outside.
He never does housework.
He said it?
He is the one doing the work normally. Why did he have to bluff to you?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Are you full?
I am quite full.
About that, thank you for washing the dishes.
Don't I wash all the dishes every time?
That's true.
Are you cold?
I wore so much, how can I be cold?
Exactly what do you want to say?
Be careful driving.
That's not what you wanted to say.
I want to say... Just that when I watch movies,
when two people date, when they say bye to each other,
the main guy would always...
To the girl...
Nian Nian. I hope that you can be more courageous when you are with me.
If you want to do anything, just do it. You don't have to be afraid,
and you don't have to be scared of me, okay?
What are you doing?!
Oh it's you.
I apologize.
Sir. Have you eaten yet?
I am very full.
Young lady, I am so envious of you.
Envious of me?
This great young man.
In our neighborhood, he might as well buy a parking spot and sleep here every night.
Every time I work night shift, I will bump into him.
I bet you guys were in a fight.
I didn't!
In the society nowadays,
how many boneheads would actually be waiting downstairs of a girl's place.
You must cherish him. These kind of people may seem wild.
But in reality, they are really stubborn.
He is a good man.
Sir, don't say too much.
This one here, she gets embarrassed easily.
I am sorry. Sorry to bother.
Continue. Continue!
So there was someone waiting downstairs everyday?
He had the wrong person.
If I really did that everyday, wouldn't I be a pervert?
I'm leaving.
He has the wrong person!
Are you done?
Go back.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Get in the car.
I know, I will leave after I see you go back up.
You get in the car first.
There are many bad people in your neighborhood. Let me see you go back up first.
Get in the car first.
You go back first.
Okay, I'm going back.
I'm really leaving.
Come in.
You look so happy that it seems like you mouth can't be closed.
Nian Nian, let me tell you. I originally thought that if you had
chosen Little Han, you would turn bad.
I thought he wasn't sincere towards you.
But I later realized, I misunderstood.
Whether it is pursuing his career or love,
he is a very serious person.
But the most important point is that,
I think my daughter, she is very happy.
When I am with him, I am very happy, and I feel blessed.
But I think it's my problem.
Perhaps it's because I care about him too much, I like him too much.
That's why for a lot of things, I always go along with him,
not having my own opinion.
Lately, he has been telling me frequently that
he wishes that I would express my own opinion more often, and not just follow what he says.
He thinks that he wants me to have my own character.
Nian Nian, do you know that day,
when we were with him and his stepmom, what he said?
What did he say?
I realized I love Nian Nian more and more.
I wish that I could see her everyday, and that a life like this can continue for a lifetime.
That's why I mentioned it.
He said he originally
only had two words in his eyes - winning championship.
But it's not the same anymore. Now, in his eyes,
there are four words - winning championship,
and Tong Nian.
He also said that he wants to marry you.
If he marries you, he can feel at ease.
He can then continue to cultivate his Chinese champions.
And for you, you can get as many Ph.D.'s as you wish.
Because he wishes that you have your own dream,
and he would support you fully.
What else did he say?
You must let mom think for a bit.
Quickly tell me.
He also said he knows you were pampered by us since you were little, and you are spoiled.
That's a perfect match for him. He thinks he doesn't really have any strengths.
That he only knows how to teach the kids, and do housework.
And the rest, only knows how to spoil you.
Mom, do you know?
Han Shangyan is really, really great.
When he used to be poor in the past, he lived with his teammates.
Cooking, cleaning and whatnot were all done by him.
He is not spoiled at all, and he also treats his friend very well.
In short, please get to know him more.
Do you think that your mom hasn't observed him?
I think that now, he is
changing bit by bit for you.
Just like when two people go on a walk, they don't have to say much.
But slowly, their pace would be the same.
And they would both see
the views that the other person enjoys. Do you understand?
It's not cooperation that only comes from one side.
Mom, thank you for understanding me
Oh right, then has he mentioned anything about the future?
He already proposed to me.
Really? Did you agree?
Why?
Is what I did wrong?
It's not wrong.
I never thought you would reject him.
Nian Nian, there is nothing bad about this.
Mom just hopes that when you make a decision,
it is made after thinking it through, and that would be fine.
You are here.
This is my first time coming here.
I am actually a bit nervous.
A grown man like you, after going through so much, what's there to be nervous about?
This is a new beginning.
Furthermore, the outcome of this is still unknown.
I am someone with a wife and a child.
Unlike you, all alone and empty-handed.
I have to take responsibilities for the people at home.
Let me ask you a question.
I kind of remember that your wife used to be your fan.
When she got together with you, would her love for you
be just a kind of personal admiration,
and a bit abnormal?
What are you saying? Why did you call my wife abnormal?
I think you are abnormal.
Han Shangyan. Are you finally troubled by love?
What troubles would I have?
I have a friend who has some troubles in these kinds of matter. I am asking for him.
Tell me. Did you do something to her?
What would I have done? Are you going to tell me or not?
Okay. I will stop beating around the bush.
As someone who went through this, let me summarize it for you.
If one day, this girl yells at you,
and then hugs you while crying,
then it means that it is love, and not admiration.
When you love someone, shouldn't you pay attention to them?
If you really love me, then you should pay attention to me.
So I don't think you understand me at all, if you understood me then you would know
that I'm allergic to Mangoes. I like to eat strawberries.
I don't care if you have money or not, what I care is if your future has me in it.
I like it when we're embarrassed and don't talk too much.
I don't like it when you talk all over the place and think too much.
Okay Okay, let's not argue anymore, okay?
If we continue like this there would be no end.
Let's calm down.
Clean up. Later, come down to have a meeting.
My second place winners.
- Boss. We...
- What meeting are you guys having?
Boss... We... We are not slacking off. Our eyes don't feel well, we are resting for just five minutes.
- Five minutes.
I didn't scold you guys, what are you guys nervous about?
Scared me. I thought Boss took the wrong medicine today.
Boss, didn't you say before that there are only champions, second place winners are all failure?
That's right.
Really?
Then face the wall and reflect on your mistakes later.
Everyone please go to the conference room and we will have a small meeting.
You've worked hard.
That's not it.
Manager, what's going on? Boss today...
What's going on? What's with the positivity today?
Let's go to the meeting. Go. Asian Championship is starting soon.
Ghost scaring people.
Have a small meeting.
You've worked hard.
Let's go.
Hello everyone.
Hello.
Sit down.
Sit.
Buff, come here now to introduce yourself. Old rule.
Then I'll start.
Everyone, we went against each other before.
I lost to you guys.
I believe that even without a self introduction, you guys know me well.
We have already analyzed through you.
I am Buff. Real name is Bi Dongran.I am 31 years old this year, an advanced age player.
I have won the national championship.
Including this year, I have been a team leader for four years.
As of now, I am number four in the server ranking.
This is my first time joining an official club.
In the old days, there were no concept of clubs.
The reason that I came back after retiring for so long
is because I want to fight one more time for my dream.
Everyone knows already that I am an advanced age player.
No club would dare to just easily take me in.
Right here, I need to thank Club K&K for giving me this opportunity.
Welcome Buff, joining Team K&K.
As a new member, Buff
will train with us for half a month.
In this half month, there will be five official players and one substitute.
They will go through a rotating collaboration training.
After half a month, we will have two assessments.
One will be personal performance and the other one will be teamwork collaboration.
After that, we will be finalizing the competing team.
And then train for another half a month and compete in the Asian Championship.
Any questions?
No.
Of course.
This is very fair.
I'll listen to Boss.
The team's reputation trumps everything.
Good.
Buff, your team uniform.
Thanks, Boss.
Little Mi, when you see Little Bai later, let him meet his new teammate.
No problem.
New teammate.
In here is the registration form for new members. Hurry and fill it out later.
And give it to me. I need to help you get social insurance and whatnot.
We even have social insurance here?
Of course. Where is your social insurance under? Hometown?
Yes. In Jinan.
Okay. Then I should help you transfer that over.
It's fine. These are all the minor stuff. I will handle it for you.
Because for these stuff, we give them all to outsourcing companies to handle them for us.
But don't worry, I will definitely get it handled for you.
What's there to be worried about? The benefits here are really good.
Right. Indeed.
There's another important thing: our balance between work and rest.
You know that our boss has a quick temper, especially towards time management.
I understand.
Thanks, team manager.
Your computer.
- Okay.
- If you have any questions, tell me.
- Okay!
You four go to Boss's bedroom for a small meeting.
For Buff?
Go.
Whatever, let's go.
-Boss.
Sit anywhere.
Why are you guys standing there? Sit.
Earlier was our public welcome meeting.
Now, let's talk about proper business in private.
Boss, whoever you want to change, just say it.
I already said that after half a month, the decision will be based on your scores.
Currently, the ranking in my brain is empty.
Us two have the lowest rankings. It's definitely one of us.
If you don't want to get eliminated, then work hard.
K&K is very fair. It's not rigged.
You? Do you feel burdened?
No.
Say the truth.
I feel anxious, but not burdened.
Boss, I'm an adult. I'm not little Demo.
What does it have to do with me?
Using our skills to determine the outcome is most fair.
No wonder you're one of my members.
It's my turn, right? I'm also not burdened.
I'll also do my best, Boss.
You're not at risk of getting eliminated. Don't add to the trouble.
That's hard to say. Other than Captain, nobody can perform well steadily.
Right. Uncle Buff is ranked fourth.
Other than DT, nobody can defeat him for sure.
Have some ambition, okay? Have faith.
As long as you believe you are the strongest, you are the strongest.
It's same as getting a girlfriend.
How are those two related?
- Bring out your fighting spirit.
- Right.
Okay. it's all pretty good. You guys can go back.
Okay. We're leaving, Boss.
97, stay.
Let's go.
Bye.
Sit.
So sad. Our team is going to be adjusted.
Let's make a promise. No matter who becomes the substitute,
you're not allowed to cry or drag the team down.
Don't worry. I know myself.
No, what's wrong with you two, huh?
Didn't we already agree on it inside?
Have ambition and faith! Got it?
- Keep fighting!
That's right. Let's go.
Wu Bai acts aloof and doesn't like to talk,
while Grunt just looks annoying.
Do me a favor. Try to unify the team.
This?
Not willing to?
I am, I am. I was wondering why you asked me to stay.
You scared me!
Boss, actually, you're not willing to let anyone go, right?
We're like your children.
Yes. We're all close,
and you're all a part of my heart.
When SP first switched out Mi Shaofei,
I even yelled at Solo,
but reality later proved
that what they did is correct.
In any case, I understand.
In this national finals, judging by the current situation,
SP has improved by more than one grade.
If we don't change, we'll never win.
Boss, not only I understand.
Everyone understands.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Oh, my.
Doing CTF depends on physical strength, too?
Going to die, going to die.
I can't do it anymore.
Second to last?
Today is the first day. Let me try again.
Tomorrow, I'll pass two people.
Can't even run faster than a 30-year-old uncle. Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm not a long-distance runner.
If the youths are strong, then the nation is strong.
How is long-distance running related to patriotism?
I know it now, Boss.
Enough! Get up! There are still 5 rounds to go!
- What?
- We only rested for one minute, Boss!
Do you want to compete?
Come on. ♪ 56 ethnic groups ♪
Ready, go!
♪ 56 ethnic groups ♪
♪ Are like 56 flowers ♪
♪ 56 brothers and sisters as one family ♪
♪ 56 different languages create one sentence ♪
♪ "I love my China, I love my China, I love my China" ♪
What flavor's yours?
- Give it.
- It's meat.
Where's he going?
You forgot to take juice.
Thanks.
The food here is nice.
Of course. Our Boss gives us the best food, even if he has to resort to eating steamed buns.
That's indeed his style.
Let me tell you. 97 is
totally evil, Buff. Be careful!
He's the best at creating factions.
Please don't let him trick you. If you treat him as a friend, he'll treat you as a follower.
What are you saying? Enough! What about it?
- It's the truth. Why can't we say it? Why did you steal my juice?
- That's how you are.
- Right.
- Didn't you get some earlier?
- I gave mine to Buff.
- Where's ours?
- I didn't even get to drink it yet.
You're not new here. Get more yourself.
Are we even brothers anymore?
- Pour some yourself.
- Seriously.
Buff. Once you're done getting food, come sit with us.
Okay! Tell me about how evil 97 is.
No problem!
So irresolute.
Tong Nian.
Zheng Hui, why are you here?
Wait for me. I'll come to find you after I hang up my clothes.
Why are you here? Didn't I say that I'll go out to find you?
This is... girl's dorm.
I have some things that I want to talk to you about.
Are you available?
Yes. Come in.
It's just that it's a bit messy.
Let me clean up a bit. Sit anywhere you like.
Is this... busy dating?
Also, I don't believe,
that person called Han Shangyan didn't go in your bedroom before.
He has been in my room.
You misunderstood. Han Shangyan is not that type of person.
He didn't do any to me. You misunderstood.
So?
Does he treat you like a little girl who worships him
or an accessory for him to use on his path to the championship while he's feeling bored?
Senior, I don't think it's suitable for us to chat here today.
You... I'm not feeling well right now. How about this?
Go back first and I'll treat you to coffee someday. Is that okay?
Tong Nian, look at me carefully.
Why can't you look properly at me?
I am looking at you.
I like you.
I like you. I like you!
I liked you for two years. Total of two years!
Didn't you realize how well I treat you?
Also, whether in education level, temperament, age,
or our majors,
I am the most compatible with you.
Also... Also, I'll earn more money!
I can become better. I can surpass him!
I... I can give you happiness. I will do all that I can to...
I know, senior! I know that you'll earn a lot of money in the future.
I know that you'll become better. You definitely will.
But that's not what I want. That's not what I want.
I thank you for liking me.
But let's end it here, okay?
Just right here.
Why? Why?
How am I worse than Han Shangyan?
How am I worse than Han Shangyan? Tell me and I can change, Tong Nian!
You're great. Zheng Hui, you really are great, but do you know how it feels for two people to be together?
When I'm with Han Shangyan,
there's a certain feeling to it. We understand each other.
We don't need to say anything to know what the other is thinking.
After he and I started dating,
I didn't care if he isn't giving me enough.
Instead, I'm more worried if I have given him too little.
When I'm with him, I just want him to be happy. I want him
to be happier each day.
So you're so sure...
You're sure that you like him?
I love him.
I really really love him.
Each day, I love him more.
These past few days have been hard for me.
I can't eat or sleep properly.
I just want you to please give me a chance.
Can you give me a chance?
Thank you for liking me.
But I believe that in the future there would be a better girl
that is better than me for you.
For sure there will be.
Keep fighting, okay?
Sorry.
Zheng Hui.
I'm sorry.
As I watched Zheng Hui walk away,
I suddenly understood something.
I love Han Shangyan, not because he's the famous Gun God,
but because I can truly feel his happiness and sadness.
I want to stay with him as he works towards his dream.
Over this half month, other than Wu Bai who trains alone,
the others have been training at K&K with all they've got.
Even Buff and Little Mi
are treasuring this rare opportunity.
Of the six people, only five can compete on the stage.
Although it's determined by skill, it's still very cruel.
As the competition date comes closer,
everyone is even more nervous.
Exhaustion and running low on energy
are inevitable consequences.
Because of this, they need even more determination and perseverance.
Everyone cheers on the other because we are all on the same team.
We are each other's best companion.
Boo!
What?
Why are you this nervous?
Why are you guys laughing at me?
Little Demo!
You guys, don't always each instant noodles. Eat something else.
Instant noodles are fast. We need to train, Boss.
That's right.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫