♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 21]
I'm telling you. I've met that classmate of Nian Nian's.
He's decent and hard-working.
I heard that he is doing a Ph.D. now.
My brother and sister-in-law really like him.
They say this kid's prospects have no limit.
They're very optimistic about his future.
No, no.
You're saying that Nian Nian is with her male classmate?
Yeah, that's what I mean.
No, that's not right.
- Isn't Nian Nian dating my grandson?
- Oh my.
You don't know yet?
Know what?
Look at my big mouth.
The kids are probably worried about you and didn't dare tell you.
This... Then tell me!
Nian Nian broke up with Little Han long ago.
Broke up?
It's the kids' business, I didn't ask too much.
My sister-in-law warned me, lest I should say something wrong.
Look. With my big mouth, I've still said the wrong thing.
No, that's not it.
A few days ago, Nian Nian came to chat with me.
They feel they aren't a good match and broke up, but are still friends.
No, no. I can see that Nian Nian has feelings for my grandson.
Uncle Han, today I came to pass on a message.
Tell Little Han to let go.
There's plenty of fragrant grasses everywhere, right?
(T/N: Idiom - same as "plenty of fish in the sea")
Find a person that's suited for him.
What do you say?
What's the big fuss?
What's going on?
Sister-in-Law's gift to you... was this?
What're you here for?
The tournament... The tournament schedule is out.
This cat is really cute.
This cat is so endearing to hold, Boss.
Sister-In-Law knows you're unsociable and she gave you a cat to keep you company.
So thoughtful of her.
Boss, when you are free, spend more time with Sister-In-Law. Really.
Girls need to be kept company, right?
Like training. We can train by ourselves and do fine. Seriously, you don't have to mind us.
Why do you talk so much?
My cat. Take this.
Back to you.
Then... I'll be going, Boss.
Do you know what Sister-in-Law gave him?
- What?
What're you saying? I can't hear.
Hurry, hurry!
Don't rush.
Do you all know what Sister-in-Law gave Boss?
Don't just blindly guess.
Hurry and tell us. Don't leave us hanging.
- A cat.
- What?
- A cat?
Okay, start betting.
Let's see how many days this cat can last for.
I'm betting on a week, I'll stake my latest purchase from a few days:
my new e-reader.
That much?
Auntie, who bought all of these?
Little Han ordered them. They just came.
What? Boss ordered them?
He said in a short while he's sending these things home along with the cat.
He needs to go back to headquarters for a week. There's no one to take care of the cat here.
Boss is getting serious!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
What're you looking at?
Boss, that's so cute.
Kitty is cute, or I'm cute?
The kitty's cute!
Both are cute!
Is Auntie Zhao here? Tell her to come and see me.
Okay.
What're you waiting for?
Auntie, I need to go out of the country for a week this time. I don't have the time to shut all the windows.
Be careful and don't open any doors or windows.
Cats aren't like dogs; they will jump out of the window.
And all the food and things are here.
Okay.
Hey, are you planning to spend a lifetime
to show what "trifling destroys the will" means?
(T/N: Idiom - "The pursuit of petty pleasures thwarts high aims")
It's not enough that you play on computers, now you're raising pets!
Then, that's it. Call me if anything happens.
Also, I've copied down the pet store number and vet number on the cat carrier here.
You can contact them at any time.
Hey, I'm talking to you. Are you listening?
Oh wait. There's also my grandfather.
Please, take good care of him.
Don't worry. I'll take care of Grandpa.
Then, I'll get familiar with the cat.
I've never raised one; let me try.
Slowly.
I'm leaving the country for a week and there's no one to take care of the cat.
When I come back, I'll take the cat away.
We're going to Nian Nian's house.
- Now?
- Right now.
She's at school and not at home.
She's been at home the whole week.
I'm already clear about what happened between you and her.
What're you clear about?
You! To make a girl cry so brokenly, don't you feel remorse?
I won't care about you.
You deserve to be alone! Just don't hurt others.
Let's go! Do you want me to get mad again?
You already said that I deserve to be alone, why would I go?
I'm wrong, okay.
You have such a bad temper, who can stand that?
Let alone a girl, you don't even have regular friends.
What're you laughing for?
I think your words are extremely true.
I really deserve to be alone.
Let's go, let's go!
Nian Nian's mother and I agreed on 8:00.
It's okay if you don't go in, but at least you have to take me!
Let's go!
Don't get out yet.
I need to talk to you.
You and I are grandpa and grandson; can we not argue?
I've been yelling at you for so many years that even I feel tired!
Can you give me a little less to worry about?
As soon as your stepmother remarries,
the Hans will only be you and me.
I don't want to argue with you, either.
Look. Every time you yell, I'm just listening. Right?
Tong Nian is really a good kid.
You should open your eyes.
When your mom gets admitted to the hospital tomorrow, then my heart can be more at ease.
After that, we'll just have to wait for the surgery.
- Thank you, Uncle.
- Thank you.
No need to thank me.
Your mom's condition... the earlier we perform surgery, the better.
We'll arrange it according to the patient's actual condition.
Also, it's a big surgery for your mother.
You have to stay with her and take care of her all of the time.
The only point I'm worried about is: with you taking care of your mother, will it affect your studies?
Uncle, don't worry about this. I am in a Masters-Ph.D. combined program.
If I miss some time, I can make it up later for sure.
That's good.
Mom, don't worry.
Okay.
Uncle Han!
I was slow but managed to get home before you arrived.
Coming back this late?
I had some errands.
Go in.
Greet her.
Auntie... hello.
Let's go in.
Uncle Han, come in.
Old Tong. Old Tong.
- Uncle Han is here!
- Uncle Han is here?
- Little Tong.
Uncle Han, come, come.
Come inside and have a seat.
I will carry your bag.
Little Han.
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Nian Nian!
Grandpa Han, why are you here?
To see you.
- Grandpa Han.
- Sit.
Careful now.
You're playing on the computer?
No, I'm coding.
That's great. Good girl.
Hello.
Hi, this is...
His name is Zheng Hui. He's Nian Nian's senior in university.
At the time he was in his third year, he skipped directly to a Ph.D.
Moreover, this kid is extremely sensible.
- Hello, Grandpa.
- And this?
Zheng Hui's mom.
Hello, have a seat. You're guests.
You're welcome.
Bring Grandpa some tea.
Your name is...?
Grandpa, my name's Zheng Hui.
I'm Nian Nian's classmate.
I am actually her senior classmate. I am in the combined bachelor-master-doctorate program.
Last year, Nian Nian and I represented our school to go participate in ACM; a world competition!
We were the champions of Asia.
Oh. Great.
Do you come by often?
Nian Nian and I are good friends. We often eat together or have a drink.
Sometimes, after school, we also go back home together.
Then, what're you here for today?
My mom's health isn't great.
So, I'm asking Uncle to take care of her.
It's all thanks to Mr. Tong.
Next time, she can come alone.
You don't have to come with her.
- Yes.
- His mom is getting on with age.
This child is very filial.
- Where's Nian Nian?
- I'll go take a look. How come she's so slow?
Nian Nian!
Grandpa, have some fruits.
I don't like fruits.
Grandpa, it's fine. Don't take me for a stranger.
I'm not that close with you.
Didn't we just meet today?
As a mother, I always hope my daughter can find someone matching in education
and age, to be her boyfriend.
That way, they could share a language and interests, isn't that right?
I'm not the kind of person who clings to the past.
But, Little Han, can you stand in my shoes and think from my perspective a moment?
Anyone who knows what you've been through since you were little,
I think would never rest easy giving their daughter to you.
Auntie, regarding my past, I have no excuses to make.
It's all my fault.
Also, you're so much older than Nian Nian.
Do you two share a language?
Also, what Nian Nian's learning right now, what is it called?
Neural network, can you understand it?
I don't understand Nian Nian's field,
but she has told me about it.
Whatever she does, I will respect it.
How about what you do?
Do you mean my club?
Right, I am an outsider. I can't criticize your profession.
I can only express my position of not appreciating it much.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
What? Are you unhappy?
No.
I'm used to it.
I never count on an outsider to be able to understand me.
I haven't in the past and I won't in the future.
I'm telling you. Nian Nian is very simple.
When it comes to feelings, she has no experience at all.
But you're not the same. You've been in society for so long!
When you act and talk, you always have that same manner.
But to tell you the truth, I don't like it at all.
Did you think I couldn't see your attitude towards Nian Nian during the New Year's Eve dinner?
Enough. I don't want to stand here and keep finding fault with you.
Didn't you two break up?
Shortly before Nian Nian's birthday, right?
She cried a lot.
Fine, then. Since it's like this,
I hope you won't use Nian Nian's soft spot, her tender heart, to let this linger.
I'm her mom, I know her too well.
This root must be cut off from your side, understood?
Auntie, what you said is very clear to me.
I don't really know how to say things, so if I said anything wrong,
please consider that I'm an elder and try to understand me.
And please consider that we are of the older generation.
Don't trouble Nian Nian again, okay?
Okay.
I promise you.
Now that you've promised, I'm relieved.
Are you still going in?
No need, I'm going to drive around.
Take your time. And when Grandpa is ready to leave, give me a call.
Then, I'll be heading in.
Little Han,
can I really trust you?
Auntie,
am I this untrustworthy in your eyes?
I'll say this again.
I promise you I won't bother Nian Nian again.
I won't go find her again.
I won't let her have any feelings of love for me.
Nian Nian is very simple.
When it comes to feelings, she has no experience at all.
But you're not the same. You've been in society for so long!
But to tell you the truth, I don't like it at all.
Did you think I couldn't see your attitude towards Nian Nian during the New Year's Eve dinner?
To make a girl cry so brokenly, don't you feel remorse?
I won't care about you. You deserve to be alone!
Grandpa Han, try this. This is Earl Grey green tea, I just bought it recently.
You know it's good, so you bought it for your parents as a good daughter, didn't you?
Not really, my mom likes tea,
so I buy her some wherever I go.
Grandpa Han likes tea, too. Next time, buy me some, too.
Okay, what tea do you like? I can buy it for you.
Really?
Uncle Han.
- Where's Han Shangyan?
- Han Shangyan? Did he come?
Nian Nian, I'm speaking with Grandpa, don't interrupt.
Little Han said he wouldn't be coming in.
He is waiting outside. He probably thinks our older generation's conversations are boring.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find him. It's unsuitable for a guest to be outside.
I'm going to find him.
The number you've dialed is unavailable, please–
♫ I carefully covered up that I don’t mind ♫
♫ So that I can be in your world, slowly walking closer ♫
♫ I attempted to cherish this experience ♫
♫ Attempt to use unfamiliarity to explain the distance between us ♫
♫ I start to portray an unfamiliar me ♫
♫ Fathoming the untrue distance behind the words ♫
♫ I thought I possessed the acting skills to deceive everything ♫
Louis, how long have you been here?
About ten years?
Louis, let me ask you. You've been a bartender for ten years,
haven't you ever wanted to see the world and travel around?
To do something more...
More glorious?
Yeah.
Actually, a bartender's knowledge isn't small. Try this brand.
What wine is it?
Besheen Wine.
Tea and Wine?
The tea and wine flavors mixed together.
How about that? I understand this but you don't.
Just like dreams, everyone has something they chase after.
What matters... is to be free.
Cheers to being free.
Hello, who is this?
Hello, I'm Han Shangyan.
Did you change your number?
No. This is my back up.
A wily hare has three burrows.
(T/N: idiom - "A smart person has several hideouts")
Where are you?
New World.
Okay. I'll go find you.
Sure, I'll send the location.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
♫ Trying to find the one that is me ♫
You're here?
I see that you are getting corrupted.
It's a rare opportunity.
We got qualified for the next round. I'm taking a half-day off.
Alcohol isn't good for professional players.
An occasional indulgence is fine.
I've been in Shanghai for several months now and I haven't come here yet.
Do you remember we used to be over there?
We didn't have any money back then. Ou Qiang found out when Ladies' Night was
and men could come in for free.
Ai Qing brought the four of us in.
When the owner saw us...
Remember that?
Remember?
Memories.
Yeah.
Have a little bit. I got my paycheck. Today, I'll buy.
No, I have to drive.
Where did you park?
A street nearby; a friend's.
What? Did something happen?
I've personally never known self-reproach.
I always thought the past was in the past.
But actually, all the absurd things I've done were noted by people.
Have you done something terrible and then regretted it?
Taking my mom's money earned from her shop and going to the internet cafe, does that count?
Your mom didn't beat you?
No. My mom loves me very dearly, you know that.
For over 20 years, I've been spoiled by her.
Girlfriend: don't have one.
Job: couldn't find one.
She told me it was fine.
As long as I was safe and healthy, it was fine.
But I do regret something.
That is retiring.
At that time my age, stamina, technique, everything was top-notch.
I let my emotions affect my decisions. All was wasted.
Little Mi,
when you say that...
it's like sticking a knife into my heart. Do you know that?
I can only tell you.
Only you can understand me.
Han Shangyan,
do you know you're the most pitiful?
Look at your attitude from back then?
Retiring?
How many people are below your level? Yet you retired.
You know how many people supported you since you were nothing until you become Gun God.
How many peoples' hearts did you break, Han Shangyan?
I know.
You and I, we thought retiring back then was really cool. Right?
When we were most powerful, we withdrew. It was like a myth!
It wasn't being unrestrained.
It was suicide.
Sometimes I also think about
what exactly was the point of me coming back to Shanghai?
Was coming back the right choice?
What's with all the depressing talk?
I just want to say that things, whatever they are, should not be forced.
I'm not suitable for competing and that's that!
Nian Nian, what are you doing at this time?
I'm waiting for a friend.
It's cold today; go wait inside.
Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Nian Nian.
Mom, didn't you say Han Shangyan was outside?
He was just here.
Nian Nian, there are still many guests inside.
Having them wait isn't nice. Come in.
Old Han, why'd you come?
Little Mi, why didn't you tell me?
Here, drink.
Here.
- Chief, add a glass!
- Okay!
What? Unhappy that I came?
Talk!
Love problems.
What kind of love problems?
You, with a face like that you have love problems?
No way.
Get lost.
You two chat, I'm going.
I just came and you're leaving?
With the kid wandering blindly outside, I can't rest easy.
Since when did you have a kid?
No, whose kid?
Ask him.
Drink.
- Little Li?
- Uncle.
I see that Zheng Hui is a good child.
Yeah, and he takes good care of Nian Nian.
Can't be! He's so young, his heart isn't settled yet.
How would he know how to take care of other people?
I saw that you talked with Little Han for a bit.
Did he make you mad?
No.
My grandson doesn't really know how to talk
and he doesn't make his elders happy.
But his nature is not bad.
Uncle, look. Little Han is your grandson,
so if I say too much, it isn't good. Right?
Right, right.
Recently, I've been researching his online competition.
Actually, it's pretty difficult.
Regular people can't just do it.
I hope you can give him another chance, to know him.
I like Nian Nian a lot and believe he'll treat her well.
Uncle, please don't put me in a difficult position.
Just let the young ones do as they please.
Let's not care anymore, okay?
Go and have some tea.
Why would you duck behind a car? It's very dangerous!
Why're you hiding from me?
They are all inside. Are you not coming in?
Or did your club come upon something that made you unhappy?
Say what you need.
Is it because of Zheng Hui and his mom?
Who's Zheng Hui?
The boy you saw at the university last time.
Just a passerby. Why would I remember him? I'd forgotten.
Although you forgot, I'm still going to explain.
Zheng Hui was raised by his mother alone. His mom is sick, but they don't have money.
So, I told my dad to treat her. He brought his mom to Shanghai.
Oh, they're staying at our house because there are no spots in the hospital.
But tomorrow there will be. They'll leave and won't come again.
Explanation concluded.
Did you understand?
How's the cat I gave you? Is it behaving?
It almost bit me.
If it bites me, I have to get a shot.
Isn't that a bother to me?
Sorry.
How about... you give it to me, I'll take care of it.
I gave it away.
Who'd you give it to?
My housemaid.
Why your housemaid?
Because I don't like it.
Making decisions by yourself will make people resent you, you get it?
When I'd just given it to you,
you didn't say you disliked it.
And it's also a living creature. I gave it to you and you gave it to someone else.
What if that person doesn't treat it well?
How about if you ask for it back?
I'll take care of it.
Go back home.
What do you like?
I'll make a game code for you, as an apology gift. Okay?
I like to be alone in silence.
I'm in a bad mood. I don't feel like talking.
Go back.
I won't bother you any longer.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
What is it? Melancholy over the passing of seasons?
(T/N: literary theme in poetry)
A moment ago... I had a talk with Little Han downstairs.
I guessed that.
Say, I've been a teacher for so many years.
I've never spoken harshly to anyone.
You're the principal of a kindergarten. Every day you face a bunch of children,
who could you speak harshly to?
But I think that Little Han...
He and our Nian Nian aren't compatible in any way.
You see, whether we talk about education or age...
and his past... and his attitude!
None of that suits our Nian Nian.
What? You disagree?
I agree! How could I not?
On this matter, you and I will always have the same opinion.
You and I are on the same side of the war; we've been against it all along.
But I think when I talked to that kid a moment ago, I was a little harsh.
I'm afraid he can't take it.
He's a thirty-year-old man.
He can't take a few harsh words from you?
Doesn't he have any psychological endurance?
You're overthinking it.
You just keep too much worry in your heart.
Okay, stop worrying. Go to bed.
You kid, what have you been mulling over since we came back? Talk to me a bit.
...that was just an excuse!
Hey, where are you going?
I was afraid you couldn't sleep well, so I made you a soothing tea.
Tell me. What do you want me to do?
It isn't as good as the tea Nian Nian makes.
Back in the day, I should have locked you at home.
I shouldn't have let you get close to a computer so early but should have made you study properly.
Say, how good would it be if you were any bit like your father!
- Are you watching this?
- No.
Look. You just like to interrupt me.
What was I saying?
My dad.
Right, right! Look how good your father was in his studies.
Say, what parent will let their daughter marry a man with no proper occupation and a mouth full of nonsense?
- Peking opera or Shaoxing opera?
- Peking Opera.
(T/N: different genres of Chinese traditional opera)
I was chatting with Nian Nian's mom.
She dropped a line here and there.
She doesn't like you at all.
You changed it.
Little Bai, you're back? Why so late? Come here.
Come watch with Grandpa.
Look how nice Little Bai is!
Grandpa wants to watch Peking Opera. Watch with him.
Dnt y sy y hd act appndcts n wntd m t tk y t th hsptl?
What're you saying? Speak louder.
Didn't you say you had acute appendicitis and wanted me to take you to the hospital?
You believe what I say?
Look how much the old man likes you. Keep him company, I'm going.
He's just like this! A mouth full of nonsense.
Whatever. What do you want to watch?
I'll watch Peking Opera.
Can you?
Yeah.
[K&K]
[NetEase Music]
[my good Friends]
[Little Squid]
It's so cute, why don't you like it?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫