♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 18]
I'm done. I'm going to rest a bit.
Sister-in-Law, you brought your computer?
I snuck out of school, so there are a lot of things I haven't done yet.
Pretty nice, huh? In the internet cafe, we don't have to fret over no WiFi.
Sister-in-Law, have you been to an internet cafe before or did you play at home?
My aunt's family manages an internet cafe.
I met Han Shangyan through an internet cafe.
- Internet cafe?
- Yeah.
He's been to an internet cafe?
Did you two fall in love at first sight?
Us two... We met right before New Year's when he came to the internet cafe for a night.
Really? Tell me the details. You two...
You really think you're here for vacation?
No, I was just worried that Sister-in-Law might have been bored.
Worried she'd be bored?
How about you go write a retirement letter and I'll immediately let you leave,
then you'll have plenty of time to chat with her.
I'm so young. Why're you making me retire?
- Still talking?
- I'm going to train now; talk to you later.
Is this hat ugly?
You didn't give me enough time this morning.
I didn't have time to brush my hair so I wore a hat.
Is there something in my eye?
Wait! I'm going to the restroom.
Didn't you go to the restroom?
I'm not going anymore.
She's going to be here for another two hours.
Are you just going to be eyeing her the whole time?
Is she going to be like this every day?
So, she'll come every day?
But I'm leaving tomorrow. How many more days are you staying for?
One week... or maybe more. I'm not sure.
She's not going to be just here. Later, we have lots of meetings, competitions, parties–
Party?
Didn't you come here to train? Why are there parties?
They can't just train, they have to rest.
You can rest. You can go and surf, swim, or bathe in the sun.
Why do you have to party?
Miss Tong Nian, we've been together a maximum of four days.
You already can't accept this?
As long as it's your work, I support you.
I support you!
Don't worry about me! Go!
Work hard! I support your work!
Work hard! I support you!
I think they've all improved.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Boss, where's Sister-in-Law?
[Linwangcun]
Playing outside.
How'd you know I was here?
Coconut!
Bored?
No. I'm just thinking about my project.
What project?
There are lots. Which do you want to hear?
Whichever one. In any case, I don't know your major. I'll just listen for fun.
Then, I'll tell you about artificial intelligence in criminal investigations.
Okay.
First, I'll tell you about criminal investigations.
Actually, we're just making a face identification system
to help them find the needle in the haystack through finding offenders from decade-old cases.
These offenders are very cunning, you know.
If they just change their names and location, it's impossible to find them.
Also, ten years have passed. A human's eye cannot detect their changes.
At that time, it's our turn.
- You've cracked cases before?
- Of course, more than one thousand cases.
For example?
For example, there was a murderer who escaped.
Then, he became a monk,
so this case hadn't been cracked since.
And then?
Then, we made a face identification system.
The police put his picture from ten years ago in the computer,
and the computer searched and found his current ID photo as a monk.
Even if your name and birth date are all fake, that's okay.
The computer can recognize faces. Amazing, right?
This case has been on the news, so I can tell you.
There are also many I have to keep secret.
Pretty nice.
Compliment me!
Getting proud?
I'll compliment you.
Reward?
You want a reward?
What do you want?
I want to see you, yourself, compete.
Isn't it enough for me to teach people?
That's not the same. I want to know you better.
Come with me.
Demo, get up.
Boss.
Get up, let me.
97, let's start a round.
Boss, please don't. How could I beat you?
Stop talking and hurry.
This... I...
I can finally see him play with my own eyes!
Years ago, he was the Gun God who was liked by so many people.
Nice!
This...
Dang.
At this moment, I'm more certain that if he hadn't retired,
he'd be the best.
Come on, 97! You could've held in there for a few more seconds!
Thank you, Boss, for showing me your skills! I'm learning a lot!
Satisfied?
Why isn't Sister-in-Law eating? Does our food not suit her taste?
I don't know.
97, bring Sister-in-Law two new dishes.
Sister-in-Law, why aren't you eating?
No, I'll eat soon.
Boss added some dishes for you. Here's more.
Thanks.
Take your time.
It's too much, thanks.
- Are you full?
- Yeah.
Let's go walk around.
- Go out for a stroll.
- Sister-in-Law, we're leaving.
- Bye-bye.
- Why aren't you eating? Doesn't suit your taste?
- No, I was waiting for you.
- Is it enough?
- Yes.
- If not, tell me.
- Okay.
So much food... Are leftovers allowed?
Leaving food isn't that good.
Aren't you eating?
Why are you only eating rice? Won't you eat some vegetables?
I'm not that picky. As long as I can fill my stomach.
Hurry and finish, don't waste.
I'm so full.
Fifteen minutes and we're leaving. Hurry and eat.
Fifteen minutes?
Hurry up.
These brats, not tidying up again.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
[The First Sanya Training Camp Individual Matches]
First, let's test your luck.
Later, everyone will draw out their opponent.
Today's elimination method is all one versus one.
Outside of this, there are three more competitions going on.
This is considered a small team competition.
Then, how is the final ranking decided?
There will be five people left.
The rest will all be eliminated.
But our teams are the most powerful. Eliminating each other isn't very fair.
What's so unfair?
Can you only showcase your skills by beating people who are weaker than you?
No, Boss. I don't mean it like that.
I just think competing like this isn't very fair towards our ranking.
Is ranking important?
There are only two rankings in K&K's dictionary.
- Winner and loser.
- All right, Boss.
Also, handsome and not handsome.
You want to die?
Joking, joking.
Okay, let's start.
Then let's flip a coin.
No. Let K&K choose first.
Cool.
Okay, Team K&K choose first.
My opponent is Lnin.
- Take good care of me, all right?
- Take good care of you? You're going to lose for sure.
Blow him up.
Following.
I got Ou Qiang.
Little Demo, call me older brother.
Mine is Hua Ti.
Okay!
- I'm against you.
- You're so unlucky.
- You seem to always be put up against the hardest people.
- It's all the same.
What do you mean? If you're against him, that means you'll get eliminated the earliest.
How will you increase your rank? I'm not saying your skills aren't good enough, just...
Okay, okay.
His ranking is number one. Whoever competes against him is the same.
Okay, let's change our seats. Sit across from your opponent.
In this one-on-one competition case, because this is a training camp, there aren't many judges watching,
so please keep yourselves in check.
Later, whoever wins will raise their hand.
I will keep track of winners and ones eliminated on the whiteboard.
Grunt won.
Bingo!
Ou Qiang won.
Yes!
Hua Ti won.
Following won.
Wu Bai won.
Today's winners are Wu Bai, Grunt, Ou Qiang, Hua Ti and Following.
Congratulations, everyone!
So comfortable! We can have a break like this.
Is Little Bai really powerful? No one can win against him.
Before Solo retired, he won against him once.
Solo? Their ages are so different, but they've competed before?
Little Bai started his career early.
Sister-in-Law! Want to go play in the water?
Want to go play together?
Boss! Sister-in-Law!
- Done competing?
- Yes!
What are you guys doing?
- Relaxing.
- Yeah, taking a break.
Relax?
You lost to SP and you still want to relax?
Don't you have a sense of shame?
No, Wu Bai and I won, right?
Right, right.
Although we lost, we still have to relax!
Yeah.
Go ahead. If you want to relax, then do fifty push-ups on the spot and I'll let you go.
What?
- Boss!
- No, seriously?
Do you want to relax?
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's do it, let's do it.
Count for yourselves.
- Okay.
One, two, three...
- Continue.
- What?
Four.
- Your... What was it? Artificial intelligence.
- Five.
Last time, I talked to you about criminal investigations. This time I'll tell you about medical applications.
- My senior is mainly in charge of medical applications.
- Six.
- We're working together with the hospital to identify pulmonary nodules.
- Seven. Eight.
- Before that, we had actually been working with another hospital.
- Nine.
- But that hospital didn't really trust us.
- Ten.
They found a very professional team to compete with our program.
Mainly, we use old medical records and imaging to identify the nodules and to see which team can identify more.
You won?
Not only did we win, we also found ones the hospital originally missed.
You know, because some nodules are especially small,
it's difficult for doctors and experts to identify all of the nodules within.
But our artificial intelligence system, on that day, was able to do it.
Within the old record, we were able to find a nodule that had not been identified.
- That's a blessing for that patient.
- 37.
That's right.
- I think if we are given a few more years, we can do even better.
- 44, 48.
- Furthermore, our program filters cases very quickly.
- 48. 46.
It can save a lot of manpower for the hospital.
50!
Are you all okay?
Boss, we finished.
You're all so tired, it must mean your bodies are weak. How about you go back and rest?
- No, we aren't tired.
-Yeah!
We're perfectly good!
- Right.
- So easy!
Go play.
- Let's go!
- Thanks, Boss!
I have to say, Old Han really has a way of leading his team.
Yeah.
Looks like these kids really look up to him.
Absolute skills bring about absolute admiration.
Shouldn't leaders be like that?
What? You two don't want to roll with me anymore?
Do you need to do some push-ups, too?
No, no, no!
- No need.
- It's so hot, go and change so we can swim a bit.
Okay.
- I'll set the bar.
- Come on!
Want to sit for a bit?
No.
- When's your flight tomorrow?
- At night.
Oh, at night.
I have training at 3:00 p.m., so I won't be able to send you off.
It's fine.
Then, you're still free in the day.
You can play around more.
Okay.
Go rest, I'll leave now.
It's already 10:00 p.m. Do you still have to work?
Of course. Two phone call meetings. One at 10:00 p.m. and one at 12:00 a.m.
Then, you'll be sleeping at 1:00 a.m.
Pretty much.
So tiring.
Then, I'll really be going.
Or after you finish your meetings, you can tell me.
I won't sleep that early.
We can chat or something.
How about if you just come with me?
Don't you have some programming code to write?
After my meeting, I can keep you company.
Okay.
Bring your computer, let's go.
- I'll look up some data for a bit.
- Okay.
I have something I'm very curious about that I want to ask you.
Say it.
I see that when you are writing code, you like to wear these headphones;
but no one else is in the room, so why do you still wear them?
What is this?
It's nice to listen to, right?
These sounds can help make me calm down and think deeply.
- Interesting, right?
- Yes!
If you press here, you can add in the sound of light rain.
And this one, listen closely.
You can add in a pleasant sound of bells.
Did I fall asleep?
When did I fall asleep?
Just when I went to go pour out some coffee.
I was just listening along, and I fell asleep!
You came to Sanya, and you didn't even go out to play. Do you feel very aggrieved?
No, not at all!
To be honest, I'm usually like this; about the same.
Compared to what I thought...
you are a bit different.
What is different?
Just...
Is it... Is it good or bad?
Say it!
Do you want to go back and sleep or go out and walk a bit?
I am good with anything, I'll listen to you!
It's also the first time those kids from the club have come to Sanya.
I can't just always arrange for them to train at an internet cafe every day.
Then, I won't sleep either.
Go back and get ready.
Go!
- Where should I put–
- Just give it to me!
Then, I'll go back first.
- Bye!
See you later!
You're not going to sleep for a little?
I'm making a small version of software; it's almost done!
What is it?
Not telling you right now!
Hey! Not allowed to look. Even if you saw it, you wouldn't know what it is.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Boss has a fear of heights. He doesn't dare to go.
Really?
Fear of heights?
Listen up. For today's morning training, we have arranged for self-training.
No way, Boss.
Look. It's just mountain trails everywhere!
How do you expect us to train here?
We've been in Sanya for so many days already.
Every day we are just training, going to class, competing.
This is a place for vacation, and we haven't even rested for a day! You are too inhumane!
Sailing against the current. If you stop moving forward, you fall back. (T/N: An idiom)
Do you not know that competitions and rankings are also very cruel?
But there isn't just one type of training method! Some people are suited to rigorous training.
- 97.
- Besides, if you stretch a rubber band too taut, it can break! We are all really tired already!
- Can you stop talking already?
- What? Are you guys not tired?!
97, don't talk to Boss like that.
What's wrong with what I said? You guys don't dare and say it, I'll say it on your behalf!
Are you guys tired? I'm asking you! Are you guys tired?
97,
I still remember when you first started. Back then, you worked really hard.
You quickly learned how to make reinforcements and catch loopholes.
And you even used log analysis to support the team,
and that's how you rose quickly in rankings.
But in our line of work, isn't this how it should be?
Just now I already said,
today is self-training.
It is to let you guys relax.
You guys can do whatever you want.
It's not like I took a rope and tied you guys up.
Also, I have a question for you.
Do you remember your enthusiasm from back then?
I remember.
Boss, I haven't worked hard enough.
I should be fighting harder.
Go relax.
- Let's go.
- Don't be unhappy.
Let's go.
Don't be upset. They're still kids; they're immature.
And how old are you?
Let's go sit for a while.
- Sister-in-Law!
Be careful!
- Okay!
- We know!
You're awake? Look, I finished it!
Right now, it is a total of fifty-two cards.
Other than the ones in your hand, there are fifty remaining.
Then in the next round, the probability of the cards dealt will be like this.
If all your cards have been pressed down by the opponent,
then you need to flip a card again and you have to continue.
But this software calculates using the cost-plus method.
You worked so hard and didn't sleep just to make a game for me to play?
Like this.
Do you understand it?
I am currently working hard to understand what you are saying.
This... It isn't hard, is it?
It's very simple. You just need to use probability to understand it.
Do you not like it?
It took me two nights to make it.
Do not sway it! Boss!
Look at 97, he keeps swaying!
Boss, control him! You–
97, stop swaying! You're representing K&K–
They are really noisy.
Boss!
There's a lot of people over here.
Let's go with them together to play for a bit!
Let's go!
It's so high up!
Look! Isn't it high, Han Shangyan?
Tong Nian? If you're scared of heights, then let's not go over.
I'm not scared of heights. I can do it.
-  Hurry. Hurry.
- You aren't scared of heights?
Then, you should go first. I'll come after.
No. We clearly said we'd go together.
Come here.
I get it now. You are scared?
If you're scared, it's fine. We can go down the mountain.
Are you joking? Why would I be scared?
Are you okay?
Tong Nian, let's just stay right here.
No, people say this is the lover's bridge.
If lovers walk across the bridge, they'll be together forever.
- We must walk over.
- No, no, no...
Don't believe in superstition. This is just a bridge, it can't determine anything. Let's stay here.
I guessed it right.
I finally know what Han Shangyan, who isn't scared of anything, is afraid of! He's scared of heights!
Han Shangyan is scared of heights!
Hold onto my waist and we'll walk there slowly.
Close your eyes.
All right. You come back here!
You're going back so fast! You're not scared!
Come back here!
Han Shangyan!
Hello.
Why aren't you getting into the car? You have something to say?
I want a new team uniform, can I?
To match with this badge.
I'll keep it as a souvenir, okay?
If there isn't any, it's fine.
Pretend I didn't say anything. Take care.
Don't always work overnight. Sleep more.
I'm going.
Take it home and wash it.
Sir, to the airport!
All right.
Bye-bye! Take care of yourself.
♫ I don't want to wake up ♫
♫ Prepare, take a deep breath in ♫
♫ I want to climb to the mountain top with you ♫
♫ Look at the most beautiful night view with you ♫
♫ I want to make you happy ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, we won’t worry regardless of how far ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, taking you to travel the universe ♫
♫ Give you everything that is the best ♫
♫ Quietly saying: I love you ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, I'll stay by your side ♫
♫ Time will stop at this moment ♫
♫ Quietly telling you: I love you ♫
You must be careful at night.
Don't let another person do "that" to you.
Tong Nian! You're back?
Man's clothes! Man's clothes!
I... I didn't say it's not.
Why did you bring back his clothes?
Did he trick you to Sanya and then live in the same room as you?
What are you talking about?
No, no, no! I had a room. I had my own room.
- Really?
- Really.
No, I'm still concerned.
Tell me straight. How old is he?
29, almost 30.
30? That old?
Not old!
Then... Then where did you guys meet?
Internet cafe.
Internet cafe? How long have you guys known each other?
Anyway, we have quite a lot of fate.
At first, we met each other, but we didn't know each other.
Then, we met each other in another city, and we just suddenly got together.
That doesn't count. That time doesn't count as dating. So later, we broke up again. After breaking up, we met again.
When we met again, we got back together again. After we got together, we broke up again because I drank too much.
After breaking up, which is now, we are back together again.
Anyway, it was all a mess but I really like him, Yaya.
I really, really like him.
Hold on a second. Hold on. Let me sort this out.
Let me sort this out. So first,
So first, in a mess you two got together and broke up.
Then you got back together again. Then, you were drunk and then you guys broke up again.
Now you guys are together again.
That's about what happened.
You... Wait.
This person and the two before are the same person?
How could you hang yourself on just one man?
Did you know that if a man breaks up with you multiple times, he doesn't cherish you–
No. At first, he wasn't the one who wanted to break up with me. Just...
Well, it's not his problem.
Then, tell me what he does for a career.
Anything's fine.
As long as he's not an old dude who sits around in an internet cafe all day long.
He is older than me, by a lot!
- Move, move. I'm going down to clean up.
- You...
I can't explain clearly to you.
Don't touch my things.
Have an orange.
Eat more, eat more. Bite it, bite it.
Is it good?
Shangyan.
I heard you caught a cold.
I especially got you this cold relief.
I've heard a very moving story.
It was during the Team Solo period.
Whenever you guys would go to a competition, Captain Solo would prepare this.
Give me a cup of warm water.
No need.
I'm going back to my room to rest very soon. Thank you.
Isn't it tiring to date a little girlfriend?
She can't take care of you, and you still have to spend time keeping her company.
I really don't know why you want to make yourself so tired.
You're wrong.
It's because I can't bear her leaving so I got sick.
Oh... right. You haven't dated for too long that you don't know this feeling.
But as soon as you fall in love with someone, your energy will be great and your strength greater.
I ask you not to spend your time and energy on me.
It's no use. I'm going.
Shangyan!
What are you looking at?
An advanced CTF tutorial.
Why are you suddenly interested in this?
It's not sudden. I even recorded a theme song for them before.
I really like this. Tell me about it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay, okay. Hurry, Yaya. Come here.
Hurry and come teach me, in case I get yelled at later.
He yells at you?
No. He doesn't. He yells at his team members.
What an attitude.
Why are you always talking bad things about him?
Okay, I won't say it anymore.
So dedicated. Is it because of that old man that you're suddenly learning CTF?
I can't just watch you be scammed.
Who knows if your boyfriend really knows CTF?
He does. His CTF skills are really, really great.
How good is it?
I just know that online he's rated as the Grand Master Level.
(T/N: basically the OG level)
Grand... He's so good at bragging!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫