♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 32]
- Hello.
Excuse me, is the guest of room 1019 still here?
Hold on a moment.
Apologies but that guest just checked out.
Oh, thanks.
You didn't catch him?
No, he checked out already.
I'll ask Old Xiang for you.
I'll do it instead.
What time is Buff's train?
It's at 11, so it won't be leaving soon.
Sorry, the phone you have dialed is currently turned off.
Bi Dongran!
(TN: Buff's Chinese name)
Han Shangyan.
What are you doing yelling and screaming in a public place?
Why did I realize earlier that you would be here?
After all these years, you still like to eat this?
You're lucky that my hearing is good.
What's up? Need something from me?
What are you going to do once you get back? Look for work?
Of course. I have a wife and a son.
I have to be responsible for the family.
Eat first. We can chat while eating.
Why are you looking for me, just say it.
Do you still want to compete?
What, you want to sign a contract with me?
Why else would I be here?
I rush here this early in morning just to rub salt in your wounds?
(TN: idiom: to throw a rock on someone who fell down a well)
Just to kick you one more time before you left?
No no, I didn't think that.
Even though we are competitors, I know you are not that kind of person.
Say it, why do you want to sign me?
Because of your record.
What, not prepared to ask for a price?
Then how much do you think I'm worth?
The captain of a national championship winning team.
This sounds nice, but has no real value.
Listed #4, this year's rank is pretty good.
But the age is getting up there, maximum two more years before retirement.
Everything you say is correct. You know and you still want to sign me?
How about this. Two years, I'll give you roughly–
Can I join the main team?
I looked for you because I wanted you to join the main team.
But you have to start as an alternate.
There's no way for this national championship since you haven't even worked with the other team members.
Fine, I agree.
Whether you can compete depends on how well you gel with the other members and your personal performance.
My plan is for you to join the team after the national championship and fight for the Asia Cup.
Are all these things you say true?
What else could it be?
But if your performance goes downhill, then I can't help you.
Everything depends on yourself.
Okay, I agree.
Agreeing so easily?
You are not going to set a starting price?
Starting price?
I want to compete, I even dream about it.
I can satisfy this request. K&K is a constantly running train that won't stop.
You better not be sick then, crying and asking me to let you off.
Oh right. I can promise you that my performance won't get worse.
Promise me that I can get in the main team. This term must be in the contract.
No problem.
You are agreeing so easily...
Wait a second.
I have to think it over.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Oh right. I just thought of another term, I want to discuss it with you.
If I go now, I will likely shake the morale of the team, right?
That's why let's sign the contract first.
As for the Club, don't go there as of yet.
When the national finals end, I will have a meeting with the kids.
Everyone recognizes good results, they shouldn't be affected much.
Okay.
I never thought that after all these twists and turns,
the person who saves me in the end is you.
Don't try to cotton up with me. If it weren't for your good performance, who would care about you.
But for these two months, you must promise me that your condition won't go down.
Or else, I will terminate the contract with you.
You just put your heart in your abdomen.
(T/N: Don't worry)
I will not let go of this opportunity.
That's all I wanted to hear.
For CTF, you either don't touch it at all,
or if you do, you must get good results.
Or else, let alone letting other people down, you are first letting yourself down.
Right.
But those brothers of mine...
Their performances do not meet my expectation.
I understand.
Your champion dream, accomplish it yourself.
Look at this terminal here. So many people coming and passing.
How many of them actually got to accomplish their dream and going back to their hometown in glory?
I think people are alive because of their dreams, sustaining them to go on.
Oh right. The ticket that I wasted, you must reimburse that for me.
Okay!
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
Let Buff live at your place for now.
He will officially come after the finals.
That works. I already paid rent and internet bills anyway.
It would be a waste if no one lives there.
Give me the receipt, I will reimburse it for you.
Oh please. Stop acting like you're rich.
I am the one managing your account now.
Look at you, you are in a big deficit now.
Do you still have underwear to wear? Did you wear any today? Let me take a look.
I heard things are going well with Tong Nian?
Looking at your expression, there must be some hidden stories.
Take a look!
Is it really that funny?
Yaya.
Yaya!
What?
Read it later, wait for me.
What's wrong?
Turn this way.
I want to discuss something with you.
Han Shangyan told me...
What did he say?
He told me he wants to get married with me.
Get married?!
Get married?! So soon!
She is at her prime years, why would she be in a rush to do that?
I don't know.
You are getting married?
You are getting married?!
You...You...
If we are talking about your age, you should be anxious.
But...
Han Shangyan, it's not that I want to ridicule you.
Other than looking good, you are really not suited to be a husband.
But being able to find someone who sincerely wants to marry. I wish you happiness.
And you're suitable?
Boss, you're getting married?
You've only just kissed, and you're going to get married?
- What kind of tempo is this?
- Honestly, I thought about it.
If we really get married, that's also fine!
You really have blindly fallen in love.
I'm not! Besides, I don't want to break up.
If we don't break up, then at the end doesn't that mean we will get married?
Then I definitely have to warn you. Don't be mad.
Tell me.
In his brain, there is only competing. Aren't you mad?
Yeah!
He's older than you by ten years. You don't want to observe a bit more?
He is infamous for his bad temper, aren't you afraid of getting scolded?
Yeah!
When you get scolded, don't you feel wronged?
I don't feel wronged!
If a man has no career, how are they different from salted fish?
And, although he is older than me,
our communication has no barriers at all.
And you guys don't even know how good his temper is!
He is actually such a great person. He can cook, and he also enjoys working hard.
Actually, you guys misunderstood him before.
Most of the time, his temper was extremely gentle, very gentle.
Especially gentle.
Gen...tle?
Are you sure you're talking about him?
I am sure!
It's over, it's over. I can't talk her out of it.
This person has become drunk on love.
Anyway, he is the best.
What's it got to do with you?
- Don't! Don't, don't!
- Who told you to eavesdrop on others?
- I was wrong, I was wrong.
- That's all you have to say?
- Boss, I swear I will never say anything.
- Control your mouth, you know?
Cutting off, cutting off!
Let's go.
Go back and train!
Strike while the iron is hot! Today, we move.
Tomorrow, we can let Buff move in.
Grunt! Demo!
What?
Exciting news!
What happened?
Boss... is going to get married!
- No way!
- Really?!
Sister-in-Law is powerful, Sister-in-Law is mighty!
No, no! Wait!
Really? The word "marriage" does not match with Boss.
I'm 100% sure. I just overheard at the tea and living room.
Boss said it to our manager! How can it be fake?
- What else did they say?
- I didn't hear all of it.
At the beginning sounds like they said something about wedding dresses, wedding candies, or something like that.
I went closer to listen but Boss found me out, and then I ran over here.
I reckon... they are going to live together!
Wait, wait. Wait!
Does this mean that they will sleep on the same bed?
♫ I want to climb to the mountain peak with you ♫
♫ Watching the most beautiful night sky with you ♫
♫ I want to tease you and make you happy ♫
You might not be very clear on this, your mom has some opinions towards me. I haven't thought through how to resolve this yet.
If I go and mention marriage to her right now,
I'm afraid... she will come find me with a kitchen knife in her hands.
W-what's wrong?
- Your dad came out.
- My dad?
Every morning he goes to walk the dog. We can't let him find us! If he finds out, I'm dead!
Nian Nian, what happened to you?
Why are you happy in one moment and sighing in the next?
I am thinking... if he is willing to marry me, then I also want to marry him.
But how do I deal with my dad and mom? Particularly my mom, she especially hates him.
I think you could let him go to your house more often.
Then have him help your mom tidy up or something like that.
How can he go?
My dad and mom still think that we have broken up.
No one told them that we got back together.
Then you should somehow give them a hint.
I don't dare!
I am afraid that after I tell my dad and mom, they will go find Han Shangyan and educate him together.
I don't want to let him be scolded again.
I don't want to let him feel wronged!
I don't want to let him be misunderstood by others again!
Especially my mom.
I don't want to let him know that my mom says so many bad things about him.
I feel... why don't you stop thinking about it for now?
Let's go and help Bro Little Mi clean up first.
You, tidy up a bit!
Come. Come in and look around.
- This place is very nice.
- There are utensils in the kitchen.
- You're here?
- Hello.
I am tidying up the bathroom. Nian Nian went out to go buy some things to eat and drink.
She was afraid your fridge would be empty because you just moved in.
You guys are so thoughtful.
- We already paid for three months rent, so rest assured and live here.
- Okay.
The shower has also been tidied. We've prepared some toiletries for you already too.
- Thank you so much.
- Don't do anymore, I can do it myself!
You put down your things and go rest!
- It's all done!
- This must be your wife?
She's such a good person.
She's not my wife.
- You haven't married yet? Then I can prepare a big red envelope for you! (T/N: Contains money as a gift)
- No, no!
No.
I... I am Han Shangyan's girlfriend's university classmate.
I am her best friend.
What is going on here?
Then... the relationship between you two is also very good.
We... take care of each other.
Take care of each other...
I-I am going to go see Nian Nian.
Why has Tong Nian gone for such a long time and still not come back?
- Go quickly.
- Right?
- She likes you?
- No. Hurry and go look around.
- That's very good!
- Very good.
- Try a bite.
- I won't eat it. You eat it!
Then I'll eat it!
Today is so hot. The sun is so bright. Is it bright?
Let's hurry and move stuff.
What's wrong?
What? You want to dance?
Stand here. Wait in the shade. I can move things.
You are moving stuff by yourself. How can I just stand here?
Eat your ice cream!
You guys are back!
He's moving things alone? You're supervising?
I told you before that he is very gentle.
You see?
I thought someone like Han Shangyan would be wild and hard to tame.
Didn't expect that our Tong Nian is a born animal tamer.
Of course! Go, help me move things.
- Move a lighter one.
- What is this?
- A pot.
Leave it there. I got it.
- Can you take all of it? I can help you.
- It's fine.
- He's so handsome!!!
- Yes, yes. He's handsome, handsome.
Isn't he really handsome? I really like him.
- I like him more and more. He is so handsome.
- Look at how happy you are.
- Okay, okay. Let's go up.
- Go, go! Let's go.
Let's close this.
Push this.
- Let's go!
- Go!
Han Shangyan, did you know? All these years, I had a lot of words I held back in my heart.
Let me make a toast to you.
- I'm fine.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm happy.
Han Shangyan. Really. You are too impulsive.
Back then, why didn't you go to the world championships?
Even if you needed to retire,
you should have waited until you played the world championships, won first place and then retired!
Little Mi, did you know? I, Buff, am one of the only people who have won against Han Shangyan!
If he won the world championship,
then I would be a greater player than the world champion!
I won against you once. So I am a player who is greater than the world champion, right?
Old Han.
Okay.
Did you guys know? I'll tell you again.
If that year, Han Shangyan did not retire.
The ones who won the world championship would definitely be the Chinese team.
Really. It really is a pity.
Here. Han Shangyan, let me make another toast to you.
I... am thankful to you for saving my life.
And also you
letting me return again to compete.
You are my savior.
You are. You are.
Cheers!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
You... really know how to drive?
Of course. I just got my driver's license. It's legal.
Why did you think to go get your driver's license?
I was just thinking what if a situation like today happened, and you drank alcohol.
I have a driver license. Prepared just in case.
Seat belt.
Are you ready? I am going to drive!
Okay. The engine is on.
And then... clutch... handbrakes.
My car is automatic, there isn't a clutch.
Understood. It's automatic.
Left is the stop pedal, right is the gas pedal. Don't mess them up.
I know, I passed on my first try of course.
You're also a genius on the driving test?
Please don't talk to me right now.
When I drive I can't talk to anyone, I have to be really focused. I'm driving now, okay?
Don't talk? But...
Can you even drive?
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
- Calling the police.
- What?
Calling a substitute designated driver.
No no no. You don't need to call one.
I told you, I know how to drive.
Just now is because you kept on talking to me.
I told you that you can't talk to me, when I'm driving I need to focus.
If you talk to me, I won't be able to focus properly.
As soon as you talked to me, I almost hit another car.
Fine, you drive. I'll give my life to you, okay?
This time please don't talk to me, okay?
Can you understand the navigation signals?
No cars, let's get going then.
♫ I think I've seen you in my dream before ♫
♫ Your eyes are like shining stars ♫
Don't go past 40 miles per hour, okay?
♫ You captured all my attention ♫
That's not okay. A steady pace is 60 miles per hour.
Our driving instructor said so.
Okay..
♫ Getting ready, taking deep breaths ♫
♫ I want to climb to the mountain peak with you ♫
Miss, do you even know how to drive? If you don't know, don't block the road!
I didn't even block him, why does he have to be so mean?
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, ♫
Don't be anxious. Don't be anxious.
♫  we won’t worry regardless of how far ♫
I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
♫ Give you everything that is the best ♫
♫ Quietly saying: I love you ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands,  ♫
Start backing up slowly. You can start turning now, you can turn the wheel till it stops. Yup.
♫ I'll stay by your side ♫
Hello? I'm on the first floor now, could you come out and help me park the car?
Why so much nonsense? Hurry, come down, come down. Hurry!
Wait, no. You turned to early, you turned too much now.
First move forward. Move forward.
Moving forward. Moving forward. Moving forward.
Have the car go forward. Not this forward, the earlier forward.
Now just stop. Put it into park and then prepare for turning.
And then turn the wheel until it stops, and then slowly release...
Release the gas pedal and then slowly press the stop pedal and then go back.
Go back slowly. Back up.
You turned too early. Yes.
You parked into the wrong spot. First stop for a bit. Stop for a bit.
Put the car into park. Into park! Come forward. Come forward.
Boss.
Boss, what's up?
Who's that? Sister-in-Law?
Quickly and help her park the car correctly.
Wait a moment, Boss. You won't park it yourself?
I was in a video call with my girlfriend!
I'm telling you to do it, so you should go do it. I drank alcohol, so I can't drive the car!
Sister-in-Law! Sister-in-Law! I'll do it. I'll do it.
Okay. Okay.
I don't know why... why my skills aren't so great today.
At the driving test, when I parked the car I got full points.
I got it in there so quickly and easily. The driving proctor even praised me. What's with this...?
This is reverse parking.
This isn't side parking?
Isn't it similar?
What are you laughing about?
I'm not.
He has a girlfriend, don't you now?
I didn't know.
Now you know? What are you thinking then?
- I have no thoughts.
- Okay wait.
Little sister, come over here. Let me get this straightened out.
Tell the truth, alright? Why are you looking for me?
I wasn't looking for you.
Okay no. I can give you an autograph, even a selfie, anything else, just tell me.
As long as you tell the truth, say that we really don't have anything to do with each other.
You can make any request, just as long as you don't ask me to be my girlfriend.
Who wants to be your girlfriend? I don't even like you.
I think she's actually your crazy fan, dude.
You even want me "to carry the black pot" for you?
(T/N: means to take the shame or blame for him)
Say that one more time. Carry what black pot?
Wait. No. no... Hey!
Hey! Little sister, if you like him, just say it loud and clear.
I was looking for you.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
You guys still won't tell the truth, right?
This is the truth!
Are you thinking about last time when he his stomach bled at the competition?
What stomach bleed... I don't know what you're talking about...
Acting dumb?
That event was from so long ago... so awkward... can we not talk about it?
Boss! I parked it.
Parked it? Okay, go back then.
He's very professional, isn't he?
Boss, Sister-in-Law, I heard that you guys were getting married?
You said so?
Who said so? 97?
Why are you so embarrassed?
Getting married is a very big exciting matter!
Our brothers have prepared a big gift for you both, a big gift!
Go back now. Call a car in a bit to send her home, okay?
Oh. Sister-in-Law, bye!
Getting married? You thought it through already?
If you are in a hurry to get married, let's settle all the matters then.
Not in a hurry. I'm not in a hurry at all.
Then... then let's wait until the final national championship ends.
Let me think about how to face your mom and dad.
The challenge of coming forward to my mom and dad definitely is a hard one to pass.
- Looks like he's really prepared for it then.
- Let's go.
[No cameras]
Little Han. Tong Nian. You guys just got back?
Auntie, how are you? Is everything alright?
I was just waiting for you to get back.
- Waiting for me?
- Yup.
I heard that you guys were getting married? And I was so happy for both of you.
Little Han, you've been by yourself in China for a long time and have no experience with preparing weddings.
I'll help you take care of a little of it.
Back at the mountainside village, I used to help prepare brides for marriage.
I'm very familiar with all these processes already, okay?
Auntie, auntie, hold on. It's okay, it's okay. When we have time, we'll come back to talk to you. Thank you, Auntie!
Don't forget to tell me if you need me!
Okay. okay.
You can just sit wherever you'd like. I told Grunt to call a car.
If you go back to your dorm late, that's okay, right?
Does he not have enough money for the wedding?
Everyone is giving him so much pressure and he still has to get through my mom and dad.
Then he must feel so burdened right now!
Where's Squiddy?
He must've run downstairs to the living room to play.
Squiddy! Meow.
Is it true that everyone in K&K thinks that you are...
thinks that you are... really soon...
Getting married with you?
Yes, I know. Usually they are pressured and easily excited while they are practicing.
As long as a little wind passes by and disturbs their typical pace of things, they'll start to gossip a lot. Don't let it bother you.
Oh it's them gossiping about it? I almost thought it was you...
Well, whatever.
I don't care what they are thinking, I won't be bothered by them.
I'm just worried about what you think.
Then what do you...
What's wrong?
Right now it's too late, it's too hard to get a car at the moment.
How about I drive Sister-in-Law back?
It's all right. In a moment, I'll go and call a car. Go back and rest.
Okay.
Then what do you think I'm thinking?
Do you not have any money anymore? I know that your team and club need money...
you also need money for signing Buff.
If we both get married right now, it will also require a lot of money.
So you think if I don't have enough money right now, I won't be able to take good care of you?
No. No that's not what I mean.
I just don't want you to have that much pressure.
So I hope you don't hide anything from me or push yourself too much.
Then are you hiding something from me now?
I'm not, you still aren't understanding what I'm saying right now.
I'm saying that I'm hoping that between the two of us...
But when Zhen Hui stayed at your place, you didn't tell me, did you?
I was scared that at the time if I told you, you would...
you would worry and get upset at me, so I didn't tell you.
So you also have times where you don't understand me, right?
Well you obviously don't understand me very well either. Last time, when I went to your house when your grandfather was here,
I can't eat mangoes because I'm allergic to them, but I still ate the whole plate of mangoes.
Then why did you have to force yourself to eat the mangoes?
Because you cut them for me. When I finished eating that plate of mangoes, I was very happy.
So I didn't think about my allergies anymore!
You just said that you wanted to be honest with each other.
If you didn't tell me beforehand, how would I know you can't eat mangoes?
That's true, I didn't tell you. Then that's my fault there, okay?
But I'm a young lady, some things and matters I shouldn't always need to tell you.
When you love someone, shouldn't you pay attention to them?
If you really love me, then you should pay attention to me.
So I don't think you understand me at all.
If you understood me, you would know that I'm allergic to mangoes and I like to eat strawberries.
I don't care if you have money or not, I just care if your future has me in it or not.
I like when we are embarrassed and don't talk too much, and I hate it when you talk all over the place and think too much.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's not argue anymore, okay?
If we keep going like this there will be no end. Let's calm down, okay? Let's calm down...
But I'm still not finished talking.
I must've gotten anxious over talking about getting married.
He clearly is really attentive to me!
I already like him a lot, and am very happy with him!
Should I go look for him?
Forget it. Forget it. It's better to let him cool-down. Don't go disturb him.
Am I a pig head? Why did I have to say those words?
Boss, did Sister-in-Law catch her ride safely?
Probably.
Boss, I'm going out for a bit?
That's weird. Why didn't he react?
[You design your own destiny]
♫ I carefully covered up that I don’t mind ♫
♫ So that I can be in your world, slowly walking closer ♫
♫ I attempted to cherish this experience ♫
♫ Attempt to use unfamiliarity to explain the distance between us ♫
♫ I start to portray an unfamiliar me ♫
♫ Fathoming the untrue distance behind the words ♫
♫ I thought I possessed the acting skills to deceive everything ♫
♫ But no matter how much I practiced, I can't act like myself ♫
♫ The me who doesn't care about you ♫
Come over here!
Boss, I just chatted for a while with some friends.
You're experienced at this. Usually, what do you give to a girl to make her feel better?
If you have money, go buy lipstick.
If you don't have money, go buy food.
The difference between the prices is too much.
But you need to get the right brand of lipstick too. For example...
It's for Sister-in-Law, right?
If it's for Sister-in-Law, then just get food.
Like cream puffs and also strawberry cake.
There's also chocolate. There's also a lot more. Boss!
Han Shangyan.
Han Shangyan?!
Looks like he's really angry. He didn't come back last night.
He didn't reply to any messages either. Where did he go?
Sorry, Sir. You don't checkout strawberries over here.
Sir, what do you need?
Do you have strawberry cakes here?
Sorry, it just so happens that we just sold out strawberry cakes.
Why don't you look at this mango cake?
It's still so early, and you already sold out of strawberry cakes?
Why don't you guys make a little more?
I'm really sorry.
Why don't you come again tomorrow or look at this newly released chocolate cake?
- Young Master, do you need me to help you?
- No.
Boss, there's so much food.
- Is it for us?
- Did Tong Nian leave already?
No. No, I didn't see her leave.
Boss, you're so stingy!
Yesterday night, I didn't control my emotions well.
Here, I would like to apologize to you.
You're not mad at me anymore?
In the future, I'll try to change. I won't make the same kind mistake again.
Okay.
Also, I don't really know how to cheer up girls.
Anyways, in the past, when Solo earned money, he would go buy good food for his girlfriend.
I think that girls that you also like to eat,
so I bought you strawberries, strawberry cake and strawberry macarons.
And the store clerk also said that you should eat the strawberry cake soon. If it melts, it won't taste good.
Maybe in the future, you can give me a list of what you want to eat. Then I can just buy what's on your list?
I want to eat it right now.
Then I'll go get it for you.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫