♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Continue chasing, who’s glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 41]
- Honey?
- Yes?
- Pass the phone to the child.
All right.
- Hello?
- Yes?
Son,
- Dad?
- Yeah.
Your Dad won the championship!
- Dad, you won the championship?
- Yes!
- The Asian Championship!
- Whoa!
Your dad's the champion of Asia!
Dad, you're terrific! Congratulations!
Thank you, son.
You have to behave, too! Listen to your mother!
Dad's the Asian champion!
My dad is the best!
My dad is great!
Let Granny talk to you a moment.
All right, all right!
Granny wants to talk to you.
Hello?
Honey, hurry and take that...
what again? "Sun"... what?
Hurry and take your girlfriend here.
Let your dad and mom and granny see her! Ok?
I will. I'll take my girlfriend to see you very soon.
Is she good to you?
Granny, she... is very good to me. Very good.
Then you have to be good to her, too!
I can tell this girl, from her voice, is a good child.
Yes. She's great.
What does she look like? Let me hear.
She... has long hair...
And then... big eyes...
but time I'm at my worst
she appears and helps me. Silently helps me.
She wouldn't ever even let me know.
Hello, Classmate, I...
I'm reading! Can't you see?
I am Little Mi; Team SP's Mi Shaofei.
I k-know! I know!
It's enough. These are enough. It's fine.
What is it?
What is it...
So, you made your decision?
- Rent!
- Success!
Yeah!
Today is my life's
last professional competition.
I want to thank you all who have been supporting me.
Accompanying me in the most beautiful, brightest fireworks.
♫ Grateful that youth let us ♫
♫ Remember the most beautiful ♫
♫ We sit in a circle that is dazzling ♫
♫ How long from sunrise to sunset ♫
♫ We quickly understood ♫
♫ We will always exist ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, we won’t worry regardless of how far ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, taking you to travel the universe ♫
♫ Give you everything that is the best ♫
So, in his heart, he already considered me his girlfriend.
Right now I feel so at peace.
Knowing you was a miracle.
My hero forever.
You used to be a far-away star.
Now, tough, your steadily
in front of me, in my heart.
- Gun God, you're the best! Number one in the world!
- Thank you!
- I love you!
There are so many people, how do we get out?
No matter, look at me.
Everyone, quiet!
Everyone, listen to me!
This woman standing beside me, she's my wife!
She's pregnant! I have to take her to a prenatal check!
So, please, everyone, make way for us to pass!
Thank you everyone!
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
Thank you! Thank you!
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
Sir, let's go.
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
Congratulations, you great scammer.
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Can you tell me what exactly you want to do?
You'll know as soon as we're inside.
This way!
In a moment, whatever I say, remember to play along.
So what do you want to say? Can't you tell me a bit in advance?
Are you bankrupt? You dare not let my parents know?
Surprise, you get it?
Summer!
- Dad, Mom.
- Nian Nian?
-  Little Han?
- Little Han.
We just saw your match online. Congratulations!
This game was fantastic.
Especially when I saw Little Bai waving the flag onstage, it made me so excited!
It was exactly the same as with the Olimpic Games!
Mom, Dad,
Han Shangyan says that this time he came to tell you something.
- Sure! Have a seat.
- Have a seat and talk, Little Han.
Uncle, Auntie, I'm really sorry
I came here without warning you in advance.
Please, you two, have a seat.
- Sit.
- What does it mean?
Today for me is a very special day.
Maybe you already know that in the past I've won the national championship,
but I was not fated to climb on a higher podium, I stopped to the Country level.
Today the kids in the club have gone further on my path,
they won the Asian championship.
To me this holds great significance.
We are also proud of you all.
Yes!
Thank you Uncle and Auntie for your support!
We support you,
but you don't need to perform such serious cerimonies!
Stand up, stand up, Little Han!
I hope that on this special day
I can persuade you two to entrust your daughter to me.
I didn't know... He didn't t-tell me before...
I'm very lucky that in my life I could meet Nian Nian.
She taught me how to smile.
Every time I see her smile
all the troubles in my life go up in smoke.
[Test rules]
[Tong Nian ♥ Han  Shangyan]
please open your heart
leave more space for yourself... and me.
I know, you are dissatisfied with my past.
About this, I can totally understand.
I don't know how to be romantic at all.
Dating is like fighting in a war.
The kids in the troop are all terrified of me.
But because of Nian Nian's appearance, I learned to love a person.
Overnight stay.
Who said I want to be your girlfriend? I don't like you!
The person I am looking for is you.
What's there to like about me?
Little girl, your information is really wrong.
Didn't you say you like me?
How come you didn't even know I am single and have no interest in girls?
Do you still want to break up?
♫ Whether the clouds in the sky are good or bad ♫
Still haven't thought of how to respond?
I don't want to.
I said, I don't want to break up.
I didn't mean to invade your privacy.
But I don't quite understand, that's why I asked.
You came to find me today, is anything wrong?
I can't come find you even if nothing's wrong?
You are my first love.
I hope that when you're with me, you can be more courageous.
If you want to do anything, then do it.
You don't have to be shy, and you don't have to be scared of me, okay?
All the titles and honors are fake, except for you.
This man named Han Shangyan doesn't have anything.
Empty-handed, all alone, only this is real.
♫ There’s always splendor falling ♫
♫ Imitators one after another ♫
And I hope that in the future, I can learn how to love her well.
♫ Who do you choose to worship, ♫
♫ who to resent? ♫
Nian Nian. Although I am older than you,
there are a lot of times that I am more childish than you.
I hope that in the future we can swap.
You don't need to accommodate me with everything.
I want you to become the center of my world.
Let me take care of you, okay?
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
Mom! I... what should I say?
What to say? Ask yourself what to say, why are you asking me?
Little Han.
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
I want to ask you. I...
I ... only have this daughter.
From when she was young, I have never let her suffer hardships.
Don't worry. I will definitely not let her suffer.
People always say that daughters are daddy's girls, daddy's heart.
I will love her like you do - but double it and double it in loving her.
Silly child, don't cry.
Then... then there is nothing else for me to say.
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
Auntie. I know that you are anxious about me.
Our age gap... I cannot change it.
But in future days, I will do my utmost to love her.
I will live everyday as if it were a lifetime.
Good.
Then in the future, please love Nian Nian well. You hear?
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
So, since we have made this decision,
I want to go and get our marriage certificate and bring it back.
This time I came to ask you both for Nian Nian's residence permit.
(TN necessary for marriage registration)
Say, this kid. How is it that when you talk, it is always things that are so unexpected!
Are you that impatient?
I-I know that me standing here now and saying these kinds of things to you is something I shouldn't do.
But I wanted to take this Asian championship title as an opportunity.
Go, go. Get Nian Nian's residence permit.
Weren't you the one to store the residence permits away? You ask me? Go look for it.
Let me think... I know where it is. I know where it is.
What's with all the sensation? Why didn't you tell me in advance?
Before the finals, who was it that told me she wanted to get married?
You think these words are said just for fun?
As soon as you mentioned marriage to me I agreed and immediately took you back to get your residence permit.
Have you ever seen anyone so sincere after receiving a proposal?
This time the Asia-Pacific Competition prize money is quite a lot. Where do you want to go for a honeymoon?
Honeymoon?
After getting married the next step... isn't it a honeymoon? Is there a problem?
Say... my daughter...
she's getting married to you in such a hurry...
Little Han. Remember, in the future if there are any difficult matters,
you need to come and find the two of us.
We are a family.
Do you hear? Don't be polite.
No problem.
Then... remember.
Every week, come back three times to eat dinner together!
We know, mom.
Don't worry, Auntie. I often pick up Nian Nian from school and bring her back.
Give it to him.
Little Han, once you take this residence permit
and register for marriage with Nian Nian, she will be your wife.
You must treat her well. Do you hear me?
Dad, mom, what are you guys doing?
I'm your daughter forever!
Don't be sad, it's not like I'm not coming back!
I don't even have the time to be so happy.
What are you standing there for? Come here!
Don't cry anymore.
Bye-bye, Summer!
What's wrong?
I've forgotten something.
What thing? I'll go back inside to get it for you!
- I've forgotten a matter.
- What matter?
Don't be like this! There's a lot of people over there who can see!
Then treat it as our wedding rehearsal!
If you're shy, just put your head on my shoulder.
No!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
You've really considered it clearly?
Once we tell everyone, you can't regret it.
Have you really thought it through?
As long as you have thought it through, I have the confidence.
Give me ten seconds.
What's wrong?
♫ I think I've seen you in my dream before ♫
♫ Your eyes are like shining stars ♫
♫ You captured all my attention ♫
♫ I don't want to wake up ♫
Now I'm ready, I got the power of the universe.
♫ I want to climb to the mountain peak with you ♫
♫ Watching the most beautiful night sky with you ♫
♫ I want to tease you and make you happy ♫
Whoa!
Have you guys enjoyed yourself to the fullest?
No!
Then continue!
Then you guys continue too!
Boss, where did you go? On the night of our victory, you left us here!
Right!
Taking advantage of the victory of the Asian championship,
I got your sister-in-law's residence permit!
I really want one too!
Sister-in-law, you said yes?
Getting the residence permit just means...
Congratulations Gun God for successfully getting off the market!
Nian Nian, you said yes? I'm so happy for you!
Little Squid, you guys are finally getting married! I'm so happy for you.
Husband, see how amazing my bestie is? She successfully pursued Gun God!
Right now the main thing is that Gun God is going to become my brother-in-law!
Then we'll just wish Boss a happy wedding!
- "Harmonious union for a hundred years!"
- "Joy as vast as the sea!"
- "Long life, like mountains!"
- "May a baby come soon"!
- "Advance to the wedding chamber!"
Come on, Han Shangyan!
Don't forget that you have some close buddies waiting for you upstairs.
Take good care of your sister-in-law!
No problem!
Sister-in-law! Sister-in-law! Sister-in-law!
Solo dressed like this looks like a rebel.
It's definitely a new style. Old Han is here.
You close buddies have occupied the bridal chamber, ruining their joyous occasion.
What happened?
Old Han!
So the cheering downstairs wasn't
for entering the global competition, but rather Old Han actually—
It's the one
with the most sour face and worst temper,
who isn't attracted to women,
and even invests all his money into his career until he's a penniless peasant,
that actually found a partner!
He even got married before us!
What kind of natural order is this? I'll go die!
- Go. Fall down, fall down.
- Hey!
I was joking, okay?
- It's okay.
- Stop fooling around.
I know...standing on this balcony,
brings back the time
when we were in Shanghai on that beat-up rooftop.
Talking about our dreams as time flew by.
We were able to fight together for our dreams.
It was great!
We were able to pass on our dreams to the next generation.
I believe, no matter if it's SP or K&K,
they will bring our dreams
and work hard towards the world championship!
That's true. For that flame of victory!
Cheers!
I won't accompany you guys to drink.
I have to drive and take Tong Nian somewhere.
But, I still wholeheartedly
hope my brothers and sisters can find their own happiness.
No...
- Take one sip.
- I'll toast with some juice.
Here, here, here.
Where are you going?
Good luck!
- Newlywed night.
- I'm leaving!
I'll have a beer!
Come! Let's have a toast for Old Han!
For China's Championship!
Go all out!
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
♫ Abandoning their dreams ♫
♫ Anyone can do so ♫
One, two, go!
♫ Today, I saw snow drifting through the cold night ♫
♫ With a cold heart, I drift off to faraway places ♫
How many years did you think you can compete?
A CTF player  Only has six years during their peak.
Your best condition is during these few years.
Once you pass this time period,
even if you don't want to eat New Year's Eve dinner and want to train,
no one will pay you any attention.
Do you have any shame losing to a 30-year-old uncle?
It's not like I'm a long distance runner.
A strong youth means a strong country. Don't you know?
We will definitely win!
♫ I’m afraid one day it’ll just be you and me ♫
I'm handing this place over to you.
Remember to call Grandpa.
Do you need to tell me?
Why didn't you come back earlier to celebrate with them?
You know I don't like it when it's too lively.
Stop being single and lonely in silence.
It's time for you to start dating.
Look at me. It feels...pretty nice.
In truth, I'm kind of envious.
It's rare to find true love in this world.
It's even harder to have confidence in each another.
Brother.
Congrats.
Good luck to you.
♫ Anyone can do so ♫
♫ I’m afraid one day it’ll just be you and me ♫
I'm leaving.
♫ Forgive my whole life’s uninhibited indulgement to love freedom ♫
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
Champions! Champions! Champions!
Hurry up!
There's no one here.
Of course not. It's only six. Of course it's still closed.
Then we came too early.
I thought, I thought it would be like on TV
where you need to line up for registration
and come the day before. I thought we would be late.
I realized...
Ever since being with you, I have been doing some outrageous things.
What things?
Like, right now.
Oh right. Let's give Grandpa a call. He probably hasn't slept yet.
- Mister Han, here is your tea.
- Yes?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
♫  I'm a little green dragon! Green dragon! Green dragon! ♫
(T/N: Children's Song)
Mister Han, your phone is ringing.
♫  I have lots of small secrets! Small secrets! Small secrets! ♫
♫  I'm a little green dragon! Green dragon! Green dragon! ♫
♫  I have lots of small secrets! Small secrets!  ♫
You stinky brat. It's rare. You thought of me?
I am with Tong Nian at the marriage registration office.
W-What? R-Right now?
Yup! There are still two more hours
until she is legally your granddaughter-in-law.
You stinky brat! You have finally done something to make me happy.
W-Where's Nian Nian? Nian Nian!
Grandpa! This is Nian Nian!
Nian Nian, the wedding must be big!
There needs to be one in Shanghai!  One in our hometown!
One in Norway as well!
- This many weddings, Grandpa?
- Yes! Yes! There must be!
Also, a Chinese style one! And a Western style one!
That's a total of five weddings!
- Five weddings!
-  Oh right! They can't be sloppy!
Okay, Grandpa! This way, you'll have things to do, right?
Okay! Then that's it. We'll talk next time!
Bye, Grandpa!
- Wait a minute!
- Yes?
Come, come, come!
Why are you so happy?
My grandson is getting married!
Congratulations!
Congratula⁠—
Sorry! Sorry!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay.
- Are you okay? Sure?
- Yes.
- Yes, sure.
- Okay.
Yeah! Yes!
Your grandpa said five weddings!
Can't help it!
Grandpa has always preferred girls. He also likes you so much. I can't do anything.
Oh, right. There's something more important.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Here.
Which finger? Your middle finger or your ring finger?
Stupid. The engagement ring is for the middle finger.
This time, it should be the ring finger.
It's a bit big.
Let's put it on your thumb first.
We'll change it to a real one in the future anyway.
Really impressive!
I feel like an emperor!
Do you like it?
I do! Thank you!
This is my first and only championship ring that I have kept.
Before, when I was with team Solo,
I won a national championship ring.
But, I threw it away. I only have this one left.
I'm sorry.
I retired too early.
I couldn't win more championship rings for you.
Why does this one seem to please my eye?
I just like this one!
- Let's start waiting in line.
- Let's go!
- Oh, right.
- Huh?
What now?
I...am someone who doesn't show much emotion.
I like to keep a lot of things in my heart.
I always thought romance was something unimportant and unnecessary.
But...
[Shanghai, Changning District]
With a life so long, I give it all to you.
I love you.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'm done saying it!
When? I didn't hear you say anything!
Silly.
You're the one who is silly! Let's go!
Say, in a little while do you think that it will be crowded with a lot of people in there?
Let's line up here! We need to be number one, you know?
After getting married, where will I live?
You... live wherever you should be living.
Then... where will you live?
I... What do you think?
If you live at the club, then I will take the double bed and change it to a bigger double bed.
If you live at my house, it has a double bed that is already ready for you.
You can directly move in.
At that time, I won't need to feed Squiddy anymore.
I will leave it to you to feed Squiddy.
If we move to your house, it does not matter to me either.
Even if we are living under someone else's roof, it doesn't matter.
Because our two families are old friends.
I still have to study for my PhD.
Now, this is a problem.
Then I will move into your dormitory to live.
You're going to move into our dormitory? It's a girls' dormitory. How are you going to come in?
If I need to climb the building, I'll climb the building. It'll be a cinch.
You've only thought about the problem of  marriage but you haven't thought about the problem of where we are going to live?
Then you should... you should give me some time to let me be mentally prepared!
Okay. I'll give you time.
How much time?
Is two hours enough?
Two hours? How can I be mentally prepared?
In two hours you'll be my officially certificated wife.
You won't be able to escape anymore.
Who's ever acted like you?
I'm joking with you! Look at how scared you are.
First, wait for me to lead the team to play at the World Finals.
Then, wait for us to have the wedding.
Then at the end, we'll consider this problem again, okay?
Now that's about it. I was joking, too.
Rest for a while first!
How can I rest here?
What are you doing?
Sit.
Where are you going?
Sit!
Thank you! Then I won't stand on cerimonies.
It's pretty comfortable!
Later on when people come and see the two of us like this,
will they think that we are crazy?
No! For the purpose of being first, waiting the entire night is pretty normal.
Thank you for taking this road with me until today.
All along it seemed to me like I was dreaming.
It turns out when two people are dreaming together,
no matter what small thing it is, it can be very sweet.
They can feel happiness from the bottom of their heart.
Even if they bicker all their life, they're still happy.
Isn't that right?
Why aren't they sweet everyday, but bicker all the time?
Anyways, no matter what we do together
we will definitely be very happy.
I don't dare say that I can tolerate everything.
I'm telling you, in the future whether you are happy or not, you better drink less alcohol!
Lest I be bullied by you nonstop!
Even if I bully you, it's because I love you, okay?
You've bullied me a lot too!
You don't even know how much I've given all through this.
Thank you.
No matter how, in the end arrived in front of you.
All of this is just right.
Having you is so nice.
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
They came so early to line up!
If I knew earlier, I would've come the day before yesterday to line up!
So early!
- This is too early!
- Right!
Tong Nian. Tong Nian, hurry and wake up! Tong Nian.
Why didn't you call me sooner? They're watching us from all around!
Excuse me!
You really came in early!
We'll line up second! Hurry!
We came first! We came first!
Come, come. Excuse me, excuse me. Who is first here?
We're first!
- What time did you guys get here?
- At 5 am.
That early? Here, come in!
Changning district Civil Affairs Bureau
This time, K&K and SP are representing China to play at the World Finals!
Hope that they do not come across the same draw result as last time,
and have to eliminate each other.
Right now the phone line has connected, let us contact our old partner,
Team SP's Team Leader, who's taking them to battle.
Hello?
Hello, Ai Qing!
I can hear you, speak!
How is it? Did you guys set off already?
I'm telling you, Han Shangyan was late bringing his team again!
We are only on our way to the airport now!
It's not that Boss was late, it's that Sister-in-law put on her makeup late!
I think it's you that put on your makeup late!
It's not me, it's not me!
Really? Then you guys need to hurry up, airplanes don't wait for anyone.
Don't worry! We are already on our way to the airport.
- Bye!
Are you okay, Little Mi?
- Are you okay?
- Are we there already?
Almost, we aren't there yet. But you should wake up a little and be ready to get off.
[K&K TEAM]
- Get off!
- We're at the airport!
You can get off from the back too!
Old Han, you're late again!
You're not bringing any substitute players?
I don't need to.
If the few people on the bus
If it doesn't work out, we'll just transfer one from K&K!
If it really doesn't work out, you can go up for us!
No problem. Performance fee: 100,000¥. Each place obtained is counted separately.
Third place, 300,000. Second place, 500,000.
What about first place?
Don't even think about first place! It's had K&K engraved on it long ago.
[Shanghai Airport]
♫ I've decided, standing in this unknown place far away ♫
♫ I need no protection ♫
♫ It's okay to just follow destiny's vastness together as we please ♫
♫ Now that my dream has fallen to this angle ♫
♫ All right ♫
♫ Make sure courage never announces the end ♫
♫ Pride, glory ♫
♫ Your resolute gaze is always looking ahead ♫
♫ The fierce call of faith ♫
♫ Let's rush together to everything in this world ♫
♫ Overcome the new obstacles, ♫
♫ the new heartbeat! ♫
♫ Who's coming to defeat the ultimate darkness? ♫
♫ Our hearts beating to each other's rhythm ♫
♫ Let your spirit shine ♫
♫ Who's making the sky light so beautiful all over? ♫
♫ Our eyes are already sparkling ♫
♫ Let your spirit shine ♫
♫ Towards the final war, waking up in victory ♫
- Do you have a dream?
- Yes.
Get first place. For China, get first place in the world.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫