♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 22]
Hi.
I won’t give you a cat anymore, okay?
Stop being angry.
Han Shangyan?
[Chat with Little Squid]
Going to sleep.
What exactly is wrong?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Who is this?
In the middle of the night.
It's you.
What's wrong? Did you argue with your girlfriend?
If you argued, staying here all night won't help.
If I hadn't seen your car tonight,
I'd think you were a thief.
How do you know I'm not?
This building is a young lady's home. I know.
What if I'm familiar with this place and am here to commit a crime with malicious intent?
Careful, careful.
Look at your bad temper. You said some things you didn't mean, right?
Seems you did get in an argument.
Don't worry. I argue with my wife often, too.
When I was young, I was like you.
Every day, I was outside her building. I couldn't sleep.
Do you know why?
I'd wait for her to come out.
You think I was being romantic? That's not it!
I'd wait for her to come out and keep arguing.
An arguing woman gets very intense.
You ignore her to avoid fighting.
But they chase after you to argue.
They even take out all their past grudges against you.
You say, with such great memories,
they must have scored enough on their entrance exams for the top universities.
I'm chatting with you. Say something. Reciprocate, okay?
If you don't have anything else, go back and patrol.
Candy?
Eat more candy and smoke less. Your wife will be delighted.
Why are you up so early?
Boss, aren't you also up very early?
I'm asking you. Why did you wake up so early?
Yesterday's newest rankings came out, I'm only in 71st place.
Captain is number one again!
I'm scared to see him; I'm afraid he'll say I'm dragging them down.
So, I woke up early to watch some of his competition videos and some important global competition videos.
Watch and learn a bit.
A boy worth teaching.
Since you're here, when they wake up, tell them
I need to report to headquarters. I won't be going to the competition next week.
What? You aren't going to next week's competition?
But it has already been officially announced.
What does the announcement have to do with me?
Boss, you don't use Weibo so you don't understand.
They announced using you as an incentive. They said Gun God would make an appearance.
How come I didn't know about this?
The internet is full of deceit.
Also, if you really don't go, many people will be disappointed.
There are many people who are disappointed in me. It doesn't matter if there's one more or less.
I'm leaving.
You really aren't going?
If I were you and had so many fans waiting for me,
I'd go even if there was bad weather!
Competing isn't for fans but for honor.
Understood?
I understand.
Also, this time in Norway, I temporarily won't be using my domestic phone.
If you want to contact me, call my other number.
Okay.
Driver, let's go.
Tong Nian, why'd you come so early?
I have breakfast for everyone.
- Wow, Sister-in-Law, is this all for us?
- 97.
I never knew with Boss gone, you'd be so nice to us.
Truly our real sister-in-law!
Then, I'll bring it in.
You said Boss isn't here? Where'd he go?
- You didn't know?
- No.
Boss left the country today.
He didn't tell me.
- He didn't?
- Yeah.
Why is he like that?
We'll still accept breakfast. Thanks, Sister-in-Law.
Come in and sit!
As soon as you get here, you come to eat and drink. Pretty cool.
Where's my money? Pay me back.
Didn't I transfer it to your account already?
Did you transfer enough?
Don't you know it has increased in value?
I'm poor and penniless anyway. Say what you want.
Did you give it to the little girl?
Little Bai told me.
Okay, okay.
I forced him to tell me.
A person like you... always worrying about your ex-husband's son.
Wouldn't your new husband be angry?
If you call me "Mom" for one day, I'll be responsible for you until the end.
Look at you now,
not even a trace of a smile.
That's cute.
I was planning to prepare a gift for you,
but there was only ¥700 left in my card.
(~US$100)
So, treating you to a meal is enough.
You didn't deny, so did you really give it to the little girl?
Son, come with me.
Come with me. Did you pay the bill yet?
- Nan Wei did.
- Good, good!
Hurry, come with me first!
Hurry!
Quick, look, look!
These things were the dowry from marrying your dad.
I remember this should be a watch...
No, I saw wrong, it's not.
This one is.
Look, a watch.
And this.
This is an emerald.
Right, this one, too. A whole set; rubies!
These are all worth a lot!
The most important one is this.
Look! This jade bracelet is the family heirloom from my grandma.
I am reluctant to wear it; it's worth a lot!
I'm giving these all to you.
Once my wedding is over, you can go back and use these to propose.
No need. Take it back.
What do you mean?
Do you dislike that these are second hand?
Gemstones aren't afraid of that!
Look! You just don't understand!
I've already said I don't need it.
You were dumped?
No way! My son's so handsome! How could he get dumped?
Could it be... that girl... doesn't like appearances, but likes money?
Stop joking around.
How am I joking?
Look at you! How disappointing.
I'm past forty and have married twice.
You? Almost thirty and can't even secure a girlfriend.
Are you done?
With you like this, how am I supposed to marry in a few days?
You were rebellious since you were young;
causing trouble for me every day.
Now you're great.
I prepared so many surprises that can't be used.
Tell me truthfully. Did I really not listen when I was young?
That's not entirely it.
Well, who doesn't have a rebellious stage?
I remember when I was younger and rebelling, I was way worse than you!
After today, you might not get another chance to scold me.
I didn't mean it like that.
Raising you all the way until now,
no matter what people say,
before I close my eyes forever, I'll always be responsible for you.
You're not my birth mother.
When it's time to let go, let go.
People... always have to consider emotions.
I still remember the first time I saw you.
That time, you were...
only this tall.
At that time, we were destined to be mother and son forever.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Keep talking.
About what?
Talk about that girl. What happened?
How'd she dump you?
Did your bad temper come up again?
But shouldn't your handsome face add some points, too?
I won't attend your wedding. I'm jealous in place of Dad.
What's up with your bad temper? You're really leaving?
Bye-bye.
You really have such a bad temper! You're just going to turn against me like that?
[K&K]
[K&K E-Sports Battle]
Hey, Anna, is Nan Wei here?
Yes, he's in the office.
Okay, thank you.
- Hello, everybody.
- Hello, Boss.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hey, you're here.
I need a budget of a million.
The headquarter is out of money.
Your really too biased towards the players in China.
The ones here will get jealous.
You know that we should all remember our roots.
China is our roots.
And the reason I entered this field was because of participating on a Chinese team.
If their results are good,
then China will have the opportunity to get a ticket straight to the Global Finals for the first time.
More importantly, then we will be able to receive lots of prize money.
The income from the side businesses can help with the huge operating problems for the club, right?
What you're looking forward to aren't just those things, right?
I understand you. You didn't get first place in the world.
You hope that Wu Bai can fulfill that in your place.
This lot of kids have suffered too many doubts from outsiders and their families.
They aren't playing.
They're training and competing.
What they're doing is a hardworking and honorable profession.
And what I need to do, is to help them prove to the world that they can do it.
Bro, we have no money!
Old rules: draw one.
If mine is greater, listen to me.
If mine is less, I'll figure it out myself.
Here we go again.
Draw one.
If mine is greater, listen to me.
If yours is greater, I'll think of a way myself.
Bro, how old are we?
We aren't little kids anymore.
Wake up! Stop messing around in this circle anymore.
Annoying.
If I'm greater, resign from your job,
and help me run this internet club. I'm betting all of my net worth.
If yours is greater, I'll think of a way myself.
Whether this succeeds or not, is not related to you.
- Let's go.
- Three, two, one...
[Ace > King]
Okay. Don't you dare cheat!
[Ace of spades]
This time I'm greater.
[Joker]
What?
Don't forget. A budget of ¥10,000,000.
(~US$1,500,000)
Okay, I agree.
As a businessman, although money is attractive,
I still hope that I can see Chinese teams and individuals on the world's stage.
I have faith that you'll be able to appear in it.
And there's no good excuse to reject you.
But, Old Han, you have to promise me,
you have to get K&K a world champion.
Okay?
While the past Solo was important,
but now, the friends here are your good brothers.
They helped get you to where you are now.
I know you must understand this.
Okay, let's not talk about work.
Tell me, where's your girlfriend?
I don't have one.
You were dumped.
- Annoying.
- No.
If you don't tell me, you won't get even ¥1,000,000.
I'm going.
Your 1,000,000 is gone!
You dare?
It's been four days.
I still can't contact him.
Could it be that he got into an accident?
Yaya, nothing will happen. Right?
No, if something happened to him, it would be all over the news. Don't worry.
He's a big shot in the industry. Lots of people are watching him.
If you say it like that, why do I feel more scared?
Is he mad at me?
Say, do you think it's because of the cat, or because of the group photo?
I don't know.
Look at his attitude towards Mi Shaofei and Ou Qiang.
He wouldn't reject his brotherss from before, so taking a group photo shouldn't be a problem.
About the cat...
He's a man but may not be able to handle the little kitty.
Even more, he's a big man.
Right now, it's daytime where he is.
He should be working in the daytime.
But why would his phone be off during work?
Why would he turn it off?
He's definitely mad at me, right?
Did he get mad at me?
He must be mad at me... what to do?
He must be mad at me, no doubt!
Hello?
Your cat has diarrhea.
Got it.
Demo's mom wants to take him away,
she won't let him compete anymore.
Tomorrow is Auntie's wedding, right?
Yes.
If you come back tomorrow, you'll make it to SP's group competition.
Depends on my mood.
I'm done.
Hold on.
Is Grandpa... doing well?
He's fine. I'm hanging up if there's nothing else.
Can't you understand "hold on?"
Um...
Has Tong Nian come to find me?
- It's Boss, hurry.
- Hurry.
She has. She has.
The day you left, she came and even brought us breakfast.
Seriously though, Boss. You left without even telling Sister-in-Law; so inconsiderate!
Boss, you care way too less.
Who let you put me on speaker, Wu Bai?
Why do you keep petting my cat?
Why don't you raise one yourself?
He doesn't even care about his own wife?
Originally, he did.
- Once you say something, he doesn't dare care anymore.
- Wait,
Boss is too boring.
Old men get embarrassed? Seriously.
- Boring.
- Let's go, let's go!
When do you prepare to leave?
To where?
You can't sleep here, can you?
What's wrong with me sitting a bit longer?
I booked a room next door.
You won't go home to sleep. Why sleep in a hotel?
You are now part of my maiden family.
What's wrong with staying with my maiden family?
Plus, you're in this room. I'm next door.
It's the same as being sent off from my maiden family.
My husband is picking me up for the wedding tomorrow anyway.
Contentious.
Han Shangyan, ever since you became my son,
I've raised you for nine whole years.
It was also your most rebellious nine years.
This movie is currently showing a young lady
raising a kid herself.
Seeing this scene, it makes me think of
the days when we depended on each other for survival.
If you want something, say it. I'll put it on my tab.
Next month, I'll be getting a bonus. I'll buy it for you.
Forget it.
The necklace was bought as a dowry.
Look at it now. I don't even know who got the necklace.
I don't even know what she looks like.
You really haven't taken a photo with her?
Then, you must feel very wronged.
I really don't know what the person in my son's heart looks like.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to sleep.
[Inn Suites]
This is the kind I like.
I just want to make sure you saw that drawing.
This one?
My drawing skills aren't great,
I don't know if you can see her clearly.
I guess I can.
From this drawing, I can see the girl has a smile on her face.
I can tell she's a beautiful girl with a caring heart.
My son has good taste.
I'll attend your wedding tomorrow, but I won't go to the after-party.
I have to catch a plane ride.
Are you putting in minimal effort with me?
No.
I have a close friend competing in China. I have to go back and watch him.
It's really not because of me?
You think too much.
I'm sleeping.
Sweet dreams.
No matter how many times you fail,
Mom will be your support.
Your protective umbrella, your worshiper.
My baby Yan Yan, I'll always love you.
[Shanghai Jiaodong University]
Nian Nian, your phone's ringing.
I'll pick it up for you.
Don't! I'll do it myself. I'll do it myself.
Who's this?
- Hello?
- Hello.
I am Jiaodong University's security guard; the front gate security guard.
There's a girl around ten years old saying she's here to find her sister.
She's wearing jeans.
Vinyl shoes. She's wearing a backpack and a hat.
She said she's called Little Ai. Do you know her?
I do know her. Please tell her to wait for me for a bit.
I will come now to pick her up. Thank you.
Come with me to pick someone up. Let's go.
Who?
You'll know once we get there.
Let's go.
- Hello. I am the one who was on the phone just now.
- Hello.
Sorry for the trouble. We'll take her now.
No trouble. I was just a bit worried.
Since you know each other,
then I can pass her on to you.
- Okay.
- It's just that both of you are Jiaodong University's students.
Did you bring your student ID?
This is mine. Here.
- I'll record it down.
- Okay.
Came to find me?
You came by yourself? Does your family know?
I'm wearing my hearing aid.
It's quite cold outside. How about we talk in the dorms?
Sounds good.
- Here, your student ID. I'll hand her over to you.
- Thank you.
Sounds good. Sorry for the trouble.
- No problem.
- Let's go.
- Bye!
That way, that way.
Which room?
- 104.
This one.
This one?
What?
What's wrong?
She... is really Solo's daughter?
Yes, but I can't explain too much right now.
I will tell you in detail tonight. Right now, we must think of a way to send her away as our priority.
No, no, no.
What now?
Are her ears—
She is wearing a hearing aid. She can technically hear us.
She ignored us earlier... She was probably just being willful.
Why aren't you guys coming in?
- We'll go in... go in...
- Go in...
Scared me to death!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Are you hungry? Drink some water.
She is probably hungry.
I'll go out and buy some food!
Okay! Okay! Little Ai is probably hungry. Right, Little Ai? What do you want to eat?
She probably has something to say to me individually.
Then I will...
- Check it out and randomly buy some.
- Randomly buy some.
- Okay. You guys talk.
- Go ahead.
Don't you have my Wechat?
Why didn't you send me a message before you came by yourself?
I wasn't happy, so I came to find you.
If I told you ahead of time, you wouldn't have let me come.
Why did you want to come and find me?
I wanted you to help me with something.
You need my help?
Han Shangyan is my mom's boss.
Make Han Shangyan transfer my mom back.
Why? Don't you want to see your mom?
Now that I've seen her, it's no longer a novelty. I'm hoping she will leave soon.
Her presence has disturbed my dad's life.
Disturbed your dad's life?
Didn't your mom already re-marry?
Do you think your mom wants to get back together with your dad?
She wants to take me away!
That's seriously disturbing my dad's life!
Then, Han Shangyan's power isn't as strong as you think.
You should just directly say you can't handle Han Shangyan.
How could I not?
Forget it. Han Shangyan's temper is so bad.
My dad's is much better. Consider my dad.
- What?!
- What?
In term's of CTF rankings, my dad's isn't that much worse than Han Shangyan's.
Besides, my dad is much more handsome than Han Shangyan.
Your dad– What kind of eyesight do you have?
Clearly, it's Han Shangyan that's more handsome.
What eyesight do YOU have? Clearly my dad's more handsome.
Your dad– Your dad is like this.
Han Shangyan's face is always like this every day.
- Your-Your dad has a big head.
- Han Shangyan's temperament is worse!
Your dad's leg is-is shorter than Han Shangyan's by a half.
Han Shangyan's feet stink!
- How would you know if his feet stink?
- I heard!
Who said?
You– Don't care about who said it. The fact is that it stinks! Han Shangyan's feet stink!
- My Han Shangyan's feet stink! No! They don't stink!
- Han Shangyan's feet stink!
- Your dad's feet stink!
- Have you smelled them?
I-I...
I'm back! I bought a lot of good stuff.
You're finally back.
Little Ai must've been starving.
I don't know what you like so I bought a little of everything.
There's Kentucky Fried Chicken, bread, pan fried buns, shaomai (Chinese dumplings)...
I was afraid you wouldn't like savory so I bought a lot of cakes, too. Take a look and see what you like to eat.
- What's wrong?
- Wait!
Little Ai, look. Yaya and I specially went to buy this after class.
"You guys," how do you plan to take care of it?
I don't know. I called Han Shangyan but he didn't pick up.
It's been a few days since we've talked. What should I do?
Seeing it's like this, he probably got into a fight with Solo.
What about this? You call Mi Shaofei
and ask him to tell Solo to come and pick her up.
I don't think that will work. With rebellious kids, we cannot do things by force.
But we should let her dad know first.
There's an SP competition tomorrow.
I'll think of a way to get tickets and bring Little Ai there.
After the competition, they'll mend their relationship.
Tonight, let's let her stay here to calm down.
It's not a big deal. We don't have to make it even more serious.
Okay, let's go with your plan.
He is on the way back.
He's back. He's back.
Okay, okay. Idol, I'll pass the phone to Nian Nian.
Okay.
We found her.
Hello, this is Solo.
Hello, Solo.
I'm Tong Nian, Han Shangyan's... friend.
I know. Is Little Ai with you right now? I can't find her anywhere.
Yes, she's with me. Don't worry.
How about this? Tomorrow, I'll bring her to the competition arena and safely hand her back to you.
Just let her stay with us tonight, okay?
Okay, thank you, Tong Nian.
No problem.
Right... She... She's okay, right?
She's fine. Everything is okay. Don't worry.
Sister Tong Nian,
Han Shangyan's temper is so bad. What do you like about him?
No, it's not.  Everything about him is good. I like everything about him.
You're looking through rose-colored glasses!
How about you consider my dad?
Forget it. I don't like him. Thanks.
Uh, Little Ai, have you considered that your dad probably likes someone who's got gaming skills?
Who said that my dad likes someone with gaming skills?
On this point, I must really debate this out with you.
Wait! What do you want? What are you doing?
What do you want?! Harassment! Help me!
Don't move! My hearing aid is really expensive.
I-I was wrong, okay?
I-I'll stand on your side, okay?
Hey, Yaya! You betrayed me so fast!
Chun Chun, go!
Uh, let me say Nian Nian doesn't like handsome men.
Then Han Shangyan...?
He... He's an ugly monster.
You're an ugly monster! How is he ugly!? He's so handsome!
You... You're four-eyed! Four-eyed frog!
Uh... I was wrong.
Sister Yaya!
So... right now you and me are on the same side then!
I– This...
When Uncle Mi first came to Shanghai, he was living at my house.
Whatever question you have, ask away.
I... I don't have anything I want to ask...
Really?
- For real?
- Really!
Okay, enough! Sleep. Let's sleep. Go. Sleep.
Just sleep over there! It's pretty good!
You can also ask about matters related to Uncle Mi!
Really?
Really real! Let's sleep!
- What are you guys doing?
- Time to sleep.
[SP]
[SP E-Sports]
I knew you'd be here.
What's up?
I can't find you if I don't want something from you?
Nervous?
Nervous about what?
It's the last battle in the group competition.
The next one will be the quarterfinals.
Didn't we qualify early? What's there to be nervous about?
Has Solo talked with you?
In my heart, I keep feeling unsettled.
What are you unsettled about?
Don't be so fussy. Just say it directly.
I heard rumors that Team Two's captain Fu Ying is preparing to be promoted.
That also means that on our team, someone may be getting dismissed.
Isn't that great?
So, I...
You're afraid they're going to swap me out?
I didn't mean that!
It's possible the one being dismissed is me!
Bro, let me tell you something from the heart.
Say it.
Back then, the five of us were the strongest.
But I never expected that now I would be the worst!
It's the most embarrassing thing in the world!
I'm telling you! If I get swapped out, it doesn't matter!
At least I won't have people talking behind my back saying that I was relying on Solo!
What crazy things are you saying?
If you say stuff like that again, I'm going to be mad!
We have never doubted your capability.
Bro, I'm begging you to please help me.
Tomorrow, cheer me on.
I must win.
It's nothing. I'm here!
I'll help you. We will win for sure.
Okay, we'll win a big one tomorrow!
Let people know that those from Team Solo aren't trash.
It's nothing!
[Chinese Region Qualifying Competition Eighth Final]
- Ai Qing!
- Tong Nian! I've brought you guys the tickets.
Thank you, thank you! Thank you so much.
You are Appledog!
- Hello!
- Hello, hello!
- In my heart, you will forever be the best main offense player.
- Thank you!
She is my classmate.
Doesn't my dad have a secretary? Why are you bringing us the tickets?
Your dad's secretary has other things to do.
She doesn't usually come to the competition.
These are three VIP tickets in the same row. It will be more convenient for you guys to sit together.
Okay, okay. Thank you so much!
Did Han Shangyan come today? Is he front stage or back stage?
He's not coming today. Did he not tell you?
I know he went abroad. I was just asking again.
He might be too busy.
Today, we are competing. It's not K&K's matches.
You guys should hurry in, the competition is starting soon.
Our competition is also very interesting.
- I'm going now. Bye!
- Thank you! You've worked hard.
If he's not coming, then whatever.
In a few moments, I'll let you see the world's greatest team captain from all angles.
Every time you describe your dad to me,
I really want to ask you.
Is your dad Kris Wu or Eddie Peng? (T/N: Kris Wu - former EXO member; Eddie Peng - a top movie star in China. Both are very handsome)
My dad is Wang Hao! The greatest team captain!
Wang Hao.
Wang Hao is the best!
It's a must!
Sir, I already came out. I'm at exit two.
Okay. Can I trouble you to be quick? I'm in a hurry.
Okay, let's go with that. See you soon.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫