♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 30]
I think everyone already knows me. We've competed in group matches and exhibition games.
So, I'll skip the self-introductions and get to business.
Let's talk about Team Buff, our adversary in the next semi-final.
I think you've already done deep research on this guy.
But point number 1:
you've never competed against each other in group matches.
Point number 2: they've been retired for 5 years,
and just re-entered the competition this year.
So there isn't much data on them.
But they used to be my opponent.
And this year, too, I competed against him in the group matches.
Trust me. My experiences can help everyone.
Buff is their assist.
Mina is their main offense.
And the other three assist with offense and defense. And then—
What else? We know all this.
I'm about to tell you something that you don't know.
Buff is actually someone who absolutely cannot lead. Did you know that?
Did you know that?
Even if he has great technical skills and overall outlook,
he can't handle it when others beat him.
When you beat him in a few problems, he starts to unravel and panic.
His need to win is the biggest downfall that he could never overcome,
especially since they turn 30 this year. They want to win so badly.
That means we already have a winning strategy.
And that is to push him. Pressure him! Pressure him to death!
I want that momentum of when Mars hit Earth!
I want to break his last defense!
Back then, that was your Boss's biggest strength.
Now, do you see Little Mi's real strength?
Now that we have him, we have the complete intel of all of the Chinese teams that are in his head.
He knows CTF's history of the last 10 years, backwards and forwards.
I know what you're thinking.
If you don't want his help,
then you can continue with your current attitude.
They also have a deadly weakness,
which is that their way of thinking is old-fashioned, as well as their strategies.
So... So does this mean that they've accepted Mi Shaofei?
This group of kids is pretty easy. They'll accept you as long as you can convince them.
I haven't asked you yet. Why did you come today?
I came to play with Squiddy! I haven't seen Squiddy for a long time.
Right, Squiddy?
Did you gain weight, Squiddy?
Did you miss me, Squiddy?
Aren't you about to start the semifinal matches?
Next Wednesday, we'll be in Shanghai, SP will be in Guangzhou.
Two teams in two cities will start battling at the same time.
You want to watch it?
You want tickets?
Do you have tickets?
Of course, I don't. These are really popular tickets.
There are no more tickets?
But... if you come with me, why would you need a ticket?
Then, what about Yaya? What if Yaya wants to go, too?
She can go ask Mi Shaofei.
Then, now are we...
Am I your...
What?
- Girlfriend.
- What else would you be?
Who does it like that?
You easily break up when you want to, and get back together when you want to.
Then, do we need a formal ceremony or something?
Tong Nian, do you want to...
kiss?
No one does it like that— I...
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Recently, I've caused you pain. I'm sorry.
You can't kiss me anymore. Kiss Squiddy!
Aren't you jealous when I kiss it?
I'm not.
Kiss him, Squiddy!
Easy, easy!
- Don't I have to scrub it clean?
- They're very obedient to you.
- Bye-bye!
- Sister-in-Law, are you leaving?
- See you, Sister-in-Law!
- Bye-bye!
- You're working hard! I'm leaving, bye-bye!
- Leaving? Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye!
- Bye-bye.
Leaving? Bye-bye.
Mi Shaofei!
Good luck! Don't worry. I'll keep rooting for you.
No fear!
Don't worry. I'll certainly not be a burden to Han Shangyan.
I'll send her home. I'll go look for you in a bit.
- Bye-bye.
Working so hard.
No, I'm just thinking about how to increase the team's average strength.
At the moment, there's too much polarization between two levels.
Here, have a look.
Wu Bai, Grunt, 97:
their ranking is all at the top.
The other two...
Though Demo has been steadily improving,
One's result is still 73.
He's pulling down the average strength of the whole team.
At the moment, all those at the front of the ranking have their own teams.
We need to choose slowly.
We can't be slow anymore. You've got to know after I was replaced,
SP's average strength has risen a lot since the team tournament.
One step at a time.
The most important thing we have on hand is to get rid of Team Buff, first.
[Welcome to our new Manager! Mi Shaofei is K&K China's new Team Manager]
What do you think?
Han Shangyan found a good helper.
Nobody fits the manager's position better than Mi Shaofei.
Emerged in Team Solo, witnessed the development of CTF in China,
knows adversaries' strengths and weaknesses,
and he knows us.
This is the most dangerous point.
[Team SP's Global Operations Director, He Nana]
Solo, this battle for you is especially important.
If you lose, it won't just be about pride, it will be a setback.
Headquarters will doubt your skills.
Knowing someone too well sometimes makes people blind.
But it doesn't matter. Our manager is the best.
Share your thoughts, brilliant manager.
Me? I'm happy.
I must find a good opportunity to beat up Mi Shaofei.
Last time you all gathered, I couldn't make it.
Let's talk about something else. Do you have a strategy to respond?
Strategy? The strategy is just to trust me.
Based on our team's average strength,
this national championship will be SP's for sure.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
[NetEase Music]
[Upload music]
[Milk Bread]
[Has joined the upload queue]
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
Hey, Nian Nian, what is this song? It's so good.
Is it a new song?
This song... both he and I like!
How romantic!
Quick!  Quick!  Look at how giddy she is!
What are you doing? You dare to tickle me?
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
This is the song! Little Squid mentioned this before in an interview.
Falling in love is like milk loving bread, embracing each other tightly.
She said milk and bread are a pair match-made in Heaven.
Did she find her Mr. Right?
Goodbye, Your Highness Squid.
It turns out I'm not your milk and I don't have bread.
I won't drink milk anymore, nor eat bread.
I definitely don't like grilled squid anymore.
My heart hurts so much at the moment,
as if it's constantly sinking down.
Goodbye, my one-sided first love.
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
Wow!
What is it?
Sister-in-Law released a new song on NetEase Music.
Seriously?
It's already topping the charts!
It's true. As expected of Sister-in-Law.
It's just as hot here on Weibo.
Boss is getting a lot of shade.
What is the meaning behind this song title?
She's showing her love. Didn't she just come by?
She probably learned the truth about love.
B-Boss.
Spill it.
97.
Spill it quickly.
Why do you pick on me every time?
It's just Sister-in-Law showed off her love and we're happy for her.
Let's be heartbroken together tonight.
Little Squid is mine! Mine! Mine!
Little Squid is in love...
That man, in his past life,
must've saved the entire galaxy.
Help me register.
Boss, you finally thought it through.
You made a NetEase account and now Weibo for Sister-in-Law?
I'll take care of it immediately.
He's actually going to sign up for Weibo.
No way...
Yaya! Chun Chun!
Come! Come! I have to show you this!
- What is it?
Han Shangyan has a Weibo now.
Wow!
Look!
Boss said... he wants a Weibo account?
He was once the first generation Grand Master Level CTF competitor.
K&K's global top honcho has arrived!
Welcome.
Kneeling down to welcome Boss!
Our most important spiritual leader
is... finally on Weibo!
Welcome back.
Wow! Gun God has returned.
The Big Devil, CTF's legend figure is back.
Ten years already, the pioneer who broke new grounds
has finally returned!
Is your blood boiling with excitement? You must show your support!
How many people did he inspire? How many people idolized him when they were young?
Wow! This is like the industry's revelry!
I never thought he'd do this.
Why do you think he opened a Weibo account?
Was it to promote the club or to recruit people?
I don't know.
Your boyfriend opened a Weibo account and you didn't know about it?
I really didn't know.
- Quick, look what he posted.
- Right.
[Han Shangyan]
"K&K Club Official Website."
Really just for promoting.
But this is too inexperienced. At least say something.
His fans count is rising so fast.
- Let me see.
- My Goodness.
[96,392 Fans to 96,404 Fans]
He has that many fans?!
[96,422 Fans]
Wow, Boss, you're amazing.
It hasn't been long and you have over 100k fans.
Oh my god!
It's been three years and I only have 60k.
The king has returned. This amount of fans is considered small.
Just wait a few days and it'll grow to who knows how high.
My fans–
People left me 30k+ comments?
Didn't you just release a new song?
Right? My comments are usually 1k, why 30k+ today?
- Let me see.
- What did they say?
My lord! What happened?
Did Her Highness get hacked?
[His Following - 1: Little Squid]
So, he followed me and I'm the only one he follows!
Right, right.
Wait. He commented.
Han Shangyan: So are you milk and I'm bread, or am I milk and you're bread?
Do I reply?
Of course, you have to reply. Hurry and do it!
I'll reply now.
Well done, Little Squid!
The burst of lovey-dovey you are showing is making me jealous.
Reply: Don't care. From now on, breakfast will be milk and bread.
Send?
No, I have to get my phone.
Are you anxious to get romantic with him?
I won't tell you guys.
Bye!
Don't follow me or eavesdrop!
[Tong Nian]
Is it Sister-in-Law?
Ad.
Ad caller?
An ad?
97, do you know why you don't have a girlfriend?
Learn from him. Just one move to conquer the enemy. Doesn't even need to buy anything.
Why do you always prick my heart?
If I were Sister-in-Law, I would be moved to tears.
Brothers, come here.
Quiet!
Go, go, go.
Wait a moment.
What is it?
All right, we are giving you the room.
There're people passing by and it's inconvenient out here.
- We are just happening to head to the market.
- Yes, yes!
Go, go!
I'll close the door for you.
Let's go.
Okay. We can talk now.
You're on Weibo now?
What is the point of asking the obvious?
If there's nothing else, I'll hang up first.
They're training. There's a competition tomorrow.
Then... Then, you hang up first.
How about you hang up first?
No, I want you to hang up first.
That way you can hear my voice before you hang up.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
- Hey!
That...
Okay, let's talk five more minutes.
Okay. Five minutes.
Five seconds passed.
So fast.
Ten seconds passed.
Wait! I want to say...
For me, you signed up for Weibo,
and I'm the only person you follow, so I'm really happy.
Twenty seconds.
I also want to say...
How about I make something for you?
I will help you put in a facial recognition system.
Then, you don't need a room card to enter or leave the building. Also...
Half of a minute is gone.
So fast.
Seriously though,
I miss you.
So this is what it feels like to be noticed by someone.
What is the feeling?
You understand.
I understand.
This feeling is... so good.
Let's hang up.
Right now?
Then okay. But you should hang up first.
Then I'll hang up.
Bye-bye.
♫ Grateful that youth let us ♫
♫ Remember the most beautiful ♫
♫ We sit in a circle that is dazzling ♫
♫ How long from sunrise to sunset ♫
♫ We quickly understood ♫
♫ We will always exist ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, taking you to travel the universe ♫
♫ Give you everything that is the best ♫
♫ Quietly telling you, "I love you" ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, I'll stay by your side ♫
♫ Time will stop at this moment ♫
♫ Quietly telling you, "I love you" ♫
[Fighting!]
Yay!
Coming!
You're here? Come in.
Long time no see.
- Missed you so much.
- Here, I'll take it. This is expensive!
Thank you, thank you.
- It's nothing.
- Come in.
- Let's go.
Summer, look here! Guests are here!
Sis, what're you doing?
What's this?
I want to go and watch a competition.
Then just go.
How? So many relatives came.
Tell your mom straight. Tell her you want to go and watch.
My mom doesn't like Han Shangyan, how could I just tell her?
Or tell her you want to see a concert.
Is my mom stupid? She would know if there were any concerts today by searching.
School?
She'll definitely say,
"Nian Nian, what can't you do after eating? You brat!"
Also, the internet speed up here is terrible.
I want to watch downstairs, but they're chatting.
I have no way to watch the competition.
How is it? I changed the rooms up bit.
Those curtains are also new; it's pretty nice.
It looks nice. Let me see.
Also, I have some new clothes I haven't worn. Hurry and try them on.
Thank you. I'll try them.
[China Leading Semifinal Competition in Shanghai Stadium]
Although we've retired for a while,
everyone has seen our performance after coming back.
We are prepared!
Our five players strength is equal.
Although we don't have a superstar like Wu Bai,
I believe as long as us five join hands,
we can defeat K&K!
After all, CTF has an emphasis on teamwork and tacit understanding.
Even more, don't forget.
I once defeated Han Shangyan, I'm his nemesis!
I will always have a way to defeat him!
Team Buff will win!
Okay, it's about time!
Bring your mice and keyboards, we're going to go hard today!
Take it easy. Give it your best shot just like when you guys usually train.
Here, here, here.
Good luck! Let's go.
Little Mi.
I forgot to give this to you.
[Team K&K Manager - Mi Shaofei]
Wear it and from this moment on,
you're an official member of K&K.
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
I didn't think we'd have another chance to meet at competition grounds.
I really admire you.
Thirty years old and you still don't accept that you're old.
So what?
For the champion, I'm going all out.
Oh right. A turtle like you who retires once there's conflict wouldn't understand.
Don't forget. I've won against you before.
How you lost in the past,
is how you will still lose to the team members I've led here today.
Did you hear that?
Don't worry, Boss.
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become anyone ♫
Old Han is still as arrogant as before.
Don't let him affect you. Play well.
This is our life and death battle.
If we win, we're second place.
If we lose,
this will be our last competition.
The last one for our entire lives.
Here.
Good luck!
Let's go.
[Buff]
[K&K]
Sis, hurry over. I've connected.
Really?
Let me see.
Really!
Look, it's Brother-in-Law!
Could you be quieter?
He's my idol.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
They still have the same old habits; they have no team manager.
He, himself, is the team manager.
Now looking at K&K, I am sure that we don't have to introduce them too much.
- They are one of the current competition's heavily favored teams to win the championship.
- Yes.
You can do it! Don't be nervous.
...is always hustling and fighting.
Yes, and yesterday the team's boss, Gun God, opened his personal Weibo.
We don't know if he did it to cheer on his team in the competition.
We're awaiting their performance!
Looking at this side, Team Buff has been fighting hard the whole time.
Fighting all the way to the semifinals is not easy.
Especially in their circumstances without any sponsors and without a club, to get to this point is extremely hard.
Yes. At the start of the competition people said that they were the "dark horse" team. Looks like they do not understand their history.
These five people have also been the national champions.
This match may be their last.
They always hoped to leave their career with a perfect curtain call.
Something worth mentioning is that a decade ago when Gun God was in Team Solo,
the only match that he did lose was to Team Buff, who is matched against this side.
And here we see that we have connected to the Guangzhou competition site, who have finished all preparations.
[China District Qualifier SemiFinals - Guangzhou Stadium]
[SP]
The organizer said that it's almost time and to get everyone on stage.
You don't need me to give more motivation before the competition, right?
Of course, we do.
I need a motivating hug.
Here you go again.
- Me too!
- What hug?
Okay, stop messing around.
If we keep dawdling, K&K is going to win already!
They won't. The competitions are taking place simultaneously.
Everyone, just maintain your relaxed state; believe you're the best.
Get ready and we'll go soon.
Give all the tags to me. It's too uncomfortable.
Give them here.
- Let's discuss how we are going to play later.
- Yeah.
Old Han should be okay, right? This time the opponent is Team Buff again.
Don't worry. He'll be fine.
Last time, he lost to Buff was because he had a forty-degree Celsius fever.
(104 degrees Fahrenheit)
He went on stage after he had an IV drip.
This time, Han Shangyan will not let Buff have a good time.
We can see that the online viewers have already surpassed 400,000.
Come in!
Greet your uncle and aunt!
(T/N: Father's younger brother and his wife)
- Uncle and aunt!
- Hello, Uncle and Aunt.
You can sit here, go ahead!
- Come, sit!
- We didn't come for a while, and there are so many changes!
Yes! I added some furnishings.
Did you plant this bonsai?
- I planted it! Come, sit!
- Okay.
- Come, let's sit!
- Earphones. Get out your earphones.
Luckily I came prepared.
- Sit, sit!
- I can see that there have been big changes!
Nian Nian!
What's going on with you two? Uncle and Aunt came here to see you,
but you two are just playing.
Is this for you to eat?
Here, have some fruits, have some fruits!
- Please don't worry about us.
- Eat some fruits. Come on.
- Eat up.
- Come, eat!
- Eat, eat! No need to be polite.
These grapes are so fresh!
Nian Nian. Nian Nian!
Come here, accompany everyone to chat!
Aunt, we are watching a live broadcast of a competition!
What? Diving?
This is CTF!
What is CTF?
I don't understand either!
Let's not bother with them. Here!
Sis, what does this "BO5" mean?
BO1 means one round decides who wins or loses. BO3 means you need to win two of three rounds.
I know! Then BO5 you need to win three of five rounds?
Nice, Sis! You've become an expert!
Nian Nian, you really are too great!
- Kids these days...
- This child is amazing.
Then, I'll bring you guys out to look around!
- Okay! Sure!
- Let's go out to the yard and have a look!
- Come. Let's go!
- Go, go!
Have fun kids!
Keep playing!
Don't bother with it, for now. Let's watch!
When did my mom start standing behind us?
- I don't know!
- Are you stupid? You don't know?
Stop hitting me.
You are too stupid. How can someone be so stupid?
You took the wrong one!
We can see here that they have already come into contact.
Beautiful.
Okay, congratulations to K&K for getting dibs to choose.
Nice!
Everyone, the semifinals of the eighth season of CTF in China is about to start.
[PRO LEAGUE SEASON 8: Team K&K vs Team Buff]
[Acquiring Network]
Let's take a look at both sides' opening moves.
On this side, under Team Captain Buff's lead, Team Buff has chosen the most commonly seen tactic;
five people are immediately charging for a single node.
But on this side, 97 and Demo are defending.
[Access granted]
At the same time on this side Buff has been broken through! DT is going in!
[Access denied]
97, what is happening? 97 could not hold the defense!
- Congratulations to Buff for an auspicious start to the semi-finals.
- Good!
Did not expect that after Buff took down one node that they did not take any more points.
Yes. On this side, I can see a duel between two main offense players - another has infiltrated!
Both attackers are showing brilliant execution.
Let us congratulate Team K&K for their victory in the first round.
And we hope that after the short break, Team Buff can adjust their own condition well!
[SHH Stadium Pro League Season 8]
[K&K E-Sports Battle: 1; Buff E-Sports: 0]
Over here we see that Buff is trying to open the loophole.
But DT's security reinforcement moves are very quick.
He is not quick enough, Buff has circumvented around.
Afterwards, DT went back on the defensive,
[Access granted]
Two nodes. It was an exciting dueling.
Demo got it. Team Buff lost the last node.
- In this case then, let's congratulate K&K for taking this round.
- Congratulations!
[SHH Stadium Pro League Season 8]
[K&K E-Sports Battle: 2; Buff E-Sports: 0]
Great. Beautiful.
Buff took three nodes in one shot.
[Access granted]
He's still got it. Congratulations to Buff.
Nice.
Even though Buff won, his expression is still quite serious.
Three wins out of five. The next round is the most critical one.
[SHH Stadium Pro League Season 8]
[K&K E-Sports Battle: 2; Buff E-Sports: 1]
Bros, steady now. Hold steady.
Captain, how's the next round going to go?
Forceful offensive, let's penetrate them.
Okay. Good luck.
Fellow teammates, you can do this. Our success depends on this round.
Let's go!
All right, we see that K&K got to the match point first.
In this round, are we going to see K&K smash all resistance
and take this round and win this entire match?
Or will Team Buff have a turning point
and tie the score?
Must remain calm.
One on one showdown.
The remaining one on one showdown. DT successfully attacked and entered.
[Password Decryptor: Calculating Hashes]
DT has one last node.
Looks like the suspense is over.
[Access Granted]
- Why're they so happy?
- What is going on?
Nice! Nice!
Yes!
Then, at this moment, we've received news that over in Guangzhou,
SP team, at almost the same time, won their semifinal match.
They've entered the finals.
[Guangzhou Semifinals Competition Venue: CL vs SP]
SP! SP! SP!
Solo! Solo! Solo!
Dear friends watching the live broadcast, we are thankful for your support today.
Today's live streaming is now completed.
The final match of CTF will be held in Beijing next month.
We will see you there.
- Bye-bye!
- See you all in Beijing! Bye-bye.
Congratulations.
They have basically cut off all forms of retreat.
I heard from Ai Qing that they resigned to come and compete here.
Thirty years old... He probably wanted to fight for his dream one more time.
Get up now, Buff. Let's go drink a round.
Yeah, after a few days we'll separate.
Who knows when we'll meet again.
We at least won the national championship before. Let's be a good sport.
I am also not satisfied with this loss, but we have no other choice.
We can't go hungry and remain unemployed.
Consider this a journey in our life. We can enjoy the fond memories.
You are still here. The final accumulated scores are out.
The losing team on the other side didn't score higher than you.
Congratulations, everyone, you got third place.
Actually, this is already amazing.
It is not easy for older players to still get third place.
You should all be happy.
We are closing up soon. Let's hurry up.
All right.
Captain, let's go, too. People are starting to rush us.
I'll pack my things.
You can leave first.
Then, Captain, we'll head out first.
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
Congratulations, Gun God.
I think this match was really awesome.
The whole audience was hyped.
Really, I'm looking forward to an even better performance, congrats.
Thanks.
Sorry, I didn't see you.
We're about to clean up.
When you leave, could you close the doors?
♫ You're walking away, begging to me ♫
What is it?
Are you still not willing to admit defeat?
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
♫ Trying to find the one that is me ♫
No, I admit it wholeheartedly.
Whether as a professional competitor or as a boss,
you will always be the bane of my life.
I know that when I beat you last time, it was just a lucky break.
To hear you admit defeat in my lifetime,
the feeling is pretty good.
Buff! Calm down.
What are you doing?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫