♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 40]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
So everyone couldn't sleep?
How can we?
-Weren't you snoring earlier? I heard it
-I faked it.
How could you snore so loudly?
right?
Anyways,
I'm super nervous right now.
I feel that even at this age,  I haven't seen such a big scene before.
Say, how many years have the two of us been competing together?
I haven't felt like this before.
Who told you to idolize Boss?
- Isn't his dream your dream?
- That's true.
But boss never had you in mind.
Watch your mouth.
Nice, I was getting thirsty.
Although I cannot go on stage, but I will be in the audience wishing you guys well.
But really, being with you guys for so long...is quite nice.
Of course!
Come! Let's cheer.
Come!
Be a bit quieter.
Let me tell you
just now, in bed I was researching a new tactics.
super useful.
Really?
Look, when we were competing, I researched the opponents in a lot of detail.
We attack together, find a vulnerability, three people go and attack the vulnerability.
Breakthrough their node.
- Take them by surprise!
- Yeah!
Because of our forceful attack, at this time all of them will definitely come and defend.
Right. Demo, remember this.
Deliberately show our vulnerability, then reinforce our server.
Han Shangyan
Han Shangyan?
I'm down here.
Couldn't sleep?
When you're excited you can't sleep.
I was afraid to disturb Buff's rest.
Then you're not afraid to disturb my rest?
You're not competing. You're not worth it.
Honestly, after that competition,
I really hoped that you would make a comeback.
We were lucky that day.
Those five people weren't from the same club and didn't have tacit understanding of each other. We won by a narrow margin.
I can't anymore, Little Mi.
A hero already past his prime!
I'm past my prime, you're not!
You really don't want to compete anymore?
No.
You really are stubborn.
What about doing individual events?
Forget about it.
Such a pity, a pity!
I'm 30 already.
If I compete, the most I can play is two more years.
Like Buff, won't last long.
But the kids I'm leading
at minimum can compete for another ten years.
Cool.
Ten years... they could get first place more than ten times, or even as much as a couple hundred.
The past...is the past.
It doesn't matter if people remember Gun God.
Right now I am not trying to myself out to be a hero.
What I care about is the training center's reputation.
You should stop hanging around with me here! Wherever it's nice and cool is where you go and stay.
The chair in the training room is fine too.
The big table in the meeting room is also fine too.
The table is big. Lying down there will be comfortable.
Give me a break. Even if I let you sleep, you won't fall asleep for sure.
I suspect, that in your heart you're definitely worried about Solo's side.
What is there to worry about?
If they can't even get third place, in the future he shouldn't say that he is my bro.
Come! Let's sleep!
Go to my bed and sleep.
It's pretty good here, no need.
Yaya! I can't fall asleep!
Me too!
Just now when I turned over I was afraid I would wake you up. You should have said earlier that you weren't asleep.
Or... why don't we go over right now?
Right now?
- It's 11p.m.!
- If we go over now, will we disturb their resting?
I know near K&K there is a 24/7 convenience store.
We can wait until morning there.
In any case, we can't fall asleep. What if we fall asleep and we oversleep, what then?
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
Get up!
Little Mi, get up!
Are you here?
Didn't you set up a facial recognition system for them?
I did!
I think forgot to set it up for myself...
It's fine, it's fine! If I make a few expressions, maybe I will look like someone and it will open up? Right?
Open.
Didn't I say, that I would go pick you up in the afternoon?
I... last night, the both of us got here. At midnight.
I... I ask for a bed. I need to take a nap for a while.
Oh, I know! They have an empty space here. I'll bring you there.
I'm bringing her there!
Be more quiet! They haven't woken up yet.
Your voice is the loudest!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
I'm coming, coming! Get out of the way!
Oh my God! Are you here making coffee or dismantling the machine?
This isn't how you do it! I taught you before how to do it, did you forget?
Look here, it's like this!
Did you see?
Forget it, forget it! Anyway, you standing there won't help me.
You. Go sit over there.
Once I'm done I'll carry it over, okay?
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
You can't look at it yet!
What are you doing? I didn't let you look yet!
When I let you look, then look!
Listen to me countdown!
- Three...
- One!
- Two! One!
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
How long have you learned this for?
Probably not that long.
Anyways, during winter vacation I was idle and
had nothing to do. So I learned some latte art, and I learned how to do it pretty fast.
Is there anything that you don't know how to do?
That's pretty hard... I think I actually know how to do everything.
There's one. CTF!
Is it good?
It's... not bad!
Asking you a question. Don't you feel that we are really fated?
Are we?
Of course we are! The first time we saw each other, you were in a bad mood at the time.
You just so happened to choose my little brother's internet cafe, resulting in us meeting.
The second time, in Guangzhou. You were in Guangzhou. I was also in Guangzhou.
And we met again!
The third time, is just now!
At the entrance I was just worrying about how to come in, and then you appeared!
It's like God deliberately arranged it! Aren't we really fated?
This coffee isn't bad.
Directly answer my question!
I am asking you, aren't we really fated?
Aren't you sleepy?
I'm sleepy... last night I didn't sleep the entire night.
I sat for so long that my back is sore. How can I not be sleepy?
Do you need to go up and sleep? Otherwise, you won't have the energy to watch the competition.
I am going to wait until you finish this coffee and then I'll go up.
Then, I might not finish drinking it.
Why?
I would hate to drink away this heart that you made for me.
Aren't we really fated?
Aren't we really fated? Really fated? Really fated? Really fated?
- It's spilling!
- Answer me!
- Just now you didn't tell me!
- It's spilling!
- Aren't we really fated? Are we fated or not?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Are we fated or not?
- Yes!
Are we or not?
♫ Quietly saying: I love you ♫
♫ Let’s go together, let’s go together, holding you in my arms ♫
♫ Holding hands, holding hands, I'll stay by your side ♫
♫ Time will stop at this moment ♫
♫ Quietly telling you: ♫
♫  I love you ♫
Wake up, wake up!
What time is it?
It's 8 a.m.
Then let's sleep for a while longer.
Why are you here?!
Did you teleport here? Aren't you supposed to be at home?
Besides, isn't Yaya at your house?
I...I...I...
Oh my God. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I forgot that Mi Shaofei was still in my bed! Oh my God.
This is really awkward. I-I am going to the bathroom to brush my teeth and wash my face!
W-w-wait! Where's Yaya? Yaya.
She... s-she came here with me together. S-she's in the other room sleeping, don't worry.
Han Shangyan, you really don't think of me as a man?
If she wanted to sleep, you should've told me and I would have went somewhere else!
I haven't even asked whether you did anything to my girlfriend and you are already acting like you are the master, huh?
I, the master, is leaving.
Mi Shaofei!
Tong Nian, I am sorry.
Last night the two of us drank too much, I really didn't know that he was on my bed. Sorry, sorry.
This time, I'll forgive you. Next time you can't be like this again, understand?
I'll get you a toothbrush.
Why do you have so many one-time use toothbrushes?
I often go on business trips.
So I prepared these so it will be more convenient.
Do you feel that this really doesn't feel like home?
Are you too busy and have no time to pack?
I feel that you should find someone to help you pack.
Then you don't need to use these one-time use toothbrushes again.
Okay.
Then in the future when I pack, I'll call you over to help me.
Depends on my mood!
Han Shangyan!
There's an urgent matter.
- How are you feeling?
- It hurts.
-  Do you need to go to the hospital?
- Have some more water!
I want to compete.
What happened?
Your old sickness is flaring up?
It's not a big deal. I won't die.
You're already eating medicine for stomach ulcers, and that's not serious?
What do you think?
We need to have two strings to one's bow.
You bring Grunt to the hospital. Everyone else come out and for a meeting.
We'll discuss the matter of swapping people.
Boss! It's not like I haven't gone up
while I was sick.
I'm fine. Once I have some medicine I'll be okay.
You can't have any more medicine! You just took it!
Rest up first. Don't think too much.
Everyone else come out for a meeting.
Boss! Boss!
Boss!
Boss! I want to play in the finals.
I beg you, don't swap me out.
For this day to come, do you know how long I have waited?
Three years. It's been three years!
Just for this one moment. And you want to swap me out?
I can go up even if I'm sick. I can do it, Boss!
Everyday I have been practicing, everyday I have been practicing!
I beg you, Boss! Don't swap me out!
What are you crying for?
Today, in this match whether we win or lose,
we've already got a ticket to the World Finals.
Right now you need to recuperate first.
Once you have recuperated, at that time if you play, isn't it the same?
But this is our home game!
If we lose, what do we do?
Do you really think you are all that? Do you really not trust your teammates at all?
Without you, they will still get first place.
Don't cry anymore.
Little Mi, bring him to the hospital and see.
Rest well. Everyone else come out for a meeting.
Boss!
- Grunt!
- 97, call an ambulance.
- Grunt! Grunt!
- Go!
- Okay!
Going down from the stairs in the front will be more convenient. The front.
I think you should go with him. This kid is stubborn and competitive, look after him.
I'll go.
Where's Wu Bai?
Team Captain and One went out for a morning run.
Call everyone to come back. Holding a meeting.
Okay, I'll go make a call.
Boss. Everyone is here.
You were looking for me, Boss?
Make some preparations. Later on, you will go on stage on behalf of Grunt.
Me?
I-I... but... me and Grunt are apart by quite a few rankings.
Grunt can't go. Other than you, who else is there?
But...
You already played at the national competition, what are you afraid of?
That's... not the same, Boss.
Stop talking nonsense. Sit over there.
Usually we train together,
so I’m not going to say anymore nonsense.
I was just telling Grunt that the result of today's competition is not important,
because we already received the spot to enter the world competition.
But...understand this from today's competition.
For the main competition, you all must get me the championship. There is no other choice. Do you all understand me?
Yes!
Go ahead and open some rounds and do some practice on coordinating.
Today I will be your manager and accompany you for the entire duration.
All right.
Captain, we suddenly have this turn of event.
I hope you will bear with it.
Do as you normally would, I will be here.
Let’s go.
Then we wasted our efforts in changing members before.
If we were to compare this on the national level, then this is similar to as if using Buff to switch out Grunt.
Using a high level player to switch another high level player.
The whole team actual ability didn't get raise up.
Buff rank is #4, he is still stronger than Grunt.
But think about it,
if we were to consider base on age, reflex and tacit understanding.
- Nian Nian! Go thing you guys didn’t leave. I thought I overslept.
- How’s that possible?
I didn’t bother you guys, did I?
How could it be?
You guys enjoy yourselves for a bit. Come to the conference room for lunch around 11:30am.
What’s wrong?
Grunt suddenly got sick.
He can't compete, has to be substituted.
Getting sick today?
That's right. They are probably in total chaos now.
Ya Ya, what should we do?
I don’t know.
[Asian Pacific Region Finals Competition. ]
SP won!
Congratulations to SP, they won the first round.
They got the third place for this season's competition.
You've got fight hard when you are young. Let's make a toast for SP.
[Ten year legend, China's zero hour. ]
Finally walked to this day.
I saw the expression of pride on his face.
He is Han Shangyan. He is my man.
This is prize I received from my first championship, a champion ring.
It might be a bit big. You might can’t put it on.
Who says I can’t put it on?
I can put it on my bracelet, or buy another bracelet and hang it there. It's all good.
He will definitely complete his dream,
Because he put in so much effort.
He is so outstanding.
Let’s get married.
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
Get married.
It's not that I do not want to say yes to his proposal,
I thought what I’m waiting is this timing.
This moment that we can be most proud of.
Han Shangyan.
Let’s get married.
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
No matter if we lose or win this competition, there’s always me accompanying you.
Let’s get married.
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
Look at the big screen.
No problem.
After the competition ends, we’ll get married.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Seeing these young people in front of me.
It’s like that I saw myself ten years ago.
At that time, it seemed the entire world is under my feet.
In my dictionary, there is no “lose” this word.
You lived for CTF.
I am a loner by default.
Even though CTF is stage full of sound and light,
But seems only when I am here,
that I can get myself to calm down.
I said it before. CTF this kind of thing,
Either don’t touch it,
or you must win. It’s that easy.
Yet I gave it up earlier.
Because I was afraid of the unknown future,  of losing, of betrayal.
Only then I know that,
I am actually not powerful at all.
I hid inside my own shell,
crying all along.
What is the correct way then?
If I fail, need to hand over my dream to others,
This group of K&K kids are lucky to have you to take care of them.
That’s because you’re great.
Thèse bunch of kids has dreams.
Also what is so precious is that they are...
Maybe only after meeting those weaker,
then we can become stronger.
So I've decided, to stand with those people who continue to keep going,
regardless of countless defeats,
to protect this thing that is more important that pride: dreams.
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
This path is difficult.
Some people succeeds, some people back out,
But they came and they fought,
They've made non believers feel ashamed.
They've helped lost ones find direction.
They've always believed...
their own very hands will be able to create a future.
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
You are the one who made me take this down.
You better wear this and get the championship.
Money might be important,
because it can give you a good life.
But people only became great because of dreams.
so my dream had never change.
I want to help them to get the world championship for China.
We already got the national championship.
Why are we giving up?
Those who have dreams will always remain young.
I did it for myself. Did you really think I did it  only for the world championship?
What is the point now that we are missing a person?
Ten years, I've never consider returning to the stage of competition.
I thought I already gave up on that beating of the youth.
gave up on the testimony to pride.
But that day I just knew,
Even though so many years had passed,
those who were quietly supported us,
never gave up on that persistence.
the persistence for dreams.
That is their memory of youth.
It is magnificent but short.
muddled but passionate.
Our youth can lose,
but who does not have any regrets in their youth?
Look at these kids.
Even if there's only one left standing,
they will fight to the end.
Because they are not fighting alone,
the thing that is standing behind them, supporting them...
is every CTF participant's youth.
What they are carrying...
is the entire ten year's worth of every Chinese CTF participants' hope and tears.
In my eyes, you will always be the best captain.
Those people who are either inside competing...
or struggling outside of the competition.
Thank you all.
The world owes you all a championship.
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more. ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
Why are you crying on such a big day?
I was so scared!
You only have this level of bearing capability? How are you going to go watch the World Finals?
You're promising to take me to watch the World's Finals?!
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
Championship belongs to K&K! Belongs to China!
Han Shangyan is holding a country flag.
Walked up to the front of the stage.
Han Shangyan gave the country flag to Wu Bai.
On this world stage,
we are airing live on the front.
Spread open our China flag
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
Champion! Champion! Champion!
♫ Continue chasing, who’s glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
I broke out in a cold sweat for you a moment ago.
The kids worked hard.
You say, wasn't it awful for me. I was beaten by Tian Ji as soon as I went up.
Your life was worth a lot, didn't you know? As soon as you went up, a master was switch down.
Fortunately, you guys won. Championships still belongs to our China!
That’s right, it’s our China’s!
Grunt! Come here.
Boss.
Nurse your stomach back to health!
If there's a next time, I will ban you from competing for a year!
Boss! Is there anyone who would treat sick people like you do?
This year is the essence of my life.
Boss, let me compete in the international tournament and work hard for the Chinese!
We'll see.
Okay. For what you just said!
Listen up! Today K&K will act as the host! Whatever you want to eat,
spend freely! Let's go!
Since K&K is acting as the host,
let's order takeout and get it all delivered to K&K! You guys haven't been to K&K before, have you?
Great! I always wanted to go but I didn't dare!
- Okay! Tonight, everyone is going to K&K to eat dinner!
- Okay!
- I'll buy!
- Yes!!!
Ripping off Han Shangyan, these kinds of thing,
we are the best at it. Am I right?
Yes!
You take everyone to the car. I have to go do something.
Little Mi, hurry!
Come here.
Let's go.
Where are we going? Aren't we... aren't we celebrating with everyone?
We do need to celebrate. But there is still one thing that is more important that we have to go do.
I'm taking her away.
Take her! Returning her to you.
Wait for me.
Solo, do me a favor.
What is it that you are so anxious?
Go to the lounge with me.
That urgent?
What's happening here?
I don't know.
China is...
The champion!
Congratulations to you. The best champion.
Thanks.
♫ Walking through the roundabout way ♫
♫ In the end I’ll reach the end of time ♫
♫ Let the future make known ♫
♫ All the unknown distant places ♫
Continue to work hard. Work towards world champion.
♫ Will become eternity’s prelude ♫
Why are you so shy?
- Let's go have a coffee.
- Sure.
- Let's go!
Why are you walking so fast?
What's the burning issue?
This way.
Get out. Get out.
What is it? Being so mysterious.
Take off your clothes.
Take off what?
Quickly. Quickly.
You called me over here just to make me take off my clothes?
There's no one here, hurry up.
No, no, no! You tell me clearly first. What am I taking my clothes off for?
Later on I need to go to Tong Nian's house. Take your clothes and lend them to me for a few hours.
Your Mother-in-law prepared a celebratory feast for you? Okay.
You should wear something formal to go. Do you want a suit?
It's such a hot day and you brought a suit?
It's because I was worried that there would be a press conference.
You don't need it. You don't need to handle these matters.
Hurry up.
Wait.
I cannot take everything off like this and go out! You take your clothes and give them to me!
I'll do it myself.
Hurry.
Hurry up and take it off! I'll help you.
- Jia Hao, they are inside, right? Let us in.
- You can't go in.
Why?
Boss is not letting one inside.
What is he doing inside?
I don't know.
- They won't let us in.
- They won't let us in?
Be careful!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
What are you two doing?
If we are brothers, then let's go together.
- We'll be done soon.
- What are you guys... doing in there?
Are you guys playing a game?
- A game?
- What is happening here?
I... I don't know! I don't know.
Boss! Why did you swap clothing with Solo for no reason?
Who are you trying to con this time?
Move aside.
Let's go.
I will talk to you on the phone.
My God! Lan Mei what happened to your husband? Why is he crying like this?
He is too excited. Old boy but young at heart.
That's why I am abusing my rights for private interest. I specially brought him to see his idol.
Gun God, congratulations.
You finally got this champion.
Don't cry. If every time I get first place you need to cry, then you'll never stop crying.
Okay.
Do you have something later? If you're free, go to K&K and join the celebratory feast.
Really?
Of course. We'll meet later.
See you later, see you later!
Later on, can I really go? Later on, can I really go?
Of course you can go! Look, this is Sister-in-law's sister.
You are Sister-in-law's brother-in-law. No matter how you say it, you guys are still relatives! Let's go together!
- Go, go, go!
- Come, let's tidy up and go back to K&K!
W-w-w-wait! Wait a minute!
Isn't that a female star? She was in a spy movie, I especially liked it!
- That's right! That's right! It's her!
- Thank you.
Can we take a photo with you?
-Of course.
-Camera!
Okay, okay. She isn't here to look for you guys.
97.
97?
Hello.
Come and give your signature to your fan.
M-my fan?
- Of course.
- I am your fan.
Can you give me your signature?
I c-c-can! I can!
Director Xiang, this string is really great.
It's a rare opportunity that I am pulling strings. Let me have some pride.
You guys are Asia's champions. Of course a lot of people like you guys.
Nice, 97!
Then...then... can I also have your signature?
Of course you can.
Please sign one for me.
Grandma, it's Little Mi.
I want to tell you... that I got first place.
Me and Old Han got first place together.
We finally succeeded.
That's great, that's great! Grandma congratulates you!
Congratulations to you! All three of us - me, your mom, your grandma congratulate you together!
Yes, yes!
Yes. Grandma, thank you so much. It's just... yes. You've always...
You've always supported me, yes.
Grandma... I-I'll let you listen to
the voice of the girl I like, okay?
- A girl?
- Let me, let me, let me!
A girl? Yes, yes!
It's my grandma.
Me?
Hello.
Hello Grandma, I'm Sun Yaya.
Sun Yaya. Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Your voice is so nice to listen to!
- This voice is nice to listen to!
- It's nice to listen to, nice to listen to!
You won't say anything anyways! Let me!
Hello, are you Little Mi's girlfriend?
I...I don't know if I am.
What is it?
They asked if I was your girlfriend.
Just say that you are. Keep talking. Tell them!
Our Little Mi is fortunate to have you take care of him!
That's right, that's right!
No, no. It's what I should do!
When are you coming here?
They asked when are you going back?
Soon.
Very soon, he'll be back very soon.
Me and Little Mi's mom are waiting to see you!
Grandma, and his grandma too!
- Okay.
- That's right, that's right!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫