♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 7]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
It doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt at all.
Boss, you can't function on an empty stomach.
You are the backbone of K&K.
You have to eat more! My cooking is pretty good.
I'll just put it here for you for now.
I don't know why you suddenly stopped eating dinner.
So... I cooked two more dishes.
I hope you will like it.
Sorry for today.
Let's eat together.
Okay!
Hurry and try it!
Are the dishes cold? Hurry and try it!
And there's this egg here! I bought it fresh this afternoon.
If you don't like this type of egg, I can also make it a fried egg.
I also didn't know if you liked to eat spicy things, so I made it not spicy.
If you like spicy food, I can make it spicy!
If you don't like eating rice, I can make–
Isn't it annoying?
Not annoying. Not annoying at all!
It's edible.
I did say that my cooking isn't bad!
[Hongqiao Airport]
[Welcome Grandpa Han returning to visit relatives]
[Grandpa Han, K&K Club welcomes you home to visit relatives]
Hello? Captain, I haven't found Grandpa yet.
Can you tell me what Grandpa looks like?
Or maybe what he is wearing?
Even now, I still haven't picked him up.
Okay, I will check. Hold the signs a bit higher.
I'm afraid that he's older now and hasn't noticed the signs.
He said that he hasn't been able to pick him up yet. You're really not going to pick him up at the exit?
If I go, I'll get scolded. If I don't go, I'll get scolded, too.
Instead of getting criticized by him in a public place, then why not just sit in the car and conserve my strength.
Why don't you go?
I think it's enough that Demo goes.
Where is it?
Grandpa, it's just up there. We're almost there.
Han Shangyan!
I flew in from so far away, and you didn't go in to pick me up?
Grandpa, aren't I here?
It is hard to find parking here. Can you not scold me publicly like this?
You're afraid of being embarrassed? Then you should have listened!
Grandpa.
Little Bai!
Come, come. Let me look at you!
Huh? How come you've gotten slimmer!
Is it because Han Shangyan doesn't give you good food?
If I don't give him good food, can he be this handsome? Don't accuse me.
You think I don't know you? Workaholic!
Once you start working, what time do you have to take care of him?
Grandpa, we are being taken care of very well.
Look, I am still nice and plump.
This-This kid...
Get in the car.
Come, Little Bai! Get in the car.
Captain, this is the first time I've seen Boss being so well-behaved.
It's been a long time since I came back.
Oh yeah, what did you say your name was just now?
Grandpa, I'm called Demo!
Demo.
Doesn't Demo mean sample?
Grandpa, this is just an online username.
After the competition,
you need to go home and find a good job.
You must not be like Han Shangyan, just making trouble all day long.
Grandpa, our Boss doesn't make trouble.
Boss?
Part of a mafia now, Boss?
Oh right. It's New Year's. Why didn't you go home?
My family... My dad and mom are getting a divorce and splitting the property.
Even if I go back, I don't have a place to sleep.
Han Shangyan, take good care of him! He is still so young.
Grandpa, I am not young anymore! I just look young.
Grandpa, you must be tired. I'll give you a massage.
Little Bai, help Grandpa buy something.
And then, meet up with us at the New Year's Eve dinner.
Okay.
Han Shangyan, bring the luggage to my room and come with me somewhere.
Grandpa, does it feel good?
Yep.
Dounan! Dounan, hurry and come down.
Your sis came back, do you hear? Stop playing!
Aunt, see what gift I got you.
Look at you, so polite!
You bring me presents every time. I'm a bit embarrassed.
Sis, are you still going to play this game?
No.
You don't like him anymore? Did you lose interest?
Don't go on my bed!
Can't you see I'm worried? Tell me clearly.
It's just that he told me he didn't want to date right now.
He wants to focus on his career, so he directly rejected me.
You believe those kinds of lame excuses?
In essence, there's only one reason.
He just doesn't like you.
Of course. I'll say something frankly.
He's so old. He doesn't suit you.
Hu Dounan, are you done? Take your laptop away!
We're eating New Year's Eve dinner soon!
Don't call my full name.
Also, I don't want to go.
Every time my sis comes home, I'm always singled out and scolded.
Everyone in the family is a scholar-tyrant, except for me.
Don't you have a conscience? Doesn't Sis (his real older sister) always bring stuff back for you?
The fancier her gift is, the more my mom thinks I am a good-for-nothing.
You already are. What can you blame your bad grades on?
Oh right, Aunt. Nian Nian and Nan Nan hid inside their rooms the minute they got back. What're they doing?
Is he not your younger brother?
He is teaching Nian Nian to play games. They must be hiding in there playing games.
Mom, be careful. Make sure he doesn't become addicted to bad games.
Okay, okay, okay. I'll scold him properly at home.
They should be here soon, right?
They should be arriving soon.
They might be on their way.
Let me tell you. This time he is the grandson of our old family friend.
You can't be stubborn.
I know! Look, my mom always talks so much.
- Right, she won't. She's such a good child.
- She's always like this.
- Right.
Aunt is the best.
[Han Shangyan Interview.mpv]
I believe in CTF's potential.
Even though K&K China is still losing, that is a natural pattern.
K&K Norway lost for three years before they began to win.
I think I won't have to talk about DT because everyone is so familiar with him.
Also, he has always kept his number one position.
About other members, I think Grunt and 97...
What are you secretly watching?
Secretly watching? What are you talking about?
You clearly weren't wearing headphones earlier! You have a guilty conscience!
- What guilty thing did I do?
- You are!
I... What? I need to go to the bathroom.
Lift up your feet! Annoying!
[URBAN MUSIC]
Little girl, your information is off the mark. Didn't you say that you like me?
How come you don't even know I'm single and uninterested in women?
[Didn't you say that you like me? How come you don't even know I'm single and uninterested in women?]
Get back here! Why are looking at my private things?
Was the person on the screensaver you?
- I-I-I what?
- Y-You're with that guy?
- What man?
- Who is that man?
- Which man?
- Let me see!
- No! I made up the characters!
- I... I...
- I did see a guy!
- Can't I make up characters?
It doesn't look like it. Are you dating?
- You're the one who's dating!
- Are you dating?
- Don't make stuff up!
- You are dating! Your are dating!
She's dating! She's dating!
- Okay! Okay! Okay!
- Go away!
- I won't say anymore!
- So annoying!
I was wrong. I was wrong.
Is it here?
This should be it.
The GPS says that this is the place.
Take it slowly.
Why are you wearing all black?
My wardrobe is filled with the same clothes.
Today, I'm matchmaking for you. Couldn't you have worn something more formal?
How could I have known you were taking me out to a matchmaking date?
I thought you were coming to see an old friend.
I'm telling you. Today's matchmaking must be a success, it cannot be a failure.
You're so autocratic. Just give me an arranged marriage then. Why do you even bother with matchmaking?
You go on, I'm going to leave first. Give me a call later!
What now?
My... My chest hurts.
That's enough.
Stop with the idle talk. Let's go!
They're here.
- Uncle Han!
- You are here.
- Little Tong. Little Lin. I am bothering you.
What are you saying? We're so happy that you're here, right?
Right! Uncle Han, we haven't seen you in a few years but you're still so high-spirited!
- Yes, yes!
- In the few years we haven't seen each other, you've gotten taller again!
- How could I have gotten taller? At this age? I'm already old!
- Greet them!
Uncle. Auntie.
- Uncle Han!
- Hello, Little Chubby Sis. Where's your daughter?
My daughter is in the house making tea for you!
- Hurry in!
- Come in, Uncle Han!
Take your time!
- A-jiao.
- Be careful, Uncle!
- Uncle Han, come.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Call him "Grandpa Han!"
Hello, Grandpa Han!
Good, good! Is this her?
This is her! This is my daughter.
Grandpa Han, China's weather is rather dry. I especially prepared some fruits for you.
I'm not sure if it will be to your liking.
Come in!
- Say hi!
- Hello, I am Hu Yuejiao.
Han Shangyan.
- Grandpa Han, quickly come sit!
- Uncle Han, sit.
You just came back from Norway. I thought that you might not be used to our domestic teas.
I specially prepared a floral tea for you.
I'm not sure if it will be to your taste.
- Your trip must have been tiring.
- It was all right.
- Please have some tea!
- Yes, yes.
Try it!
- It is quite fragrant!
- This was specially prepared by A-jiao.
Hurry up, Nian Nian!
I know.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Sis!
Nian Nian, what are you doing? There are so many guests here!
Why are you dressed like that? Hurry up and go change. Hurry.
Wait a minute.
This... is your home?
Yes... what a coincidence?
Nian Nian, what are you doing? Where are your manners?
May I ask where the restroom is?
That way. It's over there.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Nian Nian, hurry and go change!
Have some fruit!
No thanks.
Have some tea.
- I have juice.
- You...
Nian Nian. Hurry.
- Hurry and greet Grandpa Han.
- Hello, Grandpa Han.
- My daughter, she's currently majoring in computers at university.
- Why is he here?
- I don't know!!
- I can tell she is a good child.
Oh, right! I have a grandson from my daughter who is very handsome.
He is also studying computers in school.
Later on, you two can get to know each other!
I believe you guys will have a lot of common topics to talk about!
- He is going there later as well?
- Yes, yes!
You hear that?
Say, do you think her and Little Bai are a good match?
I don't know. If you think they are a good match, then it is a good match.
Psh. Hey, give him a call!
He can't be late for the New Year's Eve dinner.
Got it!
[Happiness]
Uncle Han, slowly.
Uncle Han, let's take this car. It is comfortable!
- This one?
- Yeah, let's get in this one!
Okay, okay!
Later on, find an opportunity to ask that girl about her height, weight, what she likes.
Do you hear me?
Grandpa Han, let's get in the car!
I'll help you.
Be careful.
Oh my God. Sis, what should we do?
I'm going to go over first.
Nian Nian, I'm giving you a task.
We are trying to matchmake your cousin with that big brother over there.
Later on, you sit in their car and listen to what they are saying and act accordingly, got it?
Matchmaking?
What is it?
- Dounan, you go in the other car in the back.
- Okay.
Tong Nian, hurry up!
I... I won't sit in that car.
I'm sorry. They told me to sit in this car.
I don't want to sit in that car.
- Why? Then what? You're going to take a taxi there?
- I'll just take a taxi.
Why are you taking a taxi? This is also my first time meeting him.
Later on, if there is an awkward silence, we can still chat with each other. Otherwise, it'll be so awkward!
Yeah! Be good, go on!
- We're family, no need to be scared!
- Go!
Didn't he say that he didn't have any plans to get a girlfriend?
You sit in the back, I'll sit in the front!
Fool. How is he not planning to have a girlfriend?
It's obvious he just doesn't want to deal with you.
Excuse me, your jacket...
Move over!
Understand?
I've gone to matchmaking so many times, met so many men,
but this is the one with the least amount of manners.
Sit tight.
I think we are all adults. It would be better if we were more frank.
Then, I'll introduce myself first.
I am in marketing. Mainly in charge of brand management.
What do you do?
I don't have any decent work.
But you must have a profession.
I heard Aunt say that you are starting your own business.
Profession? Does playing on the computer count?
Playing on the computer?
So, you're someone with no real job who lives off his parents.
I see.
Actually... Actually, his work is a respectable profession.
Playing on the computer can count as a respectable profession?
They are cybersecurity talents. They even win medals at competitions.
It is a new area that is encouraged by the government.
And if they win, they can earn prize money. A lot of prize money.
But they don't do it just for the money, they do it for the honor.
Actually in China, a lot of the internet technologies are at the forefront.
They've received many medals.
Well, there can't be people who spend their whole life playing on the computer!
Are we here? Why are we parking on the side of the road?
I think it will be better if we make things clear.
I don't have any interest in you.
In the future, I, for sure, will have no interest in you either.
Of course, you have no interest in people like me as well.
We are all grown adults.
Let's cooperate with our elders and finish this meal. What do you think?
Also, you don't need to act like you don't know me.
Are you not tired from acting?
What's happening here?
Nian Nian, you two know each other?
- We just met, not long ago.
- Didn't he just come back from overseas?
You are always at school and not yet working.
How did you two meet each other?
It's... at the internet cafe.
Online friend?
No. I met him at your family's internet cafe.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, about what?
Something fishy is going on here.
We've finally arrived. That was too stuffy.
- This place doesn't look bad.
- Yuejiao.
- How was it?
- Don't even mention it. He is so arrogant.
I just don't get it. He doesn't have a real job.
But yet, he has a sense of superiority.
How would it be like this?
Let me tell you. When we are eating later, just go through the motions.
It's New Year's. Please, don't make the elderly upset.
- I understand, Mom.
- In a bit when we're about done, bring these two things...
- I think they know each other.
- They?
Do you know?
- If there is anything, contact me anytime.
- I've troubled you.
I think they do.
Let's go in first. Everyone is waiting.
[South Wu Grand Feast]
Why aren't you going in?
I saw that they already went in.
I wanted to wait for you. This way is more courteous.
I am not interested in your cousin.
It would be best if she doesn't develop an interest in me.
So, what you said in the car,
is actually helping me in the wrong way.
I do not need an outsider to understand what my profession is like.
Especially someone who I will not have contact with in the future.
Therefore, there is no need to explain anything to her.
Do you understand?
Also, the reason why I exposed the fact that we knew each other is not to make you look bad.
It's because this is a lie that cannot continue on.
My cousin is coming soon. He knows you.
Plus, he would definitely be honest.
So, there is no reason for us to pretend we are strangers.
Do you understand?
I understand. We are not strangers.
Are you feeling better inside?
Let's go in.
Come, come. Come here.
What is it, Aunt?
Let me ask you. You know Han Shangyan?
What kind of person is he?
I've only known him for a week.
I only know that he is very good at the computer.
I just want to know about his character. Does he really not engage in proper work?
Or is he pretending?
Being good at computers doesn't mean improper work, right?
Then, do you think that he and your sister...
Aunt, my phone is vibrating.
A phone call. My classmate called, I'm going to pick it up.
Yaya! Yes. I'm having dinner with my family.
Today, sure. After I finished...
Yes, yes. You can speak...
Oh, so that's the situation. Is it okay if I give it to you after I go home?
It is not very convenient right now.
Little Bai, come here. Come here.
- Little Bai. This is my grandson from my daughter.
- Oh, so this is who you were just talking about.
- Yes, yes, yes. Wu Bai.
- Wow, he's grown so much.
So attractive. Do you have a girlfriend?
Not yet. We were waiting for you to introduce you to someone.
This is the present that he got for you.
Thank you.
I will put them here for you.
- Thank you!
- Thank you! You are too polite.
Sit.
What's happening?
- Her?
- You're already a grown woman.
What is the girl that likes you doing here?
- We are family friends,
- ...his temper is not good.
Grandpa wants to match you up with her.
Are you joking?
I already said. When Grandpa comes back, nothing good will come of it.
Well, even if there was a match to be made, it's for you. What does this have to do with me?
I did get matched. It was quickly taken care of.
Your problem... Take care of it on your own.
I can't help you.
Nian Nian, come here.
Come here. I will introduce you.
I forgot to introduce you earlier.
This is my grandson, Wu Bai. This is Nian Nian.
Your parents saw him when he was still little.
Go, go! You two go sit over there!
Go over there!
You two, talk more.
My grandson is also studying computers.
Yeah, Nian Nian, you two are in the same major.
You guys must have a lot to talk about.
Say hello to her.
I know her.
You two know each other?
I think she is...
my brother's girlfriend.
Little Bai, what nonsense are you saying?
Wait, no, no. Stop, stop.
I will not listen to him. I want to hear from you. Little Bai, you tell us.
I don't know the details,
but all our club members call her "Sister-in-Law."
Sister-in-Law?
No, no.
Nian Nian, aren't you going to explain what's going on?
Nian Nian, come here.
Come here.
What's going on? Why do you suddenly have a boyfriend that we don't even know of?
- I don't know either. He really isn't. That is not the situation.
- Explain it clearly.
Auntie, you might as well listen to me explain.
Don't talk. You shut up.
If you say more, I'll break your leg!
Grandpa, please don't be mad. Nian Nian also feels wronged.
Do you know what is going on in the middle of all this?
Dounan, when did your sis get a boyfriend?
I don't know the specifics... but my sis does like him.
You're saying nonsense!
I'm speaking the truth. Didn't you fall in love at first sight with him?
Stop talking about it, can you?
Dounan!
However, I really don't know when they got so close.
I suppose it was when they were in Guangzhou.
You, shut up!
That's enough. Why don't you sit down?
Our family is open-minded. Dating is not a bad thing.
Little Han, isn't it better to be open?
- Am I right, Brother?
- Aunt, you guys really all misunderstood.
- He and I really aren't...
- Please do not interrupt when grown-ups are speaking.
Okay, okay, okay.
Grandpa Han, it's fine.
We are all grown adults, not kids.
Little Han, let's just consider this our formal meeting.
If you have time, come visit us often. All right?
Let me tell you. Mr. Han is very busy.
So don't trouble him, okay?
Actually, this should have been made clear early on.
Explain everything so that we all aren't wasting our efforts.
Isn't that so, Uncle Han?
Right.
Go give greetings to Uncle and Auntie.
Let's just say that this is the first official introduction.
Go over and give your greetings!
Old people are old.
If I do defy him, who knows what's going to happen?
And it's New Year's.
The elders here all think that I've taken advantage of a young lady
and not admitting to it.
Go!
Uncle. Auntie. Hello.
I am Han Shangyan.
Tong Nian and I have been together for only a short period of time.
I didn't get her permission,
so I didn't dare pay a visit rashly.
I hope Uncle and Auntie can forgive me.
Okay. We forgive you. It's fine.
Come on. Go sit.
- Grandpa Han.
- Okay, okay. Come here.
Today is New Year's Eve, let's all just be happy and merry, all right?
Right! Right!
If there is anything else, let's save it and talk about them next year. Okay?
Okay? Here.
Here, here, here.
Oh right. Let's all be happy today.
Everyone, let's raise our glasses. Okay?
Raise your glasses!
I hope your career goes smoothly.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Waitress!
- Waitress, bring the food!
- Yes, got it.
Let me tell you. If he wasn't from the Han family, I would've already...
- How much older is he than Nian Nian?
- Yeah.
- He really is quite a lot older than Nian Nian.
- Don't copy me!
Little Bai.
The headquarters called saying that they need to speak to you.
Why don't you reply to them? Come outside with me.
Stop eating. Come out.
Do you not want to live anymore?
Who told you to only sit and watch the show?
If the room weren't filled with outsiders, I'd have started a row with you.
- Didn't you accept it?
- Bull, how could I not?
It's New Year's Eve! Grandpa is getting old.
If something had happened, would you've taken responsibility then?
Well, it's Grandpa, too. He refused to believe anyone but a big tailed wolf like you. (T/N: liar)
Just this once. I won't let it go next time, you hear that.
Brother-in-Law.
I really did not think that you were still my brother-in-law in the end. We must be fated.
Do you have something to say?
Grandpa told you guys to go in and eat.
That temper...
It's really too much for Little Squid.
Time to eat.
Right now, those who are older tend to spoil their wives more.
You see, our Little Han, although he's always got a sour face,
he actually is very responsible.
And also, you see... Little Han's birthday is on February 14.
Nian Nian is March 20. Look how close they are.
Isn't that good? Right?
Uncle, here, have a drumstick.
Okay. Here.
Here, here. Little Bai.
Right, you. Come here.
Sit here.
- Sit. Take something to eat.
- Okay.
Han Shangyan! Just sit there.
Sit there!
Go over there.
Okay, eat.
It's New Year's. Let's be happier.
Why did you tell a lie?
My cousin has a girl that he likes.
So, he asked me to help him avoid this matchmaking at all costs.
It was a sticky situation. We had no other choice but to use this method.
After tonight, we can randomly find a reason to break up.
Not considerate, not gentle.
Not sharing a similar language to understand each other, too old.
Those are all valid reasons.
You can choose the reason for the breakup.
Sorry.
It's fine. It's for helping him, isn't it?
Han Shangyan, serve your girlfriend some food.
It's fine, Grandpa Han. It's okay.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
- Eat.
- Thank you.
It's... It's enough.
I can't eat that much.
Eat it slowly; you will eventually finish it.
Here, here, here. Give your girlfriend a drink. A drink.
Hurry!
Enough, enough. Enough, enough.
Drink it slowly.
Little Bai, after we finish eating, remember to pack up the rest to-go.
Little Han, you are not young anymore. Right?
- You sure have a large appetite.
- There's a young one at home.
You've divorced, and have a child?
No, no, that's not it.
It's his club's kid.
It's New Year's and he didn't go home. So, he's temporarily staying at our house.
Here. Eat.
[A Path Among the Clouds]
Take it slow, Grandpa. There is a step here.
Okay, good child.
Nian Nian, hurry and get in the car.
Oh right!
Let Nian Nian ride in my grandson's car.
Your car?
Her parents drove here.
You... say something.
Uncle. Auntie. Let Tong Nian ride my car.
Don't worry. I'll follow behind your car.
Right, allow it for my sake.
- Go, go.
- Get in the car.
Grandpa Han, let me help you. Be careful, the step is here.
Get in the car.
♫ I start to portray an unfamiliar me ♫
♫ Fathoming the untrue distance behind the words ♫
I want to ask you a question.
♫ I thought I possessed the acting skills to deceive everything ♫
Say what you have to say.
When are we breaking up?
Because we should set a time frame, right?
So that I can tell my parents.
When do you want to break up?
You haven't finished thinking about it?
How about... How about next month?
Breaking up during New Year's is too fast.
It's not really good.
How about this? You can decide.
Whenever you decide to break up, just notify me in advance.
Before we break up, you are still my girlfriend.
Whatever you want, just say it. I will do my best to make it happen.
I'll keep my word.
Go back. Your mom is waiting for you.
Then... I'll go now.
- See you.
- What were you guys talking about for such a long–
- Nothing.
Let's go. Let's go inside. Let's go.
Nian Nian is dating for the first time.
I don't want to denigrate her.
You're worrying for nothing. It's not like the final word.
I already told you before.
Girls being too pretty is dangerous.
If I knew it earlier, I should have her eat more and get fatter.
There's a sense of security if she's fatter.
There would still be time to lose weight before dating, too.
I'm telling you, that's during middle and high school. Now, Nian Nian is an adult.
If you make her fatter, she may have low self-esteem.
I mean, I dress her up so prettily every day.
Who knew she would find such a boyfriend.
You, let me tell you.
You are being biased, you know that?
Except for his age, there are no other bad things.
I see Nian Nian being so happy.
I don't know what I should say.
It's ready!
You, it's best you don't say anything.
Figure out what kind of person he is first.
Smell this. How's my cooking skill?
Okay, okay. Don't burn yourself.
- Do you want to have a taste?
- Hurry and go. Go.
- Go, go.
- I'll go do some work first.
Okay. Go.
Nian Nian, look what Dad made for you.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫