♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 2]
[Solo]
[SP Chinese Region Representative]
Captain.
Since it's so unfortunate, I will take my leave first.
- Old Han!
- Let's talk things out.
Little Mi has my phone number.
Give me a call before midnight tonight.
- Han Shangyan.
We are all bros!  What is there we cannot sit and discuss?
Old Han!
Little Mi, long time no see.
It's been ten years!
It is still you that understands me.
Sit. Let's talk business.
If you guys were going to come, you should have told me earlier.
I would have given him an immunization shot.
(T/N: give him a heads-up)
What's the use of telling him in advance?
There's no use! With his bad temper?
Tonight, I'll try and talk to him again.
You two have business matters?
- Yes.
- No.
We do have business matters.
What business is there to talk about with me?
The Summit Competition isn't here.
The two of us are...
here to get you to sign a contract with us.
You and Han Shangyan came to find me for the same thing?
Did he come because of this, too?
I already rejected him and I will reject yours, too.
I don't have the intention to make a comeback.
Don't waste your time and effort.
It's not just the two of us anymore.
Ai Qing has joined us as well.
Now, the three of us are all part of Team SP.
[Half a year ago]
Attention passengers on flight 7381 to Beijing.
Your flight is about to depart. Please proceed to gate 7 immediately. Thank you.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Long time no see.
I didn't expect you to agree with me and be Team SP's manager.
After retiring for two years and doing some work not related to CTF (Capture The Flag, a computer security competition where you protect your network and attack your opponent's),
although I have earned some money,
what I miss the most is still my days as a player.
Say. If we didn't part ways in the first place,
what would the world be like now?
The past cannot be changed.
It's pointless to think back too much.
You're right.
Those years, who wasn't paying attention to CTF because they worshipped Appledog Ai Qing?
What is your plan from here?
My plan is to first get Little Mi and Ou Qiang back.
So, you want to...
I want to lead them and relive our brilliant years.
Just like before, fighting hard every day for our honor.
♫ I am also afraid of one day falling down ♫
♫ Abandoning their dreams, anyone can do so ♫
♫ I’m afraid one day it’ll just be you and me ♫
- We are just missing you now!
- Just missing you now!
- Ai Qing signed already?
- Of course!
But I didn't tell her that I was coming to find you this time.
If you sign, she would be so happy! I want to surprise her.
Then, what about Han Shangyan? You know he's the boss of K&K?
We just had a competition, I know.
He came to discuss my comeback, and you also came to discuss my comeback.
How do you two expect me to be a good person?
The main point now is whether you are still interested or not.
Do you still want to make a comeback?
You are not young anymore.
For you, this could be your last chance.
I don't have that strength anymore.
It's been so many years.
That is not the main point!
The main point is whether you want to or not!
Do you want to make a comeback or not?
Do you want to win back the things we lost?
Do you want to become the world champion again?
Give me your cup!
I mean, what are you thinking right now? I just don't understand!
I understand what you mean now.
Now, tell me. Who will you follow?
I want to follow you.
Then that's it!
That year, it was you who led me when I started.
Solo, you were my first team captain.
I also want you to be my last team captain.
What?
I didn't think that you would ever say that.
Actually, these years I have really felt ashamed.
Thank you.
I know you're always in this circle.
In CTF, you are the best team captain.
Back then, when the industry was at its lowest, you were there.
Even now, you are still there.
I admire you.
Let's stop saying these sentimental things.
It's been ten years. It hasn't been easy for us to get together.
Raise our glasses!
- Come!
- Raise them up!
I bless you two. The future world champions!
Getting trophies until our hands are weak!
It is a must!
I'm so glad that you're finally back.
At the World Tournament in Singapore a few days ago,
if I knew you were leading Team K&K there,
I would have gone to Singapore to find you.
We are opponents. What is there to be happy about?
So how is it? We haven't seen each other in so long, are you doing well?
Talk business.
Once you're done, you can leave.
Okay. Let's talk business.
I'm basically done discussing with Little Mi.
The contract is also finalized; just missing his signature now.
And?
You came here to show off?
You know this. I have never shown off in front of you.
And I don't need to show off.
Because in my heart, you are always the brightest star.
Same with Little Mi.
It was his own choice to join SP.
He thinks that SP is more suited for him.
I will give him the best resources to train him,
and get him to return to a condition where he can compete as soon as possible.
If this was his own choice,
I will respect it.
You are giving up so quickly? That's not like you.
It is he who gave up on me, not I who gave up on him.
I will take good care of him.
It is best that you do as you say.
Or else, I will settle both my new and old debts with you.
He is also my brother.
(T/N: good friend)
You can leave.
What? You're really not going to give me some time so we can talk about some private matters?
The two of us do not have any private matters to discuss. See you in the competitions.
A few days ago, Ai Qing saw you in Singapore. She was very happy.
I got it.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
It's been ten years.
If some things were changed to you in the beginning,
you probably would've made the same decision as me.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Rest well.
We are Team Solo.
We are the national champions.
Let's invite our MVP member to speak a few words to everyone. How is that?
- Gun God, say something.
- Gun God.
Right, Gun God, tell us how you feel right now.
- Just tell us a little bit.
- Han Shangyan, say something.
In the two years and three months that have passed,
there have been wins and losses,
laughter and crying,
we've been questioned and gossiped about,
we've been criticized and blacklisted.
We never had to give explanations,
there was no need to explain.
Tonight's feast finally comes to an end.
Success and fame are blinding folly.
I am announcing that starting today,
I am formally withdrawing from Team Solo.
Also, I am formally retiring.
- Old Han!
- Gun God, what is your reason for retiring?
- Gun God.
- Han Shangyan!
- Gun God, say a few things.
- Why are you retiring?
- Old Han, what are you doing?
Please tell us.
♫ Among the lights of a city’s dawn ♫
♫ There’s always splendor falling ♫
♫ Imitators one after another ♫
♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
- Old Han, you shouldn't be so impulsive.
- Old Han, you should stay calm.
Han Shangyan!
Han Shangyan, don't be so impulsive!
What gives you the right to just leave without talking it over with us?
Why didn't you discuss this with us?
Please calm down. We just won the championship.
Things will get better and better.
Don't be so impulsive.
Don't be so impulsive and say you're retiring, can you?
Our team is called Team Solo!
Today, you are telling me we are losing a team member. Then what is the point of all this?
Also, the person that we are losing
once told me how great this world is!
- How much the future had for us to look forward to!
- Don't be impulsive, Han Shangyan.
What else do you want me to believe in?
Everyone, please let me say something.
Han Shangyan, you shouldn't be this impulsive.
We just won the championship inside just now.
Outside, there're a bunch of fans and also a bunch of reporters waiting for us.
Everything can wait until tonight's celebratory feast to discuss how we move forward.
- Yeah.
- Can we?
Old Han!
We will meet at the usual place tonight!
We already got the national champion.
Why are we giving up?
We can be the world champions.
Why can't we go all out for it?
Here, let me make a toast to everyone.
Let me say my farewell here.
I am going back home in a few days.
Little Mi, what are you up to? Why are you suddenly leaving, too?
Little Mi, don't join in the trouble.
I've... thought it over already.
Thought over what?
I've decided to retire.
Go back home and look after the convenience store for my mom. Isn't that great?
What are you adding into the trouble for?
You are so young. What is the hurry?
Little Mi, you shouldn't be impulsive.
I am not being impulsive, Captain.
You shouldn't copy Old Han!
I am doing it for myself.
Do you really think I only care about world champion?
What is the point of our team if it is missing a member?
You are just like a pile of messy mud on the floor.
Old Han, where have you been?
Why didn't you answer my call? I called you so many times! Why didn't you answer?
♫ So many times I wish I could leave ♫
- What are you doing?
- Let's talk things out!
♫ Trying to find the one that is me ♫
Get up. You get up!
♫ Nothing to hide, not be afraid ♫
Old Han, listen to me.
♫ You’re walking away, begging to me ♫
Are you all right?
Don't stop him! Let him hit me!
Look at the teammates around you!
Are you worthy of them?
Don't forget Solo's dream!
And your own dream: to be the world champion!
Don't speak to me about dreams.
- Old Han.
Old Han.
Be careful.
♫ I could leave ♫
- Han Shangyan!
Han Shangyan!
Morning.
This is your passport.
Also, the reward money.
Did you come here just to bring me money?
From now on, you cannot be any team's captain.
If you still want to participate professionally, you can only do so as an individual.
I admit that you have the talent to be a captain, but you've wronged every one of us.
You don't deserve it and you also don't have the qualifications to be a captain.
I don't deserve to be a captain.
In this lifetime, I won't be a captain.
Remember what you said.
I promise you.
♫ Trying to find the one that is me ♫
♫ Nothing to hide, not be afraid ♫
It's been so many years,
I still do not know how to forgive you.
Do you still remember the championship game from ten years ago?
Old Han, one decipher; it was an instantaneous kill.
He got that Buff so angry that he directly kicked the chair.
Thinking on it now, that was called satisfying.
Old Han.
♫ Today I saw snow ♫
♫ drifting through the cold night ♫
♫ With the cold heart, I drift off to faraway places ♫
♫ Chasing in the storm and fog, ♫
♫ I can’t tell the shadows apart ♫
♫ You and I in the vast sky ♫
♫ It may change but who doesn’t change ♫
It's been ten years.
One day of being brothers
is being brothers for life.
If you go to Shanghai in the future, if there's anything you need my help in, let me know anytime.
No need to be polite.
I am going now. I need to catch a flight.
You're going?
Why does this kid look familiar somehow?
Grandma, you forgot? That's my best bro, Little Han.
Yes. That's why he looks so familiar.
Did you pack everything?
Pretty much.
You are not young anymore.
Do some more reasonable things in the future.
Don't worry, Grandma. This time I'll definitely win a championship and come back.
All right, Grandma will wait for you.
What is it?
Seems like he didn't pay for the drinks.
We are brothers, why are you talking about that?
Please give me a computer.
- I'm off work. Go ask that guy.
- Hello, please show us your ID.
Elder cousin! I am ready; let's go.
Let's go eat breakfast. Go home and eat breakfast.
Sis, what is the matter?
(T/N: They are cousins, but in Asian culture, they still call each other by "brother" and "sister.")
It's free to use the internet and he still doesn't come.
Sis, I have to do something right now. You go back.
- I will look for you later.
- Give me the bag. / - That's right.
What are you up to?
- Why are you back?
- Something urgent.
- Bro.
- What is it?
Do you play that often?
Ah, yeah.
What... What kind of game is this?
Doesn't your family own an internet cafe? You don't know this?
I don't play games much.
Chamber Storm.
Then, how can I find out who recently played this game?
This... As long as you know their username, that's enough.
How would I know their username?
If you don't know, how would I know?
That's true.
Dad. Mom. I am back.
You are back.
Where is Dounan?
Why didn't he come back with you? Didn't he say he will be back together with you to eat?
Yeah, he originally said he would come back with me together.
I don't know why but he went back half-way.
I'll say, what's going with you these days? Always coming back so late.
Are you staying up all night with your younger cousin?
I need to help him watch the store. What can I do?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
He probably blocked me.
- Sis! Sis!
- What?
I have a way to find that person.
- Han Shangyan.
- Yes.
I pulled the store's surveillance video and I found the game he was playing.
Even a ghost knows that. Isn't it that "Chamber Storm?"
You are a game idiot. How do you know this?
In a little while, I am going to compete for the recording of the theme song.
But what is the point of knowing the name of the game? I still can't find him.
We can find him.
- We can find him?
- Yes.
- Is that for real?
- Absolutely true.
I can even borrow my friend's pro-level ID for you. We don't even need to register.
- All right, I'm not saying anymore. Let's go in. I'll help you.
- Not bad!
Dounan!
Look at this. Let's log in first.
Okay.
And then this is the password.
Log in.
"1 Dash of Handsome?"
(T/N: friend's username)
Ignore it, ignore it. Next, we need to invite a friend.
I will enter his game ID.
[Use your friend's ID to search for user]
[grunt]
Grunt?
No wonder his WeChat ID is Gn.
So he is called "Grunt." It's such a nice name.
- Grunt. Grunt.
- All right, all right.
Stop fangirling. This... This sounds like "roller."
(T/N: grunt and roller sound similar)
- That's enough. Pro-level people all use this kind of name.
- It sounds like he's cursing someone.
At least, it sounds better than your Hu Dounan. Hu Dounan. Hu Dounan.
Stop calling my name.
All right. Let's follow my friend's instructions. I will read it for you.
The W A S D is the forward, left, back and right. You try it.
Shoot with the mouse. Left-click.
When you start every round, you need to purchase a weapon.
If you win more in the previous round, you have to buy better weapons in the next round.
Anyway, the moves are not hard. You just need to practice them. There are no shortcuts.
You are so smart. You will get it soon. Practice makes perfect.
- That's true.
- Let's start with the invite.
All right.
[Send a friend request]
Wait a second! I am a little nervous.
Do you want to invite him or not?
[Send a friend request]
Then let's invite him.
Currently playing Chamber Storm: global operation.
Let me tell you. I am more relaxed that he didn't accept my invite.
Why is he still not finished?
I don't know.
[Grunt accepted 1 Dash of Handsome's friend request.]
Dounan! Hu Dounan!
Hurry! Look! Did he accept my invite?
Take a look! Is it right? Did he accept my invite?
- Don't be nervous.
- I am not nervous.
When we go in later, you have to calmly say hi to him. Okay?
I am calm. Calm.
- What should we do now?
- Let's send him an invite first.
Okay.
Yes, here.
Did he accept it? Did he accept it?
- Crap!
- What happened?
He chose the opponent team. You won't be able to see him.
What should I do then? I want to see him! I want to see him!
You will only be able to see him if you use the public chat or if you bump into him in the game.
- Bumping into him in the game is fine, too.
- Don't be so worried yet.
Even though he is your rival, you can still greet him, right?
- Friendship comes first, competition comes after.
- Okay.
- What should I do?
Do you still remember what I taught you just now?
Here. These four keys: forward, backward, left and right.
Yes, and then...
You... the mouse! Use the mouse to fight!
The person just now already passed!
I... hit him, hit him! He won't die!
Why are you shaking yourself?
- How do I do this?
- Do you know how to play?
- I...
- Go forward!
- Why are you yelling at me?
- I'll do it! I'll do it!
Move forward, move forward. Here!
The rival! The rival!
Hit him! Hit him! Hit!
Aim for the head! Aim for the head!
I...
Hit him!
Did I die?
I... I think so.
- You made me die?
- I've been helping you all along!
- You... You...
- You helped me die!
I helped... I have been helping you! If you hadn't kept on moving the mouse...
- If you hadn't moved around randomly, how would you have died?
- It's all your fault! It's all your fault!
- Why are you blaming me again?
- It is because of you!
Why are you blaming me?
So annoying. I haven't even seen him and I already died.
- Grunt, where is your passport?
- Let me just finish this round.
- Remember to give it to me later.
- Okay.
Such noobs. It's no fun.
It's vacation time. There are a lot of newbies.
Demo! Play a round for me.
I will go get the passport for the manager.
Where is Boss?
He is taking a nap. He just got back and he is already in a bad mood.
The other day, I kept hearing his notifications from WeChat.
I thought he never used WeChat to chat?
What happened? Is he dating?
That day, a small internet cafe added him on WeChat and kept sending him advertisements.
I told him I could help him block it, but he wouldn't let me.
He went offline. Did he leave?
He needs to rest, too. Right? You can use this time to look at strategy guides.
When you play together next time, you won't be as silly.
This game seems pretty easy to me anyway.
See, there are just those four keys, the mouse, and the space bar. How hard can it be? It's really easy.
Hu Dounan, can you let me be alone for a bit?
- Okay.
- Thank you. I am grateful.
You are welcome.
That night at the internet cafe was the first time I met Han Shangyan.
I thought he was a big geek who liked to go on the internet,
and just happened to want to play at the internet cafe for a bit that day.
It wasn't until later on that I found out...
everything I thought was wrong.
- Old Han, don't attack so ferociously.
- The pressure from Ai Qing worked.
Infiltrated.
- Old Han, you...
- Nice!
Your condition is good.
If it's about module attack, I only believe in Old Han.
Old Han is getting stronger and stronger.
Old Han, I was the only one who believed in you since the beginning.
- Well done.
- Little Mi, don't mess up now.
Go, go, go. Little Mi!
- Little Mi, go through with our original plan, the one I told you earlier.
- I'm going to kill him!
Ou Qiang, block the opening.
- We infiltrated!
- Yes!
That day, he went to the internet cafe at midnight.
Perhaps, he is online now?
Online!
[Creating Game Room]
[Please wait...]
[1 Dash of Handsome]
[grunt]
Can I play with you? Can we not be opponents?
Okay.
Yes!
There are so many.
This one looks good.
Up, down.
The one with the double gun, why are you following Grunt?
Why are you bumping into the wall? Is your mouse broken?
Is the person in front of me Grunt?
[Please do not share your password with anyone.]
Hello.
[1 Dash of Handsome said: Hello Grunt]
[Press Shift+0 to reply]
He replied back. But why is his response "..."?
Let me send him a few more messages.
- Hello, Grunt.
- Is this your first time playing games?
No, that's not it. We met in the afternoon, do you remember?
"W", "A", "D", "S", forward, backward, left, and right; shooting with the mouse; I know them all.
After the round in the afternoon, I went back to look at the strategy guides. I even practiced with the computer multiple times.
I will protect you.
Why are all his replies to me "..."?
Did I say anything wrong?
Where did you go that you only just got back?
You are very weird. It's been a long time since I've seen you go online to play games.
What happened today? Venting because you are in a bad mood?
I play once in a while.
Do you know this person?
No, I don't. Just a kid.
It's a pro-level account.
He is probably secretly using someone else's account in the family.
I've also encountered this kind of situation before. Just try to play along.
I have already seen two stolen accounts this week. Is this another one?
It's so late at night. Account stealing thief, don't you need to sleep?
Little kid, let me save you this once.
Not a stolen account. Some kid in the family is using the account; just do your best.
Then, isn't this 4 vs. 5 now?
We have Grunt, we won't lose.
Do you see the door ahead?
Yes, I can see it clearly. My monitor is especially good, I guarantee it won't lag.
Hide there, until the game ends.
Why don't you register for an account instead of always using Grunt's?
If I register, what would you guys do?
I am going to shower first; start a round for me.
Right, that 1 Dash of Handsome, remember to add him for me.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫