♫ Characters that no one asks after ♫
♫ Who do you choose to worship, who to resent? ♫
♫ The desolation after the feigned passion ♫
♫ Pretending to be the shackle of freedom ♫
♫ What did you become at the end? ♫
♫ The smoke and fire that ignited glamour ♫
♫ One burst forth is enough, what else is there to seek? ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Who didn’t do their utmost and walk to life’s final stage? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Perhaps I’ll never become your radiance ♫
♫ A nameless person, who am I? ♫
♫ Who was forgotten? It matters no more ♫
♫ Continue chasing, whose glory isn’t accompanied with tears? ♫
♫ Perhaps very tiresome, in an entirely pathetic state ♫
♫ Perhaps lowly with nothing to show for my life ♫
♫ Who isn’t born the same way, don’t hesitate to call me a nameless person ♫
[Go Go Squid!]
[Episode 4]
Everyone, quiet! Quiet, please.
Sister-in-Law, here.
- Who is the sister-in-law?
Here, here.
How come there is a sister-in-law?
Sister-in-Law.
Sister-in-Law, get in the car.
Thank you.
Brothers, this is Sister-in-Law.
- Hello, Sister-in-Law.
Hello, Sister-in-Law. Nice to meet you.
Can you tell them not to call me "Sister-in-Law"? Everyone mistook me.
No problem.
That... Sister-in-Law said for everyone not to call her "Sister-in-Law" anymore, she is embarrassed.
All right, Sister-in-Law.
"Sister-in-Law," got it!
Sister-in-Law, take a seat.
Thank you.
- Sister-in-Law, I put your suitcase here.
- Thank you. Thank you. Give it to me.
DT! DT! DT!
When will your boss get in the car?
- Wait a little bit more.
- Fine.
Captain, when did your brother get a girlfriend?
Doesn't he live at the club 24 hours?
- I don't know.
- Advancing secretly...
The boss does have it together, playing this kind of game with us.
He is afraid that we'll copy him, get a girlfriend, and interfere with the competitions.
He is not young anymore; dating is a normal necessity.
The Boss is getting old.
How is he getting old? Clearly he's drop-dead gorgeous.
Compared to these tender youths, he is much more manly.
Everyone, after we get back to the hotel, go to the first-floor buffet dining hall first.
I reserved a couple of big tables.
Watch yourself. Don't eat any raw cold seafood.
You saw Grunt, how he messed up his body by doing so.
It's competition season. You have to pay more attention to your health, understand?
Understood, Manager!
Sir, you can drive them back first. Boss and I will go back ourselves.
All right.
Moreover, you guys have to take good care of her.
- Don't worry.
Bye!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Let's talk about business first and anything else later.
Everyone, sit down first.
Tomorrow is when both of our teams will compete with each other.
Then, we will all do our best.
Both sides do their best but there is only one champion. Who gets it?
I'm the last? I'm really sorry.
Both of your teams have too many fans.
I have to make sure they get out safely before I can leave.
Stop the nonsense, let's talk business.
There's no business matter. Today is about old friends getting together.
Isn't it nice to have lunch together?
- You have nothing else to do?
- That...
It's not like that.
Do you have something important to announce or not?
Eating is very important, Old Han.
I know a very good restaurant in Guangzhou.
I'm leaving.
Old Han, you're not giving me some respect?
You still have to eat after you go to the hotel. Even if it's not to accompany your brother, at least have a chat with me.
Forget it.
I reserved a 12-people private room.
Now, there's only three of us. Does it make sense?
Forget it, Director Xiang.
It will be a waste for only three of us eating.
Save it for the next time we go. Goodbye.
- I called for a car. I figure there is traffic on the road. Wait a little.
- Director Xiang still doesn't know Han Shangyan's temperament.
We have a car.
Since we happen to stay at the same hotel, why don't we go back together?
No, thank you. We called for a car already.
Don't be upset about little things.
It's us who won the competition today.
I just didn't expect there would be such a day.
We have all succeeded, became wealthy, but it's so hard to get in one car together.
Sorry.
It's all my fault. I ruined you guys.
I didn't mean to blame you.
[10 years ago]
Every teammate, look what I got for you?
Red envelopes!
- May you be prosperous and happy!
- Red envelope come to me!
Thank you, Captain!
Although this is the first championship we've gotten since the creation of Team Solo,
even though it's only the Beijing championship, it's already very impressive!
Isn't it still all your credit? It's because you led the team well.
You prepared for us so much data on the opponent, so that it was so easy to take down the championship title.
- Yes!
- That's right!
Those things are all that I should be doing.
Han Shangyan, did you know that in the CTF circle, you have now quite the reputation.
(Capture The Flag, a computer security competition where you protect your network and attack your opponent's)
All the internet talents consider Han Shangyan as their number one opponent.
You're truly now everyone's idol.
- Idol!
That's because I have you all as my brothers and sisters.
Just wait until we're more and more coordinated, and then we'll win tens, hundreds of championships.
- Yes!
- That's right!
Don't say those things. How can there not be liquor at a time like this?
- Little Mi!
Little Mi, you really know.
Here, here, here!
You actually prepared liquor secretly.
Nice!
Come on! Let's have a toast to the future world champions!
- World champions!
- Cheers!
They're so cheerful!
Shush!
I apologize, Uncle and Auntie, for the disruption.
- Good job! Good job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- World champions. World champions.
- Little Mi, nice job on preparing the liquor today.
Really nice job!
- It's the Tiananmen.
- That's right!
(T/N: Once the entrance to the Forbidden City; Tiananmen, or the Gate of Heavenly Peace, is a gate in the center of Beijing and a national symbol of China)
- Tiananmen! It really is the Tiananmen!
- Tiananmen!
Did you know that every time I see the Tiananmen, I'm filled with deep respect?
I feel that we should win glory for our country. Let's step on the world's stage soon.
That's right!
Old Han, it's Tiananmen.
Come! Cheers to the world champions!
Come, come, Sister-in-Law.
Please, please, Sister-in-Law, this way.
Come, come! You sit here.
Please take a seat, Sister-in-Law. Please sit.
Careful, careful.
Sister-in-Law, you haven't officially met us yet.
- My name is 97, I was born in 1997.
- Hello.
My name is Demo, they all say I'm adorkable.
(Demo is similar in pronunciation with the Chinese term for adorkable)
Sister-in-Law, I'm One.
Why are you called One?
Because I'm the tallest, and the most handsome.
Today, the guy who was sitting behind me, tall and wearing a hat. Who is he?
Oh, his name is Wu Bai, our Boss's younger cousin. He's our captain.
He's the same as our boss; likes to be by himself. He's probably training by himself right now.
You guys, don't scare her.
- When did we do that?
- We're not. We're just chatting.
Follow me for a second. Han Shangyan is looking for you.
- Wait...
- Goodbye.
- Bye-bye.
- You're leaving?
Is Boss in such a hurry?
Bye-bye.
Is lust dominating thoughts?
Her aura is so strong. I am incomparable to her.
Are you full?
I just drank... drank some water. I am full already, not hungry.
Come in.
If there's something to discuss, why can't we speak in the dining hall?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Do you want me to talk about private matters in public areas?
Don't worry. He won't be mean to girls.
I'm going to take care of the other team members first.
Take your time talking.
I'll give you ten seconds to decide.
Can the two of you... tell the truth now?
How many times do I need to say this, Boss?
You are a big man. Can't you be straight forward?
Just stab me to death already.
- Do you know that he already has a girlfriend?
- I don't know.
Now that you know. What do you think?
No opinions.
Little sister, come over here. Let me tell you something.
Tell the truth. Why exactly did you seek me out for?
I wasn't looking for you.
It's fine for an autograph.
A photo together is fine, too. Give me any request.
Just tell the truth that the two of us have no relations at all.
Give me any request. As long as you don't want to be my girlfriend.
Who wants to be your girlfriend? I don't even like you.
What is the situation now?
Why isn't he saying anything?
Little Sister, let me ask you something.
Do... you know him?
Then, did you come to the competition because of him?
When you went to the competition site, was it also to look for him?
Y-Yes.
This is from your own love entanglement. Quack!
Trying to put the blame on me. Not possible.
Say that again. What blame?
No... that...
Little Sister, let me tell you. If you like him, just bravely say it out loud.
A man like him... Forget about having women around him, there aren't even female animals around him.
The dog that male security guard outside our area owns is even male.
This item of the highest quality, if you miss him now, you will regret it for life.
Anyways, the person I like is not Grunt. I like...
No...
I came to look for you.
The two of you still refuse to tell the truth, right?
- That is the truth!
Nothing for you here.
Get out.
All right. I am going then.
I am not talking to you.
It's him.
Received, Boss. Then... I'll get going.
Then.. you and the chick.. continue.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
You like me?
What? Am I misunderstanding?
- No.
- What do you like about me?
If you don't know how to answer...
All right, I'll ask in another way.
What's there to like about me?
I saw you at the airport. Saw you and a group of people wearing uniforms.
I was very surprised.
Later my friend told me there was a competition.
So I thought if you guys were in the competition, I just thought to come and see you.
About the Grunt matter, I thought you were Grunt.
I thought you were having gastric bleeding, so I just wanted to see if you were all right.
I-I didn't mean to disturb you. I am sorry.
What are you afraid of? Am I that mean?
Your phone.
It's mine!
Can I borrow your bathroom for a little bit?
I have a very important phone call. Is it okay?
Thanks.
- Hello, how are you?
- Hello! Hello!
This is the 1-2-3 Communication Radio Station. I am the host, Hai Lukong.
How are you!
All right. All right.
Hello to all the audience.
This is the 1-2-3 Communication Radio Station.
We're connected to someone highly popular on the internet here; she has a several hundred thousand fan base.
Network Singer, Little Squid. (T/N: network singers are those who primary sing and upload original or cover songs online)
Let's ask Little Squid,
what lead you to start uploading your songs online in the beginning?
Mainly because it's something I enjoy doing. It is something I am very interested in.
What kind of songs do you usually perform?
I like to sing cute, cartoon, anime, and high-pitch songs.
Normally, what colors do you like?
I normally like the color white.
What kind of fruits do you eat?
I like several different kinds of fruits.
Such as apples and cherries; I like them very much.
May I ask... do you have a boyfriend?
I currently don't have a boyfriend. I am still single.
No boyfriend. Then may I ask...
what types of boys you like?
Handsome.
When he is not talking, he is cold and grim;
but once he smiles, he is very warm.
That is my ideal type.
All right, thank you so much for your interview today.
While we listen to the last song, I hope you can wish our audience a good afternoon.
All right. Then I hope everyone has a good afternoon.
- See you next time!
- Okay!
Thank you. See you soon.
Goodbye, everyone.
- Are you done?
- I am done.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I disturbed you.
Are you hungry?
Let's go and eat.
The club will be training soon. In twenty minutes, there won't be anything to eat.
I... I actually don't need to eat.
You don't need to invite me...
What is your name?
Tong Nian.
Close the door.
Not right... why are we eating together?
Forget it. We'll see when we get there.
Do you want to eat some?
You don't like this flavor?
Then pick one yourself.
B-Boss.
Have I... interrupted you guys?
Going in and out, what are you doing? Do you need to go up or down?
Down, down, down! Up, up.
I just need to go get something.
You didn't even ask whether we needed to get off.
Sorry, Boss. I didn't know you guys needed to get off.
Do you want to choose one or not?
Is he not afraid of being misunderstood?
This one. Thank you.
After seeing what I shouldn't see, will I be killed to be silenced?
Boss, I'm here!
S-Sorry. You guys can go down.
After being seen by Demo the bigmouth, this misunderstanding is going to be huge.
Let's go.
That's Sister-in-Law?
Go get food yourself.
Sister-in-Law is so young!
If you don't have feelings for her, why did you bring her for dinner?
I brought the kid here without figuring out the situation, so I bear some responsibility, too.
Even when the deal fell through, the relationship is still there. I will send her back when she has eaten.
Not bad. You're quite a gentleman!
You guys eat first, I'll get the car.
What do you think they went to do?
- Why are you finally here when we're almost finished?
- I ran into Boss!
His mood is pretty bad.
What's wrong with Boss?
When he eats candy, it means that he is super impatient and has a ton of things on his mind.
Just now in the elevator, he ate some.
- Scared me to death.
- Do you think they had an argument?
I don't know!
Anyways, the whole time I was sweating.
I was scared that Boss would toss me out from the elevator.
You're so useless, really!
If I eat shellfish, then wouldn't I have to open my mouth really wide?
If I eat shrimp,
when I'm done peeling the shell, my fingernails will be dirty.
Crab legs.
How will I eat the meat? The shell is too hard.
I'll just have some cake.
Will he think that I really love to eat sweets and think that I am really fat?
No way. I'll just eat some small snacks.
If I eat these, will it make my teeth black?
What should I eat?
That's all you're eating?
I don't have a big appetite in the evenings, I only eat a little.
She's still afraid of me.
The lot of you, send two people over here.
Who is he calling for?
Boss, who are you calling?
It's you then.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
What's wrong, Boss?
Are you full?
- I'm not full yet.
- Wait, wait!
- We're basically full, just waiting for training.
- If you're full then sit down, be a chat companion.
Chat companion?
Chat companion! Chat, chat, chat.
Chat companion.
Sister-in-Law.
"Sister-in-Law"?
Not call "Sister-in-Law"... then call... call Sister-in-Law... then... then I'll call...
Then, what's your name, Sister-in-Law?
Just call me Tong Nian. Tong Nian.
Childhood? What a great name!
(T/N: her name sounds like the word "childhood")
♪ On the banyan tree by the pond, ♪
(Chinese song titled "Tong Nian" = Childhood.)
♪ Cicadas are calling for summer ♪
Tong Sister-in-Law, what a great sounding name!
- Sister-in-Law, your outfit looks so good! It says "Hello" on it.
- Hi.
You're so pretty! Eat some more, Sister-in-Law!
- You're so slim!
- Your physique is great. You don't need to lose weight, eat some more!
Yeah!
Tong Sister-in-Law, what have you been doing lately?
Yeah, what do you do?
Me? I... guess I am considered a network singer.
- This I know!
- Really?
- My classmate from before was one, too. It is very popular nowadays.
- Sister-in-Law, where can I search for your songs?
- Yeah.
You guys can go to NetEase Music and search Little Squid. That's my name.
- Hurry and look it up!
- Search.
Boss, are you searching for it, too?
[Mailbox]
- That...
- Oh my God!
- What? What? What?
- Look yourself.
Holy! A NetEase artist. So many fans!
[Fans: 1,262,000]
Right? She has way more than us.
She is a verified user on Weibo, too!
(T/N: Chinese social media)
She's on Baidu Baike, too.
(T/N: Online encyclopedia)
Nice! Boss has got game!
[Little Squid, Network Singer Popularity Ranking: 4]
When our boss doesn't show his hand, it's nothing; but when he does, he snatches a gold-lined adorable girl.
Our boss is eating so calmly.
He doesn't even give Sister-in-Law a look!
Look! Sister-in-Law keeps staring at Boss.
Say, if I get Sister-in-Law to add me on Weibo, would I get more fans?
You ask, you ask!
That... Sister-in-Law!
Tong Sister-in-Law, I saw in your personal information that
you are majoring in bioengineering and electrical engineering.
Then, did you just start university?
Those are my double-majored Bachelor's degrees.
- I'm a graduate student right now.
- Double-major?!
Then, when did you start university?
- When I was fifteen.
- Fifteen?!
How come when I was fifteen I hadn't even graduated from junior high school...
Because universities have junior classes.
- Top student!
(T/N: literally means scholar tyrant)
- Sister-in-Law, it's my dream to meet a female top student. Can you arrange it?
- What do you mean?
Introduce one to me!
I can introduce one to you, that's not a problem. But they are all very focused on studying, so...
- Sister-in-Law! You must be great at gaming!
- Yeah!
I am terrible at games, I don't know it at all.
How could that be? Boss has never played games with you?
Yeah! Boss?
I cannot say that I played games with Grunt; otherwise, the misunderstanding will be bigger...
No, I haven't played at all.
Then, you can come to our team!
- Yeah!
- We can all teach you!
If you're done eating, then go. The driver is waiting at the entrance.
And you two...
From now on, you are not allowed to call her "Sister-in-Law" in the future.
- Boss, don't be mad. Boss, e-eat some more!
- Boss.
- Then, we will leave first.
- Then...
Then you should eat some more!
- You didn't even eat anything!
- You–
Sir! Send her to...
Where do you live?
The White Swan.
White Swan Hotel.
Okay!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Say it. I am listening.
Okay.
Did I make him think that I was really annoying?
♫ So that I can be in your world, slowly walking closer ♫
This time when I leave, will we never see each other again?
♫ Attempt to use unfamiliarity to explain the distance between us ♫
How could he not even look back once for me?
♫ Fathoming the untrue distance behind the words ♫
♫ I thought I possessed the acting skills to hide everything ♫
Why is my first love so painful?
♫ But no matter how much I practiced, I can't act like myself ♫
♫ The me who doesn't care about you ♫
I thought that Boss was using his legendary professional experience to attract Sister-in-Law's young heart.
Is that not the case?
Other than writing programs, the Big Devil doesn't have any other skills to show, right?
He spends 25 hours a day at the club abusing us.
He clearly doesn't have time to go on dates.
How did he get such an adorable chick?
Maybe she doesn't like going out on dates and only enjoys going to the library 25/7.
Plus, she went to university at fifteen; she's a super top student.
Maybe she purely likes spiritual love and attractions in personality?
Personality? You're talking about Boss' personality?
Who can he attract? Voldemort?
(T/N: Villain in Harry Potter novel)
Captain, is he not your brother?
- Don't you know any insider gossip?
- Yeah!
You want to know?
Go ask him then!
Just tell us!
You are not practicing hard. What are you chatting about?
- No, no.
- We aren't chatting about anything!
- I... I'm–
- Training!
Training.
Come out for a second. I have something to tell you.
I was scared to death.
What?
Grandpa wanted you to give him a call.
Give me your phone.
Why are you using my cell phone?
I will give it back to you later.
I can't let him know my domestic phone number; otherwise, it'll be too troublesome.
Hello? Little Bai?
Hello, it's me.
Han Shangyan! You brat, immediately book an airplane ticket back home!
You're already thirty and still playing with computers.
Don't you want to get married? Don't you want kids?
How embarrassing for me when I tell others that you're at this age and still playing with computers?
Back then, your dad left you some money. You took it all to start your club.
You might've forgotten, but I haven't!
Look, our Little Bai is so good, and yet you always bring him out everywhere!
Are you listening?
I'm listening.
You angered me so much that my hands are shaking, I can't even hold my phone!
Then you should hang up quickly, don't let the anger harm your health.
Han Shangyan! That's okay.
I knew that you wouldn't buy a plane ticket for me.
The day after tomorrow, I will arrive at the airport in the morning. You come and pick me up.
You are already old, and you still want to take long flights?
Once we become less busy, Little Bai and I will come back and see you, is that not good enough?
It is because I am old that if I don't come back now, it really won't be fine.
This time, I'm going to meet up with some old friends. At the same time, I can arrange to find you a wife.
Don't talk back! You don't have a right to talk back.
If you can't accept this, then immediately scram back.
As your grandpa, I have the duty to raise you and to not let you go astray;
in that respect, I have failed.
You... from when you were young until now your actions have disappointed me.
And you, my grandson, have only one duty
and that is to give me a proper great-granddaughter.
I couldn't tell that you like girls more than boys.
Get out! Stop joking around with me!
I forgot to say goodbye.
Yeah, how could I have forgotten?
K&K is one of the top two cyber clubs in China.
Founder and top investor, Gun is a member of China's CTF Hall of Fame.
Han Shangyan used to be part of the most famous Team Solo in CTF.
He was the first investor and major player.
He was also the champion in more than ten national competitions.
He possesses many individual world rankings:
most sabotaged servers, most cracked encryptions and numerous nominations for MVP.
He has hundreds of thousands of fans globally and his own website.
Plus, his fans named keyboards, mice, and other computer accessories after him.
In the past, he used his records and brilliance to change the public's view on CTF.
At the same time, he used his legendary professional experience
to bear witness to China CTF's progress from nonexistence to prosperity.
Yet just as Team Solo won the CTF National Championship,
he suddenly announced his retirement.
Announced his retirement?
Since Gun's retirement, China's CTF has fallen into it's cold winter season.
Now, he has low-key returned as a top club's founder.
He's so amazing! So amazing!
Lan Mei!
Lan Mei! It's me!
Are you free?
I'm free.
- Oh... I'm sorry.
- It's nothing!
- What are you doing?
- Sit, sit!
What's going on?
I have a few questions regarding CTF. Can I ask your husband?
You really are interested in CTF now?
You can't even play Liangliangkan Game.
(T/N: chinese pattern matching game)
This person! Do you guys know this person?
- Husband! Come over quick. Who is this?
- Coming.
- This person!
- This person, wait up.
Holy! Isn't this my Gun God?
He is the male god of my lifetime!
Today, it was only for him that I went to see the competition.
Have you guys seen the picture of him with his medals and trophy?
No, I haven't.
He was so handsome, no one could compare!
Ah yes, here! Let me show you!
There are videos of his legendary moments and exciting highlights of his competitions.
Reverse mining. This is my verifiable Gun God.
- Do you know what this is?
- I don't know.
This... Once a legendary moment appears in a competition,
the competition's organizer will draw a light halo around the competitor's country on the map.
Isn't Han Shangyan from China?
Look at this map. It represents China's honor.
Do you know? All the people in the world can see Gun God's three halos.
Say, isn't my idol super awesome?
Awesome. Very awesome!
Husband, I can't believe you chase stars (celebrities), too.
Of course. When it comes to my idol, even if I talked the whole night, it wouldn't be enough.
Tell me. What else do you want to know?
I want to ask about his dating experience.
Dating experience?
You want to hear gossip about him?
I want to hear them, too. He is such an amazing person.
His marks are even on the world map.
What type of girl does he like?
Hurry and tell us!
Let me think...
I'm not 100% sure about his dating experience.
Just that, back then, the CTF environment was really lacking in our country.
That time, Han Shangyan was the sole investor of Team Solo.
He was also a major player. This info is all on Baidu...
- How about this? I'll talk about stuff you can't find on Baidu.
- Okay.
Thinking back, Team Solo was at its peak when they suddenly disbanded.
People said it was because the team captain, Solo, had an illegitimate daughter.
Resulting in his and the team's main offense, Appledog's breakup.
And that was why the team disbanded.
And there were people who also said that Han Shangyan was the third party involved in the Team Captain's relationship,
that he fell in love with Appledog, so the team disbanded.
So which saying is true?
I don't know. That's an unresolved matter.
So, there's a possibility that the girl Han Shangyan used to like was Appledog.
Nobody can say for sure.
Were they ever together?
Of course not! If they were together, then the matter wouldn't be considered unresolved.
I have one more question.
Is Appledog pretty?
She's pretty! She is definitely a good match for my male god.
But the most important part isn't whether she is pretty,
it's that her professional experiences are at the Goddess level.
Go search Baidu Baike.
You can either search Appledog or her real name Ai Qing.
Back then, there were two main offenses on Team Solo.
[Baidu: Ai Qing]
One man and one woman. The man was my Gun God and the woman was Appledog.
[Ai Qing: Baidu it]
Then they were a match made in heaven.
(T/N: lit. golden boy and jade girl)
That's pretty much the meaning.
So, some people say that Han Shangyan created K&K Club now to get back together with Appledog.
Get her back?
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The 🍯 Honey Stewed 🐙 Squid Team @ Viki
Ripped & Resync By HiDeYuKi KaKaShI
Milk Bread by Yang Zi
♫ How was my heartbeat rattled by you? ♫
♫ I want to immediately move into your eyes as a dock ♫
♫ A strange love raises a storm ♫
♫ In the blink of an eye, our restraints were forgotten ♫
♫ Longing is a type of poison, it is difficult to give up ♫
♫ Once my mind is set that you are my only coordinate ♫
♫ How much more thoughts do I need ♫
♫ So I can monopolize your embrace? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ A couple made for each other. Once met, you’ll never be flung away ♫
♫ This kind of match has not too much, not too little, just sweet enough ♫
♫ Your smile is the exclusive recipe for happiness ♫
♫ Loving you is like milk loving bread ♫
♫ Sour-sweet and bitter-spicy are all love’s ingredients ♫
♫ Memories fermenting to bake a distinct flavor ♫
♫ Can you please be my support forever? ♫