[English subtitles are available]
I... I was just going to
turn off the lights for you.
He kissed me.
He's probably drunk.
His lips
are a little soft.
Just like my legs going weak.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 16]
It hurts.
Go to bed.
Stop playing video games.
You...
You're a bad boy.
It's been so long since
you played video games with me.
Look at those noob girls,
all of them have
boyfriends as their guide.
And me?
I can only
get beaten by their boyfriends.
Then, tomorrow,
I'll beat them up, OK?
Go to bed earlier tonight.
Just choose an assist for me.
Win a game with me,
and I'll go to bed immediately.
You said so yourself.
[What's with this assist?]
[He's rushed to the opposite
side to get killed again.]
[Did the boss give you a drumstick?]
He's scolding me again.
Just quit if you don't wish to play.
Don't scold girls.
[I'll quit.]
[Let's see how you'll guide
a female on your own.]
Don't, don't.
I'm dying.
We can't lose.
I don't want to lose stars.
I won't let it happen.
Go, go!
Kill, kill!
One more health point left. Hurry!
Give me five!
We won the game.
You can go to sleep now, right?
You're so good.
Not only you're good,
you're also capable
and cute.
In this world, no one else
treats me as good as you.
But you're so much younger than me,
and I still like you so.
I really,
really,
like you very much.
Are you serious,
or are you drunk?
If you'll also say this to me
when you're sober,
it'll be great.
I don't want to take advantage of you.
Tomorrow morning when you wake up,
you'll regret it.
I won't regret.
Ma Yi Yi,
why are you drinking on your own?
Where's Zeng Li?
She wrapped herself in a blanket
after coming back to our room.
That's probably what it
means by yearning for love.
After all, my sister
has never dated anyone before this.
Suddenly finding herself
caught in between two men.
It's understandable that
she's feeling a bit restless.
She's lacking in experience.
She needs more training.
Yu Yi, how are you feeling?
Yu Yi!
Tell me, where does it hurt?
Yu Yi
I don't dare to move you around.
You scared me.
Are you available now?
I need to talk to you.
I was going to talk to you.
Easy.
Are you kneading dough?
You're injured so badly,
yet you didn't even utter a word.
Do you enjoy the feeling of
shouldering the weight
of the world so much?
No.
I didn't feel anything
during the day.
Just now, after I came back to the hotel.
suddenly,
I couldn't even bend my waist.
And before I took a bath,
I saw it was quite serious.
There's only this safflower
oil in my backpack,
and I couldn't reach behind my back,
so I could only come to you.
Oh, right.
Make sure you don't tell Zeng Li
about this.
Why? You're scared she'll worry about you?
Of course.
It's normal to have
a little injury or two on an outing.
I don't want to make everyone else
feel bad.
Besides,
after that time,
I scared her with the
falling-into-lake prank,
she never went with me
on a boating trip since.
That's why,
this time, I don't want her to
get traumatized about me and skiing.
A little towards here.
That's right.
If you knew,
why did you tell that kind of joke?
I like to joke with her.
She's so cute.
Did you know?
She'll believe anything you say to her.
It's quite problematic actually.
She'll even cry if you scare her.
Easy, easy.
That's right.
Ask you something.
Do you think
Zeng Li likes me?
I don't know.
Tell me how you feel.
For the past few days,
how did you feel about it?
I didn't feel anything.
Have you finished applying?
I'm almost done.
Right, so be it.
What I mean is,
I can't tell.
True. Why did I ask you?
We're the same type of
straightforward men.
So,
did you ask her about it?
No.
Before, when I saw her
writing the novel,
I was sure she likes me,
because she remembers
everything that happened between us
by heart.
Later, I heard
she's never dated anyone else since,
so I thought
maybe she's waiting for me.
But this time after I came back,
when we spend time with
each other face-to-face,
I really didn't have the feeling,
because the way she looked at me
was like a friend.
Just like someone she could trust,
a youngest uncle
who she could depend on.
Here you go.
What she's thinking,
probably she herself
will know.
I know,
that's why I'm in no rush
to get an answer from her.
After all, we were apart
for so long.
I think
she should give it some serious thought.
Who am I
to her?
[You should give her some
time to think about it.]
You were looking for me just now?
It's fine now.
I'll go to the infirmary
to bring you some ointment.
Wait here.
Sure, let's have a match.
Mr. Ai,
he's so cocky.
Let's teach him a lesson.
Wu Ying,
time for breakfast.
Get up.
Give her a call.
She's not answering.
Did you hear her ringtone?
Yes.
Didn't you say you're
going to eat breakfast?
Why are you all standing here?
We're here to wake Wu Ying,
but we realized she will
neither open the door
nor is she answering her phone.
She had so many drinks yesterday.
Did she get alcohol intoxication?
Are you serious?
Will she be OK?
In that case,
I'll go and get the hotel staff.
Sure. You do that.
You're all here?
Good morning, Mr. Ai.
Good morning.
[As long as I don't find it embarrassing,]
[he'll be the one who's embarrassed.]
[She looks so calm.]
Mr. Ai, where's Liu Yu Cheng?
He didn't come back to
our room last night.
Could it be...
Liu Yu Cheng's inside?
Let me hear.
Don't push.
There's a sound.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Is Liu Yu Cheng inside?
Yes.
So,...
So, is everyone here?
Can we go and eat breakfast now?
He's still sleeping.
We're not going.
You guys go ahead.
Let's go.
As expected,
cats that catch mice don’t meow.
She's something.
You eat so little.
In this world,
the least stylish thing to do
is to post selfie on Moments
with the hotel's location.
Also,
turning breakfast buffet
into brunch buffet.
It's so strange.
What's so strange?
Aren't you two a little too quiet?
I remember in the past,
when you two meet each other,
you'll talk back to each other
as a way of showing respect.
Your older brother's tired today.
Why did you bring food for me?
Isn't... Isn't it your favourite?
I just helped to take it.
Where's mine?
You can eat mine.
You can have it as well.
I thought you took your own food.
Forget it.
I don't want food that's
handed out in contempt.
Eat your food.
Here, let me show you something good.
A girl you met recently?
How is it? Is she pretty?
Why does it feel like
she resembles Ma Yi Yi?
How so?
They look completely different.
Look, she obviously resembles her,
especially her eyes.
Oh, right.
Your ex-girlfriend,
Li Li, looked like this.
The previous ex,
and the one before that
also looked like this.
I realize the type of women you like
all look the same.
Go to hospital quickly
to cure your prosopagnosia.
Sure. Give me medical expenses.
Ask the person who gave you the disease.
What are you all talking about
so happily?
Why look at me?
[Seems like last night,]
[a lot of stuff happened.]
[Today, everyone]
[seems to be acting strangely.]
What's wrong?
About that...
I...
I booked spa session at 11 am.
It's almost time.
I'd better hurry.
You're going for spa?
What about me?
If you want to go,
you can join me.
I'm not going.
I'll stay in the hotel room.
That's fine.
Forget it.
It must be boring if you go alone.
I'll go with you.
OK.
Go and get changed.
Please take off your shirt,
and lie on the bed.
We'll come back in a while.
Sure, thank you.
[Why is she so calm about it,]
[as if nothing happened?]
Aren't you going to take off your shirt?
I'm not doing it.
Why?
I don't like taking off my clothes
and being touched by someone else.
I'll wait for you outside.
You're thirsty?
Deng Hao Ran,
can you act more naturally?
But I'm doing exactly that.
I...
If you don't know what to say,
just don't speak.
Don't look for things to say.
In that case...
What do you want to say? Just say it.
About what happened yesterday...
Yes... Yesterday...
Yesterday,
both of us were impulsive.
None of us should take it seriously.
This matter
is mainly my fault.
I'm unreliable.
I get ahead of myself easily.
Of course it's your fault.
Luckily I'm broad-minded.
I'll just treat it as
being kissed by a pig.
Who are you scolding a pig?
Whoever answering me.
Right back at you.
You're so childish.
[Many things are just a
thought during the moment.]
[Suddenly, you like someone,]
[and suddenly you think of letting go.]
[Certain people, after
turn around and walk away,]
[you'll never meet each other again.]
[But others,]
[if you can't be lovers,]
[and are no longer friends,]
[I'd rather remain on the same spot.]
[None of us should take
the first step forward.]
Please wait a moment.
I'll bring your shoes over.
OK. Thank you.
Are you hungry?
Shall we go and eat some food?
I have a question.
You have to answer me honestly.
Do you like me
or not?
Yes.
Which kind of like?
It feels like novelty.
Who do you take me for?
I'll like any man that I came across?
So, what am I to you?
Boyfriend.
What?
Boy...
So, I'm your boyfriend now?
What are you doing?
Are you thinking to do indecent stuff?
No.
What are you doing?
Put me...
Sorry.
I'll leave your shoes here.
OK, thank you.
Wu Ying,
it feels so unreal.
You won't go back on your words, right?
It's possible.
You can't.
You can't go back on your words,
nor do I accept bad rating,
much less return the goods.
What kind of forced
business transaction is this?
I'd also like to ask,
how many girlfriends you've had before me?
You should be my first,
second, third,
fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh...
Go away.
Deng Hao Ran,
arrange each of the luggages nicely.
I'm watching you all.
Why aren't you helping with the luggage?
I... This...
Thank you.
I'm watching you.
Do you have all your belongings?
Yes.
I have something to tell you all.
This
is my girlfriend.
What noise is that?
What's this?
What?
Am I hearing things?
My ears aren't working properly
since I'm getting old.
Liu Yu Cheng and Wu Ying
aren't here.
I'm also... I'm also leaving.
All I hear is people talking,
and dog's barking.
She's just jealous.
Can you let go of my hand now?
We've been holding hands for an hour.
No.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Move further in.
You already have a seat. Is it not enough?
You're too fat.
You... You're so fat. Come on.
Move.
No.
I'll sit at the back,
since I'm more petite than you.
I'm jumping. I'm jumping.
I'll leave the ambush to you.
I don't want to.
Ambush. Ambush.
I'm on it.
Stop battling.
Stop battling. You... You're going to...
Hurry, someone's coming.
Did you have a good sleep last night?
It was OK.
What about you?
I had a good sleep too.
Mr. Ai,
why don't we play Idiom Solitaire?
Sure.
I'll start.
"Eight Immortals Crossing the Sea."
"Boundless Oceans, Vast Skies."
"Superficial."
"Hypocrisy."
"Wholeheartedly."
"What's your intention?"
"Do whatever you want."
You... You're playing dirty.
I'll do the same too.
"Do whatever you want."
"Your head."
"Top-heavy."
"Hands-on."
"Do whatever you want."
Deng Hao Ran,
must you play this kind of prank on me?
[Face and body slimming]
Help!
I no longer look beautiful.
Show it to them.
Is this even human face?
Look at my yellow duckling t-shirt.
Isn't it cute?
It is,
but it makes you
such an easy target.
It's fine though.
You're in charge of attracting firepower.
I'll lay in ambush on the side.
I'll snipe if someone comes over.
OK.
Give me five.
Let's begin.
[Each of us,]
[starting from strangers,]
[over small little things,]
[because we're who we are,]
[we became]
[friends who have so much in common.]
[We're people who, when we're together,]
[we don't have to say a word]
[and yet it won't be awkward between us.]
[We'll]
[safeguard the
childish side of each other,]
[who can reduce each
other's sadness by half,]
[and increase happiness by many times.]
[We'll care for each other,]
[and cautiously]
[refrain from causing each other burden.]
[We'd often]
[play pranks on one another,]
[and also give each other]
[hugs when the other person is upset.]
[Someone once said,]
[whether the world likes you or not,]
[depends if your friends]
[like you or not.]
[If they do,]
[that means the world like you.]
♫ Sunset awakens the sea ♫
♫ I walk into your ocean-like eyes ♫
♫ You are watching as the waves retreat ♫
♫ I know you're waiting
for me to call your name ♫
[You all made me realize]
[good friends]
[means being together.]
[Shortly after bidding farewell]
[to my friends at the ski resort,]
[Lunar New Year arrived.]
[Good luck and prosperity]
[Me, Mother, and Yu Yi]
[went back to our hometown]
[to visit grandfather
and other relatives.]
[Always safe, smooth sailing year]
You
should just let your aunt nag for a while.
Just listen,
and don't talk back.
And it's settled.
After what happened that time,
she didn't talk to me for two months.
You also know
how your aunt is like.
Go quickly.
Go. Go ahead.
[Love side]
Go ahead.
Mother,
about what happened that time,
it's my fault.
So, does that mean after some time,
you're going to get another divorce?
What kind of child curse
their parents this way?
I have a mother
and three fathers.
Which one do you mean?
For the past decade or so,
I never saw you
as a burden.
Now, you're saying this to me?
Mother.
Mother,
today, I'm going to
formally apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
You must be hungry.
Come and eat some food.
Zeng Li,
I know that,
towards how I remarry
after getting a divorce,
only to divorce
and remarry again,
you've always held a grudge.
Especially
divorcing your Uncle Deng.
He's very good to you,
and it also took you a lot of time
before blending in with this family.
I admit,
before this,
I did have this idea.
But I think
it's actually very selfish.
Each person only gets
to live their life once.
We only have one lifetime.
You're able to
live your life by following your heart,
in fact, I should support your decision.
Mother,
do you think Uncle Peng
is your destination?
I think he is.
I also hope that he is.
So, Zeng Li,
what about your destination?
Brother.
Quickly. Come on, they're here.
They're here.
De Fang,
Xiao Li,
Xiao Yi,
-you're all here.
-Yes.
Your uncle
was pacing back and
forth inside the house.
When he heard you've arrived,
he quickly ran outside.
Go inside the house
quickly and take a seat.
-Come on.
-OK.
-Let's go.
You've gotten better.
-Let's go in and take some rest.
-You have everyone's seniority
-in the family memorized.
-OK.
Of course.
I did my homework this time.
Let's go.
Come on.
Cheers. Cheers.
Happy New Year.
Back then, Xiao Li
was still a teenager.
Her personality
wasn't as outgoing.
She was always so quiet.
When we
have reunion dinner,
she won't say a word.
If we ask her to address the seniors,
she couldn't recognize anyone.
She was so anxious, she almost cried.
Sorry, Third Cousin.
I was indeed still young at that time.
It's fine. It's fine.
I still remember,
your youngest uncle's too impressive.
He stood up
and told you to call him
"youngest uncle",
he gave you a red packet.
He even said to us,
it's Lunar New Year.
Xiao Li shouldn't do this for nothing.
If she did it, she'll be
given a red packet.
That red packet was at least this thick,
you know?
Really?
The red packet had so much money inside?
That was when I received scholarship
and I didn't know how to spend it.
So, I could only bring it here
and give everyone a red packet.
Give everyone?
But I only saw
you giving to Xiao Li alone.
Come and get your red packet.
Xiao Li,
quick, greet your youngest uncle.
He has all the red packets ready.
Come on.
The dumplings are here.
In future,
Xiao Li won't call
our Xiao Yi "Youngest Uncle".
Few years back,
when we told Yu Yi to come back to China,
he won't even listen to us.
But some time ago,
he saw you
writing an online novel,
and he just decided to come back.
Mother.
OK, OK.
Eat more, all of you.
There're some more in the kitchen.
Sure.
Sure, no problem.
Come on.
-Give these dumplings a try. Come on.
-Alright.
[Random amount RMB2,000, wishing my
family great health and happiness]
Yu Yi,
you're something.
You're giving out red packets
with such attractive sums.
Snatch the red packet quickly!
Snatch the red packet!
Wait. Give me a minute.
This is to pay for
what I owe you all before.
Next time,
don't make fun of me and Zeng Li.
Don't worry.
Come on, cheers.
Happy New Year.
Mother, Happy New Year.
Mother,
seriously.
Today, in front of everyone else,
why did you mention
what happened during my childhood?
It's nothing.
I haven't asked you yet.
How are things going between you two?
As a teacher yourself,
why are you so gossipy?
You're my son.
Can't I even ask you about it?
To be honest, about you
two dating each other,
from the beginning,
I didn't quite agree with it.
Although you're distant relatives
who are outside of three generations,
but if rumours spread,
it still doesn't sound so nice.
Look at you.
Because of her, you gave up
high salaries, green card,
and so on.
I really don't know what to do with you.
Mother,
The reason I came back this time
is mostly to look after you and father,
right?
Quit it.
Don't use me and your father
as an excuse.
This time,
if you don't bring me
back my daughter-in-law,
I won't thank you for it.
[He gave up the green card
to come back to China?]
[Is it really because]
[he saw the novel I wrote,]
[that's why he came back from abroad?]
-I'm here!
-Run slowly.
I was looking forward to setting
fireworks on Lunar New Year.
Youngest Uncle.
Not bad.
In the past, you liked
to set off fireworks,
but you were afraid you'll get burned.
During each Lunar New Year,
you'd beg me to set those off for you.
You've really grown up now.
You even dare to set off
fireworks on your own.
Of course.
I'm no longer the same as before.
I know.
Everyone says
I'm different from before,
that I became much more outgoing.
But I know,
it's all thanks to you.
Thank you,
Youngest Uncle.
You're indeed different from before.
In the past, when I told
you to call me that,
you always refused to do so.
Nowadays,
you have no problem with calling me that.
That's because in your heart,
I'm just
your youngest uncle.
Yu Yi, I...
That day, when all of
us were playing the game,
"I ever",
you said the person you like was present.
That person wasn't me, right?
It's Ai Jing Chu?
Just now,
before you answer this question,
I was still
feeling lucky,
It seems I no longer have a chance.
I'm sorry.
Silly.
Why are you apologizing to me?
I'm the one who missed the opportunity.
It's not your fault.
Ai Jing Chu
is a really good man.
You like him?
I think he's worth it.
But
I don't even know
what he thinks about me.
I think
he likes you very much.
Many people say
women's instincts are accurate.
But I feel,
when you care about someone,
men's instincts are just as accurate.
You two can have a match.
I'll take videos for you two.
Actually,
in that day's video,
he didn't video a lot of things.
It's just that,
he didn't capture me
that much in the video.
[In the past, when I
taught you how to ski,]
[did you ask me to]
[take more photos of you]
[as well as videos?]
[You still dare to bring it up.]
[You promised me]
[to go to the advanced ski trails.]
[In the end, shortly after you guided me]
[at the intermediate ski trails,]
[you left for United States.]
[Zeng Li,]
[look over here.]
[The camera's here.]
[I'm filming you.]
[Don't go at such high speed.]
[Look out in front of you.]
At that time,
when I saw the video,
I realized,
in his eyes
and his heart,
it's all about you.
When it comes to Xiao Chu,
He's a meticulous person,
and he considers much more than others.
Besides, he keeps a lot
of things to himself
and isn't ready to express it.
In fact, you two are very similar.
It's over.
In that case,
in this lifetime,
I might never get to hear
Mr. Ai's love confession.
No need to overthink.
I feel
you two are people with similar vibes.
You'll get nearer to each other slowly.
Youngest uncle.
[Hi,]
[Zeng Li from year 2021.]
[I'm very happy to get to
know you 10 years ago.]
[Thank you for growing up
healthy and happy,]
[met the love of your life,]
[and became the person you wish to be.]
Yu Yi.
Let's continue to set off the fireworks.
OK.
[Yu Yi,]
[my youngest uncle.]
[Thank you]
[for lighting up the world for me]
[during my darkest moments in life.]