MUGEN
To be able to die while dreaming...
Just how lucky are you?
It doesn't matter how powerful
a Demon Slayer you are.
A human's driving force
is the heart, the spirit!
DREAM
All you have to do
is destroy the spiritual core.
You can kill them just like that!
All human hearts are the same.
So fragile and weak, like glasswork.
You are falling...
into a dream.
It's a deep slumber.
They can...
LOWER ONE
no longer awaken.
EPISODE 3:
SHOULD HAVE BEEN
This way!
The peaches over here taste great!
And there are tons of white clovers in bloom!
I'll make you a chaplet!
I can make these really great-looking ones...
Nezuko!
Yes! Make a lot, okay...
Zenitsu?
There's a river along the way,
but it's shallow, so you'll be okay, right?
River?
What am I going to do, Zenitsu?
I can't swim.
I-I'll just carry you on my back
and jump right over the river!
Not even your toes will get wet, Nezuko!
Just leave it to me!
Let's go!
Expedition Team! Expedition Team!
We're the Cave Expedition Team!
Boss!
What's up, Underling 1 and Underling 2?
PONJIRO
I can smell the master of this cave
over there, pompoko!
CHUITSU
And I can hear it breathing
as it sleeps, squeak!
Here he is!
All right, let's go! Showdown!
- Roger that, Boss!
Hey you! Come with me, Underling 3!
Come over here! Look, I'll give you
these sparkly acorns! C'mon!
Let's go!
- Hey!
Why did I come here?
Oh, right.
To report to my father...
that I've become a Hashira.
So what if you've become a Hashira?
Worthless.
It means nothing.
You're never going to amount
to anything anyway.
Neither you...
nor I.
Brother...
Was our father pleased to hear your news?
Do you think our father will acknowledge me
if I become a Hashira, too?
He wasn't always like that.
After all, he did rise to the rank of Hashira
in the Demon Slayer Corps.
He was a passionate man.
And yet, one day, out of the blue,
he quit being a swordsman.
Suddenly.
The man who'd raised us both
with such enthusiasm...
Why?
It's pointless to think
about such things, so stop.
Senjuro is even worse off.
He barely has any memories of our mother
who died of illness when he was very young,
and just look at the state our father is in.
I'm going to be honest.
Our father wasn't happy to hear it.
He told me that it meant nothing.
But that's not enough
to extinguish my passion!
This flame inside my heart
will never go out!
I'll never give in!
And Senjuro...
You're not like me.
You have a big brother...
who believes in his little brother.
No matter what path you take,
you're going to become a fine human being!
Keep that burning passion
inside your heart!
Let's do our best!
Let's do our best and live on!
No matter how lonely it gets.
Looking good.
Those ropes that I created are used
for a special technique that allows one to invade
the dreams of whoever you're tethered to.
I always fight with the utmost caution.
Once you're asleep, Hashira or not,
you're no different than a baby.
I'll enjoy the feast
after killing the Demon Slayers.
There's no need to swing in such a hurry.
Relax your shoulders.
Like this?
That's right.
Close call. He's right there.
I have to make sure he doesn't see me!
I have to hurry to the edge of the dream!
Hurry!
The dream world I show them isn't infinite.
It's circular, with the dreamer in its center.
DREAM
The realm of the subconscious exists just outside
the dream, where you'll find the spiritual core.
SUBCONSCIOUS
CORE
That's what you must destroy.
Do that, and the dreamer will become crippled.
There it is!
The scenery doesn't end here,
but I can't go any further.
I'll destroy his spiritual core right away!
And then, I'll get to see
a happy dream myself!
What an odd realm of the subconscious.
It's hot.
It's burning up.
I have to hurry.
Found it!
The spiritual core!
I've never seen a red one before.
All I have to do is destroy this and...
it'll be my turn to...
I thought humans couldn't move
while they were under a spell.
What a strong survival instinct he has!
I'm going to make your favorite
rice crackers today, Tanjiro.
Wow!
I'll start breaking old rice cakes first.
It's our lucky day, Rokuta!
Rice crackers!
No fair! Big Bro's not the only one
who likes rice crackers!
- I like them, too!
- Me, too!
Then, let's eat them together, okay?
Can you get the grill ready for me?
Okay!
I'll crush them up in the grinding bowl!
Okay, I'll be in charge
of flipping them over, then!
Me, too!
Okay, then, I'll be in charge of eating them!
No fair!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
MUGEN TRAIN ARC
There.
Nezuko, let's go.
What did I just say?
I'm back!
Welcome home, Tanjiro.
Yeah, I'm home!
Welcome home, Big Bro!
Welcome home!
Welcome!
Huh? Where's Nezuko?
Big Sis went up the mountain
to pick vegetables.
In broad daylight?
She's not supposed to?
Well...
Um...
Tanjiro...
Could you get the bath ready?
I'm going to be busy with this for a while.
I keep saying all these strange things.
Am I tired maybe?
Huh? It's gone.
I wonder what that was
for just a split second.
A toolbox perhaps?
I guess my eyes were playing tricks on me.
Wake up!
You're under attack!
It's a dream!
This is a dream!
Wake up now!
I see... That's right, I'm...
on board the train!
Wake up and fight!
Fight!
Big Bro, give me your pickled radishes!
No, you don't! You stop it right now!
Why are you always
taking food away from Big Bro?
What's your problem?
You just had seconds!
No good! I'm not awake yet!
I'm still inside a dream!
How can I get out of it?
Now that I've realized that it's a dream...
What am I supposed to do?
I have to wake up...
Big Bro!
- What should we do? The fire is—
- Big Bro!
That's Nezuko's scent!
It's Nezuko's blood!
Nezuko...
Nezuko!
My uniform...
My Nichirin Sword...
I'm waking up!
Little by little.
Little by little!
Big Bro?
Big Bro, are you all right?
Sorry.
I have to go.
I have to hurry back!
I'm sorry.
Big Bro!
- Big Bro!
If the demon who's showing me
this dream is nearby...
I have to find him
and slash him right away!
Where is he? I have to...
Where are you going, Big Bro?
I picked lots of vegetables today!
Mom! This way!
Big Bro was on fire all of a sudden!
Mom?
Tanjiro, are you all right?
Big Bro...
What's the matter, Tanjiro?
Why are you dressed like that?
I wish I could stay here...
forever.
I wish I could turn around and go back.
By rights, I should've been living
like this forever.
Right here.
If none of this had happened...
they'd all have been alive and well now.
And Nezuko would've lived in the sunlight,
under the blue sky.
If none of this had happened...
I should be here
making charcoal every day.
I never would've laid a hand on a sword!
If none of this had happened...
But I've lost them now.
I can never go back!
Big Bro!
Don't leave us behind!
Sorry!
I'm sorry, Rokuta!
We can't be together anymore.
But I'll always be thinking of you, okay?
I'll be thinking of you all!
There are lots of things to thank you for.
Lots of things to be sorry for!
But I will never forget you!
No matter what,
my heart will always be with you!
So, please...
forgive me!
I have to destroy
his spiritual core right away.
So, this is the inside of his heart?
How can it be so beautiful?
It's so endlessly vast...
and...
also warm.
They're having trouble, aren't they?
I wonder why.
They haven't destroyed
any of the spiritual cores yet.
Oh well...
I guess it doesn't matter,
since they're buying me some time.
Not here.
But I can smell a demon, faintly.
What's this, though?
It's like there's a film over everything!
There's a faint demon scent everywhere!
I can't tell the exact location!
I have to hurry!
Nezuko's bleeding!
If everyone else is asleep,
we're in big trouble!
What should I do?
Am I unable to use
Total Concentration Breathing now?
Am I just asleep right now?
Tanjiro...
Take up your sword.
There's something you must cut.
There's something...
I must cut.
There's something I must cut...
in order to wake up.
I think I know what it is.
But what if I'm wrong?
If what happens in this dream
has an effect on reality, too...
there'll be no going back.
Don't hesitate! Do it!
You have to do it!
My death in this dream
will lead me to reality!
In other words...
what I have to cut is...
my own neck!
Good job preparing yourself for all this.
It's because of what you always told me.
Even if you're in anguish,
try to be a graceful and strong person
who can feel love for other humans.
All those people suffering at the hands
of the demons... Nezuko... Take care of them...
Tanjiro.
I'm going to give it my all, Father!
Next, Episode 4, "Insult."
TO BE CONTINUED