=Please Don't Spoil Me=
=Episode 9=
What are you doing?
Stop messing around!
I...
If you want my body,
you don't have to drug me.
I'll let you sleep for a night.
Wait! Hold on!
I...
The night is short.
Let's have some fun!
Your Majesty, you look tired
from all the work you've done today.
You should take care of your health.
It's not good to be addicted to women.
Not good at all.
Being too busy with work
is exactly why I've neglected the harem.
Tonight
is a good time to remedy you.
No... We can't do that!
I'm on my period!
If I remember correctly,
you said the same thing
back in Hua Qing Pool.
Concubine Rong,
you have a lot of periods recently.
I'm not used to the Cold Palace.
That's why I have hormonal imbalances.
Then, the Cold Palace
is not as comfortable
as you described before.
No. It's not comfortable.
Then, Concubine Rong, do you
want to live in the Cold Palace or not?
No. No.
Not anymore.
Since you do not feel well,
I will not force you
to sleep with me.
We should wait until you recover.
Yes. You're right.
Let's not talk about it now.
Your Majesty, it's not early.
I should go.
Li Zhi Duo!
I'm here.
Draft an edict that
since Concubine Rong doesn't feel well,
she's permitted
to return to her parents’
and rest there for three days.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(Yan's Mansion)
Oh, my little girl,
I'm worried about you.
Our daughter has just returned.
Don't cry like this.
(Madam Yan, supporting role No. 8,
professional housewife,）
(de facto leader of Yan Family,
a daughter pamperer.）
You must be tired from your travel.
Come on in.
Right. He's right.
(Yan Da Hai, supporting role No. 7)
Why are you standing there? Let's go.
(Deputy Vanguard Grain Officer, leader
of Yan Family, a daughter pamperer.）
- Come in.
Hurry up.
Bring it on.
Let's see how strong your cricket is.
Don't regret later.
Yan Er Er, you're playing dirty.
Am I?
Let me tell you.
My chick
is named "Little Cricket".
Yan Er Er, eat this!
Young Master!
What's wrong?
Your sister has returned.
What?
My sister is back?
(Li Ren He)
Sorry, everyone.
This is the last one.
Why not...
- This is sister's favorite pear juice lollipop.
- Please come here earlier tomorrow.
Hey, be patient!
Out of my way!
Get out of my way!
Don't grab it!
This is mine!
Who are you? Why is this yours?
Yeah! We've waited here for a long time.
- Yeah!
- We've queued all day long!
What? You're not happy?
Then, fight me.
Beat him!
Don't fight! Don't fight!
Oh no! My stall!
Let's have more.
These are your favorite
meatballs with soy sauce.
Eat them while they're hot.
My daughter,
try this sweet and sour fish as well.
(I must admit,)
(my parents treat me really well.)
Sis!
Yan Er Er!
What's... What's wrong with you?
Ah, it's nothing.
I just fought with some people,
and I won.
Disobedient boy!
You only know how to cause troubles!
Kneel!
(Yan Er Er, very good at fighting,
a sister pamperer)
(Hah,)
(this guy really sticks to the script.)
My daughter,
eat first. Ignore him.
Come.
Sis.
Sis!
This...
This is...
Your favorite pear juice lollipop!
There's only one left.
I grabbed it for you.
It should be done in two hours.
Our daughter can have it
when she wakes up in the morning.
(Ah, every parent is admirable.)
(If it were not for their daughter,)
(they wouldn't be tricked
by the empress dowager)
(and walk on the path of no return.)
(After all,)
(it's me, the author, who caused this.)
(That said,)
(since I'm now Yan Yi Yi,)
(I won't let them
repeat the same mistake again.)
Your Majesty, the spy has sent a message
that he'll be arriving
on the outskirts of the Capital.
And, we've arranged
the time and place
for the meeting tomorrow.
Go and prepare.
I'm leaving the Palace
tomorrow.
But, Your Majesty,
this is too dangerous.
Just let us do that.
The spy
has hidden in Xirong for many years.
For security,
he always talks to me directly.
He trusts no one
other than me.
Besides,
his intel is crucial.
If I get the intel,
then I can confidently
win the war against Xirong.
If less people from the Yin Empire
die because I'm doing this,
then this is all worthwhile.
But...
There's no but.
Go and prepare.
♪Listen to the sound of tides♪
♪They are saying I do♪
♪The setting sun is listening
to your whispers♪
♪I have told you too many of my secrets♪
♪I am being too sweet♪
♪The whole galaxy is shining for you♪