[English subtitles are available]
Open the book!
You're in for a good story today.
People say that on Prince Yi's wedding day,
the Second Lady slaughtered the city.
But alas! She's too calculating and overly cunning,
and in the end, she got nothing
and became a commoner
exiled to the north region.
This matter involved many.
Prince Da
and Min Tongrui
disappeared since that day.
No one knows where they are!
Among all princes, the most unfortunate
is Prince Xiu.
He kept
an ingrate by his side
who had stayed in East City for years
in search of the most poisonous recipe
of heartbreak grass.
The heartbreak grass recipe
disappeared with him.
No one knows how many
innocent lives will be lost.
Yun Li had nothing to do with the poison
that killed Manager Xue.
Why are you getting upset?
Where is he?
I sent him to get the flowers for the incense.
He won't be back for a while.
Xiu,
why are you playing dumb?
Let's say he has nothing to do
with the death of Manager Xue.
What about the Yun family?
These years,
the Yuns have been searching
for the heartbreak grass.
For the elixir,
the Yun brothers attempted to kill each other.
Yun Li's father died tragically.
He was such a heroic man!
Do you know why he left the recipe to me
before he died?
He had hoped
the extreme poison
would never appear in the world
to injure or kill people.
But look what you did?
You happened to keep the wolf pup
by you all the time.
Aren't you afraid that he'll set up a trap
by working with the force outside?
Father,
he's loyal to me.
He will never do that.
I have sent people out
to track the whereabouts of the Yuns secretly.
Once I found that
Yun Li is still in contact with the Yuns,
he can no longer stay.
Yun Li knows nothing
about this.
Are you sure he knows nothing?
Or are you defending him?
The precious stone lands its
innocent possessor in jail.
Xiu,
you are still young.
Karma and destiny intertwine amongst people.
You ought to reflect on it more thoroughly.
Prince Xiu,
take care.
I have to break my promise.
I can no longer stay by your side now.
Flowers blossom and wither endlessly.
Willows cycle through green and brown.
You play less music on the zither
when you have fewer bosom friends.
The pursuits of the past and now
are passing illusions soon forgotten.
Anyways,
in East Mansion,
some people left, and others stayed.
It's not like what it was before.
What happened to Prince Yi?
About Prince Yi,
I'll tell his story next time.
Butler Jack,
welcome back!
What is this?
The game world
is about to start the count down to destruction.
Isn't there any other way?
You know your mission.
No!
I can't do that.
I won't do anything to betray Si Yan.
Oh? Even if it means that she won't ever wake up?
It's her choice.
She chose to stay in this world
and be with her love.
Maybe there'll be a turning point.
The person you miss
is waiting for you at the posting station.
If you accept the command to kill Qi Yi,
the person by Si Yan's side
will be you.
Waiter,
has someone come for me?
He left.
He waited for a long time.
Who has to come
will come.
Who shouldn't come
will leave.
You don't understand.
When I needed him,
he always appeared at lightning speed.
You are talking about God.
We normal people can't see Him.
You're right.
In the past,
I was the only person in this world who could see him.
Jack,
I wasn't able to bid my farewell to you.
You won't blame me, will you?
Miss Si Yan,
I would never blame you.
I know you had waited for me for a long time.
It's my fault.
Although I don't know where you're going...
Where will I be?
I'll leave it to fate.
Actually,
without you,
black and white are just adjectives.
Butler Jack,
you know clearly what the punishment is
by disobeying the order from the system.
Now
you don't have any choice.
Isn't it silence and endless darkness?
I can handle it.
Even if you are not afraid
of being recycled forever,
but player Si Yan
won't be able to see
and hear you.
Are you still willing?
I want to thank you.
You walked toward me from the light,
and you stayed by my side
quietly.
I want to thank you as well,
Miss Si Yan,
for taking me on
a boisterous journey.
Don't worry, Jack.
I'll take good care of myself.
Thank you for always being there for me.
Thank you for liking me!
How about you?
Of course, I like you, too.
I like you as
the most precious friend of all.
How wouldn't I understand
your love for Qi Yi?
You're probably complaining about me.
For me now,
I only wish to safe-keep those images
of your happiness
when you laughed out loud,
when you are rambunctious,
and even those tears
when you loved and were loved.
Miss Si Yan,
I only blame myself for not being able to
make you happier.
You have to remember me.
After all, you are an AI.
You'll live on much longer than I will.
You'll forget about me slowly and surely.
I promise you
that I'll keep you in my heart
like a picture.
Follow me.
Lady Cui wants to see you.
Isn't this way to the Makeup Service?
Lady Cui was in league with the Second Lady.
She has lost her place at Makeup Service.
Lady Cui.
The so-called makeup
emphasizes
cleanliness, harmony, freshness,
compliance, orderliness, smoothness, and integrity.
Cleanliness
means keeping the appearance neat,
not dirty, and not cluttered.
Harmony
means that makeup and the look become one.
The beauty of post-makeup is natural and innate.
Freshness
refers to making sure the makeup is not expired.
The colors are pure.
And you can't neglect to manage the makeup items.
Compliance
means to have patience and delicacy
when applying hair oil.
As for orderliness,
it means following the procedures step by step
when brushing the hair.
Regarding smoothness,
it means to level up and even out when brushing the hair.
And integrity
is the highest state of applying makeup.
It depends on your heart.
Palace Makeup Service
is now under your management.
Me?
Head Matron?
Why me?
I can tell that
you like it from the bottom of your heart.
Makeup
is aesthetic.
You want to please both yourself and others.
But what matters the most is
the heart.
Greetings, my lady.
How is Si Yan doing?
Lady Cui said that
Si Yan is talented.
Perhaps
it's her destiny
to become Head Matron
of Makeup Service.
She's close to being compatible with my Yi.
You mean...
Do you agree?
It hasn't been easy for Yi.
Because of me,
he's had a hard time
growing up.
In the past,
I always thought
I should make plans for him
and fight for something.
I never asked him
what he was thinking
or what he wanted.
I channeled my efforts
in the wrong place after all.
Come to think about it,
as a mother,
I have wronged him.
My lady,
everything is going well now.
Shouldn't you be happy?
Happy?
I am happy.
Is it beautiful here?
Yes, it is.
Si Yan,
I can finally marry you.
Are you...
are you proposing to me?
Then my wedding has to...
I'll give you
the most magnificent wedding in East City.
That would be too much.
Then what do you want to do?
I also have a surprise for you.
Let's go.
Qi Yi,
are you crazy?
It's okay.
What's to worry about?
Wait for me!
Master, I can't hold them any longer.
You're not even holding much stuff.
You're not as strong as you look.
That's wrong.
You don't
even look strong.
And you're even weaker than you look.
I am holding these fabrics for you.
Why don't you hold it?
Just tell me if you need more clothing.
Why did we come here?
This place
is the place to make surprises.
Wait for me here, please.
Boss,
I want to make an outfit,
but it is difficult.
I'll draw it for you.
Don't look.
Go over there.
It looks like this...
It has a veil that's this long...
And a very long skirt...
The fluffy and puffy kind...
Do you get it?
It's going to be a bit pricy.
2000 tael.
2000 tael?
Aren't you afraid of choking?
Mainly it's because of the desired design...
Okay, I get it.
Where's my surprise?
I just checked.
The surprise is too expensive.
Since I came to the mansion,
not only have I not made any money,
but I've also run out of my savings!
I don't know...
if you're willing to lend a hand?
I'll think about it.
That's a bit much!
Forget it if you don't want to.
That'll do it, right?
A kiss for a thousand tael!
Don't you need two thousand tael?
When other princes are married,
people pay tributes and give presents.
My master is the opposite.
He's planting the flowers
needed for the wedding decoration.
Your Highness,
those plants are growing so well.
Why did you pull them out?
These are weeds.
If they grow out,
the lilac won't thrive.
Your Highness,
I'll do it.
Please take a break.
No need.
You can do other things.
Yes.
The weeds endanger lilac, so they need elimination.
You are...?
Li?
Why are you...
If a person's existence
endangers other people,
should that person be eliminated like the weeds?
Be it a flower,
or a person,
if he stays where he doesn't belong,
he will only annoy others.
If you keep pestering Si Yan,
I won't be nice to you.
You misunderstood me.
I've given up on
Miss Si Yan.
However,
Prince Yi,
it's no use when only I gave up.
You should know
what will happen here soon.
What on earth is this place?
Why did you bring me here?
Who are you?
I am the virtual reality wake-up system's
assigned butler, Jack.
Who I am doesn't matter.
What matters is that
you need to know who you are.
This...
What is this?
After hundreds of times of discussions
and revisions,
the production team eventually created you.
Prince Yi of East City.
He looks calm and introverted,
but he does a brisk job.
He's considered perfect in people's eyes.
What's untold about him is that
he lives
in the shadow of his brother, Qi Teng.
How do you know all of this?
Those are created by others,
just like the characters in the play
in your world.
As a player, one of the steps
in Si Yan's hidden task
was to meet you at the stone bridge.
After the accident of falling into the water,
your life was supposed to end right there.
Si Yan?
I am her task?
You are not alone.
Qi Xiu,
Qi Da,
Qi Bao,
or any insignificant maid in the East Mansion
is pre-written programming.
Every one of them
has their missions
and clues
to help Si Yan become the Head Matron
and wake up in the real world.
She doesn't belong
in your world.
Impossible!
I don't believe it.
Don't you always hear her
say weird things?
This is Si Yan's world.
Because of a car accident,
she entered here.
She was supposed to complete her task easily,
but she met you.
Si Yan!
That is Si Yan in that world.
Si Yan?
What happened to her?
She tried her best
to become the Head Matron,
so she could wake up from the game.
But your existence
has disrupted everything.
I saved your life!
With it,
you can conceal the rashes on your body.
I'll make you star-crossed lovers!
Jack, time-out!
For him,
I can give up everything.
You were supposed to die.
Miss Si Yan
saved you again and again.
She even gave up
the opportunity to wake up in the real world.
Are you saying...
Si Yan could have been able to return?
Even if Si Yan gave up returning,
the whole system would
face crashing because of
the bug of you.
What is the consequence of crashing?
Si Yan will never wake up,
and we will all disappear.
We are all created by others,
and everything
is unreal.
Impossible...
Then what is real?
Miss Si Yan is real,
and her love for you is real.
She wants to return to the real world.
That's also true.
Without Qi Yi...
But because of you...
There's no point in me waking up.
She doesn't even want to return to reality.
How I wish that
she could live her life according to her wish.
But as a system butler,
I can't let her.
As a character in Si Yan's game,
you can't let her, either.
Only you
can end this.
If the game were to play out according to plan,
Si Yan could get out of here.
But if that's the case...
In that case...
I have to die.
Si Yan loves you.
Even though thousands of people want you dead,
she will be the first to stop it from happening.
It may sound selfish,
but isn't it...
Isn't it love?
I truly...
envy you a lot.
Farewell, Qi Yi.
You must intercept Yun Li
and get the heartbreak grass portion back.
If it's necessary,
you can kill him.
Yes.
Brother Xiu,
when will you be back?
Yi,
you are the only one
who didn't ask why I had to go.
You love Yun Li very much.
Please be careful on the trip.
Please come back early.
Father needs you.
You know that
I don't like the ins and outs of politics.
Traveling suits me better.
Have you heard?
If you keep going eastward toward South Jiuzhai,
there's a place called Xiwu Paradise.
When spring comes,
peach blossoms are everywhere.
When I find Yun Li,
we'll go peach blossom viewing with our swords.
Sounds good.
I've never heard of that place before.
What's there to be envious?
Don't you have Si Yan?
By then,
bring her to South Jiuzhai.
Maybe, when we have the chance.
I'm the one who's leaving.
Why are you down in the dumps
as if you'll never see me again?
Brother Xiu,
sometimes
I feel we are like the characters in a play.
All the challenges we went through
are for engaging audiences.
You
and I
are both unreal.
If we are characters in a play, that'll be nice.
Because in plays,
people love happy endings the best.
Yi,
I don't know what you went through,
but I believe
everything you said.
When I come back,
if you're willing to tell me the stories,
I'll be all ears.
Sure.
I'll wait for your return.
What brings you here?
I can't sleep.
I miss you.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
Don't be absurd.
I remember you once told me
that the moon in this world
is bright and round.
Too bad that
there's no moon today.
It's not a big deal
as long as you're with me.
Si Yan,
what is it like in your world?
Can you tell me?
Why are you asking this out of the blue?
Don't you always say
they're different worlds?
I was making things up.
Did you believe all that?
I did,
and I am curious.
My world
is so big that
you can go up in the sky and under the ground.
You can go wherever you want.
It is also so tiny that
all you need is a cell phone
and you can see people you want to see.
Even though you are far apart?
Like this?
Yes, like that.
If only there is
the thing
called cell phone in this world...
then I could
see you anytime and anywhere.
In the future,
if you do
this gesture,
I'll know that you miss me.
Rui,
I'm sorry.
If I were not impulsive,
you wouldn't need to
hide in here with me.
It's me who's always been hiding.
Until you brought me here,
I finally dare to face it.
Thank you.
You know what?
I thought that
I don't deserve to be happy,
and I don't deserve love
until I met you.
Wherever you are
is where my home is.
I won't let you down.
I'm delivering a letter from Prince Yi.
Big brother, how are you?
You must be shocked
that I know where you are.
The truth is that
Father has been looking for
your location secretly.
I wanted to visit you two in person,
but I don't want to intrude.
So I sent a messenger.
What's in the past,
be it a misunderstanding
or fate,
has already happened.
So, let's leave the past behind us.
Since you left,
Father has been worried.
Father has always had high expectations for you,
but
expectations gradually became a shackle.
Big brother,
come home.
Father is waiting.
Please tell Prince Yi
that I've received the letter.
Tell him to take care of Father.
Yes.
Wait.
I have a letter here.
Please deliver it to Miss Si Yan.
Si Yan,
How are you?
Although it's kind of late,
I still want to confess.
I was driving on the day of the accident.
I wanted nothing but to be a beauty blogger!
You were drunk.
And I was worried.
I didn't expect that
we'd get into an accident
a few hundred meters in the ride.
I am very sorry
that I didn't tell you the truth sooner.
I used to
think that this world was only a fantasy.
All I cared about was the task,
so I deceived you.
Other than apologizing,
I also want to say thank you.
Thank you for showing me that
our emotion is the only real thing.
I thought that
I don't deserve to be happy
and loved in my life
until I met Qi Da.
He gave up everything to take me away.
At that moment,
I finally mustered up the courage
to face my utmost real emotions.
Now
I think I finally found
my happiness.
I hope you will find yours, too.
I will,
Glasses.
For better
or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in health
or in sickness,
I'll love you forever.
Si Yan,
do brides in your world
all wear white wedding gowns?
Yes.
The brides in my world
are beautiful, right?
Very beautiful!
Si Yan,
I will keep you engraved deep in my heart.
I'll never forget you.
Thank you.
Thank you for doing all of this for me.
If you are so grateful,
use your whole life to thank me.
Having met you,
I have never regretted it.
Though my world might be unreal,
you...
you are my only reality.
Thank you
for helping me find myself.
Qi Yi,
What's wrong?
Don't scare me, Qi Yi.
Qi Yi...
Si Yan,
this time,
don't save me again.
Brother Yi,
I found Yun Li.
Since you'd like to keep the heartbreak grass elixir,
I'll leave it to you.
Please make sure it won't be displaced.
Also,
congratulations on getting married.
Go home.
I won't go home.
Don't die.
I only want you.
I don't want to go home.
No!
Doctor!
Doctor,
my daughter's awake.
You're awake!
You're finally back.
What do you think?
It's not bad, isn't it?
Here is
the makeup style I'm featuring today.
It's the most unforgettable makeup style
and my all-time favorite.
I gave it a name.
It's
The Maid from the East City.
Wow! So beautiful!
What does makeup mean to you?
What does makeup mean to me?
For me,
it is
a fantasy journey
from the body to the soul.
You'll encounter
many unforgettable experiences.
Alright.
This is it for the day.
I'll see you next time.
Bye!
Miss Si Yan, excuse me.
As a successful beauty blogger,
you have led the research and development
of the game The Beauty Blogger 2.0
and become the owner of
a costume makeup game company.
Can you comment on that, please?
I just wanted to
promote the virtual reality
costume live-action role-playing game.
By combining education and entertainment,
traditional cultures and modern technology
are merged.
Other than entertaining, I think games can
benefit the public, popularize science,
reinforce cultural heritage,
foster positive values
of the young generations,
and enable the comprehension
and passion about Chinese artistic traditions.
Alright, thank you.
How are you
over there?
I've taken over the game company.
I've also extended the game time
indefinitely.
If you want to come back,
anytime is fine.
I'm your butler, Jack.
Come.
Your adventure
is about to start.
Please make sure your VR glasses fit well.
I heard
that you hate women who act crazy when drunk.
Here.
Fill up the glass.
Let's make a toast
for a successful blind date!