GYMNASIUM
Go.
I always
feel satisfied with a moderate distance
in a relationship.
What? You get to dance with girls?
I should have taken that class.
Look at all those guys without partners.
They're all guys like you.
He seems to have a crush on Na-bi.
I bet he'll ask her out
on the last day of class.
Let's go.
We didn't make any mistakes!
I did good, right? Did you see?
We're getting an A+ for sure. Let's go!
You danced pretty well.
-Did you see?
-Yes. I saw it when I was passing by.
I knew you'd be a good dancer.
I never stepped on my partner's foot.
-Thanks.
-Is that it?
I'll buy you a meal.
All right.
Did you stay up all night?
You're overworking yourself.
I've gotten a grip on myself
thanks to you.
You told me to be sincere.
I was only talking about dating.
I tried applying lacquer on glass,
but I screwed up.
It just keeps falling off.
-Isn't there a way to do this?
-You should make the surface rough.
How do you know that?
My aunt does pottery.
I learned some from her.
I want to learn, too.
I tried baking glass with glaze on it,
and the color came out different
each time. It was cool.
I'll teach you.
I'll be better at it than you.
A distance that's close enough
yet not too close
to hurt each other.
-Isn't it good?
-No.
It's bad?
Isn't it pretty?
EPISODE 6: THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS LOVE.
NEVERTHELESS,
But are you really just friends with him?
Yes. We're just friends.
That's a relief.
I thought maybe I said something
I shouldn't have.
You should just keep your hair that way.
What?
Jae-eon…
likes doing it with your hair tied.
Everyone, take a look at what I gave you.
There's a list of commonly used colors
and the image and keywords
that people associate with those colors.
Even if it's the same color,
the associated images
could be the exact opposite.
And some are different
according to the culture or country.
And of course, it could be different
for each individual.
Good work today.
-Thank you!
It's finally over!
-Is this it?
-Give me my bag.
Did anyone see Na-bi today?
Na-bi? I haven't seen her.
-Me neither.
-What about you?
-She ignored my message.
-Did she not contact you either?
-No.
Is something wrong?
She's not answering her phone, either.
I'm sure
she just felt like skipping class today.
Na-bi isn't like you.
We'll be off. See you tomorrow!
-Good work today.
-Bye.
Hey, where are you going? Wait for me.
-We're eating lunch.
-I'll be back after lunch.
-Hey!
How about tteokbokki?
Do you want to eat tteokbokki?
-Sure.
-Did you bring your wallet?
My treat.
All right.
-Let's go.
NOODLE SHOP
I'm worried.
About what?
Na-bi. I can't get in touch with her.
Really?
She must have been shocked.
-What?
-It's nothing.
She's attractive.
You only saw her for a minute,
and you felt that?
I could see why you fell for her.
What are you talking about?
It's not like that.
I broke up with Chris.
Why?
You're actually asking me why?
He said he thought he would be okay
with me seeing other guys, but he wasn't.
But I think I can understand
how that feels now.
So that's it?
Yes. I just let him go.
I did good, right?
What? That's what you hate the most.
Getting clingy.
Ms. Yun Seol-a. This way, please.
You can go if you're busy.
It's fine. Go on.
WHERE ARE YOU?
YU NA-BI
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable. Please try again later…
She disappeared.
Thank you!
Yu Na-bi!
Auntie!
Oh, my.
It's so nice to see you.
-Right, Auntie.
-Yes?
Don't tell my mom I'm here, okay?
Are you involved in some crime?
It's nothing like that.
Then it's fine.
How long are you staying?
About a week?
That long?
What? You don't want me to stay?
It's not that.
I'll clean the house.
All right. Let's take care
of all the household chores
that I've been putting off all this time.
Okay. I'll do my best.
POTTERY WORKSHOP
This feels so great.
-The weather's so nice.
-It is.
Oh, right. I saw Do-hyeok at the market.
He grew up so well.
Do-hyeok came, too?
When you headed back to Seoul
when you were little,
all the other kids came to see you off
but Do-hyeok didn't come.
That's right.
You were crying and whining about it
the whole way there.
No way. I didn't cry.
You did. You two were so close.
Right.
I did like Do-hyeok a lot.
-You liked him the most.
-Come on, it wasn't like that.
-Yes, it was.
-No!
-Give it to me.
-No, I can carry it.
-We're going to your workshop, right?
-Yes. Let's go.
Let's go!
-Come down after you unpack.
-Okay.
-See you later!
-See you later.
You're so cute.
-What are you on about?
-You're so adorable.
-Let's eat.
-No.
-No!
-We don't have time.
But…
don't you think
we should tell the others now?
-Tell them what?
-That we're dating.
Why? It's not like we're getting married.
I want to tell them, though.
Why should we hide it?
No, I don't want to.
Why?
They'll just keep talking about us
if we tell them.
Why don't we kiss some more
instead of arguing?
You're just trying to change the subject.
-No…
-There's no one here!
-Come on, there's nobody…
-Let go of me.
What are you two doing here?
We're eating!
What are you doing here?
Did you come here to make out?
What? We have a platonic relationship.
Wait. I have something to ask.
I heard Ms. Jo and Mr. An
were seen coming out of a motel together.
Is that true?
It wasn't a motel. It was a house.
What? They were in the same house?
-Yes.
-Then they're living together?
Even if they're not,
it means they're dating at least.
No way!
-Why?
-They don't suit each other.
They are so different.
Yes, it's ridiculous.
I don't believe the rumors.
They spend a lot of time together,
so they could have fallen for each other.
YUN SOL
-Hey, Sol.
-Hey, Na-bi!
-Why did you ignore my calls
-Lower your voice.
and answer Sol's?
Oh, it's you, Ji-wan.
You're coming to the workshop, right?
Sol's coming too.
I don't think I can come.
Really? I thought we changed the location
because of you.
What? To where?
You know, the guesthouse
that your noodle shop friend is running.
-You're coming here?
-"Here"? You're there right now?
No, I'm not.
But my aunt lives nearby.
Are you staying there until the weekend?
I am, but…
I still can't come.
Why? You're nearby. Come hang out with us.
-Come on.
-Well…
Is Jae-eon coming?
What? No, he said he has other plans.
Oh, really?
I'll go if I have the time.
And don't tell the others I'm here.
Okay, I won't tell.
Don't ignore my calls anymore, all right?
Okay. Bye, then.
Didn't Jae-eon say he's coming?
-Yes, he did.
-Then why did you lie to her?
I know, right? Why did I do that?
Whatever. I had to say that
to get Na-bi to come.
That might cause huge trouble.
No, they could get back together
thanks to us.
Please don't say "us."
You heard me, so you're an accomplice now.
She doesn't even like him.
I know.
But when she asked if he was coming,
it sounded like she wanted him to come.
So don't tell Na-bi, okay?
You better keep this a secret.
-Okay.
-Let's go watch a movie today.
I have plans.
What? Who? You didn't even tell me.
Se-hun asked to eat lunch with me.
What's he up to this time?
He's not up to anything.
He wanted to ask me something about work.
He can just ask you over the phone.
You have to come to the workshop.
PARK JAE-EON
WHERE ARE YOU?
Jae-eon likes doing it
with your hair tied.
You're crazy.
Why are you so pathetic?
No…
I can't do this.
POWER OFF
Hey, Na-bi.
I heard you came today.
Yes. I just arrived.
Where are you headed?
Me? I was going to go see you.
What?
-You were coming to see me?
-Yes.
Then you should've called me.
We could've missed each other.
I did, but your phone was off.
I got worried.
Oh, right. I turned off my phone.
Were you headed somewhere?
I was just taking a walk.
A walk? Then…
Do you want to go to the beach?
GRANDSON OF A NOODLE SHOP OWNER
BEEF TARTARE NOODLES AT A FISHING VILLAGE
Why isn't he showing his face
when he's so handsome?
I'm sure he'd get
way more viewers if he did.
You didn't change the workshop location
because of money, right?
You just want to see him, right?
No. I mean, that's one reason.
It's not the only reason, though.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm just a fan. I mean it.
Come here.
-Oh, my head.
-Why did you do that?
It hurts. Come here and nurse me.
Come on.
-Let's go outside today.
-What?
We kept staying inside.
-Don't you feel stuffy?
-No, not at all.
Come on! Come here.
MYEONGWON-DONG, 26, DIMPLES
Why are you so heavy?
What? Who is it?
-Who is it?
-Just some guy I know.
His name's…
Gosh, I can't remember his name.
Kim…
What? I didn't pick up.
That seems more strange.
Why would he call you?
How would I know? Should I ask him?
You didn't delete that dating app?
Jeez.
Stop trying to change me.
You're suffocating me.
What? Suffocating you?
Yes, you're making a fuss over nothing.
What do you think
being in a relationship means?
Why do you even date me?
Because I like you.
-You like me?
-Yes.
-You really like me?
-Yes. I told you.
Not just having sex with me?
Is it that different?
Gyu-hyun…
Why is everything so complicated for you?
It's not complicated.
To be honest, you haven't changed
at all since we started dating.
Hey, that's ridiculous.
Have you changed, then?
Why am I the only one who has to change?
What are you doing?
I knew you'd be like this.
You boring nerd.
It's been a while since I came here.
It's so nice.
Are you sure it's okay to hang out?
-Don't you need to get ready to open?
-It's okay.
Both the noodle shop and the guesthouse
aren't opening yet.
That's a relief, then.
Can I help you with anything?
I'm good at cooking and cutting.
Use me as your assistant.
It's done.
Wait right here.
All right.
Did you see this yesterday?
I did.
It's amazing.
Oh, right. I wanted to go somewhere.
-This place is popular too.
-Where?
This one. I think it's nearby.
-I reserved a table for two.
-It looks nice.
-Right?
-I didn't know you'd be coming along.
I've always wanted to come here.
And I heard
that you guys were meeting here.
How could I not come?
If you're going to have a serious talk,
I'll leave you two alone.
Is it something important?
What?
Oh, well. It's…
No, it's nothing special.
I just wanted
to have a nice meal together.
I'll pay.
No, my treat. I asked to eat with you.
I'll pay for yours too, Ji-wan.
-Okay.
-Enjoy.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
This looks good! Let's take a photo.
This is awesome.
When did you prepare all this?
I prepared this
when I heard you were coming.
You're really not filming this?
-I shouldn't be the only one seeing this.
-You saw it, so it's fine.
Hey, you're kind of good
at saying sweet things.
You must've dated a lot.
I haven't.
You've never dated?
No. So what?
No, I'm not saying it's weird.
It's just unexpected.
You must be pretty popular.
You have a very gentle and pure image.
I don't know why,
but I kept liking someone
who had a boyfriend.
Oh.
I see…
I'm okay. I have to drive.
Oh, right.
Should I drink alone, then?
Then I'll do this,
so it's like I'm drinking too.
-Cheers.
This is so nice.
Do you have someone?
What?
Do you have someone you like?
Or a boyfriend?
Not now.
Eat up.
Okay. Let's eat.
So I dated that jerk for a long time
and broke up early this year.
What? Why are you grinning like that?
Are you laughing at me?
It's not that.
You had a boyfriend before too.
I did?
What do you mean?
That was my first relationship.
What? No, it isn't.
You said you were dating,
so I gave up last time.
"Gave up"?
What?
Hey, don't you need to drive?
You're my first love.
What?
I had a crush on you,
but you were leaving for Seoul,
so I was about to tell you I liked you.
But you said you had a boyfriend,
so I gave up.
I told you I had a boyfriend?
Not to me. You told someone else.
I don't remember saying that.
I guess I didn't want to get teased
for not having a boyfriend.
Hang on.
Is that why you didn't come to see me
when I was leaving?
Yes.
Hey, I was so upset about that!
Would you have accepted me
if I confessed my feelings to you?
I don't know. But I would've
stayed in touch with you.
We were best friends.
Then I guess things
would have been different.
I don't know! You were such an idiot.
-Look at the red dot.
-Okay.
One, two, three.
You did great.
It's my turn now.
Can I sit here?
You're already sitting there.
Are you with someone?
No, I'm not.
Can you hand me the menu?
Sure.
That butterfly is pretty.
What meaning does it have?
The ugliness and pain of happiness,
and lack of freedom.
That's what butterfly tattoos symbolize.
I see.
I just did it
because I like butterflies, though.
Come to think of it,
butterflies look so pretty
but some people say
if you rub your eyes after touching
butterfly wings, you'll become blind.
That's not true.
There's a kind of scale powder
on their wings,
and it's not really that harmful.
It can only cause some allergies.
-No way.
-It's funny, right?
-What do you mean?
-People are so funny.
The butterflies are the ones
that get hurt.
If they lose their scales,
they'll lose the patterns and colors
on their wings.
And they won't be able to fly.
Do you want to see some?
It was my last vacation in the military,
and my friend asked
if I wanted to go see an exhibition.
To be honest, I don't know much about art.
It was my first time going
to an art exhibit.
Right.
But I saw someone
who really looked like you.
I was almost sure it was you,
but it had been such a long time
so I couldn't call your name.
I regretted that after.
But I met you again on the bus.
It really was you at the exhibition.
My heart was beating like crazy.
Isn't that stupid?
Hey, Do-hyeok.
-Do-hyeok!
-Na-bi. Did you sleep well?
Why did you give me the blankets
when you were sleeping outside?
It's okay.
-The thing about Youtube is…
-That's right.
-It's no joke.
-You're talking about views, right?
Getting one million views is amazing.
-That's amazing.
-It is.
-Our couple number 12.
-Couple 12.
When Jae-joon ordered noodles…
Gyeong-jun.
Gyeong-jun! You can't hear me, right?
You startled me.
What the…
-You're not wearing your glasses.
-No.
What?
What is it?
My glasses.
What?
-Those are my glasses.
-What do you mean? They're mine.
Oh, they're yours.
Then where are mine?
Yours?
Oh.
I see.
No wonder. You looked a bit weird.
Here.
What is it this time?
-Thankfully, it doesn't smell.
-What?
I guess you just fart loudly.
What are you talking about? That's not me!
You were pretty loud!
-Farty pants!
-It wasn't me!
Jeez.
What's with you? I told you, it wasn't me!
You're so annoying!
YU NA-BI
What are you doing here?
Hey.
Did you see Bit-na by any chance?
No, I didn't.
Okay.
Are you joining the workshop?
No. I'm not going.
Why? Everyone will make a fuss
if they hear you're not going.
What about Na-bi?
Na-bi's not coming either.
-You didn't know?
-No.
We're not talking much these days.
You did something wrong, didn't you?
Well…
I'm not sure.
Don't lie. You know what it is.
But still, she likes you.
Can't you treat her sincerely?
Na-bi, be careful
when you're taking them out.
Don't worry.
My stomach hurts.
You must've drunk so much.
I guess it was fun.
-The food was so delicious.
-I know.
And the beach was so pretty.
I should head back to Seoul soon.
I'm resting too much.
That's why you came, though.
Oh, but you should fix that shelf
for me before you go.
Okay.
Look at how pretty they are.
These look a bit strange, though.
Why is the color different?
It's the same glaze.
It was a bit windy a while ago.
Even if you apply the same glaze,
they look different depending
on the humidity or temperature.
So once you start baking them,
you don't get to decide
what color they turn out to be.
Doesn't that make you uneasy?
What do you mean?
It's fun because it's unpredictable.
That's why
I've been doing pottery for so long.
I tried baking glass with glaze on it,
and the color came out different
each time. It was cool.
You're saying the same thing.
What? Same as who?
Never mind.
It's getting scary to do sculpture though.
One mistake could ruin everything.
I feel like it'll be better
to do something digital
where I can save and undo my work.
My goodness.
You're not living up to your name.
You know why your name's Na-bi?
Yes. You said you named me
because your favorite author--
No. You said you had to present it
at school,
so I made that up.
What?
Your mom says she named you like that
so your life would be as sweet as honey.
But butterflies don't always eat honey.
Insects and poop
are all nutrients for them too.
Everything you're going through
in your life right now
are your nutrients.
So what's there to fear?
To be honest,
I don't think I can take it anymore.
When we're together, she acts like
I'm the only one in her life,
so I thought she cared for me too.
But then when she gets interested
in something else, she ignores me.
So I keep getting depressed
even while I'm with her.
She does say that she likes me.
I want to believe that,
but I can't help doubting it.
This isn't what I'm usually like.
Maybe I should have just stuck
to being friends with her.
I've never seen you talk so much.
Why was I blabbering on about that to you?
Have you told her honestly
about what you just said?
No. Never.
It's not easy to be honest with her.
-What?
-I have pride, you know.
I'm already upset since I feel like
I'm the only one who likes her.
What do you want from her?
Certainty about the relationship
and sincerity toward me.
That's unrealistic.
As soon as you have certainty,
that relationship becomes weak.
How does one get
that certainty?
Are you sure it'll help you?
You're pretty twisted, aren't you?
I think you're the one who's twisted.
But anyway, I'm sure there's a reason
why she's staying by your side.
SONG SEO-YEON: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
KIM EUN-JU: IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY TODAY?
KANG SEO-YEON: YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD ME
IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY!
Oh, Do-hyeok. Come inside.
Yes.
This place is so pretty.
What?
I think I remember this place.
-Really?
-Yes.
You know what?
They say that if you catch a falling leaf
and make a wish,
it'll come true.
What? You believe stuff like that?
It's romantic.
You don't?
No.
I don't.
Why?
Just because. There's no evidence.
But that's why I like it.
I just have to believe in it. That's all.
Is that so?
-I caught one.
-Make a wish.
I don't believe stuff like this.
Forget it. Just give me the camera.
Do-hyeok, why don't you try uploading
vlogs of your daily life?
You can film stuff like preparing
to open your restaurant
instead of always just showing
your hands and scenery.
I bet you'll get way more viewers.
Are my videos boring?
It's not that.
You look really great on camera.
If you reveal your face,
I'm sure you'll get way more subscribers.
-No way. Come on.
-Hey, just once.
Just once. Please?
What's that?
One, two, three.
See? You look great.
-Let me take a photo of you too.
-No, not me.
I look awful in photos.
No, you looked pretty.
What?
Oh, to be honest,
I took a photo of you last time.
-Sorry.
-When?
-At the beach.
-Do you have it now?
-Yes.
-Let me see.
They look good, right?
Well…
This one is nice.
They came out nice.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
-You don't have a gift for me?
-A gift?
Of course I do.
But I don't know if you'll like it.
-Did you want this that badly?
-I must have lost my mind.
I wanted to have it.
I lied to your friend Na-bi.
-Lied about what?
-She asked if we were dating,
and I said yes.
She believed me right away.
I didn't know she'd disappear like that.
Sorry about that.
She didn't just stay quiet though.
We're here.
You should go.
-I'll come and pick you up tomorrow.
-No, it's fine.
I'll see you at the market.
I can go there alone.
It's dangerous at that hour.
I'll be off. See you tomorrow.
Okay…
PARK JAE-EON
WHERE ARE YOU, LET'S TALK
Na-bi, let's eat some apples.
Okay. I'm all done.
"Where are you? Let's talk."
That means you're angry, right?
What's this random question?
I promised myself I would never date
while watching my mom.
When did you make such a decision?
When I was little.
The day before I left for Seoul,
Mom came here and cried her eyes out.
Oh, that day.
She really liked that man.
It was pretty intense.
I told her he was a scumbag
and that she should break up with him,
but she never listened.
But still, she dated him.
There was nothing between us.
I don't know why I did that.
I was so stupid. It's so embarrassing.
This is the worst.
Hey, there is always
something between people.
I still respect your mom.
She got so hurt,
but she falls passionately in love
with new people.
That's nonsense.
Your mom said that dating
isn't about picking the nicest person.
It's about meeting someone special to you.
I think that's why she failed each time.
You're wrong about that.
If she failed each time,
how could she have gotten
such a precious daughter?
Here.
The shelf's crooked.
Oh, no. I drilled all the holes already.
Why isn't anything working out?
You look great today, as usual. Come in.
Happy birthday.
I heard that there's a lot of things
to carry and move for sculpture majors.
This is too much.
Let me at least do this.
Thank you.
Mom.
Did the performance go well?
Yes. I'm performing in Paris next.
How is Paris?
It's nice.
Do you want to come with me?
Someone wanted to go there.
It must be someone you like.
No.
Just someone bothersome.
Jae-eon.
You know what I regret the most?
Not knowing my own feelings.
No…
pretending not to know.
Who would love someone
who doesn't even take care of themselves?
All right.
Who would love someone
who doesn't even take care of themselves?
I know very well that a person
who doesn't know how to love someone
can never be happy.
That's what you hate the most.
Getting clingy.
What?
You always draw the line like this.
You just want to see me when you want,
but you're scared I'll get clingy?
Don't worry.
That's not going to happen.
MISSED CALLS
PARK JAE-EON
YANG DO-HYEOK
It's what you made for me.
You still have that? I'm touched.
Of course. You gave it to me. Good night.
Good night.
Hey, Na-bi.
-Hi.
Did you sleep well?
-Yes. You?
-Me too.
-Should we go?
-Okay.
-Sir.
-Yes?
Can you watch these?
-Sure. Go ahead.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, let's try this.
-Could we have some sweet potatoes?
-Okay.
Hello.
Oh, you brought your girlfriend.
You two look so sweet together.
We're not…
-Well…
-Why aren't you saying anything?
That will be 8,000 won.
Some potatoes too.
-Potatoes?
-Just a few.
Let's see.
You look so happy.
That's 13,000 won.
Thirteen thousand?
I'll give you a discount
since your girlfriend is so pretty.
-Just give me 10,000 won.
-Thank you.
-You're so pretty.
-You got a discount thanks to me.
-Okay. I'll cook something nice.
-Bye.
It's so pretty.
How much are those?
Those flowers? They're 23,000 won.
-What? 23,000 won?
-Yes.
-I'll take those.
-All right.
-Hey.
-What?
It's fine. We'll come back next time.
It seems like it's broken.
Why did you do that, Do-hyeok?
-I didn't do it.
-Jeez.
Hey, Na-bi.
Hey, it's really Na-bi!
-Who…
-Oh, I guess you don't remember.
My cousin, Do-yeon.
Oh, right. Do-yeon.
It's been a long time.
-You're unbelievable!
-Don't say anything weird.
I mean, I was so surprised.
You look so pretty!
-You're right.
-No…
You've grown so much.
I didn't recognize you.
Na-bi. The tire's flat.
You can't ride it now.
Did I do that?
No, it's not your fault.
I think someone played a prank.
-Let's go get it fixed.
-Okay.
There's no need for that.
You two can ride yours together.
I'll get this fixed and ride it home.
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Bye.
-See you later, Do-yeon.
-Thanks!
What are you doing?
Oh, in case it's uncomfortable for you.
Get on.
Let's go.
Are you sleeping here with your friends?
No, I'm going to sleep at my aunt's.
Really? Then I'll take you home.
I need to tell you something.
Tell me what?
I'll tell you later.
Do-hyeok, where should I put this?
Over there. No, I'll put that away.
Hello. I'm Park Jae-eon.
Hello. I'm Yang Do-hyeok.
How have you been?
Fine. So-so.
I haven't been well.
His familiar smells are haunting me.
He's charming.
I wouldn't mind if you went after him.
They look like newlyweds.
It's true that Na-bi is my first love.
What is your relationship to Jae-eon?
There's nothing between us.
I kept thinking about you. I missed you.
You have a girlfriend.
That's not the issue.
Stop playing games with me.
Let's end this.
-Stop it.
-What?
What you're doing right now.
Where's Na-bi?
-She said she's too tired to come.
-She's not coming?
Just tell me if you don't want this.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park