♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 7=
All my thinking was in vain,
as Xiao Ai made a good point.
You are here!
What's the matter?
He is always so cold.
Forget it.
I will get engaged in four days.
Congratulations.
How come you said that.
You know I like...
Well, first things first.
I want you to help me
escape from the marriage.
I will not help you.
Don't refuse me in a hurry.
I am not asking you.
I am making a deal with you.
A deal?
You help me run away from the palace.
And I will find you
the blood night-blooming cereus.
I know I am right.
You need the blood night-blooming cereus
for treating cold poison.
Right.
So how do you help me find
the blood night-blooming cereus?
I am the leading role.
I can definitely find it.
Don't worry.
I will help you find it.
Just tell me
deal or not?
Deal.
At midnight after three days,
let's meet at the
north gate of the palace.
All right.
It is a beautiful night.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Chang Kong doesn't understand
why Your Highness
is still in a good mood,
as 9th Princess wants
to cancel the wedding.
Look at her temper.
She will definitely cancel the wedding.
I would take her away,
instead of letting someone else
take her away.
But I didn't realize that
she is smarter than I thought.
She used the blood night-blooming cereus
to make a deal with me.
No wonder I am in love with her.
Does 9th princess know everything?
Yes, but not all.
One thing I don't understand.
What's up?
She was so confident
about finding the cereus.
We were together all the time.
And we shared the same clues.
Did I miss something?
Your Highness.
You have seen this account book
for several times?
I must take the wrong way.
The key doesn't lie in the entries.
But the characters.
The characters?
Chang Kong.
Fetch me a scissor.
OK.
(Egret Villa)
That's it.
I even mocked her handwriting before.
Your Highness.
What's the matter?
If I don't make it wrong,
in order to hide the secrets,
Egret Villa's accountant
wrote with a magic pen.
On one side, the ink appears as normal;
On the other,
the ink disappears after a while.
When they were writing,
they reversed the pen.
Then without a trace,
one buyer became three ones,
and their purchases were dispersed.
I am sending someone
to inspect Egret Villa right now.
Wait!
People in Egret Villa aren't
ordinary ones.
They even deceived me.
Tian Ji Pavilion can
only find what they want us to know.
Your Highness, you mean?
I will go by myself.
Just take it.
This is the aloe vera honey facial mask.
And this is the almond facial mask.
These are ingredients.
Listen to me.
A woman should take care of her skin
as early as possible.
It becomes too late after the age of 25.
A Liang.
Just take it.
I made Werewolf cards by myself.
I think,
in this palace,
you are the most gifted player.
Keep going!
Hope you can promote this great game.
A Liang will never fail you.
Well,
it is late.
It's time to sleep.
Well,
A Liang will leave.
Good night.
Xiao Ai.
Go to sleep.
Why are you crying?
You will leave soon.
How did you know?
What you said
can cheat A Liang.
instead of me.
You are not sending gifts to us.
You are
bidding farewell to us.
(Xiao Ai,)
(why can't you play your lovely role?)
(How come you are being so smart?)
Xiao Ai knows clearly that
Your Highness will leave soon or later.
But...
But when you suffered a memory loss,
I thought you forgot about it.
But you didn't.
(What a plot!)
It seems you can't remember anything.
But,
your personality didn't change.
You are still stingy,
fooling around,
and keeping the same habit
of saving money.
Do you have to be so straightforward?
(Since you know I am about to leave,)
(then I...)
Then leave!
In my heart,
Your Highness is the most
important person.
And Xiao Ai hopes Your Highness
can find true love.
Xiao Ai.
Until now, I truly know that
you are the one who cares
most about me in the game,
and the one I trust most.
Your Highness!
No!
If you let me go,
what about you?
At most, they would beat me up.
Well.
How about going with me?
Alright.
But,
we have to steal
- another suit of A Liang's clothes.
- Alright.
We will soon get to
the north gate of the palace.
Who are you?
Damn!
Palace patrols.
What's the matter?
There are two eunuchs acting stealthy.
I suspected that they took something
out of the Palace.
I know them.
Their father is ill.
Life is at stake.
General permitted them
to leave the Palace tonight.
This is his permission.
(Their father is badly ill and they are
allowed to go home to take care of him.)
It was a mistake.
Take you time.
9th Princess.
You are Song Che's guard？
Yes.
General gave you these.
He said that it was conspicuous to
wear eunuch suits outside.
I have done what he said.
I am leaving now.
Thank you.
Though Song Che refused to help us,
he still did.
Let's go.
General Song.
I wandered over here.
Mengmeng.
Can you see
it rains heavily when you leave?
Forgive me I can't send you off.
I am afraid,
once I see you,
I can't let you go.
By using skills
instead of inner strength,
you are looking down upon me.
Mengmeng!
(Northern Gate of Palace)
Your Highness.
It is already midnight.
Where is Yun Ya?
(What is the plot?)
(Trick of missing the appointment?)
It will never happen.
Be patient.
Damn!
I have cold poison attack again.
No!
Mengmeng is waiting for me.
Mengmeng.
Why are you here?
It isn't safe in the palace.
So you are sending us off?
I…
I leave with you.
You may leave the palace,
but you can't leave the city.
No one knows the city
better than me, be it every corner
or every checkpoint.
In the past,
I followed the command
of Her Majesty and my father.
Now I want to rely on my own.
You are ambitious.
(He is not here now.)
(I guess he will never come.)
So let's go.
Alright.
Let's go.
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
I didn't see Your Highness
at the appointed place.
I am worried about you.
So here I am.
Your Highness.
You have cold poison attack again?
I am fine.
Song Che suddenly appeared.
He was a tough opponent.
I had to use
my inner strength.
What about 9th Princess?
She left with Song Che.
So what shall we do now?
There is a change.
We can only bid farewell to the Queen.
You said that Jiang Mengmeng
escaped from marriage with Song Che?
Yes.
Terrific.
I worked so hard
to stop them from getting married.
But she fled the palace.
Now Murong Chen
belongs to me.
But...
But what?
5th Prince left as well.
What?
Sister queen.
4th Princess.
- 4th Princess!
- Go away.
You can't break in, 4th princess.
Sister queen.
Sisi,
why are you
so mad this morning?
Let's apply this
aloe vera honey facial mask together.
9th Princess has left.
And you are still
caring about the facial mask.
All of you can leave now.
You don't worry about 9th Princess.
I...
Calm down.
Mengmeng and 5th Prince
will take a tour before the wedding.
Tour before the wedding?
I know my sister.
She will not be tamed
until she sees the outside world.
Your Majesty.
I request to bring back 9th Princess.
What if you couldn't make it?
If I don't bring her back,
I won't dare to marry her.
You are a determined,
and courageous person,
with the royal demeanour of Cang Yun!
Your Majesty.
I will protect 9th Princess
from any danger.
And
when I leave,
4th Princess can calm down.
Please allow me, Your Majesty.
I leave Mengmeng to you.
Young people are really full of ideas.
Far from our reach.
Sister queen,
why do you let them go?
It does not matter.
Our parents let us go as well.
It is different.
Sister queen, you are being partial.
No matter how 9th Princess acts up,
you always spoil her.
I raised
all of you.
I should be fair with each of you.
But do you know
why I favor 9th Princess?
Yes, I know.
When our Mother suddenly passed away,
you inherited the crown.
When 9th Princess
dropped into the river that year,
you blamed yourself
for being devoted to the work
and neglecting her.
Thus you felt guilty,
and wanted to compensate her.
I want to ask you one more question.
Do you want to be someone like Mengmeng,
or someone like me?
Of course, I take pride in sister queen.
I want to be someone like you.
Good.
Sisi,
I am aware of
what you are up to.
But you have to give up
something
in life.
I have no descendants.
So I will pass the crown down
to either you or Mengmeng.
She isn't interest in power and fame.
She only wants a happy life.
But you are different.
You are my hope,
the future of the Ruo Shui kingdom.
So you have to
give up something.
Sisi understands that.
I am being too capricious.
It's good you can understand me.
Think about it.
There are plenty more fish in the sea!
Next year you still have the chance.
Or the year after next.
I will find someone better for you.
A man who bears the
whole country in mind.
A man versed in both
literature and military affairs.
A man that shares the
same future with you.
Thanks, sister queen.
I understand.
(The Imperial City to Qing Luo Town)
(Finally in a new map.)
(Qing Luo Town)
Do you find it strange that
there are so few pedestrians
in daylight?
And each of them is in a hurry.
I find it a little strange.
But Your Highness.
What should you call me outside?
Childe.
Right.
What did you want to say?
I wanted to say
it is so late.
Maybe everyone is going home for dinner.
Look, there is an inn.
I'll check out if they have empty rooms.
You stay here.
Don't run about.
Ok, you can go.
Let's go, Da Huang.
Now it is two of us.
Xiao Mei.
I finally find you.
- Come home with me.
- I...
Wait! What are you doing?
Do you find the wrong person?
You are my daughter.
My husband, I found...
- My wife.
- I found Xiao Mei.
I found Xiao Mei.
You come home with me now.
Wake up, you find the wrong person.
Sir, what is the matter?
The only daughter in my family,
Xiao Mei has disappeared lately.
My wife missed her daughter so much
that she lost her mind.
She calls everyone her daughter.
These days she has been seriously ill.
She can't even distinguish the gender.
Did you request help from the officials?
To tell you the truth,
this month,
in Qing Luo Town,
fifteen girls have disappeared
without a clue.
Even the officials can't find them.
Fifteen girls!
You are lucky
as you are men.
Yes, we are lucky.
Sorry for our offence.
Please forgive us.
- I understand.
- We will leave.
- Excuse me.
Well, my wife.
Let's go.
Hope you can find your daughter.
Xiao Ai, I still feel strange
about this place.
I am a little afraid that
someone is following us.
Stay close. Don't turn around.
Let's go.
(Yi Chun Tavern)
Innkeeper.
Two decent rooms.
You are lucky.
We happen to have two rooms available.
Really?
How many of you will check in?
Three.
Two friends and I.
Please wait for a moment.
Where are they?
Childe,
how come there is
a stick in the package?
You'll need some weapon
when you are in the outside world.
You always fall for me.
Fall for you?
I was so scared of you.
Tell me
why you are following us.
To have a talk.
Who are you?
You want to return to Cang Yun kingdom?
Yes.
9th Princess escaped from the marriage.
I am an abandoned husband.
What else can I do?
You are not here to bring back Mengmeng?
If I want to bring her back,
will there only be Chang Kong and me?
That makes sense.
Well,
nothing serious now.
How about we split up?
Mind our own business. Right?
Wait!
What's the matter?
You are the 9th Princess
of Ruo Shui kingdom.
Why are you so irresponsible?
That day I was...
That day I was not intentional.
And,
we drank a lot.
Being so drunk,
we couldn't do anything.
That day...
I didn't mean it that day.
I wanted to say
you should be responsible for me.
Send me home.
Send you home?
Send you home!
So you agree?
You are setting me up.
I am sincere.
Think about it.
I travelled a long way
to Ruo Shui kingdom for matchmaking.
Everyone knew
I was the future 9th royal son-in-law.
But you escaped from the marriage.
If I returned home by myself,
it would be awkward for me.
Even if I get engaged
in the future,
everyone will laugh at me.
So,
you should be responsible for me.
Send me back to Cang Yun kingdom.
And take back your invitation.
Then we will officially break up.
In the future,
let's take care of our own marriage.
Do you think so?
Of course.
I figured it out that
I won't force you to marry me.
I won't force you.
Jiang Mengmeng,
I give up on you.
(When he said he gives up on me,)
(I felt a little bit sad.)
What?
You don't want me to give up on you?
Don't be a narcissist.
I even want to celebrate.
Then everything is fine.
We can be relieved.
Murong Chen.
A handsome man.
In term of the appearance,
family, and talent,
I am outstanding!
Why should I always
like you?
(That is to say...)
(Right.)
(Just because I play the leading role,)
(I thought I didn't have to choose him.)
(But he had to like me.)
(That's right. It must be like that.)
Murong Chen,
you should behave like this earlier.
I would be the nice guy
to send you up to Hea...
to send you back home.
That's a deal.
(If he goes back to Cang Yun kingdom,)
(he will go with Mengmeng)
(day and night.)
Objection!
Overruled. Overruled.
(Damn)
(I ignored these two.)
It is late.
Let's check out the rooms.
Right.
Xiao Ai.
- They two.
- We will pay the bill.
Stop watching. Let's go.
I know that
you break up with Mengmeng
as an excuse for stalling.
You still like her.
It is the same with you.
You stay close to her as a friend.
In fact, you
retreat in order to advance.
You also like her!
Don't worry.
I will send you back to Cang Yun kingdom
safe and sound.
Thank you.
Stop!
What are you doing?
I am
admiring the moon.
How come you
admire the moon on a cloudy night?
Stop it. Let's go.
What?
Only one room is available?
Two rooms were available
in the afternoon.
When you were away,
one room had been booked.
Someone here is
unreliable.
If you didn't come to mess up,
I couldn't miss the booking.
Well,
I can share the room with Mengmeng.
You find your own place.
I...
Stop!
It is all about a room.
The room isn't available in this inn.
- We can find another one.
- Let's go.
There's no need!
Qing Luo Town is a small place.
At this time,
the room isn't available in all inns.
If you don't make your decision,
you will miss the last room.
(Another trick of one room left)
How about this?
Our common room has two beds.
You two can sleep there.
And you three share the
last decent room.
No!
You are three men.
What is the matter?
I mean the room is too small.
Yes.
Well then,
waiter,
place another bed in their room.
Let's go to sleep.
You.
Sleep over there.
Mengmeng, let's go.
Why?
Because we grow up together.
We slept together since we were kids.
Are you saying I haven't slept with her?
Mengmeng and I are still a couple.
I am entitled to sleep with her.
Mengmeng, let's go.
You will break up.
If you sleep with her,
you will ruin her reputation.
You are a healthy bachelor.
If you sleep with her,
you will not ruin her reputation?
Stop!
Both of you want to sleep with me?
Yes.
How about you sleep together?
Is the bed small for you?
A small bed is never comfortable.
But we are rough men.
We can put up with
inconveniences tonight.
No big deal.
I am rough?
I am not rough as you!
Are you rough or not?
I am rough.
Mengmeng, just go to sleep.
I can put up with
inconveniences tonight.
Alright.
Stay away.
Give me that.
No.
Give me.
- No!
- Give me!
No means no.
There isn't enough room for me.
And you want to take the quilt.
You can only blame
yourself for being thin.
Just take it.
Don't you dare wake up Mengmeng.
No. I said No.
No.
Earthquake?
Why are you so passionate?
I want...
What do you want?
I want to ask you if it is too crowded.
Yes.
I.
I'd rather sleep outside.
Breakfast is ready.
You guys are good.
You didn't sleep at all,
and you owe the inn one bed.
Well, just eat something.
Save some food
for Xiao Ai and Chang Kong.
Did you hear that?
Last night, another girl disappeared.
Again?
And,
she disappeared in this inn.
For real?
So weird.
Now all the girls of this town
have been sent away for safety.
I think the criminal
must keep an eye on the girls
from the outside.
I am full. Let's go.
Well, where are Xiao Ai and Chang Kong?
Xiao Ai disappeared.
What?
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪