[English subtitles are available]
[Ji Sung]
[Kim Min-jung]
[Jinyoung]
[Park Gyu-young]
[Moon Yu-seok]
[Choi Jung-gyu]
[The Devil Judge]
[This drama is set
in the dystopian future of Korea.]
[All characters, organizations,
places, and events are fictional.]
[A New Leap for the People]
[Home of Dreams Becomes a Reality.]
The Social Responsibility Foundation
is accepting donations
for its "Home of Dreams" project.
However, I received a tip
that all the money for the project
[is actually being used elsewhere.]
These are the key people
behind this project.
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
Let's find out exactly what
your donations are being used for
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
and the real purpose behind this project.
I'll compensate anyone
who sends in a tip with my own money.
That is my promise to you.
[Thank you all.]
[Social Responsibility Foundation
Suspected of Embezzlement]
What's wrong with that Kang Yo-han?
How dare he puts the heads of the state
on a wanted list?
[Episode 7]
I can't believe my network aired
my face for something like this.
Hey, Mr. Park.
You think that's the problem?
He technically declared war
against the country.
This is a rebellion!
How dare he attack the heads of the state?
We stole our people's money?
That's just ridiculous!
To help out those poor people,
I donated my precious money.
And it was a hefty sum too.
So this is the result
of doing a good deed?
What's up with Kang Yo-han?
Is he a left-wing socialist?
What on earth is Mr. Seo doing right now?
He just sent his secretary?
How on earth is he going to fix this?
I know this is off-topic,
but it seems to me
that you are very worked up right now
when this is nothing
but a groundless suspicion.
Am I wrong?
Of course. This is a groundless suspicion.
Why would you put it like that?
Be more careful.
How dare he play us like that?
Who does he think we are?
Exactly. Don't you know
what that money means to us?
You kidnapped Jang Ki-hyun, didn't you?
I needed to talk to him.
"We must get our story straight
to fool the entire country."
"If you don't comply, you could be
in danger as well." Something like that?
Don't be so harsh.
You got the details wrong,
but my big picture is what you just saw.
Wrong?
Did you really help him out
because his story was heartbreaking?
You didn't promise to pay him
if he did everything you asked him to do?
It's possible that I found his situation
heartbreaking from the get-go.
Why are you jumping to conclusions?
Anyway, you weren't
behind the attack on Soo-hyun.
It sounds like you believe me now.
And that I wouldn't do such things.
You are very capable of doing so,
-but there was no need for that.
-"Need"?
You must have gotten Jang Ki-hyun
after finding out
Cha Kyung-hee got his bank statement.
So it wouldn't matter to you
if Soo-hyun who showed up out of the blue
took his bankbook or not
and you wouldn't have gone after her.
If you are this smart
to figure out what happened,
why did you go berserk
and lose all of your rationality?
You're the last person to ask me that.
After all, you almost killed me because
I took Elijah out for a quick meeting.
Then, who attacked Soo-hyun?
I know that at least it can't be
anyone who thinks favorable of me.
[Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
What on earth is Mr. Kang plotting?
I thought that foundation
was doing good deeds.
Don't they help people in need
and do volunteer work?
Ms. Oh.
There's something I didn't tell you.
What?
[Why did you guys leave me out of that?]
[Live Court Department]
[Associate Judge Oh Jin-joo,
Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
A secret party only key members
of the foundation attended?
So only the two of you went
to that secret party without me?
I even have a really expensive dress
Mr. Kang got me for the last fashion show.
I'm really sorry.
But of everything I told you,
I'm sure that's not the only thing
you're upset about.
I know. Getting involved in the trials
to get what they want
is so inappropriate.
Should we expose them to the press?
I do know a reporter.
-A reporter?
-Yes.
Gosh. She does work for
a fashion magazine called Bling Bling.
No.
Let's go over this again
and talk about this.
So these rich scumbags
including the President gathered around
and got involved
in Lee Young-min's trial. Right?
And they are probably trading favors
during investigations.
Right.
-Sorry for not telling you sooner.
-What about Mr. Kang?
-Pardon?
-What did Mr. Kang say to them?
Is Mr. Kang on the same side with them?
Why aren't you telling me about that?
I don't know.
At the meeting, he didn't say anything.
But seeing how
he's taking this matter head-on...
I don't know
if he's doing it from the bottom
of his heart or pretending.
It is true that
he gave money to the witness.
How can a judge do that?
The press conference he just had
is nothing but a show.
And then, out of nowhere,
he made the public take a vote.
I feel like he's deceiving us.
I was a huge fan of Mr. Kang.
I thought he was confident and righteous.
He sparkled like a star.
To be honest, I'm not sure about him now.
[Be more ambitious.]
[Among everyone
at the live trial I watched,]
[you were the shiniest one.]
It was blinding.
[If you wish to obtain a star
that is shining from afar...]
[If you desperately want]
[that star,]
[you should improve yourself first.]
[Be someone magnificent]
[who can]
[reach the star.]
Perfect.
-Sun-ah.
-Yes?
Gosh. Why is your skin glowing today?
What a surprise.
A compliment from a cranky girl like you?
Are you feeling guilty about something?
I'm just jealous.
Right. What should we do with this?
The bankbook I took from Yoon Soo-hyun.
The seed?
Throw it out.
Seriously. You're such an awful boss.
If you don't even need it,
why make me take it?
Who says I don't need it?
I need it to write my story.
Your story?
You don't have to know that.
Now, what we do now will matter.
Keep a close eye
on those geezers from the foundation.
Not Kang Yo-han?
My wolf made
a much more aggressive entrance
to the farm than I had expected.
The sheep will be chaotic
because they are scared.
Okay.
Right. Sun-ah.
I think you will be the healing mentor
for the foundation's website.
Me?
Kang Yo-han put a photo of Seo Jeong-hak
and yapped about how he was
stealing people's donations.
Reporters will swarm
if they find out about his lecture.
Gosh. I don't like giving
those feel-good lectures.
Jae-hee.
Yes?
Had you arrived there a bit sooner,
you could have gotten
Jang Ki-hyun before him.
Am I wrong?
I'm sorry.
I had no idea that
a judge would take things that far.
Do a good job.
Can't you?
I can.
I won't make another mistake.
We only have one more step to go.
You know that, right?
You. If I catch you doze off
during Mr. Seo's lecture,
there will be consequences.
Okay.
Gosh. You kids are so sickening.
Hello, ma'am.
Are you from the foundation?
Mr. Seo is late today.
Hello. I came here
in place of Mr. Seo today.
This is Senior Director Jung Sun-ah.
I see.
Welcome, Ms. Jung.
You look so beautiful.
How old are you?
I'm 18.
She's beautiful, right?
Go upstairs now.
Go now.
Excuse me, ma'am.
They are either orphans or runaways.
They can be quite nasty.
You should keep an eye on your values
when you approach them.
They are nasty?
Pardon?
You must have your plate full, ma'am.
Don't mention it.
Shall we go upstairs now?
[Social Responsibility Foundation
Mentor Lecture]
[Sun]
Darn it. What's she trying to say?
[Sun-ah]
This is my name.
"Sun" means "good",
and "ah" means "child".
[Sun-ah]
I'm all grown up now,
but I still have to be a good child.
My mom must have hoped
that I'd grow up to be
an ordinary, good person.
Why did she do that to me though?
If that was her wish, why did she hit me
every time she was drunk?
I'm sorry.
Seeing you girls
[Home of Dreams Youth Welfare Center]
is bringing back memories,
but I should stop being silly.
My mom did that too.
Really?
Normally, she was so nice like an angel,
but she suddenly changed
whenever she drank.
She'd start crying and...
It's because life is tough.
She must have been going through a lot.
I didn't really understand her back then,
but I do now.
Her husband had abandoned her
and their child.
And it was exhausting
to eke out a living all on her own.
Even so, she shouldn't have done that.
She shouldn't have done that
to her child, no matter what.
You see, I thought my mom hated me
because I was a bad kid.
I swore at people, got into fights,
and got in trouble for stealing stuff.
But at the time, I had no choice.
Everyone around me insulted me,
made fun of me,
or beat me.
And I was always hungry.
But you see,
when I was 12,
I started working for a wealthy family.
And the boys in that family
were so adorable and nice.
They smelled nice
and never used swear words.
They sparkled from head to toe.
Had I been as good as they were,
would my mom not have beaten me?
[Sun-ah]
Would she have loved me?
Well, my point is...
What should you do to be a good child?
[Home of Dreams Youth Welfare Center]
You have to become rich.
You can only be nice
when you can make ends meet.
This world is like a jungle.
How can you be nice to everyone
when you have to prey on others
and win to survive?
First, you must survive at all costs.
If others hit you, bite them.
And if you need something, just steal it.
And just so you know,
this world is a tougher place
for lonely girls like you.
Beasts are everywhere.
[Social Responsibility Foundation
Mentor Lecture]
No matter how educated
or admired they are,
all men are the same
at the end of the day.
If such dirtbags come on to you,
what should you do?
Report them to the police.
Wrong. You need to use it
to hold leverage over them.
The law is never on our side.
You must secure evidence no matter what.
Record whatever you can.
And then,
you can torment them
until the day they die.
Threaten them
to destroy everything they have
until they become your obedient dogs.
Okay?
-Yes!
[Social Responsibility Foundation
Mentor Lecture]
Yes, go ahead.
You have such a successful career now.
Then does your mother love you now?
My mom died when I was 12.
She got really drunk
and fell down some stairs
in the neighborhood.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's all in the past anyway.
My gosh, your lecture was
so refreshing and realistic.
I was so moved, Ms. Jung.
I haven't given many lectures.
I'm sure it could've been better.
What are you talking about?
You did such an amazing job.
That said, we'd love to have you back
for another touching lecture.
Sure.
Then please invite me again
for another lecture.
Yes, of course.
How did you find me?
Did you put a tracker on me or something?
Didn't you already find it?
Why are you even asking?
I get to decide where I go and who I meet.
The decision is solely up to me.
Who are you to decide?
Whether you like it or not,
I am your guardian.
"Guardian"? You treat me like
I'm your pet or something!
Haven't you learned your lesson yet?
No one approaches you without a motive.
Aren't you sick of it now?
You always act like the smartest one,
but you follow anyone
who shows any interest in you
and end up being used and kidnapped,
like a complete idiot.
Enough.
Is it her fault that she feels lonely?
Don't talk to her in that manner.
How dare you lecture me on how to talk?
She's under my protection.
That's right. You're the only one she has.
Can't you be a little more honest
for once?
This is ridiculous.
How long have you even been here?
You think you know everything?
I apologize if I was out of line.
Let's go.
Butler.
[Yes, Master.]
How can I have a conversation
with a teenage girl?
[Let me see.]
[Experts say you should first listen
from the other person's perspective.]
[It's important to use positive language
to help improve the self-esteem of--]
Forget it.
Just order some books about it.
[Yes, Master.]
You asked me why I said I was
a restaurant owner's son for 16 years.
Remember?
That's when my parents
passed away.
The year I turned 16.
Oh, really?
What happened?
Was there an accident or something?
They were conned by an evil con artist
and lost everything.
My father took his own life.
As for my mother, she collapsed
from the shock and ended up...
I see.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Gosh, I never know what to say
in situations like this.
It's okay. It's been a long time.
Right, but it's not something
you can forget easily.
That's true.
It must've been so hard for you.
It was the same for me.
I hated being home alone,
so I slept anywhere
and hung out with anyone.
I was lonely,
like a stray dog.
You're strong, Elijah.
-Am I?
-Of course.
You got through everything on your own
in this giant house.
You're amazing.
Why are you suddenly being nice?
That's not like you.
I thought you were the snobby type.
Is it too obvious?
It's certainly not easy saying things
that I don't mean.
You want to fight me?
You've got some strong smacks.
I wonder who you got that from.
Goodnight.
Will be less stubborn...
[How to Talk to Your Child in Puberty]
I must smile as I talk to her.
I can smile.
All right.
What is it? It's you?
What's with that face?
What do you want?
I must smile as I talk to her.
-I...
-If you don't have anything to say, go.
-How has your day been?
-What?
Well, was it a good day?
Or was it a bad one?
Is there anything we can talk about?
Well, you know...
What is it?
That bad guy who scammed Ga-on's parents.
What kind of person is he?
Is it Ga-on again?
Right. I must smile as I talk.
He scammed poor people
for billions of won.
There are a dozen of people
who committed suicide from the scam.
-Really?
-Yes.
I see.
So...
Come on! You've got to be kidding me!
Are you kidding me right now?
Everything will be fine
if I do as the book says?
[Sir, it's not good for your health
to be stressed.]
[There are supplements on the...]
-What are you doing?
[-You only need to take one a day.]
[It's important to look after your health
at your age.]
Whatever. Go away.
[Centrum]
[The Blue House]
We will now begin.
Regarding the unexpected statement
by Judge Kang Yo-han
at the last live trial,
we will carefully investigate it
from different perspectives...
That's fake news!
[The Blue House]
Hello, I, Heo Joong-se,
have gone through all sorts of things
to get here.
Now, even a judge of the country is
spreading false news about me.
How can a country be like this?
Is Judge Kang Yo-han, who's spreading
false news at this difficult time,
a true Korean national
that I love and respect so much?
The truth is,
I'm receiving many reports
on Judge Kang Yo-han as well.
People are saying that he is connected
to a foreign country to cause a mess.
What people are also saying is
that he's not purely Korean.
Meaning, he's different from us!
Not only so, but I've also been told
that Judge Kang Yo-han
is being paid
and controlled by a foreign country.
For the security of the nation,
if anyone reports anything
on Judge Kang Yo-han,
depending on the quality of the report,
I will give out a hefty sum of prize money
in return.
I will be very generous
with the prize money!
Are you paying out of your own pocket?
[The Blue House]
-That is all.
-Please answer us!
-President!
-What do you mean, "prize money"?
We will summarize the announcement
and publish it shortly.
[President Heo Leads Strong Response
to Judge Kang Yo-han's Statement]
Don't you think you're making moves
too bold?
Politics isn't comedy.
People are going to have a lot to say.
The more comic it is, the better.
-What?
-Once you're fixed
on comedy and competition,
you forget about the complex things.
You know why I said the better the report,
the better the prize money will be?
It's a competition.
I'm just going off the scale on the fun.
You're quite the man, honey.
I'll make them lose their minds.
[Is this okay?]
[What?]
[Ten years ago,
it was a mere famous actor,]
but it's the President this time.
Right.
It's the President,
the Minister of Justice, and the press.
So, basically, entire Korea.
[Chief Judge Kang Yo-han]
Exactly. You waged a war
against the entire country.
Is this going to be okay?
Do you know
how they gained their authority?
Through hypocrisy.
[Your small help improves Korea
for a better tomorrow.]
The more in danger people are,
the more appreciative they are
of the smallest things.
Since the epidemic, the foundation
aggressively expanded its charity work.
But what they spent the most money on
wasn't on the epidemic.
What was it?
Advertisement.
They used all sorts of platforms
to exaggerate their work.
They claimed it was all noblesse oblige.
They convinced people that the upper class
was owning up to their responsibilities.
They took over the politics using that,
so what do you think they could do next?
[Your small help improves Korea
for a better tomorrow.]
Reap what they've sowed.
No, more than that.
Their big Home of Dreams project,
in the end, uses people's money
to make a mass prison
to lock in all homeless people,
poor people, and whoever is against them.
It's their way of getting rid
of everyone undesirable to them.
Then,
they want to pursue
a large-scale city redevelopment project.
And they must've bought the lands
to be developed in borrowed names.
Do you have key evidence for this?
That can't be that easy, can it?
They blew up a judge's office
as if it was no big deal.
And yet you waged a war against them
in front of the whole country?
-It's fun.
-What?
It has to be fun at least,
if I'm hanging on the edge.
Is this fun for you?
[At last, justice will prevail in Korea.]
Don't you think you're being too reckless?
What about Elijah?
Have you even thought
about what'd happen to her?
Always.
All the time.
Give me all the documents
you've collected on the foundation.
Are you saying you'll help?
Just promise me one thing.
What is it?
Perjury, kidnapping, blackmailing,
and lying to fool innocent people.
I can't become a criminal
and commit shameful crimes.
For my parents who died because of fraud,
and for Soo-hyun.
A judge
[At last, justice will prevail in Korea.]
is at his strongest
when he goes by the law, Mr. Kang.
You cannot become a criminal
and commit shameful crimes?
A judge is at his strongest
when he goes by the law.
All right, then.
[At last, justice will prevail in Korea.]
Now that you've gotten
the public's attention with the question,
what's your next plan?
Division.
[Minbo]
If those who rule the world are together,
there's no way to win.
So, we need to shake them up first.
I think this should be
a good place to start.
[Minbo]
[Overwork at Minimum Wage]
[Minbo is An Evil Corporation]
[Min Yong-sik Must Resign!]
Yes. Thank you.
Which floor is the Chairman's office?
Judge Kang?
It's on the 20th floor.
[Overwork at Minimum Wage Kills Us!]
Hello, this is the reception.
Judge Kang Yo-han came.
Hello, Mr. Kang. Chairman Min is
having a meeting at the moment.
-I'll wait.
-Oh, okay.
This way, please.
-Please do whatever you have to do.
-Okay.
[7 minutes and 30 seconds.]
Sir, are you leaving?
-I'm done with my business here.
-I see.
[Minbo, Namsandaero 297-6, Jung-gu, Seoul]
Goodbye, Mr. Kang.
Hi, you said I should let you know
if something was up.
[Min Yong-sik must apologize!]
Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
0.5. 0.25.
[CEO Park Du-man of HMBN]
Hello, Mr. Park.
[We're Closed.]
[Come on and just tell me, Mr. Kang.]
Is there something I don't know?
You know, I'm always on your side.
You know the whole thing
about bribed witness issue.
Cha Kyung-hee did that.
Do you think you can handle it?
You made an enemy
of the entire foundation.
Is there anything you want to ask me?
I can tell you everything I know.
You're licking your fingers.
Hey, you must be hungry.
Sorry. I was inconsiderate.
Go get some food.
Now get out!
Get something expensive!
After all, this is all about
earning our bread. Right?
I'll catch up with you.
It's me.
So the person
my old man is seeing now is...
What?
Whatever he said when he met you.
Everything he said is a lie.
Whatever he gave you, it's all fake.
Whatever he says is a lie.
Whenever he talks, he tells a lie.
Since he was little...
All he cared about was
how he would beat me.
Back when he was in middle school,
he told everyone
that he was a college student.
I mean, think about it.
Why would I steal the foundation's money
when I have enough money?
Min Yong-sik is the only person
who would do something like that.
[And do you know how he married his wife?]
I'm talking about Ms. Pi.
It was in a nightclub.
She was drunk and...
Minbo Group is...
faced with a serious financial crisis.
I'll get you
the foundation's financial statements.
Of course, I got it all prepared for you.
Don't worry about it.
[I got it all ready
and I can give it to you right away.]
Whatever you heard from Min Yong-sik,
it's all a lie.
Don't let him fool you.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Eat up. Let's eat while we talk.
Try this. This place is pretty good.
[Standard Construction
Subcontracting Contract]
[Land Contract]
[Foundation's Business Plan]
Hello, Mr. Kang.
We would like you to come with us.
A VIP wants to see you.
This is unexpected, Mr. President.
What is?
I did not know
you would call me in this way.
It was scary.
I thought they would bury me somewhere.
Come on, Mr. Kang.
You put up my photo
before the entire country
and made a fool of me.
This wouldn't be a good time
to do anything.
But you know what?
It's probably a good time
because people would find it
hard to believe
that the President of this country
did something like that
in this troubled time.
Wouldn't that be fun?
While people are confused, time will pass
and after a few big celebrity scandals,
people will soon forget about it.
They're like goldfish.
That's a pretty good scenario.
You must be nervous, Mr. Kang.
The mighty Judge Kang Yo-han is nervous.
You look great in the suit.
By the way, you seem busy these days
meeting different punks.
That's right. Just like I am now.
I wonder what those punks
gave to you.
About that scenario
I talked about earlier...
It sounds fun, right?
I might as well just start the shoot now.
If you say so...
["Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot",
Start live-streaming]
What?
Hi, everyone.
This is "Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot".
Nice to see you again.
Today, the President invited me.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I just started to stream,
and we already have so many viewers.
We're getting so many comments already.
Yes, I am Judge Kang Yo-han.
Thank you, sir.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
You said you'd go over
the foundation's corruption issue.
-Well...
-He even invited me to the Blue House
to tell me that we should cooperate on it.
-Thank you so much, Mr. President.
[-Judge Kang.]
[-What? That's so sweet.
-The President is looking out for us.]
[Mr. President and I will work together]
[-I knew it. I believed in you.
-Let's get all the embezzlers.]
[to get to the bottom of
how your donations are being used.]
All right. This is it for today.
Shall we all shout it out together?
-A total change to Korea.
-To Korea.
This is "Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot".
-"Hits the Spot".
If you're a patriot, subscribe,
leave a comment, and like my video.
-Don't forget to turn on notifications.
-And turn on notifications.
You should wave at them.
With a smile.
Smile.
Hey. You're already done
going over the materials?
-That's impressive.
-They made it sound complicated.
-But I did find a flaw.
-A flaw?
It's PR. They advertised it way too much.
They kept advertising that
the foundation donated
10 or 20 billion won for the project.
They kept taking the credit
by publishing stories.
But it's way too much money.
Given the scale of the project,
the donations from the public
should be enough to kickstart it.
When they are using the donations
from the people,
they pretended and took
the credit for the donations?
It's just a suspicion for now.
I can only confirm it if I have
the ledger from the foundation.
The materials from Park Du-man
and Min Yong-sik
were fake, right?
Right. They doctored the documents
to frame each other for embezzlement.
Those sly snakes wouldn't
hand over the documents that easily.
Did you get any tip-offs?
Nothing useful.
They are either prank reports
or fake reports to get the rewards.
I should still give them out.
-Pardon?
-The reward.
Why would you?
The tip-offs weren't useful.
What's important isn't the content.
It's the number.
I'll post the number
of tip-offs I got online.
We can make it look like
something crazy is brewing.
Do you know
the most important factor in deception?
It's your attitude. You must not
be hesitant even for a moment.
That's how people fall for crooks.
You sound like an experienced con artist.
I forgot.
You were burned by a con artist.
But this is different.
Have you seen a con artist who saves
the world with his own money?
[This evil con artist
scammed 800 billion won!]
Punish Do Young-chun.
[Punish Do Young-chun!]
[Punish him!]
[Punish Do Young-chun who scammed]
[Bring my son back!]
[-my family in a pyramid scheme!
-Punish him!]
[Punish Do Young-chun!]
[Yoon Soo-hyun]
[-Punish him!
-Punish him!]
He's responsible for my family's death.
Execute Do Young-chun!
-Execute him!
Punish Do Young-chun!
-Punish him!
-Execute Do Young-chun!
-Execute him!
[-Execute him!
-Execute him!]
[Execute Do Young-chun!]
[-Execute him!
-Execute him!]
[Execute Do Young-chun!]
[-Execute him!
-Execute him!]
[Punish Do Young-chun!]
[-Punish him!
-Punish him!]
[Execute Do Young-chun!]
There he comes!
-There he is.
-He's here.
[Emergency Transport]
-Do Young-chun!
-Bring my family back!
-Punish him.
-That scumbag.
How dare you!
[1B8 70618]
[Don't do it.]
[Don't ruin your life
for a scumbag like him.]
[He's not worth it, Ga-on.]
[-Thank you.
-Thank you.]
I'll be discharged soon.
Why do you keep visiting?
What a nuisance.
What happened to the girl
who was complaining this morning
about not having any visitors?
Care to protect the patient's privacy?
Come on.
Is the doctor outside?
You were?
By the way, what on earth
is Kang Yo-han plotting?
I think he's scamming everyone.
What is it?
You should rest up.
You need to recover first.
I have no time to rest.
There are so many things I must check.
He fabricated the testimony.
And I must get to the bottom of the fire.
Elijah. Is she doing okay?
It must've been so tough.
She was so young and alone.
She didn't remind you of me
when I was young, right?
You shameless man.
How can I compare you
to that beautiful girl?
You need to have an objective idea
about yourself. Got it?
Got it.
I'll get going. You seem fine.
No matter how bothersome you are,
you still came to see me.
Do you want to have some?
Gosh, Soo-hyun.
Let's see how well you can peel an apple.
All right. Let's see.
What are you doing?
-Soo-hyun.
-Yes.
I'll peel it.
You tend to peel off more than the skin.
Gosh, you're so brutal.
[Judge Kang Yo-han]
[Accounting Department]
[has received over 20 tips
about the corrupt deeds]
[that the Social Responsibility Foundation
allegedly committed.]
[The Foundation hasn't released
an official statement yet,]
[other than stating
that they're groundless allegations.]
[Meanwhile, the national petition
demanding an investigation]
[National Petition Signed
by Over 100,000 People]
[has been signed
by over 100,000 people...]
No more slacking off.
Let's get some work done.
Hey, I heard they pay you
even for tips about nothing major.
And I heard you can get paid quite a bit.
Really?
I'll have a lot of expenses next month.
Should I do it too?
[Overdue Payment Reminder]
You'll get in trouble if you get caught.
"We strongly support Kang Yo-han"?
Gosh, these opposition party jerks.
"The live trial is just a show
to attract the public's attention."
"There's a risk of
human rights infringement."
They said stuff like that and acted
like some enlightened aristocrats.
That's how politics work, you know.
An enemy's enemy is your ally.
By the way,
you two gave something to Kang Yo-han.
What was it?
Nothing, really.
I just tricked him
to mess with him a little.
So you can mess with me as well?
Goodness, what do you take me for?
Anyhow, it'll only get him in trouble
if he looks further into it.
What about you? What did you give him?
Planning to start a broadcasting business
if I'm gone?
That's a good idea.
-You rude jerk.
-Let go, you prick.
You two fighting like this...
Who'd be most excited to see this?
When a castle collapses,
it usually starts from within.
Get it sorted out before it's too late.
Kang Yo-han will make a move
without letting us catch our breath.
[Sir, I'll connect you to Kang Yo-han's
emergency press conference.]
What's going on?
[Live Court Department Holds
Emergency Press Conference]
[Informants]
Tips are pouring in.
Many brave informants are coming forward
to help us uncover the truth.
Thanks to all the brave informants,
the foundation is changing its attitude.
I'm sure you all saw
the President's most recent video.
[A total change to Korea.]
[This is "Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot".
-"Hits the Spot".]
[Informants]
[There's something else
that will surprise everyone.]
Two of the foundation's board members
gave me something,
saying it was an accounting report.
-What?
-Seriously?
-What's that?
-What is it?
-What is that?
-What's going on?
It's very interesting.
Apparently, they hired
a family-owned business as a subcontractor
to purchase land
for the project in advance.
However, the two reports I received
are telling me very different stories,
[so I'll have to look into it.]
But that's not the only problem.
Please take a look at this.
[Donations to secure the site
for the Home of Dreams project]
[Donation Details]
This astronomical amount of money
that was donated to the foundation.
Where did it all go?
[Donation Details]
Judge Kim Ga-on here
combed through the foundation's
accounting records and found out
that the total amount of the donations
and the actual amount received
by the foundation do not match.
Did you actually obtain
the foundation's accounting records?
["Live Court Show"]
Yes.
We have a brave whistleblower.
If the amount doesn't match,
does it mean someone embezzled the money?
It's either that,
or they never made such donations
in the first place.
[Will SRF's Alleged Corruption
Be Uncovered?]
Is Judge Kim Ga-on joining you
on this investigation?
["Live Court Show"]
Yes, he is.
As you all know...
[I object.]
Everyone knows that Judge Kim Ga-on
is an uptight man of principle.
But I'm sure none of you knew about this.
[Restaurant Owner Couple Dies
After Falling Prey to Fraudster]
-What's that?
-My gosh.
[Restaurant Owner Couple Dies
After Falling Prey to Fraudster]
[Many Fell Victims
to This New Type of Pyramid Scheme]
This is about Judge Kim Ga-on's parents.
[Restaurant Owner Couple Dies
After Falling Prey to Fraudster]
[Many Fell Victims
to This New Type of Pyramid Scheme]
[Restaurant Owner Couple Dies
After Falling Prey to Fraudster]
Mr. Kim overcame such hardship.
And that is why he could not
just stand by and watch
the entire nation get fooled
by such hypocrisy.
After we take all measures
to protect everyone who has sent us a tip,
we will reveal the content
of every report we received.
It'll happen right here,
a week from today.
Thank you.
Do you have an informant
inside the foundation?
Do you know the informant?
Mr. Kim, is the article
really about your parents?
-Is it true?
-Is this really true?
-Could you please tell us more?
-Just a comment, please.
Mr. Kim.
-Mr. Kim, give us a comment.
-Just a comment, please.
-Mr. Kim.
-Please tell us more.
-Just a moment.
-Mr. Kim.
-Mr. Kim, just a moment.
-Do you know the informant?
-Just a comment, please!
-Wait!
-Mr. Kim!
Was this your plan all along?
Am I just a tool in this scheme of yours?
You're no different from them.
Is it okay to use whatever you can grab
to achieve your goal?
"I can't become a criminal
and commit shameful crimes."
"A judge is at his strongest
when he goes by the law."
Don't you think you're a bit too naive?
This is war.
What do you plan to reveal next week?
Forged accounting records?
Tips that don't even exist?
Even if it takes more time and effort,
we should punish them properly
according to the law.
Is that so? I suppose you were satisfied.
You must've been very touched
by the judgment of the fraud
who got your parents killed.
-Shut your mouth.
-Just like you said,
they followed all the rules and protocols
while putting up with the tricks
pulled by those expensive lawyers.
After the long, drawn-out trials,
he was sentenced to 17 years in prison.
Were you satisfied with that?
Is it the "justice" you always talk about?
Watch what you say.
Ordinary citizens like my parents
sat on the jury
and arrived at the decision
after long, careful consideration.
It was the conclusion they arrived at
in accordance with the law
despite all the tricks.
That is the system.
Even if we hate it,
that is how the system works.
Is that what you had to believe
in order to live?
Is that what Yoon Soo-hyun
and Min Jung-ho,
the two people you have left in your life,
persuaded you to believe?
Have you been suppressing your desire
to kill him and take your life
by holding onto that belief?
Yes? Is that it?
Don't talk like you know everything.
Who do you think you are?
There's something I want to show you.
What the... What on earth is happening?
It's impossible.
There's no way he got his hands
on our accounting records.
Can you take responsibility for this?
What will you do if it's true?
He said he'll reveal everything in a week!
The entire nation will be watching.
What are you going to do about this?
-But rating-wise, I'll hit the jackpot.
-You...
That's enough!
You prick!
You see, I know this
because I'm good at poker.
Kang Yo-han is bluffing right now
because he's holding no good cards.
However,
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
if Kang Yo-han doesn't have cards,
he'd make his own
without batting an eye.
We need to cut his hands off, then!
This is a big game
with the whole country watching.
You three voluntarily made
the game even bigger.
Now, in order to expose
that Kang Yo-han's cards are fake,
we need to expose our cards, too.
Are you okay with that?
The exaggeration of your donations
isn't the only issue.
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
An entire log of what the funds
for the Home of Dreams are used for,
plans for future spending,
and the true intention behind the project.
Ms. Jung!
I'm sorry.
I guess I crossed the line.
So, what are you saying?
How are we going to clean this mess up?
We have
Mr. Seo.
[A fast prayer in session
for the salvation of the country]
So, does this mean
that thanks to Kang Yo-han,
this old man will get another chance
to live again?
[285 S 7511]
He's here.
-Sir.
-Hello.
I know we can't really see you
during your prayer,
but thanks for coming out to meet us.
You all look very exhausted.
What is it?
Are you all anxious
because of what's happening?
Yes, it's a disaster, sir.
We'll need to clean the mess up soon
before it's too late.
I think my employees are starting
to turn away too.
I'll take care of it.
If you're going to help us,
we'll have nothing to worry about!
That's right.
Sir, you're the only one who can
clean this mess up in this whole country.
Indeed. You're the only one.
The only remaining true teacher.
The true adult.
Don't exaggerate.
Anyway,
when I appear before the public myself,
the people, who are being played
by Kang Yo-han,
will calm down.
There's no need to address
every little thing.
You're right, sir.
The thing about the people
is that once you get their attention,
their entire opinion shifts.
You're amazing.
You're precisely right.
However,
we do need to throw something at them.
What do you mean?
The public becomes quiet
only when they're given something
to nibble on.
Something to distract them.
Who do you have
in mind?
We all know who.
The one who's been taking care
of the entire foundation
while I've been busy
praying for the nation.
Do you mean Ms. Jung?
Ms. Jung is a very competent woman
who gets her job done.
She's merely our slave
at the end of the day.
Haven't we kept her around all this time
so we can use her at a time like this?
What do you want to do with Ms. Jung?
How do you want to use her, sir?
If we were to blame everything on her,
she wouldn't just stay quiet.
Then, first,
we should find a way
to make her keep her mouth shut.
-Right?
-Of course.
Forever.
So that she can't say anything
even if she's blamed for everything.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Forever.
[285 S 7511]
[Righteous correction
for a brighter future]
What are you doing?
Get out.
[285 S 7511]
[Righteous correction
for a brighter future]
We're huge fans, Mr. Kang.
-We are!
The power!
-The power!
We look up to you, sir.
-We are!
-The power!
[Seonjin Correctional Facility
brings future.]
[Silence]
[Process for the meeting]
[If you have a dream,
you can get back up on your feet.]
[Seonjin Correctional Facility
brings future.]
Prisoner 70618.
Do Young-chun. Meeting in Room Seven.
Do you want me to go crazy?
You want to see me choke him?
You're terrible.
Prisoner 70618.
Do Young-chun.
[1B8 70618]
No.
He's not Do Young-chun.
He's a completely different man.
Something isn't right.
He's Prisoner 70618, Do Young-chun.
No, he's not.
He's not Do Young-chun.
No way.
He's a completely different man.
Special economic crimes,
violation on additional punishment,
sentenced 17 years in prison.
Name, Do Young-chun.
[Do Young-chun]
I don't know what this is about,
but his prisoner number, ID number,
and date of admission into prison
all match.
I didn't forget his face,
not even for a single day.
No. He's a different man.
Sir, what are you doing there?
Sir.
What are you doing there? Come on out.
Hey!
Let's go.
[With dreams, you can always start over.]
[Establish order, develop morality]
If anything can fabricate the whole thing,
it would be the entire system.
This is the system.
And the system is helpless against power,
which has absolute control
over the system.
[Develop morality]
[Establish order, develop morality]
You've been out.
No.
I just wanted to get some fresh air.
Oh, no.
Isn't fresh air too cold
for your old body?
It hurts your joints too.
No, I'm okay.
You're pretty old.
Is it because of me?
Because I've been disturbing you
with the thing I have on you?
No, ma'am.
It's my fault. I deserve it.
I can't blame anyone.
Are you sure?
Gosh. You're amazing.
If I were you, I would've resented me.
Those who do mindfulness exercises
are different indeed.
Remember?
When I first came here
to take care of you,
I was pretty young.
Right.
You were young.
Why did you do that?
Why did you do that
to the poor young girl
who had nowhere to go?
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
I didn't get to cry.
Stand up.
Let's stop this.
I forgive you.
What?
Because you're an important person.
You're the person to fix this country.
I'm done talking now.
Don't worry.
Everything is going to be all right.
You're dying an honorable death
as Mr. Seo.
And you don't deserve it.
You don't deserve it at all.
It's too good for a scumbag like you.
[Chairman Seo Jeong-hak
of Social Responsibility Foundation]
[has passed away.]
[Rest in peace, Seo Jeong-hak]
He has taken his own life
to take responsibility
for the suspicion of embezzlement.
The employees who embezzled the money
removed all evidence and fled.
Mr. Seo was devastated to find this out,
and ended up sacrificing himself.
[Chairman Seo Jeong-hak passes
at his age 76.]
[The death of this man
who has been spending his whole life]
[helping the poor
and promoting the national spirit]
[Announcement: Chairman Seo of
Social Responsibility Foundation passes.]
[is saddening the entire country.]
[Rest in peace, Seo Jeong-hak]
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
Let me introduce the new leader
of Social Responsibility Foundation,
Ms. Jung Sun-ah!
[Jung Sun-ah, the new Chairman
of Social Responsibility Foundation]
[Social Responsibility Foundation]
[The Devil Judge]
[Special thanks to Jung Eun-pyo
for his guest appearance.]
[My goal was to go back to the world]
[he kicked me out of
and to be the master.]
[Once a monster gets out of control,]
[you can never stop it.]
[What are you doing?]
[The show must go on.]
[The public support is our only weapon.]
What is Kang Yo-han's intention?
You knew I'd be upset to see
that you don't care.
We need to get rid of
any elements of risk.
[You and I are alike.]
Is that why you like me?