[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 17]
I didn't expect Doctor Ling
to get married so early.
Yes
I always thought
he will be together with
the Medical University Talented Girl.
Medical University Talented Girl?
Who's that?
Fangning, you didn't know,
when I first entered the medical college
I heard many things
about Dr. Ling's Deeds.
It can be said
Doctor Ling is the
idol of all of us.
As for this Talented Girl
Yu Shiyi.
She's the White Moonlight
in our hearts.
What do you mean?
Everyone was there every night
to watch the moonlight.
But this White Moonlight
only follows Dr. Ling.
I heard that the two of them
could stay in the library all day.
Or in the laboratory.
And
they even conducted an autopsy on the same corpse.
You talk too much.
It's okay, go on.
Well, Fangning.
It's like this.
This is just a rumor in the university.
Like every other school
has its top ten singers.
You don't have to worry about it.
It's okay.
I know all these.
Aren't these all in the past?
Yeah.
When we were young.
In the past.
Don't mention it.
What are you guys talking about?
You guys look happy.
About your ex-girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend?
That one.
Yu…
Yu Shiyi.
Shut up.
Are you and that Ms. Yu
still in contact now?
She's studying in Germany.
We email each other occasionally
about our research progress.
You okay?
Fangning.
What happened?
It's all your fault.
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Hello.
The works of more than 30 artists are on display today.
These are Nordic paintings.
There are quite a few
are from some famous collectors
who put the art on display for the first time.
Mr. Lu,
I trust you will love them.
Hope you can pick
something you like.
Thank you.
Well, Mr. Lu.
And your secretary.
Please Enjoy.
I shall excuse myself.
What the heck.
How did I become your secretary?
Don't mind him.
He was just talking casually.
I'm obviously your girlfriend.
This painting is not bad.
This one is not bad, too.
What do you think?
Are you okay?
Director Lu, today is the weekend.
Your miss secretary
is getting off work.
Are you angry?
Not really.
Today we are not in the company.
I want to experience
how it feels to be a girlfriend.
Okay.
Then I will explain to them.
Well.
You don't have to do it on purpose.
Come on, smile a little.
Look at your face.
If others see it they will think
you are my bodyguard.
I'm kidding,
don't take it seriously.
How about this?
All the paintings here.
Which one do you like?
I'll buy it for you.
For who?
Your secretary or your bodyguard?
Excuse me, Mr. Lu.
There is a reporter over there.
They want to interview you
about today's exhibition.
Okay.
I'll go first then.
Wait for me.
Miss, this way please.
Currently,
this is the one
with the highest bid.
Director Lu wants this one, then.
Also,
please double the bid.
Okay, no problem,
I will handle it.
Thank you.
I will buy it.
And give it to my bodyguard.
Bodyguard.
Welcome back babies
to my channel.
Today I am honored
to have received an invitation
from a Nordic painter
to see his exhibition.
I'm so excited.
Really.
I can't describe it in words.
Now,
I will take everyone
to have a good look
at this exhibition.
Come, shoot over here.
Get my good angles.
You must capture my
noble and elegant temperament.
I'll buy you a chicken drumstick tonight.
Sorry.
-It's you?
The paparazzi at Lu Fangning's wedding?
Ruining someone else's wedding…
You can't say that.
Looking at paintings?
Do you even understand them?
You…
How about you, you minx?
You paparazzi wench!
Jerk!
Small fry reporter!
A woman who only knows how to stomp her foot!
Whether you understand the paintings or not
you can't have them.
I'm sorry.
This painting is already mine.
How is this possible?
This painting,
is it bidden?
Mr. Lu just bought it.
Mr. Lu?
Which Mr. Lu?
Mr. Lu Yiyao.
Lu Yiyao?
Yes.
What does Lu Yiyao have to do with you?
He asked me to choose one.
This painting
is what he bought for me.
Excuse me.
Are you kidding me?
How could Lu Yiyao
spend this money for you?
I know.
Must be because of your
relationship with Lu Fangning.
So he…
He did this just to make me happy.
Gosh.
Are you dreaming?
How could Lu Yiyao
fancy you?
Look at yourself.
Do you know who is Lu Yiyao's
ex-girlfriend
and fiancee?
Are the people of the Lu family blind?
You are so ordinary.
How could he fall in love with you?
Lu Yiyao's taste
can't drop this much.
So you must be dreaming.
Miss Tang.
Please don't harass
my girlfriend.
Girl…
First of all,
My taste
I think.
Has nothing to do with you.
Secondly,
Miss Cai Siyu next to me,
She is no worse
than any of my exes.
Her good features
I don't think I need to
or am obligated to let you know.
In addition,
the way you wear a wedding dress
is really ugly.
You…
Let's go.
Stop shooting. Why are you shooting?
Why shoot him? Shoot me!
Shoot me, idiot!
What are you looking at?
There's nothing to see here.
Break up.
Shameful.
[Castfast Hotel]
I drank a little too much.
Thank you for the treat, Fangning.
I didn't.
Who did then?
It's the same if I did or she did.
Yeah, it's the same.
Hey, Fangning.
You seem like you have indigestion.
Should we go
help with your digestion?
Disco?
Let's go!
Well, then we will…
Oh, to the disco?
Why do you only think of disco
whenever we go out?
How does karaoke sound?
Professor Luo, you…
Then you young people go and play.
It's too loud there.
My heart can't stand it.
You guys have fun.
Goodbye, Professor.
-Goodbye.
-Okay.
Goodbye, Professor Luo.
Goodbye.
It's my treat.
Let's go.
Then let's go first.
We are going.
Goodbye.
If you don't want to go.
Then we…
You don't want to go, right?
If you don't want to go
I'll go.
Okay, now that we are all here.
First of all, please welcome our
Flower Couple
to sing a song, "I love You So Much".
Welcome.
Come come.
Come, Dr. Ling.
Don't be shy and go.
Yes.
Come on.
If you don't want to sing
we can say no.
I want to sing.
But I don't know how to sing this song.
Don't tell me at this age
you have never been to karaoke.
I came once,
back in college.
Just once.
Was it with that
Dr. Yu.
Yes.
I don't want to sing.
If they don't want to sing.
Let's sing this.
Okay.
-Let's sing this.
-What's the matter?
Are you feeling uncomfortable anywhere?
In my heart.
The heart is on the left.
Is it because I can't sing the song you want to sing?
No.
I'll sing a song I know.
Let you listen to that song.
No need.
Ling Rui, let me ask you a question.
Is Yu Shiyi better at singing?
Or am I?
But I never heard you sing.
This kind of thing.
Do you have to listen
to get a conclusion?
Probably.
I'm thirsty, I want to drink beer.
Peng Bo.
Drink with me.
Cheers.
Fangning.
Do you know why
Ling Rui is called
the flower on the hill?
Hill flower.
The hill is tall.
The terrain is a bit high.
And high places are cold.
Sometimes it's easy
to freeze your brain.
So don't you
get down to his level.
Did he make you angry again?
Yes.
I asked him if I sang better
or the Medical University Talented Girl.
He said he could only tell
after listening.
That was not what I meant.
Stop talking.
No matter who
cannot beat your wife at singing.
Do you need to ask?
Fangning,
look, it's not just you.
Even if a singer was here
he couldn't tell the difference.
The key is,
the issue is,
the fact is,
I really sing better.
Me.
Yeah, I think so too.
Who are you?
You are his wife, right?
You two are
in a loving husband and wife relationship.
He and Yu Shiyi
were only ordinary classmates.
That's it.
Don't even talk about Yu Shiyi.
No one can compare to you.
What can Yu Shiyi compare with you?
Right?
Yes.
Listen, Fangning.
He is like this.
He is usually handsome,
looks smart.
When his brain is frozen
and he's dim-witted,
no one can argue with him.
Who's dim-witted?
Am I wrong?
For example, before we conduct surgery
he would always tell a joke.
He has been telling this joke
since university.
I told him
again and again
but he won't listen.
He thinks it's fun.
Tell me, is this guy stubborn?
-Stop it.
-He's just like that.
It's the same as when he confessed to me.
He asked me, "Did you have breakfast?"
"Did you have lunch?"
"Did you have dinner?"
Nothing else.
Right.
Cheers.
One more thing.
You know, before a surgery
we have to wash our hands.
He's so good.
The first one to go in and wash his hands.
Always the last one
to come out.
My gosh, those hands.
While washing his hands,
he talks to his hands!
You know?
He's like a pervert.
He does this at home too.
Always cleaning.
Forever cleaning.
And not only that,
he also asked me to wash my hands.
He's not satisfied after I washed it,
I have to wash it a second time.
You know what's the scariest thing?
What?
These hands
are just like his brother to him.
Even closer to him than I am.
Tell me, is he a pervert?
-Am I right?
-Yeah, pervert.
What pervert? Who is a pervert?
Ling Rui is not a pervert!
As a doctor
maintaining cleanliness
is very normal.
Moreover,
only when he is clean
his patients will be safe.
This shows that he is serious and responsible.
Did you hear that?
It's too difficult for me.
I know.
Don't be mad.
Okay?
Mom, I'm going out.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Sit.
You haven't been home recently.
What did you do?
Something.
You work at the front desk,
why would you be so busy?
I blame Fangning.
She did this to you.
This has nothing to do
with my sister.
Shut up.
Tell me honestly,
what are you doing?
Just meeting friends.
You have a girlfriend?
Mom, you misunderstood.
That's good.
What's her family like?
Does she have a sister?
That doesn't matter.
As long as her family has a solid foundation.
You should get married quickly.
Then your dad would be happy.
The inheritance is yours.
Mom, you think too much.
You know
I am not interested
in these things.
Are you short-minded or pig-headed?
Why are you not like me at all?
If you have nothing else, I'm leaving now.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Didn't I just say？
I'm meeting friends.
Girlfriend?
Take Mom with you.
Mom, you are thinking too much.
It's not convenient.
I'm going to study.
Study?
I didn't like studying when I was young.
What are you studying at this age?
I'm learning how to do business.
Live and learn.
Just leave this matter
alone to me.
I'm leaving now.
Don't leave. You…
[City Ballet]
Niuniu.
How is the class today?
Are all the students here?
They are all here.
They are all here, right?
Right.
There are so many people in class today.
Quite a lot of people today.
Stinky kid, I thought you were studying?
Mom, why are you here?
Why am I here?
You are not at home every day.
Coming to a messy place like this.
If your dad knew he would kill you.
Go home with me.
-Go home and study.
-Mom.
-Hurry up.
-You misunderstood.
Misunderstood what? Learning to do business?
Mom, you misunderstood.
Misunderstood what?
Let's go.
Fangyu.
Erfan.
Mrs. Lu is here too?
I told you.
Don't tell others.
In the case where
Ms. Lu finds out…
Finds out about what?
You're afraid if Fangning finds out about what?
You two were hiding from her.
What are you doing secretly?
Mrs. Lu, it's like this.
I've been teaching Fangyu recently.
How to do business.
How to manage the company.
Correct.
But this matter
was done secretly.
That's why I chose this place.
Because I and the person in charge here
are good friends.
They say here
is quiet and we won't be disturbed.
I really dare not
let Ms. Lu know about this.
Otherwise, my
pay and leave will…
I hope you can understand.
After all, I just want to live.
I understand.
Of course I understand.
Good son.
You finally understand.
Knowing how to learned behind Fangning's back.
Both of you are doing this is behind Fangning's back.
Mom is so happy.
But Mrs. Lu,
I'm afraid if you are here
we will get noticed easily.
Correct.
Oh, yes.
I'll go then. I'll go now.
Study well.
Mom is so relieved.
I'll make some soup for you.
To give you some nutrients.
Thank you, Mom.
I'll save you a bowl.
Good luck.
Mom, you're really leaving now?
Study well.
Teach him more, okay?
Goodbye, Mrs. Lu.
Goodbye.
You're awesome.
Then I'm leaving too.
Erfan,
thank you.
It's nothing.
No matter what you do
I'll support you.
And I heard that your mother
is bad at cooking.
If she really made my portion,
you drink it for me.
Erfan,
don't you have anything
you want to ask me?
So all these years
you've been secretly
learning ballet.
Yes.
More than ten years already.
You are hiding it very well.
If I didn't
happen to be working nearby
won't you be exposed?
It's usually fine.
I never thought my mother
would follow me today.
But this is nothing
shameful.
Why are you hiding from your family?
You don't know about this.
I mentioned it to my mom before.
She scolded me
for half a month.
Let alone my dad.
You also know my dad's temper.
Back then, my eldest sister
because…
Forget it.
By the way, Erfan,
I have something to ask you.
Erfan?
This one.
This is?
This is the male version of Swan Lake.
I know there's a
stereotype in most people's minds.
They think Swan Lake should be
for girls.
But this show,
I loved it since I was young.
The dance.
Now comes my chance.
This troupe
came to our school
and is casting the students.
I want to try.
Erfan.
Did you know?
Swan Lake is my elder sister's favorite
ballet.
When I went to see for the first time,
it was my sister who took me there.
After watching it
I was deeply attracted by it.
From that moment,
I feel that
it's the most important thing
in my life.
Now that I have a chance,
I want to interpret this dance
with my own methods.
After all,
this is the best gift I can give
to her.
That's very good.
I support you.
You know that
my parents are so strict,
they certainly won't allow me to do this.
Fangyu.
In the past,
I have a friend
who told me something.
Today, I will give these words to you.
Regret and frustration
are countless times worse
than fear.
So while there is still something
you want to do.
Just do it.
I support you.
Okay.
Next.
Stretch a little.
Come here.
Me too.
You can just line up here.
This role suits you well.
Your styling is also very special.
We will contact you later.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
-You're welcome.
-Goodbye.
Reporter Zhang,
I've been expecting you.
Please wait a moment.
I'll get the information on the performances.
In the future,
You have to write to us.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Okay.
A male version of Swan Lake.
[Ballet Troupe Registration Form]
Lu Fangyu.
Quite the unique last name.
I have a question.
Does the head of the Deer Sing Group
have a son?
Okay.
Interesting.
Sir.
There's a parcel for you.
Okay, you may go.
Okay.
How's my writing?
Great.
Amazing.
Awesome!
Oh my gosh.
Don't don't don't move.
Don't look!
Mr. Lu.
Why are you laughing so happily?
Why?
Look at what you did!
Look!
Look what you did!
Qiqi was sitting in the latest
Maserati model.
Smelling the gasoline at the gas station,
feeling a little uncomfortable.
Duan Muleng took out his gold card,
eyes staring sharply
at the gas station employee, and said,
"Air."
"Replace."
I think the author's brain
should be replaced instead.
Are you all right?
Fangning.
Why did you buy so many snacks?
I eat them.
Are they from Bai Jing?
No.
I bought them myself.
Here you go.
There are so many in the living room.
There are also in the kitchen lockers.
You'll be too full to have a proper meal.
I will eat it.
Stand properly.
Don't move.
What do you want to eat tonight?
I want to
eat you.
Hello?
Fangyu, open the door.
Listen to Mom.
Good son, have you heard?
Fangyu, Fangyu!
Son.
Your father is angry.
Don't you…
Open the door now!
I can hear you.
Quickly open the door!
Open the door.
Madam.
Sir said that
Fangyu must never go out.
You should leave him alone
so that he can calm down.
Good son.
I know
there must be
a misunderstanding, right?
When your Dad feels better,
explain to him
and solve this misunderstanding.
You are his only son.
He won't ignore you.
Open the door.
Open the door!
You make me so anxious, open the door!
Fangyu!
Fangyu.
Erfan.
How are you? You all right?
I'm fine.
Well,
I did it too thoroughly
this time.
I'm afraid I can only rely on you.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
If you leave now,
you can never come back again.
Ok.
-Let's go.
What are you doing?
Who are you guys?
-Come.
-Let me go.
Let me go.
-Let go.
-Let me go.
-Fangyu.
-Erfan.
Fangyu.
Let me go.
Save me, Erfan!
-Save me!
-Fangyu!
Let me go!
Fangyu!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, Mom.
Why did you escape?
Why did you run away?
How dangerous it was!
You…
How can you escape?
-Big Brother.
-Look, your Dad is angry.
Calm down.
He is still a kid.
Don't be mad.
Go.
Big brother.
Wen… Wenbin.
Well, he…
He knew it was wrong.
He knows.
If he knows, that's fine.
Dad, what are you doing?
Stop!
Move aside!
You have no right to do this!
This is mine!
Yours?
Everything on you
I gave it to you!
Even you are mine!
Son.
Dad, you can't cut it!
Let him cut it.
That is my thing!
-Let him cut it?
-How can you cut it?
-Mom will buy new ones for you.
Mom, it's not about money.
This is my dream!
What's happening?
I could hear you yelling
from the entrance.
Wonderful.
Fantastic.
Lu Wenbin, President of the Deer Sing Group.
What are you tearing apart?
A tutu?
Father and son fighting against each other.
Sexism.
What else?
Drama in a rich family?
I heard you have been doing ballet.
That's pretty good.
Finally,
you have found something you are good at.
In this house,
other than the both of us
who love money,
there's finally an artist.
Isn't this a good thing?
Pretty gorgeous.
I bet you spent a lot of money?
It's also the money of our Lu family.
Keep it away.
What a shame to cut.
Oh, right.
Ling Rui and I,
Aunt Gao.
Yes?
Put these dirty things away,
throw them into the sea.
-Okay.
-Stop.
-Stand aside!
-Don't move!
You!
Before coming, Ling Rui asked me
to talk to you
and be reasonable.
But I realized that people like you
can't be reasoned with.
The reason is right in front of you.
But you just don't want to watch or listen.
What did Lu Fangyu do wrong?
He did nothing wrong.
He is just doing
what he likes to do.
Big Sister.
Let him throw it and let him cut.
Anyway, I won't give up
my dreams.
I have loved dancing since I was a kid.
If it wasn't to not upset you
and not make mom sad…
-Don't say it.
-I have to say!
I won't think about anything else now!
Not even death!
Great, go then!
You can go die for me now!
Go what?
Say it.
What is it?
You can't say it?
After all, it's not your first time.
Say it, say it!
Fangning.
Anger cannot solve any problem.
Don't make yourself regret it.
Dad.
We're leaving now.
Let's go.
Go.
Lu Fangyu, come with me.
Big Brother.
Calm down.
I'll go.
I'll deal with it.
Don't be mad.
Okay?
Fangning.
Get in the car first.
Let me talk to him.
Fangning.
It's okay.
Take care of Lu Fangyu.
Speak.
How do you want to persuade me?
Give him some time.
You saw it just now.
Your dad is actually feeling quite bad about it.
It's been ten years.
Is that not enough?
What's the difference between this case
and my sister's?
Because he is too authoritarian, my sister…
You can't blame him for today's matter.
Fangyu's photo was sent by a reporter.
They are obviously
blackmailing your dad.
Your dad is also afraid
if something went wrong.
It might affect Fangyu's future
and Deer Sing's reputation.
Future?
He doesn't even know
what is the future Fangyu wants.
Take it easy.
He will understand.
I don't expect him to understand.
If he did,
it won't be like this now
to Fangyu.
Fangning.
Listen to me.
Fangyu's matter,
I will solve it.
These few days,
stop irritating your dad.
Whatever.
I don't want to
stay here anyway.
You will stay in the hotel temporarily, all right?
I've arranged everything for you.
Don't worry about the cost.
I will get Gao Erfan
to send you your luggage.
Okay.
Sister.
This time,
thank you so much.
You have called me a sister
so many times.
But this one just now was the most pleasant.
Lu Fangyu,
listen to me, all right?
Okay.
Regardless of your decision
in the future,
whatever you plan to do,
I will always support you.
So don't be afraid.
Okay.
All right.
Go.
Sister.
I'm really going up.
Stop talking to me
like a coward.
Go.
Goodbye.
Fangning.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Ten years have passed.
I thought he has changed.
Until I saw Fangyu today,
I realized,
he is still like that.
Fangning.
You don't have to treat everyone
as your enemy.
You don't have to
close your heart to everyone.
We are married now,
I am willing to share with you
my happiness and pain,
every part of my life.
I hope you can do the same.
If
there's something
that can make you happy,
I am willing to do it for you.
Thank you.
Ling Rui.
Can you accompany me to a place?
Before this,
I often come here alone,
standing right here
and observing the store.
Now,
I'll be with you.
You can watch it as long as you want.
Ling Rui.
Did you know?
I have been telling you before,
founding Infinite
is my wish.
Actually that's not true.
This is not my wish.
Founding Infinite
all this while
has been my elder sister's wish,
if
she hasn't left yet.