[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 08]
Flu
is contagious.
The effect's so strong?
What is in that soup?
Whatever, come on.
-No.
-Why are you hesitating?
-What are you doing?
-Come down.
We have to
talk about it tonight.
Why did you tie me up again?
I don't feel comfortable like this.
Ling Rui.
So,
you married me
just to legally get...
my...
Alright.
I completely understand
why you, Lu Fangning,
would do this.
It's just... Why me?
Why not you?
You're handsome and well-educated.
You have a good personality.
Of course, it's you.
Besides, you still owe me money.
You have to pay your debt.
It's perfectly fair.
Don't worry.
After I have a baby,
I'm not gonna bother you.
Our marriage
will automatically end in a year
as we agreed on the contract.
Of course,
the baby will be mine.
But, you're still the father.
You can see the kid whenever you want.
I would never stop you.
However,
if one day
you have a new relationship,
I'm not gonna let the baby
call that woman mother.
So,
you have never had any intention
to keep the father of the child?
I'm perfectly capable of handling
the risks and responsibilities
of raising a baby.
Besides,
I have a stable financial income
to give the kid the best possible life,
education,
and all my care and love.
I'll be with him as he grows up.
Why
does he need a father?
It's not a question of necessity.
Then what's the problem?
Ling Rui.
You've got to open your mind.
Think of it as
helping a lovely girl
who wants a baby,
but can't have one by herself.
I can't do this alone.
I can't do mitosis.
Of course, I need your help.
Ling Rui.
Look at me.
Being with a girl as attractive as me,
someone else would have been
attracted a long time ago.
Someone else?
So if it's not me,
you would've found someone else
to carry out your plan?
Can't I?
You can't!
Two mature adults
raising a child together
would meet a lot of problems,
let alone someone like you
who's childish and ridiculous.
Childish?
I thought of your feelings
and your ego,
so I stayed there
for such a long time,
and you call that childish?
Immature?
How do you know I'm immature?
Have you ever seen me doing anything
before you said that?
Anyway, I'm not going to
have a baby with you.
A baby should be a gift
to two adults who are in love.
We're not.
How do you know we're not?
I love you.
I like you.
No.
It's not up to you.
You're just saying no to anything.
Why are you such a pain in the ass?
Anyway, I'm not gonna
have a baby with you.
And, you will never do it
with someone else too.
I'm going home for a few days.
Ling Rui.
-Don't look for me.
-Ling Rui.
Ling Rui!
One more.
How about I feed it into your mouth?
Have you ever stopped eating?
Ling Rui.
Why did you come back at such late hours?
I have something to do.
What is it?
Why are you home so late?
Where is your coat?
My coat...
I left it at the hospital today.
I had surgeries all day.
I'm too tired.
I'm gonna go get some sleep.
Did you
have a fight with Lu Fangning?
Fight?
How could I possibly fight with her?
It's nothing like that.
I'm going to bed. Good night.
Well, off you go.
Are you hungry?
No, I'm fine.
What happened to Ling Rui?
Came back to his mother's house
in the middle of the night.
What are you talking about?
How could you
say that?
He's a man.
Can't he just come home?
She's not wrong.
You're his mother.
Sister.
Why don't you go to sleep? It's late.
Alright, go to sleep then.
Don't you want to sleep?
You're still eating?
Go to sleep.
No.
You...
Wait a minute.
Hurry up.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm just using the toilet.
Keep your voice down.
Look.
Ling Rui has been
cleaning up since the morning,
from this side to that side
and back and forth
for a long time.
Isn't it normal
for him to clean the table?
Cut the crap.
Is that normal?
When was
the last time he was like this?
Last time?
When was the last time?
Nothing like this happened before.
No.
Yazhi, go ask him.
-Go.
Ling Rui.
Did you fight with Fangning?
Return me my money.
I'll leave you to it then.
See? I told you I can't.
Why did you send me?
Sister, why don't you go?
Me?
He has always listened to you
since he was a kid.
He'll do whatever you tell him to.
You're his mother. Let's go together.
-Let's go, Yazhi.
-Let's go.
Ling Rui.
Today is the weekend.
Why don't you stay with your wife at home,
but come here?
Son, will you stop doing that?
You have been doing this
from here to there
and the other way around.
You haven't taken any rest.
Good boy, come here. Take a break.
Take a break,
okay?
Be good.
Hi.
Mom and aunts,
here comes your daughter-in-law.
What are you doing here?
Here.
Help me get the stuff inside.
Fangning is here.
Hi.
What's going on here?
I'm going to visit
a friend of mine who lives nearby.
Her little baby
is one year old.
These are all the things
that I plan to give her.
You have friends
who live at places like this?
Of course.
Alright, you take a seat.
I go get you some fruits.
Mom, please sit.
Hold on, hold on.
Sit here.
What is this?
These are socks for
the little babies.
With their little feet inside,
it's so cute.
It's so soft and tender.
Mom, look.
What's this for?
This is to put under the heads
of the little babies.
Their little heads on top of it.
Such a pleasant view.
This one's so soft, too.
Feel it, mom.
You opened the things
that you're going to give others.
How are you supposed to give it away?
No problem.
I'll just put it in later.
I can imagine
the little babies' little arms,
little feet
that look like little lotus roots,
soft and tender.
Imagine them kicking their little legs
and stretching their arms,
it melts my heart.
Do you like kids?
Of course, mom.
In the future,
when you have your own
grandchildren,
I'm sure you'd love them too.
Take a look.
Ling Rui.
Mom.
Do you remember the friend
you play cards with?
Which one?
The one who rarely talks, but plays fast,
and always lets you win.
Ever since she got a grandson,
you haven't seen her anymore.
Didn't you tell me that
she cried when she told you,
after having a grandson,
she was surrounded
by diapers and milk bottles,
and had to take care of the baby
all night?
So,
you think it's going to be
troublesome for you to have a baby?
It's a real pain in the ass.
I don't think
I'm gonna take care of your kids.
Is that right, sister?
Yeah, we won't.
Mom, I haven't...
Didn't you just say that...
Mom, I...
You know what? Never mind.
Please ask Ling Rui about this.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
What's up with all that?
Fangning.
Sit over there.
Move over and let me sit down.
Fanning.
Try this tea.
Thank you, aunt.
When I went out
for inspiration last time,
I watched the old farmer cooked this.
Aunt.
I've been preparing myself for pregnancy,
so I can't drink tea.
Look.
A lot of people think that
career-minded women like us
don't have time
to take care of the kids.
But it was a misunderstanding.
Look at me.
I'm fully prepared
to welcome
the baby.
Because motherhood is strong.
Our children are our backbones.
Isn't that right?
Aunt.
I'll drink it.
I apologize on behalf of Fangning.
She definitely didn't mean that
a woman without children is weak,
and her life is imperfect.
That's not what I was saying.
I know.
I won't take it personally.
Actually,
it's nice to have a kid.
But people like me
who choose not to have children
and live on their own
are also living
a good life.
Yes, of course.
Oh, Fangning.
You're pretty bad
with your languages.
"Motherhood is strong."
That's not how it's supposed to be used.
Aunt Yazhi.
I'm here.
Come, sit.
Aunt,
haven't you been
trying to find a job
and sending out resumes online?
Resumes?
Go ahead. That matters more.
Au... Aunt?
I'll go send out resumes.
Oh, I forgot to tell you that
Aunt Yazhi divorced,
and her ex-husband got the baby.
Be careful
with your words.
It's tasty.
Mom.
Come on in, kid.
Come on in.
Close the door.
Come on, come on.
Let me ask you something.
Sit, sit.
Out there, you just said that
you want kids
and then you said you don't.
What exactly were you thinking?
I don't actually
want a child
very, very much.
Besides, mom, you don't
want it that bad either,
do you?
I didn't say that...
Of course, I do.
You just said that
you don't want to take care of the kid.
No.
I was sitting next to Ling Rui,
so I had to say that.
Otherwise, he would
feel embarrassed.
Mom.
You might not
gonna be able to have a grandson
so soon.
What do you mean by that?
Since Ling Rui and I got married...
Never mind, it's okay.
What's going on? What do you mean?
Since you are married, then what?
We don't act like a couple.
Not like a couple?
It's exactly like what you're thinking.
There's nothing wrong with my son.
Nothing wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
Who knows?
A little orange peel.
That's enough.
-Oatmeal.
-Oatmeal won't do.
Don't move, don't talk.
Wolfberry, black sesame,
and green beans.
What is
Ling Rui thinking?
How am I supposed to know
what he's thinking?
Perhaps, he doesn't love Fangning.
What are you talking about?
How could he not
love a girl like Fangning?
Alright, stop talking.
It's already a mess.
Just figure out a way to fix this.
Alright.
Why are you still here?
Why should I leave?
I'll be right where you are.
Where else would I go?
Listen to me,
whatever you're planning
is not gonna work.
What are you talking about?
What could I possibly have planned?
Of course, I should stay
with my husband.
Right?
Mom, Ling Rui doesn't want to drink it.
Come on, Ling Rui. Drink up.
Drink up.
Drink.
Okay.
Mom, Ling Rui still refuses to drink it.
What's wrong with you, Ling Rui?
Just drink it.
You don't listen to mom now?
You don't listen to your mom now?
Go wash the cup.
Okay.
He drank up.
Come here.
I'll take a shower first.
Okay.
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Later,
when he's in the shower,
you should just sneak in.
-Shall I do that?
-Don't let him hear you.
I'll lock the door.
No one can see you.
Keep your voice down. Don't talk.
Mom, no.
Stop talking.
Forget it, forget it.
Be good.
Just get in there.
Turn it off.
Turn it on.
She's shy, you know?
Excuse me.
Go, go, let's go.
I won't be back for a few days.
No way.
My family is going to be suspicious.
I've talked to dad...
I've explained to Uncle Lu that
I've got something to do at home.
I'll stay here for a few more days.
Alright.
No matter what,
I'll stay with you.
Okay.
You can stay here.
You'll sleep on the floor.
No.
Mom wants us to sleep together.
Also,
don't you forget that
according to the contract,
for the rest of the year,
you have to fulfill every requirement
as my husband.
Then, I suggest that
you should carefully read
the fifth clause in section six
of the contract.
What?
The contract clearly states that
if you, Party A,
coerce me, Party B,
to do anything unethical,
or illegal,
I would have the right
to break the contract
without any legal responsibility.
Oh, I need to add one more.
All the rights and duties
stated in the contract
have to be done
without violating the law.
I, Lu Fangning, am the general manager
of Deer Sing Group.
Why would I do anything illegal with you?
I'll add this anyway.
Very good.
Well, since you've made up your mind
to do this,
I'll find someone else
to work with me.
Bye.
Lu Fangning.
You'll be blamed
for marital infidelity.
Half of your money,
your house,
and your favorite Deer Sing
will be mine.
You sleep on the floor.
Comfortable.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
Leader,
do you think it's going to affect
Director Lu's brain waves
and let him adapt your plan
if you keep
staring at this?
I really don't want
to work overtime anymore.
I'm the one who's working overtime,
not you.
Look how well I did.
If he doesn't like this,
it certainly won't be
because of my ability.
It would be...
You know, the perfect couple
sometimes starts as enemies.
Siyu.
Again.
It's quite good, isn't it?
Left guard.
Assistant He, what can I do for you?
Director Lu demands
all of us in the Planning Department
to gather at the exhibition center
immediately.
Make sure you bring
all the proposals along.
In our plan,
we have three days to set up.
But right now,
something came up at the last minute.
There will be no construction
this weekend.
So we're gonna have to
get everything set up
by end of today.
But, we'll be off work soon.
I don't want to...
Do we need to work overtime again?
Overtime again?
If you don't want this to happen,
you should have included
a contingency plan
when you were making the proposals.
Do you want the company
to pay for the failure of the plan?
The layout of the exhibition
must be finished today.
Is there any problem with this?
-No problem.
Louder
Once again.
No problem.
Alright.
Let's go to work.
The earlier you get this done,
the longer you get to sleep
after you go home.
And if you all slow down,
you may need to come
to work straight tomorrow.
Let's get started.
He's so determined
and does all the things first.
He's getting more attractive.
Staying here is better.
I dare not even breathe
with Director Lu around.
Director Lu is handsome.
When he's wearing a suit,
he is extremely charming.
Working overtime with him
heals my eyes.
But, Lu Yiyao is too scary.
No one dares speak with him around.
What woman could stand him?
You can.
I think you can.
-You can.
-You.
I think you might be more efficient
if you just shut up.
Mi.
What's going on with
the labels on these bottles?
Anything wrong with that?
Can't you see?
The words are all blurry.
Look at this.
This is the previous batch of labels
that got rejected, right?
We're supposed to use the new one.
As long as the information is correct.
We'll put the new ones on later.
I mean, we're done with all these.
We can't just
do it all over again.
Besides,
it's too late.
No one will notice.
But if these...
My stomach hurts...
I'll bring her to the toilet.
-It hurts so much.
-What do you want to drink, Siyu?
I'll get you one.
You guys are going to the toilet
or to buy drinks?
Who is it?
Must be him.
At times like this,
the male lead will be here to help.
What are you doing all alone?
I...
This is the distribution of work.
You must strictly follow it.
Do not leave your position
without permission, understand?
Also?
Also,
don't forget the details
just because the time is running up.
Do everything perfectly.
Have you guys heard me?
Cai Siyu, why did you do that?
We didn't say we weren't gonna do it.
Exactly, what's the point of snitching?
I didn't.
Assistant He.
Whenever a job is done,
cross-check everything
like how you put the labels
on every product.
If you encounter a similar problem again,
keep me posted.
Okay.
What did you check?
Alright, go ahead.
What did I check?
Let's go.
He not only helped me,
but also got revenge on them,
and tried to keep me out of trouble.
What kind of perfect male lead is this?
I caused trouble
the first three times we met.
I am so sorry.
But without those three accidents,
how could we get to where we are today?
Come and get something to eat.
-Here.
-Hold this for a second.
Come on, come on.
The red ones are beef burgers
with beef patty and onions.
And this one is the chicken burger
-with fried chicken and tomatoes.
-I like fried chicken.
Siyu, which one do you want?
Can I have both?
I know I can't.
Then I'll have the chicken burger.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Director.
We have beef burgers and chicken burgers,
which one do you want?
Beef burger.
Alright.
Hi, this one, without the onions, thanks.
Okay.
What?
There's finally a chance for me?
That's enough.
Give them more.
I thought you didn't eat beef.
Here, chicken burger.
No?
Have a little more.
A little more.
Director Lu.
What's the matter?
Thank you.
For what?
You know, because of the labels,
you've reassigned our jobs.
I was trying to improve
the efficiency.
What's up?
You thought I did it for you?
Is it on again?
Are we
turning into enemies again?
Such a cliche.
Enjoy your meal here.
Cai Siyu.
I didn't know
how you convinced Ms. Lu
to let you get into Deer Sing.
But I hope
that you're capable enough
to do your job,
or I'm going to ask you to leave.
See?
That's usually how it goes.
You won't be willing to let me go later.
Save me in a time of danger.
What a cliche.
But, it's so good.
Are you okay?
This is for you, Director Lu.
No onions.
Ms. Lu.
What are you doing?
Why do you call me here to check on
the exhibition at such a late hour?
Director Lu.
Fangning.
Look.
All the arrangements
are done already.
Two days later,
we can launch it on time.
Let's take a look over here.
Let's go. Mr. Li, come and have a look.
This couch was designed by
Infinity's designer, Gavin.
It's also the main product
of our exhibition then.
During the interview,
we'll have the designer up here
to receive the interview.
I think it's all good here.
Why don't we look somewhere else?
Wait a minute.
I think there's something wrong with
the couch's position.
What do you think, Simon?
Maybe it's the lighting.
I'll tell you what.
Mr. Li.
Why don't you go up there and give it try?
We can get your feedback directly.
It's all good.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
Making furniture
is all about precision.
Besides, this couch really matches
a successful man like Mr. Li.
Give it a try.
Please.
Mr. Li, don't be so nervous.
You've seen everything.
This couch really matches
you perfectly.
[CBNTURY]
Turn slightly to the left.
Simon, do you think it's better
for him to face right?
Let's turn right.
Maybe it's the lighting.
Look how pale
Mr. Li's face is.
Mr. Li, sit down. We're not in a hurry.
Director Lu,
even though we don't have much time left,
but we still have to do our best
to make it perfect.
Yes. We have limited time.
Otherwise,
we can do better than this.
The plan was made in advance.
Why did the exhibition hall
suddenly change their mind?
What do you think
about this, Director Lu?
People
are easy to be manipulated.
Ms. Lu, are we done here?
With this light,
my eyes can't take the glare.
That's enough. Mr. Li, thank you.
What's wrong with this, Lu Fangning?
Right.
What's wrong with this, Simon?
Sorry, Mr. Li.
I forgot to tell you that
this light right here
almost hit
our own staff.
I've checked on it.
Someone did this on purpose.
On purpose?
Thank God Mr. Li sat here in advance,
or it might hit somebody else.
And that's gonna be bad.
Lu Fangning.
Would you like me
to call an ambulance for you?
No need.
Get me an ambulance when I'm dead.
Let's go.
How absurd.
Ms. Lu, I'll go check over there.
Go ahead.
We're almost done
after the light is fixed.
The rest of the place has been checked.
No signs of tampering.
Don't worry
about the exhibition.
You've done a lot, Simon.
It's alright.
What? In a bad mood?
Why do you say that suddenly?
I saw you come here
with a long face.
You didn't even argue with him
and just directly went to the point.
Did you fight with Ling Rui?
No, we're fine.
Fangning.
If anything is bothering you,
remember that you still have me.
If anyone bullies you,
I will beat him up for you.
If you just want to
let it all out,
I could do boxing with you.
In short,
don't keep it all to yourself.
It always takes
some experience to grow up.
You told me this.
If I tell you,
you might just
beat the crap out of me.
Hold on, I need to
borrow someone from you.
Simon, bye.
Let's go.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
What does she want from me?
And with this vibe...
Is it too early for
the break-up scene?
How's your work recently?
It's going well.
What can I do for you, Ms. Lu?
Have you
ever been in love?
I...
Yes, I think.
That's good.