[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 35]
Youyou.
What should you call me?
Little Grandpa!
What should you call her?
Auntie Cai.
You can't call us like that.
Why?
She is my girlfriend.
If you called her that,
the relationship would be messed up.
Then should I call Auntie Cai
Little Grandma?
No.
I don't want to be
your grandpa's girlfriend.
Youyou,
you should call me Uncle Simon from now on.
If I were
your Little Grandpa,
I might not get married.
Then you would
only get one red pocket.
If you call me
Uncle Simon,
you can get two red pockets
from me and Auntie Cai
during Lunar New Year.
Isn't that a better deal?
You're happy.
You're smart.
Why are you
so serious with a kid?
You're so much older than him.
Right?
Besides,
who said I'm going to marry you?
You...
Who is old?
Then why are you so eager to get married?
Look at
Fangning and Ling Rui.
They have a happy life.
We're different.
How could you tell without trying?
Is this a matter of trying?
Well,
if it doesn't work out, we can always get a divorce.
Lu Yiyao, what's wrong with you?
Why are you thinking about divorce before we get married?
No, wait.
I'm not going to marry you.
Give me a kiss.
Call me Uncle Simon.
Uncle Simon.
Right.
Good.
What do you want? I can get you some.
Never mind.
Aren't you going to have anything?
No, I'm on a diet.
I don't want to look fat on the camera.
Well,
I saw photos
of your new drama.
I think you're in great shape.
You're not fat, really.
You saw them?
Really? I look pretty, right?
The director said I did well
for that love scene.
He's going to give me
a heartbreak scene next.
I believe I can do well.
What's wrong?
It's embarrassing.
I didn't mean that.
I'm not blaming you.
I understand.
One doesn't have to
own what one likes.
Enough about that.
Today is Lu Fangning's birthday.
Let's not
talk about the unpleasant stuff.
Here.
Have some.
This is your favorite.
Don't go on a diet.
I'll gain weight.
No, you won't.
I think
you're already very beautiful.
You know what?
I don't want to lose weight,
and I don't want to be a superstar.
I just want someone
who truly cares about me
and likes me.
That's what I want.
I know.
You know?
Yes.
I know.
Do you really get it?
I knew it!
Do you get it now?
You're here.
I…
I missed you so much.
I really missed you.
Erfan,
all my wishes
have come true.
I have my family.
Uncle, what are you doing?
And the kid.
I understand now.
[Deer Sing Group]
[This is perhaps]
[the most memorable birthday I've ever had.]
[But it definitely won't be the last one.]
[Maybe we don't have]
[that much time in our lives,]
[and we can only celebrate our birthdays so many times.]
[But as long as we can be together]
[with the people we love,]
[perhaps...]
[the future holds endless possibilities for us.]
Sister.
Fangning.
Happy Birthday.
Sister.
You saw it, too.
Would you be proud of me?
I'm very proud of you.
I've always been proud of you.
Actually, I've always wanted to tell you
that life could be
shackled by many things.
Don't make it so complicated.
Do whatever you want.
Be the person you want to be.
Remember,
no matter what you do,
I'll always be there for you
to give you my support
and keep you company.
Thank you, Sister.
I miss you so much.
Well,
I'm going to start my own life now.
Fangning.
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Nothing,
I'm overjoyed.
Really.
Thank you
for the birthday party.
Actually,
Infinity,
our family,
and our kid
are the wishes
my sister wanted to realize
before 30 years old.
That was why I wanted to have a child
with you so badly back then.
Your wishes came true.
I've always wondered
how I was able
to be a man of perfection.
Maybe
you're the gift
from my sister.
Fangning,
no matter what you want to do,
I'll always be there for you
until you realize your dreams.
So where's my gift?
Isn't the party
the gift
you wanted?
That's all?
What else do you want?
Well,
let me show you
how magnanimous I am.
Listen,
I would be very happy
no matter what you give me.
Thank you.
Thank you, too.
Daughter-in-law,
I'm so happy today.
You must be tired
from being here all night.
Go home and rest well.
-Okay.
-Don't stay up too late.
Let's go home.
Rest well.
In-laws, I'm going home.
Drive safely.
See you.
Tell Ling Rui when you arrive.
-Goodbye.
-Goodbye, Auntie.
Well, Fangning,
we should leave too.
I'll send her home.
Don't worry.
Don't show off here.
I'm going now.
Listen to me.
Don't get too tired.
That's enough.
Bye.
Off you go.
Don't miss me.
Peng Bo.
See you.
-Goodbye.
-Peng Bo.
Good luck.
Good boy.
Dad, I didn't really
have the time for you today.
I'm very happy.
You're not a kid, save it.
You have
your son now.
Youyou.
Do you want to sleep with your daddy and mommy
or your grandma and grandpa?
With grandma!
With grandma and grandpa?
I have chocolate for you.
Grandma and grandpa!
Then you can sleep with grandma.
You naughty boy.
You just don't want to stay
and clean up with us, right?
-That's exactly it.
-That's right!
Okay, just go.
Rest well.
Don't worry, Sister.
-Dad, goodbye.
-Goodbye.
Don't worry, I'll take good care of him.
Don't let him play too many games.
-Okay.
-We'll take care of him.
Bye.
Say goodbye to your mommy.
Goodbye.
-See you tomorrow.
-See you.
Goodbye.
Let me carry you.
Slow down.
-Let's go!
-All right.
Okay, it's time to go home.
We should...
No, you got it all wrong.
We are going to our own homes.
Okay, whatever you say.
Suit yourself.
-See you.
I would give you a bigger surprise
for your birthday.
Who cares?
Where's Ling Rui?
Don't be so full of yourself.
[The wind chimes broke]
[when you left six years ago.
[Now,]
[I'm giving you a new one.]
The kid behind him.
Yes! Higher!
Here.
Keep the change.
Grandma.
Thank you.
Young man.
Look.
It's the photo from when you were little.
[Fangning,]
[it's the first photo we had together.]
[You lost it,]
[now I got it back.]
[It's the beginning of our destiny.]
[You used to think]
[that everyone else]
[knew me better than you,]
[therefore,]
[I've recorded every day of the six years]
[in this diary.]
[I hope I could give it to you]
[when we meet again]
[so that you won't be upset anymore.]
[From now on,]
[you'll always be the one]
[who knows me the best.]
[MARRY ME]
Is it
a little too mushy?
I was worried
you might not like it.
But I decided
to take a leap of faith.
Fangning,
I'm going to proceed with
the last step now.
Do you remember the coin?
I've had it
melted into the ring.
It was
your deposit before.
Now
it's my turn.
Fangning,
are you willing to
marry me?
Although
you've melted your ring,
but I've always
carried mine with me.
You still have it
after so many years.
It has never left my side.
It's all right.
This ring
was a gift from my husband Ling Rui.
This one
is from my boyfriend Ling Rui.
I want them both.
Great.
You have both now.
You could never run away.
I never want to run away.
You're not going anywhere either.
Fangning,
over the past six years
we've missed out on too many things.
Consider these gifts
as my effort to make amend.
I want your birthday
to no longer be
a day of sadness,
but a day
to remember.
So all of this
is the real birthday present
you prepared for me, right?
Are you satisfied?
Very much so.
Thank you.
Actually,
the present I want the most is…
Okay.
Now I've received the deposit,
and you're mine.
Let's open the gifts inside.
[For the millions of fans, we packed a little surprise for you...]
Is it okay?
It's too much.
Go a little left.
Left. A little left.
Is it okay?
A little left. Just a little.
A little more left.
I'm still injured.
I'll give you paid leaves.
Come on.
A little left.
I'm a designer.
How could you order me around
for the hard labor?
Is it upright?
It looks…
Is it okay?
How obnoxious.
[Sister, can you see this?]
[This is my new store.]
[It's my brand and my dream.]
Excuse me,
are you Ms. Lu Fangning?
Hello.
Hello,
a man asked me to
give you this.
Thank you.
[Contract of Share Transfer]
[Transferer: Gao Erfan] [Recipient: Lu Yiyao]
Is it okay?
Fangning.
Lu Fangning.
Ms. Lu?
What are you reading?
Any good stuff?
Company's Equity Assignment Agreement?
Youyou is now loaded!
Fangning,
is the painting okay?
Gao Erfan.
What do you mean?
I knew you would come.
What's wrong?
You look anxious.
Is it because I didn't give you the share?
Are you upset?
I'm serious.
I'm just as serious.
You've read the specific terms.
I'll leave the Deer Sing Group.
All my shares
will be handed to
Lu Yiyao for safekeeping.
If you need them,
he will give them to you.
If you don't want them,
it will be Youyou's in the future.
As for
whether you want to restart Infinity,
it's up to you.
Why?
You've found
what you really want to do.
The shares of Deer Sing Group
don't mean that much
to you now.
While Lu Yiyao has been working for
Deer Sing Group for years.
He didn't just do it for you,
he really wants to
protect Deer Sing Group.
Therefore,
it's only proper to let him have it.
I mean,
this is all too sudden.
Why are you doing this?
You already took it out on me.
I must reflect on my mistakes.
I plan to leave this place.
Fangyu sent me tickets.
He was such a show-off.
I couldn't waste them.
So...
what is your plan
after leaving?
What I'm going to do
is none of your business.
Come on.
If it's none of my business,
why did you come to
celebrate my birthday for me?
Since you've done that,
I'll consider that
that I'm a friend to you.
Besides, it's been years.
Why can't I just care about you?
I'm going to continue traveling around the world.
Don't worry.
I won't send you
postcards this time.
But if you need…
No, thank you.
It's been so long.
I haven't really lived for myself.
I want to see the world again.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll find out
what my purpose is.
Maybe
that's what Lu Yue wants.
It might happen soon.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Bye.
Gao Erfan.
The hair gel you used today
smells fine.
I like it.
Bye.
Siyu,
let's get married.
No.
I'm still young.
Maybe I'll meet
someone better in the future.
[No.]
You feel insecure
because you're old.
Or perhaps you might not
meet another girl prettier than me.
Is that why you're getting impatient?
[No!]
Old man.
[Ling Rui and I]
[are going to have another wedding.]
[It's the real wedding.]
[I'm giving you a chance to be my best man.]
While I was single the whole time,
my friends are already getting married for the second time.
Cai Siyu,
your story should be
at the climax by now.
I'm coming.
Lu Yiyao?
Siyu.
I don't feel well.
I miss you so much.
Siyu.
I've turned thirty...
Thirty...
five,
six,
seven.
I'm almost forty!
Why am I so old?
The kid called me grandpa!
Why am I still alone?
Lu Yiyao.
Have you reached
male menopause?
Who said that? I'm only…
I've looked up the symptoms of male menopause.
Lack of concentration.
Loss of memory.
Hair loss.
I'm suffering from all of them.
It's okay.
Calm down.
One more thing...
My waist is getting weaker!
Lu Yiyao, what are you doing
at my home
drunk and crying?
I...
Sleep.
You...
I'm a little tired.
I am drunk.
Just like what you wrote in the novel.
Become a couple
when the boss is drunk.
That would solve my problems.
Solve what?
What are you afraid of?
You wrote those details
in your novels.
They aren't that detailed.
Siyu.
I,
I've prepared everything.
Let me show you.
See?
I just want to marry you.
I'm not demanding anything.
I'm just afraid
that
if you're
only my girlfriend,
and you don't give me any promise,
you might leave me
once a nicer,
better-looking guy shows up.
Don't think
so little of me!
I'm just worried.
Listen to me.
I'm already so old,
and my waist is getting worse.
Who would want a sorry old man like myself?
That's enough. Sober up.
I used to be a jerk.
It was wrong for me
to treat you that way.
It was my fault.
But I love you!
Do you know?
I love you, Siyu!
I'm begging you to forgive me.
Please, Siyu.
Forgive me.
Do you still love me?
I'm begging you.
That's enough.
You're not old.
You're so handsome.
You will still be
a handsome old man later on.
Actually,
I've always thought it was such a shame.
You have a nice figure,
but I didn't see anything that day
and nothing happened.
Wouldn't that be a shame?
Dr. Ling,
your project on pancreatic cancer
has won the recognition
of many international medical institutions.
You've achieved greatness at a young age.
This is the last question.
It's been the main discussion
of many female readers.
You're married
at such a young age.
It's said that your wife was
just as outstanding.
Dr. Ling,
could you tell us
about your wife?
Her name is Lu Fangning.
She's
funny,
bossy…
She's just an ordinary person.
But she
is hardworking...
and remarkable.
A person
will meet a lot of
unexpected problems in life.
But she's the one
whom I want to
spend my life with.
[Fashion Doctor: Feature Interview with Ling Rui]
I don't think this photographer
is as skillful as me.
Your daddy looks ugly.
See? His left face is so puffy.
I don't think so.
Daddy is always so handsome.
But he looks better in person
than in this photo.
Don't you think
I'm better at taking photos?
Mom,
then why did you buy so many copies?
You don't understand.
I can't let
your dad's handsome look
distract the others.
I've heard the good news
about you and Dr. Ling.
See?
Why two rings?
But these two
are not as bright as the one before.
I didn't know
Dr. Yu was suffering
from weak eye-sights.
But why do I have two?
It's because
I'm no ordinary woman.
It took two rings
to tie me close to him.
Anyway,
Dr. Yu, just remember,
Ling Rui is mine
from now on.
I know.
Well,
do you need me to keep an eye on him
so the home-wreckers inside
and outside the hospital
won't seduce him?
What if
you are one of them?
Here's the deal.
I'm not interested in married men.
If someone's harassing him,
let me know at once.
Deal.
But…
What do you want?
3D Surgery Simulators.
I want three of those.
I'll settle for two.
One. At least one.
Two.
Cool.
Deal.
You must inform me firsthand.
I heard everything.
What was the deal?
I have to go now.
Don't forget my machines.
Dad.
Mom and that lady
made a deal.
A deal?
What deal?
Nothing.
I'm going to donate
some medical equipment to your hospital.
Really?
That's a good thing.
Why did you buy so many?
Because you're handsome.
I can't have enough of it.
But my photograph skill
is better.
-Of course.
-Yes.
Good-looking. Can't have enough of it.
-Can't have enough of it.
Can't have enough of it.
It's so nice.
So nice.
I'm going to make breakfast.
Sleep in for a little.
Okay.
Ling Rui.
You've done so much for me.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
Aside from making breakfast,
you can do everything else for me.
What was that?
Is my cooking so awful?
Your cooking is amazing.
Fangning,
I need you
to be with me
when I'm happy
and sad.
I will.
When I'm hurt
and feel vulnerable.
I will.
Whether I'm successful
or hitting rock bottom.
I will.
When
I'm old
and ugly.
About that…
No promises.
What did you say?
I will
always be there for you.
Forever.
♫ Your arrival in my world ♫
♫ Makes me believe in destiny ♫
♫ I'm moved beyond my expectation ♫
♫ I can't move my gaze from you ♫
♫ I know the future is too uncertain ♫
♫ I can only be sure that you are the only one ♫
♫ I'm not afraid to walk in a sea of ​​people ♫
♫ Because I really love you ♫
♫ My dear, I have three hearts for you ♫
♫ Listen to this carefully, this shall not be done half-heartedly ♫
♫ You must love and give with all your heart ♫
♫ I'll love you well ♫
♫ When I speak of love, I mean it wholeheartedly ♫
♫ To prove that you'll always be my one and only ♫
♫ From now on, my heartbeat, pulse, and breath ♫
♫ exist only for you ♫
[Begin Again]
[GAME NOT OVER]