(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
(Final Episode)
Do you have an umbrella?
It's raining out.
What...
What's your deal?
I'm your hand holder.
I can't stop the rain anymore.
I have to use an umbrella like you people.
Because...
I've become like you people.
I can't get sick.
You'll be upset if I do.
I think I'll hate rainy days because it's cumbersome.
This isn't a dream, is it?
You're real, right?
I wanted to avoid getting wet. Oh well.
I'll make an exception today.
Stop staring. You'll burn a hole in me.
What happened?
Where have you been?
I took a trip to the fiery pit.
Stop joking.
That garden.
She sent you back?
No. She let me be born.
Thanks to you,
I grew up nicely and made her happy with me.
That's why I'm back.
What does that mean?
You saw those flowers there, right?
Those are all you.
She and I are caretakers of that garden.
To be more precise,
I was a butterfly for that garden.
- But? - But I bloomed...
because I died for you.
- Then you're... - I no longer bring doom.
I am...
just human like you.
Is that okay?
Even if I'm nothing now?
Even if I can't do anything for you?
I've missed you so much.
It was so hard without you.
How could you say that?
Okay. I guess so.
You must've spent many days...
thinking about me.
Sorry.
You're hungry, but this is all I have at home.
No. I'll go out and pick something up.
I would've gone grocery shopping had I known.
It's your first meal as a human.
You didn't know.
You didn't know we could even meet again.
You didn't know I'd be back as a human.
I thought it was really the end.
I can't believe it.
I'm hungry, so I'll have to eat.
I'll be sleepy, so I'll have to sleep.
I can see you.
I may get sick at times and recover.
I can live with you like that and die together with you.
Me too.
I can't believe it.
This is delicious.
This isn't a dream, is it?
No, it isn't.
It really isn't, right?
No.
It can't be a dream.
Don't disappear on me.
- Okay. - Ever.
Okay.
You're up.
You have to leave for work, right?
What's wrong? Did you have a bad dream?
I thought you had left.
Why did you bring your boyfriend to work?
Well... He has no friends.
I can't leave him home alone.
Why not? He's an adult.
Well, his mental state...
His mental state is that of a child?
No, not a child. But...
I'm all he has right now.
Why?
Does he not get along with people?
No, he doesn't. How could he?
Since he wasn't...
He wasn't what?
Here... He wasn't from here.
You have a meeting with Dalgona today.
You won't take him with you, right?
I will.
Hey. You need to separate work from your personal life...
He has a car. He's a good driver too.
Your life becomes work and work becomes your life.
I like that attitude. You're like a real manager.
You look the most like a CEO at times like these.
And what times are those?
When you change your tune based on what's profitable.
I'm dependable, aren't I?
Like I'll build the company well and stuff, right?
I don't know about that, but I don't think it'll go bankrupt.
It won't go bankrupt if you go and get the contract signed.
I'll try.
Let's go.
If you don't like your CEO, should I kill him?
You can't kill people anymore.
That's right.
There's something else that you can do for me though.
Drive me around.
I'll see you later.
Don't come back. Go home from the meeting.
Got it.
Reunion?
What reunion?
How nice is it to meet up often like this?
This time, Eun Bi, Da Young, and Jung Hwa are really coming.
I let Ji Na know too, but she hasn't responded.
You'll come, right?
- I'll see. - Don't give me that. Come.
Hey, I'm busy right now. I'll call you later.
Bye.
Why are you bringing that here?
It's clearly for a grand opening.
You should bring that to a newly opened business.
It came in your name.
Joo Ik sent it.
Think of it as me and raise it.
He says to raise it as him.
Shouldn't you raise it yourself?
That's why I brought it.
Seriously. I told him I needed him,
and he sent a plant with his name on it.
He must want me to pay him back for raising me.
Put it up there.
- There? - Yes.
Hi, sis.
Me? I'm at the first location. Why?
This is probably not the face that Sun Kyung knows.
Say you got a new boyfriend.
You punk. How will that make me look then?
Like a popular girl.
A girl who's popular only with guys with this car.
I didn't think about the car.
This is how detail-oriented I am.
Here. Right here. Come this way.
Hey. So... What happened was...
- He's... So... - Brother!
Brother!
Brother! Do you have any idea how much I've missed you?
I've missed you so much, Brother.
Me too.
This moving reunion is nice and all,
but look at him. Doesn't he look different?
No. He looks the same.
Even the mole right here.
He looks the same?
That can't be.
See? He looks the same.
No? Did he gain weight?
What... How is this...
No?
He looks the same.
(Kim Ji Eun)
I'm nice like that.
Ji Eun! Let's go!
Okay. Be right there!
What are you doing?
- What's this? - What?
Something new that I'm raising.
What is it?
I don't know. I won't know until it blooms.
You have to tell us once it does.
Let's go. The restaurant will close soon.
- Okay. - Let's go.
So...
She did it?
What else could explain it?
She did it.
It's amazing.
It's not that amazing.
Isn't my being with you amazing?
Of course, it is.
You don't seem that amazed.
You're always touching rather than amazing.
Wow.
Who knew you could be this sweet?
I could be even sweeter.
Anyway,
you said you had a meeting but you went to see your brother.
Is it okay to lie at work?
It's okay.
That jerk always says he's off to meetings...
and goes to Ji Na's place. I know everything.
I just turn a blind eye, that's all.
Also, I can just have the meeting now.
Now?
Let's test it one more time.
Where to?
You haven't broken up with him yet?
Even he recognizes me.
What do you mean? Do you think I'm an idiot?
Sir.
Take a close look. Doesn't he...
seem different?
- He's the same. - What's the same?
You're still an annoying jerk.
I ought to...
Why won't you answer my question?
Are you still going out with him?
We won't break up until we die.
I wasn't asking you.
Seriously.
May I hit him?
No.
I'll go pick up our drinks and dessert,
so please calm down, both of you.
You may be happy now,
but you never know what life may bring.
We're getting married.
You never know until you walk down the aisle.
It isn't over till it's over.
We'll probably walk down the aisle before you turn 20.
- How did you know? - What?
That you like her?
How did you know?
How could I not?
I knew from the first time I saw you at the tteokbokki place.
Did... Did you tell her?
- Should I? - Don't you dare.
Why not?
In case she thinks I'm cute.
I'm speechless.
Do you think you're cute?
Okay.
I'm busy, so I have to go. Goodbye.
I just got our drinks.
Let him go. I guess he needs to run away.
Anyway, call me later.
Sir.
I'll let you go, but can you do something for me first?
I'm begging you.
Please.
What is it? Make it quick.
Hold on.
Hello. You can come in...
Hi.
It's Park Young.
Let's have a one-on-one fan meeting.
Just 30 minutes. No. 20 minutes. Please?
What?
You didn't say we were meeting her.
I didn't say we weren't either.
It was a great opportunity.
I can test it and do my work.
Two birds, one stone.
Thanks to that, I got Dalgona to sign the contract...
and repay her.
This is also two birds, one stone.
I still hate him.
Why do you hate him so much?
Don't you?
Why? He's cute.
Don't you think that's the problem?
Did you see how his face changed?
That's how he is.
He did that to me first.
What choice do we have?
He's our best author.
It isn't midnight yet.
We have a lot of time left.
We don't have a contract like that anymore.
That's right. We don't.
We can hold hands for no reason whatsoever.
You're so right.
But seriously... That kid...
- Hey. - I'm back.
Hi, Brother-in-law.
Go on. Say hi.
I'm back.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hi.
Hey. Are you here to get your hair done?
Yes.
Right.
It's a salon. Why else would you be here?
I heard Da Young worked here.
She's good.
I come here often because of her.
Did you get your hair done? It looks nice.
Thanks.
I heard...
that your friend that you mentioned recovered.
How did you hear that?
Sun Kyung told me.
About how he knows you too.
That's right. Sun Kyung.
Yes, she got better. She's healthy now.
I'm glad. I was worried.
Thanks.
I hear we're having a reunion.
Yes, I heard.
Are you going?
No.
Okay. Bye.
Thus, I am no longer a café worker.
I am the manager of the second store.
That's all.
- Really? - I'm so proud of you.
I have nothing to worry about anymore.
Soo Ah and Jong Won...
are finally pulling their weight from above.
They're finally pulling their weight.
- Sun Kyung, that's great. - Great.
Your dream is finally coming true.
Is it your 49th?
48th?
Is it the 49th?
What does it matter what number it is?
What matters is that he's doing something.
You're eating well today.
You barely ate in the past.
He must've missed Korean food like crazy.
- Isn't that right? - Yes.
I missed everything.
Gosh... Goodness, Brother.
You're embarrassing me.
What is wrong with this kid?
When are you going to move in here?
What?
Well, so... I've thought it over.
My job is closer from there...
No.
Move in. I want to live with you...
until you get married.
Come on. You're so dense.
It's because she won't be able to spend time alone with him.
Hey.
We can just go to my place then.
I have a lot of rooms.
I see. You have your own place?
You have a lot of rooms?
Yes. It's quite big.
I see. Okay, then.
Are you done with everything in the US?
So you told them I was in the US.
Wasn't he?
- I was. - Okay.
What do you plan to do...
to make a living in Korea now?
I plan to continue doing the same job as before.
(Ambulance)
(Rescue)
- This way. - Please make way.
Excuse me.
(Kim Human)
She was in a car accident.
There aren't any external injuries,
but she's pregnant.
She had stomach pain and fainted.
Call OBGYN...
and Pediatrics just in case.
Yes, doctor.
Excuse me.
Do you hear me?
My baby...
Please save my baby.
How far along are you?
- Hello? - Her BP is dropping.
I called OBGYN.
- Someone will be here in 10. - She looks bad.
She may have a brain hemorrhage.
Bring her to an OR right away.
Call Anesthesiology...
and tell OBGYN and Pediatrics to come there.
Yes, doctor.
I'm so very happy for you. Congratulations.
Here's a little gift.
What are you congratulating me for?
I hear you're having a baby.
How did you know?
Well. People at the hospital are always talking.
I heard a little rumour.
I'll go to the first birthday party.
There's no need. You came to our wedding too.
Thank you.
Sure. And...
This is the new contract I mentioned before.
What? Out of the blue?
The document describes the detailed terms,
so please read it thoroughly.
I'm sure you're busy with your main job,
but please review the terms.
I hope for a positive response.
Be honest with me.
This was why you really came, isn't it? Not to congratulate me.
Well... It was for both.
What is there to think about?
Of course, I'll sign.
Still, you should review the terms...
and call me afterwards.
We're very confident...
(Human)
We're confident...
Excuse me.
I'm almost done.
Yes, I'm coming now. Okay.
Sorry about that.
He has the worst timing.
Who...
My boyfriend.
That boyfriend who went far away.
Is he finally back?
Yes.
My gosh, doctor.
You look as handsome as ever.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I'm going on a date with my girlfriend.
It's nice out. It's perfect for a date.
Hello.
It seems like just yesterday when you were fretting...
about whether or not you'll get married.
But now, you're completely healed too.
Life is unpredictable.
Back then, none of us knew he'd end up working here.
Right.
But when are you two getting married?
Well, we haven't decided yet.
We'll be off now.
I hope you two also recover so you can go home.
Don't worry about us.
We're very healthy.
Goodness, we stayed for too long, didn't we?
We'll leave so you two can spend time together.
By the way, you haven't mentioned anything...
about that ghost these days.
I haven't heard any stories lately.
I think he went over there.
Do you think so?
I hope he got there safely.
Hey, wait for me.
I can't believe you actually became a doctor.
I didn't live that long for nothing.
Do you think it suits you? Is it okay?
No, obviously not. It's not something I used to do.
But you're doing awfully good.
It's because I've always wanted...
to do something that saves lives.
What are you going to do about your name?
Are you really going to live as Kim Human?
I like it. You gave me this name.
Gosh, what do you like about it? It came from the top of my head.
You named me from the top of your head?
Yes, I did.
But now that I think about it, I'm starting to think...
it all happened for a reason.
I really am learning things as I live.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I would've given you a cooler name.
I can't believe I named you Human.
When do you want to get married?
Gosh, we don't need to get married.
Has your love faded?
Do you not like me anymore because I'm average?
Why? Do you not like me because I'm average?
You were never average.
From the first time we met up until this very moment,
you were always special to me.
I know that was a line, but my heart skipped a beat.
It wasn't a line. I really meant it.
Are you getting used to this?
Yes.
The only uncomfortable thing is that I can't read minds.
But at the same time, it's also kind of nice.
Because I'm unsure, I find myself making an effort.
You're really human now.
Fate doesn't change.
When I knew how things were going to end,
I never reached out to them.
But now that I can't see that, I end up trying my best.
Sometimes, I feel like it's going to end,
but that becomes a new beginning.
I guess that's how you guys are able to live eternally.
All humans are terminally ill.
They live forever only when they're not aware of that.
Isn't this what you said a long time ago?
When I was immortal, it felt like I was terminally ill.
But now that I've become mortal,
it somehow feels like I can live forever.
Let's live together forever.
Is that a proposal?
No, it's not.
Standing here with you like this reminds me of that day.
The day we went to a world where no one else existed but us...
and watched the sunset together.
I couldn't forget the look you had on your face...
for a very long time.
How do I look now?
You look comfortable.
You don't look lonely.
Right.
I'm not lonely.
Now I know which direction to walk to.
And that's you.
You talk so well for someone who couldn't even send a text.
What do you mean I couldn't send a text?
Back when you were gone,
I found your cell phone at your place.
And I saw that you wrote a text but never sent it.
You sent a lot of texts.
You read them all? Why didn't you tell me?
- I'm telling you now. - No, I mean...
But I must say, it's weird. How did your cell phone...
manage to stay turned on for three whole months?
It was probably her.
I see.
I wonder how she's doing.
Wherever she is,
I bet she's doing well...
and still has a lot of love for humans.
In the past, I didn't understand why she loved humans so much.
I didn't know why she said love derives from hate.
She also probably hated humans at first.
Then she probably forgave them.
And one day,
I bet she felt grateful that they created her.
I finally get it now because I also felt the same way.
It's cold. Let's go. We'll catch a cold.
Hey.
How's life?
It's nice.
My gosh.
Did you see that I made it into the top 10?
This is my first time.
Congratulations.
This is amazing.
See? I told you romance wasn't my genre.
Okay, fine.
("The Demon Landlord")
By the way, isn't the main character based on me?
Well, yes.
But I added my imagination to it.
Do I seem like a demon to you?
Why is he a demon?
That part isn't important.
You need to focus on the fact that he's a landlord.
What? So are you offended?
Devils and demons are very sexy, you know.
- You think I'm sexy? - Yes.
- No. - I'm not?
What?
Yes. No.
Did you cut your hair?
Yes, a little.
How did you know? I only cut off a little bit.
To go to a school reunion?
No, because...
you told me you were coming.
What's that look in your eyes?
What's your hand doing there?
I mean, it was all too sudden.
Would you like to go for a drink?
A drink?
- Why? - Let's drink.
I want to drink today.
I've always wondered how it'd feel to be on the top of the list.
I finally get how it feels to be in the top 10.
It's burdening and scary.
But I'm also on cloud nine.
I'm so excited.
In the next episode,
the demon is going to bribe all the modern ghosts...
and send them to the building next door.
He's going to make the price drop and use that chance to buy it...
So he's going to... What was I saying?
He's going to make the price drop and use that chance to buy it,
- then put it up for sale again... - You don't seem surprised.
Well, to be honest,
I kind of expected it.
- Really? - Yes.
I used to write romance novels.
You didn't expect this one, did you?
Well, I kind of did.
Then I'll just continue to meet your expectations.
So have you made up your mind?
About what?
Are you going to be my girlfriend or not?
What if I choose not to be?
I'm going to cry.
Will you just ignore me if you see me cry?
No, I'll even hold an umbrella above your head for you.
Why would you say that?
You shouldn't make me cry in the first place.
Okay, fine. I won't.
You just said so yourself that you won't make me cry.
Okay, I won't make you cry.
- What do you do tomorrow? - Why?
So we can hang out for a bit longer if it's your day off.
Are you normally like this?
I don't really get what you mean by that,
but I have to tell you that I'm not entirely sane.
I'm not free tomorrow. I have plans.
What do you need to do? Let's do it together.
You want to do it together? Are you sure?
Yes. What is it?
Put it down there.
Auntie, why are you suddenly making kimchi?
I moved back to Korea,
so I should make kimchi to commemorate.
Auntie, your kimchi tastes amazing.
I can easily finish a bowl of rice with your kimchi.
But this is way too much.
How are we going to make this all on our own?
We're expecting more people.
Who?
- Hey, I'm here. - What?
I bought makgeolli too.
It just happened.
- Hello. - Hello.
I heard a lot about you. You're Ji Na's boyfriend, right?
Yes.
He's also my boss.
What?
- Hey, Joo Ik. - What?
How do you know him?
Well, Joo Ik and I...
share a really big secret.
- Right, Joo Ik? - Yes, right.
He came to help out.
The more the merrier.
If he bothers you, should I just kill...
Put it in here. You guys can put it in here.
- Okay. - Okay.
Good job, you guys.
Why would you even come here?
- Well, you're here too. - I'm family.
- Are you married? - No, but we're going to soon.
- Oh, sure. - "Oh, sure"?
You never know whether or not you'll get married until you do.
Why do so many people keep saying that to me?
No man's ever done what I've done.
Brother, come on. Rub in the sauce properly.
- Who are you talking to? - Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to my brother-in-law.
- Which one? - Which one?
Dong Kyung, this is exhausting.
Auntie, Uncle, your glasses are empty.
Let me pour you guys a glass each.
- Okay, go ahead. - A glass for my uncle.
Here you go.
You too, Auntie.
Goodness, thank you.
Brother, are you not going to drink?
No, I quit drinking.
It's bad for your body.
I want to live a long life.
I see. It's for your health, right? Being healthy is great.
Yes, you should be healthy.
Okay. I hope you and my sister grow old together.
Here you go.
Nice.
Joo Ik, aren't you going to have any alcohol?
I had enough yesterday.
Then what does that make me?
What's going on? Did you two drink together?
I thought you kept things professional with writers.
But you told me to approach her as a woman, not a writer.
When did I say that?
You have a way of misinterpreting things.
I told you to get her as both a woman and a writer.
When did I ever tell you to drink with her?
You also got drunk and got me hooked on you.
Hey, zip it.
So are we finally going to hear how you guys first met?
Did my sister get drunk and ask for your number?
I guess you could say that.
Are you kidding me?
You were the one who barged into my house.
Dong Kyung.
No, Auntie. That's not it.
You're seriously...
Never mind. I guess it runs in the family.
So tell me. When did you two start dating?
Ji Na, why didn't you tell me...
that you guys officially started dating?
- No, it's not what you think... - Today's our second day.
My gosh.
Then invite me to your 100th day anniversary party.
Who celebrates their 100th day? We're not in high school anymore.
Oh, right.
What's with that smile?
I think it's cute.
Who's cute? Joo Ik?
No, of course not.
I think it's cute that it's only your second day.
How long have you guys been dating?
Who cares how long we've been dating?
What matters is...
how much you had to overcome for the other person.
It wasn't easy for us either.
We even bet our lives and fate for each other.
It's a pity I can't show you guys anything to prove it.
You don't need to show us anything. We've seen enough.
You guys went through a lot to protect each other.
It was really touching.
Why are you suddenly being so serious?
What does that make me?
I'll also bet those things on you starting from now.
Stop talking nonsense.
My gosh.
You must've really lost it now that you're dating.
I've never seen him like that.
I think you've all gone mad.
My goodness.
Listen, kids. I get that your love's all grand.
But let's be honest. Kevin and I went through the most.
We overcame race, language, culture,
and so many other things with our love.
- I love you, Soo. - Me too.
Me too. I love you.
My gosh, seriously.
I can't be here anymore. Why am I the only one who's single?
- Where are you going? - To buy more alcohol.
You can't go outside on your own. It's too late.
I'll just call Sang Geun on my way to the store.
It's like he's dating Sang Geun.
A love that overcomes gender.
That's true love right there.
Are you going to write that? Should I help?
Nice. Should we give it a try?
By the way, Auntie.
Ji Na's new novel became a mega hit.
Oh, really? Did you start writing a new novel, Ji Na?
What is it about?
Well, it's called "The Demon Landlord".
These days, fantasy novels are very popular.
Demon or devil?
- "Devil". - "Devil"?
- Okay. - You know those evil guys.
- Yes. - I used to write romance novels.
- Human, follow me. - So the demon...
bribes the ghosts...
and makes the price of the building go down.
- He makes the price go down? - Then he buys that again.
That's the overall storyline. I'm still thinking about it.
You're really bad at explaining.
I'm still brainstorming.
I called you out here because I had something to say to you.
Are you... Are you going to marry Dong Kyung?
Am I going to marry her?
- Yes. - Then we're family now.
I'm really glad you joined the family.
- Family? - Yes, family.
We're family.
Family.
That word really doesn't suit me.
So you and I have to be responsible for our families.
For the happiness of Soo Ja, Sun Kyung, and Dong Kyung.
Of course, I'll live for your happiness as well.
Because we're family.
- Me too. - Do you swear?
- I can even bet my life on them. - Your life?
You're a true man.
I'm sure. You know I've liked you since I first saw you?
That's not true. I heard your thoughts that day.
Yes. I'm glad you're back.
Otherwise, Soo would've found you and killed you.
That doesn't sound like a joke.
My gosh, you really are amazing, Brother.
Is it because you lived in the States?
You can actually talk to him a bit.
Gosh, I'm so impressed.
Uncle. Brother.
I love you guys.
So I have to start living my life for him too?
Yes.
Yes! Of course!
Brother.
You're really weird.
Me? Why did you say that?
Why did you bring me to make kimchi there?
Wasn't it fun? We got kimchi too.
Do you not like kimchi?
I do.
See? I knew you'd like it.
No.
I even like your quirky quality.
Stop saying stuff like that.
Why not? Do you not like it?
No, I really like it.
It makes my heart pound.
You wrote lines like that a lot in your novel.
This is real life, not a story.
Why is it any different?
By the way,
do you remember your first love?
I do.
You're my first love.
Liar.
You don't have to be the first woman I loved to be my first love.
When you start loving someone, it's new and feels like first love.
Love comes in different shapes every time when you're in love.
Well, in that sense, you are my first love.
You don't seem to believe me.
If you don't believe me, I'll teach it to you.
I'm a good teacher.
But do lines like that make your heart pound?
Like crazy.
I should say them often.
No, stop it.
That makes me want to do it even more.
- Gosh, your personality... - What? Is it weird?
It can't be weirder than yours.
I'm very ordinary.
Weird people think they are ordinary.
So you don't like me?
That's why I like you.
I don't want to go home.
You should still go.
Come with me.
I have work tomorrow. I can't.
I'll drive you to work.
You're busy too.
You're way busier than me.
I think I picked the wrong profession.
That's funny.
Funny? Then, smile for me.
You did.
Go. Drive safely.
I want it here...
You should go.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
- I'll get going. - Okay.
- You should go upstairs. - Bye.
I'll go after I see you go up.
Drive safely. And call me when you get home.
Okay.
I'll watch you go.
Hello?
I just got home.
What?
You told me to call you when I got home.
You did what I asked.
Then, call me after you wash up and are ready to sleep.
(Human)
I washed up.
Are you ready to go to bed?
Yes. I am.
I'm lying down now.
Good.
What were you doing?
- I wasn't doing anything. - What?
What does that mean?
Well...
Not doing much...
You'll figure it out as you live your life.
By the way, I need your help now.
Now?
Should I head over?
No. You don't have to come.
You can help me with the phone call.
What is it?
Remember that day when we saw each other at the hospital?
What made you hug me?
Oh, that day.
Tak Dong Kyung.
I couldn't hold myself back.
I didn't know why I was overwhelmed and what I was feeling.
So I just did.
I knew it. You loved me back then as well.
I did.
Then,
Remember when you suddenly came to me and said...
you loved me for the first time?
Why did you do it then?
I love you.
Well,
I realized for the first time...
that I wouldn't be able to see you after I dissipate.
And that scared me like crazy.
I see.
That's how you were feeling.
Not being able to see me...
scared you more than dissipating?
I felt the same way.
At some point, not being able to see you started to scare me a lot...
more than dying.
Isn't that funny?
Are you there?
Hello?
Are you...
sleeping?
Hey. Are you sleeping?
You really are human now.
Goodnight, Kim Human.
This feeling of inability to stop myself...
What should I call it?
I do not know the answer to that.
So the only thing I could do is call it you.
Dissipating didn't scare me.
But not being able to see you scared me.
It's been a while.
This place...
Don't worry. I'm in your dream.
I secretly sneaked in.
I thought you would want to see me.
You were curious what would grow in this flower pot.
It's a cosmos.
Isn't it perfect for him?
How beautiful.
What about me? What do you think?
I wanted to show off my school uniform,
but I had no one to show it.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Thank you...
for everything you did for me.
I don't know why you chose me.
I knew everything...
that you would overcome all the hardships.
- You know, - Yes?
when you know how it would end, why do you let us go through it?
I was always curious.
At times, the deity lets you experience it...
even knowing the end.
Even when we know the flower will bloom, the sun will rise,
and you will smile...
because we always want to see it.
Yes. That's it.
I wanted to see that smile.
That's all I need. That's enough.
Go, Dong Kyung.
Your story isn't over yet.
Her story had just begun.
Doctor.
I'm the husband of the pregnant woman who was in a car accident.
- Okay. - You were her doctor, right?
Before she lost her consciousness,
she saw your name on your coat.
It's a unique name.
(Kim Human)
Is there a problem?
No.
Thanks to you, my wife and our baby are all okay.
My wife wanted to thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
I want to thank them for staying alive.
Gosh. I'm so sleepy.
Aren't you Ms. Tak's boyfriend?
Hello.
I didn't know you were a doctor here.
How come I didn't know that?
Right. This hospital is really big.
But then, why did you look so young that day?
Is it because you didn't have your coat on?
Did you know?
This hospital is haunted.
I saw a ghost here.
Have you seen a ghost?
No.
Actually, you sort of resemble that ghost I saw.
Are you a ghost?
Gosh. I was just joking.
Why? Are you scared?
Don't be scared. You look nothing like that ghost.
It was a joke.
Do you smoke?
No. I don't. It's not healthy.
Right. It's not healthy. It does more harm than good.
I was going to drink two cups as I was sleepy.
It's your lucky day.
What's your specialty?
Emergency Medicine.
You must be super-busy.
Yes, sort of.
Ms. Tak, did you read that?
It's been getting some traction.
- It's... - Which one's getting traction?
Well, a lot of novels are getting traction nowadays.
The one with the long title.
- The pen name is Harubang. - What?
Was it "Doom..."
"at Your Service"? Something like that.
It's pretty good. Did you read that?
Well, I did come across it.
- What did you think? - What? What do you mean?
Why are you acting so surprised? Did you write that?
No. I mean, it doesn't get a lot of views.
That's why I want to sign the writer.
Don't you know that my specialty is helping writers...
who has potential become successful?
Forget it.
- I didn't ask you. - What?
- What? - What?
What?
I'm going home.
Ms. Tak.
Yes?
How about a team dinner to build our teamwork?
I have plans.
I see. Okay.
Bye.
Kids these days. Seriously.
Thank you. Please wait.
Yes, I just walked in.
Okay. I'll wait.
Okay.
Are you ready to order?
One iced Americano, please.
One iced Americano.
It's four dollars.
Why are you staring at me?
You have a nice smile.
I get that a lot.
- What? - You're handsome.
I get that a lot too.
Mr. Lee!
What? Brother!
- Cute. - Cute.
What?
Are you guys friends or something?
This is my boyfriend.
And they are my forever colleagues.
He doesn't have any friends. I want him to make some friends.
No.
I just made a friend.
See? I told you he was tall.
Right.
He looks young.
Why did I think he was old that day?
Gosh. You always feed me when there are people around.
My boyfriend does that too.
He feeds me when there are people around.
I'm sorry about the other day.
Pardon? When...
Gosh. What's this?
Did she really manipulate their memories?
That's fascinating.
To be honest, I was a bit worried about today.
But how could she leave only the essential parts?
She's very detailed.
Look at me.
She made me look so handsome,
so you would fall in love with me.
What are you saying? Gosh, you're ridiculous.
When you first saw me, you thought I was handsome.
I didn't.
Sleep over tonight.
- Dream on. - Is this a dream?
No, it's not.
Hey. Hey! Make a wish.
Did you make a wish?
- Yes. - What did you wish for?
I won't tell you.
Why not? Tell me.
Gosh, you're so petty.
What did you wish for?
I won't tell you.
So petty of you to copy that.
You started it first.
(What is the wish of your life?)
Let's get married quickly.
What? Why are you bringing up marriage again?
(Doom at Your Service)