Shaun, did you undress me?
Except your underpants.
How long have you been here?
All night.
You should be at work.
I'm taking the day off.
No, you should be at work.
You're sick all the time,
not just after hours.
Shaun, you shouldn't give up your life.
You have my number. You check in with me.
I have 15 paid vacation days
and 10 sick days per year,
but I can only take sick days
when I'm sick,
not when you are, so this is a vacation.
[SIGHS]
The plan is to align your eyes
using what's called
distraction osteogenesis.
We cut the bone and implant posts
on either side of your eye orbits.
Then we slowly expand that distance,
allowing for new bone to grow
in the gaps.
MOLLY: Will it hurt?
Mm, for mere mortals it would,
but with your pain tolerance,
it'll tickle.
You up for this?
So I'll have perfectly aligned eyes
but still look like a wad of chewing gum.
Molly...
You lost an awful lot of bone and
soft tissue in the accident,
and in terms of facial reconstruction,
we've actually come a long way
in the past two years.
CLAIRE: And after 12 surgeries,
you get your own personalized coffee mug.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Okay, when can we get prepped?
- Is now too soon?
- [CHUCKLES]
Car accident. Karin Tindle, 14.
She was sleeping in the back.
Trucker in the oncoming lane fell asleep.
She wasn't wearing a seatbelt.
Head trauma, not responsive,
GCS of 5 with decorticate posturing.
MORGAN: Sounds like a bleed in the brain.
And she has a 25-point
difference in blood pressures
between her arms.
- Possible aortic dissection.
- Head and heart.
LIM: Page Dr. Melendez. Have
him meet us in the O.R.
Have you contacted Karin's father?
He passed away three years ago.
Let's go.
Why isn't she waking up?
We're gonna take good care of her.
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
PARK: CT confirmed an aortic dissection.
She needs a thoracotomy.
Aorta hasn't ruptured yet...
And she has a pseudoaneurysm.
We need to get after
her head trauma first.
I don't see any major brain bleeds
and we can monitor pressures.
In this case, the heart trumps the head.
♪
Okay.
I have two major symptoms...
nausea and boredom.
I didn't know boredom was
a symptom of chemotherapy.
It's a symptom of
sitting on my ass all day.
I used to run a 700-bed hospital
with a staff of thousands.
Now all I have to think about
is how I keep my food down
and how many bowel movements
I've had all week.
Four.
And I don't have to think about that.
You know what I need?
My meds.
Will you do me a favor
and run and pick these up?
When I come back, we can do "Mad Libs."
♪
MELENDEZ: Unclamp.
Graft is holding.
LIM: That's one fire out. Drill.
MORGAN: Pupils are blown.
PARK: ICPs are spiking way up,
brain perfusion CPP is down.
She needs a hemicraniectomy.
Let's sit her up.
It's marijuana.
Yes, it is.
Medicinal marijuana. Hold on.
One... for the boredom.
One for the nausea.
Can I try one?
I met someone who said cannabidiol
improved his ASD symptoms.
A person?
You met a person once?
Shaun, have you heard of
the scientific method?
I'd like to perform a practical,
albeit anecdotal, experiment.
Since you're on vacation...
and we can keep an eye out
on each other...
♪
One. One. Uh, whoa.
One. Take one.
♪
LIM: Cruciate wide incision of the dura.
- Brain edema.
- She's bradycardic.
Push another 50 grams of Mannitol
and ventilate down her CO2.
MORGAN: No corneal reflex.
No overbreathing vent.
No brain stem reflexes.
She's brain-dead.
♪
[SIGHS]
[MONITOR BEEPING, VENTILATOR HISSING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- GLASSMAN: Fore!
[BOTH LAUGH]
You broke my house.
You got to club down. It's just 12 yards.
It's a little dog leg.
Here. Watch this.
[THUDDING]
[LAUGHING] It's in the cup.
Nice shot, Glassy.
You're gonna call me Glassy?
All right. I'm gonna call you Smurf.
Smurf. This... This is very interesting.
I find that very funny.
But it's not.
It's not. Am I high?
I think you're pretty high, yeah.
Am I acting more... normal?
- No, you're acting high.
- Smurf. Smurf.
- Why is Smurf funny?
- I don't know.
It's... It's, um...
You take the first letter
of the first name
and you attach it to the first
syllable of your last name, see?
S-S-S-Murph. Smurf.
We did it all the time in high school.
So your name was A-Glass?
Yeah, no, it didn't work for me.
Okay, serious now.
Where's the next hole?
Right there. Careful of
the hazard right behind it.
- Okay, Sam Snead.
- Dr. Glassman.
See what you got.
[CLUB HITS GOLF BALL]
♪
How's Lea?
Lee-Ya.
[CHUCKLES]
Lee-Ya!
There should be a "Y" in her name.
Lee-Ya.
She still into Jack?
No.
She is into Jake.
Who the hell is Jake?
Jake is the guy
Lea is into.
You okay with that?
I don't think you're okay with that.
I think that's why you're here.
I'm here to help you through chemo.
When a guy is stoned,
he can tell another guy
anything that's in his heart.
You know, all the messy,
scary, embarrassing stuff
that he would otherwise never,
ever, ever tell anyone.
So what are you thinking?
A dog pooped on your lawn.
[CHUCKLES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR OPENS]
You were right to insist
that we deal with the aorta
before the brain.
I appreciate you saying that.
Don't let guilt make you
second-guess yourself.
Why would I have guilt?
You shouldn't. That's my point.
Good.
I'm hungry. Are you hungry?
I think I am.
When a man's hungry,
you know what a man wants?
There's an open can of chickpeas
in the fridge.
- Mallomars.
- What are Mal...
What are... what... what is the Mallomar?
Pure chocolate, fluffy marshmallows
on a crispy bed of graham goodness.
Get us an Uber.
♪
The next few days are going to be filled
with many difficult decisions.
Decisions no parent
should ever have to make.
We've kept your daughter on life support
- because we...
- You...
want to ask about organ donation.
Yes.
You want her what? Her heart?
[SNIFFLES]
Unfortunately, her heart
was injured by the trauma,
as were several other organs.
We have a 16-year-old girl
who had a tragic accident
a couple of years ago
that destroyed her face.
And we were hoping that you might...
You... want to take my daughter's face...
and put it on someone else?
This young girl's life
has been devastated,
and you have a chance...
No.
I'm sorry, Dr. Andrews.
No. [SNIFFLES]
♪
- Okay, how about this one?
- Mm-hmm.
"The ugly can be beautiful.
The pretty, never."
[CHUCKLES] Seems a little judge-y.
Yeah, well, it was Oscar Wilde.
Hmm. Fair enough.
So I'm guessing you didn't see
the Quakes last night.
The San Jose Earthquakes?
Your home team?
Yeah, I know who the Quakes are.
I recorded it.
No, you didn't.
Don't worry.
I watch enough soccer for the both of us.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
They won 3 to 2, by the way.
Beautiful goal in extra time.
They didn't have any either.
Well, that's all the major chains.
We're 0 for 4.
Our next place is on Thornwood Drive,
just west of Santa Teresa Boulevard.
That's in Alamitos.
Yes.
There are still 28 stores
in the greater San Jose area
that we can try
and I've devised a route
starting in the south
working counterclockwise around the city
to best avoid traffic.
We'll buy you a box, I promise.
Okay, guys, I, uh, like a big fare
as much as the next driver
but racking up hundreds of
dollars on a munchie quest
is starting to feel exploitative.
What do you say I order ahead for pizza
and then we just pick it up
on the way home?
- I don't want pizza.
What takeout food do you like?
- I like pancakes.
- I don't want pancakes.
I don't want to go home.
[CLEARS THROAT]
We're paying you to drive us.
You want these cookies?
What is the real reason?
- You'll laugh.
- What's the funny reason?
[SIGHS]
I had a crush on a girl.
Robin Demayne.
Senior year in high school.
Her favorite snack.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Are we going to get Mallomars?
Nope.
You have been harboring
feelings for this girl
for over 40 years.
That is a worthy quest.
Now, how do you spell "Demayne"?
D-E?
You're the same sex, race,
approximate age,
share compatible blood types
and antigens,
and a whole bunch of other things
that make you the perfect match.
And we just received permission
from her next of kin.
♪
Yeah.
Our donor's on life support
but her heart is compromised,
so we are very much on the clock.
Cancel all elective surgeries,
all personal plans,
and all hopes of sleep.
[LAUGHTER]
This is your home for the next two days.
Let's give Molly a new face.
[APPLAUSE]
♪
There is another Robin Demayne
living in San Mateo.
That's less than half an hour from here.
Ooh, I found one in Los Gatos,
even closer.
You realize how stupid this is, right?
This is a quest. A quest is never stupid.
A quest is, by definition,
almost always stupid.
Why would I want to see Robin Demayne
after all these years?
To tell her you love her?
I just want a cookie!
I wasn't in love with her.
I was a teenager.
I was infatuated.
And whenever you thought about her,
it made you happy.
And you thought about her all the time.
And every time you saw her,
you felt a rush, light-headed...
Is that how you know you're in love?
That's how it starts.
And when you're not with that person,
you miss them so much you're
willing to drive to 32 stores
to find a sensory reminder
that might bring back those memories.
[NATHANIEL RATELIFF & THE NIGHT
SWEATS' "YOU WORRY ME" PLAYS]
♪
♪ I'm all right today
♪ You gonna find a way to cross
and you gonna get there ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all
out there to dry ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all out there ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all
out there to dry up ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all out there ♪
♪ But you worry me
♪ You worry me
♪
Ride home's on me.
Flake.
Flake's a guy from my high school.
He knew everyone,
he kept track of everyone,
and I guarantee you
he never left Livermore.
We need to go to Livermore
and ask Flake about Robin.
We're going to Livermore.
[TURN SIGNAL CLICKING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
CLAIRE: Every lab and imaging
test that comes back
just reinforces the fact
that this really is
a one-in-a-million match.
Nice.
Yeah, it is.
It's also very scary
and natural to be having second thoughts.
It's just...
I-I don't know how to
accept a gift like this...
Someone else's face,
someone else's identity...
The face is just a mask.
It's what's... Underneath that counts?
[LAUGHS] Really?
Those lame quotes we've been mocking,
you're gonna use them on me?
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
♪
Molly.
Right now, your face is
the only thing anyone sees.
This operation will change that.
It'll let the world see not your new face
but what has always been behind it.
♪
Will it count towards the coffee mug?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
SHAUN: Flake lives at
your old high school?
GLASSMAN: He was the janitor back then.
He's the janitor now.
He'll probably be the janitor
when this planet crashes into the sun.
- Flake.
- Findlay Lake was his name.
Hey, Flakey.
Hey yourself, Glaaron Assman.
[CHUCKLES] Your name was Glaaron Assman.
[LAUGHS]
His name was Glaaron Assman.
1973 state championship.
He threw for 460 yards.
And if you squint hard enough,
you'll see who was named MVP.
GLASSMAN: You said you had
something to show us?
Oh, yeah. Wait right here.
♪
[VENTILATOR HISSING]
Shannon?
[VOICE BREAKING] I keep
thinking she's just sleeping.
[SNIFFLES]
How can I say goodbye?
♪
We call it the Walk of Honor.
To thank your daughter for her sacrifice.
♪
Do you remember a guy named Bobby Juarez?
Tall kid but too clumsy to play hoops?
He told me that Robin
married a dentist named Scaplin
and moved out of state.
You couldn't tell me that when I called?
I wanted to see you.
[CHUCKLES]
SHAUN: I found her.
Robin Scaplin is in Portland, Oregon.
It's an 11 hour and 27 minute drive.
Fill up the tank, I guess.
We're going to Portland.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[MONITOR BEEPING]
♪
MELENDEZ: 10 blade.
ANDREWS: 10 blade.
♪
Proximal facial nerve
isolated and dissected.
Okay, let's start the heavy lifting.
[TOOL WHIRS]
♪
[WATER SQUIRTING]
[TOOL WHIRS]
Clamping the left and right
common carotid arteries
and jugular veins...
Cutting the carotids and jugulars...
Let's do it.
♪
[VENTILATOR HISSING, MONITOR BEEPING]
[FLATLINE]
♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
It's a long way to go
to visit a married woman
you haven't seen since high school
who may not even be home.
She's home. I called at the last stop.
What did she say?
"Hello."
What did you say?
Nothing. He hung up.
When you sober up,
you are gonna want to
turn around and go home.
Probably.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
♪
ANDREWS: As rehearsed...
veins, arteries, nerves,
in that order, from the chin up.
Yes?
♪
Can I get the osteosynthetic
plates and screws, please?
[SCOFFS] Damn it.
I tore part of the donor's artery.
I need more interrupted sutures.
Let's keep our focus, people.
NURSE PETRINGA: Dr. Browne,
Molly's parents would like to see you
on your next break.
Take it now.
You, too.
Uh...
Dr. Park?
♪
I had a huge crush on Robin Demayne.
A thoroughly unrequited crush...
that slowly turned into a grudge.
Last day of school,
kids were passing around their yearbooks,
and I signed in hers
something that was borne out of anger
and resentment and pettiness.
It was designed to be
somewhat humorous, but...
was really just mostly hurtful.
Later that day, at the award ceremony,
I was skimming through my yearbook
and saw what she wrote me...
"I have only two regrets...
my haircut in junior year
and that you never asked me out."
And just then, I looked out
in the crowd and saw her.
Her eyes were red,
obviously crying, obviously very hurt.
And at that exact moment,
I was awarded my trophy.
I looked for her after
but never saw her again.
Is that all the scary,
messy, embarrassing stuff
that guys never, ever tell anyone?
♪
Pretty much.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
♪
Dean and Lori?
This is Shannon.
LORI: Thank you for meeting with us.
And for...
everything.
DEAN: If you don't mind, we have
so many questions for you,
about your daughter.
We'd like to know what she was like,
what she liked to do.
Molly wants to know, too.
Uh...
Her name was Karin.
And I killed her.
♪
I'm supposed to tell you to get back in.
Don't let him get to you.
It's not him, it's you.
Your advice that I shouldn't be
second-guessing myself
is making me think you must be
second-guessing yourself.
About what?
You're the one who insisted we deal
with the heart before the brain.
And you didn't fight me. Why not?
- Because you were right.
- I was right.
But you have never thought anyone
other than yourself was right in an O.R.
since you first stepped foot in one.
You backed off 'cause
we're sleeping together.
♪
The car accident was my fault.
It was my idea to leave so early.
It was my idea
to let her sleep in the back.
It was up to me to make sure
she was wearing her seatbelt.
CLAIRE: None of which would've mattered
if the truck driver hadn't fallen asleep.
It's natural to feel guilt,
but you have to understand
this wasn't your fault.
It doesn't work that way, Dr. Browne.
It was my handgun that hurt Molly.
And you can say that
it was a freak accident
or that Molly knew
she wasn't supposed to touch it
or some other B.S., but...
it was my fault.
I had one job...
...and that was to protect my family.
I didn't do my job.
And you could try to make sense of it,
try to find something,
some pleasure somewhere,
some meaning.
But there just isn't.
♪
And then your daughter...
...does this for us...
♪
[SIGHS]
Hi, Robin.
Aaron?
♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
He had a huge crush on you.
Yeah. Uh... [CHUCKLES]
That's not why I'm here, though.
I'm here to apologize.
For what I wrote in your yearbook.
Yearbook?
Yeah. Uh...
I wrote something, um...
[CHUCKLES]
...hurtful and untrue and really stupid.
And then I read what you wrote in mine.
What did I write?
She had a bad haircut in junior year.
Oh. [CHUCKLES] I certainly remember that.
Yeah, well, it was a long time ago.
Anyway, I just...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
Well...
Apology accepted.
Thank you.
Mallomars.
Robin's favorite snack.
♪
Right side donor to recipient
vessels are anastomosed.
Ditto on the left.
Let's see how our plumbing works.
Unclamp them, please.
[VENTILATOR HISSING, MONITOR BEEPING]
PARK: She's pinking up.
♪
Moving on. Motor and sensory
neurorrhaphies...
♪
How's our girl doing?
She's just waking up now.
[CHUCKLES]
Hi, Molly.
How are you feeling?
MOLLY: Terrible.
Then we're right on target.
You want to have a look?
No.
No rush.
It is going to look...
surreal.
Like you're looking at a stranger.
But it won't always.
Because nobody laughs or holds their head
or looks someone in the eye
exactly the way you do.
♪
[QUIETLY] Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
I apologize
for telling you how to react
to losing a patient.
Thank you.
When I accused you
of second-guessing yourself,
that's because I'm doing it, too.
Our relationship has me
questioning everything I do
and everything you do.
You're making this way more
complicated than it has to be.
It is complicated.
The fact that we're seeing each other
changes the context
of all of our interactions.
I guess that's why
there are rules against it.
I think I can keep
being a jerk to you at work
if that's what you want.
You think we should end it?
No.
♪
See you tomorrow.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[BAG ZIPS]
CLAIRE: So, once you're feeling
a little less woozy,
we'll set you up with
a whole bunch of therapists...
speech, occupational, physical.
LORI: Shannon.
Please come in.
SHANNON: I'm Karin's mom.
Hi.
I brought something for you.
♪
[SIGHS]
She was beautiful.
♪
Thank you.
And thank you for timing
that elevator ride so perfectly.
[EXHALES]
Can I ask you for a favor?
I'd like to say goodbye.
♪
[DOOR OPENS]
GLASSMAN: Eh, we'll clean up tomorrow.
SHAUN: And buy a new vase.
Yeah, buying a new vase is easy.
Vacuuming up my grandmother's ashes,
not so easy.
Are you glad you apologized?
Yeah.
Do you still feel guilty?
Guilt must be a bad thing
if it makes people feel badly
about something they can never fix.
Or maybe it's a deterrent
so we do the right thing the next time.
You loved Robin
but could never be with her.
Do you wish you'd never met her?
Not for one second.
I'm not okay that Lea is into Jake.
♪
Good night, Smurf.
Night, Glassy.
♪