This is Andrews' fault.
Agreed.
The bourbon may also bear
some responsibility.
Agreed.
You said "fault."
You don't regret that we...
No, not at all.
Seriously.
It was...
Pretty great.
Yeah.
And definitely shouldn't
happen again.
No, it shouldn't.
It'd make things
too complicated at work.
Let's chalk it up to, uh,
"Andrews screwed us, so we
screwed each other" impulse.
I gotta get going.
I'm covering
the E.R. today.
Ooh, right before Christmas?
Gonna be a madhouse.
Yeah.
What is that noise?
"Jingle Bells"?
Two ambulances coming in,
back-to-back.
Hey. I need you on
your game today, Murphy.
Okay.
Uh, male, mid-30s,
found unresponsive in Arrivals.
Restarted his heart
on site. Low O2,
wheezing, significant airway
resistance to the bag mask...
We need more hands on deck.
STAT. I've been calling,
everyone's left town
for the holidays.
Reznick's around.
Weird you know that,
but glad you do.
Get Reznick in here.
On it.
Take him to Bay 4.
Murphy, I need you with me.
What do we got?
This is Marianne Southam, she
collapsed in Baggage Claim.
Both patients came
from the airport?
It's that time of year.
Everyone's traveling.
Right leg is red and swollen.
She's complaining of chest
pains, shortness of breath,
and she has a low-grade fever.
Did you just get
off a long flight?
20 hours, from Malaysia.
Deep vein thrombosis formed
while she was seated,
that explains the red leg
and the fever.
Part of the clot broke off,
traveled to her lung,
that explains the chest pain.
Pulmonary embolism.
We lost his pulse again!
Take Marianne to Bay 5.
I'll talk you through managing
a pulmonary embolism.
I'm gonna light him up.
Clear.
Got a rhythm.
Barely.
He can't live
on 30 beats a minute.
His lungs are too stiff
to pre-oxygenate.
Fiberoptic blade
and a 7.5 ET tube.
Murphy, anti-coagulate her with
a 5,000-unit heparin bolus.
Set the ventilator
to assist control.
Heparin bolus infused.
Fever's spiking at 103.5.
Could be ARDS
from a viral pneumonia.
Get a chest X-ray.
Lost him again.
O2 SAT is 92.
Your chest pain
should be getting better.
It is.
Thank you.
Peak airway pressure's 50.
Switch the ventilator to PRVC.
Pushing I.V. epinephrine.
Now you need to insert a central
line in case we go to thrombolysis.
I need you, Murphy.
Still V. Fib.
Push 300 of amiodarone.
Asystole.
He's still not responding.
That's over 30 minutes
of brain and cardiac hypoxia.
Stop compressions.
Time of death, 10:07.
Have you had contact
with this man?
He was on my flight
from Malaysia.
They both have vesicular
rashes on their necks.
Whatever infection killed him,
she may have it, too.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
This is a negative
pressure room,
designed so no air flows out.
Keeps germs from spreading.
Because whatever I have
is gonna kill me,
just like the man
from the plane?
Your symptoms are not
as severe as his.
Although, yours
will probably get worse
as the virus progresses.
We don't know for sure whether
you have the same thing.
We know nothing about him,
his condition, or his history.
When did you start feeling sick?
On the plane.
I've never even been
outside the U.S. before.
My ex-husband hated
to travel and...
Was the man who died
sitting near you?
No, he was six or seven rows
in front of me.
Were you ever physically
close to him?
Say, waiting for the restroom
or in line to board?
No, I think he slept
almost the entire flight.
That suggests the virus can
be transmitted in the air.
Which means everyone
in the plane
and this emergency room
has been exposed.
We'll start conditioning
tomorrow,
so we use chemo and
total body irradiation to...
To wipe out my crappy
leukemia-producing bone marrow
so you can replace it with
some good stuff. Well said.
Looks like your dad's good
to go on his marrow donation.
Please don't call him that.
Bob Cravens walked out on me
and my mom when I was four.
His biological material
gave me life,
and apparently
he's gonna save me,
but he's not my dad.
Any unusual complaints or pain
we should know about?
I've been tired.
And the last day, achy,
kind of stiff...
Standard leukemia woes.
Anywhere in particular?
My neck, left arm.
Right, Chris, you're
having a heart attack.
N-No.
My chest feels fine.
We need to get you up
to radiation right away.
Call and let them know
we're coming.
Get his donor in here.
How is radiation gonna help
a heart attack?
Your blockage is most likely
excess blast white cells.
The best way
to clear out your heart
is to treat your leukemia.
It's what we planned.
Just a day early.
It might not be airborne.
Maybe both passengers
were already infected
when they got on the plane.
Marianne said she felt fine
before the flight.
But even if she did
contract it on the plane,
it could've been
through a shared water cup
or napkin...
Which would make
a quarantine unnecessary.
I'll call the Public
Health Department, the CDC,
they may want
to track the passengers
and anyone they
came into contact with.
Keep me up to date.
Okay.
Hey. I'm done.
Jill, are you still on?
Get me the CDC and a change of clothes.
I'm coming in.
Thanks for
getting me called in, Tyler.
You're welcome.
That was sarcasm.
Oh, was it?
If this turns into a crisis,
where else would you want to be?
I hear you're having
some stomach pain?
It hurts a lot.
I figured it was probably the candy
canes, but I took some Pepto.
Didn't help at all.
How many candy canes we talking?
Three or four... Dozen.
Of the little ones.
They pass them out
at the mall where I work.
I like to munch on them.
Keeps me in character.
Sounds like you might
be overdoing it.
Take off your shirt.
How did you know I was still in town?
Because the holidays are
"an obligatory performance
"where families buy each other gifts
and pretend everything is perfect."
Which is why you tell yours
you have to work every year
even when you don't.
He's a good listener.
What's that scar from?
Rudolph is an ass.
It's a minor bowel resection
for diverticulitis
eight months ago.
Oh, we need to do a contrast CT.
You need to come with me.
Dr. Lim,
he has it, too.
There, on his neck.
A rash.
It wasn't there earlier.
It hasn't fully developed, but
it could be the same thing.
It can't be.
I had on a mask, gloves...
Did you keep on the mask
the whole time?
Not... With airborne diseases,
that's important...
It's Marianne.
Her O2 SATs are crashing.
Get another dose of
I.V. methylprednisolone.
We need to move up
the transplant.
No, it doesn't change anything.
You'll be anesthetized,
you won't feel a thing
and when you wake up,
your son will be on his
way to being healthy.
We'll see you soon.
Sorry I couldn't meet you
at the airport.
That's a cool t-shirt.
It probably freaks
you out, right?
Like, "is he gonna
gender-transition or something?"
No, if that's your thing,
I'm cool.
How long am I stuck here?
Just for the rest of this shift.
And then I'm out of here
for three days.
There's a new rock-climbing
gym we can check out,
and the batting cages.
I'm good.
I got a season of
"Rick and Morty" on my phone.
Clear.
That's six rounds of defib.
And 30 minutes of CPR.
Okay, Dr. Murphy,
you can stop.
I just spoke
with Dr. Andrews.
We're on soft quarantine
while he consults the Board.
Call dispatch, put all
ambulances on diversion.
Do your best to stop
all walk-ins.
Say we're at capacity
and send them to County.
Stall all discharges.
Tyler stays in isolation
and on antivirals.
Fever is likely the next
stage, so keep a close eye.
What else are we dealing with?
I always have lunch
by 2:00.
It's 2:15.
I need to eat.
I've got a banana in my bag
if you want it.
A banana isn't lunch.
A turkey sandwich and milk
is lunch.
Dr. Murphy,
patients first,
then we'll work
on that sandwich.
What else? 60-year-old
woman with angina,
visiting her family
for the holidays.
Forgot her blood pressure meds.
Came in for a prescription.
Her refill just got delayed.
What else?
The crib was almost finished
when the screwdriver slipped.
My family doctor's closed
for the holidays.
They would've sent you
here anyway.
This type of injury can
cause permanent damage.
Makes me feel less guilty for
bringing my baby into a germ pit.
No offense.
Guessing this is your first?
My husband and I
waited a long time.
I want everything to be perfect.
Which, as my husband
reminds me, is impossible.
Yet, my birth plan is five pages long.
All closed up.
So I can go home?
Not before we do a nerve study.
I would hate for you to lose
feeling in your fingers.
You can't leave.
I'm sorry.
What? Hospital policy.
Look, I'm...
I'm not a patient.
All right, I just came down here to
get some chips. My dad's a doctor.
Who's your dad?
Dr. Alex Park.
Can you call him?
My phone's charging upstairs.
I'll call him, so he knows where
to come find you when he's free.
But for now,
you've got to stay put.
Why? Because I'm older than you.
Find the employee contact
list, call Park.
He should know where his son is.
Sure.
I feel so much worse than
when I was having a heart attack.
I don't doubt it.
Because of the urgency
of your situation,
we used combined leukapheresis,
chemo, and radiation.
You're no longer at risk for
another heart attack or stroke.
And I also no longer
have an immune system.
My donor's on his way, right?
I spoke with him. He said
he was getting in his car.
When was that?
I'll follow up.
He's still finding
new ways to let me down.
I thought you guys
were gonna do a C.T.
We're doing a KUB X-ray instead.
It's almost as good.
Why would you go with "almost"?
Can you hear that?
Hear what?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a patient.
You'll need to speak
with a nurse.
I've been waiting
to speak to a nurse.
You must hear that.
The light is buzzing.
I don't hear anything.
It's loud
and very distracting.
It needs to be fixed.
You like Italian?
La Nostra?
It's great.
Barbecue? Ethiopian?
What are you talking about?
Where we're going on our date.
You haven't asked me on one,
and I haven't said yes.
Who turns down the request
of a man trapped in isolation?
What about sushi?
Everybody likes it.
Also, I'm pretty good
with chopsticks.
Never hurts to display
a little manual dexterity.
You know, tends to impress.
I will want a cocktail to soothe
my nerves, but...
Why would you be nervous?
Have you seen you?
You are smart
as well as beautiful,
and I will need all the tools in
my toolkit to dazzle you, so...
No drink for me.
Have one after the appetizers.
I'll be impressed by then.
You have a fever.
He has a fever, and the rash
is fully materialized.
Okay.
Here we go.
Quarantine has been approved.
Yeah.
Can I have everyone's attention?
This emergency room and everyone
in it is now under quarantine.
We're hoping none of you
have been exposed,
but a serious respiratory virus
has infected three patients.
What?
This can't happen.
We're starting everyone on
antivirals just as a precaution.
We'll also be bringing in
food and water,
so if any of you have any dietary
restrictions, please let us know now.
You can't make us stay here.
That's right.
I-I can't... Especially not
if someone's seriously ill.
We are legally entitled to
keep you for...
They locked us in.
Are we locked in?
Oh, no way.
I gotta get out.
Sir.
Sorry.
Like it or not,
no one's leaving.
The decision to implement
the quarantine
was made after consultation
with the Board.
The CDC has been kept
fully informed,
and we will be proceeding in
accordance with all protocol...
Shaun, Morgan, and Lim
are in there.
And our patient is out here.
There's still no sign of the
donor. He's not answering my calls.
I asked my contact at San Jose
PD to do a home check-in.
Park.
He's down there?
How... Yeah,
put him on.
It's Security... Kellan's
stuck in the quarantine.
I'll pass along anything
I hear from San Jose PD.
Tyler started coughing.
Let's up his antivirals. Start
high flow oxygen and zosyn
to counter
any underlying infection.
Santa Pete has
a sigmoid volvulus,
he needs surgery very soon.
My call ended 37 minutes ago.
I'm supposed to be somewhere
else, It's important.
No, it's not.
We need a non-surgical fix
to a bowel obstruction.
Anyone?
Murphy.
Mmm.
You got something?
Not really.
Anything at all.
Please.
We...
We usually...
We usually make a hole and...
And come at an obstruction
from the side,
but we can't.
We need to use
the existing holes.
An endoscope risks tearing
right through the bowel.
A saline enema doesn't.
And it might untwist the bowel.
Simple, but it could work.
Nice.
I'm fine.
Do you have your inhaler?
Of course I do.
What were you doing down here?
This isn't my fault.
If you hadn't been working...
Kellan.
I know you must be scared.
I'm fine.
I'm keeping this hat on
for luck.
Here we go.
I'm threading the tube
into the rectum.
Now, slowly push the saline.
That's...
It's not a pleasant experience.
I'm getting some
resistance to flow.
I must've reached
the obstruction.
Push harder.
Hang in there, Pete.
Call me Santa...
Ahhh!
Keep pushing the saline.
I'm sorry, Santa.
I feel so much better.
We've got you on a
pretty high dose of antivirals.
So, what's next?
We're debating nitric oxide...
No, I mean if
this doesn't turn around.
What happens to me next?
ARDS.
Then full respiratory failure.
Hey, I've got a new idea
for our first date.
Archery.
I used to compete
when I was young.
Basically, you'd be showing off.
I can show you some tricks.
Teach you a spit-finger hook,
how to anchor...
And then proceed
to demolish you.
Well, that sounds like a reason to live.
I'm here to take you
to your imaging appointment.
Where's Shaun?
Shaun is quarantined in the E.R.
Quarantined? What, what...
What quarantine?
Apparently for some highly
contagious, deadly virus.
But Shaun sounds fine.
Except for some buzzing light
and his concern about lunch
and you missing your appointment
at the imaging clinic, so...
Let's go. Take me
to the hospital.
We are going to your
appointment and making sure
your think-melon
remains tumor-free.
Take me to the hospital please.
I'd like to help.
How?
By taking your old job back
and saving the day?
Putting on an "Outbreak" suit
and rescuing Shaun?
Some people may find
your sassy attitude appealing.
I'm not one of them.
And I am crushed.
Sir, I'm sorry.
You can't...
My wife's in there.
Viola! Look, that's her.
I need to get in there.
They're setting up a room
inside for friends and family.
Clifton, what are you doing?
Look, I'm coming in. Stop...
Let go of me!
Calm down
or you're gonna get hurt.
Stop.
This is all my fault.
No. If I'd put the crib
together like you asked...
Forget about the crib.
I need you to take care
of yourself.
Because if something
happens to me...
our son needs someone
to take care of him.
It's... It's a boy?
I'm sorry I'm ruining
your surprise.
No.
Baby, I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I love you.
Dr. Shaun Murphy.
Shaun?
Why are you answering
our donor's phone?
Because he's here in quarantine.
What happened to the CDC
getting a team here today?
They confirmed that it
started in Malaysia last week.
Between the virologists
already there
and the ones grounded on the East
Coast because of the snowstorm...
Stay on them.
What do we know about the virus?
Similar symptoms to SARS,
but much faster moving.
Is Bob Cravens infected?
Not so far.
Currently Tyler Durnes, the EMT,
is the only person
displaying symptoms.
I need his bone marrow.
I'd like to go in and get it.
I'll comply with all protocol.
You're not hot zone certified.
None of us are.
My leukemia patient
has no immune system.
He'll die soon without
a marrow transplant.
Well, then you best find him
another donor
because no one, or their bone
marrow, is leaving that quarantine.
Have you heard from County about
taking our PICU transfers?
H-How are my O2 SATs?
Holding steady.
Do you want to call anyone?
Uh, I, uh...
I... I thought about
letting my mom know...
what was going on, but...
She'd just worry about me
and feel bad she's not here.
So...
She... She knows I love her.
How's it going in here?
Dr. Reznick was just telling me
about some college lesbian experiences...
Was that just my imagination?
Actually, we were talking
about your mother.
Interesting.
I don't like the drop
in his O2 SATs.
Let's start him on nitric oxide.
I knew you liked me.
He's in this hospital?
Bob actually came through for once.
Unfortunately, we can't
wait for him to get out of quarantine.
But we found an alternative
donor in the Bay Area.
How compatible are they?
They share five out of eight
of your markers.
Bob is a much better match.
I can't handle marrow rejection,
or having to repeat
this nightmare.
That's a symptom
of the MAC pneumonia.
The antibiotics aren't working.
You need bone marrow, or this
infection is going to kill you. Soon.
Days, not weeks.
Seven years I've been
battling leukemia.
Been through four
full courses of chemo,
so many trips to the hospital
I've lost count.
Just knowing my father
showed up,
I'm grateful, relieved.
I'm okay if this is the end.
I'd like to sign a DNR.
Chris, the CDC will be here
tomorrow.
If they can identify the
virus, we can test Bob.
If he's negative... Whatever you
can manage before my heart stops,
go for it.
Please get me the form.
His fever's climbing.
Give the nebulizer time to work.
Cooling blankets,
that could help.
I'll go get some from
the supply closet.
Put your mask back on.
Why?
Because I'm infected.
You got it, too?
You guys any closer
to figuring this thing out?
Afraid not.
On the bright side, I...
I think I'm growing on Morgan.
There's got to be a way.
You can't go in.
Bob can't come out.
The marrow can't come out.
What if it doesn't?
What if the marrow never leaves?
Are we suggesting we put a man with
no immune system into the quarantine?
We expand the quarantine,
create a section just for him.
One of the doctors inside could do
the extraction and the transplant.
And then one of two things happens.
He stays in isolation till we
know he hasn't been infected.
Or it kills him.
There's no way Andrews will
let us expand the quarantine.
Wish me luck.
Going to 360 Joules.
Clear.
We can crack his chest
and do cardiac massage.
Dr. Reznick.
Have Petringa bring in
the internal paddles
from the trauma bay...
Morgan.
Hey, Doogie.
You didn't hear me
talking to you?
My sugar's crazy high. 650.
That doesn't make sense.
I gave you the proper
dosage of insulin.
10 units.
10 units?
10 units doesn't even make
a dent with me.
You got a doctor around here
who knows what he's doing?
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
I'll give you another 10 units.
Waste of time.
Make it 20.
I'll give you 10.
What's wrong with you?
You sound like an idiot.
Don't be a jerk.
Mind your own business.
Doc. Doc, I don't
feel so...
Ahhh!
What the hell?
Did he just infect me?
Possibly.
I need to examine your abdomen.
Your obstruction has returned.
You need surgery, now.
But we're stuck in here.
And there's no operating room.
We will have to improvise.
There's no Neptune machine.
Without suction, the surgical
field will be filled with blood.
We can use the wall suction,
set to continuous.
That'll do.
No electrocautery
to control the bleeding.
You'll have to do this
combat style.
Tie off each artery
before you cut.
Dr. Reznick.
Are you ready?
Because I think we are.
I'll go get the patient.
You should lie down.
He's out.
Scalpel.
If we expand the
quarantine, I can do the transplant.
The only technical breach
will be...
She's infected.
Melendez.
Yeah.
Take down the adhesions on the sigmoid.
How are his vitals?
Holding steady, Doctor.
That's dead bowel.
It's perforated.
Damn it.
NURSE
PETRINGA: I need a doctor!
Petringa needs help.
If I don't secure these clamps,
there'll be stool everywhere.
Murphy, go.
He signed a DNR.
He shouldn't have.
This is battery.
He doesn't need to die.
We're gonna get
his donor's marrow.
Andrews agreed to the plan?
Not yet.
If he doesn't, we'll think
of something else.
He said he was
feeling lightheaded.
I hear you,
but please stay back.
- He's...
- Is he infected?
From when Santa vomited on him?
He should go to isolation.
He's in...
hypoglycemic shock.
Give him D50.
It's spreading.
Kellan!
- DR.
- Kellan!
Kellan!
Kellan! Kellan!
Dr. Glassman?
Hi.
We got what we needed for images.
You are okay to go.
We'll send them to Dr. Blaize.
Anything I should be worried about?
You're seeing Dr. Blaize
before the holiday?
As a matter of fact,
I'm seeing her now.
So, I could just show her
the hard copy.
I'm not supposed to do that.
Oh, no. I know.
I've been a neurosurgeon
for, like, 100 years.
I understand protocol.
I'm not gonna look at it.
I just want
to move things along.
Thank you.
It's back.
Suction.
I must've nicked a branch of the
inferior mesenteric artery.
I can't see where.
Can you feel it?
I think so. Use your
finger to plug the hole.
Now what?
Dr. Lim?
Everyone, calm down.
Hey, Kellan!
Kellan! Look at me!
Look at me!
Breathe!
Can... Can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Help my son!