Shaun...
You need to give me
your driver's license.
No, I don't.
- Do you remember the memory test I gave you?
- Vividly.
Yes. It demonstrated
you have a deficit.
A deficit. You shouldn't be driving.
Dr. Blaize agreed.
Shaun, that test was supposed
to be between us,
that's why I didn't want
to do it at the hospital.
Yes, your doctor needs
to be informed
of the results
of all your medical tests.
Even tests
that are done at home.
Shaun, I've been driving
for like half a century.
I'm an excellent driver,
okay?
I don't need to give you
my driver's license.
Okay. Then I'll have
to notify the DMV.
Dr. Glassman?
You're not gonna notify
the DMV, Shaun.
Yes, I will notify
the DMV.
Shaun, you will not
notify the DMV.
Dr. Glassman,
if you don't give me
your driver's license,
I will notify the DMV.
NURSE: Dr. Glassman?
George Reynolds, 28,
sudden onset of arm
and leg weakness,
right facial droop,
and trouble speaking.
CT confirmed a middle cerebral
artery embolism.
I booked us
into interventional radiology.
When did you first notice
your symptoms, George?
About, uh,
four and a half hours ago.
Wait,
what's wrong with me?
You may be having a stroke.
You're on monthly injections
of Lupron?
For three months.
That may have
caused this.
Do you have
prostate cancer?
No. I... I was diagnosed
with atypical hyperplasia.
That shouldn't have any effect
on what we're gonna do now.
We're gonna take care of you,
George. Don't worry.
♪♪
SHAUN: This is local anesthetic,
you'll feel a pinch.
Are you a real doctor?
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
People ever call you
Murph?
No.
I'm going to make
a small incision
so we can insert the tube
and re-inflate your lung.
What do they call you,
Billy?
(SCOFFS)
CraterHead, Volcano,
ThreeEyes,
those are just
the creative ones.
Hold tight.
Here comes the tube...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
You guys really know
what you're doing.
Yes, we do.
We'll order an MRI
for your lungs.
Then we will fix
your fractured eye orbit,
that will require surgery.
What do you say
we fix your forehead, too?
You could do that?
- I think so...
- I don't think so.
It's a pre-existing condition, and
it's not medically necessary.
It shouldn't be approved.
♪♪
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
The MCA clot is obstructing
all distal flow.
CLAIRE: Anti-androgens aren't
indicated for hyperplasia...
He said atypical.
You think he's lying?
Maybe he's
gender transitioning.
Aside from cancer, there
aren't many other indications.
Let's focus
on what we do know.
Feeding the catheter.
Suctioning the thrombus,
and he's recanalizing.
Slowly retract.
Whatever his reasons are
for taking anti-androgens,
hopefully
there are options.
He either drops them or he's
gonna keep having strokes.
♪♪
The forehead repair would be
expensive and cosmetic...
It's not
about prettying him up,
it could give him
a new life, friends,
maybe a few less beatings.
Stopping the beatings
is the guards' job.
You really don't have
any empathy for Billy?
Empathy is a bad reason
to fight for someone.
If empathy makes me
only want to help patients
who are from Wyoming
or have ASD,
then that's very unfair
to all my neuro-typical
patients from Idaho.
I need to take
those drugs.
They caused your stroke.
We don't think
you have hyperplasia.
If you tell us
the real reason,
I'm sure there are
other safer treatments...
No, there aren't!
If you're transitioning,
there are alternatives...
I told you
why I was taking the meds.
George,
we are your doctors,
we need to know
the truth.
We're not gonna
tell anyone.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I'm not transitioning.
And I don't have
hyperplasia.
I have problems...
With my sex drive.
I know it sounds stupid, like why
can't I just control myself, but...
It's all I think about.
It's all I can think about.
I can't work,
I can't socialize,
I can't have a life.
And those meds
are the only thing
that makes it
even remotely tolerable.
They'll kill you.
(SCOFFS)
AOKI: The residents
have a betting pool
on who you're going
to appoint
as your replacement
as Chief of Surgery.
The decision needs to be made
with decorum and expediency.
I haven't quite gotten
around to analyzing...
You've had little face time
with your attendings
since you became
president.
You need to correct that.
I've scheduled
your announcement.
You've got two days.
♪♪
- Where is he?
- He's gone, signed out AMA.
- I tried...
- How long ago?
Five minutes...
Why are we
in a hurry?
I was researching
alternative meds for him.
Realized Lupron didn't
make any sense.
Prescribing anti-androgens
for sexual urges
is like hitting a mosquito
with a mallet.
Unless
they're deviant urges.
We might've just released
a child molester.
♪♪
(AIR BRAKES HISS)
DR. REZNICK: Should
we call the police?
We can't.
We have
no evidence of a crime.
DR. PARK: Lim's at 3 to 2,
Melendez is just behind at 2 to 1,
Cooperberg's 7 to 1, and if
Dartling, or anybody else comes in,
you can retire.
Andrews might bail
on Melendez
when he finds out
our patient bolted.
Which is why Melendez
is now 4 to 1.
Pari-mutuel betting
is very exciting.
Do you need empathy to be
a good doctor?
No. I think
it can interfere
with effective
decision-making.
She's just saying that to
avoid hurting your feelings,
thus making her
fake point for real.
Her empathy
made her lie to you.
I think
you just agreed with me
and insulted me
at the same time.
I think empathy's
very important...
Telling the cold hard truth
even when it hurts,
sometimes is the most
empathetic thing we can do.
Which is what I'm doing
for Shaun right now.
You're welcome.
I have autism
which means I have a
deficiency of mirror neurons,
which inhibits me from emotionally
trading places with people,
which makes empathy
very difficult.
Does that mean
I can't be a good doctor?
No, it doesn't.
We all have our strengths
and weaknesses, Shaun.
One of Claire's is making sure
everyone feels validated.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
The creep is back.
♪♪
Is George having
another stroke?
No.
Severe lacerations
to the scrotum.
Did you give him
anything for pain?
Morphine. Four milligrams.
And I notified the cops.
I think
it was a hate crime.
Yeah, I don't think so.
♪♪
All right.
On my count.
One, two, three.
We'll take it from here.
I'll pack him
and prep him.
You did this to yourself,
didn't you?
I think I know what kind
of urges you've been having.
I'm not a monster.
I never touched anyone...
Any... Child.
My sister and I
were always best friends...
But then she had children.
If I can't keep taking
the drugs...
...I had to do this.
Home surgery tends
to not have
the results
you're hoping for.
You did a lot of damage but
your testicles are unscathed.
(SIGHS)
Please, finish the job.
- I say we do it, he's a pedophile.
- No, he's not.
He just told us he was.
He has never acted
on his urges,
and he's asking us to do something
to ensure he never does.
- He is a decent person trying...
- I'm confused.
What do you want
to do with him?
Treat him like a patient
with a diagnosis.
Put him
on antidepressants,
refer him to a urologist,
give him a psych eval.
Let the experts determine if
he should have a castration.
Psych eval?
Antidepressants?
When we refer people
for counseling,
how often
do they get cured?
I am looking to help him
manage this dis...
And if they don't get cured,
what happens?
They get more depressed,
can't cope, quit jobs,
maybe kill themselves?
All bad, but not
rape-a-child bad.
DR. ANDREWS:
So what are you going to do?
We can't ethically remove healthy
organs for crime prevention.
We don't amputate
a kleptomaniac's hands
to prevent them
from stealing.
Hands have many purposes,
the balls of a pedophile
have but one.
Set up his referrals
and patch him up.
♪♪
How long you been
in Foothills?
Nine months.
Time flies in juvie.
Any visitors?
I don't have a granny bringing me
cookies, if that's what you mean.
This is why empathy
is bad.
You're talking to our patient
because you like him,
which is causing him
to move,
which is affecting
our imagery.
He's scared.
I'm talking to him
to calm him down
which is improving
our imagery.
The fact that I like him
is beside the point.
You grow up in San Jose?
East Paly, but I got out
of there as soon as I could...
I was 15.
Your parents still there?
Mom's gone,
dear old Dad is terrible.
Siblings?
Little brother...
He's gone too.
Crappy dad.
Lost his brother...
- I mean, you really don't ha...
- He's not scared.
He's short of breath because
his diaphragm is lacerated.
His stomach has passed through
that tear and is now in his chest.
Billy needs emergency surgery
on his diaphragm.
DR. PARK: The defect
reaches all the way
from the center
to the anterior costal margin.
DR. LIM:
So what do we need to do?
Divide the inferior pulmonary
ligament to bring the lung upwards.
Uh-huh.
Mesh.
Whoever kicked him was
wearing some serious footwear.
And they'll be waiting for him when
he goes back. Unless we help him.
Dr. Park wants
to fix his forehead.
The constitution
guarantees prisoners
get the same care
as everyone else.
Most non-prisoners can't
afford cosmetic surgery.
He would be getting better
care than everyone else.
Kid is smart and personable and puts up a
great front. But he's scared to death.
And he got 36 months
for selling weed,
a crime that doesn't
even exist anymore.
You think his life
would be anything like this
if he didn't grow up with a
massive dent in his head?
Sorry,
I'm not convinced.
Is that because you don't have
any empathy for Billy?
No. It's because
I agree with you.
It's expensive, risky
and unnecessary.
But empathy can be
an invaluable motivator,
Dr. Murphy, that truly connects
the physician with their patient.
(WHISPERS)
Is he still up there?
♪♪
(WHISPERS) Yes he is.
We can't do the castration,
George.
Not without the proper
psychiatric clearance.
That'll take forever.
Just a few months.
A few months is forever.
Binge watch your favorite shows,
catch up on your reading.
You attracted to men,
Dr. Reznick?
Yes. Adult men.
And if that
were reprehensible,
do you think
you could stop?
You have no idea
what it's like
to live
with these thoughts.
I hate them,
and I hate myself
for having them.
But I can't stop them.
And I'm afraid
of what I could do.
♪♪
We will start the process
immediately.
In the meantime, we'll transfuse
you, get you on antibiotics...
No.
I'm refusing treatment.
No transfusion. No antibiotics.
No repair.
Let 'em rot.
We have something
in common.
Neither of us has
a driver's license.
How do you feel about
not having a driver's license?
I'm pissed, Shaun.
You feel pissed.
Yes, I feel pissed.
I feel very pissed
because something important
was taken away from me.
And by a friend.
You feel very pissed
because something important
was taken away from you,
and by a friend.
And parroting everything
I say isn't helping.
I'm finding commonality,
Dr. Glassman,
and inquiring
about your emotional state,
and actively listening
by restating your responses.
"External corroboration enhances
our sense of self-worth."
Okay.
The day after I got
my driver's license,
you want to know
what I did?
I went out and bought a 1963
Galaxie, Midnight Blue. 1,255 bucks,
every penny I earned for the past
three years working in a gas station.
How do you think
that made me feel?
You liked it?
No, Shaun.
I loved it.
You want to know why?
Because a car to a 16-year-old
kid means independence,
which means he can go
wherever he wants
whenever he wants.
And that doesn't change
with age, Shaun,
in fact,
it means even more.
When you took my license,
that's what you took from me.
I don't expect you
to understand.
So you don't have
to pretend.
Hey.
Is Andrews stalking you?
- Yeah.
- It's annoying.
We need to stand together
and tell him to back off.
(LAUGHS)
I'm not telling the president
he's annoying.
He's infringing
on our autonomy
and inhibiting
the free flow of ideas,
both of which affect
our ability
to deliver
the best patient care.
That sounds
slightly better.
Okay. I'm in.
- Are you?
- No. Of course not.
The last thing I'm gonna do right now
is confront him. I'm the front-runner.
Not according to Vegas.
I'm 3 to 2.
(LAUGHS)
Guess they don't know that you
have double my mortality rate.
I'm a trauma surgeon,
you're comparing apples
to asshats.
I resent
being called an apple.
The diaphragm repair
went very well.
And we've scheduled
your orbital fracture repair.
We'll get you some stronger
pain meds for the recovery.
When are you gonna
fix my forehead,
make me all John Legend?
I tried, Billy.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't really getting
my hopes up anyway.
My dad taught me that.
He'd say,
"You know what, Billy?"
And he'd just punch me
in the face.
At least, I think that was the
lesson he was trying to impart.
That's what happened
to your forehead?
He was a big A's fan.
Watched every game
with a bat in his hand.
August 14th, 2008,
they lost
in the 12th inning...
♪♪
(GEORGE GROANS)
Infection's setting in,
but his testicles
still show good flow
on the Doppler.
- Pain meds?
- He won't take them.
Thinks they'll knock him out and
we'll step in and repair them.
(GROANING)
I hate this.
Me too.
(GROANING)
I'm going to be
a good driver.
I got every answer correct
on the written test.
Except one, but that was because
it was improperly worded.
I told the DMV
they need to rewrite it
and they said they'd
take it under advisement.
Great.
Let's go.
♪♪
Okay,
let's close our eyes
and take
some nice, deep breaths...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
And how about
a little guided imagery
to evoke
positive visualizations?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay.
Let's picture
the parking lot,
the cars around us,
the yellow steel thingy at the
entrance of the parking lot
that could really do
a lot of damage...
A bollard.
The speed bump that is
15 feet from the corner
with the stop sign that someone
put a "Hate" sticker on
so it says "Stop Hate,"
which is right in front
of the Jiff-E Mart,
which says it's open
"8 til Late, 24/7,"
- which can't be true beca...
- That's great, Shaun.
Super amount
of visualization.
And now that we're feeling
comfortable about our surroundings,
we can put the car
into drive,
ease our foot
off the brake...
Very nice...
We can open our eyes now,
Shaun.
What we're doing is cruel.
I'm open to all options,
Dr. Browne.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to give us some privacy.
Really?
You want to throw the president of the
hospital out of a medical discussion?
You're infringing
on my autonomy
and inhibiting
the free flow of ideas,
both of which affect
my ability
to deliver
the best patient care.
Dr. Melendez.
(DOOR OPENS)
♪♪
SHAUN:
There are many drivers
not following
the rules of the road.
They fail to signal,
check their blind spots,
display a red flag
when the load extends
more than four feet
past the tail lamp.
You're right, Shaun,
it's a mad world.
But there's nothing
you can do about them,
you just got
to focus on you.
Yes, let's focus on me.
Yes.
Let's take
the next right.
You can drive
in the bike lane
when you're this close
to the turn, Shaun.
No, I can't.
It's a broken line.
That was the improperly
worded question,
whether it's broken
or solid,
you can't enter
the bike lane
this distance
from the intersection.
I told them
that it...
Okay, Shaun. You don't
have to go so slow.
(HORN HONKS)
She's in the lane, she's not
supposed to be in the lane.
It's a violation
carrying a fine...
Okay, Shaun, don't worry
about what she's doing...
- No.
- Shaun, you have to pull into the bike lane...
Don't worry
about what she's doing...
(TIRES SCREECH, HORN HONKS)
You can't just stop.
Shaun,
you can't just stop...
(HORNS HONKING,
CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY)
Shaun!
George is screaming
in agony
and we are doing nothing except
hiding behind ethical red tape.
Ethical red tape is there
to protect people like him
from making permanent
regrettable mistakes.
I'm glad we're not using it
to cover our asses
the day before the new
Chief of Surgery is announced.
(SIGHS)
Let me sign off
on the documentation.
I'll note his scrotum
is already beyond repair
and surgical castration
is our only option.
- I vote yes.
- No.
I'm not gonna let anyone
falsify medical records.
Not for pain.
Not for a pedophile.
Once his testes
are actually beyond repair,
we will castrate him.
So we're just gonna
leave him there screaming,
keeping his entire unit
awake?
Move him.
DR. LIM: I'd like a clean dissection
through the periosteal planes
so I can slip the MEDPOR mesh
over the fracture.
Why do I prefer
MEDPOR mesh?
It allows
fibrovascular ingrowth
and integration
of the patient's tissue.
Prisoner surgeries
are approved
for psychological reasons
all the time.
Tattoo removal,
gender reassignments
include breast implants.
Hell, if he had a crappy smile we
could justify dental work as needed
for proper mastication.
You sent a few kids
to juvie?
More than a few.
You feel guilty.
Think that's maybe clouding
your judgment?
Maybe.
You're afraid of ruffling Andrews'
feathers this close to decision day.
Think that's maybe
clouding yours?
We could give Billy
a breast implant.
We could insert it over his split
thickness frontal bone defect.
It would only require a tiny
incision at his eyebrow.
Now you're in favor
of this?
I was against it because it was too
expensive and unnecessary and risky,
but if we do it now,
it won't require
any additional surgery,
and it'd be
very economical.
He did give us verbal consent
when he was first admitted.
Keep him under.
Get what we need,
Dr. Murphy.
♪♪
(GEORGE SCREAMING, GROANING)
(GROANING STOPS)
Ready or not...
Tell Melendez to meet us
in the OR.
CLAIRE: Showing signs
of ischemia,
we have a strong medical case
for removing.
Dr. Lim.
You a castration fan?
Right now, I am.
- Andrews told me he's backing off.
- Great.
Because you presented him
with a very good argument.
My argument.
Which you regurgitated to him
right after you said you wouldn't
back me up. Call that leadership?
Yes, I do.
You presented me
with a very good argument,
but you didn't have the guts to
take it to Andrews on your own.
One more reason I don't
want to work under you.
You don't want this promotion so
that you can improve the hospital.
You want it
for the pretty title.
You're an adrenaline junky. You won't last
two weeks liaising with board members.
There's a long
and dusty trail
littered with people
who have underestimated me.
JL: We're ready to go.
Curved tissue scissors,
please.
(MONITORS BEEPING RAPIDLY)
DR. REZNICK: His systolic is 68.
And look at this.
- He's septic.
- He's going into D.I.C.
Rerun his labs.
Have platelets, plasma
and cryo ready.
If he starts bleeding,
he'll die.
I reduced the volume
from 80 cc's to 35.
♪♪
Have the odds changed
in the last 24 hours?
- Little.
- Where am I at?
6 to 1.
I'll put $100 on me.
(MONITORS BEEPING RAPIDLY)
He's becoming
severely bradycardic.
The pressure on his orbit
caused a retrobulbar hematoma.
DR. LIM: If we don't relieve it now,
he'll arrest. Forceps and scissors.
Just lost his pulse,
pushing atropine.
Set up a temporary
transcutaneous pacemaker.
If we inject the orbital
muscle with local anesthetic
we might be able
to fatigue the reflex.
Do it.
(FLATLINE)
Starting CPR.
I hope
that's a look of resolve.
Melendez stood up to me
in front of his residents.
I did the same thing to
O'Connell when I was his age.
What about Lim?
She has the kind of focus
that took me years to develop.
And Cooperberg, he reminds
me of me when I was...
Marcus. You were good.
But no one's gonna be as good
as you think you were.
One of your weaknesses
was decision-making.
I trust you've gotten past that
since I made you president.
♪♪
DR. LIM: Continuing compressions until
I have capture on the pacemaker.
Pacing pads
are in position.
Stopping CPR.
Injecting lidocaine.
I have set the rate
to 80.
(FLATLINE CONTINUES)
DR. LIM: Increase the
ventricular by two milliamps.
(BEEPS)
♪♪
Increase by two more.
- (BEEPS)
- (FLATLINE CONTINUES)
♪♪
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Blood pressure is
responding, 102 over 68.
DR. LIM:
Keep those pacer settings
and let's get back
to the main event.
DR. REZNICK: Both his PT and
PTT are coming back down,
his systolic is stable at 110,
and no ectopy on the monitor.
His D.I.C. score is back
under four. He's stabilized.
Ball's in your court.
Dr. Melendez?
Effects of low testosterone on
cardiovascular function and sepsis?
CLAIRE: Possible acute
vascular response,
circulatory collapse...
And what about
on D.I.C.?
DR. REZNICK: Increased risk
of clots and stroke.
George's body
can't tolerate
any loss of testosterone
right now.
We want to save his life,
we have to save his testicles.
Sutures.
(SIGHS)
I know
how to get you to drive.
I can't drive.
Driving
is just like surgery.
Say you're driving
down the street
and suddenly, somebody
steps off the sidewalk,
right in front of you.
Things like that
must happen
when you're deep inside
someone's belly.
That doesn't make
any sense.
It's an analogy, Shaun. I need you
to work with me just a little bit.
Give me.
Okay.
It would be
something unexpected,
out of our control,
from an aberrant source,
and very bad.
It would be analogous
to an arterial bleed.
How about if a truck stalls
out, crippling traffic?
A thrombus impeding blood
flow, so we divert.
A thrombus, exactly.
What if you're just
cruising along
and a car comes out of nowhere
and goes racing by?
A tachyarrhythmia.
- Yes! Shaun, you got this.
- Yes.
So let's get you driving
that hooptie.
(CHUCKLES)
I've got this, Albert.
♪♪
We did the surgery.
Your circulatory and clotting
systems were shutting down.
But removing your testicles
would have put you
at greater risk
by reducing your...
You would have died.
♪♪
I've set you up with a
psychiatrist and a urologist.
They'll screen you,
get you cleared,
and then we can do this
the right way.
George,
we can get this done.
You just cannot
try this again.
I get it.
I do it your way,
or it just doesn't happen.
♪♪
It's just another
intersection, Shaun,
just like the last one
and just like the next one...
The last intersection isn't where everyone
honked at me and made me freeze...
That was a different day,
with different drivers
and a different Shaun
behind the wheel,
because today,
this Shaun has a plan
for this intersection,
which is...
...I am going
to dissect it.
Damn right you are.
And today,
you're gonna turn right
which you will do by...
Determining laterality.
And waiting until I can
legally enter the bike lane.
♪♪
Somebody just made
a turn...
Shaun!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HORN BLARES)
MAN: Everybody okay?
You were wrong.
You were wrong, Lea.
I can't drive.
Shaun, I thought
I had it figured out.
I can't drive.
I...
Surgery is mechanical.
Mechanics are predictable.
Driving is subject
to human foibles
which means there are
limitless possibilities.
You're right.
My metaphor sucked.
It sucked very much.
Because...
Becoming a surgeon is about
way more than operating.
You had to learn
about interacting
with teachers,
co-workers, patients, bosses.
Cooperating with them,
communicating with them...
I am very bad
at communicating.
Shaun,
you became a surgeon,
one of the hardest things
that anyone can do.
And you proved that just
because something is hard,
doesn't mean
you can't do it.
And look what you just did.
I just hit a trash can.
Exactly, a trash can instead of
an oncoming car or a pedestrian.
You did great, Shaun.
(SIGHS)
That soccer ball was
a dropped Metzenbaum.
I know, right?
When I accidentally drop
an instrument in the OR,
I react quickly
to minimize damage.
- Yes.
I dropped a Metzenbaum.
♪♪
I can drive this hooptie.
DR. PARK:
Window's about to close.
$10 will get you $20
on Melendez,
$10 will get you $1,000
if you want to bet on me.
Hey, everybody.
I can't be prouder
of all of you.
We have grown into a preeminent
surgical department,
which has been recognized
with the official designation
of Surgical Center
of Excellence.
(APPLAUSE)
It's now more important
than ever
that we maintain
our high standards.
And so, while there are
many worthy candidates,
I've decided...
...to retain the title myself.
Thank you.
(APPLAUSE)
Thank you!
♪♪
Yes!
(DR. PARK LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
♪♪
(GASPS) Y...
(SIGHS)
You... You did it.
You...
You really did it.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
DR. PARK: It was his idea.
Murph? You...
We inserted a small breast implant
to fill in the depression
and create a more aesthetically
pleasing contour.
(CHUCKLING)
Breast implant?
Yes.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
You saved my life.
♪♪
It was a mistake.
It caused an oculocardiac
reflex and you almost died.
It was a mistake.
George?
Why didn't his
monitor alarm go off?
He was stable, I disconnected it
so he could use the restroom.
- I didn't...
- Morgan! He's gone!
♪♪
George!
(BOTH SCREAM)
♪♪
I was never gonna
confront Andrews.
I was playing you.
But damn if you didn't
actually make it work.
It didn't work
for anybody.
He played us both.
He set us against each other.
(SIGHS)
I think you were right.
Even if you were
just bluffing,
we need to stand together.
Where was that wisdom
two days ago?
Still in the bottle.
(SCOFFS)
♪♪
Hey. How'd you come up
with that idea?
You mentioned breast implants
and I thought...
Of his forehead.
We were operating
on his eye,
his forehead was covered.
Why were you
thinking of it?
You care about him,
you were worried
about his problem.
You empathized with him.
My idea almost killed him.
No, it didn't.
I found these
in Billy's drawer.
Three days of pain meds.
He was cheeking them
to build up a stash.
He wasn't exaggerating.
You saved his life,
Shaun.
♪♪
(INDISTINCT PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
This isn't the way
this should have ended...
But I'm not so sure
the world is a worse place
than it was
a couple hours ago.
LEA: You almost look
comfortable behind the wheel.
SHAUN: This seat has
excellent lumbar support.
But I am still
very nervous.
(HORN HONKS)
(HORN BLARES)
I can drive a car.
I can see that.
Lea taught me
using a very bad analogy.
Nothing works
like a bad analogy.
He's getting
pretty good.
Won't be long
before he gets his operator's.
Your next radiation
appointment is in 45 minutes.
Ow.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SEAT BELT CLICKS)
Thank you.
♪♪
(ENGINE STARTS)
♪ I'd go the whole wide world
just to find her
(TIRES SQUEAL)
♪ I'd go the whole wide world
♪ To find out
where they hide her ♪
♪♪