=You Are My Glory=
=Episode 3=
(Can you be my coach?)
(I think)
(you should find someone else.)
(I might quit this game)
(at any time.)
(Well, could you at least)
(give me some advice when we play?)
(Like telling me where I do wrong,)
(or how it should be done.)
(Is that all right?)
(If you feel like quitting,)
(I'll find someone else.)
(Please, Jade Rabbit God.)
(Okay.)
Okay?
One step at a time.
Since you agreed to the first step,
the second one is not far now.
Wait.
What's the second one?
(Let's get started then.)
Hey, my support character.
(Use Wang Zhaojun.)
(Use Wang Zhaojun?)
(I don't know how to.)
(I haven't tried it before.)
If you guys have a unit competition,
there's a good chance
it's in Draft Mode.
You might not necessarily get Cai Wenji.
It's all right for a newbie
to get Wang Zhaojun.
The summoners' abilities.
Change it to Flash.
Hold on.
Is there something
that I'm not aware of?
What unit competition?
It's the Honor of Kings competition
organized by our unit.
I would like Jade Rabbit God
to teach me.
Look.
Yu Tu is quite a good coach.
Zhai Liang is a good example.
Look how screwed up it was
when he used Xi Shi.
I watched him for a bit
to learn the techniques.
But I learned the rest
all by myself.
Come off it.
Finally,
the kill counts are more
than the number of times slain.
(Why are the opponents
using Wang Zhaojun as well?)
(It feels worse than an outfit clash.)
I won't lead you guys to defeat.
Get to higher ground!
When I was learning acting,
I had to watch the videos
of my seniors repeatedly.
Now, I have to do the same and watch
how I got slain when playing games.
I bet
it's because I have been gifted
with such great beauty.
So all other talents
need to be cut back.
That was so devious.
Yu Tu is way more devious.
That's why we won.
Is this game
all about being devious?
That explains why I lost.
It's all because I'm an upright person.
Chill.
Sure enough.
It's more satisfying
than using Cai Wenji.
Cotton, not bad, huh?
How is it?
I'm doing better now
than I did yesterday, right?
That's really good.
I've been practising
all day today.
Hard work pays off!
I'll prove it with my singing!
I have to save this game.
Cool!
Nice one, girl.
Yu Tu, I never thought
a kill stealer like you
would let her get the kill.
(He let me get the kill?)
(True enough. He let me win.)
He still won't reply to me.
I know you let me win
when I got the Triple Kill.
I've earned enough.
You should get the kill.
Thank you.
Dandan.
Get me
the cosmetics contract.
I'll go over
and discuss the details with them later.
Tell Mr. Wang to get the car ready.
Okay.
Give Mr. Wang a call.
Where's Jingjing?
It's only one o'clock,
and she's gone already?
Jingjing hasn't been here
for a few days now.
Xiao Zhu said she did apply for leave.
She merely asked
for a day off.
Wait, she didn't come here at all
while I was away on the business trip?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll check her place.
Jingjing.
Why didn't you come
in the past two days?
You've been practising at home?
Let me see.
Not bad.
Are you battling AI players?
Are you kidding me?
I'm doing solo queue, all right?
Solo queue?
Not bad, huh?
You have the guts to solo queue now.
I was nervous at first.
But it's better now.
I've reached Gold IV now.
I solo queued and ranked up myself.
What has gotten into you?
You're so good now.
I'm gifted.
That's so awesome.
Let me see.
Wait.
Guo never taught you
how to use this hero.
Did you practise it yourself?
Actually, I asked a game expert
to teach me.
I think he's better than Guo.
That's hard to say.
Is he reliable?
Will he expose your identity?
Don't worry.
I bet he doesn't even know
who I am.
Is he an online friend?
How did he teach you then?
Through the voice chat.
He teaches me how to use the abilities,
how to move,
and what I should do.
I'm going to take a sip.
Let's see.
Which is it?
Open up my friend lists
in the game.
His name is Jade Rabbit Pounding Elixir.
Click on the avatar,
and you can see his performance record.
He has a 93-percent win rate.
For real?
Indeed.
He seems to be better than Guo.
It's a shame.
He's just an online friend.
If there's such a good player
in real life who's that reliable
to teach you in person,
you'll progress
a lot faster.
(Yu Tu)
(exists in real life.)
(If he teaches me in person...)
But it's okay.
Just keep up the training.
There's still a month to go.
You need to step up the game.
Basically,
I've declined all the job offers.
But for those that we accepted
a few months ago,
we still have to fulfil them.
Why are you in a daze?
I know.
You do?
Really?
I'll get going then.
I still have a contract to discuss.
Okay.
Keep it up.
Drink more water.
Protect your skin.
Bye.
Why is Yu Tu
online every day?
He plays games every day.
Is this how he spends his holidays?
(Rabbit God.)
(Do you spend your holidays)
(playing games at home?)
(What does he work as now?)
(It doesn't feel like
he's in the financial industry.)
(Peipei.)
(Do we have any classmates)
(who have a really cool job now?)
(It's you, isn't it?)
(I mean)
(what are those with good grades)
(doing right now?)
(I see. Those guys?)
(Qi Qi is working as an editor-in-chief)
(in a book company.)
(Wang Jiang is now a vice president)
(in one of the top 500 corporations.)
(Who else?)
(Sun Xiu is working in the Office
of the Secretary to the Mayor.)
(How about Yu Tu?)
(I think Yu Tu is working)
(in Aerospace Research Institute
in Shanghai.)
(Aerospace?)
(He's in the aerospace industry?)
(But didn't he study finance)
(back in college?)
(How do you remember so clearly?)
(How would I know)
(why did he join aerospace?)
(Why do you ask?)
(Check this out.)
(Yu Tu)
(bought the air purifier)
(that your friend posted on Moments.)
(It broke down all of a sudden.)
(He called to request a repair,
but he couldn't get through.)
(Could you help him with it?)
(I just managed to reach him.)
(He said)
(he could only go over tomorrow night
to fix it.)
(This is for the kid's room.)
(Could you inform him)
(to come as soon as possible?)
(This kid coughs a lot
when he has a cold.)
(Yu Tu sells purifiers?)
(I think they developed it)
(for civilian use or something.)
(I thought aerospace tech
must be really cool.)
(But still, totally unexpected.)
(Which part is broken?)
(I couldn't turn it on.)
(Are you staying in Minhang?)
(I'll go over and take a look.)
(Why did you send this to me?)
(It was in the group chat.)
(I just recalled.)
(So I sent it to you.)
(He's indeed in the aerospace industry.)
Yu Tu.
Chang'e 1 has been launched.
Someone else
is a step ahead of you.
That's perfect, isn't it?
Perhaps, by the time I graduate,
the moonbase has been built.
I'll use the moon as a starting point
to conquer Mars
and fly through the solar system.
Come off it.
It doesn't cost me anything
to brag, isn't it?
Fine.
You're the top student.
So you must be right.
Wait up!
It turns out that
he didn't give up on his dream.
Yu Tu is in this city too.
(Peipei.)
(Show me the purifier advertisement)
(that Yu Tu sent you.)
(It's time to unleash my acting skills.)
The smog in Shanghai
is too serious.
How about your place?
What a coincidence.
Yu Tu and I are in Shanghai too.
The smog in Hangzhou
is pretty serious too.
The situation in Wuhan
is all right.
What brand of purifier
do you use?
I bought
a Jade Rabbit Air Purifier.
But it broke down after a few days.
Yu Tu?
Isn't that your company's product?
Is that a product
of Jade Rabbit God's company?
That explains it.
I bought it because it's the same
as your name.
What a coincidence.
It's a product developed by our lab
and another company.
Try using another adapter.
A classmate of mine bought it
and said it wasn't working either.
I took a look
and found out it was the adapter.
(Why did this classmate)
(steal my idea?)
I tried using another adapter,
but still, it didn't work.
I called for repair,
but they said it was scheduled
for the day after tomorrow.
But my parents
are having really bad coughs.
The after-sales service isn't that good.
Yu Tu.
Take a look for Cotton.
(What a good line.)
(I have to send So Panicky)
(a set of skin.)
Jade Rabbit God.
You even know how to do that?
Of course.
He is a part-time
troubleshooting expert.
Well, Jade Rabbit God,
could you
take a look at the purifier at my place?
Send me
your contact details.
(That was easy.)
I'll get the guys at the lab
to go to your place
and take a look.
(I knew it wouldn't be that easy.)
(It was so hard to get him
to add me on QQ back then.)
(Good thing
I have a trick up my sleeve.)
Thank you.
But
this is actually
the second repair.
I think there's no point for them
to come anyway.
That's so unreliable.
What actually went wrong?
I wanted to buy it.
But I changed my mind now.
That's right, Yu Tu.
Are your products reliable?
Jeez.
That's right.
I bought it
because it says on the ads
that it's the aerospace tech.
But I never expected this.
(Sorry.)
(The great aerospace industry
of the motherland.)
(I'll make it up to you next time.)
Didn't the repair guy say
what went wrong?
He seemed to be in a bad spot,
and he didn't say what was the problem.
Yu Tu.
Why don't you go and take a look?
Do you stay with your parents?
That's right.
Are they in now?
Yes.
If it's convenient,
I'll go over and take a look.
My house is in Pudong.
Is it too far?
So sorry to bother you.
It's fine.
Send me the address.
You're so lame.
Why do you have to go
when her parents are around?
You're the lame one.
Xiao Zhu.
Quickly unpack
this newly bought purifier.
Hurry.
How's my makeup?
It's too thick, isn't it?
I knew it.
It's too thick.
Do I look girlie?
Yes.
Well.
Jingjing, it's late at night.
What are you doing?
Is this a dress-up game?
Destroy the air purifier.
Cotton.
No, it's not me.
I'm her assistant.
She sent me down to get you.
Assistant?
It's right in front.
I'm Xiao Zhu.
We're almost there.
Jingjing, why did you come downstairs?
I'm worried someone might think
that I'm being a snob.
That's why I came down to welcome him.
Long time no see.
Has it been ten years?
About that.
Let's take a look at the purifier.
I've stayed in the house for days
and haven't stepped out of it since.
I'm feeling a little lightheaded.
Why don't we go for a walk first?
Here's the thing.
I wanted to use the excuse
that the power's off.
But I didn't expect Ding Chaoqun
to have used it.
I couldn't bear the thought
of destroying such a cute purifier.
So it's doing its work right now.
It's quite cold out there.
I'm going back up to get changed.
Wait for me.
I don't feel so safe
walking with you.
Are you kidding me?
I should be the one to say that.
Look.
When I came out with Xiao Zhu,
which is the girl you saw earlier.
There weren't as many people
who turned around to look at us
when I came out with her.
Don't make me get photographed,
or I'll hit the headlines.
Why would you play games with me?
Didn't you invite me?
You added the wrong person.
Have you forgotten?
But...
why would you
be in my QQ friend list?
Do I have to explain about me
using an alt
to secretly add your QQ account?
Do you have amnesia or something?
Are you also
going to ask me
why I asked you here?
Do you have a Weibo account?
Yes.
Well, log in to your account
and check out mine.
(Yes, my muse is so adorable!)
(An air purifier
recommended by the muse.)
(I'm buying it!)
(I'm posting the review.)
(I think it's the last unit.)
(When I checked again,)
(the product is sold out.)
(I'll post one.)
(I almost didn't get it.)
(You snatched the same product
as my muse.)
(How much did she get paid
for posting this?)
(Xieyue Yilun.)
(Isn't your husband)
(working with that company?)
(Ask him.)
(I did.)
(He said he didn't pay her.)
(The less popular celebrity)
(charges 300,000 yuan for one post.)
(Let alone Qiao Jingjing.)
(My husband said)
(it's all sold out.)
(There are many more orders)
(with limited stocks.)
(We didn't see this coming.)
(Speaking of,)
(the only publicity)
(is for all employees)
(to post on their Moments.)
(This is so cool!)
Why?
It's not like I'm endorsing
any other similar products.
There's no conflict.
Support the motherland's
aerospace industry.
Thank you.
That's so not cool of you.
I thought what was uncool
was lying to me
about taking part
in the Honor of Kings tournament.
I didn't lie to you.
I'm taking part in the tournament.
Don't you know I'm the spokesperson
of the Honor of Glory?
I did see the event of you
giving away inscriptions
when I logged into the game.
A few months ago,
a WeChat friend of mine
recorded a video of me
playing games
and sent it to the marketing account.
You should know
my gaming skills.
So one month later,
I'll be going on the same stage
with professional players
to prove myself.
Thus, everything that has happened.
Are you playing
with professional players?
Not all.
There are five lucky players.
So there are six of us including me.
Four professional players.
Two on each side.
What do you think
of my gaming skills
if I were to join the tournament?
There's no telling if we will win
even with you on the team.
So you want me to teach you?
Can you?
Not the kind
through the Internet.
That's too inefficient.
It's best if you could teach me
in person.
You happened to be on a break
right now anyway.
It wouldn't get in the way
of your work, right?
Here's the thing.
I've never watched a professional game.
I don't know much
about their gaming skills.
I don't know if I can teach you.
It's okay.
I won't get anyone else
to teach me anyway.
You should know that.
You trust me?
You're my classmate.
Yu Tu.
Teach me Math.
I'll treat you to crispy chicken.
Okay.
Really?
Are you doing it willingly?
Enough walking then.
Let's go back and play games.
Hold on.
Your parents are at home.
It's not so appropriate.
Says who that my parents are around?
My parents are in their hometown.
The only thing at home
is the Jade Rabbit Purifier.
What day is the game next month?
Sunday, the second week
of next month.
It's on the 10th.
There's not much time left.
Let's get started now.
And do what?
I've just started playing this game
recently
and haven't studied it.
So I'm not so sure
how I should teach you.
But
you can start by telling me the mistakes
you made
when you had a match with us
in the last few days.
(That was quick of him)
(to enter the coaching mode.)
Let's start with the errors collection.
Are there a lot?
Not really.
More than ten.