[English subtitles are available]
The King ordered to cancel
the engagement of Si Yan and Prince Xiu.
Why isn't she sad at all?
As the old saying goes, "Extreme joy begets sorrow."
You're right.
No one wants to cry in front of others.
Moreover,
as maids,
who we marry
is determined by our masters.
This year's Dendrobium Miyakei didn't flower well.
The Marvel-of-Peru has dried,
so the rouge made from it
will render poor colors.
If only there's Mountain Pomegranate!
Mountain Pomegranate is rare.
I heard
the rouge made from it
is only for the Second Lady.
Your Highness.
Stop.
You there,
come with me.
I have a few extra Mountain Pomegranate
in my garden
for Palace Makeup Service.
Thank you, Prince Yi.
If you want to see me, just say so.
Don't use the excuse of giving plants.
If you don't have them,
what do I do?
If I don't have it in my garden,
I'm afraid that
you can't find it anywhere in East City.
How cocky!
Prince Yi is despotic.
Mountain Pomegranate is delicate and rare,
but he gave it away so easily.
Palace Makeup Service got lucky.
But...
since when did Prince Yi
care about makeup products?
So mountain pomegranate
is a kind of rhododendron.
I thought it's rarer than that!
It has many effects.
If it's taken orally,
it stops bleeding and detoxifies.
Taking it often
is good for women.
A bush of mountain pomegranate
gives thousands of flowers,
squeezing against the railing.
It looks like a red piece of cloth cut into pieces
and clustered as one.
They sway with the breeze as if dancing,
while the wind carries the aroma far.
So...
The morning dews on the flowers
are like makeup...
Hearing the person you like recite a poem
feels so sweet.
Finally, it's done.
How come it feels like it's missing something?
No tasks,
no rewards,
and no nagging from Jack.
What's a task?
Who is Jack?
He's a friend of mine.
I haven't seen him for a long time.
Then
I'll send Wang to find him.
Don't bother.
You can't find him.
He'll come to see me.
He'll come to you?
This old friend of yours
surely puts on airs.
What good timing!
Help me find a guy
named Jack in East City.
Jack?
Is there a Jack
in East City?
It's okay.
He's my friend,
and I'll look for him myself.
Please get back to work.
I'll get going.
Your Highness,
should I find the guy?
Congratulations, Prince Da,
for winning the best hunter title
in the autumn hunt.
What did the King
give you as the reward?
How about marrying you?
I'll buy your contract out for you.
Why?
Do you regret it?
When I met you for the first time
at the posting station,
I knew you were the one I'm searching for.
About me disguised as a man,
you didn't blame me for deceiving you.
How would I regret anything?
I will never let you down.
But right now,
there's one thing more urgent
I need to plea to the King.
What is it?
Sources from the Mins reported
that the battle in Northland is tight.
East City will send more troops
to the battleground.
Your Highness shall ask the King to make you
the commander-in-chief at once.
Supervise the war at the front line.
Perform military exploits.
Supervise the frontline battle,
perform military exploits,
and I'll marry you
as the crowned prince.
Don't worry, Miss Tong.
You bring me luck.
Your identity
and status don't matter.
As long as we team up,
we will dictate our destiny.
Qi Yi,
though you did not die,
it doesn't mean you'll always be lucky.
Being involved with the girl
brings you the spell of bad luck.
You won't live to see the end.
Nonsense!
How do you plan to thank me?
How about the Luoyang Red in your private garden?
Or the daisy spray mums as thank you gifts?
What for?
Are you playing dumb with me?
I haven't greeted father today.
I think we might have canceled the engagement
too hastily.
Si Yan
is pretty awesome.
Thanks, Brother Xiu.
What?
I didn't hear it clearly.
Thank you, Brother Xiu,
for not marrying her.
I came here today
because of the Linchuan Cliff ledger
you asked me to investigate.
I found something.
Let's hear it.
I searched every single
underground bank in East City.
Director Li is very sly.
He circulated the money
through more than ten different
underground banks and casinos.
Where'd the money go?
I heard that
he purchased food and fodder.
With that much money,
he's got a lot of food and fodder.
A director with little power
could do these things quietly
under our eyes without getting caught?
Unless...
You think someone higher-up was involved.
That's what I'm worried about.
That much food and fodder,
no matter where it goes,
will pose threat to East City.
Don't fret.
You have to watch out.
That Luna kept pestering you
trying to kill you.
Who is she?
There's some evidence,
but we don't know her identity yet.
Attachment, hatred, ignorance, grudge, and greed.
It must be one of these causes.
It's hard on you, Yi,
still caught deep in the vortex,
trying to figure everything out.
Brother Xiu.
Keep investigating where the food and fodder went.
Before obtaining solid evidence,
don't let the cat out of the bag.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
How are things with Si Yan
going?
Oh, that?
Brother Xiu.
What are you saying?
Focus on your task.
So things are going well.
But as an older brother,
I must say
have a sense of urgency.
Please don't think
the King called off the engagement between us,
so everything will be fine.
There is still a long way ahead.
What do you do with Miss Min?
What will you say to the First Lady?
Father won't agree to it.
A maid and a prince?
It's not going to be so easy.
Enough, Brother Xiu.
Nagging like our father,
you imitated it so well.
Wang,
see him out.
I'm off.
Though the war in Northland is urgent,
Your Majesty has to take care of your health, too.
If you keep sighing and moaning,
and staying up the whole night,
my heart
will ache for you.
The Northland King
is always restless,
intruding on our north border again and again.
He always provokes war without cause
only to put the lives of innocent people in jeopardy.
My brother is stationed at the north border.
I'm sure he can stop the bandits.
Of course.
But,
don't you think something's wrong?
How does a little brute king
have enough food, fodder, and money
to initiate war all the time?
What brought you here, Prince Yi?
Greetings, my lady.
Go to the Makeup Service
and fetch some calming incenses
to send to the King.
Yes.
While Wang was catching the assassin,
he startled Second Lady.
I came to apologize.
You are too kind, Prince Yi.
Just a few days ago,
you sent the bloody bird nests
and wild ginseng to me.
I haven't had the chance to enjoy them.
Today Prince Yi came to visit in person.
You must have something else in mind.
If you'll allow me,
I want to ask one thing.
About the fires in Cloud Brothel three years ago,
do you still remember anything?
I've heard.
Luckily, I left early that day
and avoided the fires.
On that day,
was the top Courtesan Luna of Cloud Brothel there?
This ...
I'm unclear.
I also
just wanted to give back
by helping the girls there with ransoms.
I wasn't there for the show.
Everyone knows
you are a saint.
Lady Cui of Makeup Service said
there used to be a page boy at Makeup Service.
His name is Qing Yan.
Do you remember him, my lady?
Qing Yan?
This name sounds familiar.
What's wrong?
Is he linked to the Cloud Brothel fires?
While investigating, we found
that the time Qing Yan left the East Mansion
and the time Luna appeared
was about the same.
So we suspect
Qing Yan and Luna
may be the same person.
Before Qing Yan left here,
I heard that
you caught him of wrongly keeping the book.
Now that you mention it,
I do remember.
I remember
I reprimanded him a bit,
but I never saw him again after.
After all,
he worked in Makeup Service for the First Lady.
So he left the East Mansion.
But
how could the top courtesan
and the servant
be the same person?
I encountered him before.
He's a master of disguise.
Do you recall
any strange behaviors
or suspicious conversations
before he left the mansion?
I only remember
he's good looking
and clever.
I never thought
he'd have anything to do with
a top courtesan killer.
Other than that,
I can't think of anything else.
Sorry, Prince Yi,
I can't help much.
Don't say that, my lady.
Thank you for your time.
Look at this.
The craftsmanship
and the rendering!
I'm just a few steps away
from becoming a Head Metron.
Don't you think so, Jack?
Won't I get a reward from the system?
My dear Si Yan,
everyone is too busy to have a break.
Can you please
give your precious rouges to us
so the ladies and misses can choose?
Miss Si, did you lose your mind?
Let's help her.
I mean...
my cake!
Jack...
What do you want?
I'm looking for Tong...
I mean Peach.
What do you need Peach for?
She's not in Peace Pavilion now,
but I can pass on the message.
She and I are
from the same hometown.
Please let me see her.
No.
Glasses,
come out, please.
Do you have a butler?
My butler disappeared.
What is a butler?
Don't make a scene.
Leave.
My lady?
Jack?
Who is Jack?
He is the first person I met after I came.
You may not believe it,
but he also knows you.
He knows Hu Ying,
the princes,
and the ladies.
He has supported me throughout
my time in the Palace Makeup Service.
Where's he now?
He is gone.
He got angry with me
and left without saying goodbye.
No loyalty!
Not a true friend!
Si Yan,
Stop repenting.
Find him
and explain everything.
Maybe
he's just busy.
Find him?
Where do I go?
I am stuck in this lousy space.
The tasks are even on time-outs.
How do I go on like this?
Wherever Prince Yi is
will never be a lousy place to be.
Speaking of which,
let me ask you a question.
Say that you've gone through all the trouble
to be with someone you love,
but you need to pay a price.
You must hide
in a place where no one can find you.
You can't return to East City, either.
Will you do that?
Of course not.
It's nice to be with someone I love forever,
but
if I can never return to East City,
it means that
I'll never see my parents,
and I won't see you anymore.
To me,
all of you mean a lot.
I can't bear it.
How about you?
What will you do?
I am not sure.
My top priority
should be getting the tasks back.
I am stuck.
Are you referring to the task
Second Lady asked the Makeup Service
to make sleeping incense?
It is not an easy task.
Making incense is cumbersome.
Since the incense is for the King,
it needs to be premium quality.
It sounds like a good opportunity.
The task seems to have
a high degree of difficulty.
If I complete it,
maybe I'll level up.
Lan Miao,
thanks!
I'll get my hands on it.
Your Highness,
who are
the earrings for?
After so many years,
it's the first time I saw you
fiddle with accessories for girls.
Miss Tong helped me resolve my longtime issue with women.
Dao,
Go and reserve a table
in Meeting Tower for me tomorrow.
I'll thank her in person.
Yes, Sir.
Prince Yi,
greetings!
Si Yan is still working inside.
Shall we go and get her?
He's waiting to pick up Si Yan.
You sounded jealous!
I can see the envy in your eyes.
I'm not jealous
because my idol is Prince Xiu.
Just stay like this for a bit longer.
Why are you here?
I passed by.
Did you come to see me?
I've made up my mind.
I'll confess our relationship to Mother.
You shouldn't feel aggrieved anymore.
Actually,
First Lady didn't give me too much of a hard time.
She is nothing compared to
the typical mothers-in-law out there.
We aren't married yet,
but I like that you called her mother-in-law.
Qi Yi,
I don't dare to think about it.
We've just started dating.
It's all in two episodes.
It's progressing too fast.
It won't do.
How could you give in to marrying Xiu that easily?
It's different.
It is just a game.
No,
I mean it was arranged.
But marrying you here...
I am afraid.
What are you afraid of?
I fear that we are not the same.
I fear that the system wants me to harm you.
I fear that I will regret everything
if I can never leave here.
I fear that you won't get used to the real me.
Can't we enjoy being in love with each other?
Just like now,
we only have each other in our eyes.
There is no First Lady,
no Miss Min,
no identity,
and no need to consider the future,
but to peacefully look at you.
Si Yan,
you showed me not to run away
and face my heart with courage.
I want to marry you
to keep you by my side.
Morning, my lord,
First Lady
and the officials in Garment Service will be here shortly.
They'd like to take your measurements.
Congratulations, Prince Yi.
Hurry
and take Prince Yi's measurements
for his wedding gown.
Miss Min has stayed in our mansion for several days.
Since you two like each other,
I think that
it's better to hold the wedding early.
It'll also
lift some weight off my shoulders.
Mother,
as the battle in Northland is tight,
everyone in the city worries about the North.
Discussing my marriage at this time
may be inappropriate.
Let's discuss it later
once the situation stabilizes.
My lady,
aren't you forgetting something?
That's right.
I forgot to share another good news with you.
I heard from Xiu and the King
that Xiu's engagement is canceled.
Actually,
I also like
Si Yan very much.
She is clever,
and she's more than capable of
doing the work in the Makeup Service.
Since Prince Xiu isn't the lucky one,
I was thinking...
How about
you take her in as a concubine?
Don't worry.
I'll talk to the Mins.
If their daughter can be your official wife,
she should be
more tolerant.
At that time,
you can marry both girls.
It'll be a good thing.
Prince Yi,
Her Ladyship goes above and beyond
in your matters.
After that, Miss Si Yan
will be legitimately married to you,
becoming a rightful Lady.
This is the best of both worlds.
You should take it.
Look!
I picked out
the fabric with my heart.
Do you like it?
Mother,
I'm willing to marry,
but...
What are you doing?
Get up and talk.
But I'll only marry Si Yan,
not Miss Min.
You are foolish!
For a low-class maid,
you are throwing your life away.
Should this be in the mind of a man?
You're straying from the paved route
for a girl of little worth.
What's the point of being wholehearted?
Please don't get mad.
Did she teach you to say that?
Si Yan has nothing to do with it.
Enough!
Stop making excuses for her.
You must marry Miss Min
even if you don't want to.
If we offended General Min,
and thus breached the barrier of the North,
East City will be in danger.
If you are concerned that
General Min will no longer serve East City,
I'll go to the battleground and fight in the front line
to serve East City.
Even if I die in battle, so be it!
You are not allowed to say so.
Don't you forget
how your Brother Teng died?
This sword
fought with me in numerous battles.
Da,
you are
the commander-in-chief for East City troops.
This sword
is yours now.
I hope that
you gain victory
and return safely.
Yes, Father.
I'll bring you honor.
Father,
I plead to go to war, too.
Father!
Your Majesty,
please reconsider.
I only have one son left.
Teng has passed away.
I can't...
I can't risk jeopardizing Yi,
Your Majesty...
Yi,
listen to your mother.
Stay in East City
and help me take care of affairs.
Father,
I went to war three years ago,
so I am more familiar with the area
in Northland.
Allowing me to assist my big brother
increases the chance of victory.
Three years ago,
Teng died because of me.
I did not forget about it.
I wish to go to the frontline
to avenge Teng.
I beg for your approval.
Yi!
Get up!
Yi,
stand up.
Fine.
I hereby appoint
Prince Da as commander-in-chief,
and Prince Yi as deputy general.
I command you
to join forces
and return with victories!
My lord...
The kids are grown.
They should share responsibilities.
Furthermore,
If I don't let Yi go
he can't conquer his demons.
Going to war,
you must be careful.
Don't be reckless.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You wanted to kill me.
Aren't you afraid I'll kill you?
If you kill me,
your plan will be ruined.
After being with me for so long,
you finally grew some brains
and learned to analyze the situation.
However,
you don't think you'll be able to
take my place by killing me, do you?
You can't wrap fire in the paper.
A secret cannot be kept forever.
All I can do
is maintain the lies
for a little while longer.
Nonsense.
It is like a moth to a flame.
No.
I know clearly
if I don't do anything
Prince Yi and I
will never have a chance to be together.
If I were like you,
born to a wealthy and upper-class family,
then no matter my skills, wisdom,
I'd never been below you.
And the only barrier between Prince Yi and me
is social status.
You don't actually think
the reason you can't be with Prince Yi
is only because of social status?
You care a lot about social status.
Isn't it because
you look down on yourself?
How laughable!
The old me had the same desire as you.
To seize the hard-to-catch
nothingness,
I was confused,
and I struggled,
believing I was mistreated by fate unfairly.
If even you look down on yourself,
why wouldn't others look down on you, too?
What do you mean?
You don't know, do you?
Prince Yi
refused to marry you, Miss Min.
He asked to marry only Si Yan,
and he only wanted to marry her.
Because of this,
he reached a deadlock with the First Lady.
He has asked to go to war.
Impossible.
I'm a lady.
She's a maid.
She's no match!
Is she no match?
And you are?
You never would've thought
what Prince Yi cared about
was not social status or class.
You can just continue to stay here
and be an ailing
shameful
Miss Min.
Get me a bottle of the best wine.
Never mind.
Prepare some nourishing soup
and her favorite four-flavor cake.
Yes, sir.
My lady,
come with us.
I heard Prince Da and Prince Yi
will be traveling far tomorrow.
Too bad East Mansion's rules
prohibit women from seeing them off.
We can only quietly wish them well.
Is Prince Yi going to war?
His Highness requested to lead an elite troop
to fight the frontline battles.
Brave and heroic!
Si Yan,
why doesn't Prince Yi
visit you before he leaves?
I don't know, either.
Did Prince Yi send the flowers to me?
He's been sending flowers quite often lately.
The flowers are
for the King.
My master said
these African daisies from the west
have calming effects.
They can be used to make drugs
and incenses.
Using these on the King
is beneficial.
Where is he?
He's nowhere to be found.
Why is he going to war?
Is it dangerous?
How do you battle in this game?
How could he not discuss such important matters with me?
Miss Si Yan,
Prince Yi wants to come,
but he can't.
You don't know?
He got into a huge argument
with the First Lady because of you.
The swelling on his face where she hit him
still hasn't disappeared.
The First Lady prohibits him
from seeing you before battle,
saying tears only bring bad luck.
Prince Yi knows you worry for him,
so
he sent me to deliver his message.
Put on the best makeup
and greet him on his victorious return.
Qi Yi!
Qi Yi,
let me go with you, please!
I'll go, no matter how far.
No.
Hurry back inside.
I'll return safely.
I come from the West Region.
I want to go home.
Don't leave me alone, please!
Somebody!
Hold Si Yan back.
Don't let her leave.