♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 13=
What are you doing?
Pupaa.
Ouch.
Pupaa. Pupaa.
Hello?
Who’s that? Is it Prapai?
Yes.
Why are you the one
answering Pupaa’s phone?
She’s answering his phone
this early in the morning.
I think they’ve been together
since last night.
Shouldn’t have asked.
Is it true?
He was very drunk last night, so I...
Took advantage
and spent the night with him, right?
Yes. And what is your problem?
Well, we’re dating.
It’s not weird for us
to be staying together, is it?
Alright, we won’t disturb you.
You can spend your time together.
Hold on, it’s not like that.
- Hey, a cockroach.
- Cockroach? Where?
Hey.
Were you fake sleeping?
When did you wake up?
So
you must’ve heard me on the phone.
Hey.
Come on, let’s continue resting.
Sneaky.
Hey, girlfriend, slow down.
You’ll slip and fall.
(Heart marks, care level, smile level)
I made you a sandwich. Go on, have some.
You’re a mess.
Don’t you have to go to the laboratory?
I thought they were calling for you
this morning.
Maybe they have something for you to do.
I don’t think I have to go.
They can still work it out without me.
Pupaa, that’s wasa-
Hold on.
Here, have some milk.
Do you feel better?
What were you daydreaming about?
I thought it was mayonnaise.
Pupaa.
I’m alright. You can go to work.
Alright.
I’ve got to go now.
Bye.
Time.
(WeTV: Time explains he didn’t hurt them)
Why didn’t you come out to explain?
Well, I have to say,
I don’t want anyone to be harmed.
And also,
about the truth of the incident,
the people who saw it
know exactly what happened.
But my fans have been showing concerns
about whether will people will be
misunderstanding me or not.
So the truth was revealed as shown.
So what would you do next
with the fans that accused you?
I’m not going to do anything,
because my fans
are the group of people
who have always supported me.
And what the fans did
is because of their admiration for me.
But it might be a little too much
at times.
So do you want to leave a message
about this?
I would like to tell my fans,
to all my fans, thank you very much
for supporting, admiring,
and still trusting in me.
Pai, it’s time for the meeting.
Sure.
This is our new product, cat food.
Soon to be launched.
So they wanted to do an online ad
before launching.
So then, Pai, you can go brainstorm
some ideas to present.
I’ll have a look and help you with it.
Sure.
Who do you think we should suggest
as the presenter?
Time.
If Time heard what you said,
he’d love you to death.
But the latest news just came out.
Time didn’t hurt his fans.
And in his latest interview,
he’s been receiving positive feedback.
I agree.
We should take this as an opportunity
to create an eye-catching project.
And for our previous work,
I don’t think we should replace Time.
Otherwise people will be saying
that when there’s a problem,
we just ditched him.
I think
it will be bad for both the company
and our client.
Interesting.
So I’ll bring this up with the clients.
Sure.
Yes.
(Care level, obedience level)
(Smile level, responsibility level,
gentleness level)
Oh.
You’ve been doing this puzzle all day?
Um.
Taking it serious
just like your research.
I’m going to bed now.
Hold on.
Don’t be like this.
I know you’re feeling upset.
But did you know?
Not everyone
can do a research like this.
You’re smart and talented.
You can’t be using it
to do just puzzles like this.
It’s a pity.
I’m not that smart.
It’s so embarrassing.
Like I told you,
I never missed a scholarship.
(Faculty of Science and Technology)
What are we doing? This is boring.
Where is Pupaa anyway?
He hasn’t come in weeks.
Yeah.
Professor is also very mad
that he just left work like that.
I get goosebumps every time I see him.
Meena too. She’s even worse.
She’s become so arrogant
since she got the scholarship.
She used to keep asking for Pupaa.
Now she doesn’t say a word.
- Hey.
Oh.
Are you here for Pupaa?
He’s not here today.
Yeah. I haven’t been able to contact him
the past few days.
Have you seen him?
I don’t know what he’s up to.
He’s disappointed
for not getting the scholarship.
I’m here to see if there’s anything
that will inspire him
to get him back on his feet.
So that he can reapply
for the scholarship.
But you have to be quick.
Because Professor Sunan is very mad.
I also heard him say
that he won’t introduce
another scholarship for him.
What?
Do you have any of Professor’s contacts?
Can I have it?
Hello, Professor.
Hey.
You’re Pupaa’s girlfriend, aren’t you?
I wanted to talk to you about Pupaa.
He’s lost his confidence
after he lost the scholarship.
But I know he still wants to work
on the research.
Do you happen to have any more
scholarships for him to apply?
Can you give him some more time, please?
There are some scholarships left.
But the deadline to apply for it
is tomorrow.
Can you extend it for a little while?
I don’t think that’s enough time.
How can I extend it?
I’m not the one who set it.
Also,
if Pupaa is the one
who really wanted the scholarship,
the person who should be
standing in front of my gate right now
should be him, not you.
But Professor...
That’s enough.
Say no more. It’s time for you to leave.
But Professor, can you please help find
any other scholarships?
Professor, Professor.
Hello. Are you here for Professor?
Come on in first.
What’s wrong? Did something bad happen?
I’m back.
You’re home already, honey.
I’ve been waiting for you.
Come, come.
You’re still here?
She came to ask for the scholarship
for her boyfriend.
The guy isn’t even here himself.
I don’t think he really wants it.
Oh you.
Can’t you give the kid a chance?
Think about yourself back in the days.
When you failed the scholarship
and flee into the woods for months,
I had to beg the Professor
to not cut you out of the system.
Oh dear,
why are you talking about the past?
It’s not the same.
Me back then
did everything perfectly.
But lost it to the guy with connections.
But Pupaa didn’t.
He didn’t present all of the data.
Especially the medium used
to refract light.
He didn’t put any details about it in.
Instead of feeling bad for himself,
he should spend the time
to fix the mistake.
And make it correct. Am I right?
I will find the mistake and fix it.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
She’s gone.
Find a new scholarship for him.
Do you understand?
Yes, my dear wife.
Good job.
This tea is nice.
The medium used to refract light?
How can it be missing?
We’ve calculated these data already,
I remember.
Exactly.
Normally Pupaa is very detailed
and careful.
I don’t think he’ll miss
such an important data like this.
Meena was even the one who sent
some parts of the data to us.
Am I right?
I don’t remember.
(Advanced Holography
- Metrology and Imaging)
(By Puwadol Kittaset)
OMG, it’s really gone.
Let me see.
(Advanced Holography
- Metrology and Imaging)
There’s been an edit.
But this is before Professor
reviewed it.
Or did someone replace and save it?
Or someone intentionally deleted it.
Hey, who would do it?
Exactly. Because in this room,
there’re only me and you,
Pupaa, Professor and...
Then we’ll have to prove it.
The time that it was edited
is 8:45 PM.
And Meena walked into the building
at 8:20 PM.
And she walked out at 9:02 PM.
But we can’t see anything
from the laboratory.
For the safety and confidentiality
of the research,
that’s why
there’re no security cameras inside.
This is bad. This means that
we don’t have any proof.
Then we have to let her
admit her own crime.
Huh?
How so?
Her face says it all.
I think she’s got a plan. Spill it.
Hello. What’s wrong, Ken?
Hello, Meena. Can you please
come to the security camera room?
Security camera room?
Yes, the security camera room.
Professor is also here.
Please come quick.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you trying to erase the evidence?
What are you talking about?
I don’t understand.
We’re suspecting Pupaa’s research
for the scholarship application
was edited after the submission
to Professor.
So we wanted to find proof.
During 8:30 PM of that day,
where were you? What were you doing?
I went into the data room next door.
And I didn’t go into the laboratory
that day.
If you don’t believe me,
then you can check the security cameras.
Us lab students know
that the laboratory and the data room
has no security camera.
We won’t see anything anyway.
And so what?
You’re going to say I did it?
If it’s not you, then who can it be?
If you’re really innocent,
can I please see your smart watch?
Don’t make us do it the hard way.
What are you going to do?
Don’t come over.
Stop it, Meena.
(ECG heart rate monitoring data)
Why is your heart rate during
8:40 PM and 8:50 PM
not normal?
I was having a problem
with my research at that time.
Can’t I be anxious?
I thought you just said
you were in the data room.
You weren’t in the laboratory.
Why is there a problem
with your research then?
This means you really went into
the laboratory, right?
Calm down, Meena.
Don’t come close.
Pupaa.
Just admit the truth, Meena.
What’s going on?
(Faculty of Science and Technology)
Meena.
Did you really erase
part of Pupaa’s research?
Why did you do that?
What are you proud of getting
the scholarship with this kind of act?
I guess you’re happy
for getting me in trouble.
I didn’t want to win in this situation.
But I did this
because I don’t want Pupaa
to blame himself
for not trying hard enough,
and not wanting to do what he loves.
I will have to report this situation.
You guys should go prepare the file
to submit it again.
And we’ll see what they say.
You don’t have to.
Huh?
Why?
Actually, for my research,
if Meena didn’t help me,
I wouldn’t have had
all the data collected.
You should be the one
getting the scholarship, Meena.
Pupaa.
Is this the time to be the good guy?
Meena.
I never taught you
to be this kind of person.
I’m very disappointed in you.
I’m sorry.
How could you let her go?
She made you lose your opportunity
in getting the scholarship.
Never mind.
So you’re ready to come back
and continue with the research?
Um.
But isn’t the due date tomorrow?
Actually, there’s also
another scholarship you could apply for.
But its deadline is next week.
Will you be able to finish it on time?
- Sure.
Thank you so much, Professor.
Thank you.
Well,
someone told me to do this.
Um.
So from now on,
don’t you ever blame yourself again
for not trying hard enough.
So this means I have to push harder
in gaining marks
in becoming your real boyfriend, right?
So how did you do it?
To let Professor say yes to me.
It’s a secret.
Come on, tell me.
No.
- Tell me.
- No.
Look, there’re so many stars.
Look.
I can’t believe that
we could still see stars in Bangkok.
That must be
the Triones,
or the seven principal stars.
Huh?
Try and count how many stars there are.
Seven stars.
When arranged,
does it look like a big spatula?
It’s part of the
Ursa Major constellation.
Its tail
points to different directions
in each season.
If we can find the Triones,
we’ll be able to find
other constellation stars.
Wow, amazing.
How about that one?
That should be the Aquila,
or the Altair.
Altair?
Is it the story of the Cowherd
and the Weaver girl?
The Chinese love story.
I once read it from a book.
It said that the two
loved each other so much,
but they didn’t make it together.
The Weaver girl was taken to heaven,
and the Cowherd tried to follow her.
But a river was blocking the way.
Only one day out of the entire year
that magpies would line up as a bridge
for the lovers to cross the bridge
to see each other.
A bridge?
It’s probably the Milky Way.
Isn’t it pitiful for them?
They get only one day
out of the entire year to meet.
They have to long for each other
up to 364 days.
Astronomy is part of science.
Myths like that aren’t real.
It’s just a beautiful fairy tale.
Boy, you don’t know
how to be romantic, do you?
If I wasn’t here anymore,
would you be sad?
Why are you asking this?
You can’t leave me.
I’m not going anywhere.
I haven’t even been passed
being your intern boyfriend.
He’s very easy to take care of.
Just feed him two meals regularly
in the morning and evening,
and you can let him run around.
Don’t worry.
We’ll take good care of him.
Joobjoob, mommy will be back.
Mommy will come for you
as soon as possible.
Hello, kitty cat.
You’re so cute.
Isn’t the shooting next week?
Why is the cat here now?
The client knows the owner,
and said that it must be only this cat.
But the owner is leaving the country
today.
So the client told her
to leave the cat with us first.
So we can get familiar with it.
Isn’t all of them the same?
This one won a competition.
You won’t know how much it costs.
It’s “him”, instead of an “it”.
Six figures.
- Six figures?
So who’s going to take care of
Mr. Joobjoob?
I have a dog,
I don’t think I can take him in.
Seems like you like cats.
Yes, I do.
Actually I really want a cat.
But my family won’t let me.
Then
I’ll let you take care of him
until the shooting.
But pets aren’t allowed at where I live.
Just ask for permission.
It’ll be only a few days.
But he’s a six-figured cat.
If something happens to him,
I can’t take responsibility for it.
You can’t say no, because you’re
in charge of taking care of the actors.
And this is one of the actors
that you must take care.
Right?
Prapai, you’re back?
Stay quiet, alright?
What are you doing?
Just doing some more research.
Oh.
So how is it going? Going good?
I just have to find the missing data
and it’ll be ready to submit.
- Oh.
- It’ll sure be completed on time.
That’s good.
What’s this cat food for?
Well,
it’s a product used for work.
I bought it back
so I could continue with my brainstorm.
They’re giving you work
to do at home again?
Next time charge them for overtime.
It’s unfair to be working overtime.
Hey, it’s alright.
Don’t worry about it.
I think you’re getting sick.
You should go get some rest,
so you can get better soon.
Go to sleep early..
Have a good night. Bye.
Don’t come over. Go away.
Don’t come over.
Don’t come over. Go away. Don’t come.
Hey, what are you doing?
That’s a six-figured living creature.
Are you okay?
No.
I really have to do this.
If I don’t bring it back,
I’m going to get fired.
That’s not going to happen.
Pets aren’t allowed here.
Well,
it’s going to be only a few days.
Don’t tell anyone then.
You can’t.
Pupaa, please let me stay.
Meow.
If you let him stay,
I’ll give you two extra marks.
Please, let me stay. Pretty please.
Alright.
- Yay.
- Don’t come over.
You must promise me
that you won’t let it
run around outside.
I’m allergic to cat fur.
Hey, call her Mr. Joobjoob.
He seems to like you.
No way. What kind of funny name is that?
How is it funny? See, it’s Joobjoob.
Is this the person who said
he would change himself?
He really can’t change, can he?
Alright now.
Can we test the lights?
- It’s okay.
- Okay.
Are you ready?
Pupaa, thank you.
I’ve put myself at risk here.
Am I close to getting full marks?
I said don’t come over.
Move away.
Just go.
(Are you looking for this?)
(Yarn hygienic masks)
(What everyone is looking for)
It’s cute, isn’t it? Put it on.
What do you want?
I can’t understand you.
Use the cat language translation
application.
What do you want?
(Hungry)
Hey, it really does work.
Here, let me try. Come on here.
Come sit with me.
Is Prapai cute?
(Yes)
How about Pupaa?
(No)
Watch yourself.
(Scared)
You can communicate in cat language.
There’s only a limited frequency
of cat sound.
Do you want to help me
with the shooting tomorrow?
I’m afraid I’ll be too busy and
won’t be able to take care of Joobjoob.
I’ll give you extra marks.
Can extra marks be full marks?
Dream on.
Then I’ll go now.
Where are you going?
Going to the laboratory.
There’s a team from
a university from China coming today.
Professor wants me to go
and get familiar with them.
Okay.
Just a minute.
Huh?
Here you go.
What is it?
Yarn hygienic mask.
I knitted it myself the entire night.
Wear it so you don’t sneeze.
Prapai.
Yes?
But yarn doesn’t protect you
from cat fur.
Oh.
It’s alright. I’ll add in my own filter.
I’ll wear it every day.
Um.
Prapai and Joobjoob
will always support you.
Fighting.
Meow, meow.
Bye.
- Hello.
Please come in.
Hello, hello.
This is our research team
who’s working on the hologram project.
This research was inspired
by a 3D book of childhood memories.
They said they would like
to support your project.
But we hope
you can work with
the Chinese research group
to finish this project together.
So more people from
different academic departments
could participate.
You mean
you need me to do the research in China?
Yes.
You don’t have to worry.
We will finance your research
until it’s fully completed.
That’s great. Great.
If I wasn’t here anymore,
would you be sad?
You can’t leave me.
Thank you very much.
But I’m going to say no.
What?
I think Pupaa may be
a little too excited.
You’re doing it again, Pupaa.
Why are you doing this?
This is the most important thing
in your life.
How can you say that?
Think before you speak.
We’ll get back to you later.
This will be the next scene
that we’re going to shoot.
We might take a photoshoot too
because it’s the same costume.
This one here...
Prapai.
Pupaa.
- Pon.
- Huh?
This is Pupaa.
He’ll be helping with Joobjoob today.
Oh really? That’s great.
Let’s go set up.
Sure.
You don’t have to help me
the entire day.
I want to help you.
So I can get full marks soon.
Are you doing this for an exchange?
Of course. It’s worth it.
Servant, come here.
I know.
- I’ll get to work now.
- Um.
Please take care of Joobjoob.
Bye.
Prapai.
Meow, meow.
You don’t have to be this cute.
I’m falling for you already.
Are you friends?
What do I have to do today?
Just give me a short brief.
Oh okay. This is the next scene
you’re going to shoot.
We’ll shoot this one and this one,
all together.
Because you’re wearing the same costume.
And the scene doesn’t change.
Hey, listen carefully.
Take it serious.
Listen to me.
This is the scene
where you have to be here.
And you’ll go in and play with Joobjoob.
This is a great filming location.
(Biography of Einstein)
Meow, meow.
Hey baby.
Let’s go for a walk.
Meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow.
You know you’re allergic to cat fur,
and you’re still forcing it.
Just go home.
Meow, meow.
Time.
What are you doing here?
It’s time for the shoot.
I’m just trying to get familiar
with the cat before the scene.
Am I right, little girl?
Joobjoob is a little boy.
Give it to me.
You should get on set.
Joobjoob.
Why has no one taken the cat
onto the set?
This is bad, Pon.
Joobjoob is on the tree.
Hey.
What did you do?
I told you to take care of it.
You know it’s worth
probably your entire year’s salary.
- Get it down now.
- Yes.
I’ll get it down.
I’ll take care of it.
(Special scene)
Meow.
Meow, meow.
(Love)
Meow.
(You)
Meow, meow, meow.
(I love you)
Prapai.
Meow, meow, meow.