♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪For us to be together♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 17=
Hello, tree.
My name is Prapai.
It’s so nice.
You have many friends around you.
Unlike me.
Even though I’ve got so many people
around me,
but why do I feel like I’m all alone?
Even though today’s Valentine’s day,
but I have to be all lonely here.
Sometimes,
I don’t even know what I’m doing here.
Prapai.
Hey, I’ve passed this way before.
Hey.
Hey, it’s the same tree.
This is the same route.
Hey, why is my battery out now?
Calm down, Prapai.
Concentrate. Just calm down, calm down.
That should be the Triones,
or the Big Dipper.
If you can find
the Triones constellation,
you’ll be able to find
other constellations too.
This means that this is the North.
If I follow this star,
I will be able to find you,
right, Pupaa?
Prapai.
Prapai, Prapai.
It’s me, Pai.
Pupaa.
It’s okay, I’m here now.
Why did you come out here all alone?
I was worried sick.
I don’t understand
what you guys are saying.
So I didn’t want to be there.
So I just came out for a walk.
But I kept walking round and round
and I got lost.
I’m sorry.
It’s alright.
Pai, what’s wrong?
No, nothing.
I don’t believe you.
You’re looking at something
on my shoulder.
- Hey, get it out.
- Don’t move, don’t move.
- What is it? Get it out, get it off.
- Okay, okay. I got it.
- Get it off me.
- Oh, tiny caterpillar. Come here.
Please get out.
Don’t mess with my Pupaa.
- It’s gone.
- Is it gone?
Um.
It’s already late. Let’s go back.
I’ll take you out of here.
Come on, let’s go.
I always have to let you help me.
Who said so?
You just helped me
get the caterpillar off.
And that chili chocolate
the other day too.
No matter how smart the scientist is,
we can’t think of that.
Everyone has their own expertise.
And you’ve done what you’re good at
pretty well.
Therefore,
you don’t have to understand
what I study.
Hey, is that them?
Stop, stop.
You guys can continue.
Let’s go.
- Let’s go back.
- Um.
- Be careful.
I’ll go take a shower first.
I’m all sticky.
Um.
Here, can you take it?
Here, your clothes.
Thank you.
Hey.
That’s a huge mirror.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I was about to.
Well.
How about this? When you shower,
I’ll go wait outside.
Don’t be dumb.
It’s so hot outside.
And you’ve been working hard all day.
Then how are you going to shower?
You’re going to let me see everything?
Are you crazy?
I’ll just shower like this.
You’ve been lost for a long while.
I guess you’re hungry.
Go have some dinner.
And I’ll sort out this bathroom issue.
Um.
Dinner is there.
Okay.
Wow.
It’s so good.
The bathroom is all done.
What a Pupaa idea.
Happy Valentine’s day.
Thank you.
Here, I’ll put it on for you.
What a pity it’s past midnight.
There’s nothing to feel bad about.
It’s just a name of a day.
I love you every day
anyway.
So then this necklace
means never changing love.
Right?
Actually,
there’s not substance
that does not change.
Because everything has a reason to be.
But human was the one who invented
value of numbers.
The value of pi is a constant number
that will never change.
I...
May I?
Your shirt...
- You...
- Yes?
- You go first.
I’ll go get you some water.
I guess you’re thirsty.
Sure, sure.
I’m really thirsty. Thank you.
Don’t worry.
I’ll be back as soon as possible.
Then,
can you give this to Kwang for me?
And also
open this when I’m gone.
Hey. Come on, I’ll drop you off.
It’s alright. You go ahead.
Pupaa, I saw an announcement today.
They said there’s going to be
a short film competition.
Its topic is about memory of love.
So I was thinking of competing.
Hello.
Hello, Prapai.
Hello, Pupaa.
Have you had anything to eat?
Not yet. I’ve been working.
Oh.
How have you been? Busy?
A little busy.
But once I add in a few data here,
it should be done.
Um.
You don’t have to worry about me.
Focus on your research.
Keep fighting.
Bye.
Cartoon.
Prapai.
What’s going on here?
Of course something’s going on.
Our company competed
in a short film competition and won.
Isn’t it great?
A short film?
Won a prize?
Yes. Look here.
Time’s acting skills is great.
But what’s better is Faye’s idea.
Her script writing skill is great.
Such a great creative director.
This is so good.
Faye?
Yes.
Faye is so happy.
The boss is so proud of her.
It’s so good.
Cartoon, Cartoon, come here.
Time, what do you want to eat today?
I’ll let you have anything.
I’ll give you one cheat day today.
Why are you suddenly being nice to me?
What do you want?
You’ve been doing great.
So I just wanted to give you an award.
Doing great at what?
Do you remember
that you went to
play in C Agency’s short film?
There’re a million views right now.
It covered up all of your rumors.
Either the rumor about drugging a girl,
hurting your fans,
and the latest, about your ex.
There’re so many series projects
contacting you for work.
What a flow of cash.
Look at the news.
Here, look at it.
(C Agency won first prize)
Faye, the director of the short film,
said there’s going to be a press round
of the winning team.
And also a Q&A session.
I’ve locked your schedule.
Until then, we can wear our new clothes
to promote too.
And also...
Time.
Thank you for calling
to congratulate me.
Whenever you want to create
any more advertisements,
you can always call me.
Faye.
I assure you I will do my best
like I did in the short film.
Sure. Goodbye.
Why is it you
who directed the short film?
Oh, Pai, you’re back?
I need an explanation.
An explanation of what?
A great feedback
from the viewers like this.
I’m so proud, I have nothing to say.
But I was the one
who created this project.
But who submitted it for you?
Actually,
you didn’t seem to care
about this project that much.
The project wasn’t even submitted,
and you went off on a holiday.
And the fact that
you got Time to play for you
is because you’re working
in this company.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t have known Time.
Right?
I want to talk to Pon.
Sure.
Yim, have you seen Pon?
I haven’t seen him, Pai.
(Prapai)
Prapai,
(I have a big meeting with the Professors)
I have a big meeting with the Professors.
(I may be busy all day)
I may be busy all day.
(Cheer for me too)
Cheer for me too.
I’ll call you when I’m done.
Pon, where have you been?
She said she was going to find you.
I don’t know where she’s gone now.
I don’t know what’s the fuss.
Pon.
The short film competition,
you know I was the one
who did it, right?
Let’s go talk somewhere else.
I need an explanation.
Otherwise, I’ll go talk to the boss.
Are you threatening us?
I just went to see my lawyers.
They say that any work
that is produced
by an employee of a company
is considered as
an asset of the company.
So if Faye wants to say that,
she is not wrong.
But the actors, photographers
are all my friends.
Time
isn’t also contracted
under the company’s name.
But we included everyone
in the end credit, including you.
Someone your age,
having a name in the production
that won an award is great already.
You knew about this since the beginning,
right?
Do you think what you did was right?
The system of working in a company
is like this.
You alone couldn’t have done it.
You’d still need the resources
from the company.
The fact that you’re able to work
for a leading company like this,
even if you didn’t even graduate
from this area,
it’s not easy, and you know that.
Make sure you keep your job.
(Movie Night)
This is the Q&A party invitation.
I want you to go.
Because you
also “contributed” in this project.
And the other staff,
I’ll arrange a party later.
(Movie Night)
Come on, let’s go.
How did you know I’m here?
Are you a stalker?
No, no.
I’m a superhero.
Are you that free
to be coming to me here?
I don’t want you to be alone.
In situations like this,
it’s better to have me messing around
than you being alone.
Am I right?
Alright, let’s just go.
I want to go now. Let’s go.
Get in.
The experimental data
are very accurate.
And the result is inspiring.
But why didn’t you try
different brightness levels?
Maybe we’ll find out other phenomena
that might help us with the research.
Using different divergent materials
to see the best result.
But it may take some time.
No, it won’t.
I’ll finish the experiment
in the shortest possible time.
Um, good, keep it going.
We’ll head out for lunch.
See you.
OK.
Welcome.
What would you like?
I’ll have one latte, and one iced cocoa.
Extra sweet.
Sure.
You know me well.
- Extra whip cream too, please.
- Sure.
Hey. You really are stressed,
aren’t you?
Um.
(Movie Night)
I’m going to attend
to congratulate on your project too.
They even had the guts
to invite me to go.
You don’t have to say much.
Just sue them.
I’ll get the lawyers for you.
Oh.
From what they said,
it’s going to be difficult.
I guess Pon was right.
All work created by a company’s employee
belongs to the company.
But it should be under your name.
Not Faye’s.
Just quit from that company.
And just post it on social media.
I’ll think of the caption for you.
“The secret of the latest work
and a hot celebrity like Time”.
“Famous company falsely claims
employees work”.
How about this one?
“Revealing the story
behind company’s senior and leaders,
cooperate in a scandal”.
Hey.
A superstar like me
thinking of a caption for you,
don’t you like any of them?
I’ll get fired that way.
Do you know?
I’ve always dreamed of
working in Bangkok.
I’ll probably have to keep this job.
Just like Faye said.
And you’re just going to let it go
like this?
What do you want me to do?
Forget it.
I guess it’s just my bad luck.
Does Pupaa know about this yet?
Or are you and Pupaa
over?
Watch your mouth.
He’s just still busy,
so I haven’t told him yet.
That sucks.
Girlfriend always comes first.
Don’t talk about Pupaa like that.
Thank you.
(Pupaa)
Hey, what are you doing?
- Let me see.
- Give it to me.
Who called?
Hello. What’s up, Pupaa?
Hello, Prapai.
I’m done with the experiment.
The experiment went well today.
Just only a few experiments left
for additional data.
Um.
I want you to come back already.
Don’t worry.
This should be the last part.
If I don’t go back soon,
I bet someone’s going to steal you
from me.
Prapai, are you alright?
Oh, nothing. I’m okay.
Wait for me.
I’ll be back as soon as possible.
What’s wrong with you?
Oh, nothing.
I got bit by a dog.
Pupaa. Hello?
Are you still there?
Just turn on the camera,
I have something to say to Time.
Um.
Hi.
How did you know I’m with her?
The possibility.
Seems like you really miss me.
Stop messing with Prapai.
If I don’t, what are you going to do?
Look. We’re really close to each other.
Hey.
Hey, is that your new girlfriend?
No, she’s not.
She’s one of the team members.
If you can have someone close to you,
then Prapai doesn’t have to
feel bad about it too.
Prapai, I’ll be back
as soon as possible.
Um. I’ll wait for you.
If you’ve got anything, just tell me.
24 hours. I’ll have my phone on.
I know.
If I’ve got anything,
I’ll text you right away.
Alright, you can get back to work.
Okay.
Prapai.
Pupaa is always busy
with the experiment.
Don’t just always keep texting Pupaa.
Just do what you can on your own.
Hey, if you’re that busy,
I’ll take care of Prapai for you.
Your girlfriend just...
I’ve got to go now. Bye.
Think about it, I was the one
who came up with this project.
I was the one who cast the actors.
I also asked you for help
to be the set’s photographer.
But then
Faye just put her name
under the project.
If you have the chance,
you’ve got to help me prove it.
(Pupaa)
Sure, always.
Just let me know when.
Um.
But Pupaa doesn’t know
about this, right?
No. You must not tell Pupaa.
Currently he’s doing
a very important research,
I don’t want him to
lose concentration with this problem.
If Pupaa knows about it
and has a problem with his research,
you’re dead.
I know.
But actually, you really want Pupaa
to come back, don’t you?
Why is love so difficult to understand?
You’ve really changed.
I’ve never thought I’d hear anything
like this from you.
I’m being honest here. I’m not playing.
So what’s your problem? Tell me.
My dad wants me to go back to Chiang Mai
to continue his legacy
of the family’s business.
You know well
that my relatives are fighting for this.
And I don’t want to do it too.
Oh, so then what did Wawa say?
She told me to go.
Huh?
What do you think Wawa really thinks?
Why does she have to push me away?
Girls are difficult to understand.
(Wat Kalayanimitra)
Oh, dear God,
I hope Pupaa comes back to me soon.
If Pupaa comes back within today
or tomorrow,
I will bring you 100 boiled eggs.
No, I’ll do it again.
If Pupaa comes back within today
or tomorrow,
I will...
I will dance in order to honor you.
(Ticket number 23)
Ticket number 23.
Hey.
When talking about true love,
they say you’ll find one
in your hardest times.
How did you get here?
Why? Can’t I come to the temple too?
Can I read yours?
You’ve read mine already.
Let me see. Let me read it too.
Here, I’ll read it for you.
(Ticket number 25)
Ticket number 25
says that I’ll be able to win the heart
of a girl with short legs,
who’s short, clumsy, and eats a lot too.
This is very accurate.
So cute.
Hey, shorty, come here.
It looks so real.
A lot better than the first one.
I agree.
I think Pupaa’s project
will win a big reward this time.
Awesome, really awesome.
Congratulations, Pupaa.
You haven’t changed at all.
You always do your best in everything.
Thank you.
Um, the experiment is successful.
Can I go back to Thailand?
I have some emergency.
Well.
Actually
I was about to talk to you with this.
OK.
It’s difficult to have such
an excellent student like you.
So our university
will offer you scholarship
for you to further your study here
until you graduate with a Ph.D.
This is the application form.
Think about it.
OK.
(Application Form for
Beiqing University Scholarship)
Yes, mom?
Mom.
Hello.
How long are you here for?
I’ll be off
to another business trip soon.
I have a transit flight at this city,
so I just came by.
Mom.
Do you know any lawyers?
Especially those who specialize
in copyright laws.
Is there a problem with your experiment?
Why do you need a lawyer?
Nothing.
The work
just needs some information
from the lawyer.
Then I’ll send you the contacts
of the lawyer of my company to you.
Thank you.
Are you going to fly straight back
to Thailand?
Or are you going to continue
staying here?
Well,
I prefer to be back in Thailand.
Why so?
The curriculum here is better,
and the equipment is better.
There’s more creativity
and more chances for success here.
I think you should know best about this.
Mom,
why did you and dad choose to work
far away from each other?
What if someone has a problem,
and can’t be together.
Don’t you feel anything?
Even if our family is far apart,
but the relationship never fades.
But the reason that we are not together,
is because we have responsibilities.
If we could choose,
we probably wouldn’t choose to do this.
Thank you, mom.
You’re not having this problem, are you?
I know what I have to do next.
I have to get back to work now.
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, mom.
(Pupaa)
Prapai.
Just handle what you can by yourself.
(Pupaa)
My clever Prapai, keep fighting.
Hey, did you know?
When it happened, I was so mad.
I couldn’t think of a solution.
All I thought was it would’ve
been better if you were here.
But Ta and Time said they’ll help me.
But when they help
they’ll also be effected by it.
Kwang was right.
I shouldn’t let others
be helping me all the time,
waiting for others to help.
I need to rely on myself.
I will bring back what belongs to me.
My clever Prapai, keep fighting.
Don’t forget to cheer for me, Pupaa.
(I want to ask about some legal advice)
(My girlfriend’s work
was stolen by her boss)
(by claiming it as her own)
(Seek for the truth and find evidence)
(Ta, call me when you’re awake)
I’m glad you like it.
Hello, Mr. Tum, Mrs. Add.
- Thank you.
- Please.
Please.
Squeeze in more.
Look here.
This one here.
Time, Time. Come here.
Time, this camera, please.
- Sure.
- Come on.
The other side, please.
This camera too.
- Hello there, Time.
- Hello.
Please feel comfortable.
Thank you.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Great.
Thank you.
Why are you dressed like this today?
I’m just a regular employee
who contributed in this project.
Dressing up won’t look too good.
If you want to dress accordingly,
you’ll have to
dress up as Wonder Woman.
So you can find the bad guys here.
Do you want a superhero to help?
Don’t you dare do anything.
I warn you.
Otherwise, we’re done.
Is there something going on?
Nothing.
Maybe I’m seeing things.
We nearly got caught.
Thank god we hid first.
Keep it quiet, or we’ll get caught.
The plan will be wrecked.
We’re undercover like this,
it’s impossible to be caught like this.
So pretty.
(Q&A PARTY)
(Film by Fuangfah Suriya
C Agency Co., Ltd.)
It’s time for the Q&A session.
May I please invite all guests here.
Who would like to ask
the first question?
The lady at the back, please.
What was your inspiration
to create this short film?
The meaning of love.
Over the past years,
I have been collecting information,
both from direct experiences
and many stories.
I’ve written many stories.
But I think this one is the best by far.
So I decided to do it.
There might be a following episode too.
But I don’t think so.
Because I was the one
who did this short film.
Hold on.
Is it true?
I thought of everything.
Faye has nothing to do with it.
Really?
That’s impossible.
What are you talking about?
Everyone, excuse me.
If you want the evidence,
I’ll prove it to you.
Because I have all the information
about it.
You can just copy all the information
into the thumb drive for me.
I’ll sort it out for you.
Did you...
Prapai.
It’s not nice to be accusing me
like this.
If you don’t have other evidences,
I might have to sue you.
Is it so?
What’s the matter?
I can be the witness.
I am the photographer
of this short film.
And this girl here is the leading role.
We can prove to you that
Prapai was the one who directed it,
and planned everything herself.
You’ve known Prapai for a long time,
why would you do this to her?
You guys are all going
against me, right?
You’re all friends.
You have to be on her side.
There’s not enough weight here.
Hey sis,
why are you accusing us like this?
Security.
Take out the uninvited guests.
Wait, what is this?
Stop.
- Hey, let go.
- Let go.
What if I’m the one proving it?
The work that everyone is seeing
What?
is all done by her.
Why is it like this?
Prapai, the fact that I let you
help out a few projects
doesn’t mean that this project is yours.
Do you know the consequences
of your actions
for accusing your company?
You too, Time.
Do you think people will believe you?
I know your relationship with her
is not just friends.
Oh really?
What?
Is that true?
That’s Lisa, Time’s ex.
Why is she here?
Is that his ex-girlfriend?
What?
Oh my god.
Hello, Lisa.
I heard a rumor about Time.
He’s planning to open up
about his new relationship
during the Q&A session of my short film.
I just wanted to tell you.
In case you wanted to congratulate him.
Lisa, hi.
Hello.
Lisa just came to congratulate
with our agency.
And also Time.
Are you both not mad at each other
anymore?
So you’re here to congratulate Time
with his new girlfriend, right?
Prapai, the girl
who had the problem with the fans.
She’s the one
who got drunk and he took her out.
So that means
there’s really something going on
between you two, right?
So when did you guys start dating?
Did you date with her before
or after you were dating Lisa?
Time, can you please answer?
So everything you just said,
was to protect your new girlfriend,
right?
Is that right?
Am I right?
- So you’re helping your new girlfriend?
- Is that true?
Time, please answer.
- Does she just want the work?
- Really?
- So who’s work is this?
- What’s the matter?
Everyone please listen to me.
Me and Prapai are just friends.
And we have nothing more than that.
That means you think of her
only as friends?
Everyone, I think
about that issue,
you can ask that later.
- Time, so what’s going on?
- Yeah, what is this?
- What happened?
- What’s the matter?
- Is it just work or more than that?
- What’s the situation?
- So who’s plan is it?
- Please answer.
- Yes, please answer.
- What’s the matter?
- I’m sorry.
- What is happening?
- I didn’t think
- Really?
- that it would be a big problem.
- Answer, please.
- What’s the matter?
- Please answer the question.
- Please answer.
- Please answer us.
- What’s the matter?
- Please answer.
- Prapai.
Please answer us.
(Special scene)
Excuse me, excuse me.
- Hello?
- Pupaa.
Where are you? Prapai is in big trouble.
Alright.
I’ll get there as soon as possible.
Excuse me.
To here, please.
Thank you.
You can go.