♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪For us to be together♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 18=
Prapai and Time
have nothing between them.
Because her boyfriend is right here.
I’m sorry
for letting you fight alone for so long.
I have proof to show
who is the real director of the film.
You’re here just in time.
Please help out.
Sure.
Pupaa, I saw an announcement today.
They said the topic is about
the memory of love.
So I’m thinking of competing.
I don’t want any prize,
I just want it to be our story.
Don’t worry.
I’m here now.
I would like to tell you again
that Time and Prapai
have nothing between them.
Because I’m Prapai’s boyfriend.
Time just wanted to help
reveal the truth.
Let’s just say Prapai helped the company
and I created this work.
It must be the company’s work.
I submitted under the company’s name.
And what’s the problem with that?
First of all,
according to the footage
you weren’t the one who started it.
It was Prapai.
You stole her work.
Second of all,
you said this is the company’s work.
This is also another evidence.
Pupaa.
I was thinking of
going to talk with Wawa.
I think she’ll be great
with playing as me.
Pai, how’s your project going?
Well,
I’m in the process of
looking for the actors.
But I’ve only got time
after work to do so,
so I’m not rushing it.
Will you be in time to submit it?
Let me know if you want time off.
I don’t want to disturb working hours.
I planned to film it next week.
It should be in time.
I’m so excited.
This is the first time
that I’ve worked on anything to compete
in something like this.
This is what I want everybody to know.
I’ve tried
calculating the possibilities.
If we really decided to sue,
these evidence wouldn’t be enough
to accuse the company.
Because the company’s lawyers
would also have to fight hard.
But I want everyone to know,
and decide for yourselves,
whether this work
should belong to who.
Everyone.
No matter who did it,
it is done by
one of C Agency’s employees.
We’ve got many talented employees.
Prapai is someone who has a dream.
And the dream that made her successful
all came from learning with C Agency.
Thank you so much, C Agency,
for making me see
both sides of the world.
This work represents
the story of my love.
That’s why I wanted a name in it.
And that all my friends helped me,
they were all willing to help,
without anything in return.
I want to announce right here.
From now on,
I’m not an employee of C Agency anymore.
I quit.
Miss Faye, what is going on?
What is the truth?
Yeah, What’s the truth?
Please answer.
Is it really Prapai’s,
and not from the company?
- What happened? What’s going on?
- What’s happening?
Can you please answer?
Please explain to us.
I guess that’s the real superhero.
- Please give us an answer.
- Please answer.
I finally quit.
It’s best you came out
from a place like that.
I never thought
someone I knew for many years
would do this to me.
What am I going to do next?
You don’t have to think about it now.
Just take some rest.
It’ll be better tomorrow.
Isn’t it strange?
Every time I have a problem,
you’re always here to help me in time.
I missed you so much.
Thank you for coming back.
I missed you too.
Oh yeah.
I have somewhere
I want you to go with me.
Oh.
Pupaa.
Why are you hiding there? Come here.
Quickly.
Quick.
What did you wish for?
I wished for you to come back to me.
And here you are.
Come here quickly.
You’re the one who wished for it.
You should be dancing alone.
Why do I have to dance with you?
Oh.
I thought you said whatever I do,
wherever I go,
we’ll do so together.
Wait, hold on.
Are you really going to let me
dance alone?
Dance with me, please.
Pretty please.
Hey.
You don’t love me, do you?
But
I don’t know how to dance.
Never mind, we can follow them.
Come on. Come, come.
Right here.
Excuse, we’re ready now.
You’re ready, right?
Yes.
Then let’s start.
Sure.
So
how did you know about my problem?
Did Ta tell you?
Oh, Ta, I told you not to tell.
I need to punish him.
Ta didn’t tell me.
You’re the one who told me.
Me?
When did I tell you?
When you told Ta not to tell me.
Ta is so sneaky.
Why didn’t you tell me about it?
Aren’t we dating?
Next time whenever there’s a problem,
you have to tell me everything, alright?
I know.
During that time
you had your own problems.
So I didn’t want to bother you
with mine.
Well, how did yours go?
All done.
Huh?
All done?
I thought you said it would take a year.
Someone like me doesn’t need a year.
Of course, genius.
So what are you going to do next?
Hold on.
Hello. This is Prapai.
Yes.
Yes, I’m a creative worker.
But I’m not working for
C Agency anymore.
Really?
Sure. See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Pupaa, someone contacted me for work.
They said they wanted to do
an advertisement.
But they don’t want to work
with an agency.
So they wanted me to work with them.
If I get this job,
I’ll take care of you.
(EGAT Learning Center)
(Welcome)
Hello.
I’m here.
The meeting room?
Sure, I’ll be right there.
Yes. Goodbye.
Let’s go.
So in summary,
EGAT Learning Center
wants to promote to everyone
about energy
and the process of electricity
to the community and the environment.
And emphasize EGAT’s reputation
to the nationwide level, right?
Yes.
I feel like I’m
one of the target consumers here too.
Yes.
If you have any questions,
you can always ask me.
Sure.
I’ll have a look around the place
and see what we can bring out.
Then I’ll propose the idea to you soon.
That’s great.
Our leader here will be personally
showing you around.
He’s new and just joined our team.
He’s very dedicated.
And he wanted to deal with the project
by himself.
Oh, here he is.
- Ken.
Hello.
After you went to China,
Professor recommended me
to someone from here.
I thought it was a stable job
and also interesting,
so I gave it a try.
That’s great.
You’re also a leader.
That’s so cool, right, Pupaa?
Nah, you’re overreacting.
I still need to learn a lot more.
And I also have to know
a broader range of knowledge.
The higher the position,
the higher the expectations.
So I have to do everything on my own.
So what’s interesting here?
You want to know, right?
Follow me, I’ll take you around.
Let’s go.
Pupaa, let’s go.
There’s a lot more.
Really?
Hey, Pupaa.
What’s wrong with Prapai?
Pupaa, let’s go.
Leave her alone.
Let’s go over there.
Let’s go.
Pupaa.
Look at this, a hologram.
It’s great.
Just like what you did.
Um.
Let’s go look at something else.
Wow.
I want to take you to see something.
- Hey.
- Alright, let’s go.
Pupaa, look at this. It’s so scary.
- Pupaa, look. Pupaa?
- Come on.
Pupaa.
The only thing I can never win
for Pupaa
is science, I guess.
Hey.
Go follow her, what’s wrong?
Prapai.
Prapai, hold on. Prapai.
What’s wrong with you?
Aren’t you having fun?
I don’t understand anything.
It must be too hard for someone like me.
It’s not that hard.
Have a look at this.
♪Where is true happiness♪
♪In the far away sea♪
♪Or in the great mountains♪
♪Please tell me, tell me♪
So you’re not with Tum anymore?
Um. Tum got a job at the amusement park.
Um.
It suits him well.
Wait.
Hold on.
Isn’t he a scientist?
Why do scientists
work in the amusement park?
So you don’t know
that Tum is crazy about machines.
And now the amusement park
is not the same anymore.
All the new rides
need physicians to help design and plan.
I also heard Tum is going
on a business trip overseas too.
At big amusement parks.
I’m so jealous of him.
Wow. That’s great, right?
Oh yeah.
What about you research?
The one Professor said it’s great...
Do you want to go back now?
Huh?
Why do you want to go now?
Ken must be busy.
Oh, right.
I’ll go now.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Good luck.
Bye then.
- Bye.
- See you.
Do you want me to see you off?
It’s alright.
Bye.
Just a minute.
Hello.
Pupaa,
I want you to think about it again.
You’ll still make it
if you come back now.
I’ve made my mind.
And you’ll regret it later.
I won’t.
I have to go now.
Who were you talking to?
Is it about the research?
Nothing. Let’s go back.
Let’s go.
Oh.
You have a guest?
Yes, I do.
Very much like me.
Do you remember Prapai?
Hello.
Oh.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to become one of your students.
No, no. I don’t want this.
Honey, please help.
Think of it as tutoring a student
enrolling into a university.
But you...
I don’t need to be extra clever,
I just want to be able to talk
with Pupaa.
That’s the difficult part.
We’re going to learn something important
about the galaxy,
about our Earth.
And those people who have been
creating these new theories.
The three rules of Newton.
If I had to guess,
I think it’s about ice, right?
That’s not it.
Newton experimented on energy.
He was the one who discovered gravity.
He was sitting under a tree,
and an apple fell on his head.
It made him realize...
It’s so delicious.
Let’s talk about this one.
The closets planet to the sun.
The first is called the Mercury.
The next one is Venus.
That means our Earth is...
What are you laughing at?
Oh.
Talking about it, it made me think about
the cartoon Sailor Moon.
Have you heard of it?
Transform.
I can’t stop but laughing at it.
I can’t do this anymore.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Oh.
How about this?
I’ll talk about prism
and the refraction of light.
Oh.
It’s the refraction of white light,
refracting into a rainbow.
It’s called a spectrum.
Seems like you have some knowledge
about this topic.
Just a bit.
Hello.
Prapai.
It’s time to come home.
Well.
I know you’re at Professor’s house.
Here, let me speak to him.
Pupaa.
I’m sorry she’s been disturbing you.
It’s alright.
Oh.
About the project in China...
Everything is completed.
There’s nothing left.
I’ll go meet you at the laboratory
sometime.
Um.
Thank you.
Here, water.
Oh.
Are you going already?
Yes. He knows.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Goodbye, bye.
Um. From the looks of it,
he hasn’t told her
about the scholarship.
It’s so hard to understand
the love between kids these days.
Isn’t it?
But in the end,
Prapai will have to know anyway, right?
I don’t even want to think about it
when she figures out.
Oh.
Using my brains drains me so bad.
Come here.
I told you already
that you don’t have to know
about science.
Just be yourself
and do what you do best.
Well, recently,
whenever I ask you about the research,
you never talk to me about it.
I just want to be someone
you can tell anything to.
There’s nothing.
Don’t worry about it.
I’m just tired from working
on the research for so long.
So I just wanted to stop thinking
about it.
Then you can go to bed.
They say sleeping is the best way
to relax your brain.
You should be sleeping a lot.
I’m really relaxing my brain.
I haven’t heard this kind of melody
for a while now.
It’s lovely. New song?
What’s up?
I think it’s time to go.
Or we’ll be stuck in traffic.
Where do we have to go?
Oh, you forgot?
We’ve got an amusement park to review.
Stand up now.
Oh.
Okay.
Follow me.
We’re done with today’s review.
Don’t forget to come and have some fun.
That’s great.
Time, great job.
That should do, right?
Sure.
Great.
You can have a look
at the footage first.
It’s great.
Hold on.
Will it be okay
if I have a favor to ask?
What is it?
Hey, where is Tum?
He’s the one who made this appointment.
I don’t like people not being on time.
We’re not in school anymore.
Why is he so irresponsible?
We’re all grown now.
Watch me, when he comes,
I’m going to embarrass him.
I really don’t like it
when people are irresponsible.
Oh, there he is. He’s there.
Go on, Ken, you can do it.
Watch me, watch me.
I’m here.
Hey, why are you late?
I was stuck in traffic. Sorry.
Oh.
I said just do it.
Just do it like what you just said.
- You want me to do it?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Don’t be late again.
Um.
Good.
What’s wrong with him?
Never mind.
What happened?
He’s just late. Never mind.
I think you should find a way
to win her heart
before Time makes a move.
For example, practice some singing
and playing the guitar.
I don’t know how to sing.
Don’t worry.
Professor Ta will teach you.
Great.
1, 3, 2. Not this 2.
2, 2, this finger here.
Um.
Try again.
Strum it slowly.
I never knew
being a musician is this hard.
Can you do it?
Or you’re starting to understand
your competitor?
I didn’t want to understand.
I’m doing it for Pai.
You can take the guitar and practice.
I’ll be going back to Chiang Mai,
and I won’t be using it.
Hey,
what do you think I should do
about Wawa?
You’ll have to ask yourself.
What makes you happy?
For me,
long distance relationship
really doesn’t work out.
You can do it.
Um.
What are you doing?
Did you need anything?
I thought I heard a guitar.
Oh, I was listening to music.
Really?
Um.
Huh?
What’s up?
Nothing.
Um.
Okay, bye.
So this is all I’ve got.
If you want any changes,
please let me know.
It seems alright.
Did you want to edit any details?
Um.
I don’t think so.
Prapai has her own proofreader.
I’ll continue with coordinating
the work.
I’ll have to excuse myself too, Prapai.
Ken.
Huh?
Just a minute.
Well,
Pupaa’s been acting strange lately.
Do you know anything?
Um.
I don’t know.
Tell me right now. What do you know?
I really don’t know.
Your phone’s ringing, Prapai.
I have to go now.
Oh.
Ken.
This guy.
What’s up, Mr. Idol?
Can you come to see me?
Huh?
Why do I have to go see you?
I’m not working for C Agency anymore.
I’m not your servant anymore.
I have a client
who wants to do some advertising.
So I thought I’d introduce them to you.
Do you want it?
Can I trust you?
You’ve tricked me so many times.
I’m not stupid anymore.
If you don’t want it, then that’s fine.
Hey.
Where do I go?
Amusement park. Tonight. 7:00 PM.
What?
(Siam Amazing Park)
Am I being played on again?
Hey.
I thought you said
you’re meeting me for work.
What are you going to do to me again?
I’m not going to trick you.
I have something for you.
Please, can you just listen to me?
I’m for real this time.
I wrote a song.
I want you to be the first to hear it.
Because if I hadn’t met you,
there wouldn’t have been this song.
♪Late tonight, oh oh♪
♪It’s prettier than any other night♪
♪The wind is whistling by♪
♪Bringing us close together tonight♪
♪A night like this
won’t happen so often♪
♪Can I take advantage of it?
I want you to♪
♪If tonight was the night of my dreams♪
♪Where there’re only me and you♪
♪In the perfect hour♪
♪Will you be with me the entire night?♪
♪And talk until sunrise♪
♪And make this a memorable time for me♪
♪The perfect hour♪
(Coupon)
When will Pupaa be signaling us?
Or did we miss it?
Um, maybe.
I really like you.
Can you like me?
Oh.
Pupaa.
What are you doing here?
I’m here to take you home.
Hey.
Were you always here?
Even though you saw me
confess my love to Prapai.
And you didn’t even come over to stop?
When I listened to your song,
I just feel that everyone has the right
to confess their love.
And I want Prapai
to have the right
to choose the love she deserves.
Time.
The song you just sang was beautiful.
I’m sure your fans will love it.
It’s...
It’s not my song.
But it will be the song
for everyone that loves you.
Hey.
How can you reject the dream
of all the girls in the country?
You’re such a
weird girl.
I guess so.
Weird girls like me
don’t suit a nationwide superstar
like you.
But
I thank you for the good feelings
you have for me.
But
my heart
has been used by a scientist
in solving all the equations already.
Even though I failed
with confessing my love this time,
I wish the best for you.
Um.
Thank you.
Can I hug you?
To our friendship.
Thank you so much.
Um.
What were you talking about for so long?
I told him
that the song he sang today
was very touching.
But
I don’t like singers.
I like scientists.
(Coupon)
Hey.
Hey. It’s time.
It’s show time.
You also have a surprise for me?
What if
I chose Time and didn’t choose you?
What would you do?
I knew you’d choose me.
You know too much.
Congratulations.
As you both already have a happy ending.
I have a favor to ask.
I’ll have fried pork skin,
northern chili paste and chili dip.
Pai.
Thank you.
Wawa.
Wait, hold on.
I thought it was only you and Pupaa.
Well,
come sit down with us first.
Ta won’t go to Chiang Mai.
He wants to stay here.
Are you okay with this, Wawa?
Ta wants to stay, but his dad doesn’t.
My dad doesn’t want me to stay
and so what?
It’s not about me.
Stop acting like a kid.
Your dad built this business
and you should go back and help him.
I don’t want to work
for my dad’s business.
I want to build my own business.
Your own business?
Everything you’re and using right now
is all from your family’s money.
If you stay with me,
I believe I can do it.
Please, Wawa, don’t leave me.
I’ll tell you something, Ta.
I never said that we’re back together.
And especially with a kid like you,
I’m not with you.
Is this
how you see me?
Yes.
Wait, hold on, Wawa.
Hey.
What are you thinking?
If you were Ta, what would you do?
I would stay in Bangkok.
We can work anywhere.
But we can’t find love anywhere.
If there’s success,
but with no one by your side,
it won’t mean a thing.
But if you don’t go back,
it means you’ve cut the relationship
with your family.
What would you do?
I would make them understand.
But if they don’t understand,
I will still choose love over anything.
I believe, one day, they’ll understand.
What if you were Wawa?
What would you do?
I would probably want to be
with the one I love.
But
I don’t want to be a burden in his life.
Ow.
Why is this so difficult?
I’ll go to the restroom first.
Um.
(Kwang)
Hello?
Do you have anything with Pupaa?
Is that Prapai?
Um.
It’s good that it’s you.
I want to ask you
the fact that you made Pupaa
leave his future like this,
are you really going to be happy?
(Special scene)
Hello, Professor.
Pupaa, your girlfriend is at my house
right now.
She’s trying
to let me teach her science.
But she has no foundation.
My head is exploding.
There’s one thing she might know.
What is it?
Prism and light refraction.
And I’ll try to get her home.
Um.