♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 9=
I’m going now.
Please calm down.
Why should I wait for someone
who is not punctual?
I beg you, Time.
Can you think about
the other staff as well?
If you leave now,
then what is everyone else going to do?
That’s not my problem.
Please, Time.
I’ll do whatever you tell me to do.
Please just stay.
You’re willing to do everything. Really?
Um.
Okay. Alright then.
Then from now on, you will do as I say.
Everything.
Huh?
Alright.
The cocoa drink in your hand.
Can I have it?
Alright.
Thank you.
Pon, so what are we doing?
I’ll try to follow up.
Alright.
This way, please.
We’re here. Time is here.
Here we go.
(Seasonal fruit)
This way, please.
If we’re ready
then let’s do a blocking rehearsal.
How are we going to do that?
My rehearsal partner isn’t here yet.
Well, Time, during the shoot,
you will have to say
you can also live life at the market,
and then wink at the model.
Just like that.
You’re going to be my rehearsal partner,
servant.
Okay?
Okay. If we’re all ready,
then let’s start.
What did you call me?
Well, you have to do everything
as I say, don’t you?
Hey.
Sure.
You can rehearse your blocking now.
(Seasonal fruit)
Go ahead.
You can also live life at the market.
Okay. Just about right.
Where’s the model?
I’m still trying to contact her.
This set’s staff is just useless.
What location did they send?
I was lost for ages.
Such a waste of time.
And what is this?
Why are you using a dwarf
as my stand-in? This isn’t right.
Well, it wasn’t her job to do so.
If the real actor
had some responsibility,
did some research on the route
before travelling,
then you wouldn’t have to be screaming
and blaming it on others like this.
And this dwarf
wouldn’t have to be standing here.
I’m here already. Can we just start?
Hold on.
Just wait.
I need to use the restroom.
Sure.
I’ll go get him.
Okay.
Guys, let’s take a break.
Time.
Give me your phone.
You don’t need to be shy, come on.
Just a minute.
Okay.
One, two...
Thank you for supporting me here today.
I have to get back to work now.
Servant.
You followed me here?
Time, I thought you left.
You think I’m that irresponsible?
No, I didn’t mean it like that.
What are you looking at?
Oh, I thought I saw a friend.
I don’t think so.
Because my looks
must have blurred everyone out already.
Shall we go back to the set?
So we can finish soon.
Okay.
This way.
(Jom, sugar cane dessert)
You can also live life at the market.
Cut.
Water.
Are you hot?
(Guide for men to chase after women)
(How to win a girl’s heart)
Oh, you’re back?
(Guide for men to chase after women)
Is this yours?
Who are you chasing after?
Well,
this isn’t mine.
Tum forgot it with me.
I’m going to give it back to him
tomorrow.
Hello.
Good morning. Have you had breakfast?
Is it Pupaa?
Um.
Not yet. I just got up.
Aren’t you going to work?
I finished the shoot late last night.
So I’m having the day off.
What do you want?
Well, I...
Hold on. Why is it so echoey?
What are you trying to do?
Why did you call
when you’re right in front of my room?
Why didn’t you knock?
They said to call regularly.
They?
Who are they?
So what do you want?
Today is the 14th of March.
14th of March.
Oh, White Day.
What is it?
Open it.
What is this?
Do you like it?
It’s a special day today.
I know.
I know today is the 14th of March.
It’s White Day.
It’s world Pi day.
And it’s also Einstein’s birthday.
Take it back.
I’m going back to sleep now.
And don’t wake me up for lunch.
I’m not going to eat.
You don’t want it?
Why don’t you like it?
It’s so meaningful.
Is something wrong, Prapai?
I got a weird gift from a weird person.
Who is it? A pervert?
Not to that extent.
But
he gave me a gift that
no other person normally gives.
A gift?
Um.
Or he likes you?
Are you out of your mind?
Never. It’s impossible.
Then why would he give you a gift?
Normally,
guys will only give gifts
to the girl they like.
I don’t think so.
It doesn’t seem like he likes me.
All he does is calculate
and experiment stuff.
I don’t even know
if he knows what love is.
Or is he doing an experiment on you?
But getting a weird gift
is better than having a boyfriend
who doesn’t care about you.
I’m done with this, Pai.
He doesn’t answer my calls.
I send him texts,
he reads them but doesn’t reply.
If you’ve had enough, then just stop.
I’ve tried hard enough, right?
I don’t think Ta
even deserves your love.
Holding on will just hurt me more.
Breaking up would be the best solution.
But ever since I’ve been born,
I’ve never broken up with anyone before.
Will he be sad, Pai?
Wawa, stop thinking about others.
Think about yourself too.
If you don’t want to go alone,
I’ll go with you.
Thank you.
(Ta)
Hello, Ta.
Sure.
I have something to tell you too.
Great move, Ta.
Ta.
Are you free next week?
Let’s break up.
That’s all I wanted to say.
You can get back to your game.
Ta, are you still playing?
Come on.
Wawa.
How was it?
I was the one who told him.
But why am I the one sad?
It’s alright.
It will be better.
You will always have me here.
It’s alright.
Everything will have to be better.
I think it’s Prapai.
I know it is.
Cute, right?
It’s so cute.
Both of you please concentrate.
I’ll be back.
How’s your experiment going?
Why are you asking?
You’re helping me with it now.
I was talking about your
personal experiment.
Not bad.
Not bad? What does it mean?
As in, you understand the variable now?
Well, there’s a daily exchange
of information.
What information are you exchanging?
Cheesy romantic ones?
Well, Hello, Pupaa.
I’ve got to go, Pupaa.
Oh, Pupaa.
Me and the security guard
has a better relationship than this.
What a waste.
You’re such a handsome guy,
why are you such a loser in love?
Then what can I do
to understand the variable more?
You have to study its properties
and its nature.
Collect data from the environment too.
What experiment is it?
You can talk to me. Maybe I can help.
The most relatable environment
to a variable like Prapai.
That’s right. Wawa.
Hey. Is that papaya salad?
You don’t normally have fermented fish,
do you?
What do you want from me?
I just brought it back.
It’s alright if you don’t want it.
It’s so good. You’re so kind.
So,
how has your friend been lately?
My friend? Who?
Wawa?
Girls really do have strong sense.
You know about it already?
But I feel bad for Wawa.
Wawa really loves Ta.
I think she’ll need a lot of time
to heal.
The amount of time
to heal from a break up
is half the time they’ve been in love.
But if you want to heal faster,
you must find a replacement for the loss.
Wow, what a quote.
You read it from that book right?
It’s not nice to be reading from
someone else’s book.
I asked for information
on an experiment.
An experiment?
Or is he doing an experiment on you?
(Memory Box)
Let’s go.
I can’t stop laughing seeing that scene.
I thought you were going to help me.
But you held on to the music box
so tight.
Then from now on, I will help you first.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
That I’m more important
than a music box now.
Wee, why didn’t you call me?
Do you know how important today is?
I’m sorry, Ta.
Oh, hey, friends.
Ta.
You talk with him first. I’ll be back.
Um.
What happened this morning?
Why did the event start late?
It’s because of Wee.
I told her to call and wake me up,
but she didn’t.
Well, first year student.
You can’t really rely on them.
New girlfriend?
Ta.
Don’t you plan on changing yourself
for others?
Are you going to continue
changing girlfriends like this?
What you said was true.
I’m not good at keeping people.
I don’t really take care of people.
But whatever, it’s the past.
It’s too late to fix it.
Instead of being discouraged,
why don’t you actually
start doing something?
I don’t know if it’s too late or not.
But it depends on
whether you still love Wawa or not.
Thank you.
It’s alright.
We’ve been friends forever anyway.
Thank you.
I’ll go talk to others first.
Hey, Ta.
Yeah?
Can I have Wawa’s number?
The amount of time to heal from a break up
is half the time they’ve been in love.
But if you want to heal faster,
you must find a replacement
for the loss.
Or the person that Pupaa likes is Wawa?
I never thought
that you’re this kind of person.
I thought you said you like Prapai.
Ta.
You too.
You know that Pupaa likes Prapai?
I know now.
You know and you’re still doing this?
But Prapai is still your friend.
You can’t just start flirting
after a break up right away.
That’s enough, Ta.
The reason I’m meeting up with Wawa
is because I wanted to ask for help
about Pai.
Oh really?
Why don’t you ask me then?
I’ve been friends with Pai
for longer than Wawa.
Then what kind of guy does Pai like?
Someone like me.
I’m joking.
But I’ve had more girlfriends than you.
How about this?
I’ll teach you the techniques
to win a girl’s heart.
After winning her heart,
make sure you know how to keep it too.
Then where do we start?
What about starting from
changing your looks?
Prapai likes someone who...
Where are you going
dressed up like this?
Nothing.
I just wanted to switch things up.
Trying to switch himself up like this.
It’s so obvious.
He’s really in love.
Oh really?
So how do I look?
Do you like it?
I don’t know.
This technique doesn’t work.
Or she is still not over me?
Oh my friend,
I’m so sorry.
I really am sorry.
So then,
what should I do next?
I think the next step should be...
A girls advice won’t work out.
Let’s try the guys’ way out.
Hello there.
Oh, why are you early today?
I’m not lazy enough
to come late like you.
It’s not called being late.
It’s called being on time.
Hey, I’m talking to you nicely.
Can’t we be kind to each other for once?
Sure.
Servant.
Cut.
Servant,
touch up.
Sure.
Servant, where’s the lip balm?
Yes.
Servant, water.
Cut.
Are you done, Mr. Idol?
Wait, where’s my water?
Sure.
Don’t.
Go back to your work.
Yes.
Only I can boss her around.
Camera set.
Sound set. And...
Action.
Living Life in Bangkok.
Cut.
Come on, quick.
Right here, come on.
Today’s a great day.
Do you see the guy over there?
He’s trying to get close to her.
This is how guys do it.
Hey, where are you going?
Are you going to leave him
to touch her like that?
Don’t go bother them.
Pupaa.
Already a problem on the first day.
- Pupaa, what are you doing?
- Hey, I think that’s enough.
Servant.
No one’s here to pick you up today?
Do you need a lift?
No, thanks. I can go alone.
We don’t often finish early like this.
Do you want to go for a walk?
Hey, are you trying to
take advantage of me?
You’re not fun at all.
Don’t think that everyone is like you.
What? What did you say?
How was the situation
during the incident?
Those two guys harassed a girl.
So I went in to help.
Then what next?
Then I got punched in the face.
What happened here?
How old are you guys?
Why are you still fighting?
I’m fine. It’s alright.
It’s good that you’re alright.
I’m the one who’s hurt.
Why are they caught?
For fighting in the place.
But those two were harassing a girl.
So I’ve become the injured hero here.
What harassment?
I saw that she was dizzy,
so I wanted to give her a hand.
How is that helping?
It’s obvious you were harassing her.
I can explain the situation,
police officer.
That’s enough.
Both of you should discuss
about yourselves first.
- No.
- Sure.
I don’t think it should be a big issue.
How about this? Next time you guys come,
I’ll let you drink for free.
Is that okay?
- No.
- Yes.
But those two guys
were harassing a girl.
You’re just going to leave it like this?
Is society really this bad nowadays?
You weren’t in the situation,
why are you even bothering?
I’ve listened to you talk for a while,
I want to know, if a celebrity
came to review your place
that you ignored human rights,
will there still be customers coming?
Police officer,
we will give you the video evidence
from the security camera,
and will contact the girl
as soon as possible.
Does the police need any more details?
Let’s conclude to this then.
If there’s nothing else,
then we can split ways.
Come on.
Please lead the way, officer.
Thank you for doing it for a girl.
Don’t thank me.
Actually,
I didn’t do it
for the girl I don’t know.
But I did it for...
Come on, let’s go home.
Hold on, go home?
Well...
My house and his
are in the same direction.
I’ll go now. Bye. Ta.
Pupaa?
This is what you call the guy’s way?
Better call it an excuse to go party.
Not a single plan works.
What should I do next?
The fact that Pai saw me
going to the club like this
discredits me even more.
This time, I’ve thought about it.
It will work for sure.
How so?
Have a romantic meal together.
This plan never disappoints anyone.
Really?
Being alone together.
Confessing love in a good environment.
Anyone would fall for it.
The person that Pupaa likes
must be Wawa.
That’s why he’s trying so hard
to be close with me.
How about yesterday?
Was he thinking anything?
(Wawa, how are you?)
(Are things with Ta better? Have you...)
(Typing…)
(You put fresh food in the bin today.
It smells.)
(Clean it up.)
(Are you free tomorrow?)
If I respond immediately,
he will think that
I’m interested in talking to him.
I’ll wait for a while.
(I’m free. What’s up?)
(I want you to go somewhere with me.)
(Where to? A date?)
Am I too obvious?
I’m just an experiment subject.
Hey, you’re liking someone, right?
If you want me as part of your
dating experiment,
then just tell me.
Don’t just use me like this.
You’re not a gentleman at all.
So will you be my date partner?
Yeah, sure.
I’m not a mean person.
Wow, a huge damage on me.
Be in control, Prapai.
So beautiful.
I’m hungry already. Let’s go.
Here you go.
Thank you.
This place is lovely. It’s a pass.
But why is there no one here?
Thank you.
Have a bite.
This is just like chicken soup.
This is a molecular cuisine.
It’s a new way of presenting food.
It’s appearance may be
different and unique.
But if you taste it,
you will know what it is.
Because the real taste
will never fool you.
Hey.
Are you alright?
I forgot to take a photo.
Can I borrow yours for the photo?
Actually, your flirting skill
is quite on point.
Seems like you’ve done some homework.
The restaurant has a nice environment,
and the guy is also very pleasing.
The girl who is pursued by Pupaa,
the scientist,
must be feeling special.
I’m so jealous.
You don’t have to be jealous.
Because that girl...
is...
I’m sorry. I have to take this call.
Hello, what’s up?
Come to the location I sent you
immediately.
But this is my day off.
Where do you want me to go?
It’s work. I’ve got an urgent job.
You must come quick.
Otherwise, you’re doomed.
Hold on, it’s your job.
What does it have to do with me?
In 15 minutes,
if I don’t see you here,
be prepared to answer your boss’ call.
Hey, hold on.
(Siam Amazing Park)
An amusement park?
I have to go now. It’s an urgent call.
Right now?
I’ll treat you to a meal later, alright?
I’m sorry. See you later.
What a Prapai thing to do.
(Siam Amazing Park)
I thought you said
you had a shooting going on.
No.
I just wanted to
come to an amusement park.
But I don’t have any friends.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you like this?
I’m taking you out for some fun time.
You should be happy.
Unless I was interrupting you
with something.
Were you on a date?
No.
Then good.
You can go have fun alone.
It’s my day off today. I’m out.
Are you really going to go?
I thought you said
you’d do everything I said.
But I meant it being work-related.
But I meant everything.
Fine, if you want to go, you can.
But I won’t promise
if you’ll be seeing me
at the next shoot or not.
(Special scene)
Is this yours?
Is this going to work? I’ll try.
(There must be a gift for every holiday)
There must be a gift for every holiday.
(Gifts will win her heart)
Gifts will win her heart.
(Prapai likes colorful things)
(Prapai likes furry things)
(Prapai likes things
with lots of decorations)
Open it.
Do you like it?