♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that
what I thought was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 6=
What are you doing?
I’m 100% man.
If you don’t believe me,
do you want to try?
No, I believe you now.
Well, to summarize this,
he’s a real man. We’re all clear?
So then...
Let’s all split up now.
I’m sorry. I really am sorry.
Calm down, Prapai.
Your radar is just a little broken.
It’s going to be alright.
But...
Calm down.
Prapai.
Breathe in.
Sleep. Just sleep.
You’re the one to blame.
Why are you hiding?
That’s enough, Prapai.
Stop thinking too much.
Just calm yourself down.
Pai, Pai.
I was about to go to you.
What’s the matter, Faye?
I presented your idea
to the client today.
How was the feedback?
It passed. The clients loved it.
You’re great.
I was thinking of letting you
suggest a few references
to help guide me.
Sure.
I’ll help you after I clear of my work.
Great job, Pai.
Send them to me tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I have a department meeting tomorrow.
So I can bring it up then.
Please, Pai. Help me out.
Just think of it
as a collection of ideas.
Alright.
Great job, Pai.
Take it as an experience
in working as an advertiser.
This is too sweet.
I’ll take this one instead. Thank you.
You’re an accountant.
You have to be detailed and careful.
How can you do this?
This is all about money.
What if something happens?
Can you be responsible for it?
I can’t. I’m sorry.
Pai, I’m going now.
A late night again tonight?
It’s just 8 p.m.
I’ll wait till it’s a little later.
You’re really strange.
No one here
wants to stay late after work.
Why?
Because
no one gets paid an OT.
Man, what were you doing?
I’m not joking. It’s true.
I’m out. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
He’s probably not asleep yet.
When will he be asleep?
So I can finally go home.
I’ll go now.
Even the ghosts don’t want me here.
I’m going now. I’m sorry.
It’s late already. Why is he still up?
Why are you hiding from me?
I’m not hiding.
I just dropped something.
Are you okay? Why are you acting weird?
No. Nothing’s wrong.
Nothing at all.
I told you already.
I do believe that you’re a real man.
Mom,
I think Pai has been bit by a zombie.
Just like in the movies.
Oh my god, Pai.
Why do you look so drained?
Would you like one of my vitamins sets?
Or do you want a face moisturizer?
Can I change from the vitamins
to something else?
Sure. I’ve got everything. Just tell me.
Do you have a new room
with the same price range
as the one I live in now?
Oh, why so?
Oh, Tookta.
The reason I decided to stay
is because I thought
Pupaa didn’t like girls.
But now I know the truth.
How can you let me live with a guy?
Living with a guy is exciting.
What if one day he does something to me?
What am I going to do?
Well, don’t act like you’re innocent.
Alright, I will try
and find one for you.
Thank you.
Sure.
Bye.
Look at yourself.
Block him.
Ta, come here.
Look at him play.
Go on, Pupaa.
Everyone, let’s take a break.
What’s this?
What is going on between you two?
You’re off the game.
Oh.
Hey.
What’s going on? Spill it.
Well,
my friend told me
there’s a girl who lives with him
and she misunderstood
that he doesn’t like girls.
What kind of friend is he?
How did he manage to confuse her?
Well,
just a regular guy.
A regular guy.
Is he handsome?
Well...
Well..
He looks good.
If he looks good,
got fair skin,
takes care of himself well,
she could misunderstand.
But when she knew he’s a real man,
she starts acting strange
when he’s around.
What do you think she’s thinking?
It’s not that difficult.
She’s just shy, right?
She’s afraid.
Afraid?
Of course.
Well, a guy and a girl,
living together in a room.
It’s not weird that she’s afraid of him.
Especially if someone like Ta
creeps up on her. She’d be done.
Yeah.
Pai, you’re not done yet? So dedicated.
Cartoon.
Can I go sleep with you for a few days?
It’s not quite convenient.
But I wouldn’t mind for a few days.
Really? Thank you so much.
But
why don’t you go home?
(Prapai)
What are you looking for?
Do you need any help?
Oh, nothing.
Hold on, Pupaa.
I want to be straight.
If Pai moves out,
can I rent out the room again?
Move out?
You didn’t know?
This morning Pai was asking me
to help find her a new room.
Honey, you’re back.
Honey, that’s my friend Pai.
I’m really sorry.
Honey,
Pai will be sleeping over tonight.
Why didn’t you call me first?
I was close by already.
Cartoon,
I’m sorry I didn’t know
you lived with your boyfriend.
It’s okay. Bo doesn’t mind.
You can sleep on the bed
with me tonight.
No problem. You guys have the bed.
I’ll sleep on the sofa.
It’s alright. You want some water?
Come here.
Feel at home. You’re welcome.
Stop it, Bo. What time is this?
Bo.
Come on.
Be quiet.
Just a little kiss.
Come on, come on.
I haven’t seen you the entire day.
(Missed call)
(Pupaa 22)
(Pupaa)
What’s up, Pupaa?
Where are you?
Why aren’t you back yet?
I’m at a friend’s place.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Oh.
Why do I have to tell you everything?
Well...
It’s your turn for chores tomorrow.
Don’t forget.
Oh.
What’s wrong with him?
Stop it, Bo.
Just a little bit.
No, it tickles.
Thank you so much
for having me over last night.
Don’t worry. It’s all good.
I’ll have to disturb you again
tonight...
Hello.
Are you wearing yesterday’s clothes?
You didn’t go home?
Oh my.
Why don’t kids these days
have any responsibility?
Did you apply for the job
because you really wanted to?
Because you keep making
the same mistakes.
If this continues,
you’ll never pass probation.
Once you’re done with Pla, come to me.
That’s wild.
Let’s have dinner tonight.
Sure, but it can’t be too late.
I’ve got an early meeting tomorrow.
Okay, sure.
Where do you want to go?
Oh, Pai, how did it go?
How are your ears?
Pon, this is Pai.
The person I was telling you about.
Pai, this is Pon, the creative director.
- Hello.
Is there a problem with your job?
I couldn’t catch up
with the accounting work.
It’s alright.
Do your main job.
You can finish the job
you’re helping me with tonight.
I was thinking of
letting you do the key visuals.
To put in your portfolio.
If this job is really used,
you can say that you did it.
Really?
Um.
Sure. I’ll finish it tonight.
Good job.
Kids these days are so motivated.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Okay.
- Keep fighting.
- Bye. Thank you.
We’ll buy something back for dinner.
For Bo too.
I’ll go get my clothes too.
- Sure.
- Um.
Prapai.
Let’s go home.
Cartoon, I’ll go to you tonight.
Ouch.
Are you afraid I won’t do my chores
that you had to go take me home?
Well…
Yeah.
Alright.
I’ll finish it quickly, so I can go.
Man.
I’ve finished cleaning.
I’ll go clean the toilet.
This area is not clean yet.
It wasn’t dirty when I was sweeping it.
I’ll mop it then.
Mopping will only take 10 minutes.
Hey.
You already cleaned the toilet?
It’s still dirty.
Ah.
I already cleaned it.
Are you messing with me?
I...
Why would I do that?
It’s dirty.
Clean it properly.
Sure.
Pizza delivery is here.
Thank you.
You’re tired. Grab something to eat.
Food is the best way to keep her here.
You normally don’t eat carbs.
Why did you order pizza?
Oh,
well,
I saw there was a discount.
So I tried ordering it.
You can eat it first,
I’m not hungry yet.
She’ll fall asleep if she finishes that.
I’m stuffed. I’m sleepy now.
Just as planned.
I’ll hurry out now then.
Oh.
When did it rain?
Um.
It’s raining heavily.
Hello, Cartoon.
I don’t think I can go. It’s raining.
Really?
But it’s not raining around here.
Oh alright. See you then.
Oh.
You’re still going?
You’ll get sick.
My friend said it’s not raining there.
It’ll probably stop soon.
Okay. Take care. It’s a dark street.
Recently, there have been many stalkers
following women,
and kidnapping them.
However, the police have not yet found
the suspect.
Why have they not caught the suspect?
If you’re not in a rush,
then you don’t have to go.
It’s late. It’s dangerous out there.
And you want me to be alone with you?
You’ve been for ages,
you didn’t say anything.
Well, I didn’t know
that you’re 100% man.
I’m a 100% man.
And I’m a gentleman too.
Leaving late at night,
being dark and dangerous like this.
If you think I’m more dangerous
than those stalkers,
then it’s up to you.
Hello, Cartoon.
I don’t think I can make it.
It’s really late.
I’ll see you at the office.
Alright, bye.
Oh,
you’re not going anymore?
Um.
I don’t want to disturb my friend.
Why do you like eating unhealthy food?
(I’ve prepared breakfast for you)
(See you this evening)
(I’ve prepared breakfast for you.
See you this evening.)
(See you this evening)
(I’ve prepared breakfast for you)
I’m all done, Professor.
Oh.
Hey.
Where is he rushing off to?
Prapai.
I’m doing this for you.
So don’t scold me.
I, I...
I wasn’t going to do anything.
I...
I was just going to rub your fever off.
Love you.
What did you say?
You’re so cute.
Prapai.
Hey you.
Are you feeling better?
I just had a little fever.
Why are you in here?
Did you do something to me?
Don’t be afraid of me.
I won’t do anything like that to you.
(Hourly body temperature record)
Your fever is better now.
You don’t need to go to the doctors.
Why is your face still red?
Oh, I’m normally prone to congestion.
My cheeks get red easily.
You don’t have to go to work
if you’re sick.
Take more rest.
I’ll go get some medicine for you.
Oh,
I made you some porridge.
Just come have some when you’re hungry.
Drink lots of water too.
Um.
Thank you so much. You’re so cute.
(Faye)
How is it going, Faye?
Where are you, Pai?
I don’t see you at the office.
I’m sick, so I took a sick leave.
Oh, what should I do?
The key visual that I told you earlier,
I need to use it soon.
I’ll finish it for you
as soon as possible.
I’ll send it to you once I’m done.
Then I’ll leave it to you.
I’ll go prepare my other works.
There’s so much going on at the moment.
Alright. Goodbye, Faye.
Hope he doesn’t scold me
for working at home.
Why do I have to be
afraid of him anyway?
Why are you working during sick leave?
Did I accidentally sleep?
No, no.
Hey,
does accounting work need Photoshop?
No, it doesn’t.
Is the work at the office too little,
or you don’t have enough income?
Yeah.
Are you going to pay for me?
Hey, what is wrong with you?
I just want to do what I like.
A genius who gets to work
their dream job like you
will never understand.
I wasn’t born a genius,
but I wanted to choose this path
and dedicated myself towards it.
When you set a goal,
and dedicate yourself to it,
you’ll be successful.
If you choose to do something,
just do it.
Put in your full effort.
A dedicated person like you,
no matter which path you choose,
I’m sure you can do it.
Thank you.
You’re actually cute when you smile.
Why don’t I normally see you smile?
Well,
I don’t have any reason to smile.
So I’m the reason to make you smile.
Right?
You’re crazy.
Hurry and finish your soup.
And get some sleep.
Yes, sir.
Don’t go off smiling alone.
Cartoon.
Are you sure you’re done?
Go redo it.
I was about to let someone call you.
All of Ann’s job is done.
- From now on you can...
- Pla.
I want to quit.
What is wrong with you?
I just wanted you
to help with editing the work.
And you want to quit?
It’s not like that.
I really want to quit.
I want to go do something I want to do.
And I want to start now.
I see you’ve decided.
Up to you then.
Thank you.
Pai, have you been working so hard
that you’re going crazy?
Calm down first.
Do you want to rethink it?
It’s not that easy to find a job.
Thank you for caring for me.
But I have thought it through.
Pai.
Why are you packing?
I’ve quitted, Faye.
Quit?
What about the work
you’ve been helping me?
I’m really sorry, Faye.
But I think you should let
someone in the creative department help.
I have to go now. Goodbye.
Cartoon, bye.
Did she really quit?
Pupaa.
You’re back already.
What’s all this?
Oh,
I quit my job.
Why did you quit?
Well, I followed your advice.
If I choose to do something, just do it.
And do it with full dedication.
But I didn’t mean to let you quit.
Pla, I don’t want to quit now.
Hold on.
Calm down.
Get yourself together.
Since you’ve made up your mind,
you’ve got to move on.
What do I do next?
You can start again tomorrow.
Find a job you really want to do.
You’ve had enough for today.
You should get some rest.
(Find your dream job)
(Job description)
Why is it so difficult
to find my dream job?
Doing house chores is way easier.
Or should I be a maid?
What if I find a bossy boss like Pupaa?
I’ll probably be dead.
No, no.
Prapai.
You want a job in advertising.
Advertising.
If searching online is difficult,
then I’ll go outside and find one.
Thank you.
Oh, Pai.
Hello.
You’re going to work late?
Well,
I already quit my job.
Oh.
Will you have the money
for my rent next month?
Can I please talk with Pupaa first?
Pupaa won’t let you.
He didn’t want you to stay
since the beginning,
and now you’re not going to pay.
I don’t know how to help you anymore.
(Special scene)
Oh.
When did it rain?
Um. It’s raining heavily.
Recently, there have been many stalkers
following women.