♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 7=
Mr. Pupaa, you’re back home.
Don’t worry. I will do it for you.
Here you go.
You’ve been tired from work.
Do you want to take a seat?
Come on, come sit down.
Just sit down here,
so you can get comfortable.
Just wait a moment.
I’m coming.
Here’s some cold water.
Have a sip so you can feel fresh.
I’m not thirsty.
Even if you’re not thirsty,
you have to drink it.
You’ve been hot outside,
have a sip. You’ll be dehydrated.
Good job. I’ll give you a massage.
Here you go. Does it feel good?
What’s wrong with you today?
What’s happening?
Nothing.
I just wanted to be a good roommate.
What do you want? Tell me.
Well, right now I’m unemployed,
and I don’t have any cash.
So I’m going to do all the chores
instead of paying rent.
Pupaa, please, I beg you.
Don’t kick me out, please.
I really have nowhere to go.
I’ll do everything for you.
Including sweeping the floor, mopping,
washing the dishes and laundry too.
I’ll do your underwear too.
What did you say?
See, here. You don’t have to feel bad.
I’ve washed
my brother’s underwear before.
Don’t mess with me. Stop right there.
No.
I won’t give it to you, unless
you promise me you won’t kick me out.
- Give it to me.
- No.
I’m not giving it to you.
You must be responsible for this.
(BOTTEGA VENETA)
I never said
I was going to kick you out.
Always thinking things yourself.
Tookta made me scared.
You’re the one who wants to go.
So you’re saying you want me to stay?
Anyway,
you’ve got to stay to pay for the sofa.
You can’t go anywhere yet.
So stingy.
You know I’m unemployed.
Hey you, I’m already hungry.
Do you want to go get something to eat?
What should we eat?
It’s so so.
How about some milk tea?
Milk tea? Sure. I’ll go buy it for you.
Okay.
You can continue shopping.
If I had the money,
I’d buy everything.
First of all, you need to get a job.
I know.
Is the sofa here already? So fast.
Hello, Prapai, good girl,
and my best friend Pupaa.
Ta, how did you get here?
Why can’t I be here?
We normally sleep
in the same room anyway.
This room is nice.
I’ll have a look around.
Hey.
Rule number two, no visitors.
You used to tell me Ta is an outsider.
Why are there rules?
Oh, so you guys are staying together?
I thought Prapai was just over
to hang around at your place.
So this is it.
What’s it about this time?
How did you come stay with him?
You asked her over?
Such a friendly person.
But living alone with a guy?
Ta, it’s not like that.
Then how is it?
Explain it to me.
I was the one who asked her to stay.
You think I believe what you just said?
Isn’t it a little too much?
When I asked you about Pai,
you never told me anything.
Am I still your friend?
If we’re going to talk now,
you’ll be full of emotions.
Let’s wait until you calm down.
I have to use my emotions.
I’m asking you for real,
what are you thinking with Pai?
You like her, right?
So you planned to let her stay here.
And planned not to let me meet her.
How can you do this to a friend?
I told you already, didn’t I?
To keep your distance.
Because I know,
whoever gets close to her
will fall in love with her.
Darn it.
What does it have to be like this?
It’s like karma is after me.
Real bad.
I’m sorry.
I was too angry.
Are you hurt?
Never mind.
According to Newton’s Law,
actions equals reactions.
So we’re equal.
If Prapai has someone caring like you,
I should be happy, right?
Right now, even if she just befriends
with me again,
for me,
it’s more than enough.
Pupaa, what did Ta do to you?
Why does he have to be this harsh?
Such a gangster.
Come on, let’s get you treated.
Someone wants to talk to you.
I don’t know either
how to make you believe what I’m saying.
That I really regret everything.
But if there is anything that I can do
to make you forgive me,
you can tell me.
I’m willing to do everything.
I just want us to be friends again.
I really mean everything, Pai.
You know I can’t be mad
at anyone for long.
But talking about being friends again,
I don’t think I can do it now.
It’s alright. I can wait.
Because for me,
you’re always my best friend.
Nosy. Always on your friend’s side.
And you knew he’d punch you,
why didn’t you move?
You could’ve punched him back.
Do you think you’re the good guy
in the movies?
Why are you quiet?
Why aren’t you talking?
You make me feel...
cold that I’m numb.
Do it yourself then.
Wawa.
Ta, what happened?
I’m sorry.
Where did you go?
Never mind. It’s not your problem.
It’s not my problem?
But I’m your girlfriend.
You left me all alone all day.
And you’re saying it’s not my problem?
Isn’t it too selfish?
Why are you like this?
Do you know you’re a bad boyfriend?
Yes, I’m a bad boyfriend.
I’m bad and why did you want to date me?
Did I force you to like me?
You didn’t force me.
I’m the only one running after you.
If I knew that
it would be this tiring and useless,
I wouldn’t have since the beginning.
Here you go. It’s still hot.
Where did you buy it from?
Don’t you think
I have any cooking skills?
Is putting it in the microwave
called having cooking skills?
You caught me.
Is it good? Can I try?
Go get a new spoon.
I just want to taste only a little bit.
Can I have some?
You’ll eat all the eggs if I go.
I want to eat the egg too...
Yes, mom?
How did you know?
Ta didn’t tell you?
I should be asking you how you knew?
I already got a job,
as a Professor’s assistant.
I have to get to work now.
Talk to you later.
I’m sorry I made you hide this
from your mom.
I’m not hiding anything.
I just don’t want my mom to bother me
during my research.
Thank you anyway.
Then I better get to work.
Wait a minute, hold on.
What do you need?
Are you really going to go like this?
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Taking responsible
for being the reason you got this.
Stay still or it won’t look good.
I’m going to work now.
Hold on.
I’m not even done.
Why is he in such a rush?
What are you thinking with Pai?
You like her, don’t you?
(What do I feel?)
They say
love is more complicated than science.
You don’t need to be shy.
Love and teenager always come together.
Back when I was young,
I was everyone’s go-to person
to help out about love.
What do I have to do, Professor?
You have to prove it.
It’s not that difficult.
You can use science.
First of all, observe.
Then make an assumption,
collect all your data.
Analyze your data, and then...
Conclude.
What are you guys talking about?
Sounds like something serious.
About the scholarship, right?
There’s an opening for a
scholarship to do research.
Pupaa, if you’ve decided your
research hypothesis,
then send me the proposal.
I’ll have a look at it for you.
Yes, sir.
Meena, you’re doing your research
for your masters’ degree, right?
You can submit yours as well.
So maybe I can submit
for the scholarship for you.
Sure.
If you understand now,
then go try to figure it out.
Yes, sir.
Oh Tookta.
Hello.
I have something to disturb you
for a bit.
I have a business seminar to attend
with the diamond team,
so I would like to leave Tintin with you
for a night.
In return to the rent
I’m supposed to get.
But Pupaa said
Pai can stay without paying rent.
Sure. I’m available anyway.
Thank you so much.
I’m sorry I have to bother you.
Tintin has Chinese and Science homework.
I’ll leave you with that.
I have to go now.
I’ll be late for the ride.
I’ll come pick him up tomorrow.
Ahh, ahh...
Goodbye.
Maybe she’s really in a rush.
Come on Tintin,
let’s go watch television.
Yes, put it in there. You’re so good.
What are you doing?
I’m just teaching Tintin homework.
Tookta had an urgent meeting.
So she asked me for help
in babysitting Tintin.
You don’t need to worry.
I’ll take care of Tintin myself.
I won’t let him disturb you.
Let’s see.
Can you read me the last sentence?
I’m in the house
with dad and mom.
Good job. You’re really good.
Pai, I’m hungry.
Are you hungry?
Pupaa cooks delicious food.
Try asking him to cook for you.
Pupaa, I’m hungry already.
Tintin,
you can go wait on the dining table.
Wow.
You’re awesome.
Tintin, let’s eat.
Let’s have a bite.
Mom.
Dad’s cooking is delicious.
Tintin, why are you calling us that?
I’m practicing my Chinese,
I’m in the house with dad and mom.
It’s not like that, Tintin.
Come on. Let’s eat.
I’ll feed you.
Open wide.
Is it good?
Rock, paper, scissors. The other side.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Let me give you a kiss.
I’ll let you kiss me on this side.
Hey, what are you doing?
Assumption number one, getting jealous
when someone gets close to her.
Keep it down.
I can’t concentrate on my studies.
Why are you pissed?
You’ll be frowning like a bulldog.
Come on, Tintin. Let’s go to bed.
So we don’t disturb him.
Hold on.
What now?
You’re a girl.
How can you let a boy into your room?
He’s a kid.
Come on, you come sleep with me.
Are you going to be alright?
You don’t like kids, do you?
But it’s up to you.
Let me know if you need help.
Come on.
Goodnight. Bye.
Mom, I’m hungry.
You can go wash your face
and brush your teeth.
Then we’ll have some sandwich.
What are we going to play today, mom?
Don’t be too noisy.
I need to concentrate on my work.
Then I’ll take Tintin outside.
So we won’t disturb you.
Yay. Go outside.
How can both of you be going alone?
How are you going to
take him to the toilet?
I’ll take him out.
I’m not in a rush with my work anyway.
I’ll go get dressed then.
(ICONSIAM Shopping Center)
Are you hungry?
Cake.
(Coffee Beans by Dao)
Let’s see. Wow, they all look good.
Hey, look at this. Chocolate cake.
Assumption number two,
your heart beats faster when she’s near.
What cake would you like?
We’ll take this one.
This chocolate cake is the best.
Can I have a bite, mom?
Of course.
Come here, open your mouth.
Is it good?
Mom, let dad have a bite.
He doesn’t like this flavor.
It won’t hurt to try, will it?
Excuse me, can I have another fork?
It’s actually really good.
Assumption number three,
she unbelievably changes you.
I’ll go have a look over there.
Dad, can I get a toy?
This one?
It doesn’t seem to help
with your development at this age.
So that means I can get a different one?
Yay.
(Solar system)
(Our solar system)
(Origin of the universe)
Our greatest scientist.
Enjoying it like a kid, hey?
I remember when I was young,
we were trying to catch it.
Have you played it before?
Of course.
But my friend always beats me to it.
But I think soon
we won’t need a book anymore.
It would be floating
right in front of us for sure.
Did you mean a hologram?
Yes, yes. I saw it in a movie before.
If we get to see those
who we’ve lost once again,
even though
if it’s just a virtual image,
I think it will help a lot for those
who are longing.
I got an idea for my research topic.
I will develop hologram
to become more realistic.
Maybe by including more
computer technologies.
It should be a great research topic.
Thanks to you.
I think we should head back.
Tookta should be coming
to pick up Tintin soon.
Where’s Tintin?
Should we split up?
Tintin, Tintin.
Mom, mom.
Oh, this isn’t mom.
Where are mom and dad?
It’s alright. Don’t cry.
Tintin, are you alright?
Why did you go wandering around?
I was worried.
I’m sorry, dad.
Is this your child?
No.
Dad, where’s mom?
Tintin, Tintin.
Where did you go? I was worried sick.
Are you alright?
Are both of you
taking your kid out for a walk?
No. No, we’re not.
Mom and dad, I want to go home now.
Let’s go home.
Okay, let’s go home.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Me too.
Wait for me.
(BOTTEGA VENETA)
About your senior colleague.
I think she’ll misunderstand.
We just ran out like this.
You should explain to her.
Otherwise, I’ll be the one to blame.
Um.
Even if it was a bit hectic today,
but it was a good day, right?
What’s the difference
between these two images?
Cheese and...
Cheese? You know cheese?
I’ll get it.
What else is there?
Eyes.
Here you go.
What else?
Oh hello, Tookta.
- Hello.
- Come on in.
- Oh Pupaa, both handsome and smart.
- Oh hello, Tookta.
And also loves kids.
He’s so perfect.
Did Tintin cause any trouble?
Oh, not at all.
He was a great kid and very sweet.
Good job, son.
Otherwise,
I wouldn’t dare to disturb them anymore.
Next time,
if you’re busy,
you can drop him off with us.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I’ll get his shoes for you.
Alright.
Tintin.
Tintin, help me carry this.
- I’ll head out now. Thank you.
- It’s alright.
- Goodbye.
Come on, son,
let’s get back to our room.
Open the door.
- Bye.
Hello.
That’s me.
You’re interested in
being a creative worker, right?
Yes.
Alright. Then tomorrow at 10 a.m.
Come in to talk to me.
Bring your portfolio with you.
I’ll send you the details via e-mail.
Sure. See you tomorrow.
Hey, I got a job.
They called for an interview.
So what do you want to eat today?
My treat.
Anything will do.
Assumption number four,
I can’t not be happy when she is.
Come on, let’s do this, Prapai.
If you said
you didn’t graduate from this area,
your ideas are actually really good.
Thank you.
But you didn’t graduate directly
from this area,
you know you have to start
from zero, right?
Learn everything,
and work harder than others.
Because you don’t have experience.
I’m willing to learn.
I’m willing to learn everything.
Currently our department is very busy.
We’ll work together through this.
You’re taking me in already?
Um.
Really? Thank you so much.
Thank you for giving me the opportunity.
I’m so excited.
I’m sorry.
I was a little too excited.
Thank you so much.
If you want to thank someone,
you should thank her.
Because she suggested me to contact you.
Thank you, Faye.
It’s alright. Work hard then.
Yes, I’ll do my best.
Yes.
I should invite Pupaa to celebrate.
But if I ask him,
it won’t be a surprise then.
It’s time to show your cooking skills,
Prapai.
Hello, Professor.
Oh Pupaa, hello.
How is that thing going?
I’ve got a topic already.
But I’m still doing more research.
(Digital Holographic Interferometry)
I didn’t mean the research topic.
I meant your love story.
I’m still in the process
of collecting data.
But I’m not sure of the conclusion yet.
You will have to keep collecting data.
Do you need a hand?
It doesn’t look easy.
I don’t think so.
I don’t think it’s that hard.
I’m talking about the research topic.
It looks very complicated.
Sure, I will try looking for one.
Oh, Meena.
Hello.
You’re here.
I just finished talking with Pupaa.
The kid from yesterday looked cute.
Is he your son?
He’s my neighbor’s son.
She asked to babysit him.
Then why were you with Pai yesterday?
Or do you live together?
Pai also knows Tintin,
so we went together.
And,
I’m not quite familiar
with being with kids.
I think you seem to be well with kids.
I don’t see this side of you much.
It looks cute.
I’ll have to excuse myself.
Professor, goodbye.
Alright.
I’ll just have to wait
until it’s cooked.
Cooking isn’t that difficult.
This way, please.
Please gather around here.
(Special scene)
Hold on, why is this like this?
This uniform is not good.
Pupaa.
- Yes, Tookta?
- Pai quit her job
and she doesn’t have the money
to pay rent.
Are you okay with that?
But I don’t think I’m okay.
She’s going to stay
without paying for anything at all.
Isn’t she taking too much
advantage from us?
I’m okay with it.
I’ll let her stay with me
without paying yet.
If I’m okay,
then I don’t think
there should be any problem.
The problem is I’m losing my income.
Yay. Pai won’t get kicked out anymore.
I have to go now.