♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪For us to be together♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 3=
Wawa.
Great job.
Because I’ve got good support here.
Prapai.
I’ll drop off Wawa myself today.
I want to be a good boyfriend.
I’m sorry, Pai,
I forgot to tell you last night.
Ta and I are dating now.
Then I’ll let you drop her off.
But it seems like it’s going to rain.
Do you want to come with us?
No worries. You guys can go.
I can go by myself.
Do you want me to drop you off
at the front?
I said no.
I have something to do.
I have to go now.
Then I’ll go shower first.
Wait for me here.
Okay.
Let’s go shower.
You and Wawa,
when did you like each other?
Why are you asking?
Are you jealous of me?
I thought you liked Pai all along.
Pai and I have known each other
for too long.
I’ll never have feelings for her.
Maybe people see us being close,
so they just think like that.
I’m going now.
Hey you, what are you doing here?
Are you alright?
No, I’m not.
I’ve been left out again.
Pupaa is also heartbroken from Ta too.
I guess we’re in the same shoes.
You’re probably as sad as I am.
I want to be strong like you too.
It’s good that it’s raining.
So no one can see my tears.
Don’t you need it?
It’s fine.
My hair is wet anyway.
Pupaa.
Wait for me, Pupaa.
We can go together.
You don’t need to act cool.
You.
I’ll hold it for you.
Oh, the rain stopped.
Just like what they say,
there is no rainbow without rain.
If the rainbow was here,
it should be a good sign to start over.
Look at this.
A rainbow.
Isn’t it strange?
Whenever I’m in a bad position,
you’re always here to help me.
It makes me feel what I’ve experienced
wasn’t so bad.
You can keep it.
So you don’t forget
that you can always start over.
Thank you.
Yes, mom?
How are you, Prapai?
This semester is nearly over, right?
I’m doing well.
Just a little busy
with the final project.
What about your job search?
How is it going?
I’ve had interviews
with a couple of places already,
but still waiting for them
to contact back.
Pai, it’s very difficult
to find a job in Bangkok.
If it’s too much,
you can come back home.
Mom, your daughter is a talented girl.
They’ll contact back soon.
Don’t worry.
I’m not worrying.
I know a lot of people.
I can help refer you as an accountant
to a good company.
Mom, are you even listening to me?
Don’t worry. I can get a job on my own.
Up to you.
If it’s too much, just come back home.
Yes, mom.
Take care of yourself.
I miss you.
I miss you too, mom.
See?
There’re so many other guys
for you to like.
Now you’re ending up
like an old vegetable.
I wasn’t stressing about that.
Really?
I think I’m over with Ta.
I really am this time.
I’ve heard you say this
since first year.
You’re graduating soon,
but you’re still saying the same thing.
Good morning, new Prapai. Fighting.
(Start a new day with a smile)
(Ta)
The formula uniform circular motion
should help.
V=2πrf.
[*V=velocity π=pi r=radius f=frequency]
Oh my god.
Amazing.
Why did I not think of this formula?
This is great.
Who are you?
Oh, Pupaa, you’re here already?
Oh, Pupaa.
The person Meena keeps talking about,
right?
Yes, sir.
The person I said whose brain waves
is faster than electricity.
I believe so.
What are you doing now?
I am currently doing some research.
Your ideas are very interesting.
Does this mean that you accept Pupaa
to help with the research?
Let’s say...
Summarize this work for me.
If you do well,
I’ll take you in.
Sure, professor.
I will finish it as soon as I can.
Goodbye.
He’s so motivated.
I love it.
Excuse me, can I sit here?
Oh, this seat is taken.
Alright.
(Maesa, where are you?)
(Pai, I’m still presenting.)
How did you get here?
I soiled your handkerchief.
I’ll go wash it for you.
It’s alright, I’ll wash it myself.
You won’t wash it clean enough.
Alright.
Hey you, who is this girl?
She invited Pupaa too.
I don’t know either.
You put in the wrong number. It’s 23046.
Not 406.
You’re right.
Wow.
Your eyes are like a hawk.
So,
do you think this is correct?
It’s wrong.
How is it possible?
Pupaa is helping her with her work.
Normally he never talks to anyone.
What does this part mean?
I don’t know too.
Pupaa,
can you please teach us this part?
I’m not quite familiar with this topic.
How about this one here?
- A girl is flirting with you.
- History subject...
You should be uncomfortable.
I’m not quite sure too.
You should ask your professor.
I’ll help you.
What are you reading?
I’m reading Prince Rupert’s Drop.
Prince Rupert’s Drop. What’s that?
You really want to know?
It is one of the physical phenomena
of glass.
A molten glass.
When dropped into cold water,
it will become the “glass’ tears”.
Shaped like a tadpole.
It is stronger than other glasses.
Layering it with an object of 8 tonnes
won’t even break it.
But if it’s squeezed or pressed
at the end of the tail by only a bit,
it will shatter completely.
Many things on this earth
that seems strong,
it is truly very fragile.
Wow, I can picture what you’re saying.
What are they talking about?
They don’t even see us.
Let’s go.
That’s it.
Success.
I’m hungry.
Let’s go have lunch.
My treat today.
You helped me a lot.
Never mind.
No, it’s not okay.
You helped me
with completing my assignment.
I’ll pay for you. Don’t be shy.
Normally...
You don’t have to worry.
Let’s go eat.
This place is the best.
I’m sure you’ll love it.
Come on, let’s go.
Come on, quickly.
Come on, pack up.
Get up. Quickly.
Quick, quick.
Come on.
I’ll have papaya salad.
Just like my usual.
And some steamed clams.
Pork spicy salad.
And garlic stir-fried with frog.
How about you? Do you want anything?
I’ll have a grilled fish.
And also a sharing spoon.
That’s all you’re having?
Do you want a hot and sour soup?
It’s their signature dish too.
No, thanks, I don’t like spicy food.
How about this one?
No, I don’t eat intestines.
It can cause hyperlipidemia.
How about sticky rice?
- No.
I don’t eat carbs for dinner.
If that’s all you want,
then it’s up to you.
I’ll also have one bowl
of sticky rice too.
Thank you.
Give me your hand.
The other side too.
Don’t worry, I use food grade.
I’m digging in.
Oh, my lovely papaya salad.
This is delicious.
You’re really
not respecting our traditional dish.
Can I have some?
Wait.
This dipping sauce is delicious.
You’re eating too spicy.
Be careful of your kidneys.
How do you eat that?
That fish looks bland.
But this one I haven’t tried.
I’ll let you try first. Try it.
How is it? Is it good?
What is it?
It’s garlic stir-fried with frog.
Here’s water.
Have some water.
Hello, Wawa.
Do you want to have dinner?
You don’t want it anymore?
Do you want to try this papaya salad?
What a coincidence.
Me and Wawa
are about to have dinner here.
Can I sit with you?
It’s more fun
having dinner with lots of people.
Excuse me, can I order, please?
Thank you.
I’ll have one grilled pork neck.
And one spicy pork salad.
And I’ll have another
set of plates and cutleries, please.
I called you many times
and you wouldn’t pick up.
Now I know you’re busy.
Yes, I’m very busy.
Busy with doing my project.
So I can finally start something new.
Nowadays,
since you’ve had new friends,
you’ve forgotten an old friend like me.
How about the poster
you said you’d do for me?
Is it nearly done?
I’ve already sent it to you ages ago.
If you checked my e-mails,
you would’ve seen it.
I called you many times
and you wouldn’t pick up.
If you answered my calls,
I would’ve known.
Am I right, Pupaa?
Ta.
You didn’t tell me Pai and Pupaa
were coming too.
I didn’t invite them,
I accidentally met them here.
Take a seat. I already ordered for you.
Sit here.
These two suit each other, don’t they?
Have this first.
I don’t like spicy food.
It’s alright.
I’ll have the grilled pork neck.
Oh, Pai.
How was your interview the other day?
Let’s not talk about it.
I applied for the creative position,
but they were looking for an accountant.
You’re graduating from accounting,
shouldn’t you be doing accounting?
Better salary and a more stable job.
It’s difficult to find jobs
in the advertising area.
It’s a lot of work too.
The creative job is better off
as a part-time job for you.
There’s something in this world called
“Prince Rupert’s Drop”.
It’s the melting of glass
into a tadpole shape,
and drop it into cold water,
making it rain made by glass.
Tears.
Yes, tears of glass.
What’s next?
It’s just like work.
We may see some jobs
as being more stable,
but there are also downsides to it.
Exactly.
Pai,
are you interested
in physics nowadays?
Obviously.
Because Pai is close with Pupaa.
She should know a lot about physics
from him.
Yes.
I just
want to know more about other things,
other than food
and something nonsense.
So others can’t look down on me.
Do you want some flowers?
They look beautiful.
Do you want it?
I’ll have one rose.
Yes, sir.
Thank you. Here you go.
Do you have any more roses?
I’m out. There’s only the yellow one.
The magnolia is fine.
Thank you.
Here, for you.
I bought it especially for you,
stop being mad at me.
If you don’t want it, I’ll take it.
I have to go now.
Pay for me.
You said it’s your treat.
Pupaa, wait for me.
I met Prapai at the library.
And I helped her with her work.
So she thanked me with a meal.
What else do you want to know?
I didn’t say anything.
Prapai is a friendly person.
She gets close with people easily.
And she’s not quite careful
with distancing herself from guys.
Anyway,
can you help distance yourself?
But it’s interesting
you didn’t know about it.
About what?
Prapai is allergic to pollen.
Who told you?
You should learn to notice more details.
Ta seems to care about you a lot.
Since I’ve known Ta,
I’ve never seen him take care of anyone
as much as with you.
You know you’re really lucky.
Most of his exes,
I have to take care of them for him.
Wawa, what happened? Why are you crying?
Did I say something wrong? I’m sorry.
Ta doesn’t care about me as you said.
He doesn’t sound like
he wants to talk when he calls me,
he said he’d call back but he never did.
The reason he’s being nice to me today
is because he wants to make you upset.
Calm down.
Stop crying.
Let’s calm down.
Pai, can you help me?
At least make him open up to me.
I know he listens to you.
Can you help me, please, Pai?
I really like Ta.
Please help me.
Alright, I’ll find a chance
to talk to him.
Don’t think too much.
Stop crying. Look at you, all messy now.
That’s enough. Come on, let’s go home.
No more crying.
Come on, smile.
Just start over. You can do it, Prapai.
I’m here to submit my seminar assignment
for Professor Samitree’s class.
Just leave it there.
Thank you.
Hello there.
I’ve read the work you’ve handed in.
You’re fantastic.
You’ve read it already?
But I just submitted it.
Oh, who’s that? Isn’t it Pupaa?
No, I’m not.
Anyway, please pass on the message.
I’m accepting him
into the research team.
He can start next week.
Yes, sure.
(Faye)
Hi, hello.
Is Prapai not there?
Oh, Prapai?
Yes.
Alright,
I’ll let Prapai know to call you back.
Thank you.
This is my number.
What? Hello?
I’m Pupaa.
Oh, Pupaa.
Our phones must have swapped.
Where are you?
I’ll bring your phone over.
OK, I’ll go to you. Wait for me.
Pupaa.
Here you go.
We have the same phone.
Our bags too.
We even met at the library
the other day too. What a coincidence.
Just a statistical possibility.
Oh,
someone called Faye called you.
You should call back.
Oh yeah, someone called you too.
He said
you’re fantastic.
You should go help with the research,
and you can start next week.
That’s all?
Aren’t you happy? You just got a job.
I am happy.
But I already calculated
that I will be getting the job anyway.
I’ve got to go now.
Such a show-off.
So confident.
Hello, Prapai.
Hello, what’s up, Faye?
How are you?
You haven’t contacted me
since you finished your internship.
I’m doing well.
Are you interested in a full-time job?
At the advertising agency?
Yes, exactly.
Ann, the person you did your
accounting intern with,
she left to take care of her child.
You used to do intern here,
so you already know the process here.
I wanted to ask you
to come join the team again.
So we don’t need to find someone new
to start over.
In accounting?
Can I think about it first?
I’ll contact back as soon as possible.
OK, sure.
That’s great. Your project is done.
You’ve got a job offer.
Prapai, you should
take this opportunity.
It’s so difficult
to find a job these days.
But if it’s a job that you don’t like,
you’ll have to stick with it
for a few more years.
I think you should take a break
for a while.
One day you’ll be offered the job
you want to do.
Where did Wawa go?
Yeah, right.
She has a date.
Since she’s been dating with Ta,
she hasn’t met up with friends at all.
New, can you not mention Ta?
I’m so frustrated.
I don’t know why she likes him.
Exactly.
What about that physics guy,
would he be better?
Exactly.
You being at the library with Pupaa
has become a rumor.
If you guys know the truth,
you won’t be teasing me like this.
Hi, mom.
Pai, how are you?
Has any company contacted you yet?
It’s fine if there hasn’t been any.
I met with Orn, one of my seniors,
the other day.
She’s an executive
at a well-known company.
I heard that the company is...
I’ve got an offer already, mom.
You don’t need to worry.
You don’t need to help me find a job.
I’ve got a job in Bangkok already.
And I’m not ready to go back
to work in Chiang Mai too.
Alright, mom? Thank you. Bye, mom.
Just like that?
That’s all I can do.
It’s great. At least you’ve decided.
Let’s cheers. Congratulations to Pai
on getting a job.
Yay, to Pai.
To the life after graduation.
Yay!
(Room for rent)
Welcome.
This is the living room.
We can go have a look inside.
Sure.
This is the bedroom.
Is everything okay?
Yes, okay.
Please come in.
Please come to this room.
You can have a look. The room is big.
Very comfortable.
You can invite your family over.
It’s very comfortable.
They forgot to pack it up with them.
It’s nothing much.
Have a look around.
The closet is also spacious.
I’m sorry. It’s nothing.
It’s my grandmother’s photo.
She forgot it here.
It’s nothing.
Oh, please wait.
I’ll take you to the other room.
Sure.
Hello.
How are you?
Have you got a new place yet?
None of them look good.
I’ve been everywhere already.
Some of the places
don’t even look like their photos.
But the good ones are very expensive.
I’ve seen a place I like.
But
the neighbors are unbelievable.
I just can’t.
I haven’t found any.
Thank you.
I have to go now.
I need some sugar right now. Bye.
Excuse me,
don’t think I’m being rude or anything.
I overheard you’re looking for
a room to rent, right?
Yes, I am.
I’m renting out a room.
You’re really lucky to have met me.
Because my client just canceled on me.
And the condominium is right next door.
You can have a look and decide later.
This one. This exact room.
Wow.
This room is spacious.
Do you like it?
You can have a walk around.
Wow, the view is great here.
You see, it’s lovely, isn’t it?
Where is the bedroom?
The bedroom is here. Come have a look.
Here it is.
Isn’t the bedroom big?
It’s very spacious.
Do you like it?
This place is really nice.
Isn’t it?
What about the neighbors?
I’m the one who lives next door.
You don’t need to worry.
The owner bought it ages ago,
it’s been a while
since they’ve been here.
This room is just everything.
But there’re two bedrooms,
and I’m living alone.
It may be too big for me.
Such a pity.
Well,
how about this?
I’ve never been so generous with anyone
to rent out only one room.
But I feel I have a connection with you.
So I’ll let you rent out one room.
Really?
Yes.
But you have to pay
for the first month’s rent first.
I’m already helping you a lot.
I don’t know what to do
if you’re not taking the offer.
And now I have to go pick up my child
from school.
Alright, I’ll pay for it now.
I’m so happy.
We’re going to be neighbors.
Me too.
I’ve set your work
and project schedule for you already.
And for the daily tasks,
I’ll call to remind you again.
Yeah, thank you.
Are you free this week?
Can you help me move?
Why are you moving?
Pai already moved out.
So I think I’m moving back home.
She moved out so fast,
maybe she found the place she likes.
I don’t know. I heard she got a job.
So she decided to move closer to work.
So now I have to travel more.
So where does she work?
Why don’t you ask her yourself?
Then I’ll go help you move this week.
Umm.
Why are you all packed up?
I want to concentrate on my research.
So I’m planning to move
to my condominium.
This is broken.
Why are you taking it with you?
It’s in the process of getting fixed.
Fixing?
Umm.
More of keeping it for the memories.
Or you’re afraid of missing me?
Don’t you worry, Pupaa.
No matter where you are,
I will follow you everywhere.
Yeah, right.
Don’t challenge me.
Do you need any help?
I’m all done. It’s fine.
I was just asking.
The owner of this room left it for rent,
and hasn’t been here for ages.
You can do whatever you want.
So cute.
And this...
little piggy.
But there’s one room you must not open.
You must not open.
Hello.
How is it going?
Your new place, new life.
It’s really great.
It’s like living a new life for real.
I feel so lucky to have met Tookta.
Really? I’ll go visit you sometime.
Stop right there,
you didn’t even help me with packing.
Because I had a job interview.
Who knows.
Whatever. Just be there alone then.
Hey, whose voice was that?
What voice? There’s nothing here.
Or the place is...
Nonsense.
There’s no ghost. Nonsense.
I’ve got to get up early tomorrow.
I’ll talk to you later.
It’s my first day too.
Got to go now.
Or Tookta offered a low rent
because...
In horror films,
if I left the room now,
I wouldn’t make it back.
(Special scene)
I’ll have one rose, please.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Do you have any more roses?
I’m out. There’s only the yellow one.
The magnolia is fine.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I bought it especially for you,
stop being mad at me.
If you don’t want it, I’ll take it.
I have to go now.
Pay for me.
Oh, you’re going already?
Pupaa, wait for me.