♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 4=
May all beings be free from hatred.
May I pray for all beings
to not interfere with the human world.
Please.
I’ll make merit for you.
Help!
Hey.
You stalker.
What is going on, Pai?
What time is it now?
Why are you knocking so late?
My child will wake up.
I need an explanation.
This guy came into my room
and he said he’s the owner of the room.
What does this mean?
Pupaa.
How did you get here?
This is my room. Why can I not be here?
How can this be your room?
I rented the room from her.
Does my family know
you’re renting out this place?
Who is it, mom?
Alright, everyone,
let’s calm down first.
I will take care of this.
Your mom won’t answer.
She should be overseas as usual.
Your mom said
no one was living in this room,
so she told me
to rent it out.
And normally your mom
trusts me to sort everything out.
And she didn’t say you would move in.
Prapai already paid.
Then you can give back her rent.
I’ll tell my mom.
No, you can’t do that.
I paid already. I moved everything in.
Exactly. Payment is made. No returns.
But this is my room.
Why do you have to be mean to girls?
You’re so cute, little boy.
Did your mom teach you this?
Nope, my teacher taught me.
My teacher said,
guys have to help girls.
Right? It’s unfair for the girl, right?
Yes. Please let her stay. Please.
Well, we are all Thai.
We should help each other,
and be kind, right?
And this room has two bedrooms.
Wait.
You’re going to let me
live with this guy?
Otherwise go stay somewhere else.
Well, he doesn’t like girls anyway.
Nothing’s going to happen.
Better than having no place to stay.
Alright.
I don’t have to move anymore. Yay.
- Yay.
But only for this month, alright?
We’ll talk about it
once my mom gets back.
Hey.
Hey you.
Why are you in here? I’m on the toilet.
How did you get in here?
I was here first.
Then why didn’t you lock the door?
Normally I live with guys.
Why would I lock the door?
Are you going to stay any longer?
Get out first.
You get out. I’m going to shower.
Hey, what is this?
If you’re going to stay here,
there need to be some rules.
Rules of staying together.
Number one, no personal belongings
in the living area.
The common area must always be tidy.
Yes. So you have to take those stuff
into your room.
How about your stuff?
Why is it out here?
This is my room. I set the rules.
If you can’t follow, then leave.
Number two, control and limit
the number of visitors.
Hey.
Don’t you ever have friends?
Have you never invited any friends over?
If you want to stay,
then follow the rules.
I’ve thought about it already.
How about Ta? Is he an outsider?
According to my
anthropological research,
Ta is considered a close friend
but still an outsider.
How about your parents?
Who’s considered an insider?
In this case,
it’s only me and you. Just us two.
Stupid rules. So bossy.
What did you say?
Nothing. I’m in a hurry to work.
We’ll talk later.
I’ve got to get to work early today.
Don’t you remove the plastic bag first?
Did you know
if you put it in the microwave,
the plastic bag will melt
and stick to your food?
Why? Is it one of the rules as well?
What are you looking at?
You want some, don’t you?
Do you want some? I’ve got many.
No, thanks. I don’t eat food like this.
Why so? This is my favorite.
How can you say that?
Full of cholesterols and carcinogens.
I think you should take care of yourself
and your health more.
The plastic bag that you use
also contains carcinogens.
If you put it in the microwave...
Hello.
You’re Prapai, right?
Yes, I am.
My name is Pla.
Come on, follow me.
Yes.
This is the creative department.
Creating quality work for the company.
Including online media,
posters, print ads, etc.
This is the accounting department.
And this is your table.
I’ve let Cartoon prepare the essentials
for you already.
But if you need anything else, tell me.
I’ll get it sorted for you.
Sure. Thank you.
No problem.
Hi, I’m Cartoon.
I’m from the information department.
I’m Prapai. You can call me Pai.
You’re replacing our old accountant,
Ann, right?
Yeah.
It’s going to be tough
if you’re not strong enough.
Ann only asked for a maternal leave,
but she quitted after that.
This is what Ann hasn’t finished.
You can start with finishing these off.
Okay.
(Financial statement)
Hi, hello.
Yes, sure. I’ll get it done for you.
Please excuse me for a minute.
Yes, it will be done soon.
I’ll handle it for you.
Thank you.
Hello?
Pai.
Yes?
It’s the reimbursement
of the creative department.
Yes.
These are my files,
can you type it up for me?
Pai, can you send these over
to the finance department?
Can I have it done today by noon?
Drop a bit more. A tiny bit more.
Amazing.
Oh, Pupaa, you’re on time.
Do you want some?
It’s coffee.
No, thank you, Professor,
I’ve already had breakfast.
You’re going to regret this.
Hello, Professor.
Oh, Meena, you’re here.
Take Pupaa to see our laboratory.
Show him where to find the equipment
and where to return them.
Okay, sure, sir.
Okay.
Are you sure you don’t want some?
No, thanks.
First of all, let’s go put on our gown.
I knew we’d meet again.
I have to thank you for introducing me
to Professor.
No problem.
I’m also happy Professor has you
to help out with the research.
So we can spend some time together.
I mean,
I’ve always wanted to work with someone
as talented as you, Pupaa.
Let’s go and have a look
at the laboratory over there.
Please take over this for me.
Sure.
(Ta)
(Missed call)
If you’re going to start over,
you have to be strong.
Prapai.
(Prapai: What do you want?)
(Ta: Where are you?)
(Prapai: I’m working. What do you want?)
Prapai.
If I’m not dating Wawa anymore,
will you be my girlfriend?
(What is wrong with you?)
(You’re a grown man.
Be responsible for your actions.)
Useless.
The budget you did was not usable.
There’re omissions in the texts.
Also miscalculations.
You’re so careless.
I’m sorry. I will...
I want the rest of the work done
within this week.
Pai.
How’s your first day
of being a full-time employee?
Hi there, Faye.
A little bit tough.
You’ll do fine.
So fit and talented.
And why aren’t you going home yet?
Not yet, I have to finish these first.
I’m leaving now. Fighting.
Sure, fighting.
Goodbye.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Rule number three.
You must put away your shoes
once you enter the room.
Are you satisfied now, Mr. Homeowner?
Not yet.
You must read all the rules
and follow them strictly.
Number four.
You cannot enter the other person’s room
without permission.
Don’t worry.
I won’t go into your room.
You can’t come into mine too.
Next one.
Number five
Chores are to be done
according to the schedule.
Louder.
Number five.
Chores are to be done
according to the schedule.
Number six.
Time spend in common area
should not exceed 30 minutes.
Hey, I’m a girl.
I need some beauty time.
Isn’t it a little too much?
Then you can use it between
10 p.m. and 6 a.m.
It’s my resting time.
And do not disturb me.
Sure.
Then after 10 p.m.,
I’ll take all the time to shower.
Number seven.
Only put things in the designated areas
in the fridge.
The top shelf is yours,
and the bottom shelf is mine.
And whoever is using the freezing
can put their name on it.
And be responsible for your own laundry.
That’s all the rules I can think of now.
If I can think of any more,
I will add it on.
But if you don’t follow the rules
for more than three times,
you must leave.
Anything else?
Yes.
That area there,
I will use it to leave a message
when I don’t see you.
I’ll just leave a note on there.
You too.
If you have anything,
you can leave a note.
Yes, Mr. Homeowner.
Hey, why did you turn it off?
I was watching it.
Others are trying to sleep.
You cannot make loud noises like this.
It’s not one of the rules.
(Number eight)
(No loud noises
during watching the television)
Can I continue watching now?
Prapai.
The board is only for
useful information.
It is not for doodling.
Please understand.
This is the first warning. Erase it.
Erase it.
This is the first warning.
Prapai.
Prapai!
Oh, what is up with you?
What is wrong with you?
What did you do with the fridge?
Oh, fermented fish sauce. Why?
I put it in the correct shelf already.
But the smell of your food
is all on my food.
What do you want me to do?
Clear everything out.
Or else we can’t live together.
I know.
Hi there.
Hello, how are you doing?
I never thought life after graduation
would be this cruel to me.
Both my new place,
and my new work place.
It’s alright.
At least you have a job
and you’re not unemployed.
Look at me,
I’ve applied to so many places,
none of them have contacted me.
I’m so fed up.
Do you want to go shopping this evening?
I can’t go. I haven’t finished my work.
I don’t even know if Pla will give me
any more work or not.
I don’t even want to think about it.
Hey.
I have to go now.
If you’ve finished your lunch,
go get back to work.
Don’t sit here, hanging around.
That’s why your work is not done.
Yes.
So have you finished the first quarter?
Not yet.
Finish it before you leave.
Put it on my desk.
I will come and check it tomorrow.
You want it today?
If you’re not wasting time
talking on the phone,
you would finish it on time.
Noted.
I’m all done, Professor.
Let me see.
You’re very neat. This is great.
Good job.
Hang on a minute, I’ve got a call.
Hello?
Yes, it’s me.
Yes, our training event is this week.
What? You can’t come?
What a pity.
There will be many great professors
from around the world.
Alright, never mind.
I’ll find a replacement.
Who should I ask?
Are you free this week?
Yes, I am.
You know me.
How can it be only you two?
Pupaa is in the lead now I see.
Then both of you come.
So Pupaa can also gain some experience
from big events like this.
Because I believe,
in the future,
it could be you on stage
like other experts.
Finally I’m done.
It’s a late night again.
It’s your turn to clean the toilet.
It’s 10 o’clock already.
Can I do it tomorrow?
I’m really tired.
Rules are to be followed.
If you’re not going to follow, then...
OK, OK.
I’ll clean it now, Mr. Homeowner.
This stupid guy, why are you so mean?
Prapai, you can stop now. Go to bed.
Prapai.
I know. I’ll go change later.
Are you crazy?
Go to bed.
Go.
I told you to go to bed.
Hey, that’s my room.
Where are you going?
Hey, why are you on my bed?
Get down now.
Come here.
You’re sleepwalking?
Prapai.
I’m so happy tonight.
Thank you very much.
Where are you going?
Going to work of course.
I’m already late.
But today is Saturday.
Oh, today is Saturday?
Really? I thought it was Monday.
That’s good. I don’t want to go to work.
Oh, so comfortable.
But my body aches so bad.
Maybe I’ve been sitting down
for too long.
Why do you look so tired?
Did you sleep last night?
Let’s say I had a bad dream.
A nightmare?
But I had a really good dream
last night.
Last night I dreamt
that I went to a ball.
And you know, the event was gorgeous.
It was a huge event.
The ballroom was like a palace.
And everything was set so perfectly.
I was dancing in the ballroom.
How about this,
whenever it’s your turn for chores
and you’ve finished work late,
let me know.
So I can change it.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
I’m doing it for myself.
I can’t do this every night either.
(Ta)
What’s up, Ta?
Can I go over to your place?
Yeah, why not?
But I have to go somewhere else first.
Maybe next time.
See you later, Ta.
Alright.
Thank you.
What for?
For not letting Ta come over
when I’m here.
Who said I’m helping you?
I’m about to go outside.
It’s your turn to clean the living room.
Finish it before I get back.
Yes, sir. I know.
(Chores schedule)
(Rule number four)
(You cannot enter other’s room
without permission.)
You’re back?
You came into my room?
What does rule number four say?
I just came in to clean.
What about my stuff here,
where has it gone?
Did you throw it away?
I told you how important it was to me.
What kind of person do you think I am?
I felt bad after I saw it.
So I fixed it for you.
How is it? Is it better?
You must really love this, don’t you?
I’m really sorry.
This is considered the second time
you’ve done wrong.
If there’s a next one,
prepare to pack your bags.
Ta.
You have a meeting
with your consultant on Monday.
I saw you didn’t reply to my text.
I thought you might forget.
I can remember.
It feels like we haven’t seen
each other much recently.
I’m trying to finish my final project.
I saw you were looking for references
for your final project.
So I took a look in the library.
I think these two can help. Have a look.
Thank you.
I’ll take it back for you when it’s due.
So I’ll go now.
(Going to a training event.
Will be home late.)
It’s finally time for freedom, Prapai.
Welcome, brothers and sisters.
Hello everyone.
Thank you for your support.
I won’t disappoint you.
I thought I was early.
You’re earlier than me.
Why are you so diligent?
I want to help Professor set up.
- Hello, Professor.
- Hello there.
Everything should be ready.
You can help just during the day.
Because
the person who’s coming this afternoon
will come take over soon.
Alright.
OK, OK.
Bring up the first slide.
We’ve finished earlier than I thought.
Do you want to go grab some lunch?
No, thanks.
I think I’ll be heading straight back.
Hey, have you got a dress for the party?
Not yet.
It’s nearly the graduation party.
Have you prepared yourself?
Us science students
aren’t really interested in it.
But girls are really
looking forward to it.
I don’t even know who to go with.
Can you go with me?
I don’t want to go alone.
It feels strange.
I think you should ask someone else.
Why?
I’m going with someone else.
Was I too slow?
Thank you. If you could excuse me.
Oh Pupaa. You’re back already?
Why are you back early?
Come, come sit here first.
Come sit down.
Do you want some snack?
I was planning to clean up everything,
but why are you back early?
Are you saying it’s my fault?
You’ve violated the rules
three times already.
No.
I’m sorry.
I will clean everything up now.
Please don’t kick me out.
Rules are rules.
Pupaa.
Don’t you feel any pity
for a small girl like me?
Look, if you kick me out now,
I don’t know where to go.
Do you want to see me
sleeping on the streets?
Please. Pretty please.
I have an offer for you.
To fix this.
What is it? You can tell me.
I’ll do everything for you.
You have to be my partner for a day.
(Special scene)
Sleep.