♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪For us to be together♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that
what I thought was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 2=
You two can come too.
- Sure.
- No, thanks.
It’s a graduation trip for the club.
The juniors set it up for us.
It’s going to be only us.
It’s just for fun. Come with us.
Come on.
We’re going to the beach.
Yeah, it’s going to be fun.
If the girls are going,
you’re all welcome.
Great job.
Come on, Pai.
Let’s go have fun together.
- Come with us.
- Please, come on.
So Pai is...
Shouldn’t go.
This is our club’s activity.
Those who are not involved shouldn’t go.
You guys should go. I’m going home.
- Wait, Pai.
- Pai.
I’ll go talk her back. Pai.
You know what you just said?
I’m just saying the truth.
(Ta)
Pai,
so are you going to the trip Ta invited?
No, I want to stay
and finish my final project.
Come on, let’s go. It’s only a few days.
We won’t have any occasions like this
when we graduate.
Please, let’s go, please.
Hello, Ta, what’s up?
Ta wants to speak to you.
Hello?
If you’re calling about the trip...
No.
Because my roommate
is still bugging me about it.
Pai, what is wrong with you?
I’m not upset.
If you’re not upset,
then you have to come with us.
Otherwise, I’ll say you’re upset.
Please go.
Please.
If you’re not going,
then who am I going to sleep with?
Pai.
Oh my, alright, alright.
Yes!
Here, take it back.
You’re the best.
That’s enough. Go back to your bed.
What are we waiting for?
Well,
Pai and Wawa.
It’s late already.
I don’t think they’re coming.
Come on, let’s just go.
We need to catch up with the others.
Come on, just wait a bit more.
I’m calling them now.
Just wait a minute.
Pai, quickly.
I know. I’m rushing too.
(Elevator is broken)
Why does it have to be broken now?
The elevator is broken.
Can I not go anymore?
No. Hurry up.
Come on,
we’ve waited for 10 seconds already.
Wait, just 10 seconds?
Oh my, just bossing me around.
Ten seconds is not called waiting,
Pupaa.
Come on, start the car.
Yes, sir.
You can’t even wait.
You’re so impatient.
Ta, it’s another 10 seconds late.
Let’s go to the beach.
Is that Ta’s car?
Hey, where is he going?
Wait, wait. Wait for us.
Be careful.
Hey.
- Stop the car.
- Hey.
- Pai.
- Ta, what’s wrong?
- Are you hurt?
- I’m okay.
Prapai.
Oh, is my car alright?
Is there a scratch?
Why are you laughing?
You’re the one who invited us
and didn’t even wait.
Do you really want us to go?
This guy.
He said not to wait.
You were late,
so I thought you’re not going anymore.
Look at all your wounds.
Why aren’t you staying in to rest?
I didn’t want to go anyway.
I’m going to go back now.
- Wait, we’re just joking.
- Pai, come on, let’s go.
Alright, let’s go.
Let’s go.
Come on, I’ll help you.
All done.
Why are both of your bags the same?
- Traded in after shopping.
Come on, let’s go.
Can Pai sit at the front?
She gets car sick.
But normally she’s fine.
It’s fine. Let Wawa sit at the front.
I’ll sit at the back.
So what? What if you get car sick
and vomit in my car?
I don’t get car sick anymore. I’m fine.
I’ve known you for how many years?
It’s not easy to stop getting car sick.
Are you crazy? Come on, let’s go.
Just sit at the front.
If you don’t hurry up,
Pupaa will start complaining again.
Come on.
Just both sit at the back.
Stop fighting.
We’re already 22 minutes late.
Why are you so jealous?
You think people won’t notice?
Oh man.
Are you alright, Pai?
I’m great.
Look at you saying you’re fine.
I told you Prapai gets car sick.
You didn’t believe me.
Lovely smell.
What are you doing?
Pressing your Hegu point.
Just like traditional Chinese medicine.
Helps with car sickness.
What point is it?
Hegu point.
Oh, Hegu point?
Teach me too.
Give me your hand.
I’ll press it for you.
Professor Ta.
It really does feel good.
You’re feeling good,
but others are about to die.
Come on, let’s go. Hurry up.
We’ll all be late because of me.
Hold on.
You can sit at the front.
(Coastal road)
Wawa.
Come on, I’ll help you.
Here you go.
Here you go, Wawa.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Here’s another one.
The last one.
But not the least.
This one is the last one.
I’ll go check on the keys for you.
I’ll come too.
Let’s go.
See you.
I’m hungry.
Thank you.
Why are you so cold?
Let me lie down.
There’s only one bed.
Whoever sleeps first, loses.
Oh man, you’re not playing with me.
Oh, Mr. Pupaa.
We’re only here for a night.
Why checking the entire room?
I just want everything to be in place.
Up to you.
I’m going to go for a walk.
I was thinking of going to check out
the party area for tonight.
Do you want to come?
No, thanks.
The sun is too bright.
I don’t want to get skin cancer.
OK, OK, I’ll go ask Pai.
Wait a minute, Ta.
Did you change your mind?
Wear your sunglasses,
you’ll get cataract.
Sure, see you.
Yeah, what do you want?
Do you want to go for a walk?
Can I go?
Can I go too?
Yeah, sure, it’ll be fun going together.
I’ll go get my stuff.
Let’s go.
Quickly, let’s go to the beach.
Why are both of your bags the same?
Ta, look at that.
It’s beautiful.
- There’s more over there.
- Let’s go see.
Are you alright?
Ta, come help me. I can’t walk anymore.
You can sit down and take a rest.
You can catch up when you’re ready.
Come on.
Ta, if you turn around and just call me
I wouldn’t give up.
Prapai.
Look at that.
Why are there buildings there?
It’s called a mirage.
This phenomenon is caused by
the refraction of light.
Because the temperature of the air layer
that light travels through is different,
so it causes a reflection.
A delusion.
Something like that.
But in the end, the delusion disappears.
Because it’s not real.
Just like when we have our own thoughts,
thinking that one day he will see me.
If you know it’s not real,
then you should accept the truth,
and be with what’s real.
I guess so.
So, what are you doing here?
Your bag was swapped with mine.
I don’t think so. Mine has a key chain.
It must be.
Because...
I saw...
a bra in the bag.
Really?
Let’s go change it now. Quick.
Give me a pose and smile.
Great.
One more photo.
Another one.
Move the scarf.
1, 2, 3.
I thought you’re a real model.
Ta, don’t look at me like that.
Your girlfriend will be jealous.
Who’s going to be jealous of me?
I don’t have a girlfriend.
What about Prapai?
Apart from... that...
You didn’t see anything else, right?
What a relief.
You didn’t take anything, right?
There’s one thing.
See, you’re a pervert.
Give me back my bikini.
I meant this.
The kitty?
Yes, the kitty.
So where is it?
Here it is, I found it.
Ken, Tum.
Come on.
Ta is here, I’m here.
Pai, can I talk to you?
What’s up?
What do you want to talk about?
I will be honest with you,
only this one time.
I like Ta.
I want to ask him out.
And I know you like him, too.
Shall we let Ta choose
who he wants to be with?
If Ta chooses you,
I will give up everything.
You can shout or scold at me,
but I really want to fight for
this love.
Why are you smiling?
Smiling for your dedication.
Me and Ta, we used to...
Never mind. You don’t need to worry.
From now on,
Me and Ta are just friends.
Okay?
Really? Are you serious?
Then you must help me with Ta.
But you need to be careful,
I don’t want to see you upset.
Why?
You’ll know
when you’ve known him for a while.
Come on, let’s go.
They’re waiting for us.
And this is the climax of the trip
that everyone’s been for waiting.
Waiting for.
- Which is our beach activity!
- Beach activity!
This is the two-legged race game.
But we’re not just going to let you
waste your energy for free.
Yes, exactly.
We have a special prize for you too.
Which is a bouquet of blue roses.
It’s a rare item.
Let me tell you,
if any guy gives this to a girl,
she’ll take it for sure.
Take what?
Take your heart.
The second prize? A lipstick.
This color is limited edition.
Like, winning the prize, putting it on,
and getting a kiss?
Whoever gets the first and second prize
can take it.
I want the third prize.
Why?
Because it’s a Gold series basketball.
Then what are we waiting for?
Come get the rope and pair up.
Ta, can you be my partner?
Yeah, of course.
Let’s go get the rope.
Ken, Tum, can I have a rope?
Done.
Everyone, we’re going to start now.
One, two.
Two.
We need to run at the same pace
to get through this.
Don’t run alone. Let’s count together.
One, two.
- One, two, one.
Pupaa and Prapai are in the lead.
They’re leading now.
- One, two.
Can Ta and Wawa catch up?
Pupaa and Prapai are winning this.
Ouch.
Oh, they fell.
Are you alright?
I’m fine. It’s just a small wound.
Oh my.
Ta and Wawa have beaten them.
Hey, they’ve beaten us already.
Never mind.
How can you say that?
I’m not getting hurt for nothing.
Come on let’s go.
Step on my foot.
- Let’s go. One.
- One, two.
What’s happening?
Can they catch up?
- Two.
- One.
They’re catching up. Hurry up.
- They’re catching up.
- Can they catch up?
Hurry up.
We can’t catch up anymore.
- Can they catch up?
- Ta and Wawa.
- We’re nearly there.
- Pupaa and Prapai.
- Ta and Wawa.
- Nearly there.
- Pupaa and Prapai.
- We’re nearly there.
- Ta and Wawa.
Just a bit further.
Ta and Wawa are at the finish line.
- They won.
- Just by a tiny bit.
- Good job.
- Our team is great.
What a pity. We were so close.
Come on, I’ll get your wound treated.
Get on my back.
I can walk. You don’t have to carry me.
Just come on.
Come on.
All done.
Thank you.
I’ll be back. Just wait for me here.
Oh my god, did we win this prize?
That’s great.
Being second isn’t that bad.
We got a lipstick.
Why do girls like lipsticks?
Because lipsticks are like
a girl’s secret weapon.
It’s like when guys play games
and they have secret weapons.
Because lipsticks are like
a girl’s weapon.
You see?
Does it look like a commercial?
Does it?
Hey.
I’m trying to be beautiful, not funny.
Sorry.
Isn’t it beautiful?
It looks like the old one.
Really?
Isn’t it sad? We’re graduating soon.
We’ll all have to go our separate ways.
Wait a minute, I’ll be back.
No matter what happens,
our friendship will never fade away.
Let me hug you.
After all this,
I don’t have you as a roommate anymore,
I would probably be lonely.
If I didn’t have you,
my life would be so quiet.
Do you want to take me with you?
No, thanks.
But thank you for the great friendship
throughout the past four years.
No, it’s forever.
Come on.
I haven’t eaten.
Try it.
How is it?
Is it tasty?
Some grilled shrimp served hot.
Wow, it looks great.
Of course, I cooked it.
I’ll go get the dipping sauce.
Wait a minute.
I’ll peel them for you.
- It’s delicious, right?
- Ken.
Yeah?
Can you give this to Ta and Wawa for me?
There’re three bowls.
You can take one of them. I’m off now.
This is so fresh.
Here you go, Wawa.
Prapai told me to give you this.
Where did Pai go?
I don’t know. I saw her go off that way.
Can I have one?
You’re also waiting for the
meteor shower?
It was announced that there will be
a meteor shower phenomenon.
But this time
won’t be as much as last year.
But being in the countryside like this,
it should be easier to see
than in the city.
Because there’re no other lights around.
And if we put our hands like this,
we can see it more easily.
You normally stay quiet,
but you’re actually quite talkative.
Like this?
Like this.
Oh, look, a meteor. Make a wish.
A meteor is just a falling meteorite.
Shh, make a wish. Look.
You normally have a straight face.
You look better when you smile.
What are you looking at?
At Chiang Mai,
there’re way more stars.
If you like watching the meteor,
you should go visit sometime.
I used to live in Chiang Mai
when I was young.
Really?
We might have met before, right?
Just like the
six degrees of separation theory?
How many people do you follow
on social media?
Maybe about 400 people?
And how many of them
do you actually know?
Maybe about 100.
Mathematically explaining,
if everyone knew on average 100 people,
meaning they will know about six layers
of 100 people.
This is already more than
the population of the world.
This means I’ll know the prime minister,
right?
Am I right? Yeah?
It’s only a theory.
There’s always a possibility.
But maybe not that much
of a coincidence.
I thought you said
you went to get the dipping sauce.
Is your dipping sauce here?
Or,
if you wanted to meet up with a guy,
you can tell me.
Ta, don’t start a fight on me.
We just met in coincidence.
We don’t need to explain.
We were talking.
What does it have to do with him?
But,
because I’m Pupaa’s best friend,
I’ll tell you now, you and Pupaa
will never understand each other.
Because you know nothing about science.
Because all you do
is look for good food
or just something nonsense.
Ta, that’s too much. Say sorry to me.
Why do I have to say sorry?
Did I say something wrong?
You’ve been my friend for so long.
If you think I’m like this,
then it’s up to you.
Ta.
Isn’t Prapai your best friend?
Friends don’t do this to each other.
Hello?
Mr. Pupaa,
from the department of physics right?
I apologize for calling so late.
It’s alright.
I happen to look through your research.
Do you want to get interviewed
as my assistance?
Yes, I am interested.
How about tomorrow at 10 a.m.?
Sure, sir.
Great. See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Pai. Pai.
Let go.
Pai, where are you going?
I’m going to leave. Stop following me.
Pai.
Wait a minute, can we talk?
Ta, I’m going to leave now.
I’ve got an interview tomorrow.
Really?
What a coincidence.
It’s not a coincidence.
I’m following Pupaa back. Are you happy?
Then please take care of Prapai.
Then you take care of Wawa, too.
Let’s go.
You can talk if you want.
I won’t get annoyed.
It’s kind of good that we left early.
So I can go back and finish my project.
Did you know? I actually hate math.
But I’m here doing accounting.
Isn’t it funny?
Actually,
I wanted to study advertising.
But my father
was afraid it would be difficult
to find a job.
We fought all the time.
And in the end, I gave up.
When I was in middle school,
I deliberately chose language arts.
And you studied together with Ta, right?
Umm.
It was me, Ta and Kwang.
Just the three of us.
But
one day, Ta and Kwang started dating.
So I became useless.
Why do I have to like someone like this?
You’re so stupid, Prapai.
Ouch, who hit my head?
I...
How are you going to
take responsibility for this?
I don’t even know if my head has a lump,
Give me your hand and feel it.
Feel my head, is there a lump?
Here, over here.
Pupaa, is this your type?
It’s okay, don’t be shy.
I have to go now.
- Take care of yourself.
- Where are you going?
Let me come too.
Let me come too, wait for me.
Wait for me. Stop. Wait for me too.
I really like your research direction.
You have a very open mind.
But there are a lot of people
who are interested in the position.
Yes, anyone would love to do
a great research.
Well, this research
still has a long way to go.
If we received some financial support,
we can develop to a larger scale.
Until then,
we shall have a lot more to do.
But I think
I won’t be working with you anymore.
I don’t know any investors.
What are you saying?
Those who can come here to study.
I believe their family status
is well-off.
I hope you find your investor soon.
I should get going.
Excuse me,
are you Pupaa?
I overheard you’re looking for a job.
I know a professor,
he has a similar personality as you.
Are you interested?
Sure.
Can I have your contact number?
I’ll send you
the professor’s contact details.
You can try and call him.
Tell him Meena introduced you to him.
Thank you.
You don’t need to thank me.
You can buy me a meal
if you pass the interview.
I’ll excuse myself.
The final settlement is 250,000, right?
No, it’s 280,000.
Really?
I think you miscalculated.
I don’t think so.
So how was your beach trip?
It was okay.
Why so? You went with Ta, didn’t you?
No.
What happened? Did you guys fight again?
Can you stop talking about him?
From now on,
Ta will be just a regular friend.
He’s just as unimportant
as everyone else.
So then stop talking about him.
Okay, I won’t ask anymore.
Pai, let’s go
to the basketball club tomorrow.
Nope. Why not invite Maesa?
I don’t want to go.
I don’t like basketball players.
Pai, let’s go.
Everyone goes to watch
the basketball players before the match.
If you don’t go,
I will keep disturbing you
so you can’t work.
- Until you say yes.
- Alright.
- Are you going?
- Okay.
I know, I know, I’ll go.
Yay, you’re the best.
All happy now I see.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I’m just looking at your screen.
Keep researching.
How about this one?
Pai, come on.
Calm down.
Slow down or you’ll fall.
We’ll be late.
You missed again.
Wow, so cool.
I wouldn’t have guessed you being gay.
Ta, concentrate.
Sure, I’ve got the best support.
You got the three points.
They were frightened.
Great job.
It’s normal.
Wawa.
(Special scene)
- Come on.
- Step on my foot.
We’re nearly there. You can do it, Wawa.
The second prize will be the lipstick.
Quickly, they’re catching up.
- I can’t catch up.
- Come on.
Just a bit more.
What a pity. We were close.
It was so intimidating.
They won by just a tiny bit.
There’s no pity.
I came in second as planned.
What are you saying?