♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 5=
Don’t say I gossip too much, Prapai.
He’s the best of the science faculty.
How did you guys know each other?
Are you secretly dating him?
That’s nonsense.
Pupaa is a friend of Ta.
They’re in the basketball club together.
We’ve met only a couple of times.
Only a couple of times, but he asked you
to the graduation party?
Isn’t it strange?
What did you say?
The faculty’s graduation party.
I don’t really want to go.
But I told a friend
that I have a date already.
So I...
You’re just using me as a shield, right?
Normally I’m only with guy friends.
So I don’t have any girl friends.
So if I agree to go,
you won’t kick me out, right?
Umm.
Alright, it’s a deal.
But clean up all this mess first.
Yes, sir. I will clean up everything.
But Pupaa has never had
rumors with any girls.
Of course, he likes guys.
You’re going to be
the focus of the audience.
I think this one. This one here.
And this shoe too. Here.
I think this dress and this shoe.
Perfect.
Isn’t it too high?
This is what you should wear.
So you suit your handsome date.
Exactly.
Balance is important.
What did you say?
When wearing high heels,
the body’s center of gravity
will shift forward a bit,
making it difficult to balance.
So,
you must make your center of gravity
be closest to your center.
Easy for you to say. Do you want to try?
I can’t wear your size.
You actually want to wear it, don’t you?
One more thing,
wearing heels this high,
the area to hold your weight
is going to be less.
The front of your heels will have to
carry up 40% of your original weight.
Wearing it throughout the entire night
is going to make your muscles sore.
Can you stop talking so much?
Because I’m going to a party,
I just want to be pretty.
Wait and see how I look tomorrow.
I will shock you with my beauty.
Pai.
Oh, why are you leaving early today?
I’m in a hurry
to go to a graduation party.
Who are you going with?
With a friend.
He asked me to go with him.
Oh.
We’re all grown.
You’re really calling him a friend?
Don’t mess up your work though.
Faye, it’s not like that.
Alright, alright.
It’s your personal life.
I won’t be nosy.
Let’s talk about work.
I know you wanted to do something
related to advertising, right?
I wanted to show you this.
What do you think of this idea?
(Welcome to Bangkok)
I think I’ve seen something similar
from other countries.
In this case, how do you think
we should change this,
so they don’t think we copied from them?
What should we do?
Travelling in Bangkok?
What about a campaign on
Living Life in Bangkok?
“Living Life” in Bangkok?
Sounds interesting.
What next?
I haven’t thought about it yet.
But if I can think of an idea,
I will let you know.
Once you have an idea, just text me.
Sure.
Go glam up. Your date will be waiting.
Don’t tease me. Please excuse me.
Have fun.
Goodbye.
Prapai means late.
Pupaa.
You look great today.
Aren’t you going in?
I’m waiting for my partner.
But it’s late already.
Do you want to go in with me first?
Hey, how do I look?
I’ve practiced my walk too.
Meena, this is Prapai.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
I didn’t accidentally step on her foot,
right?
Why does she seem like
she doesn’t like me?
It’s late, let’s go inside.
Be careful.
I thought you said you practiced.
I’m sorry I’m late again.
If you know you’re going to be late,
just let me know in advance.
Girls always take time
in dressing up for parties like this.
Am I pretty?
Well,
it’s alright.
Can I look as good as you?
Prapai.
Hey, Pupaa.
What about Wawa?
I’ll go find my friends first.
Ta.
When are you going to stop
being like this?
And what’s your problem?
Of course. Wawa is my friend.
You’re dating her.
You have to be responsible
for your actions.
How about you?
How did you come with Pupaa?
Well,
you’re so close with my friend nowadays.
So I don’t think you should be
telling others what to do,
if you can’t even do it yourself.
Ta, actually I was the one
who asked her...
Sure.
From now on, I will not mess with you.
I think that’s enough.
Are you going to finish all that?
Yes, I will. Don’t stop me.
You’ll get fat.
I don’t care.
Because desserts make me happy.
Like this one,
makes me 5 minutes happier.
This one, makes me 10 minutes happier.
And this one,
makes me 15 minutes happier.
So I’ll take it.
- Hello.
How are you all? Are you having fun?
But before we continue on having fun,
let’s do a replay on the past.
In this session,
- Photo gallery, a memory of the past.
Let’s hear for a round of applause.
After our small video
of the memory of the past,
it’s time for what everyone is
for waiting.
- No, waiting for.
But we would like to invite everyone
to the dance floor.
Let’s not waste any more time. Music.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Where are you going?
I can’t dance.
Come here, I’ll teach you the moves.
Follow me.
It’s not as difficult as math.
I don’t know how to dance like this.
What a good dancer.
Do you care for a dance?
Can I borrow your partner?
Sure, I’m about to take a break.
Please excuse me.
Where are you going? Come dance with me.
Let go of me, Ta.
Ever since I told you how I felt,
you’ve always rejected me.
Can you not make a scene?
Please excuse me.
You want to play
with my feelings, right?
You always shout at me.
But did you know that
everything happened because of you?
Ta, that’s enough.
I beg you, Ta.
Don’t hurt anyone anymore.
I’m going to go now.
Take care of yourself.
I’m sorry I ruined your night.
I should be the one saying sorry.
If I hadn’t invited you to this party,
you wouldn’t have to face this.
And I don’t really like parties
like this anyway.
You can go back to Ta.
Ta will be mad at you too.
I invited you to this party.
So I should be taking care of you.
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Hop on.
No worries, I can walk.
No need to feel bad.
This isn’t the first time anyway.
Come.
I told you about your heels.
It’s too high to carry your weight.
If it hurts, then stop trying.
Wait for me here.
I’ll put on some medicine,
so it won’t swell tomorrow.
Actually, he’s really gentle.
Ouch.
Be gentle. Are you insane?
I’m just massaging the medicine for you.
Ouch. I said be gentle.
I’m not going to let you do it anymore.
Be gentle.
Ouch. I said be gentle.
Ouch. That’s enough. Stop.
Ouch.
Be gentle.
Why do you keep pushing so hard?
What are you doing, mom?
Can you hear that noise?
It’s the girl’s voice.
Or is he hurting her?
Should we go in and help her?
I don’t think we should disturb them.
Maybe they are doing...
What does that mean?
You’re still too young to know.
Go on, back to your homework.
Be gentle.
Ouch.
Thank you. I think I’m better now.
This handkerchief helped me
so many times already.
Cleaned my tears and saliva.
I’ll wash it and return it to you.
Ta.
Are you alright?
You don’t look so well.
Is everything alright?
I ruined everything.
It’s alright. I’m always beside you.
Rule number four,
do not enter my personal space.
If you violate it again,
be prepared to pack your bags.
You’re close again, Prapai,
you nearly did it again.
Stop it, Prapai, he’s your gay friend.
Stop thinking like that.
(Thank you for last night)
(I hope you can find a better guy)
(And not get stuck with Ta)
Will he think that I’m saying Ta is bad?
No, no.
(Thank you for last night)
(I’m glad I have you as a roommate)
Oh my god, Prapai. You’re dead.
Pretend as if you saw nothing.
Maybe pretend sleepwalking?
Hey.
What is this?
I just wanted to thank you.
Who taught you
how to fold airplanes like this?
Like this.
Both sides.
Yeah, both sides.
Fold both sides.
And then fold it in like this.
It will help reduce wind resistance.
And it will help with
navigating the direction.
Sounds like I’ve heard it before.
But I can’t really remember.
How is it again?
Like this.
You don’t have to be so close.
Of course, I’m a girl.
Hey, slow down. I can’t catch up.
How is it again?
Fold it down.
Then fold the right and then the left.
Fold it down like this.
And then the left too, fold it down.
Wow, your folding skill is great.
So I’ll get back to work now.
Oh.
Don’t you want to take it with you?
Then can I have it? Yours is better.
I’m out.
Who is this girl? Do you know?
Oh wow.
Hey.
Why...
He’s here now. Go ask him.
I’m scared.
Hello, Professor.
Hello there.
Ask him. Ask.
Is there something going on?
Last night’s party was fun, yeah?
But who’s that girl?
You never mentioned her.
Well,
just a friend of mine.
So I invited her to the party.
This is a big issue.
I don’t think you’re just friends.
(How can you do this?
You’re not from this department.)
Ta, that’s enough.
(This guy is disgusting.
Pupaa is so much better.)
Ta, I beg you.
(Who is this girl?
Why did Pupaa help her?)
I’ve got a friend
who’s become viral on social media.
Just like in the Chinese series.
This is so romantic.
Should I even be happy about this?
If he knows that it’s going viral,
I’ll probably be dead.
Stupid Ta. Getting me in trouble again.
Hey, I have to go now.
Have you seen those photos?
Yes, I have.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t want to get you in trouble.
Why are you apologizing?
It’s not your fault.
Aren’t you worried?
Everyone’s gossiping about you.
No, people just say whatever.
When a new rumor comes,
they’ll forget about it.
Wow, you’re so strong.
But I don’t have the guts
to go to university anymore.
You’re stressing out too much,
your wrinkles are showing.
I’m wrinkly?
Wait a minute.
- Come here first.
- What?
Sit down there.
Sit down.
I know you’ve been through a lot too.
We’re in the same position.
Here, I’ll do a mask for you.
I just want to thank you.
Come on.
Hey.
What are they doing?
What are you doing?
Nothing’s happening.
Let’s continue with your homework.
Why are the hormones
of teenagers these days so strong?
Ouch.
Hey, that hurts.
It’s huge.
It’s tiny. How is it big?
Hey, it’s coming.
OK, OK, calm down.
- I know, I’ll catch it. Stop.
- It’s going to fly.
Hurry up.
- Fairy Prapai will help you now.
- Kill it.
Let me see, little roach.
Hurry up. It’s flying.
- Don’t worry.
- Hey. You touched it. No!
Little roach,
do you want to go be with big sister?
- No.
- Do you?
I’ll let you go.
Throw it away.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing. I wasn’t laughing.
You’re the one who made this room messy.
That’s why the cockroach is here.
From now on,
you will have to double the chores.
What? Why are you blaming me?
Stupid guy.
Pupaa, which one
do you think is better?
I’ve been sleeping late lately.
Both my eyes are like pandas now.
Look at this. It has vitamin C.
It will help with pigmentation problems.
And it’s also made from
natural extracts.
I knew I had to ask you.
Then I’ll buy it
and we can use it together.
Hey, your shirt still has a tag.
Oh true. Can you take it off for me?
All done.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hello, Tookta.
Hi there.
Did you just drop off Tintin?
Yes, I did.
It’s great that
during the mornings Tintin
doesn’t cry like other kids.
He’s great. I’m so sleepy.
How can you not be sleepy?
You were playing catch
so late last night.
You heard us?
I’m sorry to disturb you.
He was running around,
I had to catch him all night.
It’s giving me the tingles.
Don’t worry. I understand you.
But you should take care of yourself.
I know you’re still young,
but you need to use protection.
The brand I’m representing
also has condoms.
I’ll give you some to try out,
so you don’t get pregnant.
Wait a minute.
I don’t think you understand me.
You don’t have to be shy.
I’ve got one child already.
I know it’s natural.
You’re misunderstanding me.
I meant I was playing catch
with a cockroach.
Oh really?
Yes, it’s true.
Why would I be having something
with Pupaa?
Why not?
Girls and guys living together
can always have something going on.
Oh.
No, we can’t. I’ll probably be cursed.
Why so?
Pupaa doesn’t like girls.
Oh my god.
I think you’re misunderstanding.
No, I’m not.
Pupaa’s type
must be tall,
good-shaped like a basketball player.
Oh my god. I couldn’t tell.
My radar is broken.
I know, right?
But you can’t tell anyone at all.
Alright, I won’t tell.
Thank you. I have to go to work now.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Prapai.
Oh, how can I help you, Faye?
About Living Life in Bangkok
that you said you’d help me with,
how is it going?
Have you had any other ideas?
I haven’t had time to think about it.
I thought you promised me.
I’m sorry. I’m a bit busy these days.
Prapai, I understand
that you only live once,
but don’t let it ruin your work.
See,
I’ve been talking to Pon,
the creative director.
He seems interested.
Really?
Umm.
I’ll try to finish off the idea.
Then send me the idea tonight.
Sure.
Alright, I won’t disturb you now.
You can continue working.
Be careful the devil Pla will scold you.
Wait, calm down first, Pai.
What do you think you’re doing, Ta?
Listen to me first.
The other day at the party,
I was really drunk.
I didn’t know what I was doing.
I’m really sorry.
Hold on, Pai, listen to me.
I’m really sorry. Can you forgive me?
Pupaa.
You’re here in time.
How was your work? Are you tired?
Just a bit.
You can stop following me.
Pupaa will misunderstand
that I like you.
Are you two dating?
No, we’re not. I’ve got to go.
Even if me and Pupaa are not dating,
it doesn’t mean I have to forgive you.
I’ve heard you apologize too often.
I’ve always forgiven you.
But from now on,
your apologies mean nothing.
Hey you. Why didn’t you help me?
I thought we were friends.
Your roommate is in trouble.
Don’t you think of helping?
Hey.
Or you’re afraid Ta
will misunderstand you,
so you didn’t help me?
So you’re going to keep
making up excuses like this?
Facing the truth
will end things better.
Take off your shoes and put them away.
Excuse me,
the restaurant is closing now.
Okay.
(How can you do this?
You’re not from this department.)
(This guy is disgusting.)
Stop looking at it.
Here you go.
Pai wanted me to give it to you.
I thought it was getting close
to the submission date.
So I printed it for you.
I’ll hold on to it for you first,
so it doesn’t get dirty.
Thank you.
You’ve always been nice to me.
You know that drinking causes trouble,
and you’re still drinking?
Have you met Prapai?
Yeah, I did.
She seems happy.
It seems like
she’s doing it for real this time.
It’s impossible to forgive me.
You know she can’t be mad
at anyone for long.
Give her some time.
I think she’ll be better soon.
Aren’t you mad at me?
There’s a meeting
in the condominium today.
You have to go with me.
Why do I have to go?
You’re the owner of the room.
Why don’t you go?
If you don’t want to stay here,
then you don’t have to go.
I’ll go. Who said I wasn’t going?
Alright.
I am going to introduce you
to the waste management policy.
The community is rushing
to implement it.
Everyone will be receiving
the instructions next month.
The project that I introduced...
Look at Pupaa.
- Won’t stop staring at Mr. Jo.
- That is...
The idea of 3R1S
What does 3R1S contain?
- This is his type.
- That is...
Reduce, reuse and recycle.
What is reduce?
Reduce is to minimize the usage
to reduce the amount of wastes.
Reuse is to put...
That’s good. So he can move on from Ta.
to be able to reduce and reuse
without any expenses.
Your policy is great.
I’m glad there’s someone
who’s strict on this.
Thank you.
If we can really
make it into a
zero waste community, it would be great.
I would like to do that too.
Hey you, Jo is my boyfriend.
Stop trying.
Is there a problem? Can we calm down?
I think there’s a misunderstanding.
You can stop hoping,
so you don’t have to feel worse.
Let’s go. Don’t get into trouble.
We’re in the same building.
We’ll probably meet up often.
There’re so many more better guys,
I’ll help introduce them to you.
What did you say?
Let me tell you something,
Jo likes women.
Yes, and so?
Stop pretending.
I heard it all
that your friend said you like Jo.
I know you don’t want to
let anyone know about this,
but I’ll tell them
that you actually like me.
So everything will end.
And when you’re with me,
you can just be yourself.
What are you doing?
I’m 100% man.
If you don’t believe me,
do you want to try?
(Special scene)
Ta, that’s enough.
I beg you, Ta.
Oh boy, Ta.
You got me into trouble again.
I have to go now.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t want you to get into trouble
because of me.
You’re stressing out too much,
your wrinkles are showing.