♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn about it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Let’s practice love♪
♪We’ll learn it together♪
♪To build our relationship, baby♪
♪We’ll take it slow
I don’t want to rush it♪
♪We’ll practice love with this heart♪
♪Before we fall in love♪
♪From not being familiar
From not liking it♪
♪No, I’ve never thought about it
Never thought I’d learn to love♪
♪I’m starting to get used to
From not liking it♪
♪You changed my mind♪
♪I like me better when I’m with you♪
♪You are the only one I want♪
♪Just wait for the right time♪
♪It may not be hard
If we work it out together♪
♪We’ll find that what I thought
was right♪
♪I didn’t want to make commitments♪
♪I just want to know you more
Before we get into a relationship♪
♪I just wanna be a beginner lover♪
♪So that one day we can be together♪
=Put Your Head On My Shoulder 2021=
=Episode 8=
Come here. Please gather around here.
Hurry up.
Hey, come here.
Prapai.
Where are you going?
They’re heavy smoke on our floor,
let’s go down.
Where’s Prapai?
I didn’t see her.
Pupaa.
Prapai.
Next time be careful with what you do.
What if Pupaa
didn’t rescue you in time?
It’s alright.
No need to scold her.
She might still be scared.
I’m really sorry. I just wanted to cook
and celebrate with Pupaa
because I got a new job.
I didn’t think it would be
a big problem like this.
Never mind. At least no one got hurt.
I’ll have to go back to my child now.
Everyone. There’s nothing going on.
We can all get back to our rooms now.
I’m sorry, Pupaa.
I really didn’t mean to do it.
It’s okay. It’s okay.
At least you didn’t get hurt.
It’s alright. It’s alright.
Assumption number five,
if we love someone,
we will care for them more than others.
I’m sorry I destroyed your kitchen.
You don’t have to apologize anymore.
No one wants anything like this
to happen, right?
I’ll admit my cooking skills is zero.
Then I’ll cook for you instead.
Hey, don’t make that face.
Didn’t you get offered a job today?
We should celebrate.
Then you can order anything,
it’s my treat.
You can order for me.
Sure. I got it.
Excuse me,
Can I have two noodle soups?
No MSG, please.
Thank you.
Come on, let’s cheers.
Here.
To the talented Prapai.
Yay.
Hey Pupaa, what’s wrong?
Come, come.
Are you alright?
Take it slow.
What’s wrong with you?
Have you got diarrhea?
Don’t tell me...
Two noodle soups, please.
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have ordered street food.
Even though I know your body is weak
and I still took you there.
I’m sorry.
It’s alright.
Do you want to go to the hospital?
I feel better now.
How are you better? You look so drained.
Come on. I’ll take you to the hospital.
Come on, get up.
Okay, let’s go.
I think he’s got food poisoning.
Yes, I think I have an idea about that.
He’ll feel better after a shot.
Thank you.
I feel better now.
We don’t have to do this.
I’m sorry, I can’t say no.
The doctor said so.
Are you afraid of needles?
No.
I just don’t know
what she’s injecting into me.
Hey, this is the hospital.
And she’s also a nurse.
Yeah, I’m afraid of needles.
Don’t worry. I won’t tell anyone
that the perfect Pupaa
is afraid of needles.
It won’t hurt. Don’t be scared.
Here, hold my hand.
All done.
She’s done.
Hey, it’s done.
See? That’s it.
He can go home
after he’s taken his pills.
Thank you.
Come on, let’s take the pill.
Come on.
I’ll go take it back at home.
Hey, just get it done now.
Don’t tell me
you’re scared of taking pills too?
Hey, it’s not funny.
I nearly choked on it to death before.
Aw.
It’s alright, little kid.
Don’t cry. Don’t be upset.
Aw.
Here’s water.
Are you better?
Any better?
Prapai.
You’re so sneaky.
I did it because I want you
to get better.
Come on, let’s go home.
You lied to me. Carry me back home.
Alright. Come on.
Are you okay?
Walk slowly.
(I got my dream job already)
(Wealth, luck, bad luck)
(Lucky color for clothing table)
(Power, wealth, luck, back luck)
Oh, you’re better already?
Probably because of the pill
you tricked me into taking last night.
Thank you.
It’s your first day of work, isn’t it?
Good luck.
I’ll head out now. Fighting.
Bye.
Hello, Pon.
Great. You’re on time.
Tomorrow we’ve got a poster shoot,
doing a teaser about tourism in Bangkok.
Living Life in Bangkok.
Like the one I helped Faye with?
That’s right. Come on, follow me.
Everyone, this is Prapai.
She’ll be another creative worker
on our team.
Hello. You can just call me Pai.
Take a seat.
Yes.
How’s it going?
I’m fine.
Note down the details too,
so you don’t forget.
Sure.
Let’s start now.
This is a big project.
So we’re suggesting the client
to use popular celebrities
at the moment.
To capture the attention of teenagers
both in the country and overseas.
I’ve already talked about the concept
with the photographer.
And the details about the poster,
Cop will be responsible for that.
I think this is it.
Who’s taking care of the model?
Everyone already has a job.
I think you can point out
who you want to let them be in charge.
It’s easier that way.
Then I’ll let Pai do it.
You don’t have any responsibilities yet.
Just take it as your first task then.
Sure. I will do my best.
Is Professor not here yet?
Professor has a seminar this morning.
I heard the seminar has been extended,
so he might be a bit late.
If you need any help, just let me know.
Sure.
Pupaa.
Can you help me with this?
Sure.
There’s this one person who’s doing
the same research topic as I am,
so I was thinking of
exchanging ideas with them.
I think we could share some ideas.
Do you think I should add anything else
to this?
I think you need a little fixing here.
Try put it in.
Excuse me.
I’m sorry. Excuse me.
- Ta da.
Ken, Ken. My name is Ken.
He’s here with Tum and oh...
- That’s all. It’s just the two of us.
I told you coming in like this
wouldn’t work.
- Look, dead silence.
- It’s not even complete.
Look, everyone’s so still.
Why are you two here?
I told with Professor already.
He said this research is a big topic,
I should find some help.
So I invited Ken and Tum to help.
If you have anything for us to help,
you can let us know.
That’s right.
It’s fine.
I’ll go take my work to do outside.
Then where should we start?
This one here.
Oh wow.
Do smarty pants use these?
Hey, Ken. Tum.
Come here.
Excuse me, for how many years
have we been working together?
Exactly.
Why is there still a problem?
It’s the same problem.
Please fix it.
Oh, I’m sorry. I’m really sorry.
Be careful.
Hello.
I’m Pai.
I will be taking care of you today, Tan.
Hold on. What did you call me?
Well, Tan.
Time.
Tan is the one with the rumor
about the swimming suit right now.
Where have you been?
I’m the year’s teenager’s idol.
But you called my name wrong.
I’m sorry. I just started working here.
Did they send a newbie
to take care of me?
This is not professional.
I must make a comment on this.
Please, don’t tell Pon.
I don’t want him to know
I made a mistake.
I promise I will not call you
with the wrong name anymore.
Please.
Time, I’m going to go out for a while.
Did something happen?
Nothing. You can go.
Good. I’ll be back.
Can you just turn a little?
Just to the side.
Put your hands in your pocket.
Turn a bit more.
Everything should be fine.
I’ll be back then.
I’ll go grab a coffee.
Sure.
- Come on, Faye.
- Sure.
Put your hands in your pocket too.
- I’ll be right back.
- Alright.
Put your hands in your pocket.
Hey,
if you don’t follow the reference,
how will the client be using it?
Don’t be so problematic.
I’m not trying to be problematic,
but are you sure
you want me to pose like this?
Do you want to ask the agency?
Let’s calm down first.
So what do you want?
If you can’t conclude it for me,
I won’t do this shoot.
Right now Time is upset
with the pose that he is forced to do,
But the photographer wants the set
to come out perfect.
If this continues,
this is going to be bad.
But Time is a famous idol.
If we make him upset,
it’s going to be bad.
Think, girl, think.
So can we do this instead?
During the first part,
he can do a freestyle pose.
Act all fun and happy.
Then after that,
we can follow the reference.
Acting cool and sleek.
Let’s give a try.
- Let’s try this.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Time, the set is ready.
You can get into your position.
Everything is clear, right?
Yes.
So we’ll do a freestyle pose here.
I want fun.
And excitement.
Then we’ll change the mood
to be cool and sleek.
Sure.
All done.
Of course.
Because if there’re Ken and Tum,
everything will be double
the efficiency.
You got anything else for us to do?
Actually, there’s another thing
I need you to help me with.
- Sure.
(Hypothesis)
It’s the correct document, right?
This is very theoretical.
Assumption number one.
Always jealous
when someone gets close to her.
Come on, Tintin, let’s go to bed.
Hold on.
Jealous even with the kid next door?
Even if it was a kid, but it’s a boy.
Oh boy, let’s look at the second one.
Assumption number two.
Heart races when she’s near.
It is found that
the heart rate is with an average of
100-135 beats per minute
every time she gets close.
Let’s get onto the next one.
Assumption number three.
She changes me unbelievably.
Excuse me, can I get another spare fork?
Is it good?
Assumption number four.
I’m always happy when she’s happy.
I’m getting a job.
I got a job interview.
Assumption number five.
If we love that person,
we will care for them more than others.
So,
what’s the conclusion?
This is so obvious.
How can someone smart like you not know?
Exactly.
Should’ve known since assumption two.
(Like or not like)
So who is this girl?
Who is it?
You don’t have to know.
Once we’ve got the conclusion,
what do I do next?
Just continue flirting with her.
What are you waiting for?
When did you get here?
So, how do I flirt with her?
It’s hard work,
being at a production shoot.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
Only staff is allowed in here.
I just wanted to get Time’s autograph.
Can you please help me?
I travelled on the train from far away.
I came here since morning.
Can you please help me?
Please.
I really want it.
I came here just for it.
Alright.
I’ll try talking to him for you.
Thank you.
Oh Time, have you not changed?
No one told me what to do.
How can you guys work like this?
And what’s that?
You want an autograph?
And you called me the wrong name?
Your fan asked me to get your autograph.
I can’t sign.
Why?
It’s not in the work schedule.
What? It’s only an autograph.
She came from far away.
I said I can’t sign.
Don’t you understand?
So what do you want me to tell her?
I feel bad for her.
You accepted it. Fix your own problem.
You’re so mean.
How can this type of person
even have a fanclub?
Such a pity for his fanclub.
You can’t even sign one autograph.
(Time)
How to flirt
and make her fall in love with you.
So how does it work?
Start with giving attention.
Just call her.
Yes.
Ask her how she’s doing.
Show her your care.
Why do I need to call?
We’ll meet in the evening anyway.
So,
I’ll go make a call.
Hello, what’s going on?
How are you doing?
I’m a bit busy right now.
We’ll talk later.
How was it?
It didn’t work.
She said she’s busy and just hung up.
Don’t give up.
Girls are like this.
You’ve got to keep trying at first.
Let’s do this. Send her a text.
- Send it.
Send it. Send it.
(Take care of yourself
and don’t forget to eat)
This seems too normal.
It doesn’t feel special.
(Take a break some time. I’m worried.)
That seems too direct.
You don’t look sophisticated.
I’ll think of one on my own.
Good job.
(Pupaa
I won’t be home too late today.)
(Take a break some time. I’m worried.)
(How does it
feel working in the job you like?)
(It’s actually really fun.)
(It’s only the model
that’s giving me a hard time.)
Start by giving attention.
(There’s a lot of dust outside.
Lots of diseases spreading.)
(Take care of yourself.)
(The name of the group
has changed to Secret Mission)
(The highest possibility is that
it’s the girl from the party.)
(I don’t think so.
That’s his best friend’s best friend.)
(Let’s consider other possibilities.)
(Where are you working at?)
(I’ll check for you
if the dust level is high or not.)
- All done.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
You can come
and check out the photos first.
This one looks great.
Don’t you think?
Calm down, please.
Everyone, please give me some time.
Today Time is only here to work.
He’s not giving out autographs.
Then why is she the only person
to get the autograph?
Exactly.
We’re not okay with this.
We’ve always supported Time.
Wherever you want us to go,
we’re always there.
But there’s someone
who’s had more privilege.
What do you want us to think?
Yes, we can’t take this.
Why is she the only one
who got the autograph?
I think
today Time worked in the studio
the entire day.
He didn’t come out to meet anyone.
I don’t think
this is the real autograph.
Hey you.
You faked the autograph?
I didn’t fake it.
I really didn’t fake it.
I gave the photo to one of the staff.
And Time really signed it back to me.
Here. Here she is.
Prapai.
Hey, how can you do this?
Why did you do this?
Explain to us.
Come here, everyone.
Because I’ve already finished the shoot
today,
I’ll give everyone a photo
and an autograph to everyone
who came to support me today.
For every Timer here today.
Is everything good?
Certainly.
I’m so happy today.
Yay.
Thank you everyone for coming
to support me here today.
We are so honored.
First job
and you’ve already caused trouble.
Why didn’t you think things through?
I’m sorry.
I didn’t think
it would come out like this.
You’re a creative.
You have to think smart.
It’s good that Time came to help
on time.
Otherwise you’ll be doomed.
I really apologize for what happened.
She just joined the team.
She really doesn’t know.
Making you waste your time
to sign a lot of photos.
It’s not a waste of time.
Because I didn’t say
that I’d sign it myself.
(I’m just passing by the studio.
Do you want to go back together?)
(I’m not done yet. There’s so much work.
You can go home first.)
(It’s alright. I can wait.)
(Up to you. I warned you.)
Are you Prapai?
Yes.
Your smile really is bright.
Someone gave this to you.
Thank you.
Good work. You can’t even tell
it’s not my real autograph.
When you’re done signing,
don’t forget to give them to the fans.
And this too.
Give the masks to my fans too.
When are you going to finish all this?
I know, right?
I now understand why you didn’t sign it
in the first place.
I’m really sorry I caused you trouble.
I really didn’t think things through
like what Pon said.
No, please don’t.
I caused the trouble.
I should be responsible for it.
The fact you sorted things out
with your fans for me,
I’m grateful enough already.
Why do you keep talking so formally?
Makes me think of when I first debuted.
There weren’t as many fans as now.
I signed every photo for them.
Here you go. Give these out too.
Sure.
What are you waiting for? Go on.
I’m sorry for the long wait.
I’m sure there’s enough for everyone.
Here you go.
Thank you.
See you again.
I have a male fan too?
It’s late already. Where are you going?
I’ll drop you off.
Thank you.
But I’ve got someone
to pick me up already.
Up to you.
- He’s really handsome.
- True.
He’s so handsome, right?
Come on, Prapai, let’s go home.
Hey, what is this?
Are you a creep?
- I’m sorry.
- I don’t know him.
He looks good.
Shouldn’t have been a creep.
Pupaa.
Did you meet a friend?
Oh.
I talked to the wrong person.
Where’s the mask I gave you?
Oh, it was you?
It’s not this one.
They’re all the same.
Come on, let’s go home.
It’s not the same.
(Wawa)
What’s going on, Wawa?
Pai.
Ta hasn’t even talked to me.
He just disappeared.
What should I do?
It’s what I’ve been trying to tell you
all along.
I didn’t want to see you
crying over and over again like this.
I’ve known him for a long time.
I know he can’t be changed.
I know too.
But it’s not easy
to stop loving someone.
But if one day,
you’ve made your mind and be strong.
You’ll get over it.
And you’ll meet the right person
for you.
I don’t know, Pai, I don’t know.
(Rendering video)
It’s alright. I’ll be here for you.
(I miss you)
(This page is a must)
(Tomorrow’s the first day
of mid-term exam. Study hard.)
Here,
you can put the dessert right here.
Please.
You can put the purple one here.
Thank you.
Prapai.
Time asked for you. He said it’s urgent.
Just go.
And don’t cause any more trouble.
Sure.
- You replace her here.
- Sure.
How’s it going?
How can I help you?
Nothing.
I just asked to see
if you’re here today.
You can go now.
Sure.
Pai.
- Yes?
- I want a cold wipe.
Cold wipe?
Sure.
Here’s your cold wipe.
What have we got for lunch?
I’ll go check it out for you.
Chilli basil stir fry.
Too spicy.
Noodles stir fry.
Too fat.
I want some water.
I said I’m thirsty.
Sure.
Here’s your cold water.
I want room temperature water.
Can’t you make do with cold water?
Room temperature water.
Room temperature.
Sure. Please wait a moment.
Here’s your water.
Here you go.
Alright?
I want a straw.
Sure. Please wait a moment.
Pai.
What is going on?
What?
I’m sorry.
I was just going to tell you
the set is ready. Go get Time.
Sure.
I haven’t called you yet.
The set is ready. You can head over now.
Stop talking to me so formally.
Then I’ll go.
What are you talking about?
Time, please head to the set.
Just a bit more.
Time, please go to the set.
Time, let’s go to the set.
That’s it. Come on.
Please go.
Please go, please.
Just this one, trust me.
The reason I got to date my girlfriend
is because of this book.
Really?
Are you serious?
Yeah. After I finished the book,
she said yes.
Thank you so much.
Come on, trust me.
(Guide for men to chase after women)
There’s only a few left,
meaning a lot of people have bought it.
(Biography of Einstein)
This book is really popular.
Everyone says it works.
480 baht.
Do you want a bag?
No, thanks.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Pai. What should I do?
What’s going on?
The girl model
that needs to shoot with Time,
we’ve told her to be here at 8,
and she’s not here yet.
She said she’ll be here in 15 minutes.
Then just wait. It’s only 15 minutes.
We can wait.
But we’re afraid that Time won’t wait.
Time is very strict on being on time.
That much?
Yes. The reason we’re stressed
is because it happened once.
He left the set before.
because the other actor
didn’t come on time.
If he knows that our model
is not here yet,
it’s going to be...
I’m going now.
(Special scene)
You can’t go in if you’re not a staff.
I just wanted to give a friend
something.
Oh, what’s her name?
So I can give it to the right person.
Her name is Prapai.
Her height is about 163 cm.
Her eyes are bright and shiny.
And when she smiles,
everything becomes bright.
Overall,
she’s cute.