This is procedural justice.
It is the foundation for the realization
of substantive justice.
You mean
if the procedure is destroyed
and rules overturned,
the law has no meaning.
Even though
we feel sorry about the victims…
If they lack legal awareness
and didn't save strong evidence,
even if we want to help them,
there is no way for us to start.
So after today,
this reinforced
one of my thoughts.
At the time I have money
and get enough ability and energy,
I'm going to run a non-profit
legal aid platform.
With it, we not only handle cases,
but also popularize the law
more broadly.
I think that's a good idea.
How could you think of doing this?
Actually this is what
I want to do most after graduation.
But Li Chongwen doesn't support me.
Later I worked in Zhanying
and told Director Tao about this.
He didn't give me a response, either.
If I can start it over now,
I'm going to do whatever
I want to do.
Look.
These cases
we were consulted today
actually
are trifling matters.
But because
people lack legal awareness,
they missed the best time
to protect themselves.
You know, sometimes
compared with my failure,
the thing that makes me sadder is
I could've made it.
So, I don't want
more fairness and justice
are devoured because of ignorance.
Cool!
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪how to prove♪
♪You know how much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises for you♪
♪What's to be continued prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪
=Episode 10=
=Go Away Leukemia=
=Legally Romance=
What?
What do you want?
This afternoon,
I will have the first date
with Tang Lyu.
So, I came to ask you
for advice.
Me?
Help me
choose the best outfit for dating,
which can blow Tang Lyu's mind.
Love drives people crazy.
Even a tomboy
learns to behave like a girl.
Cut the crap!
Give me a good choice.
Or you'll see.
(For Women For Men)
Are you going to prick Tang Lyu
with your rivets?
The first date focuses
on winning his heart,
not his head.
Stop it! Stop it!
Brother, please don't put me
on the spot.
Can you wear a little bit
decent clothes?
Stop it!
Are you going for a fight or a date?
Not satisfied?
These are my most expensive clothes.
All right.
Send Buddha to the West.
To assure
you have a successful date tonight,
I will be responsible
for your clothes.
Get changed.
No way.
I would die here
today
rather than
wear this girlish dress.
What's the most important thing
for a relationship?
Do what he likes!
Tang Lyu likes
a sweet girl.
Clean and pure.
Not a rock girl, okay?
To live or love?
Think about it yourself.
Impossible.
I'm not even gonna wear it.
What are you doing?
No, why here?
Oh, my God.
Just listen to me.
Hello, sir.
I'm a regular customer here.
Why do you bring me here?
Do some skin care for her
to make her skin bright
immediately.
It'd better make
her skin look clean and smooth
as a shelled egg
Is there that skin care?
Miss Liu,
you always hydrate your skin
all the time.
I think
he wants you
to try out
timeless youthful skin care.
You can rest assured.
It must work very well.
Fine.
- This way, Miss Liu.
- Go.
This way, please.
Come on.
Go, go!
I never did it, I…
Go. Go.
Go.
Shiyun,
you look special today.
Yeah?
I… I feel awkward, too.
Not awkward.
You look very pretty.
The wine
is directly delivered here by air
from its country of origin.
Do you want a taste?
Okay.
Here.
Cheers.
How is it?
This wine is not strong enough.
It's so hot.
I
don't even drink much.
I always drink warm water.
I am inconsiderate.
Waitress.
Bring us a lemonade.
Thank you.
Miss, what else can I do
for you?
It's okay.
I just choked a little.
Please help us
open the window.
Waitress.
Hello.
What smell is this?
Why is it so stinky?
Sorry, sir.
Nearby is a restaurant
selling river snails rice noodles.
Its taste is strong.
In order not to affect customers,
we don't usually open windows.
A qualified western restaurant
not only guarantees
the quality of the dishes
but also takes into account
the dining environment.
How could there be such a restaurant
on the opposite side?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
No way. I'm gonna report it.
Smelly? I think it smells good.
You like these?
No, no, no.
How could it be possible?
I just think
it's not easy
to open a restaurant.
Just forget it.
Please close the window.
Okay.
You know what?
The taste of river snails rice noodles
is mainly
from pickled sour bamboo shoots.
In the fermentation process,
two amino acids are transformed.
One is hydrogen sulfide.
The other is skatole.
Essentially,
river snails rice noodles
taste the same as excrement.
But don't worry.
I won't allow my girlfriend
to eat
this kind of humble food.
It turns out
I not only am humble,
but also like to eat humble food.
Shiyun, you really needn't me
to give you a ride?
I needn't.
My roommates happen to live nearby.
After our date,
I want to get together with them.
Okay.
Take care on the way.
When you arrive, send me a message.
Okay.
Bye.
Oh, my God!
The food is expensive and unpalatable.
How could it be ranked
in the Food of the Year?
(River snails rice noodles)
Smells good.
What are you doing here?
Come on.
You are athletes.
But you came all the way to eat here.
You are really idle.
You don't understand.
It's called love.
I'm V-V-VIP
of this restaurant.
I found this place by accident.
And then I become addicted
after eating once.
What happened to you?
This isn't like a place
where a couple would come
after the first date.
Forget it.
I felt very uncomfortable
when having dinner with Tang Lyu.
The western food
is expensive and unpalatable.
More seriously,
I have to behave well all the time.
If I hadn't heard of
this restaurant here,
I couldn't make it through at all.
And finally, Tang Lyu told me
a lot of
chemistry terms.
He means that
eating river snails rice noodles
is eating shit.
I'm so pissed.
This is the price
of falling in love with a super scholar.
Stop laughing.
When will you pay a price?
For Zixin.
I wish.
But she's been avoiding me lately.
I can only turn love
into an appetite.
If I don't fall in love,
I can eat whatever I want.
It's also pretty good.
Aren't you full?
I'm buying you.
Madam.
A bowl of signature rice noodles.
Madam,
give me another half a dozen beers.
Okay.
This humblest shack
of a restaurant is amazing.
Cool!
Drink it.
Drink. Cheers.
Come on! Come on!
Come on. Drink it up.
Look at your dress.
What will you wear on your next date?
It looks much more comfortable now.
- Come on.
- Come on. Drink it up.
If I had known that setting up a stall
would make money,
I should have tried.
Listen,
I would make a great fortune.
You will also be beaten
by the conductor.
Only for couples.
(Pre-sale of concert tickets)
Ten years later, if the couple
enters the venue with their own tickets,
all ticket fees will be refunded.
There is no possibility of losing money.
My parents would have been very excited
if they had known this.
(Ten-year Promise Signing Session)
Anyway, people like me
who are as close as wax
see that
they voluntarily pay,
but not for me,
I feel very uncomfortable.
Have you asked Yuzhou?
Lu Xun is so persevering.
Can't he move Zixin?
Anyway, judging from
the last law popularization
and fellowship activity,
it's hard.
This concert
is very important to me.
Could you think of a way?
There is no other way.
Lu Xun.
Is this what you want?
How could you…?
I think Yuzhou
might suddenly figure it out.
(Ten-year Promise Signing Session)
(Great)
(My subline task)
(has finally progressed)
(This time, Zixin took the initiative)
(to send the ticket to Lu Xun)
(There is no way)
(that it fails)
I think
you look sad.
It's because of money.
Let's go.
Maybe there will be a miracle.
And they would be together.
♪It's not that I'm too sad♪
♪The world is way too complicated,
you said it's hard to be simple♪
♪Of course I understand♪
♪But only you were with me
in the first place♪
♪Only you understand
that the dream I want is simple♪
♪We're not together
At least we're still like a couple♪
♪I cried most in front of you
with pain and madness♪
♪I know you can't take me back
to that place♪
♪You said you are fine now
and like to have long memories♪
♪We're not together
At least we're still like a family♪
♪We always care and share from afar♪
♪But only you were with me
in the first place♪
♪Only you understand
that the dream I want is simple♪
♪We're not together
At least we're still like a couple♪
♪I cried most in front of you
with pain and madness♪
♪I know you can't take me back
to that place♪
♪You said you are fine now
and like to have long memories♪
♪We're not together
At least we're still like a family♪
♪We always care and share from afar♪
♪We're not together
At least we're still like friends♪
♪Your care from afar is actually longer♪
(Concert ticket pre-sale)
You've been in Law Department
for an academic year.
I believe you have a clear vision
of your future
and profession.
Although the wish bottles
can't help you succeed,
they can
at least make you remember
your original aspiration.
Ten years
sounds like a long time,
but it's just a blink of an eye.
Please write your wish on paper
and put it in the bottle.
Put the wish bottles
in these two boxes in the front.
I have a meeting.
Qian Wei.
After everyone finishes writing,
collect the bottles
and send them to my office.
Okay.
Are you wishing so much
that one piece of paper is not enough?
Do I have to get another one for you
from Professor Zhen?
Am I such a person?
Only kids dream of
making their dreams come true.
Adults only believe
that it all depends on human effort.
So sensible?
Seriously?
Of course it's fake.
If I believe this,
why am I writing so much?
Well.
Even if you work hard,
you will not necessarily succeed.
But if you keep wishful thinking,
your dream will come to nothing.
So I think
you have to be brave
to fight for it.
You have to try
but not always wait.
Are you trying to get me?
Don't worry.
When my wish comes true,
I will definitely tell you.
Do I still have to guess your wish?
Of course
it's for Zixin.
So stubborn.
Everyone.
Just write and hand it in.
Whatever you want to do,
you have to do it yourself.
It's useless
to write it on paper.
Just write
and let them rest in peace.
Come on.
Don't hesitate.
Even Einstein
had a dream about the violin.
As a student of Law Department,
of course you could
have a dream of music.
Show your attitude
as a tigress.
Qian Wei,
will my wish come true?
I can't feel it.
But listen.
If you don't try it now,
no matter how much money you make
in ten years,
you'll regret it.
Zixin, what did you write?
I want to start from scratch
and have my own business.
Save it.
You don't have to.
Isn't your dad
the king of stock's value?
Starting from scratch is his business.
You just have to
inherit his estate.
Listen.
Don't talk nonsense.
I have a hunch that
Zixin in 2022
will be so successful
and busy that
she doesn't even have time to
come back to open the wish bottle.
All thanks to your lucky words.
You are so biased.
You didn't say anything about my future.
Collect them for me.
I will pick up a phone.
Mom.
What's up?
To the hospital?
Why?
It's all your dad's fault.
He wanted to find
the feeling of youth.
So he rides me on his bike
without holding on to the handlebars.
Soon
we hit a tree.
I can't move now.
I have to go to the hospital
for an X-ray.
You sprained the ankle?
What about dad?
Is he fine?
He's fine.
But his nose hit the tree.
So he has a nosebleed.
Don't frighten her.
It's okay.
Qian.
Why are you still having a nosebleed?
Here. Paper for you.
Why again?
Has he had any
headaches or fever lately?
Fever?
Qian, come here.
Let me try.
Kind of.
It's fine.
I feel good.
Maybe it's a seasonal cold.
Well, mom. Listen to me.
When you go to
the orthopedic department to register,
help him register for blood routine
and bone puncture.
I will go back with Qian Chuan
right now.
Wait for me.
Take things back
for me.
Okay.
I am leaving.
What happened to her?
It seems her parents called to say
they were in the hospital.
(Gate 3, East Campus, Guanghua University)
Don't worry, Qian Wei.
You just had a dream.
It won't come true.
You don't understand.
What should happen will happen.
No way.
It's just an accident.
Why don't they stop?
Let me help you.
Why are they leaving?
There is no taxi at all.
No…
Qian Wei.
Where are you going
in such a hurry?
Thank you, Li Chongwen.
It's alright, just go.
Let me handle it.
Okay.
Just go.
(Outpatient)
(Police)
Hello.
Why are you running?
I won't do this again.
How come?
You were healthy
half a year ago.
How can you possibly have leukemia?
How come?
It shouldn't be that serious.
Exactly.
Stop crying.
Others may think
you are the one who is sick.
We must calm down at this moment.
Understand?
I can't make it.
Our dad never
smokes or drinks,
and he goes for a walk
every day after dinner.
It is said that walking after meals
is good for longevity.
There are so many bad people.
Why it's our dad's turn?
Why?
(Haizhou Tonghe Hospital:
Certificate of Diagnosis)
Wei.
(Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia)
Why did your dream
come true?
Darling.
I said I would take you
on a global trip.
(Home page
of outpatient medical records)
(Diagnosis: Early Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia)
I guess I can't make it.
Stop talking about this
at this moment.
Only early symptoms.
(Diagnosis: Early Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia)
Early?
Only early?
It's leukemia any way.
It's all your fault.
Why did you dream
to scare our dad?
I was asked to assemble for training.
Not for now.
I'm going to ask for leave now.
All right.
Stop being like this.
Just go for training.
Dad.
Do you believe me?
Well…
Enough.
It's not a big deal.
Listen.
I never told you that
I had another dream.
I dreamed of your recovery
and witnessed me
becoming a real lawyer.
We accompanied Qian Chuan
to the national team.
Then you and mom
went on a tour.
Great!
Don't worry. I got it.
We can certainly
get through this.
Stop crying.
Be a man.
Your first priority now
is to be with mom.
Leg injuries also need attention.
Don't make her leave
any aftereffects.
Understand?
Well.
My mom should be on duty today.
She told me that
there might be beds
in the inpatient department.
I will deal with it.
Okay.
Qian Chuan,
how's everything going?
The streetlights down there are broken.
Walk slowly.
How about this, Qian Chuan?
After I get packed,
I'll go back to accompany him.
When he's taking the infusion,
remember
to confiscate the snacks
in his pockets.
He mustn't eat such dry snacks.
Got it?
And remember
to buy a respirator for him.
He's vulnerable now.
He has to wear one in the open air.
And turtle soup, right?
I'll go...
I'll go get
the electric cooker and so forth.
Don't worry, all right?
Wei,
I'll keep it in mind.
I used to think
that you were only
half a minute older than me.
But today, I'm convinced.
You're indeed my elder sister.
We nearly lost our father.
I'm so scared.
Wei,
did you tell the truth?
Did you really dream
that Father will get better?
Rest assured. He'll get better.
Are you all right?
Qian Wei.
Qian Wei, are you all right?
Everything will be all right.
I asked Qian Chuan this afternoon.
I know you're feeling sad.
But you have us.
Stop crying.
Stop. Stop.
We know you must be too busy
to take care of the school thing.
We... We've packed
your clothes, books, and laptop.
And the torch.
When you go to
or come back from the hospital,
it must be dark at night.
Use the torch then.
If you need anything,
text us.
We'll bring it to you,
all right?
Don't worry, Qian Wei.
From this day on,
I'll take the roll call for you
in all kinds of classes.
For you,
I'll study hard
and take notes carefully.
You won't
fall behind in study.
I also packed some ginseng
from Changbai Mountain.
Let your father eat it
for some nutrition.
A leukemia patient can't eat ginseng.
Or he'll have blood-heat.
Don't... don't let him eat it, then.
It doesn't matter.
I'll eat it.
I'll eat it up.
Qian Wei, don't worry.
My parents know some experts
in hemopathy.
If your father needs them,
I'll contact them immediately.
Okay?
Thank you.
Stop crying.
Everything will be all right.
(Calling from the Matron)
Didn't I ask you not to eat it
when you came for hospitalization?
Why did you still try to eat it?
I'll confiscate the knife.
What happened, Father?
There are you, Qian Wei.
Your father's platelet index is poor.
Even a little cut or scratch
will cause massive blood loss.
But look at him.
As soon as your brother left,
he peeled an apple
on the sly.
I caught him in the act.
I'm no longer bleeding. I'm fine.
Stop complaining to her.
What's wrong with you?
How many times have I told you
not to eat apples for the moment?
What if your intestine
is cut accidentally?
I... I don't mean to eat it.
Every afternoon,
I peel an apple
for your mother.
Don't you know
you're sick?
Even if I'm sick, life still goes on.
I should be still a good husband.
Think about Stephen Hawking.
When he was so badly sick,
he still did scientific inventions.
I'm okay.
Never mind, Uncle Qian.
I've peeled apples for you.
Look.
Good job.
Come on. Whose side are you on?
Don't make an animal for her.
Make her an ice cream
so that she'll cool down.
She's quite bad-tempered.
When you're together,
concede to her.
Or she'll really beat you.
I've been conceding to her.
She just hasn't realized it.
What... what are you talking about?
All right, Mr. Qian.
Just this once.
Don't do it again. Got it?
Lu Xun,
after you peel the apples,
hand in the knife
to me.
Come over, Qian Wei.
Don't be too worried.
Your father thinks positively.
This is good for him.
You know, during the treatment,
not only
the medical service is important,
but the mentality is important too.
When your father thinks positively,
his body will exude
enzymes and hormones
that are good for his health.
It'll be very helpful
to improve his immune system
and organs.
Come on.
He's rather dramatic.
I can't stop worrying about him.
You always worry.
But Lu Xun can help.
Isn't it good
when he takes care of your father?
Fine. I'll leave you alone.
He... He and I are not...
Do we need some basic skills
to peel apples like this?
No matter how I try
to change the destiny,
I can't let it go this way.
(Outpatient)
Hurry.
I'm not going.
Get up.
I'm not going!
If you still force me,
I'll call the matron.
If you make me bleed,
I'll suffer.
Call the matron, then.
But you have to take the puncture.
Struggling with me
won't do you any good.
When the matron comes
and gives you a sedative,
you still have to go.
When I had the bone puncture last time,
I felt terrible.
I hear after taking
the lumbar puncture,
I have to lie flat for six hours
without moving.
The hospital gown
feels bad.
It's rough. It hurts my skin.
How about asking your mother
to bring me
my silk pajamas?
Silk pajamas?
Why don't you ask for pour-over coffee?
Don't be dramatic.
Just get up.
No, I won't.
Lu Xun.
Restrain her, will you?
I... I can't, Uncle Qian.
It's so rude of you.
I can't restrain her
when she's being rude.
I don't dare to.
I'm going to win, Uncle Qian.
Double kill.
Why don't you just kill me?
It feels so good.
What are these?
They're for you, Uncle Qian.
(Adult diapers)
Adult diapers?
You have to lie in bed
for more than six hours
with the infusion.
What if you want to pee?
I...
I don't use diapers.
I thought they were for you.
I wondered why you needed them
(Adult diapers)
when you were so young.
You won't use them?
Then will you pee in bed?
You will use them, Uncle Qian.
I can hold back the urine.
I must defend my dignity.
If my wife knows it,
I'll be ashamed.
According to Qian Wei,
this is what you pay
for your silk pajamas.
I'm sorry, Uncle Qian,
but you have to wear a diaper.
I can hold back the urine.
You can't.
I once held for 12 hours.
Sorry, but you can't do it this time.
I have to help you wear it.
(TCM Rehabilitation Hospital)
Come on.
What are you doing?
Qian Yanping!
Come down!
What are you doing?
Keep your voice down.
Don't dazzle me.
Come down quickly.
What are you doing?
Today is the wedding anniversary
of your mother and me.
She can't walk for the moment.
What a perfect chance!
I must do something.
It's our 20th wedding anniversary.
What a rare chance!
Just come down immediately.
Do you want to come down personally
or do you want him to get you down?
Give me a hand.
So, you learned
to climb the wall from him?
Hurry.
Come down.
I won't.
Be careful, Uncle Qian.
Come down.
Stop climbing.
Give me a hand.
No. No way.
Come down.
What are you doing?
Come down, or I'll call the security.
Push... Push me up.
I won't.
Just come down.
Come down.
Be careful.
Let me go home
and meet your mother.
You can't. No way.
I'll be back after dinner.
No way. Come down.
I won't.
Help me to get him down.
He won't.
Get him down.
You...
Time to test your loyalty. Hurry.
Get him down.
Take her away.
Get him down immediately!
Push me up.
What...
Get him down!
Push me up.
Done.
You can have a video chat now.
I can?
Here he is.
Hello, Uncle Qian.
Honey.
Look at them.
Good evening.
Good. Good.
Very clear.
Come on.
Why did you bother Lu Xun
when it was so late?
It's just a wedding anniversary.
It's okay if we don't celebrate it.
Never mind.
I'm glad
when you feel happy.
It's getting cold recently.
Every year when it gets cold,
you have a stomach ache
and I make yam porridge for you.
But now, I'm away.
I'm afraid you can't have a good diet.
Look.
Lu Xun and our daughter
are taking great trouble
to take care of you.
Don't keep them worried,
or they'll lose weight.
My father only
cares about his wife.
He doesn't care about me at all.
Come on.
You never said you wanted some porridge.
She's just asking for trouble.
How are you doing at home?
Take to him, Aunt.
I'll check some texts.
How are you doing at home?
(You accompany me
to the hospital every day,)
(and tonight,
you even brought the laptop)
(for my mother.)
(Thank you.)
You take care of yourself.
(You're welcome.)
Just rest assured.
(I did this so we could)
(discuss the work schedule in the club.)
Enjoy your life.
(I need to pick up my mom
from the night shift,)
(so, I was on my way there anyway.)
You... You sing me a song.
The kids are here.
(Yam porridge)
I just got up a little late,
and why is the line so long already?
How long do I have to wait?
Hello?
(I know you like to get physical,)
(but don't hit yourself.)
(Try to look straight ahead)
Here, here.
Why are you here?
I saw
your Renren post last night,
OK?
You said there would be a queue
for the ultrasound, right?
So, I set my alarm clock for 4:00
and got up to queue for you.
The doctor starts work at 8:00.
In this way, your father
won't have to wait.
Come on.
Young lady.
There's a queue here.
How can you jump the queue?
Sorry, madam.
This is my girlfriend.
No, I'm his aunt.
We are relatives.
Yeah.
Come here.
Stand here.
Just wait here.
I'll wait for you in the back.
Sorry, madam.
Sorry.
Gloves!
Or your hands will itch
after cutting the yam.
No time for gloves.
Boil for half an hour and then
put rock sugar and wolfberries.
In all my years at work,
I haven't had
my son's homemade breakfast.
Why don't we all eat
in the ward later?
Don't, Mom.
Please,
don't scare her, okay?
When you asked me
to register for a bed,
you promised
to let me see the girl.
The matron talks about her a lot.
Why can't you let
your own mother meet her?
Wait.
I've checked it for you already.
You should get married
after graduation in 2015,
and then have a baby
in the year of the Sheep.
It's a good match with your animal.
The Sheep is gentle and attentive.
And the baby can
study medicine with me.
OK, OK.
You can meet her.
Can you not
tell me that now?
I'm cutting something here,
what if I cut
my finger off?
You didn't even brush
your teeth in the morning
and you came here to talk to me.
Go clean up first.
Go clean up.
You brat!
You're just like your father!
Why can't you be like me?
Unbelievable.
Are you…?
Watch your mouth, young man.
You're not a morning person,
and that hasn't changed at all.
Scold me.
This…
I think she'll find me
quite warm.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're my aunt now,
I suppose I should
queue for you.
How's your dad doing?
His condition is basically
under control.
We're waiting for the chemo to finish
and then he can have
a bone marrow transplant.
Good.
If you need
any help later,
just let me know.
It's okay,
I can handle it myself.
Actually, I'm not
saying this or doing this
because you're Qian Wei,
or because I want something from you,
but because
I'm a man
who lost his father,
and I don't want this
to happen to you too.
This is
a video of Professor Zhong Xiuyong's
civil law lecture.
I see you have been posting
his views and memes
on Renren.
I was representing the student union
at the reception,
so I made a copy.
Yeah, right.
I forgot that Professor Zhong
was coming to our school
to give a lecture.
But the School doesn't
allow video recordings, right?
Isn't this a bad idea?
This is actually the good news
I want to tell you.
You're going to be
a member of the board soon.
The teachers just finished their review
and the public review
will be next month,
so you're not an outsider.
Take it.
Really?
What?
You think I'm lying to you?
Lu Xun.
This porridge is really good.
I've always craved it,
but my dad only made it for my mom.
When you have a wife…
Yes, let her cook it for you.
You cook it for your wife.
Wei.
You love yam porridge, right?
I saved a bowl for you.
Why are you here?
Where did you get the porridge?
Extra food from the hospital cafeteria.
The matron got it for you.
Lu Xun was asked to bring it here.
Right, Lu Xun?
What are you eating?
Some porridge.
My favorite.
Who gave it to you?
The matron said it's extra.
If you're not hungry,
leave it here
and eat it later.
Wei, have the porridge.
It's still hot. Don't waste it.
(Lu Xun made this porridge.)
(It's him all along)
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪