Your Highness
Assassin
All well-trained dead men
Only two survivors left
One dies after being jailed
only one left
Jin Yiwei
free at kisskh.me
I'm looking down on his line.
As for the New Year's Day
Records of entering and leaving the palace
Hundred Opera Troupe Singing and Dancing Artists
Craftsmen from the Ministry of Industry and the various supervisory bureaus of the inner government
A total of six hundred and forty-three
All personnel are registered
It will take some time to check
What do you think
Your Highness
Who is the real culprit is revealed
If Your Majesty and the Prince
The servant dared to say something
Can't be separated from left and right
The handwriting of the two princes
ok ok
Don't keep taking these things
Come to disturb His Highness to recover from illness
Okay ah
Afternoon has been delivered
what about her
still outside
His Royal Highness Hat
Mr. Mei
what happened last time
i am deeply disturbed
always looking for a chance
sorry to you
Meal for me
did you do it yourself
I see
meal went wrong
I'm to blame
Please forgive me
these are enough
His Royal Highness has been insomnia lately
It is not advisable to put more ginseng in the soup
Too much tonic can also cause insomnia
Yao Dianshan
how do you know
Your Highness is not sleeping well
delivered lunch
Your Highness is not finished
Only the lily jujube soup has run out
It can be seen that it is for peace of mind
Your Highness
You don't have to worry about things in the courtroom
Just take it easy
Your Highness
How dare the slaves reveal
these things
Mr. Mei
You testify for the slaves
I just stepped on that threshold
smelled blood
Your Highness is pale
The sound is also weaker than before
Still don't hold on
Yes
It seems today
I can't visit my mother
so as not to be discovered
feel good today
come to a game
Your Highness
The minister's face may be dirty
You frequently look to the minister
Naturally, the minister must be misunderstood
or I am today
extraordinarily handsome
graceful
His Highness finally smiled
Weekday ministers enter the door
Your Highness always smiles
Today since I crossed that threshold
Your Highness has never shown her face
The minister almost thought
Where did you offend Your Highness?
Shaoyuan
free at kisskh.me
are you married
Mr. Mei
let's go
The doctor has already said
won't let you get up
what about you
don't listen to him
This is just great
The wound opened again
you for
Don't let the queen be worried
still covering the wound
let others become
big hero rescue
what's the matter
Just some skin injuries
how precious
go get my book
Your Highness
Shang Food Bureau came to deliver dim sum
at your command
bring people in
when did i order
let her in
Yes
The slaves greet His Royal Highness the Prince
The afternoon meal in the palace was almost untouched
Meng Shangshi asked his servants
bring some pastries
you're awake
don't have to get up
I just came to see you
apprehensive
They said no need to be polite
are you hurt
Prince Xie
Do not
yes i want to thank you
Escort is a matter of ministers
Don't dare to say thank you to the prince
You protected the emperor for me
fulfilled the responsibility of the son of man
should be thankful
but
In the past, ministers only acted on orders
Occasionally guilty
Also looking forward to His Royal Highness Haihan
thank you so much
I didn't come to see you
came to kill you
Grandpa said
you know the military
change with military
Suppress bandits
Remarkable achievements
I thought your ambition was only martial arts
But now it seems
This room full of classics
Landscape Travel Notes
I just knew
you dabble
lofty aspirations
The emperor suspects that his ministers have poor knowledge
Order the minister to read more
Nai Hechen is a warrior
Poetry and songs are really unbearable
But find some books to fill the door
Make the prince laugh
Yes
nature
You adult
His Royal Highness
nothing more
Let's talk another day
Congrats to His Royal Highness
Why is Eunuch Liu here?
You adult
take it
The emperor bestowed upon you
death-free gold
The slaves and servants of the adults ordered to give meals
Your Majesty's decree
You are seriously injured
Free gift
Put it here, you go first
Not yet congratulations, Mr. You
a blessing in disguise
gifted
Not to mention the death-free gold medal
I heard that Prince Lian
They all came to visit
Royal gift from Emperor Taizu
The hero of the Danshu iron coupon is honorable
All died of treason and no one was spared
don't you curse me
today's day
The name of benevolence spreads all over the world
Your blood will not be shed in vain
Yes
tell a joke
Why should you be angry?
From now on, follow this recipe
Cooking for His Majesty
forgot your promise
rest assured
not poison
go
What's up
do not move
don't do superfluous
young and naive
always hope to meet one
someone who can bandage my wounds
Too bad it didn't wait
today
Just let me take care of my business for a while.
then i'm luckier than you
i waited
son
son wake up
closed one there
guilty woman
As for what crime she committed
why are you locked there
how long will it be closed
Nobody knows
I'm curious
How could anyone be in jail?
still so nosy
So I disguised as a beggar
want to see her
what kind of person
Freshly baked buns
steaming hot buns
gadgets gadgets
sachet sachet
Sugar-coated haws
when i found the world
When there are such fools
I think
no matter what crime she committed
I want to set her free
So did you see her last?
no
The food is cold
eat first
Mr. Mei
Please
free at kisskh.me
Mr. Mei
His Highness invites ministers to a small gathering
I thought it was a joke
I didn't expect His Highness to be so meticulous
prepared meals
It's Chen's favorite food
That minister was disrespectful
Your Highness
It's the food bureau that has a heart
Back to His Highness
His Highness ordered a banquet for Yushi Mei
Shang Food Bureau dare not neglect
Mr. Shui Xin has poems
Don't wait for full forest frost to ripen
Steamed for Dongting Incense
This is Dong Ting
Mr. Mei
This is made of chopped lotus
And orange leaves
with rice flour and honey
Finally, wrap in orange leaves
steamed pastries
Sure enough
The lingering scent of oranges
When I was young, I read the section on Shizi Soup
curious for a while
also took
Cooking with stones in the clear spring
The so-called spring stone gas in the book
I can't understand
It cost a lot of firewood
Mr. Mei can really joke
The reader is so arty
isn't it funny
Mr. Mei
Su Yijian was drunk in the Song Dynasty
Waking up thirsty in the middle of the night
See a pickle jar buried in the snow
drink it
I thought it was a wonder in the world
That sour soup
How to compare dragon liver and phoenix gallbladder
But that's what it said
no taste
palatable jean
The ancients eat jade drink dew
Probably the same
It's boring in this house
go outside
Yes
what are you doing
take it outside
Hidden set
take it out
slow down
what is this dish
this
This is a pigeon
This yellow croaker
Can imitate the taste of crab meat
you have to talk to me
Your Highness
have a cup of hot tea
warm stomach
Mr. Mei
Don't let His Highness wait long
how
Your Highness is angry
It's all the minister's fault
Talking with Yao Dianshan is too speculative
correct
I heard that Yao Dianshan is proficient in medicinal formulas
I happen to have something to ask
Mr. Mei is serious
There is something to command
I
Your Highness
Your Highness has been feeling unwell recently.
How can you sit in the vent?
Your Highness
let's move in
Yao Dianshan
this world
heart-healthy diet
I think His Highness is very ill.
Mr. Mei
Your Highness is heartbroken
I remember one more urgent matter
Please plead guilty to His Highness on my behalf
I'll go first
Mr. Mei
This painting is not finished yet
come back tomorrow
what are you doing
move in
Hidden set
stop
Mr. Mei
please stay
you slow down
stop running
catch her
what are you doing
give her
I heard Yao Dianshan say you are in the palace
I have always
Carry this purse with you
This is the salary the restaurant should give you
you were young
I'm afraid you're messing around
fall into theft
I've been saving for you
Now back to the original owner
I'm leaving
free at kisskh.me
Your Highness, please have a meal
you play the piano to me
Your Highness
slave's hand
I can't play the piano now
Then I play the piano, you come and listen
slaves dare not
His Royal Highness is not healed
How dare you overwork yourself
Yes
i forgot
He is also good at piano
when you want to listen to the piano
Of course someone will caress you
send her out
Yes
List
Eunuch Chen
What did your Highness mean just now?
Yao Dianshan
I don't want to blame innocent you
willing to keep silent
so don't ask
how is your highness
you don't know
How could he bear to break his heart?
I break the heart of Your Highness
what did i do
I have been with His Highness since childhood
Your Highness will always be
The look of high spirits
never saw him
so disheartened
you
you are too much
I'm too much
nothing more
That's not what I said
You're better off
His Highness ordered
let me take you back myself
please
Eunuch Chen
what did i do
Please
Sheng imperial doctor
please
Yes
what does this mean
every day
Physician Sheng will heal you
until your hand heals
Your Highness's orders have been brought to me
just say goodbye
how
guilty
why are you guilty
This girl is rude
but hit me with words
I would have put my heart to the bright moon
Who knows that the bright moon shines on the ditch
You
the word is used here
But it's not right
voila
Give me
I don't know how to draw
But it was painted so carefully
It can be seen that the other party is very affectionate.
Who is not impressed by this?
i am not impressed
you have a heart of stone
this is me
I'll leave what ruby
Emerald
emerald opal
won't stay
What the hell is this?
what is this
Yin Ziping
this purse
But for men
who is this
Zijin, give it back to me
You tell me
give it back to me
who is this man
tell me to give it back to you
give it back to me
I'll tell you again
you give me back
who is this
Zijin
give it back to me
I'll give it back to you
who
give it back to me
ok ok ok
for you
lighter
my hand
Breech birth
His Royal Highness is not healed
how can your majesty let you now
Are you going to Nanjing?
Jin Yiwei has found out
intermediary with assassin
when they arrive
People have committed suicide
But the identity of that person
very unusual
Do you remember
i was eight
Grandpa himself
From the civilian levy army avant-garde young army
follow me to practice martial arts
He was a soldier in the infantry
This is clearly a trap
How can your majesty believe
such nonsense
This man not only divides our father and son
He also managed to transfer me out of Beijing
It's heartbreaking
Your Highness, please have a meal
He is upright
strong character
However, those who are strong are easy to break
Too early to get involved in officialdom
not necessarily a good thing
I will find a way
let him out
practice for a few years
wait for him to be full-fledged
another day
Must be the pillar of the country
He has the world and the country in his heart
tend to be lenient
self-discipline
especially with family
Constraints will be too strict
I'm afraid you won't get used to it
correct
I forgot
you are so nice
how could he tell you
Your Highness
what do you mean
Aren't you going to leave the palace?
Your Highness wants to let me leave the palace
But the queen
I have my own way
nothing to do with others
Your Highness did not lie to me
but why
I haven't seen you in a long time
laugh so happy
At least he can make you laugh
Wait for your future husband and wife to follow
harmonious
do not know
Will you still remember this study?
will you remember me
His Highness said that he
Who is it
let's go
Otherwise I'll go back
Your Highness allows me to go out of the palace to marry
But no matter how good that person is
but not my sweetheart
who is your sweetheart
no one
Your Highness
This Guiqi Steamed Chicken
Angelica
And stewed chicken with astragalus
People with blood loss after illness
best used
free at kisskh.me
I know you have a bad appetite lately
can use some
Great for your injury
Said you don't care about me
Your Highness has misunderstood
It's a prescription prescribed by Imperial Physician Sheng.
we are just
Just make meals
Your Highness
Sheng Taiyi knows
Your injury has not healed
It is best to take the medicine with meals
Therefore, today ordered people to bring medicinal food
This Sheng Yin
so confused
Mingming told you to prepare meals
But ask someone to send it again
The slaves retire
Ali
you step back
your highness
you don't want to say
i don't force you
anyway
I can't bother you for a few days
I'm going to Nanjing soon
Your Highness
your injury is not healed
Don't overwork yourself
This is the father's order
This is the fault of the prince
It's obviously my father who is suspicious of me
why is it my fault
Your Highness wishes father and son reconciliation
You should let go of the barriers
Sincerely to the Emperor
show your sincerity
you thought i didn't try
every time
Father will take me
Rejected thousands of miles away
perhaps
It's that His Highness used the wrong method.
well done
Hidden set
can i today
go with you to deliver meals
When was the Shang Food Bureau so unruly?
a small meal
I also want to enter the Qianqing Palace
don't quit
Souji Zen
Meng Shangshi is slightly infected with wind and cold today
Can't go to Qianqing Palace to deliver meals
I just want to help Fang Dianshan
It's time to deliver
His Majesty
this dessert
From Lin'an City in Southern Song Dynasty
Made with cheese and cane sugar
Oysters are often called abalone
so this oyster-shaped snack
abalone
This porridge is good
The slaves are in the fire room
Cultivated chamomile seedlings for porridge
Refreshing and appetizing
of course i know
This is the taste of hometown
Nanjing calls this chrysanthemum brain
eat as soup
You recently
That's a lot of gain
The last time was the reckless servant girl
Your Majesty's forgiveness
father emperor
Your Highness be careful
It's all unintentional
i don't blame you
no
Your Majesty forgives the slaves
The slaves are grateful
The slave is listening to the doctor
From the Shangyuan Banquet
His Majesty was frightened
dizzy all the time
This reminds me of chamomile seedlings
Can cure dizziness headache
That's a dare
freak out
The slave is really frightened
been hiding in the corner
trembling
saw later
The imperial concubine is also beside
That's relieved
hurry up
rescue
protect the emperor
His Majesty
Concubine Guo asks to see you
not see
Yes
I'm going to the school this afternoon
Bring dinner there
Yes
father emperor
Aren't you going to set off for Nanjing?
why haven't you moved
son prepares meal
Let's eat together
no need