=Please Don't Spoil Me=
=Episode 6=
Hoeing in the paddy
under the mid-day sun.
Sweat dripping to the soil
underneath the plant.
Stop!
(Lan Xin Palace)
Who knows that the meals in our plates,
every morsel of them
comes with toil and pains.
I awake light-hearted
this morning of spring.
Everywhere around me
the birds are singing.
Why do they keep
repeating the first half?
Where's the other half?
I awake light-hearted
this morning of spring.
Everywhere around me
the birds are singing.
Greetings, Eunuch Niu.
You are...?
Niu De Yi, at your service.
Greetings, Concubine Rong.
Eunuch Niu, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Your Highness, what...?
There's nothing much for me to do
here in the Cold Palace.
I've read a few poems,
so I asked them to recite with me.
Sorry you had to see that, Eunuch Niu.
Your Highness, you're too humble.
The poem I heard just now,
"Hoeing in the paddy
under the mid-day sun."
Although the words are simple,
the meaning is profound,
wonderful and extraordinary.
But this "Everywhere around me
the birds are singing.",
is there a second half?
Eunuch, you're right on time.
I just thought of the other half.
Listen to this.
I remembered the storm
that blew in the night,
and I wonder how many
blossoms had fallen.
What do you think?
Oh, my.
I awake light-hearted
this morning of spring.
Everywhere around me
the birds are singing.
I remembered the storm
that blew in the night,
and I wonder how many
blossoms had fallen.
The first half is enjoying the spring,
and the second half
is cherishing the spring.
Love and cherish.
Cherishing the spring
is loving the spring.
Wonderful!
I have a few more poems inside.
If you're interested,
you can take a look at them.
How wonderful!
These are what poems should look like.
This is what food should look like.
Eunuch, we should be heading back.
Oh, Your Highness,
I didn't realize I took up
so much of your time.
What a sin that is.
That's okay.
If you don't mind,
you can come over whenever you want.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Next time I drop by,
I won't come empty-handed.
(Beautiful mountain view)
That's not right. I won't be able to
stay alive in the Cold Palace
for a hundred days.
Yan Yi Yi was banished to
the Cold Palace on June 1st.
On September 10th,
the Yan family was beheaded.
(Yan Da Hai)
Yan Yi Yi was killed in the Cold Palace.
But the day of my time-traveling
was June 1st.
I didn't drug Qin Yu that day.
The matter was then
delayed for a few days.
Today is June 5th.
Book Officer, come out!
(99 days 11 hours 37 minutes 18 seconds)
You've been in the Cold Palace
for 12 hours 23 minutes.
The time remaining is
99 days 11 hours 37 minutes.
What if I end up being killed
in the Cold Palace
without reaching a hundred days?
Then that's game over.
You would cease to exist in both worlds.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
(I cannot just sit and wait for death.)
Fu Ling, get me a brush and some ink.
What did you say?
You mean
Concubine Rong is eating and
sleeping well in the Cold Palace,
and has even assembled a poetry group,
chatting away with Niu De Yi?
Your Majesty, I saw it with my own eyes.
Everything I'm saying is true.
Are you sure she's that capable?
If you said she could subdue
a few palace maids and eunuchs,
I'd still believe you.
Writing poetry?
She doesn't even know how to read.
What a joke.
Your Majesty,
I heard it very clearly.
I even made a copy of it.
Your Majesty, take a look.
(Chu River has become five.
Where does the dry land go to the soil?)
Chu River has become five.
Where does the dry land go to the soil?
What rubbish is this?
Wei Liu eats it for nothing.
You can pick apricots and eat it.
Such nonsense.
How is this poetry?
Your Majesty,
every single word here
was heard with my own ears.
It is correct.
How pretentious.
Continue observing her.
If there's anything new,
report to me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(To my dear parents)
(Respectfully, your daughter)
Help me send this letter.
You must hand it over
to my parents personally.
Do you hear me?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Have a taste.
Are you blind?
Was that a thief?
I knew you didn't have the guts
to steal from me.
(To my dear parents)
Why is it you again?
You've bumped into me twice already!
You're doing this on purpose!
Oh, no!
The letter!
Thank God.
(Yan Residence)
Stop turning in circles.
Have you even thought of a plan
to save our daughter?
Your daughter messed up so badly.
What can I do about it?
My daughter?
Is she not your daughter?
Yes, yes, she's my daughter.
Then hurry up and think of a way.
If all else fails,
let's send some money.
When other families' kids
make a mistake,
that's what they usually do, right?
Yi Yi made His Majesty angry.
Do you think his Majesty
would care for the little
money you have?
You...
You yelled at me.
You yelled at me!
I... I didn't!
You're really something, Yan Da Hai.
You can't think of a way.
All you know is to vent
your frustrations out on me.
Now that I can't save our daughter,
I don't want you anymore!
Calm down, my dear, calm down.
Now is not the time to cry.
We have to think of a way
to save our daughter.
My dear,
it's my fault.
Stop crying, stop crying.
Okay?
If all else fails,
I'll go and beg Her Grace.
We're still relatives after all.
Consort Li is
Her Grace's niece.
You're such a distant relative.
What use is that?
This... This won't work,
and that won't work either.
Then you think of a way!
I have a way!
♪Listen to the sound of tides♪
♪They are saying I do♪
♪The setting sun is listening
to your whispers♪
♪I have told you too many of my secrets♪
♪I am being too sweet♪
♪The whole galaxy is shining for you♪