Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs
BILL RED, HONDA RESEARCH,
JIN SEONGHO OF PLANNING TEAM
SONG WONKYUNG: UNTITLED
[beeps]
[screen beeping]
[pop-up message chimes]
[Dr. Song moans softly]
[sighs]
MAY THE DECEASED REST IN PEACE
SPACE AND AERONAUTICS ADMINISTRATION
[somber music]
[rustling]
[Wonkyung]Jian.
Look there.
Do you see all those dark spots?
It's called "The Silent Sea."
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
[screen beeping]
[pop-up message chimes]
[dramatic music]
[theme music]
THREE STORAGES
[alarm beeping]
[gasps, sighs]
[Soohyuk] Captain, we should refill
our life support systems.
[automated voice]Warning.
Recharge life support system immediately.
[all breathing heavily]
-[beeping continues]
-[door opens]
[beeps]
-[beeping fades]
-[all breathing heavily]
[Heesun] That feels so much better.
[breathing heavily]
I thought I was going to die for a second.
[Doc Hong] How's everyone doing?
[Gisu] God, damn it.
[Captain Han] Begin the pressurization.
[whirring]
AIR LOCK AIR PRESSURE,
AIR LOCK GRAVITY LEVEL
[thrilling music]
[gasps]
-[yelps]
-[power shuts off]
[all panting]
[tense music]
[Captain Han] Now we head
into the station.
Let's turn the power on first.
Yeah. If we can get to the command center,
that's where we'll find
the main power supply.
[ominous music]
[breathes heavily]
[beeps]
If anyone feels dizzy
or nauseated, tell me.
-[Heesun] Okay.
-My feet have been numbed
since the crash.
[breathes heavily]
What the hell were they even doing
in here, anyway?
Oh, shit. What the hell is that?
-[Heesun] What is it?
-[Soochan] Oh, my God.
[Gisu] Right here.
Everyone, stand back.
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
-[Captain Han] Officer Gong.
-[Soohyuk] Yes, sir?
Take a reading here.
I want to know what happened to this man.
[Soohyuk] Right away, sir.
[Captain Han] E1. Bring the scanner here.
[scanner whirs]
[Soohyuk]
We've had reports of attempted breaking
since they shut the station down.
By the look of his gear,
I'd say he's a mercenary.
I don't think we could identify him.
Does the body look odd
to anyone else here?
It looks to me like he drowned.
Do you think he drowned up here?
But that makes no sense at all.
I didn't say that's what happened.
But you see all that foam.
There, around his mouth and nose.
[Doc Hong] Plus,
his lungs are swollen too.
Those are common signs
when the cause of death is drowning.
We'll do an autopsy.
So we can find out for sure.
I'm jealous.
I mean, I realized that he's dead,
but at least the guy didn't die thirsty.
[snickers]
[sighs deeply]
Let's keep moving.
-[Soohyuk] Yes, sir.
-[Soochan] Yes, sir.
[ominous music]
SATELLITE HUB TARGET REACHED
ENTRY COMPLETE
[doors thud]
[footsteps]
[E1] That dead guy,
who do you think sent him?
[Doc Hong] The US? Russia?
[Soochan] Well, maybe he's working for RX.
[E2] Isn't that
a huge transnational corporation?
[Heesun] Resource Exploration for, uh…
I forgot the rest.
[Taesuk] How could anyone?
For Space Mining
and Planetary Development.
[Heesun] Yeah. RX for short.
[Taesuk] That's right.
[Heesun] Seems like every country on Earth
has a problem with them.
They're like the resource mafia.
[approaching footsteps]
This place is huge.
It just keeps going on forever.
What do you think they were doing in here
with all this space?
[Doc Hong] Something they don't want
to tell us about.
This station must cost a fortune.
Hold on a second.
What's wrong?
[Doc Hong] You good?
-The radiation level.
-[Soochan] Isn't it weird?
That's a normal level of radiation, right?
Same as the other areas.
Then I guess this is not the area
where radiation leaked.
I'd expect it to vary,
but not as low as this.
It's strange.
Unless the government report wasn't true?
What do you think?
We don't actually know
what kind of radioactive substance
killed the crew here.
Or how that substance leaked
or from where.
They haven't told us anything
about what happened.
Are you suggesting that accident
wasn't caused by a radioactive substance?
That's what the number suggests.
And that body we saw,
I don't think he died in an explosion,
or from overexposure.
[approaching footsteps]
Is there a problem here?
The radiation level,
looks like the reading is normal.
[scoffs]
Faulty detector.
Mine's the same.
I don't think the gear's mistaken.
How much far to the command center?
The main staircase is just ahead.
We go down one level, and there we are.
Let's go.
Getting there is our priority.
[Dr. Song] Captain Han.
We have to investigate further.
We should examine that body.
We should determine
the exact cause of death.
-Didn't you hear what I said?
-[Dr. Song] I did.
But if the radiation didn't kill him,
that means the cause of death
is uncertain.
You think we should just ignore it?
I decide what is or isn't important.
[sighs]
[Gisu] Great. Another hallway. I love it.
[Soochan] Okay.
Let's see if this works.
CLOSED
OPENED
[Soochan] Bingo!
Wow. Get a load of that view.
[Gisu chuckles]
-[Soohyuk] Check over there.
-[E2] Yes, sir.
-[Soohyuk] You go this way.
-[E1] Yes, sir.
[E2] All quiet over here.
[E1] Same here.
[sighs]
We're clear, sir.
[suspenseful music]
[Gisu] So there's a fuse box
in here or what?
[Heesun] There must be.
[Soochan] I'll activate
the main power supply.
[Soohyuk] E1, E2, check out the equipment.
-[E1] Yes, sir.
-[E2] Yes, sir.
[Gisu] Now this is something.
No wonder so many people
are dying to get in here.
[Gisu sighs]
[power actives]
[system chimes]
[sighs]
[machines beeping]
[eerie music]
[Taesuk] Captain.
The communication system is still down.
The rescue team will see
if the power's on.
[Captain Han] But it'll take some time
for the ship to arrive.
Focus on our mission.
Yes, Captain.
The station's life support system
seems to be working okay.
Radiation's fine too.
[Soochan] Everything looks normal.
Even the area
that's supposed to be contaminated.
[Gisu sighs]
So that thing about a filter breakdown
was a big lie.
Why would they shut this place down
if everything was working fine, huh?
It's like I told you already.
Director Choi and everyone else
at the SAA don't know anything about this.
As far as you can tell,
the station is safe?
According to the readout, it is.
Doctor, can we take our helmets off?
Uh, I guess in theory, you could do it.
-[Heesun] Hey! Hold on! Wait!
-Wait a second, we don't…
[laughs]
[sighs]
Looks like everything's normal after all.
If we're going to do
this mission properly,
then we should investigate the facility
for the cause of the accident.
Our mission is to locate those samples,
not to investigate.
You can take off your helmets now.
You… You sure?
Yes, Captain.
Soochan, make sure
everything's up and running.
Right away, sir. I will activate
the air purification system first.
[Captain Han] Remove your helmet.
[helmets clatter]
[Captain Han mutters]
AIR PURIFICATION SYSTEM, PREPARING
[system whirring]
AIR PURIFICATION SYSTEM, ACTIVATED
[tense music]
PURIFICATION INITIATED
[system whirring]
[clattering]
[indicator beeps]
[machine beeping]
Have you been breathing all right?
My throat's been sore since we got here.
I'm trying not to breathe at all.
[laughs]
And how's that working?
It would work better if I wasn't talking--
Soochan, stop goofing off
and focus on the mission.
I don't want you screwing up.
-All right, big brother, I get it.
-I'm not covering for you.
Just relax for a second, huh?
I can do my job fine, Officer.
[Soochan] You're acting just like Dad.
[sighs]
[beeping]
[trilling]
You may notice,
level one authorization
is required to enter these red areas.
[Soochan] As you can see, this schematic
doesn't have any information
on what those facilities are.
Which means that most
of the crew members here
wouldn't have known
what they were either, right?
Just keeps getting weirder.
That's not the weirdest part.
The areas that they supposedly shut down
due to extreme contamination,
were mostly all these
restricted level-one facilities.
I mean, that's some coincidence.
And where are the samples?
There are three storage areas
which should still contain intact samples.
The closest one to us
is there in Storage Two,
north of the command center.
STORAGE 2
[pensive music]
[beeps]
Supporting facilities
surround the command center
as well as the main lab nearby.
There are a total of eight gates
in Balhae Station.
To avoid the contamination,
in order to reach the machine room,
it would be safest if we were to head
through the main gate.
[Captain Han] We'll split
into three groups.
Doc Hong, E2, and I
are going to Storage One.
Taesuk, Ssun, Soochan,
and E1, Storage Two.
Officer Gong, Dr. Song, and Gisu,
Storage Three.
Dr. Song?
Right.
When you locate the sample,
check the thermoregulator first.
Its capsule needs to be kept
at a very low temperature.
If this is the case,
the status screen
on the top will be lit up green.
[Dr. Song] However,
if you see a red light,
you don't want to touch it at all.
Teams should stay in communication.
And if the capsule you find
seems unusual in any way,
let Dr. Song know immediately.
[team members] Yes, sir.
[Heesun] Why did he just clap?
-[Soochan] No idea.
-Hey, Soochan.
Yes, Dr. Song?
The crew here on this station,
they all had biometric chips, didn't they?
Yes, they did.
[machine beeps]
Can we access them from the main system?
That could be a simple way for us
to learn the victims' identities
and locations.
I gave it a try already.
It seems like the accident
disabled all of them.
[Soochan] Why do you ask?
No reason.
[Dr. Song] I'm just curious.
We can't let the family members
know anyway, so what's the use?
Oh. See you later.
[Gisu groans]
Let's find these things and go home, guys.
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[ominous music]
I've been in the Moon and Mars,
none of these places are fit for humans.
I don't mean to speak ill of the dead,
but come on!
Hwang must have been a sick man
to survive so many years out here.
I mean, what is there even to do?
It'd drive you insane.
[Gisu] There's one reason,
and one reason only
anybody ever ends up here.
And that's to get yourself
better water privileges.
Even Captain Han.
Sure, he acts
like this big hero for the SAA,
but the only reason he came back
was to get water.
Hey, you know he just handed in
his resignation, right?
But Ms. Choi got him back
for this emergency.
She suckered him in like everyone else
for a higher water class.
Guess you know him well
the way you're talking.
Yeah. I know him better than anyone.
[Gisu] Star student at the academy,
top of his class.
The guy's a legend.
Sure, he's good at what he does.
He's not an idiot.
But you've seen
what working with him is like.
He's so sensitive.
Never listens to anyone.
Wait, is it this way?
I mean, what family doesn't lose a kid
in this day and age?
[gurgles]
[exhales deeply]
One out of ten children born after
the Great Drought dies within five years.
At least his daughter
was able to make it out a bit longer
-'cause he's a hero.
-Okay, enough.
I don't need to hear about any of that.
Well, that was kind of rude of you,
wasn't it?
Hey, Lieutenant Ryu,
I heard you used to be a pilot.
Yeah.
But then you immediately switched
to engineer, is that right?
That is correct.
I was feeling suffocated at headquarters.
Oh, you were feeling suffocated?
And that's why you're here now, huh?
-Fresh air on the Moon?
-[chuckles]
-That's amazing.
-Right? Who doesn't?
It took Soochan there about three,
four years to become a chief engineer.
Hey, it's not like it's an impossibility.
I could've done it if I really wanted to.
-[shrieks]
-[Heesun] What?
[Soochan] What is that?
[gasps, sighs]
[Heesun] Oh, shit.
Why the hell would anyone
draw something there?
Let's move on.
[Soochan] Didn't they have
anything better to do?
[Soochan sighs in relief]
It's just a drawing. That's all.
[heavy breathing]
Guys, wait up.
[Heesun] What the…
Why won't it open?
Soochan, we can't open the gate.
I need you to check it out for us.
The system doesn't show an issue.
[Soochan]It could be
a mechanical problem.
[E2] We could try forcing it open.
Let's do it.
One, two, three.
[grunts]
[door thuds]
One, two, three.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[Captain Han] One, two, three.
[grunting]
[tense music]
[Mr. Hwang]It must have been tough…
for you to join this mission.
[cats meowing, slurping]
But remember,
we're doing this for the next generation.
Mr. Hwang, does the name…
Luna, mean anything to you at all?
It's just…
something Ms. Choi mentioned
during my meeting with her.
I find it hard to believe
she'd mention Luna at all.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
Luna is Balhae's data storage.
[suspenseful music continues]
[gasps]
[exhales in relief]
What? Were you scared?
[scoffs]
[Gisu] Is something lurking down there?
[E2 grunting]
[Doc Hong] Hold on a second.
Captain, I think there's something…
stuck in the door.
I can't tell what it is.
[screams, panting]
[gasps]
[Doc Hong panting]
[Doc Hong whimpers]
[bodies thud]
[Soochan]Captain, did you get it open?
Captain?
Is something wrong?
We just found more bodies.
They appear to be
the station crew members.
[breathing heavily]
[beeps, buzzes]
[clicks]
Everything all right, Captain?
[Captain Han]We're fine.
We'll take a scan and keep moving.
[door buzzes]
Wha… Why won't the door open?
[groans]
It's 'cause nothing on this station
can be easy.
Dr. Hong, can you show me
what it looks like over there?
[Doc Hong]Sure, give me a second.
[device whirs]
[eerie music]
[Doc Hong] It looks like
they were trying to escape.
Based on the scene, this area
had an emergency shutdown.
Probably right after the accident.
[Heesun]That doesn't track.
According to the report, everyone onboard
died before the shutdown.
Yeah, you're right.
I wonder what the hell
really happened here.
Report back when you find the sample.
We're heading over to Storage One soon.
[Dr. Song]Dr. Hong
I'm not seeing
any burn scars on these bodies.
[Doc Hong]Right.
They're just like the first body.
They all look like drowning victims.
I have no idea what could've caused this.
[Dr. Song]Captain Han,
if conducting an autopsy now
is impossible,
we should stop by the infirmary
so we can check out
the crews' medical records there.
[Captain Han]We've discussed this
already, Doctor.
Well, the situation has clearly changed.
I'm simply sharing a professional opinion.
What exactly has changed?
We've discovered more bodies.
All of them bearing suspicious features.
[Dr. Song]If we can analyze
a tissue sample in the infirmary,
we might be able to learn something,
or find a lead.
We're not here to satisfy
your personal curiosity.
What do you mean?
You heard me.
[glass clanks]
[classical music playing]
Have some water.
To be quite honest,
I'm a little surprised.
This can't be easy for you
after what happened to your sister.
I know it's late,
but you have my word
we'll get their bodies back.
And then Balhae Station
will be permanently shut down.
[sighs]
In any case…
it's better if during the mission,
the others don't find out that you're a…
bereaved family member.
Surely you understand.
Mm.
Yeah.
If they know,
it would be a burden on them.
Mm.
But if you're still concerned about it…
why would you ask me to join the mission?
[classical music playing]
[E2]We reached Storage One.
[door chimes]
[Soochan] Hey, that worked.
CLOSED
OPEN
[automated voice]Be advised
Now opening Storage Two.
Be advised. Now opening Storage One.
[Soochan] Entering Storage Two.
Wish us luck.
[Heesun] So, what's this?
All the slots are…
That's a ton of red lights.
[sighs]
Someone emptied the place out.
Captain, we're searching the room now,
but we don't see any samples.
It looks like someone's been here already.
Let's see if there's any still intact.
[E2] On it, sir.
[beeps]
The other teams didn't find any samples.
So it's up to us now.
[suspenseful music]
They didn't find anything?
Wait.
[shrieks]
-[Heesun] Over here.
-[Soochan] What is it?
[Heesun] There's another dead body.
[exhales in frustration]
[Soochan] What's up? You good?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's okay.
[Soochan gasps]
[Heesun] Looks like another crew member.
[Soochan] The radiation level in here
is normal too.
Well, that's another person who didn't die
because of the radiation.
[sighs]
This one's empty too.
Every single one is empty.
Damn it.
We should keep looking.
[E1] Okay.
[Soochan] Hey, what's this?
Never seen one of these before.
Huh?
[foreboding music]
[Heesun] Nothing but empty capsules
over here.
We're not going to find it.
[Gisu] Hold up.
I just detected an unknown biosignal.
[Soohyuk] Is it a malfunction?
No, it's not. The sensor's working fine.
[Soohyuk] Whatever it is, it's by itself.
I don't think that that's one of us.
[Gisu] Mm-hmm.
That means there someone here
we don't know.
I'll go and investigate myself.
You two wait here until I get back.
[sighs]
What the hell are we really doing up here
in this cursed space station?
Do they really expect us to do our job
without knowing
what we're really up against here?
[Gisu sighs]
Dr. Song.
I think you should go.
What do you mean?
You know…
to the main infirmary,
like you talked about.
'Cause I've been thinking about it,
and you're exactly right
about what we need to do.
We need to know what really happened here
before we're all a bunch
of dead bodies too.
There's no other choice.
They don't want us to know anything.
I'll make up something
to tell Officer Gong.
But you should hurry.
This is probably your only chance.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[grunting continues]
[water trickles]
[groans]
I'm sorry. Whoever you are. I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about, Soochan?
-[Soochan] Just one second.
-[Heesun] You found one?
Ah, shit.
-It's empty.
-[exclaims]
All that for nothing.
Let's start heading back.
Yeah, sure.
[E1] All right.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[Dr. Song panting]
[suspenseful music]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[pants]
[exhales sharply]
[Gisu] Huh?
[grunts]
[clatters]
[sighs]
Shit, they're empty.
They're probably all empty.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
This station is cursed.
I bet my life on it.
[sighs]
Goddamn it.
[grunts]
This just isn't my day.
Where did you go?
[Gisu grunting]
[sighs]
[groans]
How'd you get so far back?
All right, you win, baby.
Daddy has new batteries.
Stay still.
[grunts]
[eerie music]
[gasps]
Oh, shit!
What the hell?
[breathing heavily]
[panting, grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[grunting continues]
Huh?
[panting]
[tense music]
[closing theme music]
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.