Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs
[unsettling music]
DS. Data storage.
[unsettling music continues]
[Mr. Kim sighs]
Years ago, I had a dog.
Its name was Umul.
[Mr. Kim] It died in the Drought.
Why are you here?
[sighs deeply]
It's not on the door. It's on the floor.
What?
The sign. The one at Balhae Station.
It's on the floor.
[foreboding music]
[theme music]
CAUSE OF DEATH
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[pensive music]
[Soohyuk over earpiece] Dr. Song?
[breathing heavily]
-[beeps]
-Yeah?
Lee Gisu is not responding to us.
Are you with him now?
Uh…
He's currently on standby
at the front, and I'm…
taking a look at the storage.
What about the signal?
I'm searching the area,
but there must have been
some kind of error here.
[signal pulsating]
[sighs]
[Dr. Song breathing heavily]
[Soohyuk] I'll be returning shortly.
Please join Gisu right now.
Please do not…
act independently.
Okay, got it.
[breathing heavily]
[Gisu grunting]
[groans, panting]
[grunting continues]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[soft chuckle]
Well…
I guess that's it.
[unsettling music]
[exhales deeply]
Team Two going to command center
right now.
[Soochan breathing heavily]
[Captain Han over earpiece]
Chief Gong, where are you?
[Soohyuk] Looks like an error.
I'm on my way to check the storage.
I'll report back.
Where's Dr. Song?
[Soohyuk over earpiece] She's coming now.
[sighs]
Let's go to Storage Three.
Yes, sir.
[wheezing]
[labored breathing]
[ominous music]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music continues]
[Dr. Song panting]
Gisu.
[grunting]
[panting]
[relieved sigh]
Shit.
[yelps]
[Gisu screams]
[ominous music rises]
[foreboding music]
[breathing heavily]
Gisu.
[sighs]
[Gisu choking]
[gasps]
[loud thud]
[shrieks]
Gisu!
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
[eerie music]
[eerie music continues]
[Dr. Song shuddering]
[unsettling music]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[Soohyuk] Dr. Song.
[eerie music]
[Dr. Song breathing heavily]
[sighs]
The cause of his death
is cervical spine fracture.
He died on the spot.
He fractured his skull, right arm, ankles…
He has fractures all over.
Even if he had fallen from the ceiling,
it wouldn't have had
an effect on him like this.
Which means he didn't die from the fall.
Do you believe Dr. Song?
In any case,
the state of his body
seems to be matching her story.
[thrilling music]
[zipper rasps]
I'll handle this.
Return to the command center.
[Doc Hong] Okay.
Don't let your guard down at all.
Yeah. I got it, Captain.
[breathes heavily]
[receding footsteps]
[pensive music]
Why was the co-pilot in the storage alone?
Why didn't you report him
to us immediately?
Are you trying to accuse me?
When the radio's back on,
I will have to report back
on why I lost two crew members
in under an hour.
I need to know exactly what happened.
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
I was just…
I was searching the premises.
Sorry, it's my fault for not reporting--
Don't make an excuse.
I'll know once I check your bodycam.
[beeps, clicks]
[footsteps receding]
[door whirs]
Forget the plan.
All we're going to do now is move corpses.
[sighs]
When I was a kid, I'd always look up
to the moon and make wishes.
-But this is one eerie place for sure.
-[door whirs close]
And what's going on with Dr. Song?
What exactly is she trying
to accomplish, huh?
All she did was make us nervous as hell
over a cause of death and all that,
and then she roamed around on her own.
Who does she think she is
to create so much trouble?
[Taesuk] She wasn't trying
to cause trouble.
She was sharing her opinion
as a scientist.
[Taesuk sighs]
I wasn't talking to you.
[Heesun] Now think about it.
-We should all work together as a whole.
-[Soochan breathing heavily]
She nitpicks everything,
and it's bringing us down.
Yeah, true.
We didn't know there wouldn't be
any intact samples left in storage.
Our captain wouldn't give up
on us, though, right?
[Heesun] We'll end up searching
the entire station.
[chimes]
SONG JIAN
[Dr. Song panting]
[Dr. Song] Gisu.
[Gisu yelps, screams]
Did you just see that?
He was dragged in by something.
[tense music]
[Gisu choking]
[Dr. Song shrieks]
Gisu!
[Dr. Song whimpering, shuddering]
Wait, look right here. Now.
That's a sample.
And the capsule is intact.
It looks like it was kept
in some kind of solution.
Wait. Right here.
[keyboard clacks]
[tense music continues]
[Taesuk] This is Balhae Station.
Control, respond.
-This is Balhae Station.
-[monitor beeps]
[Heesun sighs]
Our comms got smashed,
and the stations don't work.
What now? What do we do?
I don't think there's any problem
with the internal system.
Might be related
to the radio tower outside.
[stutters]
Would they send a rescue ship for us?
Of course, they will.
I'm sure they're trying
to figure it out as we speak.
[sighs]
Goodness.
[laughing, sighs]
Look at him. He's asleep.
[laughing continues]
Soochan!
[Heesun] Hello?
Man, what is with you?
-[Soochan wheezing]
-Hey.
-[Soochan grunts, wheezes]
-[Heesun] Are you okay?
You, you… You good?
What's wrong with your face, Soochan?
Are you sick?
Hey!
-[retches]
-[gasps]
[grunting]
-[Soochan retching]
[Soochan moaning]
[tense music]
[clanks]
What could it be?
It didn't seem human to me, sir.
But it took the sample.
If that creature was aware
of the sample's value,
then it is most likely human.
Then I think it looks like
it's probably an intruder or something.
Like that dead mercenary at the gate.
We'll catch it and find out.
It looks curved at the end.
[unsettling music]
The passage continues.
Should we go after it?
It couldn't have gotten too far away.
[Heesun over earpiece]
Captain! Captain, where are you?
It's Soochan.
Soochan just collapsed!
[foreboding music]
[Soochan retching]
[shuddering]
[Heesun] I, uh… What now?
Doc Hong, where are you?
I'm coming right now!
Do not come into contact with him!
Put on your hazmat suits and wait for me.
Do you hear me?
[suspenseful music]
[breathing heavily]
[rustling]
[groans]
[Heesun] What's taking her so long?
Don't worry. She'll be here soon.
-[Doc Hong] Get out! Get out of here now!
-[Heesun] Doc Hong!
-Stay outside!
-What's happening?
[Doc Hong] Get out!
-[Taesuk] Come on.
-[Heesun] Damn it!
[tense music]
[Soochan moaning]
What's gonna happen?
[gasping]
-[Doc Hong grunting]
-[Soochan groaning]
[gagging]
[tense music continues]
[Doc Hong yelps]
[Soochan grunting]
[Soochan wheezing]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[all panting]
-[Heesun] Captain!
-[Captain Han] What happened?
-[Soochan moaning]
-[water spritzing]
-[moaning continues]
-[water spritzing continues]
-[Doc Hong grunts]
-[Soochan moaning]
Soochan.
-[Soohyuk] Soochan!
-[wheezing]
Soochan, come on, hang in there.
[croaking]
[Soochan panting]
-Uh, Officer, you can't go in.
-No. Let me go.
[Soohyuk] One second. Will you let me go?
[Soochan grunts]
Soochan! Hang on.
Soochan! Hang in there.
Come on, hang in there.
[Soohyuk] Soochan, I know you'll make it.
Come on, hang in there. Please.
Come on, hang in there.
[somber music]
[Doc Hong] Soochan,
stay with me now. Soochan!
[exhaling deeply]
[Doc Hong] Soochan!
Stay with me! Soochan!
[bubbling]
[eerie music]
[Doc Hong] Soochan!
Doc Hong.
[Soohyuk] Doc Hong.
What's happening in there?
Soochan!
Hang in there, Soochan!
Come on, hang in there, Soochan!
[exhales sharply]
[somber music]
[automated voice]
Air purification system activated.
[metal clanking]
[Doc Hong breathes heavily]
[Captain Han] Doc Hong.
Have you seen this before?
[Doc Hong] No.
I've never seen anything like this.
I think…
he has to stay away from us.
[breathing heavily]
We can't afford
to lose anyone else right now.
We should move him to the main lab.
[sighs]
And I'll do an autopsy
once I have him there.
Should I talk to Chief Gong about this?
[sighs]
I'll talk to him.
[Doc Hong exhales sharply]
[automated voice]
Air purification completed.
[footsteps receding]
[somber music]
I'm sorry.
We are…
gonna have to do an autopsy,
you understand?
[somber music continues]
[whimpering]
[sniffles]
[sighs]
Dr. Hong.
Yeah?
Is there a way to find out everything
that happened in the other mission?
What are you saying?
There's data storage…
somewhere in this station.
[door opening]
So how long will this take?
The autopsy itself
will take one to two hours.
But it will take me a while
to find the exact cause of death.
I'll inspect the medical records
and the other bodies.
Very well.
What else do you need from me?
I just need your permission
to conduct an investigation.
I thought you didn't need my permission.
You've been doing whatever you like.
After everything that's happened,
don't you get it?
We can't get any answers
if we don't ask questions.
[clacking]
[zipper rasps]
It's gonna be tough.
But we still have a mission to do.
-You have to remember that.
-Captain…
Can we just call it quits?
We don't know why Soochan died
or what it was that killed him.
The culprit got away
through ventilation shaft INP-07.
It passes through
all the key facilities of this station.
Soohyuk and E2, you'll search with me.
Taesuk and Heesun,
get us connected at any cost.
We'll call for backup
after all of that is over with.
Yes, Captain.
[footsteps receding]
[exhales sharply]
It has to be tough on the captain as well.
But for now,
we've got to do our jobs
as best as we can.
[Heesun sighs]
[suspenseful music]
-[switches clicking]
-[lights humming]
[wheels rattling]
[suspenseful music continues]
[door whirs]
[wheels rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
I have to take a look at the main board.
Comms continue to be down.
[both sigh]
[Taesuk sniffs, sighs]
Is that real meteorite?
They look like rocks, right?
But these ones are real.
Superstition.
[Heesun] Meteorites fall on Earth,
but they don't get harmed.
So we wear these as a bid to our survival.
We put our trust in the universe.
[scoffs]
Also Soochan had one of these.
I survived.
Why couldn't he as well?
[Taesuk] Why would you believe
something like that?
-Huh?
-[Taesuk] Think about it.
If you die, you die.
If you live, then you live.
There's no fate in the universe.
[sighs]
[Soohyuk] The machine room is the closest.
The dormitory is down the hall.
I'll take the lead. E2, you stay back.
Yeah, I got it, sir.
-[breathing deeply]
-[footsteps thumping]
[squelching]
[unsettling music]
[squelching continues]
[Dr. Song] There are logs
up until before the accident,
but I see no leads.
In that case,
don't you think they really died
because of the radiation?
[suspenseful music]
SONG WONKYUNG, LEVEL 1
[suspenseful music continues]
[chimes, beeps]
[sighs]
I can't watch this.
[E1] Found anything yet?
Some of the files have been locked up.
Uh-huh.
[E1] You can't look at the records
of the higher-ups.
Yeah, I guess so.
Showing the same symptoms,
on the same day…
-It happens quickly.
-[E1 sighs]
And has a high death rate.
[gasping]
I think we should gather as much tissue
as we can from the other bodies.
So I'll be able to trace back
to when Soochan's symptoms broke out.
Are you saying you're going
to go look at the bodies?
I can go alone.
You can stay here with Dr. Hong.
[sighs]
You cannot do this on your own. I'll come.
Can I leave you here for a minute?
[Doc Hong] Mm-hm. See you later.
[inhales]
[exhales deeply]
[torch clicks]
[unsettling music]
[footsteps thumping]
[signal pulsating]
[unsettling music continues]
[Soohyuk] Captain.
[suspenseful music]
[sighs]
[gadget beeps]
[signal pulsating]
[E2] Captain.
I see someone approaching from the front.
[tense music]
Are you sure?
-Yeah, they're ahead of us.
-[signal beeping]
[approaching footsteps]
[dull thudding]
[rapid beeping]
It just passed by us.
[muffled footsteps]
It's moving forward, back towards us!
[E2] To the left. To the left.
[tense music rises]
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[squelches]
[E1] He didn't look too well.
He was sweating profusely,
and he fell behind.
[E1] He would space out
and just look at the wall.
He was acting pretty weirdly.
[E1] Hold on.
I think I was in contact with him too.
This isn't contagious or anything, right?
[Doc Hong over earpiece]
Dr. Song, I need you in here for a second.
[Dr. Song] Why?
I'm still collecting the samples.
[Doc Hong] It won't take long.
[E1] Sure thing.
I'll be there in a couple of minutes.
[Doc Hong] I don't need you.
I just need Dr. Song, please.
You can stay and do your work.
[E1] Well, I don't have much
to do here, so I'll…
[Dr. Song] I'll be back shortly.
[E1] Dr. Song!
-[beeps]
-[door whirs]
-Please come back soon!
-[hurried footsteps receding]
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[panting]
[tense music]
[beeping]
[sighs]
[panting]
[tense music continues]
[tense music rising]
[sighs]
[exhales heavily]
[tense music fades]
[panting]
[E1] Dr. Song.
What's going on with you?
Nothing. Let's go.
Dr. Song, is this really contagious?
I'm feeling itchy.
[grunting]
[pants]
[sighs]
What's in here?
There's no indicator that
it's one of our facilities, Captain.
It's located right next
to the machine room.
-[Taesuk over earpiece] Captain.
-[chimes]
Are comms back up?
[Taesuk] I found a way to fix it,
but things aren't looking too good.
[Captain Han] Got it.
Head back to the command center.
-Yes, sir.
-[breathing heavily]
-[footsteps receding]
[E1] Everyone here
came down with the same sort of sickness.
How else would they have ended up
like this, do you know?
[E1 sighs]
[clattering]
[E1 breathes heavily]
[unsettling music]
[unsettling music continues]
[door slides]
Here I am, Dr. Hong.
[sighs]
I thought we should look into
as many things as we can.
[door slides close]
The results came out just as I expected.
I found mucus
surrounding the bronchial tubes,
and, uh, there were signs of water
seeping through his organs.
His body was completely filled with water.
So…
he essentially drowned to death?
Yeah.
[Doc Hong] There's no external damage.
He's all clean.
That means the water
must have come from the inside,
and it happened so suddenly
that his bronchial tubes are swollen.
Other bodies shared similar symptoms.
[Doc Hong sighs]
I've never seen anything like this before.
[chuckles]
Where did all that water
come from, anyway?
Have you ever seen anything like this?
[sighs]
[pensive music]
There's nothing here.
What do you mean there's nothing there?
There is nothing abnormal.
There are no viruses or bacteria,
or toxins related to disease.
The crew was all in very good health.
[machine beeping]
[machine beeping, whirring]
[suspenseful music]
Look at this.
This here is Soochan's blood.
[Doc Hong] Look at that right there.
[Dr. Song] In the blood?
What could it be?
There's a problem with the digital unit
connected to the communications tower.
We're going to need someone
to fix the equipment about the same time
someone else edits the protocol,
so then we can reboot the system.
[Taesuk] But I'm the only engineer
on this mission,
and I can't do all this by myself.
Is this the unit you mean?
Yeah. But there's a problem with it.
All the station was up, everyone would use
the main elevator to get to the unit,
but it's out of order,
so we need to find another way.
The station was neglected
for five years after the accident.
That's probably why
there are some problems.
The only way to get there
is to go out to the gate,
then grab the elevator rail
and climb down. But that's just not--
We try setting up an anchor
and get down that way.
It won't be too hard.
No, you can't do that.
It's better to wait
until the rescue ship comes.
-It's way too dangerous.
-I'll do it.
Tell me what I need to do there.
Will you be all right?
I have to reach Director Choi
as soon as I can.
[ominous music]
[footsteps receding]
[sloshing]
[door opening]
Did you find the root cause?
We're analyzing Soochan's blood
at the moment.
Once comms are up and running,
I'll make a reinvestigation request
to the accident
on behalf of Director Choi.
Only if we have enough samples, though.
So to do that, we need to find out
how Soochan died.
Yeah.
[Doc Hong] Captain.
Are you really gonna go?
Yeah.
[door beeps, slides open]
Captain Han, wait.
There's something I'm concerned about.
It's the intruder.
It did not try to hurt me.
How can you be so sure of that?
[Dr. Song]
It's called "critical distance."
When animals find intruders,
they watch them at first.
Then they attack them
when they come into a certain distance.
That's why it's very important
that you don't get too close.
On top of that,
it moves by using the shafts,
and escapes because it's always
a step ahead of us.
It seems like they're familiar
with this entire place.
Are you suggesting it could be a survivor?
[suspenseful music]
[sighs]
The government would have known
if one of the crew had survived.
It's been five years. It seems impossible.
How could there be a survivor?
It's not so impossible.
The radiation turned out
to be completely normal.
So if they rationed their food
and their water,
there's a chance they'd survive.
And tell me why haven't they informed us
of any of this before?
If this wasn't an intruder,
there'd be no reason to steal the sample.
If they survived…
they'd be welcoming us, not attacking.
[suspenseful music continues]
[whirs, trills]
[beeping]
[chimes]
[foreboding music]
[tense music]
[breathing deeply]
[tense music continues]
[tense music rising]
ELEVATOR GATE A
BALHAE LUNAR RESEARCH STATION
[closing theme music]
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.