Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs
CONDOLENCES
MAY THE DECEASED REST IN PEACE
SONG WONKYUNG: UNTITLED
[beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
[computer whirring]
[pop-up message chimes]
[Dr. Song] Luna.
1,783 FILES CONTAINING "LUNA"
UNIDENTIFIED CONFIDENTIAL FILE
CLASSIFIED
CHECK YOUR SECURITY CLEARANCE LEVEL
[sighs]
[pensive music]
[theme music]
SECRET STORAGE
What could this be for?
Why don't we go and find out?
E1 and I will climb down first
and check it out.
You stay here.
Call us if something happens.
Copy that.
[grunts]
[ominous music]
[leaves rustling]
What is this?
[E1] How could there be
so many plants here?
[E1] It's a storage facility.
[Heesun] What's with
all the plants in here?
It's a jungle.
Are we sure it's safe for us
to just walk in here?
[Soohyuk] This facility
wasn't on the station's blueprint.
[Heesun] Check out the size
of some of these. It's incredible.
[E1] You're right.
I've never even seen plants
grow like this back on Earth.
[Heesun] Why did they try
to keep this place so secret?
How did they even manage to do all this?
I mean…
[gasps]
…I can't believe my eyes.
[Soohyuk] It looks like
there are several storage rooms.
[sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music]
[E1] We only have
to bring back one of these, right?
Look at how many there are.
We did it!
[Heesun chuckles]
And look, all green lights.
That… that means they're all
in good condition, doesn't it?
[laughs]
[Doc Hong] So that's what happened.
They hid everything down here.
Hey, what's this?
It's likely…
this facility is independent
from the rest of the station.
Right here.
[Doc Hong scoffs]
Some lunar water escaped.
How does all this grow
with this little water?
It doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't matter how it happened.
We'd have all the water
we'd ever need with this stuff.
Only if we can keep it under control.
-Retrieve the sample.
-Yes, Captain.
-Go and secure the premises.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
-E1, Heesun.
-Yes?
-This way.
[Doc Hong] They're too many to count.
[ominous music]
[whirring]
[container beeps]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[sighs]
[wind whooshes]
[device whirring]
Move in. Keep your guard up.
We're still in danger.
Yes, Captain.
[beeps]
Officer Gong, how's the other storage?
Similar situation.
I'd say most samples are intact.
[E1] There's a ton over there.
We'll need a rover to carry them all.
[Heesun and E1 laugh]
[Heesun] Why don't we just get out of here
and go home?
-[rustling]
-What was that?
-Wait.
-Hold on.
[footsteps approaching]
[suspenseful music]
[Heesun gasps]
What? What is that?
What's wrong? What is it?
Shit! Get it!
[Heesun grunts]
[Soohyuk] E1, get out of the way!
-[E1 screams]
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
-[E1 screaming]
Wait here.
[E1 screaming]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[ominous music]
[device beeping]
[breathing shakily]
[gunshot]
[Dr. Song gasps]
[whimpers]
[suspenseful music]
[device beeping]
[Captain Han] You good?
[Heesun] Yes. Yes, sir.
[gunshots]
-[Captain Han grunts]
-[Doc Hong gasps]
-[Captain Han panting]
-[gunshots]
[gasps]
[Doc Hong whimpers]
Get back inside!
[gunshots]
[tense music]
-[Heesun] Captain!
-[gasps]
[Soohyuk] It's headed your way, E2!
[E2 grunts]
[panting]
[breathing heavily] Captain Han.
We have to get out of here. Right now!
Evacuate!
Samples. I'll grab the samples.
I will. I'll run and get them.
You should go first.
What about E1?
We have to go. Come on, run.
-No. Wait!
-Let's go.
Come on.
[panting]
[automated voice] Warning.
Thermoregulator anomaly detected.
Warning. Thermoregulator anomaly detected.
[breathing heavily]
Warning.
-Thermoregulator anomaly detected.
-[Captain Han] Get over here!
-[hurried footsteps]
-[water sloshing]
[water trickling]
[ominous music]
[device beeping]
I need help!
[Soohyuk] E2.
-E2!
-I think his leg is damaged.
[Doc Hong grunts]
-He needs medical attention.
-[Heesun] What?
[Doc Hong] Come, help us out.
[all breathing heavily]
There's blood in his lungs and pleurae.
His pulse is at 136, BP is 75 over 43.
I need to operate. The gauze.
Scalpel.
[Heesun sighs]
[Dr. Song] His BP is way too low.
Check the medical kit over there.
Bring me all type B blood bags.
Two bags here.
That's not going to be enough.
We need someone to give.
We need more type B blood.
I'm a type O blood. Take it from me.
[sighs]
[Doc Hong] Are you dizzy?
No, I'm okay.
Let me know right away
if you feel dizzy at all.
Yeah.
She ripped his arm right out.
Then she crawled all over the ceiling,
like a…
[exhales sharply]
Bad enough with poison water around,
and now a monster decided to show up?
It was probably the same creature
that killed Gisu.
Yes. I think it was.
But… but why is she following us
around the station?
Is she trying to kill us?
I think it's the lunar water.
Huh?
I think that's why she killed Gisu,
and why attacked us.
Whenever we find lunar water,
she shows up.
Perhaps she's after it as well.
Do you think…
it's possible that she's a survivor?
[Heesun] A survivor?
But how can she be a survivor?
I don't think a kid
could survive long on their own.
She was a kid. We all saw.
It was behaving like a child
[Dr. Song] A child who wanted
to keep what's hers.
Who didn't want it taken away.
I know it sounds odd, but…
a child behaves like that.
From her perspective, we're the intruders.
[girl breathing heavily]
Just like the first time,
her attacks have come
from the ventilation shaft.
You can get pretty much anywhere on board
by using this main shaft INP-07.
We're connected, Captain.
Whenever you're ready.
COMM STATION
RECEIVING SIGNAL
Did you find her?
[Captain Han] She escaped
and we lost track of her.
And the samples?
[Captain Han sighs]
Let's end this before we lose
anyone else from the crew.
You'll get your samples.
I already told you,
this operation will become a failure
if anyone else gets the sample.
[Director Choi] Kill her if you have to.
She can't be allowed to go free.
Also, the samples you took,
get it back from her.
She's only a kid.
What?
It appears the intruder is a young child.
She was also wearing a lab coat.
What's your point?
Is there any possibility
that she survived the accident?
[laughs]
Come on.
It doesn't have to be more complicated
than it should be.
Just focus on what's important.
[Director Choi] Forget about who she is.
It doesn't affect your mission.
You know…
sometimes, I…
I dream of standing in the rain.
And when I wake up
from that wonderful dream,
I feel indescribable pain,
facing our horrible world.
We must make sure it rains…
once again.
That's the world I dream of.
A world where water flows endlessly.
We must…
must make that world a reality.
[Director Choi] Go.
I'll send you backup very soon.
Just hold on a little longer.
[computer chimes]
PHOTOS
[Dr. Song] The director got to you,
didn't she?
Tell me the reason why I can't go
back down there to investigate.
It's too dangerous to go back in.
For all we know, the lunar water
is still multiplying.
I'm close to an answer.
And you want me to give up now?
I want you to survive this.
[sighs]
We can't lose another.
Once, there were 87 people
aboard this station.
Not one of them survived.
If we don't know what we're taking back,
we could end up losing everyone.
The answer won't matter.
Whatever we do, they'll take it back.
And that kid with it.
All the more reason to risk getting
what we need while there's a chance.
We know just how dangerous
lunar water could be.
Understanding it is our responsibility.
I don't care if you don't trust me.
I'm not doing any of this
for personal reasons.
[Soohyuk] Captain, the search party
is ready for your orders.
Roger that. I'm heading out.
If you're really so deadset…
just make sure to bring Doc Hong as well.
If you discover any new information,
report back as soon as you're able.
Okay.
[door opening]
[sighs]
I'm nearly at Storage Three.
[Soohyuk] We're almost in position
in the hallway.
Get into the shaft and take a look around.
-[Soohyuk] Yes, sir.
-I'll start searching here
-and move toward you.
-[Soohyuk] Yes, sir.
[Captain Han grunts]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
It'll take a while.
If you feel it up before we return,
call me and I'll head back.
Yeah. You got it.
Are you guys sure that you'll be okay?
Reasonably sure, yeah.
[scoffs]
Why? Any last words?
You really think…
the lunar water research data is there?
[sighs]
I'm praying that's the case.
[Doc Hong] I really am.
I'll be back.
Okay.
[door closing]
[ominous music]
[door chiming]
[beeping]
[Captain Han exhales sharply]
[Heesun] Oh, shit!
Those creepy drawings again.
They keep showing up everywhere.
[sighs]
This kid's a real artist.
[Soohyuk] Captain.
We've reached the shaft entrance
on our end.
The cover is still intact.
I don't think she escaped through here.
Hey, Soohyuk.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[Heesun grunts]
Oh, shit. Shit!
[breathing heavily]
[Doc Hong] Outside looks fine?
[Dr. Song] Yeah.
[Doc Hong] Let's go.
[beeping]
DATA BRICK SEARCH
LEVEL 1
[computer whirring]
[sighs]
SEARCHING DATA BRICK
[sighs deeply]
[Doc Hong] Your sister worked here.
She must have talked about it.
[Dr. Song] Actually, I had no idea
she had been on this station.
I found out about it from the news,
like everyone else.
I heard you two grew up all alone.
She kept this from you?
Well, I guess back then, something else
was more important to her than I was.
[sighs]
[keyboard clacking]
There was this one time,
she tried calling from inside the station.
SONG WONKYUNG
[Dr. Song] It was right
before the accident.
[ringing]
I wonder if I had…
taken her call and heard
what she had to say to me…
would that have changed anything at all?
[Heesun puffs]
Captain, we found a new passage
from the hallway.
This area of the station
is not on the blueprint either.
But it looks like…
this passage runs all the way
to the dorms.
We should expand our search
and check out the dorms as well.
[Captain Han] Okay. Be careful.
[Heesun] Do we have to?
[Captain Han breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
[keypad clacking]
It worked. It's open.
SEARCHING DATA BRICK
DATA BRICK SEARCH COMPLETE
HARD DISK EMPTY
What?
This cannot be possible.
[Doc Hong] There's nothing on here.
You think there was some kind of glitch?
Someone erased the data on purpose.
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
-[loud thud]
-[Heesun gasps]
Oh, jeez.
Captain.
[Soohyuk exhales in relief]
What are you doing here?
What happened at the dorms?
[Heesun] I think I finally understand
how people can die of fright.
This is very odd.
From the blueprint, this passageway
should lead us straight to the dorms.
I know. But it seems more like
we've just been circling the same area.
[Soohyuk] Exactly.
It's like a game of hide-and-seek for her.
[Heesun] She knows exactly where we are
and always manages to avoid us.
She knows her way around here
much better than we do.
[Doc Hong] Who could have deleted this?
How and why?
[Doc Hong sighs]
[sighs]
[clanks]
Didn't I say to call me?
Don't worry. I feel okay.
Did you find any data?
What are you doing with the samples?
I thought you were supposed
to join the search?
Oh, there's new orders.
We decided to regroup
at the command center.
[Doc Hong] Mm.
There could be a security issue
if we just leave these out here.
So I'm moving them
to the safety of the command center.
Why?
You heard this from Captain Han?
You said as much yourself,
the monster seems to be
after the lunar water, just like we are.
Don't worry. We're just being careful.
Just in case
anything unexpected were to happen.
Hold it.
I'm the one who decides
where the samples should go.
And we are going to keep that water
right where it is.
[scoffs]
I guess you would know.
Be sure to call me if anything happens.
Are there any more passages?
Something we missed or anything?
I'm not sure. I'll check again
once we reach the command center.
But why is this girl…
This monster…
Whatever you want to call it.
Why do we have to find her?
We have the sample.
We should just go home.
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
[shrieks]
[Doc Hong gasping]
[breathing heavily]
[Doc Hong] Captain.
Captain!
The girl, she's here.
You have eyes on her?
Dr. Hong, respond.
[Doc Hong breathing heavily, shrieks]
[ominous music]
[panting]
Captain Han.
[breathing heavily]
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[grunts]
No, stop!
[breathing heavily]
[tense music]
[Captain Han] Dr. Song, step away.
Wait a second.
Don't come any closer.
[breathing heavily]
[tense music continues]
[tense music intensifies]
[closing theme music]
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.