Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs
Come here and help.
[Soohyuk] Come here and help.
[automated voice] Warning.
Internal pressure loss
detected in landing module.
-[Soohyuk] Hey, are you okay? Let's go.
-Oxygen levels unstable.
-Warning.
-[Soohyuk] Be careful.
Internal pressure loss
detected in landing module.
[Soohyuk] E1, check the equipment.
[Doc Hong] I think he's wounded
internally, so be careful.
-[Soohyuk] Easy.
-[Doc Hong] Can you breathe normally,
Mr. Hwang?
Warning. Internal pressure loss
detected in landing module.
Oxygen levels unstable.
-[Soohyuk] E2, check the equipment!
-Warning.
-[E2] Yes, sir!
-Internal pressure loss
detected in landing module.
-Oxygen levels unstable.
-[Dr. Song groans]
[alarm beeping continuously]
[Doc Hong] Careful.
He might be bleeding internally.
Mr. Hwang, can you breathe?
[Heesun] Captain.
It looks like all engines
are down right now.
Where are we?
About 7.6 kilometers
northwest of Balhae Station.
[machines crackling]
And the fire alarmed?
[Heesun] Shit. The system's down.
Son of a bitch! Damn it.
Nothing fucking works!
This fucking shit.
Looks like we're about to lose power.
-All right. Send out an SOS.
-Yes, sir.
Control, this is Lieutenant Ryu Taesuk.
Do you read?
[static]
-[Taesuk] Control, do you copy?
-[grunting]
[Taesuk] This is Nuri 11. Control!
Control, do you copy?
-[Dr. Song] Come on.
-[Taesuk] Control.
-[groans]
-This is Nuri 11. Control!
Dr. Song.
Dr. Song, are you all right?
[pants]
Doc Hong, how is he doing?
-[Doc Hong] Hang on.
-[Mr. Hwang grunts]
One of his ribs is broken.
[grunting]
[grunts, panting]
All I can do right now
is try to keep him comfortable.
All right. See if you can move him.
-[Doc Hong] Turn him over.
-[Soohyuk] E1, E2,
check all the equipment.
-Yes, sir.
Can you move it all?
[Mr. Hwang groans]
[Doc Hong] Okay. Hang on.
Communications are down.
The whole system's crashing.
[gasps]
[monitor beeping]
[grunts]
Water. There's a leak.
[Dr. Song panting]
[groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music]
BALHAE LUNAR
RESEARCH STATION
[reporter 1] The average annual rainfall
hit another low.
Rivers in major cities around the world
are revealing dried-up riverbeds.
And sea levels are falling,
posing challenges for desalination plants.
The World Water Resource Council predicts
the world's water will be reduced by 40%
in the next ten years.
[reporter 2 in French] According
to the National Institute of Statistics,
infant mortality rate
hit an all-time high this year.
Among the main causes mentioned
are various infections and diseases
caused by the consumption
of contaminated water.
[reporter 3 in English]
Both governments and private corporations
are investing heavily in vertical farms,
which can drastically reduce water usage.
This can prove a timely development
in the midst of a drought induced
global food shortage
which many eagerly anticipate
strong rebounds
in the international agricultural
supply chains.
Illegal pet-keeping remains
a growing problem in many communities.
The government has offered to waive fines
and provide free euthanasia
during this amnesty period,
but only a small minority
has utilized these options.
[reporter 4]
Meanwhile, the Fair Water Distribution Act
was rejected yet again in the Assembly.
As inequalities in water access intensify,
so do demands for the abolition
of supply regulation,
but there's no end in sight.
-[man] Abolish the regulation!
-[crowd] Abolish! Abolish!
[man] Abolish the regulation!
[crowd] Abolish! Abolish!
[man] Fair access to water!
[crowd] Fair access! Fair access!
[crowd chanting]
[man] Abolish the regulation!
[crowd] Abolish! Abolish!
RED MEMBER, LEE JINSEOK
WITHDRAW WATER
WITHDRAWING
BLUE MEMBER, KIM JAEMIN
[somber music playing]
[Jaeyoung] So, I heard your water grade
got bumped up to Class B.
Congratulations, Mr. Kim!
[Mr. Kim scoffs]
It's not exactly a point of leap.
But the researchers here
are at the top of their game.
[Jaeyoung]
Good to hear. What's Dr. Song like?
[Mr. Kim scoffs]
Scientist.
She's an egghead, condescending,
full of herself.
So why exactly do we need an ethologist?
She used to be a hotshot astrobiologist.
Then why did she quit
and get into ethology?
No idea.
But there was probably more money in it.
[Jaeyoung] Have you met her before?
[Mr. Kim] Just once. Five years ago.
What's that?
[tiger purrs]
[growling]
[Dr. Song] Mr. Kim.
You got new glasses.
You used to wear brown horn-rimmed.
Wow, you have an amazing memory.
That was five years ago.
So what are you doing here?
Your work in astrobiology
has been getting a lot of attention
in the scientific community.
It's very impressive.
Did you come here to ask me
about the Mars Project, then?
I'm not interested
in astrobiology anymore.
Ah, I see.
[Dr. Song] The universe is…
Well, it's barren.
I came to see you this morning
because we have an important mission
and we need an expert astrobiologist.
Director Choi also recommended you
personally for the position.
Director Choi did?
So, what's the mission?
I can only give details
if you choose to accept the offer.
Has any scientist ever fallen for that?
I think you might change your mind
once you hear about the destination.
Where is that?
Balhae Station.
[mellow music playing]
CONDOLENCES
MAY THE DECEASED REST IN PEACE
SAA, SONG WONKYUNG
[footsteps approaching]
[dog slurping]
You must be thirsty.
[chuckles]
SPACE AND AERONAUTICS ADMINISTRATION
[automated voice] This memorial
is to remember the 117 crew members
who lost their lives five years ago
at Balhae Station.
A lunar station
built by the Republic of Korea SAA.
Through independent efforts…
-Dr. Song?
-…the SAA was able to construct
a station on the moon.
Yes?
I hear you're going to Balhae Station.
Who are you?
Han Yunjae, the captain.
I see.
I'm Song Jian.
I've heard a lot about you.
You got here early.
Yes, I wanted to make sure…
I saw this.
[Captain Han exhales sharply]
[automated voice] This memorial
is to remember the 117 crew members
-who lost their lives five years ago…
-Things are still…
-…at Balhae Station.
-…pretty gloomy here.
A lunar station
built by the Republic of Korea SAA.
Through independent efforts, the SAA was…
[Captain Han] Why don't you reconsider?
Reconsider?
Going to Balhae Station.
You should reconsider.
[men laughing]
[Heesun] Captain!
Sir Han!
Hey.
[sighs]
This always breaks my heart.
Shouldn't they at least
put their names up there?
[Heesun] Exactly. You'd think
they'd honor the members of the crew.
Long time no see, sir.
Oh. Ryu Taesuk.
Oh, this is Lieutenant!
The famous toughest nails commando?
Oh. I got a good feeling
about this mission.
-Nice to meet you.
-[Heesun] Same.
I'm Gong Soochan. Pound it!
-Oh, right.
-[Soochan laughs]
Nice to meet you. I'm the Top Gun of SAA.
-Kim Sun. It's a pleasure.
-[Taesuk] It's a pleasure.
[laughing]
What?
What kind of guy
nicknames himself Top Gun?
Shut it. He couldn't hack it in the army.
[chuckles]
Well, he got dumped last week
because he's so butt-ugly.
-It wasn't because I'm ugly.
-Why then?
Hi there, I'm Eun Jiyoung.
I was just assigned
to this mission as a co-pilot.
-[Soochan] Oh.
-Good to meet you.
I'm Kim Heesun, the Top Gun of SAA.
Oh, yes. I already know who you are, sir.
How do you know me?
[chuckles]
[Heesun] Oh, man. I'm really
looking forward to this mission.
[beeps]
[Doc Hong] Ooh. The golden card.
Wow.
I've definitely heard about it.
But never seen it before.
[water pouring]
Yeah.
Are you nervous?
It's scary at first.
But I'm sure
you'll get used to it soon enough.
When you're in space,
everyday out there
feels like a year on Earth.
So, a little advice,
the way the crew members look
is actually really important.
Think about it.
You're stuck in a tiny spaceship,
staring at the same faces every day.
Without any eye candy,
you just go insane.
[laughs]
I'm the team doctor for this mission,
Hong Gayoung.
Just call me Doc. Doc Hong.
-Nice to meet you, I'm--
-Oh, I know, Dr. Song.
Oh, yeah. You're quite a celebrity.
Can I be honest with you?
No.
[exclaims]
You'd rather keep your distance. Hmm.
So, so, so… Dr. Song or just Jian?
-[scoffs]
-[Doc Hong chuckles]
Ah. Well…
Dr. Song.
You're a gold member,
let's just go with that.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Ooh.
Here come the higher-ups. Hello.
It has been a while, Dr. Song.
Balhae Station
has to be closed permanently
because of the radiation leak
five years ago.
Your mission is to retrieve
an important sample
before we close the station for good,
and you return safely to Earth.
Once you land on the Moon,
you will have only 24 hours
to complete the mission.
The sample we need you to retrieve
is in this capsule right here.
[Mr. Kim] The capsule was designed
to maintain a very low temperature
to protect its contents
from harsh environments.
If the capsule is in good condition,
the retrieval should be no problem at all.
However, if you find
even the smallest defect
either on the outer shell
or its thermoregulator,
you'll have to be extremely careful.
Yes, Dr. Song?
What exactly is the substance inside?
Why does it have to be transported
under such low temperatures?
Well…
That information was lost in the accident,
we do not know for sure.
[Director Choi] Please continue.
[Mr. Kim] Uh, we believe the samples
were left in three separate locations.
We know that the accident
left the station in total disarray,
but we don't have any data
on whether or not
the samples were damaged.
That being said,
we don't need a large amount.
Our main goal
is to safely retrieve at least one sample.
Don't you think this is a little vague?
I mean, you really can't give us
any more details on the samples?
We're not some delivery service
just picking up a package.
It's like any other mission.
We just have to do as we're told.
The SAA itself was given
very limited information.
We share in frustration
at the lack of details.
If we do not know
what this dangerous substance is,
how are we going to retrieve it safely?
Or is it that the mission
is supposed to fail us all?
[Director Choi]
This is why we need you, Dr. Song.
Dr. Song…
it seems like you think
we're deliberately hiding information
that could be crucial
to the success of the mission.
But like you,
we really don't know anything.
That's why we sought out
a very talented astrobiologist
to help guide our crew.
Or…
did we have the wrong idea?
Captain Han is in charge of the operation,
but when it comes to the sample,
your decisions will take precedence.
So, keep that in mind.
5 YEARS AGO
You'll never have to worry
about water again.
Rather than a government check,
consider this one
as a gift from your sister.
[scoffs]
GOLD MEMBER, SONG JIAN
[somber music playing]
[Dr. Song] Go on.
[dog whining]
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
Captain Han.
Does this happen on all your missions?
It makes no sense
to restrict vital information.
Are you always that passionate?
There's less than a 10% chance
our crew will survive this.
If you're concerned about their safety,
you should reduce the uncertainty
as much as you can.
Uncertainty is everywhere,
in space and on Earth.
So from now on, you just want me
to keep my mouth shut and do as I'm told.
Sounds a little ominous.
Aren't scientists people who find a way
no matter what?
[chuckles]
Are you sure you still want
to join the mission?
You just questioned my work ethic.
I am now.
[chuckles]
I will ask for your opinion
if and when I deem it necessary.
[Doc Hong] Oh, wow.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Why did you bring so much stuff?
Do you have your whole lab in there?
[laughs softly]
Well…
I have no idea what I'm going to need.
[grunts]
[shutter beeps]
Gosh, look at everyone hard at work.
Reporting for duty.
I'm Lee Gisu, the co-pilot.
[Gisu] Nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
[laughs]
[Soochan] I've never seen him before.
Why'd they switch her out?
[Heesun sighs]
I can't believe they treat us like this.
Do you think they ever heard
of teamwork here?
I mean, we're not just
little mechanical parts.
Come on. They can't just switch out
a pilot right before we take off.
We dock in five minutes.
Do you want him gone?
No. I guess I'll make it work.
[grunts]
You look really nervous, Miss.
Relax.
[Gisu chuckles]
Have something sweet to help you relax.
[Doc Hong] What are you doing?
Go do your job.
Okay? Mr. Nosy,
if you bring us down hard, get ready.
I'm going to throw up
on the back of your head.
[chuckles]
-Have we met before?
-No.
You look familiar.
Uh, I just have one of those faces.
[chuckles]
Nice to meet you.
Oh, Dr. Song.
I heard EHSRC gave you
a really good water grade.
So, what did they give you? B?
No way, is it higher? Class A?
[Doc Hong]
What do you care what her grade is?
What difference does it make, anyway?
We all get bumped to Class A
after the mission.
[groans]
Come on.
We might as well be family now.
I was just trying
to get to know her a little.
Don't be so harsh on me, Doc.
[Dr. Song] It's like…
you're all going on a road trip.
Mm. Yeah. We're all just pretending.
What else can we do?
We're already on board.
[Soohyuk] All crew members,
please put on your helmets.
[man] Nuri 11. One minute to docking.
[Heesun] Preparing to dock.
Beginning docking procedure.
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
[control tower]
Countdown. Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, main engine, ignited,
four, three, two, one.
Vernier engine ignited.
[breathes nervously]
[Heesun] Control, this is Nuri 11.
We have entered the orbit as scheduled.
[control tower]
Nuri 11 is in orbit as scheduled.
[Heesun] I now have control.
Switching to autonomous navigation system.
[control tower] Copy that.
Autonomous navigation confirmed.
Flight orbit and speed, optimal.
When do we enter the Moon's orbit?
It's scheduled for 9:06 a.m.
We will be out of touch with Control
for two hours.
There's a meteor shower.
Ask for the revised data when we're back.
Keep your eye on things.
[Taesuk] Yes, sir.
[Mr. Kim]
Mr. Hwang made a substantial contribution
to the construction of Balhae Station.
And stayed there for a long time
as a part of the research team.
He has decided to assist us
as an advisor on the current mission.
Anyway, have you guys noticed that
Mr. Hwang is almost a little too quiet?
Has anybody heard him talk? I haven't.
Is that just how he is?
Yeah. I don't know.
But he talks less than you.
[laughs]
I mean, he's the only one here
who has been to Balhae Station.
[Soochan]
I just have a million questions for him.
What really happened there?
I really want to know. Should I ask?
Yeah, I will.
[Heesun] Hey, Soochan.
Don't do it.
Trust me.
I really don't think Mr. Hwang
or Director Choi know more than we do.
[Doc Hong] I can hear you.
Just like everyone else.
[sniffs]
[bolts clanking]
[alarm beeping]
[automated voice]
Anomaly detected in spacecraft exterior.
-What's going on here?
-The system… One second.
[Soochan] It's the docking system.
The bolt won't last
if we get into the landing orbit.
[Gisu] Oh, shit!
If the bolt falls off,
they'll slam into the engine.
[Taesuk] We can't reach SAA control.
Communication should resume in 20 minutes.
[Soochan] The bolt is shaking like crazy.
-It's going to come off.
-[Gisu] Damn it!
How long until we land?
Uh, we have seven minutes
until landing orbit.
[Soochan] It's going to come off.
Release the module.
-[Gisu] What?
-[Heesun] Sorry?
If we do that,
we'll change the point of entry.
We have to save the landing module
before it's too late.
Release it.
[Captain Han] We have to land
no matter what.
Everybody, make sure
you check your seat belts!
[Soohyuk] Brace for impact!
[rumbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[automated voice]
Switching to module release mode.
Releasing.
[bolts clanking]
[Heesun] Ignite main engine!
[Gisu] Damn it!
The main engine won't ignite!
[grunts, whooping]
-[laughing]
-[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Prepare for thrust control.
[Heesun grunting]
Igniting thrust control!
[grunting, screaming]
[Heesun]
At this rate, we're going to crash!
Hold on tight!
[Gisu] Please work! Come on!
[Heesun] Brace for impact!
[Gisu screaming]
-Motherfucker!
-[Heesun] We're crashing!
[Heesun grunts]
[all screaming]
[Captain Han]
The spacecraft is starting to tip.
We need to get out of here.
[alarm beeping]
Let's go.
Put it down.
[Captain Han grunts]
[grunting]
[all grunt]
[grunting continues]
[Captain Han] Hold on.
[whimpers]
[man shouts]
Watch out!
[Soohyuk] Is everyone okay?
[glass cracking]
[woman gasps]
[Heesun] Hang on tight!
-[screams]
-Dr. Song!
Hold on, Dr. Song. Don't let go.
-[Captain Han grunts]
-[Soochan] Captain!
[Dr. Song gasping, panting]
[whimpers]
[sobs, breathes heavily]
[grunting]
[Taesuk]
The satellite communications are down.
We can't reach SAA.
[Heesun] They probably saw the whole thing
back on Earth.
[Doc Hong] Mr. Hwang, it's going
to be tough for you to breathe
because your fractured rib
is pushing down on your lung.
Can you move it all?
[Mr. Hwang] Yeah. I'm all right.
[Mr. Hwang breathing heavily]
Coming through.
How far are we from Balhae Station?
We're about 7.6 kilometers away.
[rumbling]
[tense music playing]
I just got the chills.
Me too.
[Soochan]
We're not astronauts without a spaceship.
What the hell do we do now?
[Heesun] What do you think?
Hold on until the rescue ship gets here.
Move on to Balhae Station.
[Soohyuk] Let's move.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Soochan] Captain, do you still think
we could finish the mission
in 24 hours now?
[Heesun] Forget about the mission.
We don't even know
if we can get to the station…
before we run out of oxygen.
[Gisu] You'll definitely get there
if you keep your mouth shut.
[Captain Han] Once we get there,
we'll contact control and reassess.
[all breathing heavily]
[Mr. Hwang grunts]
[E2] Mr. Hwang.
[Mr. Hwang groans, breathing heavily]
Are you all right, Mr. Hwang?
Dr. Song, you can't stop here.
Just keep going.
Dr. Song, we can't stop here.
[Captain Han] Get moving.
[Mr. Hwang breathes heavily]
-Huh?
-Yeah, I can.
[Mr. Hwang grunting]
[all breathing heavily]
[panting]
Is that…
Balhae Station?
It looks a lot bigger than I expected.
We should hurry.
If we stay at this rate,
we could run out of oxygen.
The southern side is on a downhill slope.
It might get us there faster.
[Doc Hong] Captain!
[Gisu] Are you sure Mr. Hwang's
going to make it to the station?
[E2] Hang in there, Mr. Hwang.
We're almost there.
[Mr. Hwang breathing heavily]
[groans]
His blood pressure keeps dropping.
Bone fragments have punctured his lungs.
We have to get to the station.
Water…
[breathes heavily]
What did you say?
[grunts]
Water…
Water?
[Mr. Hwang breathing heavily]
Water…
He's out of water.
Bring some water.
[Soohyuk] Here you go, sir.
[grunts]
Mr. Hwang!
[monitor beeping]
Don't…
[panting]
The water…
Don't…
[static beeping]
[somber music playing]
[Doc Hong] What do we do now, Captain?
Keep moving.
We'll take him with us on our way back.
Yes, sir.
[Captain Han] Let's go.
[pensive music playing]
[all breathing heavily]
[alarm beeping]
[automated voice] Oxygen level at 1%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
Oxygen level at 1%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
[rapid beeping]
[all breathing heavily]
[automated voice] Oxygen level at 3%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
Oxygen level at 6%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
[rapid beeping]
[all breathing heavily]
[automated voice] Connect
to life support system immediately.
[tense music playing]
Oxygen level at 1%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
Oxygen level at 1%.
Risk of body temperature
regulator malfunction.
Connect to life support system
immediately.
[automated voice]
Failed to unlock. Please try again.
-[whirs]
-Failed to unlock. Please try again.
No. Not like this…
Just hurry up!
It's all right, Soochan.
[automated voice] Unlocked.
APPROVAL
CORRECT PASSCODE
[all breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[closing theme music]
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.