LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 4
Si Feng, leave with him!
Hurry!
- Ling Long!
- Xuan Ji!
Let go of my sister!
Xuan Ji!
Troublesome girl.
Ling Long!
Ling Long and Xuan Ji are in trouble!
Let’s go!
Chu Ling Long, show
me what you’re capable of.
If you’re the reincarnation
of the God of War or Star of Mosha,
you’ll be able to escape this.
If you perish under this spell,
that means you’re not
the person we’re looking for.
Ling Long!
Try and escape!
Try and escape this!
Ling Long!
- Ling Long, are you okay?
- I’m fine.
I was so scared!
It’s Senior Hao Chen.
Si Feng!
Are you okay?
We’re fine.
What about the merman?
The merman...
The demons took him away.
Hero Yu, I know the Lize Palace
has a different way of doing things,
and other sects didn’t interfere as well,
but you brought my fellow juniors
to save that demon.
I don’t think that’s suitable.
We wanted to save him ourselves.
The merman didn’t harm anyone.
He even helped us in the cave.
How could you pity a demon?
You mustn’t have thoughts like that.
But...
Seniors, thank you for saving me.
I know my fault now.
It’s fine.
Maybe the demons left some tracks.
Hao Chen, let’s scout the area.
Yes.
Si Feng, did the demons
really take him away?
Follow me.
What spell is this?
This is Lize Palace’s spell of deceit.
- It can hide any scent or figure.
- Are you okay?
That’s why no one discovered him.
Hurry, bring him to the riverside.
Are you in pain?
I have some medicine here.
Why are you laughing?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do we know each other?
We don’t know each other in this lifetime.
But now, we know each other.
You know how to speak?
You were captured by the demons.
What did they want to do?
The entire demon tribe
is gathering at Sky Hall.
They’re trying to find the spirit keys.
Spirit keys?
What are those?
Your sect leaders will know.
I don’t know about anything else.
You mustn’t speak.
You’re severely injured.
You need to recuperate in the sea.
Regarding the news that you’ve told us,
I will send an anonymous letter
in order to remind the Five Great Sects.
Do you feel better now?
He’s crying?
Their tears do become pearls?
If you hold a Merman’s Tear
under your tongue, you’ll cry.
And only a few people
know about this secret.
They won’t find out.
That’s great! Xuan Ji won’t need to
stay in Mingxia Cave again!
You can try.
Ling Long, look!
- I’m crying! I know how to cry!
- Xuan Ji!
Xuan Ji, this is great!
You two are so silly.
Stop mocking us.
You’re the silly one here.
He’s thanking us.
Xuan Ji, that’s beautiful.
This is just like how I felt
after I ate some sweet snacks.
It’s sweet. I feel happy.
Si Feng, thank you.
Thank you for the Merman’s Tear as well.
You don’t need to thank me.
It’s a gift from the merman.
You said that everything
happens for a reason.
You accumulated good karma
after you saved him.
And this is your reward.
Chu Xuan Ji, if you want
to recover your six senses
and acquire genuine tears,
you should collect the shards.
What shards?
Shards of the Mirror of Origin.
Mirror of Origin is the immortal item
of the immortal, Xi Wangmu.
It can reveal the origin
of everything in the world.
Xi Wangmu shattered the mirror
and scattered them in the human realm.
Collect all the shards, and
you’ll recover your six senses.
I found one in the secret ground.
And I recovered my taste.
Is that the Mirror of Origin?
Did I recover my taste
because of the Mirror of Origin?
Only the Mirror of Origin
is capable of such feat.
Not only that,
you’ll know your true identity
after you collect all of them.
My true identity?
I’m Chu Xuan Ji. Who else can I be?
You are you, yet you are not.
Maybe it’s for the best
if you don’t know the whole truth.
But this is your fate.
Chu Xuan Ji, I wish you luck.
Maybe we’ll meet in the future.
I think the merman can
swim back to the sea from here.
Speaking of which,
I haven’t seen the sea before.
Si Feng, Lize Palace is
located beside the sea, right?
How about we meet up
with Si Feng in Lize Palace next time?
Sure!
Women are not allowed in Lize Palace.
I only know that they
don’t accept any female disciple.
But women are not allowed inside?
Are you guys going to stay single forever?
We won’t be able to marry anyone
after we enter Lize Palace.
Is that why everyone in Lize
Palace needs to wear a mask?
But Si Feng, your mask was removed.
We’ve seen your real face as well.
Don’t tell me the people
who had seen your face need to marry you?
- I’m done for.
- Marry?
I saw your real face.
- That means I need to...
- Little Six, you’re overthinking.
All of us saw his real face, you know?
Besides, Xuan Ji was the first person
to see his real face.
It has nothing to do with you.
Si Feng, am I right?
Such rule doesn’t exist.
It’s just that...
I’ll owe someone a favour.
Owe someone a favour?
Are you talking about the merman?
- We saved him of our own accord.
- That’s right.
We support each other
through thick and thin.
Father told me that favours
don’t matter in friendship,
only loyalty matters.
Friendship.
In the past, no one told
me about these things.
It was my first time
hearing these strange thoughts.
Why don’t you join Shaoyang Sect?
That way, we won’t be separated.
Maybe we can drink in secret every day.
Come, check out this amazing wine.
The speciality of Mount Lutai, fruit wine.
Since we’re going to be friends forever,
let’s finish this drink together.
- Great!
Sure.
Cheers.
Xuan Ji, don’t worry.
We will help you find the shards
of Mirror of Origin.
If we train hard enough
and travel around the world,
I’m sure we’ll find them.
By then, not only will you taste the wine,
you’ll enjoy the fragrance as well.
And we’ll be able to see
a Xuan Ji who’s afraid of pain.
That’s right. No matter
what’s your true identity,
it’s fine because we know who you are.
After I find the Mirror of Origin,
I’ll be able to recover my six senses.
And I will become like everybody else.
No matter what happens in the future,
I just want to
stay together with everyone and be happy.
That’ll be great.
- Cheers!
Chu Ling Long wasn’t
the person we’re looking for.
I will try to test the others
who have the same birth date
as the reincarnations of
the God of War and the Star of Mosha.
We wouldn’t need to go through
all these troubles
if you all didn’t lose track
of their reincarnations
at Fenru City 16 years ago.
It was our fault.
My lord, don’t worry.
I’ll find out the location
of the spirit keys as soon as possible.
I’ll find out where
the Five Great Sects had hidden them.
We’ll save Left Lieutenant and assist
you in retrieving the Divine Weapon.
We’ll summon the Star of Mosha
and dominate the three realms once again.
Si Feng,
if we talk about fate, it seems that
you have an affinity with Xuan Ji.
You two were born on the same day.
Even I couldn’t compare with that.
Since you’re twins, why weren’t
you born at the same time?
We’re twins.
But Xuan Ji was a lazy girl.
She didn’t want to come out.
She stayed in our mother’s belly
for another night.
That’s why I was born at 9 at night
on the fourth day of the fourth month,
while she was born at 1 in the morning
on the fifth day of the fourth month.
So that’s the case.
You’re hungry again?
You’re hungry?
I’ll catch some fishes and cook them.
Great idea. I’ll join you.
Little Six, you better catch a big fish.
Okay.
Xuan Ji, I thought you had just eaten?
I don’t know what’s going on either.
Isn’t this the book you used when
Mother taught us how to write our names?
You kept it with you?
I knew our Xuan Ji wasn’t emotionless
even though you couldn’t shed any tears.
Mother told me to write down the names
of those who are important to me.
Can I see who’s included?
Sure.
Father.
Mother.
Ling Long.
That’s all?
Who else do you want to be included?
You can write down the name
of the person you like.
These are all the people I like.
It’s not that.
I’m not talking about our family.
If you like someone,
you wish to see him every day.
And you want to be with him at all times.
You’ll share your secrets with him.
And he’ll directly affect
your mood as well.
He...
Ling Long, do you
have someone you like?
I...
I... I’ll check
how they’re doing!
If I like someone, I’ll
share my secrets with him?
I’m so hungry.
Why isn’t Sixth Senior here yet?
Xuan Ji, this is a secret between us.
You mustn’t tell anyone else.
So, the person whom I wish
to meet and share secrets with,
that’s the person I like.
I do have similarities
with other people as well.
Ling Long said I must write his name down.
SIXTH SENIOR
Xuan Ji.
- Sixth Senior.
- We caught many fishes.
- You’ll be able to eat soon.
- Okay.
Oh right, I picked the same gift
for you and Ling Long.
But seems like Ling Long doesn’t like it.
I’ll give them to you then.
Maybe it’s because I’m too dumb.
I always give her something
she doesn’t like.
Maybe it’s because other people
don’t like me as well.
Not at all. Sixth Senior, I like you.
What?
You’re the person that I like.
Silly girl, what do you know?
Little Six, come here.
- Help us with the fishes.
- Coming.
You can cook it with her.
Hurry up.
- Si Feng.
- What is this?
Sixth Senior gave me this.
Si Feng, what colour is it?
It’s blue.
This is blue?
My favourite colour is blue then.
Is it fragrant and nice?
It’s not, and it’s hideous.
Really?
I’ll be able to feel that for myself
when I recover my six senses.
By the way, Si Feng,
we’ll return to Mount Shaoyang tomorrow.
After we meet Father,
I’ll tell you about how
we can avoid the Candle Dragon
and retrieve your mask.
Xuan Ji, actually,
this is dangerous.
Maybe Sect Leader Chu would find out.
You don’t need to force yourself
if it’s too hard.
Since I didn’t manage to
obtain Gudiao’s horns for you.
It’s no problem. Friends
shouldn’t be so calculative.
I promised you I’ll do so.
That’s why I’ll do anything
to help you retrieve your mask.
Silly girl.
It was hard for you
to escape Mingxia Cave, you know?
Actually, it’s fine even if
I lose the mask.
You don’t need to find it
and you don’t need to return there.
Is it really fine?
It’s fine.
Xuan Ji,
thank you.
Uncle.
Master.
Father.
We’re back.
Who gave you permission to return here?
You’re getting out of control.
Father, please don’t blame Sister.
It’s my fault.
I only understood many things
after I went down the mountain.
It was all my fault. I was disobedient.
Now, I know the reason
you scolded me in the past.
You did the right thing.
I won’t act like this again.
Father.
Great.
Good girl.
Seems like you understood my intentions.
My effort was not in vain.
I’m sure your mother would
be relieved to hear this.
So, Xuan Ji doesn’t need to
enter Mingxia Cave again.
I feel relieved.
Xuan Ji, this is great!
Xuan Ji, you should return and rest first.
Little Six and I will send some
local specialities to the other members.
We’ll find you after that, okay?
- Okay.
- See you.
Little Six, let’s go.
Merman’s Tear is useful indeed.
Senior Hao Chen.
Don’t worry. I’m the only one
who knows about this.
Xuan Ji, let me ask you this.
Do you really want to train yourself?
In the past, I had no reason to do so.
But after the incident at Mount Lutai,
I realized that I need to train hard
to protect those I want to protect.
That’s good.
Xuan Ji, actually,
you’re as good as anyone else.
If there’s a chance for you
to learn great spells
and become a powerful
cultivator, will you grab the chance?
Senior Hao Chen, are you mocking me?
I don’t even have the right
to attend the Flower Session.
There’s no rush.
Think about it for now.
We’ll talk about that
after the Flower Session.
Now, we should celebrate
our return from Mount Lutai.
Si Feng doesn’t want me
to retrieve the mask,
but I’ve made a promise with him.
I must keep my words.
I can’t enter the secret ground by myself.
If I use spells, the barrier
will respond to them.
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji? Why are you here?
I’m here to help you.
Didn’t I tell you not to help me?
You’ll be punished by your father
if he finds out.
But you’ll be punished
if you don’t retrieve your mask.
Follow me.
The Candle Dragon is hiding here.
If we alert it, it’ll activate
the protection rock.
It’s fine. There’s a way
we could sneak past it.
Look. We’ll use this.
This Lightning Truncheon can only
teleport one person at a time.
But there are two of us here.
Just treat the two of us
as one individual then.
Don’t move. I’m going to cast the spell.
Look! I told you it would work.
Si Feng.
Let’s find your mask now.
Si Feng, your mask!
My mask.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, it’s fine.
We can come again tomorrow.
We’ll find the other half of the mask
and glue it back together.
Maybe the item broke
while we fought the Candle Dragon.
The masks in Lize Palace can’t be fixed.
Fate has decided for my mask to be broken.
We’ll just forget about it.
I need to meet my master now.
Do you still have respect for me?
Master.
Si Feng, you were distracted
by your feelings.
You even forgot about the 13 Abstinence!
You should return and receive
your punishment for your mistake.
What a great disciple indeed.
Master, I’ve let you down.
Please punish me.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, are you okay?
Xuan Ji, this is their internal affair.
You mustn’t interrupt.
Si Feng, you only said you let me down.
But you didn’t admit your mistake.
Do you know your mistake?
I removed his mask. You should
punish me instead of him.
Xuan Ji!
My lord, Xuan Ji is young and ignorant.
Please forgive her for her rudeness.
Did I say anything wrong? He didn’t remove
the mask of his own accord.
Moreover, he almost lost his life
trying to retrieve the mask.
Si Feng’s life and the mask,
which is more important to you?
Such audacity! This is
the internal affair of Lize Palace!
You have no right to say anything!
Xuan Ji, this has nothing to do with you.
Hurry and apologise to the palace lord.
Lize Palace’s internal affairs
have nothing to do with me indeed.
But he’s my best friend, and
I will do something about this.
You can’t answer my questions,
yet you’re trying to punish Si Feng.
I’m just trying to seek an answer.
I’m envious of Sect Leader Chu
for having a daughter like her.
Si Feng.
This girl is trying so hard to help you.
I’m very surprised.
What? Have you made new friends
after only a few days?
Yes. In the past, I never
knew what a friend was.
But now, I understand the
profound sentiments of friendship.
What? Profound sentiments of friendship?
My lord, the other sect leaders
are waiting for you for the meeting.
Please don’t delay this any longer.
My lord, please.
Profound sentiments of friendship.
Si Feng, get up now.
Does it hurt?
I’m fine.
Why did you try to save me
from my master’s punishment?
You’re reckless indeed.
I’m fine. I’m just afraid that
he’ll punish you for my mistake.
Si Feng, will he punish you?
I’ll be fine.
Don’t worry.
That’s good to hear.
SHOUYANG HALL
Everyone, these are the Demon Collars
that we found on Gudiao and Tengu.
Besides that, we’ve received
an anonymous letter as well.
It states that the demon tribe
is manipulating
both of the beasts mentioned.
And Sky Hall is the name
of the demon tribe’s organisation.
Has anyone heard of this news?
Sky Hall?
It doesn’t ring a bell.
An anonymous letter
without any proves or evidences.
Sect Leader Chu, you don’t need to
take it seriously.
That’s right.
The demon tribe was defeated
in the war 1,000 years ago.
Why should we be afraid?
I’m sure it’s only some minor demons
trying to cause a ruckus.
There’s no need for us to worry.
I’m afraid things aren’t that simple.
If the content of the anonymous
letter is true, the demon tribe
will try to obtain the five spirit keys
that the Five Great Sects are protecting.
Spirit keys?
What are you talking about?
Has anyone ever heard of that?
That concerns the very existence
of our sects.
I don’t think we should
discuss it in public.
If the content is fake, I’m afraid it
would cause us to turn against each other.
Valley Master Rong is right.
In my opinion,
Sect Leader Chu, you should focus on
handling the Flower Session.
Farewell.
SHOUYANG HALL
I didn’t expect the sects
to be divided among themselves
after I went for my training.
I hope the other sects
will be ready for this.
And act more cautiously.
I hope I’m the one
overthinking here.
Si Feng!
- Why are you here?
- Si Feng.
Why are you here? Is he
still insisting on punishing you?
But why? I’ll argue with him.
You mustn’t. My master has a bad temper.
He won’t let you off.
There’s nothing to fear. At most,
he’ll just give me a beating.
He’s too brave for his own good.
He broke our rules.
You should consider your position
before you try to imitate him.
He’s doing this because
he has a strong backing.
Our lord won’t let others off that easily.
Return now.
I’m kneeling here of my own accord.
My master didn’t punish me.
Why?
He’ll only be appeased if I do so.
Don’t worry. I’ll be fine.
Oh right, Si Feng, I brought
you some dried fruits.
They’re very sweet.
Since you’re doing this,
you should have some sweet stuff
in order to ease your pain. Here.
Is it delicious?
I’ll take this for now.
You should leave.
Remember to eat them.
Look. The Flower Session
hasn’t even started,
yet Chu Lei is trying to show that
he’s the leader of the Five Great Sects.
Don’t tell me Shaoyang Sect
will be the champion again?
Ask Shi Feng to prepare himself.
We need to be the champion no matter what.
The Xuanyuan Sect should be
the leader of the Five Great Sects!
Yes.
Follow me.
Master.
Master?
Isn’t friendship the only thing you need?
You don’t need me anymore.
I don’t dare to do so.
I’ve broken the rules.
I’m willing to accept my punishment.
Those who can’t keep
their true nature in check
will be judged by the elder council.
And receive the 13 Punishments
in Lianyu Pagoda.
I’m afraid you can’t
endure all of the punishments.
As your head disciple,
I should be a role model for others.
- I won’t escape.
- You!
Look at you now.
You are the most outstanding disciple
I had in Lize Palace
for the past few hundred years.
You said you wanted to
become a role model,
but have you ever considered my feelings?
Listen carefully.
I won’t allow you to
give up on your future.
You must be the champion
of the Flower Session.
And maybe, I could protect you
from the elder council.
In the future, if you embarrass
me again, I won’t let you off.
Leave.
The Gudiao has massive wings.
And its claws are sharper than swords.
I struck it with my sword
and it cried for help.
Sixth Senior is amazing indeed!
We’ll be the champion
for the Flower Session this time!
- That’s right!
- We’ll be number one!
- Right.
- Ling Long,
who will win if Sixth Senior and
Si Feng fight each other in the contest?
If Si Feng’s skill
level is as high as this,
Sixth Senior’s skill
level is as low as this.
So low?
Si Feng is that strong?
Ling Long, aren’t you
partaking in the contest as well?
What about your skill level?
Me?
It’s around...
It’s as high as that.
That high?
How could you partake in the contest
when you can’t even hold a sword?
- Idiots will be idiots.
- You called me an idiot? You!
- Ling Long.
- It’s obvious, isn’t it?
Or is it because there are
too many idiots in Shaoyang Sect?
Is that why you don’t understand?
We must be magnanimous.
No matter how loud a dog
barks, it will always be an animal.
Us humans don’t need to
argue with animals.
- That’s right.
- You know how to speak, huh?
But that won’t work in the Flower Session.
I’ll make you kneel
in front of me by then!
We’ll make him kneel
in front of us in the arena.
Don’t worry.
I’ll turn him into a tortoise.
Great!
Let’s wait and see.
Look. How about that spot?
It provides a clear view
and it’s windy as well.
It’s the best spot.
Only your amazing Sixth Senior
can find a spot like that.
I noticed that spot long ago.
We don’t need you.
The Dianjinggu Sect has arrived.
VALLEY MASTER OF DIANJINGGU SECT
Ling Long.
It’s the sect of the rude Wu Tong.
Their sect won’t be the champion
since they have a disciple like him.
The Xuanyuan Sect has arrived.
Ling Long, why are there so
few people in the Xuanyuan Sect?
Xuanyuan Sect was
the best sect 100 years ago.
But their sect is
getting weaker and weaker.
And their sect leader isn’t here.
The Lize Palace has arrived.
It’s Si Feng’s sect.
Si Feng!
Quiet down.
They hate to associate themselves
with outsiders.
You are causing trouble
for him by shouting his name.
Unlike you, he’s the sect leader’s
favourite disciple.
Hey, Master likes me as well.
The Lord and Madam
of Fuyu Island have arrived.
Ling Long.
What is everyone staring at?
- They...
- We’re staring at Madam Dong Fang.
Madam Dong Fang is the
most beautiful woman in the world.
Xuan Ji, you can’t tell
what’s beautiful and what’s not.
Look.
His eyes are popping out.
I... That’s not true.
The sect leader of Shaoyang Sect
has arrived.
- Father is here.
- Father.
The Flower Session has been
held for a few hundred years.
The Five Great Sects
held this event every year
in order to promote justice
and righteousness.
The winner of this contest will be
the leader of the Five Great Sects
for the next four years.
Everyone here must treat this
as a spar and learn from others.
If anyone here disregards the rules
and harms others on purpose,
the five sect leaders will
have no mercy on them.
The Flower Session
will begin now.
Yu Si Feng from Lize Palace
will face Tu Ren from Fuyu Island.
- Si Feng!
- Si Feng! You can do it!
Si Feng!
Who’s that?
Looks like he’s over 30 years old.
Why is he in the contest?
That’s Senior Tu Ran from Fuyu Island.
My sword skills are ruthless.
I won’t show any mercy.
You won’t suffer if you surrender now.
Senior, please show me no mercy.
Dear, you don’t need to worry.
Tu Ran will definitely win.
Seems like Senior Tu Ran is quite strong.
Can Si Feng defeat him?
It’s more than that.
Senior Tu Ran was the favourite
candidate four years ago.
But he missed the contest because
he wanted to train his Lightning Sword.
Look at the lightning contained
within his sword.
I’m sure he has mastered it.
Even an experienced warrior
might not be able to
win against him easily.
Si Feng is facing a tough opponent.
- Si Feng! You can do it!
Yu Si Feng from Lize Palace is the victor!
- Si Feng won!
- This is great!
- Si Feng, you’re amazing!
- Yes!
That disciple from Lize
Palace is outstanding indeed.
It seemed like he didn’t even
give his best.
Little Six, if you face
Si Feng in the future,
you should just give up.
You should surrender.
My Yaohua sword moves
aren’t that weak, you know?
Next round,
Wu Tong from Dianjinggu Sect
will face Lin Feng from Xuanyuan Sect.
I didn’t expect him
to be that powerful.
He’s too much!
He doesn’t need to destroy
the weapon of his opponent!
Wu Tong from Dianjinggu Sect
is the victor!