=City of Streamer=
=Episode 36=
I have one concern,
or scruple.
The man you love might get hurt.
There is no more a tie between us.
What's more,
he's a man.
Does a man need the shelter of a woman?
Most of all I want now
is to smash the evil business
of the Rong Family into pieces,
so the managers
will fight against
and destroy each other.
When they are dreaming crazy and wild,
we'll catch them all in one net.
That's the deal, then.
We must let them pay.
Young Master.
Would you like some night munchies?
There's mutton soup
stewed in the kitchen.
It's tasty.
No.
I drank a lot at the dinner party.
I don't have the appetite.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
How is it going with
my little brother's funeral?
Ma'am is taking care of it.
People were sent back to
the ancestral grave to observe fengshui.
The coffin was ordered, too.
It will be delivered tomorrow.
Concubine Sun gets better now.
She had a walk in the courtyard today.
Master took out a piece of jade
and asked to
bury it with the youngest master.
I see.
Young Master, have a rest.
Father.
The day my little brother died,
you passed out.
The doctor said
your arms were paralyzed
because of a minor stroke.
Jiashang,
that's...
that's my
private coffer.
Take out 30,000 silver dollars.
I want to
marry Fanghua off with those.
Help me
to keep the rest safe.
When Fanglin gets married,
give those to her.
I won't let my daughters
get married miserably.
Where's Shujun?
She went to her mother's house.
She'll be back early tomorrow morning.
When she is back,
tell her to see me.
I'm tired.
I want to
have a rest.
The room service is quick.
Come in.
Jiashang.
Why are you here?
Uncle Zhao, I hear
you organize card games
at the Astor House all year round.
I planned to play a few rounds,
not expecting that
I would disturb your rest.
What a coincidence.
The game finished early today.
How about this?
Let me get dressed.
Then we can go downstairs for a drink.
Don't bother.
In that case,
we can have a small talk.
Come in.
What are you doing? Hua...
Since my father was ill,
I've been busy running the business.
Thank you for taking care of my family.
But you seem to
care about Ma'am the most.
No wonder Ma'am is radiant
and looks years younger these days.
Jiashang,
about that,
it's really my fault.
Shujun
and I made a mistake on impulse.
But it needn't get out,
lest the Rong Family will be disgraced.
Sure.
My father is sensitive
about his reputation.
He's in bad condition
and my little brother has passed away.
He is in sorrow already.
If he finds out what Ma'am did,
I'm afraid he'll break down.
For the sake of the family,
we must keep it a secret.
Rong Jiashang,
you conscienceless rascal!
Like father, like son.
First you murdered my son,
then you detained Master,
and now,
you're trying to threaten me?
You monster!
Shortsighted woman.
Jiashang,
calm down.
We can
talk about everything.
Uncle Zhao,
my father told me
his name was Qin Shuigen.
To take a lottery ticket
from his sworn brother,
Rong Dingkun,
he killed the latter.
In the end,
fire cannot be wrapped in paper.
Rong Dingkun's daughter didn't die.
She's back.
I see.
Who is she?
She is
Miss Feng, your governess, isn't she?
You were the driver, weren't you?
Shizhen vaguely remembers you.
You tricked her mother
into seeing my father,
and killed the mother and her son
with my father.
It was really her.
Dingkun told me
the first time he saw her,
he broke out in a cold sweat.
He had never been afraid of any woman.
Only Miss Feng
made him scared.
Did she come to wreak revenge?
My father is always afraid of it, right?
That's why he set fire to Wenchunli
when he couldn't purchase it.
Once it was purchased by others,
the body buried in the old house
would be found.
Actually, I didn't
approve him of setting the fire.
He would have got into trouble
through clever means.
Rong Dingkun
was killed by your father.
I just helped him to hide the body.
That was the first time
your father murdered a man.
From then on,
he has always dreaded it
and never been relieved from anxiety.
Were you saying
it wasn't easy for my father
to work so hard?
Even though he dreaded it,
he still murdered
the entire Rong Family.
Shujun, now you know,
compared with the murder,
it was nothing that Dingkun
hooked up with Miss Meng
and gained the Gold Kylin
by cheating.
But, Jiashang, you should know.
If it weren't
for your father's ruthlessness,
the Rong Family would have
collapsed long ago.
You would never be
a glamorous young master.
Instead, you would be a clerk
of some commerce chamber,
or an apprentice of some store.
You should thank your father
for being shameless.
No matter how gorgeous
a blood stained robe is,
nobody would put it on!
So what?
He's your father after all.
You can't change it even if
you peel the skin off your body.
All your life,
you must carry your father's crimes.
Therefore,
instead of criticizing him,
you'd better think
how to clean up the mess.
I'll carry my father's crimes.
What about yours?
Uncle Zhao,
if the other uncles knew,
the goods they had lost these years
were resold by you in secret,
what would they think?
Why would they believe the rumors?
Now that I can bring myself
to confront you about it,
I surely have the evidence.
Since I joined the company,
I've found there were great loses
in the You Line and the Wu Line
in the south.
My father trusts you.
He blames it on uncertain situations.
But I've been looking into you.
I have both witnesses
and physical evidences.
If my father
and the other uncles knew it,
what do you think they would say?
Do you think
I'm the only one who was doing this?
Of course not.
You've been fighting for power
and profits with the other uncles.
It must be hard.
It's nothing.
As a young man,
you are not their match.
I have good advice for you.
I'm listening.
Turn the business
over to me.
What did you say?
You're swallowing such a big part
of our family business?
Jiashang can't suppress them.
Though they seem to be
at peace outwardly,
privately,
they're ready to make trouble.
Instead of waiting until
the old devils betray you,
you'd better turn it over to me
and let me run it.
Let's form a partnership.
I'll do all the work.
You'll get the dividend every year
without doing anything.
That's our family business.
Why would we turn it over to you?
You wish!
Zhao Hua'an, I was so blind.
You and Rong Dingkun
are two birds of a feather.
You're both good for nothing!
You jerk!
I'm doing it for your own good.
Shujun,
the old devils
only respect you on the surface.
They are all murderers.
If they have to,
they won't hesitate to kill
all the Rong Family.
The Qin Family.
Technically,
it's the Qin Family.
The Rong Family
had been exterminated long ago,
except for Shizhen.
I understand
your point.
If I'm not doing the work,
I won't take the profits.
I assume you know
how I hate the dark business
of the Rong Family.
If you want it,
we can discuss the share transfer.
After all,
I don't want to make money from it.
I just want a smooth transition.
Jiashang,
what are you doing?
You're so disappointing.
Why do you give up our business
without putting up a fight?
What about you, Ma'am?
A son of your family just died,
and you're still in the mood
for cheating on your husband.
Did you say
share transfer?
Yes.
As you said,
we sell our shares,
resign from the boards of the companies,
and support you to be the new director.
We'll sell the shares to you
at a discount of 10%
on one condition:
you must pay in silver dollars.
30%.
20%.
If you don't agree with it,
I can make more money
selling them to others.
It's a deal.
When do we go through the formalities?
Let the lawyers meet tomorrow.
Good.
You're exceptionally vigorous.
Like father, like son.
It's getting late.
You should get some sleep.
I'll take Ma'am home.
Ma'am.
Tell me,
how do you like to punish me?
Uncle Zhao was right about one thing.
My father isn't a good husband.
It hasn't been easy for you these years.
You're my elder.
I have no right to punish you.
I told my father
you went to your mother's house.
You would go see him when he woke up.
My father received heavy blows recently.
He is depressed.
He couldn't think straight
and remember anything.
It's just,
Fanglin hasn't married yet.
If the word about your affair gets out,
how could she find a decent husband?
Don't you threaten me with Fanglin.
Even if we have to jump into
the Huangpu River together,
we won't ask for charity from you.
Fanglin is my younger sister.
Being kind to her
and looking after her
are my responsibilities.
Since your heart
is no longer with the family,
if you want a divorce,
I'll persuade my father
to give you freedom.
I won't divorce him.
At least,
not now.
Otherwise, how could Fanglin
find a husband?
Tomorrow,
ask the lawyer to draw up an agreement,
making sure she'll get all my dowry.
When she finds a husband,
I'll move out immediately.
Okay.
Please put up with it
for some more time, then.
You're not like your father.
I know
you always hate me in your mind,
because I asked your father
to send you to the Military Academy.
But now it seems that
if you didn't leave,
if you grew up in the family
under the influence of your father,
you would probably become
another Rong...
no,
I should say,
become another Qin Shuigen.
Probably.
But,
I don't hate you anymore.
You and me,
we'll go separate ways.
(Astor House)
Come in.
Put them on the table.
Yes.
Miss Feng.
As you required,
I've brought you the detailed background
of all the secretaries
in the Rong Company.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
I have good news.
Zhao Hua'an took action immediately
(February 19 shipping from Xileshan)
after meeting Rong Jiashang's lawyer.
(February 19th shipping from Xileshan)
This is the telegram I intercepted
yesterday afternoon
after their meeting.
The biggest piece of meat
is grabbed by Zhao Hua'an.
It seems that the Rong Family
will be in disorder.
By the way, Mr. Yang,
could you help me
to collect the information
concerning the opium business
of the Rong Family?
I'm on it now.
Thank you.
(Zhao Hua'an, No. 2 of the
Rong Company, Breaks with the Rongs)
(Share Transfer Contract
to Be Signed Today)
(Zhao Hua'an, No. 2 of the
Rong Company, Breaks with the Rongs)
(Share Transfer Contract
to Be Signed Today)
You specifically
asked me to send a reporter
to follow them.
Do you have any big plans?
Excuse me.
A steak.
A celery and apple juice.
Just a moment.
The news caused
a great stir in the company.
All the qualified shareholders
are eager to have a try.
They either insinuate that
they'll make me better offers,
or try to sabotage
Zhao's acquisition of the shares.
It's completely unknown
who will get the business
before the contract
is finally signed.
You want the shareholders to
struggle for power
in order to weaken their strength.
In the end, you'll reap the benefits?
Yunchi,
some of my family business
is too dirty.
I've always detested it.
Honestly,
I don't want anyone
to take those parts of the business.
You're not going to...
I'm going to
wait until both sides suffer
before I step in
and destroy all of the gray business
of my family,
especially the opium business.
Here is your steak.
Please enjoy.
Thanks.
Have you made the decision?
If you do that,
the Rong Family will fall apart.
Even if you hate your father
and the dirty business,
you should think of your sisters.
Without the family behind them,
their life would be harder.
Yunchi,
take care of Fanghua for me.
Don't worry.
I've got her dowry ready early.
As for Fanglin,
I plan to send her abroad to study.
What about you?
Your father and Zhao Hua'an
have common opinions.
If he regains the control of the family,
will he still treat you
as his successor?
If you're driven out of his house,
you'll be deprived
of everything.
At that time,
will Miss Feng still want you?
If you want my opinion,
women need
material comforts for nourishment.
Even if she wants you,
do you have the heart to see her
living a hard life with you?
I'm not used to the vegetable juice.
It's too bitter.
There's honey in it.
Still, it's bitter.
Father.
(Study)
Father, I wonder if you
(Zhao Hua'an Breaks with the Rongs)
have heard about the Rong Family.
I feel sorry for Jiashang.
He has no elders to support him
and no relatives to help him.
You said you went out
with Rong Jiashang in Chongqing.
Do you think
he still has feelings for you?
I'm still
in love with him.
As for him,
(Zhao Hua'an Breaks with the Rongs)
in such a dazzling world of Shanghai,
(Share Transfer Contract to Be Signed)
he may have changed his heart.
But I fell in love with him
when he was poor and low.
I'm different from those women
who come for
his fame and wealth.
(Study)
Call the Rong Company
and invite Mr. Jiashang over
for a cup of tea.
Help yourself.
Thank you.
Mr. Hashimoto, what can I
do for you?
I hear you're
in a difficult situation.
Shiori is very worried about you.
Those uncles of yours,
I've heard of them for a long time.
They are like devils.
Your father is now sidelined by illness.
They resist your authority
and try to bully you.
It doesn't surprise me at all.
I know I'm crude and unlearned.
I don't blame them for
not agreeing with me.
Actually, I've been thinking of
turning the business of transportation
and opium growing
over to them.
I don't think it's a good idea.
The two parts of business account for
60% or 70% of your family business.
Don't be impulsive
and give up on your family business
just because of a little frustration.
It wasn't easy for your father
to build the business empire,
you must maintain his achievements.
Mr. Hashimoto, don't worry.
The contracts we signed before
are still valid.
The managers who take over the business
will continue to fulfill them.
They are all experienced.
They're
more reliable than me.
Jiashang,
I'm not worrying about that.
I just can't bear to see
you giving up your family business.
If you have any difficulties,
just tell me.
I'll help you.
Mr. Hashimoto,
do you have any bright ideas?
You and Shiori
once had a relationship,
but you were young then.
It didn't last long.
When I knew about it,
you were already engaged with Miss Du.
I felt so sorry.
Now you've broken off
your engagement to Miss Du,
would you consider
being together with Shiori?
You'll be a perfect match
with equal social status.
Besides, you had a bond years ago.
Though Shiori was born of a concubine,
she isn't inferior to others
in terms of appearance and talent.
Mr. Hashimoto,
I'm grateful you are worrying about me
and willing to help me.
But I'm still young.
Getting married
is too early for me.
It seems that you really want to
give up your family business.
What did your father say?
I'm in charge of
all my family business now.
You made the decision
on impulse.
It will be too late
if you regret in future.
Uncle, I don't agree with you.
Other than the transportation business
and the southern plantations,
we own construction
and trade companies.
Though they're not so profitable as the
transportation and opium growing,
they are enough to support
the whole family.
Young man,
you have no ambition.
Some blood money is sinful
that I'd better not make.
And, since my father was shot,
he's been thinking he had done
too many evil things in his early years
that he got punished.
So I'm going to
do the right things after selling
those parts of our business.
I'm doing good things for my family.
Uncle.
I have a cautious
and conservative nature.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Jiashang,
I sincerely hope to cooperate with you.
Thanks for your appreciation.
If there's nothing else,
I shall leave.
Jiashang.
I asked my father to invite you over.
As long as you need,
- my family...
- Shiori.
Thanks for your kindness.
But I'm used to separate
relationships from business.
If you think
I'm in a difficult situation
and want to give me a hand,
it's unnecessary.
I don't want to
rely on women.
Jiashang, it's not like that.
I really like you.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have suggested Father
unite your family by marriage.
I really want to marry you.
When we were in Chongqing,
it was just a crush
between two teenagers.
It wasn't even a serious relationship.
I'm in love with someone else now.
We should move on
and look forward.
You should forget it, too.
Jiashang.
Miss Feng.
This is the telegram
we just intercepted.
Zhao Hua'an has upgraded
his transportation code.
(February 28,
No. 12 of Ping'an Street, Tengchong)
You cracked the code?
Well done.
Come on, let's have a drink.
OK.
A toast to...
To our success.
Yes.
Sit down.
The Rong Family will ship a cargo
at the beginning of the year.
The managers really fear nothing.
I've checked the next
destination of the cargo.
Most they shipped
are contraband goods
other than the goods of the company.
I thought when
Qin Shuigen was in charge,
the company was better managed.
But it seems now
Qin Shuigen
couldn't do anything to his men
who had made great contributions.
So,
the Rong Family
is destined to break up.
(Zhao Hua'an, No. 2 of the
Rong Company, Breaks with the Rongs)
(Share Transfer Contract
to Be Signed Today)
The Rong Family...
What do you think
Rong Jiashang is going to do?
Will he turn over
all the gray business
to Zhao Hua'an as rumor says?
Let's wait and see.
Actually, I'm thinking
the gray income and business
are disgusting
and outrageous.
But the profit is tremendous.
He has no reason to turn down the money.
If it was me,
I would work with Zhao Hua'an,
so he'll do all the work
and I'll make money.
Two birds with one stone.
I don't think Rong Jiashang
likes to sit idle
and enjoy the fruits of others' work.
As the saying goes,
beauty is in the eye of the lover.
I've long broken up with him.
You've been at home long enough.
You need to get out and relax.
How about this?
I'll ask Baoli to take you out tomorrow
and show you around.
I'd love to.
Come on.
It's beautiful.
Baoli, enough.
We've bought too many clothes.
I don't need so many.
Stop complaining.
They're nowhere near enough.
You're working with Mr. Meng.
If people see
his woman in shabby clothes,
they would think he's stingy.
I'm not his woman.
All right, don't take it seriously.
Isn't the dress a little long?
It's okay.
Just my size.
Miss.
Do you have another dress
of the same style,
but a little shorter?
Yes. I'll go get it.
OK.
Don't bother.
It's just fine.
Short dresses are in vogue in Paris
and New York these days.
Let me find you a fashion magazine.
(The Rongs Are Falling Apart)
Weak Leader and strong members,
the Rongs are falling apart.
It sounds right.
In his early twentieth,
he is still young.
It's normal
he can't suppress the veterans.
But in my opinion,
the Rong Family
could live like a king
relying on foreign trade
and real estate.
They don't have to do
the wicked and risky business.
Alright.
Don't read it again.
Let's try some more.
How do you like this?
Come.
Let's see.
(Rong)
Young Master, it's time to go.
Perfect timing.
Just now,
several southern factions of the
Rong Family fought among themselves.
Three of their opium plantations
were destroyed.
Vehicles with iron chains
around the tires
were driven into the fields
and the newly planted bulbs were
all crushed.
So next,
what do you think we should do?
Though Zhao Hua'an
took the shares of the company,
the other covetous shareholders
are probably scheming to
bring him down.
I'm thinking,
at this time,
if we write a secret letter to them,
and inform them of
the destination of
Zhao's most important cargo,
I think,
they'll do us a favor
and make some trouble for Zhao.
Brilliant.
This man's surname is Liu.
He is one of Zhao Hua'an's
most important opponents.
(Liu Sanwan)
They are equal in strength in the south.
Mr. Meng,
I think you've already made plans.
Let's wait and see.
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪