[English subtitles are available]
[PLOT LOVE]
[Episode 14]
[Eminence Group]
Let's go.
Okay.
Mr. Su.
He's been under a lot of stress.
Don't give him coffee.
The tea is invigorating.
Bring it to him.
By the way,
don't tell him I made the tea.
[Eminence Group VS Gu's Group·Rround 2]
I declare
Eminence Group
the winner of the second round.
[Eminence Group]
Lu Nan,
don't go.
You're here to see me.
Does that mean you've forgiven me?
It's all in your head.
I'm here to check on the design progress.
Don't worry.
I'm already working on the second draft.
I will keep my promise
to help you  establish cooperative relationship with Sia.
Even so,
it doesn't require you to stay up late at work.
Let me know if you find it difficult.
But don't put on an act like this,
making it look like Eminence is pushing its employees to work.
He hasn't seen you in days.
Today
he insisted on waiting for you.
He just fell asleep.
I'm such a bad mother.
Bei Bei, you're back.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
It must be tiring
to be so busy every day.
I have you,
so I don't feel tired at all.
Well,
I just had a dream that
you and Dad took me to the amusement park.
Mom, are you and Dad getting a divorce?
Chris.
I made a mistake
that upset your father
and he probably won't forgive me.
My Bei Bei is the best person in the world.
If there's a mistake,
it must be Dad who made it,
because Bei Bei is perfect.
Mom loves you.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I love you too, Mom.
[Eminence Group VS Gu's Group·Rround 3]
This dress
perfectly blends
Chinese Han Dynasty elements
with the style of Sia,
which is
exactly what we're looking for.
So,
I declare Eminence Group
the winner of the third round.
[Another shocking scandal of Eminence: President's wife's plagiarism]
Some netizens have revealed that Su Bei, the Eminence president's wife,
[killed a promising designer!]
the famous agent, and the current president of Eminence Starlight Agency,
[Another shocking scandal of Eminence: President's wife's plagiarism]
when participated in the design competition seven years ago,
[killed a promising designer!]
plagiarized the work of Zhao Rui, the defending champion,
and after the event,
she used the forces behind Eminence
to unite interest groups to force Zhao Rui to death.
[Another shocking scandal of Eminence: President's wife's plagiarism]
[killed a promising designer!]
[An agent who can't design is not a good actress.]
These trolls
[Su Bei is so pretentious.]
swear without knowing anything.
And those who "revealed" the news
was actually making up a story about you.
An agent who can't design is not a good actress.
Su Bei is so pretentious.
What kind of designer is she?
She was kicked out of design circle seven years ago over plagiarism.
Don't know
which hapless designer's work she copied this time.
I have proof here. Click on the link below for details.
Mary Sue's experience taught me that
you have to be either tolerant or ruthless
to stand firm in this world.
Aren't you angry?
It happened seven years ago.
There're even pictures to show the "truth".
It seems that someone
bears me a grudge.
The people on the board
like to look for trouble.
Who knows
what's gonna happen this time.
The cooperation with Sia is very important.
We have to find a way
to restore Eminence's reputation.
As for Su Bei
tell her to resign,
and to make up for all the damage
she's done to the company.
Uncle Ding,
are you getting too old to think straight?
Just because a trivial matter like this happened,
and you're trying to fire her.
If something happens to me,
would you also kick me out immediately?
Lu Nan,
you're different.
Don't change the subject.
This cooperation
matters to the listing of our company.
It's such a big thing,
and I'm sure you will make reasonable decisions.
We can cooperate with Sia
all because Su Bei turned the tide.
Without her, there would be no cooperation with Sia in the first place.
I'm sure you all know
Su Bei is my wife.
As a husband,
I'll stand by her.
How is Sia?
Given the situation now,
they have intention to
terminate the cooperation with Eminence.
At the moment,
working with Eminence
will affect their brand image,
and I can understand that.
But the partnership
has a big impact on Eminence.
We can't just sit here and do nothing.
Seven years go,
I was slandered without fighting back.
Now,
I won't allow myself to be trampled upon.
As long as I can prove my innocence,
they won't have a reason
to turn us down.
Now that
the mastermind has exposed himself,
then we can follow the trail,
starting with the evidence.
Luckily you knew that Director Guo had a conspiracy,
and made a preparation
to call the mainstream media
to delete trending posts.
Also, make a statement in the name of the company
that those who made up the story
shall be held accountable according to law.
Won't that stir up public outrage?
First of all, public opinion should be directed to other topics,
which means we should deflect the public's attention.
And have an investigation into the Gu's Group.
Is it really a coincidence that
it happened right after we started working with Sia?
How about Gu Chengze?
He' busy with making money.
He's very enthusiastic about good business.
Then 7 years ago...
Wait,
I need to talk to you.
[Resignation Letter Divorce Agreement]
Please sign your name.
What do you mean by that?
The scandal has been under control for now,
but has not been fully resolved,
and it could erupt again at any moment.
So...
So we'd better get a divorce,
and I'll take all the consequences.
I'll make sure it won't affect
Eminence at all.
[Divorce Agreement Man: Lu Nan Woman: Su Bei]
[Resignation Letter Applicant: Su Bei November 2, 2019]
You want to run away when things went wrong?
I'm not running away.
I never thought of running away.
It's just
the best solution for now.
I've got the paperwork ready.
I can leave today.
All I need is your signature.
If this is what you want,
I'll let you go.
Ungrateful woman.
[Seven years ago]
Su Bei.
[Divorce Agreement Man: Lu Nan Woman: Su Bei]
[Woman (signature): Su Bei]
That's how you left me seven years ago,
and you're still treating me like that seven years later.
[Nanxi City Hospital Outpatient]
You're always hard on me
and boss me whenever you like.
But when you're with Su Bei, you act like an idiot!
You're lying in bed now,
and she doesn't even come to see you.
She is so unfeeling,
so why do you still miss her?
How is he?
Why do you care?
I just want to see him.
Now you feel sorry for him?
Lu Nan is just reluctant to admit he cares about you,
but he is always there for you.
Everyone on the board was pressuring him,
but he protected you at the expense of offending all of them.
What about you?
The doctor just called me.
I don't want to see you here
when I get back.
Lu Nan,
please wake up.
I really regret it.
Why are you here?
You're awake, Lu Nan. Do you still have a headache?
I don't need your pity.
I'll send you the divorce papers after I sign them.
I know several famous doctors abroad.
You need early treatment.
If you have nothing else to say, you should go.
My illness
is nothing for you to worry about.
You just leave when I tell you to?
You do as I say all of a sudden?
Don't be mad.
It's not worth it.
I don't need you to tell me if it's worth it.
Go away.
Go.
Seeing him in a coma,
I realized
I really cared about him.
I used to think
if he didn't remember me,
I would leave him alone.
But then I found out that
I couldn't do it.
So I want to
follow my heart.
I want to get him back.
OK.
Then we'll get him back.
But he's so angry with me.
What can I do?
It's OK.
We'll help you figure it out.
Bei Bei.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Bei Bei went on a blind date with someone else.
It's none of my business.
This is the address.
[Yonghong International Hotel]
Sir, can I help you?
Beauty, are you alone?
Can I sit here?
Who are you!?
We are still married and you're looking for someone else.
Are you that desperate?
If you want to go on a blind date,
you can wait until I become your ex-husband.
You go over there and wait for me.
Make it quick.
The blind dater left and you're waiting for the next one?
This blind date scene
is like a marriage proposal.
You're so eager to get married?
I'd like to see
which man will be interested in you.
He has come.
I'm eager to get married.
But I just want to marry you again.
What are you trying to do?
Mr. Lu.
I admit,
before,
I lied to you because I misunderstood you.
I left.
My intention was to help you keep the Eminence
and this cooperation.
I don't want you to get hurt because of me.
But when I made up my mind to leave,
I found that
my heart was in pain.
I was very reluctant.
And I was not that strong.
So,
instead of leaving alone,
I would rather face my heart.
Mr. Lu.
I wonder
if you would like to work with me
for this relationship.
No.
I know it's hard for you,
but I'll prove it to you.
The Marketing Department proposes to increase marketing investment.
Mr. Lu, what do you think?
Mr. Lu.
Where are we going to eat tonight?
Do as you say.
I asked where are we going for dinner tonight.
Workaholics also have their moments in a daze?
Because of Su Bei again?
She...
confessed her love to me.
She confessed her love to you?
Are you sure?
She's not playing any tricks again, is she?
Right?
You think there's something wrong too.
Although I often think she has an axe to grind,
every time she looks at me,
I think,
she loves me.
If that's true,
what do you think?
If that's not true,
what are you gonna do?
You! Put all your eggs in one basket!
By the way.
I'm making progress on what you told me.
Amy and Gu's Group have been seeing a lot of each other lately.
They're almost
on the verge of working together.
[Yonghong Grand Spa Thermal Resort]
Take a look at this contract.
I know what you mean.
But about Annie,
there's nothing I can do.
You understand Su Bei.
If you can be friends,
there must be mutual recognition.
Apart from whether she did it or not,
it would be unfair
to convict her
before we get to the bottom of this.
I know Sia value the Chinese market.
This is the best concession Eminence can make.
If you want,
we can negotiate the benefits.
You're really good.
If I don't say yes,
wouldn't I just reject the benefits?
But,
I need to talk to the headquarters.
Just give me a few more days
and I'll sort this out.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Annie is so happy to have you as her husband.
Hello?
Hello, Annie.
I bought you a week.
If you can't prove your innocence
by the end of the week,
our cooperation
can only go so far.
Thank you, Amy.
You're welcome.
Thank Lu Nan if you want.
I envy you
for having such a good husband.
Did you come to my house to play hide-and-seek?
I see you haven't had a good meal recently.
I just want to cook a meal for you.
Get out.
Take your food out with you.
Let me go.
Don't be angry.
I'll say it again. Let go of me.
I know I was wrong.
Or you can hit me.
Su Bei.
Don't say things that don't make sense.
You and I already have...
Let's make peace.
Lu Nan.
[Tianyuan]
Let us drink a toast to Mr. Gu.
- Wish him
- To Mr. Gu.
- a successful start.
- A successful start.
- OK.
- Come on.
Cheers.
Today,
you can have fun here!
Everything's on me.
- Thank Mr. Gu.
Thank Mr. Gu.
Come on.
Have another drink.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers.
Let me pour it for you.
Dad.
What?
What did you say?
Have you misappropriated the company's money lately?
Yes.
I embezzled some money.
I made an investment.
I just want to help the company make more profits.
What profits! It's all lost!
Lost? Impossible!
How can it be impossible?
Go back and check it out for yourself.
Get out.
Stand there.
You told dad about it?
Brother.
What are you talking about?
It's better not you.
If I find something,
get the hell out of Gu's family.
What did you find?
Here's the proof you asked for.
[Gu's Group（Confidential Files）]
Gu Chengze's investment failure
[Financial Profit and Loss Analysis]
has been found out by my father,
and he is now locked up at home.
I thought he was just being bossy.
I didn't expect he would do something like this.
And Sanglan Costume.
Sorry.
It has nothing to do with you.
Thank you.
I'm glad I can help you.
If I remember correctly,
Manager Gu should be in Gu's Group now.
This is Eminence's downstairs.
You've gone a long way.
The coffee here is good
and the people are nice.
If you don't get back,
I'm afraid Gu Chengze is going to find you again.
Well, I'll leave you two alone.
I got to go.
Aren't you busy?
You think,
you said you were leaving so you didn't have to work?
Are you jealous?
I came to see him about Gu Chengze.
You don't have to explain to me
why you found him.
I'm just trying to remind you that
we‘re still married.
And it's inappropriate for you
to meet strange men.
What about
your meeting with strange women?
When did I...?
Mine was different.
I think it's the same.
Because I'm jealous.
So,
this time we even it out.
Do you think this is going to work on me?
I haven't forgiven you yet.
Fine.
Mr. Lu.
Take your time to get angry and I'll take it.
Mr. Gu.
You're so handsome today.
Open the door.
You can't go in there.
You can't go in.
Who's so noisy?
Get out!
What are you doing!
Gu Chengze.
You're involved in a commercial fraud.
[Police]
Please come with us
and cooperate with the investigation.
I already gave it to the police.
In the afternoon,
Gu Chengze
has been summoned into custody.
I also reported
his embezzlement.
Count it as interest.
But,
why did Gu Yan help you?
Not exactly a favor.
It's mutual benefit.
By the way,
How's you and Lu Nan?
I'm still working on it. But it's starting to pay off.
Su Bei killed my daughter!
A life for a life!
I want her dead!
Su Bei, come out!
[Su Bei A Life for a Life]
A life for a life!
Su Bei, get out!