Unforgettable Love
EP18
Don't worry.
These snakes are not poisonous.
Your wife is fainting.
Are you sure?
At that time she was confused
and short of breath.
It's like being poisoned.
I've seen those two snakes.
I am sure that they are not poisonous.
Your wife was frightened.
What's going on?
If they are poisonous,
your wife should be experiencing
the symptom of near death.
So
she was really too frightened.
Yes
She did faint in fright.
Fainted in fright.
Am I that weak?
Such an adult
can still be fainted in fright?
Maybe your wife is rather delicate.
How could someone as tough as her
can faint in fright.
You've had enough, He Qiaoyan.
I am indeed fainted in fright.
Do you mind?
In front of so many people, do you have to
laugh at me?
Thank you all.
It scared me.
I thought
at this young age
I was going to die.
If you are going to die,
before death,
what do you want to say to me?
Terminating the contract.
Give me back my reputation as a beautiful single girl,
or I'll go on chasing you
even after I die to be a ghost
Six hours to go.
That's the end of the day.
We have agreed before
as soon as the Parent-Child Day is over
we would terminate the contract.
I promise you.
Thank you for today.
It's me who wants to thank you.
During this period
you have brought a lot to my family
more than I expected.
Have an early rest.
And from today on
you don't have to hide from me anymore.
Ok.
You can leave now.
Okay.
You have serious dark circles under your eyes.
Did you not sleep well last night?
I was more used to my own bed.
Let's go.
Mommy
Xiaobao
What's up?
Mommy goes home in daddy's car.
Xiaobao
Mommy has to go back to work.
Therefore
I have to go with Uncle Ning Fang first.
You're going home with daddy,
OK?
Mommy comes with us.
How about this?
Let Xiaobao go back in my car.
We'll talk about the rest later.
Mr. He, what do you think?
Ok.
I'll take care of Xiaobao.
Take it easy.
All right.
Take care!
Let's go.
Why are you alone?
Where's my sister-in-law?
Where's Xiaobao?
What's your matter?
What?
I thought
you went there in a hurry
would bring my sister-in-law back.
As a result you not only don't get your wife back
but also left your son there.
If you have nothing to do,
just go.
Take your time.
I have business with you.
Well
Let me ask you a question first.
You have to answer me honestly.
I'm not interested.
Not interested, right?
If you are not interested,
forget it, I'll go.
The similarity can be 80 percent.
Right?
I had a feeling that this girl
could be
your dream girl.
I'd like to see
if your dream girl
is actually a real person.
The view of this back has appeared for countless times
in my dream.
Now you can make your dream come true.
But I just don't know why
when I look at this picture
I feel a little strange.
Strange?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
I don't have to check on her.
Why?
You always said she was my first girlfriend.
I don't know either
if she was my first girlfriend.
I just think
I should go and find her.
Even sometimes
she is the motivation
that keeps me going.
You don't want your motivation？
My motivation is not here.
Not here?
Yiyue
Where are you? I'll come to you.
I have a surprise for you.
OK, I'm at home.
Xiaobao
Come on, mommy do it for you.
Is it good?
After the meal,
I'll ask the driver to take you back.
With mommy.
Mommy has a lot of work to do.
Our Xiaobao
is the most sensible boy.
You'll listen to mommy, won't you?
Why isn't this bubbling?
There's water.
You help Mommy have a look
why can't it make bubbles,
ok?
Come on
You shoot me, don't you?
Well
I will revenge.
Waiting for me.
I'm coming. Don't run.
Xiaobao
There are no bubbles?
Let me have a look.
There's no water.
All right,
You can put some
water we just filled in it,
ok?
Go ahead.
How did you get in here?
Do you think we
still need secrets?
Are you here to pick up Xiaobao?
He's in the bathroom.
I'll get him.
Wait a minute.
The last contract was automatically terminated.
This is a new contract.
I thought about it for a long time.
I want to start with you
a new partnership.
What?
As for the concrete content,
you can take a look at the contract.
Your contract is so lengthy.
I don't care to look at it.
Then I'll read it to you.
Party A He Qiaoyan,
during the main contract
for Party B Qin Yiyue
had feelings beyond the regulations.
Therefore, I hereby supplement the term which
proposes further in-depth cooperation.
I would like to start a relationship with Part B
in formal.
After relationship confirmation,
if Party B has no comments,
the contract period
can be extended indefinitely,
for example, a lifetime.
What did you say?
You have said that
you have no reason
to stay with me.
Then I'll give you a reason
to stay with me forever.
Are you satisfied with this reason?
Have a guess.
I guess?
Xiaobao, Xiaobao
You've come at a bad time.
Here.
Dad made it.
♪ My heart is melting ♪
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Ning Fang wants to see me for something.
I'll be back in a minute.
Wait for me. Wait for me.
Xiaobao
Why does Dr. Ning come to your mommy?
Giving her a surprise.
A surprise?
Ning Fang
-Yiyue  -What's the matter?
I tell you...
Why are you blushing?
Do you have a fever?
A fever?
Where do you touch?
Okay
Let's go home.
Go home?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
I haven't finished talking with Ning Fang.
You can talk about it at home.
Get in the car.
In the future such thing
will not bother you.
Mr. He, Yiyue is a simple girl.
If you don't think about it clearly,
I hope you...
I know better than ever.
From today,
Yiyue and I are officially dating.
I hope Dr. Ning
can keep the necessary distance.
You are a smart man.
Why did we go home suddenly?
The conversation between me and Ning Fang
haven't been finished yet.
Ning Fang came here
just to tell you
your idol's concert has been cancelled.
My idol has a concert?
He came here specially
just to tell me that?
Of course.
But don't worry,
I and Xiaobao
will go a concert with you when we go back.
Ning Fang,
thank you for your kindness.
It's fine if I don't see the concert.
Bye
welcome
I'm back again.
welcome back.
Let me show you something.
Come here.
The room has been rearranged for you.
A new TV
and a refrigerator.
There are masks and snacks in the fridge.
When did you prepare these?
Yesterday at the mountain villa,
I prepared it in advance. Go ahead and have a look.
So many snacks I love.
I don't know if you are satisfied.
Very satisfied.
This kind of surprise can be more in the future.
It's getting late.
How about a break?
I'll go back first.
Let's watch TV together.
Great.
Sit here.
Come.
Do you eat...
I forget that
you don't like
eating this junk food.
Would you like this?
Ok.
I've seen this episode.
I can tell you
if the hero
stay or not tonight.
I'd better watch it myself.
All right.
Here you are
Good night.
What are you all doing?
Witnessing the wonders of human civilization.
The millennial iron tree has blossomed.
Do you think that to love someone
is to be assimilated by that person?
All right.
Don't even stand here.
Do what you should do.
Wait. Watch it for another while.
Mr. He
Go, go, go
I come to tell you
today's arrangement.
At three p.m.
you will have a meeting with Mr. Xu.
Then is the Company
Internal R & D meeting.
What seems to be the problem?
Nothing.
Go on.
Dr. Qin is in such a good mood.
What did you say?
I said today you
look so happy.
Is it so obvious?
Did you win a prize on Sina Weibo?
I would not tell you.
Not prize.
I think she has been
shot.
Cupid's arrow.
Miss Lin, Miss Lin
Wait a minute, Miss Lin.
Mr. He, I'm sorry.
You asked someone to write this, right?
Is there anything wrong with that?
The two of us
discord in work philosophy.
You offered to resign.
I think for us it's
the best choice.
You don't want to get married with me, do you?
It's just on the spouse column
a name.
You and me are people
who have a scale in our hearts
and know best what is important.
My last name
add your first name
will be far more than two.
Thank you for your approval.
But I hope
I won't hear
such words again.
Because my girlfriend will get angry.
Girlfriend?
Yes.
I have a formal relationship with Yiyue.
He Qiaoyan, you have to think about it clearly.
Your refusal
equals to reject the whole Lin family.
Marriage is love.
Business is profit.
I didn't harm your profits
and I will not be your enemy.
He Qiaoyan, don't be
too cocky.
Not everything
can be what you want.
People like us
can not have a free relationship.
Our love contract
has not been officially signed yet.
Come to the company today,
With the witness of the legal personnel, we will
sign it.
I can't sign the contract yet.
Why?
Don't answer him!
At this time,
You should make him
flurried because of you.
Turn back.
Turn right and go out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are one to talk.
What's the matter again?
We have agreed.
Yes? No? Yes? No?
Qin Yiyue. Qin Yiyue
If you don't like the contract
then don't sign.
If you don't like me,
just say it.
No.
If you don't like me,
who else can you like?
Who else can you like?
Mr. He
Who?
It's me.
Just in time.
Inform the legal personnel
no one is allowed to leave after work.
Go.
Ok.
Fight with me?
It's all because our before
successful cooperation,
so I think it should be the most suitable
and acceptable
way.
He Qiaoyan
You're a bonehead.
Dating is such a personal thing.
How to be said
in front of so many people?
People around me
are all my legal personnel.
For the love contract, if you
have any comments,
we can modify it on the spot.
After confirmation,
We do formal signing.
Meanwhile,
the relationship takes effect immediately.
I think before signing
this love contract,
I need to know
your true feeling.
Ok.
My true feeling is
I don't want you to
with anyone but me
have similar cooperation intention.
So sweet.
Go on, go on.
It seems that
you are not satisfied with the contract.
You want to add conditions?
Yes.
I want more initiative.
Then you will be Party A.
All conditions are yours.
Now you can just mention it.
I have only one condition.
I need Part B to clearly
and formally express to Part A
his feeling.
What I just expressed
isn't clear?
I got it!
You want a gift.
This is very simple.
Do you want a car or a house?
Just say it.
I'll buy it for you tomorrow.
Or do you like
which car in my name
or which house?
Don't worry.
These are all yours.
I don't want these.
I got it!
You want me to praise you.
Although these words have been said before,
now again,
no problem.
You are a
very good psychologist.
At the same time, you are nice to Xiaobao.
Of course, you are nice to me too.
You helped me a lot.
When you at home
I'll be at ease.
I don't want to hear that.
You like me?
So you hope
to hear I say
I
Since Party B cannot
meet the requirements of Party A,
then Party A announces the suspension of signing.
Don't worry.
Not a big deal.
What's your problem?
How did you drive？
It's your garage？
For this shopping mall,
my dad is one of the shareholders。
This garage
is really mine.
It's you again.
Following me all day.
You're so free.
You have to figure it out
who's following who?
Lily,
Amy and Xiaoxue,
You took my girls.
Those old grudges
I don't even bother to mention to you.
But Yang Ruowei is an exception.
You'd better stay away from her.
I've provoked you so many times before.
I haven't seen you act like this.
Why? This time is real?
If you do this again,
I'm really serious.
Ok, ok, ok.
The girl is too tough.
I, Wang Cheng,
for the first time see
such a girl who is being disrespectful!
Her brother,
the person who was downstairs that night
ask you for 50,000 yuan.
It's really annoying.
What's up?
I don't know what he thinks.
These two days
he spent all day downstairs of my company
and told the receptionist he wanted to see me
and he called me brother-in-law.
Having such a relative,
no matter how beautiful the girl is,
I'm not interested in.
If he does become my relative,
there's no end of trouble for the future.
You octopus.
Be careful of being killed by thunder.
Slow down.
Mr. Wen
This is a document that needs your signature.
Anything else?
Is it time to admit defeat?
For what?
Yesterday, the heart number
I have seen it.
That doesn't mean anything.
I just
Just out of a boss's
care for his subordinate.
I'm just worried about what's wrong with you.
By the way,
the man yesterday
is your brother?
None of your business.
What happened?
Mr. Wen. You ordered so much delicious food.
Why come to me?
I got it!
He Qiaoyan asked you to come.
Why did he ask me to come?
What's going on?
Aren't you two already...
Look at this.
Broke up but still connected.
I didn't expect your relations are so exciting.
I can't explain it to you in a couple of words.
In short,
we've made up.
Aren't you going to be surprised?
Forget it. Forget it
It was a terrible performance.
Don't be surprised.
He Qiaoyan's feeling for you
has been found by me for a long time.
You're those closely involved cannot see clearly.
He Qiaoyan didn't ask you to come.
Let me guess.
Who's on your mind?
To be honest,
Yang Ruowei's brother,
do you know him?
No, no, no.
It's not what you think.
Don't get me wrong.
You scared me.
Here's the deal.
Recently, her brother
always looking for Yang Ruowei's trouble.
I ran into it.
I saw the way he reached out
to his sister for money
was quite rude,
and also he made a clamor to Yang Ruowei.
They don't look like brother and sister anyway.
He's too much of a bully.
What's going on?
Do you really want to care about Ruowei?
Of course, I want to help her.
Ruowei's private affairs are rarely mentioned.
I've known her for such a long time,
but I just know a little.
Her brother
Speaking of her brother
I get angry.
He not only does nothing all day,
but also often asks Ruowei for money.
It seems that she
doesn't care about the past,
bur she has suffered so much.
Yeah
She is pretending all day
that she doesn't care about feelings.
But actually she hasn't
really been in love.
I can see that
she was carefully
protecting herself.
No giving, no harming.
Has she had a relationship?
She had a boyfriend.
But as far as I know
She has not even been touched.
Okay.
That's all I can tell you.
Ruowei is a person who hates most that others
know her past
and her fragility.
It is because I
think you care about her,
I told these to you.
But in my past experience,
I can tell you,
if you really care about someone,
be brave enough to protect her.
No matter how thick her heart wall is
as long as you try
there will be a way to follow.
What way?
Please, the beautiful fairy,
show me the way.
The way is
giving up tricks.
This is delicious.
Try this one.
It's potato.
Giving up tricks.
This roast chicken is also delicious.
What's up?
I just want to tell you
I was at the place where we last
had wine.
Don't tell me where you are.
I'm not your husband.
Fine.
It's me who flatter myself.
I thought someone
needed a military division urgently
to answer his questions.
Well
I'll be there in half an hour.
Welcome Mr. He.
You are quite on time.
Sit down.
The decanter of wine has been served.
I need to drive a car.
But the deal is that
you pay today.
How did you know that
I need to be answered questions today.
I went to see Dr. Qin today.
Even though she said you made up
it's obviously you two have some questions.
Come on, what's the problem?
Nothing.
Why did you come to my girlfriend?
You're so jealous.
Don't worry.
I came to her today
just for a few questions
about Yang Ruowei.
Go ahead.
Your life mentor is in place.
Talk about your dream.
Oh no, talk about your confusion.
Your last time,
last time said to a girl that
you like her,
When was it?
Last month
or last week? I don't remember it.
Why do you ask this?
Don't waste my time.
Say something useful.
What are you doing?
What Dr. Qin wants
is just the
moment of saying your true feeling
and unabashed language expression.
You can create this opportunity
and the moment.
Tell me the way.
It's easy.
Appointment.
Appointment?
A perfect date.
A perfect date...
Keep it down.
You will scare the fish away.
Why did I come with you
to this damn place.
Don't you just want to learn fishing?
Wear such a short skirt.
Do you feel cold?
No.
Then why is your face so red?
This is my blush.
Blush.
What's wrong?
Swatting mosquitoes!
What's your feeling?
Isn't it obvious enough?
This is my feeling.
Be careful.
New shoes.
Wen Gu told me
I can arrange a
perfect date
so that you can
see my feeling.
I specifically searched for
what is a perfect date.
A perfect date
can make us
enhance mutual affection
and also
impress us.
And fishing can help us
stay together quietly for a long time
and focus on each other.
Uncle, have you caught any fish?
Not yet.
Come on!
That's it?
It moved!
Take it up! Come on!
No.
Don't you want to learn?
Xiaobao likes fish best.
If he know the fish
was caught by his mommy,
he is going to be very happy.
Hurry up!
There is a fish on the hook.