NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century
I lived in secret. Until now.
- I know the risk, but I have to know her.
DAMON : Elena. Dead ringer for Katherine.
- Our love for Katherine wasn't real.
- It was for me. I'm gonna bring her back.
There's a tomb underneath the church.
A spell sealed Katherine in the tomb.
- Tell me how to get in.
NOAH : Grimoire.
- Where is it?
- Check the journal. Jonathan Gilbert's.
The Grimoire, it was Emily's, right?
That's what you need? I'll help you.
You just couldn't live without me,
huh?
Your eye.
JEREMY : Where'd she go?
- Where'd who go?
Anna.
Elena.
I wouldn't.
Don't try to escape. Don't even move.
Do you understand?
I understand.
- Seriously?
- I told her not to move.
I did that eye thing.
But forgot the lesson about vervain.
She dates a vampire.
- Who are you? What do you want?
ANNA : Does it matter?
Bonnie?
Oh, my God.
Anna took Elena.
Yeah, I got that
from your 600 voicemails.
Damon, all night long, every single street
in town, I've been searching.
- What if your blood hasn't passed?
- At least you know you'll see her again.
Please.
What do you know?
You were with Anna,
you know where she's living. Tell me.
Nope.
You can go.
Really.
You know,
all I can remember is hating you.
Might have been different...
...but your choices erased
anything good about you.
But see, I also know that you have just
as much reason to hate me.
This all began with me.
Katherine got taken away from you...
...because of me.
And I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
So please, just tell me
what you know.
It's Elena, Damon.
If you know something, tell me.
(SIGHS)
I mean this sincerely.
I hope Elena dies.
Bonnie?
- Elena?
- Oh, you're okay.
- My head.
- Here.
- Oh, my God. Ben is a va...
- Shh.
(WHISPERING)
They can hear.
I'm so stupid.
No, he had all of us fooled.
What's going on? Why are we here?
It must have something to do
with the tomb and Emily's spell book.
- Spell book?
- Damon said that it could open the tomb.
Why didn't I know about any of this?
I was trying to keep you out,
hoping it would never come to this.
Come to what?
They need a witch...
...to break the spell
and let the vampires out.
- No way.
- I know. I know. I know.
You're wasting your time.
I'm not gonna help you.
That's why she's here.
Motivation for you to behave.
You know, you shouldn't be so desperate.
You made it too easy.
She wants to talk to you.
(ELENA GRUNTS)
Well, well. Elena Gilbert.
You really are Katherine's doppelganger.
You must have
the Salvatore boys reeling.
Who are you?
I'm Anna.
Your brother may have mentioned me?
I mean, we're, like, practically dating.
TYLER : Ten kegs? You know how much
damage we could do?
- Duke's got it all hooked up.
- Duke's a douche.
Yeah, a douche with 10 kegs.
A.k.a., my new best friend.
(CHUCKLES)
- What's the problem, Gilbert?
- Don't have one, Lockwood.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
You ever get bored of it?
- Of what?
- Yourself.
- Heh, heh.
- Keep laughing, buddy.
CAROLINE :
Hey, Jeremy.
Where is Elena? I have been texting her
and Bonnie all day about Duke's party.
Uh, she went somewhere with Stefan.
(SIGHS)
I'm not gonna be one of those girls who
disappears because she has a boyfriend.
Who is Duke?
Guy that graduated
a couple years ago.
And he throws a party
every time he comes home from Duke.
Wait, Duke goes to Duke?
His real name's Bob or something.
He's a total ass, but he buys the beer.
You know, you should come.
Uh, yeah, I don't think so.
No, seriously. Everyone goes.
Even quiet loner little brothers.
Hmm.
Think about it.
- Hey.
So I have a speech. It is fully scripted
and well rehearsed. Are you ready for it?
You wrote a speech?
Yes. It's a "You kissed me and I don't
want things to be weird" speech.
- It's pre-emptive.
- Ha, ha. Pre-emptive?
Yeah, you know, in case
you were having second thoughts...
...or regrets, or were ooged out by it.
- "Ooged," huh?
Heh.
- Can I get on with the speech part?
- Yeah, go for it.
CAROLINE : So I know that you don't think that
this is going to work out between us.
I just wanna let you know
that right here and right now...
...l'm offering you an out.
Like an escape clause.
MATT : Why are you giving me
an escape clause?
I don't wanna make assumptions
about what it is we're doing here.
Got it.
So if you would like to exercise it...
...just let me know.
I'm good, but thanks.
Okay.
- Good.
- Yeah.
- So see you for Duke's tonight?
Heh.
- Yes?
- Hi there.
I'm, uh, looking for Bonnie.
She's not here.
- Oh, do you know when she would be...?
- Never.
Heh. Quite an opinion for someone
who doesn't know me.
You got nerve knocking on a witch's door
and asking her for anything.
What did I do?
Spirits talk, Mr. Salvatore,
and so does my granddaughter.
You are no friend to us.
Now, get off my porch.
Step outside and say that.
(GROANING)
I am not Bonnie.
You don't wanna mess with me.
- Bonnie's not gonna open the tomb.
- Oh, I think she will.
ELENA : Do you really want Katherine
out that bad?
Trust me. No one I know
wants to see that girl again.
Except Damon, the love-struck idiot.
Then what is it?
Or who is it?
My mother's in there.
Katherine couldn't help herself.
She just had to toy around
with both of the Salvatore brothers.
Then when she got caught,
so did my mother.
I watched Jonathan Gilbert
take her away.
I'm sorry.
You really mean that, don't you?
ANNA : Yeah, we'll skip the "dead mom" bonding
so you can start serving a purpose.
- Which is what?
- Leverage.
This belong to you? Uh-uh.
(LINE RINGING)
STEFAN : Elena, are you okay?
She's fine, for now. Tell me you have
the Grimoire, and she'll stay fine.
- I can get it.
ANNA : Which means your brother has it.
And I have the witch.
So one of you...
...had better meet me
in the town square in 30 minutes...
...so we can safely discuss how fun
it's gonna be to work together.
Go ahead. Grovel again.
Oh, wait. No.
I don't care.
I'm leaving.
Keep them buttoned down.
Compulsion won't work.
Just use violence.
Right. I got that.
Sit. Behave.
So you're the key to this.
Literally.
The one who opens the door.
Tell me, how long
have you been a witch?
Is there anything to drink here?
Are you offering?
There's water on the nightstand.
Hey. Can I have a sip?
(SHOUTING)
Come back in, shut the door.
Don't hurt her.
Don't make me.
Lock it.
JEREMY :
Anna!
Hey. What, uh...?
What happened to you last night?
Sorry, I had to leave.
- I told your sister.
- I haven't seen her.
- I gotta run.
- Do you wanna go to a party tonight?
- Do I what?
- The guy that's throwing it's a douche...
...but it's supposed to be fun.
I figured, you know,
safety in numbers.
Heh, so you're finally ready
to go out with me, are you?
JEREMY : It's been a while since I've been to a party,
and I wanna get back out there.
You know, not be such a loner.
And, uh, I like you, you're fun.
And you're also kind
of strange and lurky...
...but, uh, I guess I like that too.
So, yeah, you should come
to the party with me.
It's in the woods
by that old cemetery.
Oh. It's there, huh?
That sounds cool.
Uh, I'll meet you.
Okay. Great.
- Cool.
- Heh.
Got a hot date or you just plan
on nabbing the entire Gilbert family?
Party. Right next to the old cemetery.
Isn't that nice of them?
Lots of warm bodies for starving vampires.
I told you, I work alone.
Yeah, so do I.
But you're minus a witch
and I'm minus a spell book.
So, what do you say?
Stefan will come after you,
you know that.
For messing with Elena.
Then he won't be too happy if I kill her
when I don't get what I want.
When do you wanna do this?
God, it's like 1864 all over again.
You Salvatores are truly pathetic
when it comes to women.
Tonight. After sundown.
Meet at the church.
BEN : Witches don't have eternal life, right?
So you guys can die.
Yeah, we can die.
Huh. That sucks.
(SHOUTING)
Stefan.
STEFAN :
Girls, get outside.
When the sun goes down, leave town.
If I ever see you again, I will kill you.
How did you know where we were?
Many things can fuel a witch's power.
Worry, anger.
After Stefan told me that
they had taken you, I had a lot of both.
A simple locator spell
was easy after that.
I'm sorry.
About all of this.
Not as sorry as they're gonna be.
- So, what do we do now?
- Well, for now, you need to stay here.
A prisoner in my own home?
I don't think so.
I can't protect you if you leave.
We'll protect ourselves.
ELENA : We need to let him
have Katherine back.
He's not gonna stop until he gets her.
If we help him, maybe that ends it.
No. He doesn't deserve
to get what he wants.
What other choice do we have?
Witches being pulled down
by vampire problems.
As much as we try to do
to stay out of it.
SHEILA : I'll open the tomb.
You get your brother's girl
and destroy the rest with fire.
Then this will be all over.
We have to get Damon to agree.
- He already agreed once.
- Yeah, and we double-crossed him.
- So now he's angry.
- He's hurt. There's a difference.
I think I know what I have to do.
You've got to be kidding me.
It was Stefan.
- There was nothing I could do.
- Just shut up. Stop talking.
Without the witch,
we don't have Damon or the Grimoire.
Damon's not gonna stop.
He'll find a way to get in.
And we're gonna be there
when he does.
I'm gonna have to change the locks.
You stage a jailbreak?
- Stefan.
- Oh, brother.
Ever the white knight.
I convinced Bonnie to help you.
I doubt that.
I'm not gonna say that I'm sorry we got
the Grimoire without you last night...
...because I'm not really.
- Well, at least you're honest.
- I was protecting the people I love.
But so were you,
in your own twisted way.
And as hard as it is to figure, we're all
on the same side, after the same thing.
- I'm not interested.
- Yes, you are.
Because you were willing
to work with us yesterday.
DAMON : Fool me once, shame on you.
ELENA : Okay. When we were in Atlanta, why
didn't you use your compulsion on me?
Who's to say I didn't?
You didn't.
I know you didn't.
But you could have.
You and I...
...we have something.
An understanding.
And I know that my betrayal hurt you.
Different from how it is
with you and Stefan.
But I'm promising you this now,
I will help you get Katherine back.
(GROANS)
I wish I could believe you.
Ask me if I'm lying now.
You know Anna won't stop, by the way,
no matter what I do.
Then we'll deal with it.
I didn't compel you in Atlanta,
because we were having fun.
I wanted it to be real.
I'm trusting you.
Don't make me regret it.
(CROWD LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
(TOKYO POLICE SQUAD'S "IN A CAVE" PLAYING ON STEREO)
The Duke party. I forgot.
I hope they stay clear of the church.
- Your hope, not mine.
MATT : Elena, hey.
Elena, oh, my God.
Where have you been?
- Long story, no time to tell it.
- I wasn't talking to you.
- Sure you were.
- We haven't met. I'm Matt.
DAMON : Matt, there's a reason we haven't met.
You and I are going that way.
I'm sorry, guys.
STEFAN : Cleared the debris away,
set the torches like you asked...
...we can get down now.
BONNIE :
What is that?
It's everything I need to destroy them.
Are you sure Damon
will come back with her?
(DAMON WHISTLES)
Brother. Witches.
STEFAN : Everything okay?
- I just wanna get this over with.
Are we ready?
I guess so.
MAN : Come on. Now go, go, go.
Keep going.
Go. Come on, man. Go, go, go.
- Done.
MAN : That's my man.
Hey, uh, I'll be right back.
Hey, man.
You got any weed?
What? You're kidding me, right?
You act like a dick
every time we cross paths...
...and now you wanna party?
- Lighten up. I'm just asking a question.
Look, I don't get you, man.
It's a party.
You're a partier.
There's no need to psychoanalyze it.
I don't party anymore. And even if I did,
it wouldn't be with you.
No problem.
TYLER : Carry on just standing there
by yourself, all alone.
The enemy of fun.
Do you even have any friends?
(TOKYO POLICE CLUB SINGING ON STEREO):
Filling an empty glass
Stained my teeth with more red wine
I'm a romantic
(CHUCKLES)
Thank God.
Weird hello, but okay.
- What's the matter?
- Uh, nothing. I mean, just...
It's nothing.
- Come on. Let's walk.
- Heh.
SHEILA :
Air.
Earth.
Fire.
Water.
That's it? Just water from the tap?
As opposed to what?
I just figured maybe it would have to be
blessed or mystical or something.
STEFAN :
What's that?
DAMON :
It's for Katherine.
I gotta have something
to get her going.
Unless your girl is offering up a vein.
(WHISPERING)
Admit it.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
You can't wait to get rid of me.
- I can't wait to get rid of you.
- Mm.
We're ready.
ANNA : This place is wild.
JEREMY : You like dead people, huh?
I'm strange, remember?
You okay?
Yeah, yeah. Uh...
This place makes me think
about someone.
A dead someone?
No, no.
Just someone I used to know.
So, uh, hey, heh, we made it all of what,
37 minutes in that party?
Heh. Not your scene?
I'm not really sure
what my scene is anymore.
ANNA :
Hmm.
So, what do you say?
You wanna be a...?
You wanna be part of my non-scene?
I would happily be a part
of your non-scene.
Except...
...uh, I'm leaving.
Wait, what?
Yeah, my mom and I
are moving away.
Oh, uh...
That's... That's a bummer.
- Yeah?
- Well, yeah.
So...
...I guess this is goodbye.
I guess it is.
Anna, your face.
- It's nothing.
- It didn't look like nothing.
You didn't have to hit him that hard.
Yes, I did.
Grab him and let's go.
I'm taking him to meet my mother.
(CROWD LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
- Swoop.
- Hey.
Where's your date?
Who knows?
- Aw, is the honeymoon over already?
- Maybe.
After all that grief you gave me
about liking her.
Figured it would have last longer
than five minutes.
Look, I don't know if I can do
the whole public couple thing.
She seems like
she might be a little clingy.
Well, good.
I need my boy single anyway.
Oh, incoming.
- Hey, there you are.
- Here I am.
TYLER : Yeah, well, I'm not drunk enough,
so I'm just gonna go get another beer.
- So?
CAROLINE : I have another speech.
Okay.
The hand thing with Elena,
it was lame.
Well, I was lame.
Hey, your feelings for Elena aside...
...Damon was there and he was always
such a jerk to me...
...and I wanted to show off
that I was with the good guy.
So anyway, I was lame.
So forgiven?
Yeah. Of course, yeah.
(BONNIE & SHEILA CHANTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
DAMON : What are they saying?
- Sounds Latin.
- Don't think it's Latin.
What's happening?
(CRASHING NEARBY)
It worked.
Well, of course it worked.
- Don't you have some fires to build?
- I'm gonna get the gasoline. I'll be back.
- You ready?
- What?
DAMON : Do you think I'm gonna go in by myself
so you can seal me?
- I'll bring the walls down.
- You'll bring the walls down if I don't.
- You think I trust you?
- As much as I trust you.
ELENA : Enough. Both of you.
Look, he needs leverage.
He needs to know
you're not gonna shut the door.
I get it.
I'll go.
May I?
BEN : Dark down there?
STEFAN : I thought I told you to leave.
I considered it.
Then I thought, "Screw you."
ANNA :
Hey, hero.
I'm going down there
to get my mother.
I can't let you do that.
Ben's about to make a main course
out of Elena's brother.
So you can stop me or him.
Your choice.
What is that?
DAMON : They can sense you.
Now, where is she?
Damon.
BONNIE :
Hey, you're not going in there.
You think you can stop me?
Bonnie.
Why did you let her go in?
Because she isn't coming out, baby.
None of them are.
STEFAN : Do you really think
that she cares about you?
Hmm? You're disposable.
I don't care.
She already gave me what I want.
You gonna say, uh, "Eternal life?"
You really that stupid?
You know, I've heard about you.
You don't feed.
You're not strong enough to beat me.
(GRUNTING AND SHOUTING)
- Is that all you got?
- No.
I got this.
(SHOUTING)
Damon?
Damon.
(SNARLING NEARBY)
(ELENA GASPING)
(ELENA SCREAMS)
Where's Elena?
Damon took her inside.
- What?
SHEILA : Stefan...
...if you go in there,
you won't come out.
What did you do?
Opening the door didn't remove the seal.
It just opened the door.
What's the seal?
Some seals
keep vampires from entering.
This one keeps them from coming out.
STEFAN :
Elena's human.
She can leave.
Anna and Katherine can't.
Damon can't.
You were never planning
on breaking the spell.
SHEILA : I told you.
I will protect my own.
Elena can get out.
That's all that matters.
ANNA : You must have a taste for it.
You scream and shriek
and even bother to escape...
...but then you just come
right back to it.
Mother. Mother.
- Your boyfriend did this, you know.
- His father did.
And Jonathan Gilbert.
Made a choice that it would be Gilbert
blood that brought her back to life.
I had Jeremy all ready to go, but...
(ELENA SCREAMS)
Stefan!
BONNIE : You can't just leave him in there,
Grams.
He made his choice.
No.
No. Here.
Just show me what to do. I'll do it.
We are not strong enough.
Even if we bring the seal down, there's
no guarantee we could get it up again.
You said it yourself, "Many things
can fuel a witch's power."
Help me.
Or I'll do it alone.
(GRUNTING)
ELENA :
Please don't.
ANNA :
Get strong.
Let her go.
ANNA :
No!
- Go. Go. I'm right behind you.
- Please...
PEARL :
Anna.
Mama.
- Annabel.
- Mother.
(ANNA SOBBING)
Elena. Stefan...
He's right behind me.
Stefan, what are you doing?
It's gonna be okay. We'll fix it.
What is it?
I can't.
"Can't"? Can't what?
The spell's still up.
We can't get them out yet.
You went in not knowing
if you can come back out?
Oh, my God.
I heard you scream.
We can't leave him in there.
We promised him, both of us.
I know.
Even if we're able to break the seal,
we won't be able to hold it for long.
She's not here.
STEFAN : Damon.
- She's not here.
STEFAN :
What?
She's not here!
(BOTH CHANTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
ELENA :
I think it's working.
I just wanted my mother back.
Jeremy's fine. He's outside.
We won't touch him.
SHEILA :
Bonnie, keep going.
They better hurry.
Stefan, they can't hold it much longer!
- Damon, we need to get out of here.
- They locked her inside.
If we don't leave now,
we're not getting out.
How could she not be in here?
It's not worth
spending eternity down here.
- She's not worth it.
- No!
ELENA :
Damon.
Please.
Oh, my God. I can't.
Yes, you can.
(BOTH CHANTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(CROWD LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
(BLACK REBEL MOTORCYCLE CLUB'S "ALL
YOU DO IS TALK" PLAYING ON STEREO)
Is this for real?
Is what for real?
You being all cool
and honest and open.
CAROLINE : Speech number three?
I want this to work.
And I'm scared that you're gonna change
your mind and you're not gonna want it.
I don't wanna mess it up.
I don't wanna mess it up either.
(BLACK REBEL MOTORCYCLE CLUB SINGING): Help yourself, don't think
Help yourself, don't speak
- He's okay.
JEREMY : Ugh.
He's all right.
I'm sorry.
Hey, let me help you.
SHEILA : Oh, I'm fine. You don't need
to coddle me, baby.
It was a big spell, Grams.
I could tell it took a lot out of you.
I'll be fine.
How's your head?
JEREMY : Uh, it's all right. I just...
I wish I knew how I passed out.
I didn't drink that much. I swear.
ELENA : And you don't remember anything?
The whole thing's cloudy. I just...
I know how this looks. I'm sorry.
No, Jeremy, don't be sorry.
You didn't do anything, okay?
Yeah, okay.
I've gotta head over to Bonnie's
for a little bit...
...but is there anything that you need?
No, I'm just...
I'm gonna crash and...
Okay, well, Jenna's here
and I'll be back soon.
- You knew Katherine wasn't there.
- You wouldn't have helped me.
No! No!
- Why do you get a happy ending?
- Please. You wouldn't have helped me.
- Why do you get it and I don't?
- The guard.
The one at the church
who locked us in.
She promised to turn him.
He was obsessed with her.
- No. Damon.
- She had him under her spell...
- Please.
...like everybody else.
He let her go.
(PEARL GASPS)
Last I saw her...
...was Chicago...
...1983.
She knew where you were, Damon.
She didn't care.
Sorry.
I just got to Bonnie's.
- Everything all right?
ELENA : Yeah.
How's Damon? Is he gonna be okay?
I don't know.
Can I call you later?
Yeah, of course.
BONNIE : Here you go, Grams.
Grams?
Grams.
Grams, wake up.
Grams?
(SOBBING)
Elena!
Grams.
Wake up. She's not breathing.
Oh, she's not breathing.
Please. Wake up.
Yes, I need an ambulance.
2 Oak Street.
It's an emergency. Quick.
- Bonnie. Bonnie.
- No, no. I can fix this.
ELENA : Bonnie. Bonnie. Bonnie.
- No. I can fix this. No!
(GRUNTING)