NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries :
STEFAN : For over a century
I have lived in secret.
Until now.
I know the risk, but I had no choice.
I have to know her.
- I'm Elena.
- I'm Stefan.
ELENA : I know. We have history together.
Last spring my parents' car
drove off of a bridge into the lake.
STEFAN : You won't be sad forever, Elena.
STEFAN :  I live with my uncle.
ELENA :  Any siblings?
STEFAN :  None that I talk to.
DAMON :  Hello, brother.
STEFAN :  Damon.
DAMON : Elena...
...she's a dead ringer for Katherine.
- But wherever you go, people die.
JEREMY : My God, it's Vicki.
ELENA : Something bit her.
She's losing a lot of blood.
Somebody help.
VICKI : Vampire.
- Don't you crave a little?
- Stop it.
DAMON : Let's just go straight for Elena.
Imagine what her blood tastes like.
STEFAN : Stop.
Stay away from Elena.
DAMON : I take that as an invitation.
- Hey, did you hear that?
- Hear what?
I heard thunder.
- There's no thunder.
- Are you sure?
Because if it rains,
we won't be able to see the comet.
It's not gonna rain.
Listen, I got you a little something.
It's back in the car.
- Don't you move.
- Mm-mm.
(GRUNTS)
- Stay dry.
- It's not gonna rain.
(SIGHS)
(PATTERING)
I knew it.
I told you it was gonna rain.
(DRIPPING)
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING AND PANTING)
Open. No.
Please.
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
ELENA :
Dear diary  :
This morning is different.
There's change.
I can sense it. Feel it.
STEFAN :
I'm awake.
For the first time in a long time...
...I feel completely
and undeniably wide awake.
ELENA : For once,
I don't regret the day before it begins.
STEFAN :
I welcome the day.
ELENA AND STEFAN  (IN UNISON) :
Because I know...
STEFAN :
...I will see her again.
ELENA :
...I will see him again.
For the first time in a long time,
I feel good.
JENNA : Hold on. Do I look adult?
As in, respectfully parental?
ELENA : Depends where you're going.
JENNA : Jeremy's parent-teacher conference.
Hair up or down?
Sexy stewardess.
- Boozy housewife.
- Up it is.
- You're feisty today.
- I feel good.
ELENA : Which is rare,
so I've decided to go with it.
Fly free.
Walk on sunshine and all that stuff.
- Where is Jeremy?
- Oh, he left early.
JENNA : Something about getting
to woodshop early to finish a birdhouse?
There is no woodshop, is there?
- No.
- Yeah.
NURSE : You can't be in here, hon.
Visiting hours don't start till 9.
I just... How is she?
She's lost a lot of blood.
Yeah, but she's gonna be okay, right?
She needs her rest.
So you come back later. Come on.
TANNER : Originally discovered
nearly five centuries ago...
...it hasn't been over Mystic Falls
in over a 145 years.
Now, the comet will be its brightest...
...right after dusk
during tomorrow's celebration.
Are we bothering you?
Mr. Salvatore?
Miss Gilbert.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
STEFAN :
I brought it.
I told you.
ELENA : "Wuthering Heights by Ellis Bell."
You know, I can't believe
she didn't use her real name.
STEFAN : All the Bronte sisters
used pseudonyms.
It was the time.
Female writers
weren't very accepted then.
ELENA : Where did you get it?
Uh... It was passed down
through the family.
- Ah.
- I have lots of books. Go ahead.
- Keep it.
- Oh, no, l...
But I would like to read it again.
I promise I'll give it back.
Okay.
CAROLINE : I'm confused.
Are you psychic or clairvoyant?
BONNIE : Technically, Grams says I'm a witch.
My ancestors were these really cool
Salem witch chicks or something.
Grams tried to explain it, but she was
looped on the liquor. I tuned out.
Crazy family, yes.
Witches, I don't think so.
CAROLINE : Yeah, feel free to conjure up the name
and number of that guy from last night.
BONNIE : I didn't see him. You did.
Why didn't you just talk to him?
I don't know. I was drunk.
JEREMY : Hey, Tyler.
Hey, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Just wondering how Vicki is,
since you guys are close.
- Is she okay?
- She's fine.
- Now get out of here.
- How bad is she?
What attacked her? Is she gonna
recover? Was she happy to see you?
- What room was she in?
- I'm gonna kick your ass.
Yeah, you keep saying that, but when
are you gonna actually do it? Huh?
Because I vote for right here
right now.
TYLER : Walk away, Gilbert.
It's your final warning.
JEREMY : This is your final warning.
I'm sick of watching you play Vicki.
If you hurt her one more time,
I swear to God I will kill you.
TYLER : Damn, that was like a death threat.
Did you hear that?
MATT : They're keeping her overnight, but she
should be able to come home tomorrow.
- That's good news.
- Yeah.
ELENA : Did you get in touch with your mom?
MATT : Called and left a message.
She's in Virginia Beach
with her boyfriend.
So we'll see how long
it takes her to come rushing home.
- Vicki's lucky that she's okay.
MATT : I know.
And now there's talk
of some missing campers.
ELENA : Did she say what kind of animal
it was that attacked her?
- She said it was a vampire.
ELENA : What?
MATT : Yeah, she wakes up last night,
mutters, "Vampire," and passes out.
ELENA : Okay, that's weird.
MATT : Think she was drunk.
So, what's up with you
and the new guy?
Matt,
the last thing I wanna do is hurt you.
You know, I'm actually
gonna go back to the hospital.
I wanna be there when Vicki wakes up,
get the real story about last night.
Okay.
TANNER :
As Jeremy's teacher, I'm concerned.
All right, it's the third day of school,
and he's skipped six of his classes.
JENNA: Mr. Tanner, are you aware
that Jeremy and Elena's parents died?
TANNER : Four months ago, a great loss.
Car accident.
Wickery Bridge,
if I remember correctly.
And you're related to the family how?
The mother's kid sister.
- Younger sister. Yes.
- Right.
Six classes? Are you sure?
I mean, that's kind of hard to do.
Not when you're on drugs.
It's his attempt at coping,
Miss Sommers.
And the signs are there. He's moody,
withdrawn, argumentative, hung-over.
Are there any other relatives
in the picture?
- I'm their sole guardian.
- Uh-huh.
Could there be?
What are you suggesting exactly?
TANNER : It's an impossible job, isn't it?
Raising two teens.
JENNA : It's been tough, but no. It's not.
TANNER : Wrong answer.
It is an extremely impossible job...
...and anything less
and you're not doing it properly.
(SIGHS)
(WOMAN TAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA)
Whoa.
Vick. Vicki, hey.
Vick, it's Matt. Hey, what's wrong?
- No! No!
- Hey. Vicki. Vicki.
- It's me, Vicki. Stop.
- No! No!
- Nurse.
STEFAN : It was an animal that attacked you.
It came out of the night and jumped you.
You blacked out.
That's all you remember.
- That's all I remember.
- An animal attacked you. You blacked out.
- That's all you remember.
- That's all I remember.
Nurse, I need help. It's my sister.
NURSE :
She seems fine.
BONNIE :
I was talking to Grams.
She said the comet
is a sign of impeding doom.
Last time it passed over Mystic Falls,
there was lots of death.
So much blood and carnage,
it created a bed of paranormal activity.
CAROLINE : Mm. Yeah, and then you poured
Grams another shot...
...and she told you about the aliens.
So then what?
ELENA : So then, nothing.
You and Stefan talked all night.
There was no sloppy first kiss,
or touchy-feely of any kind?
- Nope, we didn't go there.
CAROLINE : Not even a handshake?
I mean, Elena, we are your friends.
Okay? You are supposed to share the smut.
- We just talked for hours.
- What is with the blockage?
Just jump his bones already.
Okay, it's easy.
Boy likes girl, girl likes boy, sex.
- Profound.
CAROLINE : Mm.
- Where are you going?
- Caroline's right.
It is easy. If I sit here long enough,
I'll end up talking myself out of it...
...instead of doing what I started
the day saying I was gonna do.
JENNA :
I picked up dinner.
Tacos. Had an urge for guacamole.
- No, I'm good, thanks.
- Eat anyway.
It's a ruse. I wanna talk.
Hey, you. Come. Sit.
Back at school. Freshman year.
I could eat my weight in nachos.
With extra cheese.
It was my munchy food
whenever I got stoned.
You get high?
Did. Past tense.
But, yeah. Loved it.
Anything to get a little
distraction from life. Reality.
And it works. For a while.
Never lasts though.
I'm not saying I wouldn't
love to rail back and kick it...
...but with a thesis looming
and a waistline expanding...
(SIGHS)
- What the...?
- Finally, you're awake.
MATT : Hey, how are you feeling?
You look better.
I was worried before.
You really had me freaked out
with all that screaming.
VICKI : Wait, what are you talking about?
You don't remember?
I feel fine.
Good. Good.
The doctor said you could
come home tomorrow.
Vick, what attacked you
in the woods?
An animal.
What else could it have been?
JEREMY : Hey, how do you feel?
I'm okay.
MATT : I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go grab a coffee.
Hey, Jer.
Why are you here?
I wanted to see
how you were doing.
VICKI : Did you see that look on Matt's face?
That was suspicion.
I don't want people
to find out about us, Jeremy.
- You gotta get over that.
- Tyler is finally showing some interest.
JEREMY : You have to get over that too.
Do you see Mr. Concern?
Tyler? Are you under there?
No.
VICKI : It's not cool for people to know,
okay?
I'm older than you,
and Matt and Elena would freak.
JEREMY : No one's gonna suspect anything.
Why wouldn't I check on you?
I'm the one who found you.
- You are?
- Yeah.
I carried you out of the woods.
Thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
(RINGS BELL)
(DOOR CREAKS)
ELENA : Stefan?
Stefan?
(CROW CAWS)
I'm sorry for barging in.
The door was...
...open.
DAMON : You must be Elena.
I'm Damon. Stefan's brother.
ELENA : He didn't tell me he had a brother.
Well, Stefan's not one to brag.
Please. Come.
I'm sure Stefan
will be along any second.
Wow. This is your living room?
DAMON : Living room, parlor,
Sotheby's auction.
It's a little kitschy for my taste.
I see why my brother's so smitten.
It's about time.
For a time, I never thought he'd get over
the last one.
Nearly destroyed him.
ELENA : The last one?
DAMON : Yeah. Katherine. His girlfriend?
Oh, you two haven't had
the awkward exes conversation yet.
Nope.
Oops. Well, I'm sure it'll come up now.
Maybe he didn't tell you because he didn't
want you to think he was on the rebound.
We all know
how those relationships end.
You say it like every relationship
is doomed to end.
I'm a fatalist.
Hello, Stefan.
STEFAN : Elena.
I didn't know you were coming over.
- I know, I should have called...
- Oh. Don't be silly.
DAMON : You're welcome any time.
Isn't she, Stefan?
I should break out the family
photo albums or some home movies.
But I have to warn you...
...he wasn't always such a looker.
STEFAN : Thank you for stopping by, Elena.
It was nice to see you.
ELENA : Yeah, I should probably go.
It was nice to meet you, Damon.
DAMON : Great meeting you too, Elena.
ELENA :
Stefan?
(DAMON WHISTLES)
DAMON : Great gal. Whew. She's got spunk.
You, on the other hand, look pooped.
Did you overexert yourself today?
Let me guess. Hospital.
STEFAN : Someone had to clean up your mess.
DAMON : Well, were you successful?
Did the powers of persuasion work?
If you don't feed properly,
none of those tricks work right.
- How long was Elena here?
- Are you worried, Stefan?
Scared we may be doomed
to repeat the past?
Isn't that why you play your game,
I'm a High School Human?
- I'm not playing any game.
- Of course you are.
We both know the closest
you'll ever get to humanity...
...is when you rip it open
and feed on it.
What kind of game
are you playing, Damon?
Guess you'll just have
to wait and see, won't you?
ELENA : He's on the rebound
and has raging family issues.
JENNA : Well, at least it's an ex-girlfriend.
Wait till you date a guy
with mommy issues.
Or cheating issues.
Or amphetamine issues.
Jeremy.
Jeremy, where were you?
JEREMY : More stoner stories?
Look, Jenna, I get it.
You were cool once.
And that's cool.
Oh, no, no, no.
Ow. Why? Why did you do that?
Listen up.
Quick ditching class, or you're grounded.
No discussion.
JEREMY : Parental authority. I like it.
Sleep tight.
(MOANING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Matt.
Matty?
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
BONNIE :
Night of the Comet.
Would you like a program?
He didn't call, huh?
Or text.
ELENA : We never even exchanged that stuff.
We never got to the texting part.
- That's an important milestone.
- Isn't it?
The timing was wrong anyway.
- When is it ever right?
- I'm not ready, Bonnie.
Who is?
- At least I put myself out there.
- Is that what you're calling it?
What do you mean?
All I'm hearing
is reasons why you can't.
ZACH : What is Damon doing here?
Why did he come home?
I came home. He wants to make
my life miserable. It's how he enjoys his.
He's putting us at risk.
This girl in the hospital could talk.
She won't.
- I took care of her.
- You're sure?
(SIGHS)
I'm not sure, Zach.
I don't know how well it worked.
I'm not as strong as Damon.
- What happens if it doesn't work?
- I don't know.
- I'll deal with it.
- Is she worth it, Uncle Stefan?
This girl you came back for?
JEREMY :
What are you doing here?
VICKI : Fighting with Robert
about my schedule.
You'd think getting ripped up
would merit an extra sick day.
- Well, you feeling okay?
- I hurt, right?
- The doctor gave you something right?
- The kid stuff. Nothing with an O in it.
I think they were onto me.
Here, knock yourself out. Literally.
VICKl  :
Thanks, Jer.
So you gonna watch the comet later?
I hadn't really thought about it.
But I could be talked into it.
- I'll meet you out there in a few.
TYLER : Hey, Vick.
- How you feeling?
- Like you care.
(CHUCKLES)
What are you looking at, Gilbert?
- Hey, I got you a candle.
- Hi. Thanks.
- Hey.
ELENA :
Thank you.
You're welcome.
STEFAN :
Thank you.
Hi.
You know, that comet...
...it's been traveling across space
for thousands of years.
All alone.
ELENA : Yeah, Bonnie says
it's a harbinger of evil.
STEFAN : I think it's just a ball
of snow and ice...
...trapped on a path
that it can't escape.
Once every 145 years,
it gets to come home.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I wasn't myself.
ELENA : You seem to spend
a lot of time apologizing.
STEFAN : Well, I have a lot to apologize for.
Yesterday, that wasn't about you, okay?
You didn't tell me
that you had a brother.
We're not close. It's complicated.
Always.
He told me about your ex. Katherine?
What did he say?
ELENA : That she broke your heart.
That was a long time ago.
When you lose someone,
it stays with you.
Always reminding you
of how easy it is to get hurt.
Elena.
It's okay, Stefan. I get it.
You have no idea how much I get it.
Complicated brother? Check.
Complicated ex? Check.
Too complicated to even contemplate
dating? Double check.
It's okay.
We met, and we talked,
and it was epic...
...but then the sun came up
and reality set in.
So...
VICKI : I know you.
DAMON : Well, that's unfortunate.
Uh...
I don't know how, but your face...
(CHUCKLES)
Excuse me. Sorry.
(SIGHS)
(SCREAMS)
JEREMY : Hey, has anyone seen Vicki?
- You're her stalker. You tell us.
- I can't find her.
TYLER :
Probably found someone to party with.
- Sorry, pill pusher, you've been replaced.
- "Pill pusher"?
- Ask him.
- You wanna do this right now?
- Are you dealing?
- She's never gonna go for you.
She already did.
Over and over and over again.
- Yeah, right.
- Okay, you slept with Vicki Donovan?
I mean, Vicki Donovan slept with you?
- There's no way.
- I didn't even have to force her into it.
- What is he talking about?
- Nothing, man. Ignore him. He's a punk.
- Shut up and help me find my sister.
- We'll check the bathroom.
- I'll check the square.
- I'll come with you.
ELENA : Oh, no, no, no.
You are coming with me.
So that's your game now? Dealing?
- No, I'm not dealing.
- I'm sick of the tough-love speech, Jer.
- It's clearly having no impact.
- You and Jenna, between the two...
We could stop. Send you to a therapist
where you'll be forced to deal with it.
Or to rehab where you'll sit
and tell some stranger...
...how you let your life fall apart.
Or you could talk to me.
JEREMY : I vote for none of the above.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Hey.
STEFAN : Hey.
Have you seen my sister?
- No, sorry.
- Can't find her. She's missing.
I'll keep an eye out for her.
Hey, I saw you
at the hospital yesterday.
Did you?
MATT : What were you doing there?
Visiting.
Visiting?
You know, Elena and I,
we've known each other a long time.
And we might not be together right now,
but I look out for her.
And I'll always look out for her.
VICKl : No! No, please.
DAMON : You really have to stop screaming.
VICKl : Stop. Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me.
DAMON : Shh. I've got you.
STEFAN :
Excuse me.
(VICKI CRYING)
DAMON : Would you like?
VICKl : No!
- No. Please don't.
- I got you. I'm not gonna drop you.
Not bad.
- Have you been eating bunnies?
- Let her go.
Really? Okay.
- No! No!
STEFAN  : No, no, no.
Relax.
VICKl :
What's happening?
I don't need her to be dead,
but you might.
(VICKI SOBBING)
What attacked you the other night?
I don't know. An animal.
DAMON :
Are you sure about that?
Think. Think about it.
Think really hard.
What attacked you?
Vampire.
- Who did this to you?
- You did.
- Wrong. Stefan.
- Don't.
STEFAN :
Don't.
Stefan Salvatore did this to you.
VICKl :
Stefan Salvatore did this to me.
DAMON :
He's a vampire.
A vicious, murderous monster.
Please, Damon. Please don't do this.
You couldn't fix it before.
I don't know
what you're gonna do now.
(GASPS THEN CRIES)
VICKl :
Aah!
DAMON : Your choice of lifestyle...
...has made you weak.
Couple of vampire parlor tricks...
...is nothing compared
to the power that you could have.
That you now need.
But you can change that.
Human blood gives you that.
No.
(STEFAN GRUNTS)
You have two choices.
You can feed and make her forget...
...or you can let her run screaming,
"Vampire!" through the town square.
STEFAN : That's what this is about?
You wanna expose me?
DAMON : No, I want you
to remember who you are.
STEFAN : Why? So, what?
So I'll feed? So I'll kill?
So I'll remember what it's like
to be brothers again?
You know what? Let her go.
Let her tell everyone that vampires
have returned to Mystic Falls.
Let them chain me up.
And let them drive
a stake through my heart.
Because at least I'll be free of you.
(CHUCKLES)
- Wow. Come here, sweetheart.
- No.
It's okay.
(DAMON WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
VICKl :
What happened?
Where am I?
I ripped my stitches open. Ugh.
- You okay?
- I took some pills, man.
I'm good.
DAMON :
It's good to be home.
Think I might stay a while.
This town could use a bit
of a wakeup call, don't you think?
What are you up to, Damon?
That's for me to know
and for you to dot, dot, dot.
Give Elena my best.
MATT : She said you found her
wandering around.
Yeah.
So, um, thanks.
CAROLINE : Ugh. Just so much drama.
Ever notice how the druggies
are the biggest attention whores?
Yeah.
- Excuse me. Hi.
- Hi.
- Have you guys seen Elena?
- I think she went home.
BONNIE : I'm gonna give you Elena's
cell number and her e-mail.
She is big on texting,
and you can tell her I said so.
Thank you.
You okay?
What happened to you?
That was so rude.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
CAROLINE : Yeah, she kind of wigs out.
It's like her thing.
Jer?
JENNA :
No, it's me. The hypocrite patrol.
What are you doing?
I've become my worst nightmare.
The authority figure who has
to violate a 15-year-old's privacy.
Jackpot.
I see the hiding places
haven't gotten any more creative.
What brought this on?
Your ass-hat of a history teacher
shamed me good yesterday.
You got Tannered. Been there.
"Discover the impossible, Miss Sommers."
Got it. Thanks.
Like I didn't know I was screwing up.
You're not screwing up, Aunt Jenna.
JENNA : Yes, I am. You know why?
Because I'm not her.
She made everything look so easy.
You know,
high school, marriage, having you.
I can't do it.
I'm gonna say
or do the wrong thing...
...and he's gonna get worse,
and it's gonna be my fault.
It's impossible.
ELENA : This is just the fear talking.
You're a little scared, that's all.
We all are.
I have to go do something.
But are you gonna be okay?
(THUMP)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
DAMON : Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you.
(CHUCKLES)
No, it's fine.
CAROLINE : I was hoping I'd see you again.
I know.
(CHUCKLES)
Cocky much?
Very much.
(BELL RINGING)
Hey.
Would you like to come in?
The comet's actually this way.
ELENA :
Sorry for barging in.
Especially after earlier.
STEFAN : No, no. I'm glad you're here.
The way we left things, I didn't like it.
ELENA : So the thing is, I got home tonight
planning on doing what I always do.
Write in my diary.
Like I have been since my mom
gave me one when I was 10.
It's where I get everything out.
It all goes in this little book
that I hide on the second shelf...
...behind this really
hideous ceramic mermaid.
But then I realized that I'd just be writing
things that I should be telling you.
STEFAN : What would you write?
ELENA : I would write,
"Dear diary, today I convinced
myself that it's okay to give up.
Don't take risks.
Stick with the status quo, no drama.
Now is just not the time."
But my reasons aren't reasons,
they're excuses.
All I'm doing is hiding from the truth.
And the truth is that...
...l'm scared, Stefan.
I'm scared that if I let myself
be happy for even one moment...
...that the world's
just gonna come crashing down...
...and I don't know
if I can survive that.
STEFAN : Do you wanna know
what I would write?
"I met a girl.
We talked.
It was epic.
Then the sun came up
and reality set in."
Well, this is reality.
Right here.
(MOANING)
(SCREAMS)