NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret, until now.
I know the risk but I have to know her.
DAMON :
Elena. She's a dead ringer for Katherine.
- Hello, brother.
- Damon.
He killed Zach, he killed Tanner,
he turned Vicki. I have to kill him.
- No, you can't do that.
- You were right to stay away from me.
CAROLINE : What is that?
- A very important crystal.
It belonged to one of the most powerful
witches of our family...
...Emily Bennett.
- I want my crystal back.
- Bonnie has it.
- Get it from her.
Don't be giving that back to anybody.
TEACHER : Today we're going to talk
about shadow reckoning.
This is a method of measuring heights
by the sun's shadow.
Let's say, for example, that we're going
to measure the distance of the shadow.
We're gonna take
this measurement here...
...measure the length.
And we're going to multiply that
by the height of the source.
Building height can also be measured
using a clinometer...
...which we're going to make
in class tomorrow.
I've already given you the handout,
but I want to remind...
BONNIE :Hello?
- Please help me.
- Who are you?
I'm Emily.
You know that.
We're family.
Where am I?
This is where it started.
And this is where it has to end.
No. This isn't real.
Help me.
TEACHER :
What is similar about these methods...
...is that the right triangles
help give us an accurate measurement.
What are you looking at? Turn around.
TEACHER : That creates
the 45-degree angle between...
(SCREAMS)
ELENA : Have you talked to Bonnie?
CAROLINE : No, I'm mad at her.
- She needs to make the first move.
- Be the bigger person.
Ugh, impossible in her presence.
- Why are you so pissed at her anyway?
- She's a thief, that's why.
I gave her my necklace
and she refuses to give it back.
- It's a matter of principle.
- All right, I tried. I'm officially out of it.
Good. Your turn. Where's Stefan?
Have you talked to him?
- He's avoiding me.
- Why?
It's complicated.
(BELL RINGING)
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
- Hey.
Good morning, everyone.
Alrighty.
Let's see.
(MOUTHS)
Are you okay?
- ZMAN.
Alaric Saltzman.
It's a mouthful, I know.
It doesn't exactly roll off the tongue.
Saltzman is of German origins.
My family immigrated here in 1755
to Texas.
I, however,
was born and raised in Boston.
Now, the name Alaric belongs
to a very dead great-grandfather...
...I will never be able to thank enough.
You'll probably wanna
pronounce it Alaric...
...but it's "Alaric," okay?
So you can call me Rick.
I'm your new history teacher.
DAMON :
Rise and shine.
Gonna be late for school.
What are you...? What are you doing?
Peace offering.
Come on,
you need it for blood circulation.
Does dead flesh good.
- All right, I'm sorry.
- Step aside, please.
I got the town off our back.
It was for the greater good.
But I'm sorry.
And to prove it, I'm not gonna feed
on a human for at least a week.
I'll adopt the Stefan diet.
Only nothing with feathers.
Because I realize that killing your closest
and oldest friend is beyond evil...
...and yet somehow
it's worthy of humor.
- Are you mimicking me?
- Yes, Stefan.
Now that the secret society
of vampire-haters is off our back...
...I can go back to my routine of "how
can I destroy Stefan's life this week?"
And I can go back to sulking
and Elena longing and forehead brooding.
This is fun. I like this.
And I will finally reveal
the ulterior motive...
...behind my evil and diabolical return
to Mystic Falls.
Yeah, I'm done.
(MIMICKING STEFAN)
This is so like you, Damon.
Always have to have the last word.
BONNIE : Then I ended up
at the remains of old Fell's Church...
...before I woke up back in the woods.
And you always see
your ancestor Emily?
Huh.
Do you believe in ghosts?
- Two weeks ago, I'd say no, but now...
- I think I'm being haunted.
I don't get it. Why Emily?
Grams said she was a powerful witch
in the Civil War days.
This medallion was hers.
It's a witch's talisman.
It all started
when you got the necklace?
I think she's using it
to communicate with me.
- What does Grams say about it?
- I can't call her.
She's gonna tell me to embrace it.
I don't wanna embrace it.
I want it to stop.
JEREMY :Hey, Mr. Saltzman, I'm, uh...
I'm Jeremy Gilbert.
You wanted to see me?
SALTZMAN :Ahem. You know that your old teacher
had a jackass file?
No joke, it's, um, typed on a label.
It has all the, uh, trouble makers in it.
But really it's just an opus to you.
(LAUGHS)
Don't worry about it.
I'm not him. Clean slate.
Now...
...let's talk about grades.
I know, it's been a rough couple months
but I've been trying to turn them around.
Yeah, I saw that, but the problem is
we're halfway through a semester...
...and half of fail is still pretty bleak.
This is the part where you say,
"What can I do to change that?"
I'm glad you asked.
How do you feel about extra credit?
- Yeah, yeah, totally. Whatever.
- Good. Write me a paper then.
- Okay, about what?
- History.
Pick a topic. Keep it local.
No Wikipedia regurgita.
These old towns
have a lot of rich history...
...so just get your hands dirty,
make it sing and you're back on track.
- Deal?
- Uh, yeah, deal.
That's a, uh... That's a cool ring.
Oh, thanks. It was my father's. Heh.
A little garish but family, you know.
You've got a week.
GIRL 1 : Ha, ha. Seriously?
GIRL 2 : Exactly.
- Hey.
What is that?
- What is what?
- The "hey."
Now it's twice. That is two heys. That...
Do you have any other words
in your vocabulary?
- What's wrong with hey?
- It reeks of awkward subtext.
You spent the night in my bed.
There was cuddling, and then you snuck
out so you wouldn't have to face me.
Which I must say is a total lame-guy
move that I did not appreciate.
And now with the "heys," seriously?
I mean, I may have been some pathetic,
insecure mess after the party...
...but do not mistake that
for me being a pushover.
Because I do not let guys
mess with my head anymore.
I heard your mom
and didn't wanna get you in trouble...
...so I went out the window.
You went out the window.
Another lame-guy move.
Your mom's the sheriff.
And as for the "heys"...
...l'm pretty sure it's what I've said
to you every day since the first grade.
Oh.
Trying to read something into it?
Lame-girl move.
- Hi.
- You weren't in class, I was worried.
Yeah, I got your messages
and I'm sorry I didn't get back to you...
...but what I wanna say
shouldn't be said over the phone.
A simple, "I didn't kill my brother" text
would have sufficed.
I didn't kill my brother,
as much as he deserved it.
He has you to thank for that.
What did you wanna tell me?
I won't be coming to school anymore.
I'm gonna back off
and keep my distance.
It's the right thing to do.
Back off from school? Or from me?
Thank you for telling me.
- It's better this way.
- Yep, I got it.
You're angry, that's good.
Be easier if you hate me.
Okay, it's your last chance.
- I'm gonna scream.
- Oh, no, don't do that.
Let's stay on point.
Listen, I want my necklace.
You can't have it.
I can't take it, but you can give it to me.
I'm trying to help you.
- I don't want your help.
- You do and you don't even know it.
You've stumbled into something
you need to stumble out of.
- Just leave me alone or I swear...
- Nope, no threats.
Look, A, you hurt me last time,
B, I wish you no harm.
Believe it or not, Bonnie,
I wanna protect you.
Let me help you
get Emily off your back.
- How do you know?
- I know a lot of things.
I know more about that crystal
than you do.
And I know that she's using it
to creep inside of you.
Huh? See how scared you are?
You should be,
because I will get that crystal...
...even if I have to wait for Emily
to give it to me herself.
So next time she comes out to play,
you tell her...
...that a deal's a deal.
He's bad news, Elena.
He really scared me.
You need to stay as far away
from Damon as possible.
I'm trying. He just keeps showing up.
I don't want you to be alone.
You're sleeping at my place tonight.
We can make a whole night out of it.
Whoa...!
Where are you going?
(GRUNTS)
- Are you okay?
- Now I am.
All my problems
are because of that thing.
- Can't believe I didn't do that sooner.
- What's your grams gonna say?
Grams isn't the one being haunted
by a 150-year-old ghost, is she?
Okay then.
JENNA :
I like a man who can dine alone.
Quiet strength.
Thought you were still
in that Logan-depression thing.
I've sworn off men forever.
Doesn't mean I can't observe them
from a safe distance.
Well, I can introduce you.
Hey.
ELENA :Thanks for coming. I wouldn't
have called if it wasn't important.
I know that.
- He threatened her.
- What would Damon want with Bonnie?
She has this necklace. Caroline got it
from Damon and she gave it to Bonnie...
...and now Damon wants it back.
- He's tormenting her.
- Over a necklace.
It's not just any necklace.
It has to do with Bonnie's heritage.
It belonged to one of her ancestors
who lived here during the Civil War...
When you and Damon lived here.
STEFAN :Her name was Emily.
She was Katherine's handmaid,
and a witch.
You know?
About Bonnie?
The first night that you invited me over
for dinner, I made the connection.
And now Damon knows.
And for some reason,
he wants that necklace.
What does it look like?
- It's, um, an antique iron setting with...
- With an amber crystal.
I know it. It belonged to Katherine.
Emily gave it to her which means that...
What?
I don't know, but I'm gonna find out.
Let me talk to Damon.
Will he tell you?
STEFAN :I'll... I'll get it out of him.
JEREMY : Have you picked a topic?
JENNA : No, not yet.
It's gotta be local
and non-lnternet research, so...
- That's easy, you got all your dad's stuff.
- What stuff?
How-the-Gilberts-came-over
on-the-Mayflower stuff.
All that family lineage from way back.
Your dad really loved
all that family-history stuff.
It's all boxed up in the closet.
- Mr. Saltzman.
- Jeremy, what's up, man?
- This is my Aunt Jenna.
- Alaric Saltzman. It's nice to meet you.
Jeremy was just telling me
about his paper.
Thanks for giving him another chance.
Oh, you know, it was my first day.
I wanted to make a good impression.
Ha-ha-ha.
STEFAN :
So, Stefan...
...you know, I've been thinking.
I think we should start over.
Give this brother thing another chance.
We used to do it,
oh, so well once upon a time.
(MIMICKING DAMON)
I don't, Damon.
I can't trust you to be a nice guy.
You kill everybody and you're so mean.
You're so mean and...
You're really hard to imitate and then
I have to go to that lesser place.
Can I get a coffee, please?
So, what's with the bottle?
I'm on edge. Crash diet. You know,
I'm trying to keep a low profile.
You could just leave, find a new town to
turn into your own personal Gas 'n' Sip.
I'll manage.
Thanks.
You don't have to keep an eye on me.
- I'm not here to keep an eye on you.
- So why are you here?
Why not?
I'm sorry. There, I said it.
If you want the ugly-ass necklace,
keep it.
It's yours.
Will you hate me
if I tell you I threw it away?
- You threw it away?
- I know it sounds crazy.
- The necklace was giving me nightmares.
- You could have given it back to me.
Why? So you could give it back
to Damon?
Screw Damon. Are we doing manicures
or what? Who has their kit?
Mine's in my bag.
So, Elena, how long do you think
this fight with Stefan's gonna last?
Is it like a permanent thing?
I don't know, Caroline.
Why are you such a little liar, Bonnie?
- What?
- Caroline.
- I'm not lying to you, Caroline. I swear.
ELENA : It's true.
- I watched her throw it into a field.
- Then explain it.
Emily?
- Who's Emily?
- The ghost.
Oh, the ghost has a name now?
- Caroline, please.
- I wonder why she won't leave me alone.
Okay, what is going on? Why am I
not a part of this conversation?
You guys do this to me all the time.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
- I can't talk to you, you don't listen.
- That's not true.
- I'm a witch.
- And don't we all know it.
See? That's what I'm talking about.
I'm trying to tell you something.
You don't even hear it.
I listen. When do I not listen?
Jeremy totally ditched me.
- Where'd he go?
- Home.
It's not far. He can walk it.
So are you from here?
Are you a townie?
I'm a returnee.
Left town for a while and now I'm back.
- Why'd you leave?
- School.
- And then there's the real reason.
- Ha-ha-ha. Okay.
I was wronged. Guy named Logan.
- What'd he do?
- The basics.
Lied, cheated, lured me back in,
left me again.
- Your turn. Any sad relationship stories?
- Ha, ha.
The basics. Ahem.
I fell in love, married young...
...wife died.
Oh. Wow.
Yeah. That's always
a good conversation stopper.
What happened?
You, me and the, uh,
North Carolina Police Department...
...are all wondering the same thing.
It's what's known as a cold case.
- So why'd you move here?
- A change of pace, new scenery.
I like it here. It's got a rich history.
DAMON :Lucky shot.
More like a carefully honed skill
over many decades.
- You're beating me.
- Yeah, because I'm better than you.
I'm onto you. Reverse psychology?
It's a little transparent
but I admire the effort.
You prefer the brooding forehead?
Seriously,
what game do you think you're playing?
That's a funny question...
...considering the fact that
I have been asking you that for months.
- It's frustrating, isn't it?
- Touche.
CAROLINE :Bonnie?
Look, it's just not me.
Okay? I don't believe
in the "woo, woo." Heh.
But if you do then, okay, I'm in.
That's all it takes
for me to jump onboard.
Because I consider you
to be my best friend.
And I'm saying this knowing
that Elena's in the kitchen...
...listening to my every word.
Look, I didn't know
how real this was for you.
But I'm listening now.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Elena, you can come in now,
we're done.
Well, there is just way too much drama
in this room.
So, what do you guys wanna do?
Huh! I have an idea.
- Why don't we have a seance?
- Uh...
- I don't think that's a good idea.
CAROLINE : Come on.
Let's summon some spirits.
This Emily chick
has some serious explaining to do.
What are we doing?
- I don't know.
- Shh!
Be quiet and concentrate.
Okay, close your eyes.
Okay, now take a deep breath.
Bonnie, call to her.
BONNIE :Emily.
You there?
Really? "Emily, you there?"
That's all you got?
- Come on.
- Fine, jeez.
Emily.
I call on you.
I know you have a message.
I'm here to listen.
- Did that just...?
- Yeah, it just happened.
(GASPS)
It's just the air conditioning.
Ask her to show you a sign.
Ask her.
Emily, if you're among us,
show us another sign.
See, it's not working.
(ALL YELL)
No, I can't. I'm done.
Get the light. Please, get the light on.
ELENA :
Hold on, I got it.
You guys, the necklace, it's gone.
- What are we doing here?
- Bonding. Catch.
Mm.
Go on. Give it a try.
Don't forget who taught you
how to play this game.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(BOTH GROAN)
Ow, that hurts.
Downside of my diet,
getting hit actually hurts a little bit.
Ugh. Whoo.
DAMON :I'm impressed, Stefan.
Fun with booze and darts,
sentimental with football, and now...
...starry night.
What do you want, Stefan?
STEFAN :It wasn't real, Damon.
- Our love for Katherine.
- Oh, God.
She compelled us.
We didn't have a choice.
Took me years to sort that out,
to truly understand what she did to us.
Oh, no, Stefan.
DAMON : We are not taking that on tonight.
What do you want
with Katherine's crystal?
How do you know about that?
Come on,
you knew Elena would tell me.
DAMON : How'd you know it was Katherine's?
Emily gave it to her on her last night.
I was with her and you weren't.
STEFAN : I was the last one to see her, Damon.
Now, what do you want
with Katherine's crystal?
- She didn't tell you?
- We had other things on our mind.
DAMON : I could rip your heart out
and not think twice about it.
Yeah.
STEFAN : I've heard that before.
DAMON : I have a bigger surprise, Stefan.
I'm gonna bring her back.
BONNIE : Okay, fun is over, Caroline.
You made a point and I get it.
Now give it back.
What? Well, I didn't take it.
- What? What happened?
ELENA : I don't know.
Nothing. Jeremy, are you home?
Um...
Guys?
(SCREAMS)
- Oh, my God!
- Bonnie?
BONNIE : You guys, open the door!
- Bonnie? Bonnie.
- What's going on?
- Bonnie.
- What's happening?
- Try the other door.
- I'll check the hallway.
- Okay.
- Bonnie?
BONNIE : Please!
- Bonnie!
- Open up the door.
- Bonnie. Bonnie?
BONNIE : Please open the door!
- Aah!
- Bonnie!
BONNIE : Aah!
Open the door.
What happened? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Unbelievable.
You were totally faking it.
ELENA : Caroline, come on.
- No, you scared the hell out of me.
Bonnie?
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
- How can you bring Katherine back?
- Before Katherine was killed...
...remember what it was like
in this town?
- I remember the fear and hysteria.
- Townspeople were killing vampires.
When they came for Katherine,
I went to Emily.
Said I'll do anything.
Name your price, just protect her.
She did.
- How?
- She did some spell with the crystal.
While the church was burning,
we thought Katherine was burning in it.
- She wasn't.
- But I saw her go inside.
There's a tomb...
...underneath the church. The spell sealed
Katherine in that tomb, protecting her.
- Katherine's alive?
- Well, if that's what you wanna call it.
She's been trapped in a mystical holding
cell for the last century and a half.
You're an expert on starving a vampire,
so how you think she's doing, Stef?
Did you know that
witches can use celestial events...
...to draw energy into their magic?
Me either.
But in order
to give the crystal its power...
...Emily used the comet
that was passing overhead.
And in order for that crystal
to work again...
The comet had to return.
Downside,
long time in between comets.
And a couple of hiccups along the way
with the crystal.
But the comet passed
and I got the crystal.
Then Caroline got the crystal,
and now Bonnie has the crystal...
...and here we are.
Why would Emily...?
Why would she do this?
She knew they were gonna
come for her too.
And she made me promise
that her lineage would survive.
I remember. You saved her children.
It's the only thing keeping me
from ripping Bonnie's throat out...
...to get my crystal back.
Oh, well. A deal's a deal.
So...
...you wanna go throw some more?
CAROLINE : I can't believe I fell for it.
- Are you okay?
- I must go.
- Lf she's leaving, I'm leaving.
ELENA : You can't leave.
CAROLINE : I can.
I've had enough fake witch stuff
for one night.
Thank you for having me.
- I'll take it from here.
- Where are you going?
- Back to where it all began.
- Bonnie.
Bonnie?
Oh, my God.
Emily.
I won't let him have it.
It must be destroyed.
Wait.
- What's happening?
- I don't know. The door, it's not...
- Aah!
- What the hell?
I'm out of here.
STEFAN : What's wrong?
ELENA : It's Bonnie.
- What happened?
- Emily is possessing her.
- She said something.
- What did she say?
She said, "I won't let him have it.
It must be destroyed."
- Then she just left.
- Okay, where do you think she went?
I don't know.
Fell's Church. By the old cemetery.
That's where she took Bonnie
in her dreams.
- We have to help her.
- All right.
Just stay there. I'm gonna go find her.
DAMON :
Hello, Emily.
You look different.
- I won't let you do it.
- We had a deal.
Things are different now.
I need to protect my family.
I protected your family. You owe me.
I know.
- I'm sorry.
- You're about to be a lot more than that.
(YELLING)
(COUGHING)
(GROANS)
(DOOR OPENS)
- Ha-ha-ha.
JENNA :  You're so wrong. I'm much more pathetic.
SALTZMAN : Oh, no, no, I've got you beat.
I have pathetic down to a science.
Uh, no, we haven't even covered
high school.
Braces. A cup.
Ah. Glasses. Skin condition.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You can, uh...
You know what?
I'm not gonna invite you in.
- Jeremy.
- Well, some other time then.
Have a good night, Jenna.
Oh, uh, you found the boxes.
And I found this too.
JENNA :
Me and Logan.
- That's just cruel.
- No, cruel is dating my history teacher.
I'm not dating him.
- Yet.
- Ha, ha.
(GROANING)
- Come on.
- Ugh.
DAMON : Oh, that hurts. Ugh.
This is why I feed on people.
Stefan.
- Hello, Emily.
- These people don't deserve this.
They should never have to know
such evil.
What do you mean evil?
Emily, I swear to God,
I'll make you regret this.
I won't let you
unleash them into this world.
Them?
- What part of the story did you leave out?
- What does it matter?
STEFAN : Emily, tell me what you did.
EMILY : To save her, I had to save them.
- You saved everyone in the church?
- With one comes all.
I don't care about them.
I just want Katherine.
I knew I shouldn't have believed
a word out of your mouth.
This isn't about love, is it?
- This is about revenge.
- The two aren't mutually exclusive.
- You can't do this.
- Why not?
They killed 27 people
and they called it a war battle.
- They deserve whatever they get.
- Twenty-seven vampires, Damon.
They were vampires.
You can't just bring them back.
- This town deserves this.
- You're blaming innocent people...
...for something that happened
145 years ago.
DAMON : There is nothing innocent
about these people.
Don't think it won't happen again.
They know too much.
They'll burn your grand-witch next to us
when they find out. Trust me.
Things are different now.
- Don't do this.
- I can't free them.
I won't.
DAMON : No.
- Incendia
No.
No, no, no. Please.
Bonnie.
No!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMING)
She's alive, but barely. I can save her.
(BONNIE GROANING)
Her neck. It's healing.
- Hey.
- God.
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, your window was open.
- Thought you should know.
- Not funny.
Look. Earlier today, I lied.
- About?
- About being in bed with you.
- We cuddled, and it creeped me out.
- It creeped you out?
Did you just come over here
to insult me or what?
Because it's been a really long night.
No, it's just that I don't like you.
I never have, but it was nice.
- What?
- Being in bed with you. It felt nice.
And so I was thinking about it
and I thought that I should tell you...
...I stayed the night because you were
all sad and alone and I felt bad for you.
Well, thank you,
because I love being a charity case.
- You can leave now.
- No... Because I know.
With Vicki gone,
and my mom off with Pete whoever...
...it's just me.
So I know.
DAMON : Katherine never compelled me. I knew
everything, every step of the way.
It was real for me.
I'll leave now.
I don't understand, Elena.
What happened to me?
He attacked me and his face was like...
How do you feel? Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just this blood, I don't...
I'm not gonna hurt you.
What's going on, Elena?
I'll explain everything, Bonnie, okay?
Let's just get out of here.
Bonnie. Bonnie, look at me. Trust me.
He's not going to hurt you.
Come on. Come on.
- Is she in danger of becoming...?
- No.
No, she has to die with my blood
in her system.
Keep an eye on her tonight,
make sure that nothing happens...
...and once it leaves her system,
she'll be fine.
ELENA : I'm gonna tell her the truth.
You sure?
I can trust her.
I need someone to know,
someone to talk to. I can't live in secret.
I know that. You shouldn't have to.
ELENA : You saved her life.
I'm sorry, Stefan. I thought
that I couldn't be with you, but I can.
You don't have to push me away.
I can do this.
STEFAN : I can't.
I have to leave, Elena.
Too many people have died.
Too much has happened.
What?
ELENA : No. I know
you think you're protecting me...
I have to.
Coming home was...
Was a mistake.
I can't be a part of your life anymore.
Don't go, Stefan.
Please.
You don't have to. This is your home.
Just, please don't go.
Goodbye, Elena.
You're just gonna walk away?
Don't walk away, Stefan.
Stefan.
(CHUCKLES)
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Hello, Jenna.
- Logan.
LOGAN : Aren't you gonna invite me in?