NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
DAMON ::
She's a dead ringer for Katherine.
- Where is he?
- They have him. I can't get in.
FREDERICK : Who says we're not here
for revenge, right?
That's what we're here for.
ELENA :
Can you make it?
Take my wrist. You need blood.
(GRUNTING)
Stefan. Stefan, he's dead.
(STEFAN GROWLS)
- You were like this other person.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
They found Vicki Donovan.
The storm unearthed the grave.
- She's dead?
- Matt.
(BLACK MUSTANG'S "YOU AND l"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Who am I to make you
Could you turn it up a little bit?
It's not annoying yet.
Sorry.
A whole lotta you and...
DAMON : When you going back to school?
- Soon.
- Oh, come on, just drink already.
Come on.
This self-detox, it's not natural.
STEFAN :
Get that away from me, please?
How long did it take to wean yourself
off of it after you last indulged?
- That's not good.
- I'll be fine. It takes a bit of time.
You don't have to kill to survive.
That's what blood banks are for.
I haven't hunted a human in...
- God, way too long.
- Oh, I'm impressed.
It's completely self-serving.
DAMON : Trying to get the town off the trail
of vampires, which is not easy...
...considering there's an entire tomb
of them around.
STEFAN : What are we doing about that?
DAMON : We're not gonna be doing much of
anything if you don't have your strength.
There's nothing wrong with a healthy
diet of human blood from a blood bank.
- You're not killing anyone.
- I have my reasons.
What are those holier-than-thou reasons?
We've never actually discussed that.
- You know, I'd love to hear this story.
- You're really enjoying this, aren't you?
Just watching me struggle?
- Very much so.
- I hate to break it to you, Damon...
...but I actually have it
under complete control.
- You do?
- Mm-hm.
DAMON : Oh. Well, then you should just carry on
making the rest of us vampires look bad.
Have a great day, Stef.
Oh. Hey. Almost forgot something.
Oops.
Mm. Mm.
ELENA :
Come on, Jeremy, I'm going to school.
- Walking out the door now.
JENNA : You forgot this.
Thank you.
- Elena.
- Uncle John. Hi.
- Jenna.
JENNA : John. You made it.
JOHN :
I said I'd be in by noon.
What you say and what you do
are typically two very different things.
- Uncle John, what's up?
- Hey.
I had some business in town.
I thought a visit was in order.
- How long are you staying?
- I don't know yet.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go school.
I'll see you later.
JOHN :
So, what's up with Jeremy?
JENNA : He just lost a friend,
so try to be sensitive.
- I'm always sensitive.
- Right.
So really, how long are you staying?
Can't you at least pretend
that you're happy to see me?
Oh, my God, John,
it is so good to see you.
How have you been? No, I can't.
JOHN : Did you think I was gonna sign the
escrow papers and send them back?
- Actually, I did.
- I'm not gonna let you sell.
It's not up to you or me.
It belongs to Jeremy and Elena.
But they're minors. So I get final say,
being that I'm the estate's trustee.
- He said his trip is open-ended.
- Uncle John. I never really liked that guy.
Does anyone?
- I am here for moral support if you need.
- Thanks. I think I'll suffer this one alone.
You've been through enough.
MATT : Thank you, by the way, for just...
For everything you did at Vicki's funeral
and her memorial.
- I couldn't have done it without you.
- Of course, Matt.
ELENA : So is Caroline still baking for you guys
around the clock?
She finally went to her dad's,
which is a good thing...
...because my mom was gonna strangle
her if she dropped off more lasagna.
Oh. Hm.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
I've hit the hard times
I'm off course
The winds have changed
No.
- What's your problem?
- I just don't want any.
All right.
TYLER : They say she OD'd.
JEREMY : That's what I don't get.
She was doing okay.
Apparently not.
How'd she end up in the woods?
I don't understand.
By whoever was with her
when she OD'd.
You leave her.
You don't take time to bury her.
Maybe she saw something and...
Hell, man, I don't know.
Right this way.
FORBES : The coroner's office has officially ruled
Vicki Donovan's death a drug overdose.
Her family has been notified.
The truth will stay in this room
and we can put this behind us.
LOCKWOOD : Thank you, sheriff.
And on to a more pressing issue.
John Gilbert has asked to say few words.
- Welcome back, John. Good to see you.
- Thank you, mayor.
JOHN : Hello, everyone.
It's wonderful to see you.
I wish it were
under better circumstances.
As a founding family member, it's my
duty to report some distressing news.
DAMON : He's a Gilbert?
Elena's uncle. His name is John.
I call him jackass.
A hospital blood bank
in the county of Amherst...
...has reported several break-ins
the past two weeks.
Seven hunters, four campers
and two state employees...
...have been reported missing.
All of this within a 75-mile radius
of Mystic Falls.
Okay, okay, no need to get alarmed
right at this moment.
He doesn't wanna cancel
the Founder's Day party.
JOHN : You think all of your problems
are over...
...but I'm here to tell you,
nothing's been solved.
ALARIC : I made a copy of a paper
that Jeremy wrote for me.
I think you should take a look at it.
ELENA : Jeremy wrote this?
He was very clear
that he didn't think it was real.
I really hope you're right,
because I have done so much...
...to protect him from all this.
So how do you deal with it?
What do you mean?
ALARIC : With all the lies and the secrets.
You have to lie to everyone
who's important to you.
It's not safe for them
to know the truth.
So, yes, I keep it from them,
but it's only because I love them.
I think Stefan's a good guy...
...but at the end of the day,
he's still a vampire.
I know it's hard to understand,
but Stefan's different.
He would never do anything
to hurt me.
JEREMY : I have no interest in the Founder's Day
kickoff party.
- Sure you do. It's tradition.
- Far be it to break from tradition.
JOHN : Gilberts have been a part of this town
for a hundred and fifty years.
One of the founding families.
And with that distinction
come certain obligations...
...including going to the party.
One day, when you can appreciate
the significance...
...l'll tell you all about your heritage.
JENNA : Hm.
The Gilbert family legacy.
I forgot how sacred it was.
I'm not a Gilbert,
so I was never cool enough to hear it.
- Why does she hate you?
- We used to sleep together.
JEREMY : Ha!
- I am standing right here.
Why would he write a report
on vampires?
- Do you think he's starting to remember?
- Damon took away those memories.
You don't have to worry about that.
Tell you what,
why don't you just ask him?
- I... I can't.
- Why not?
STEFAN : I mean, if he doesn't know anything,
then it's just a...
An innocent question.
ELENA : I don't even know
how to talk to him anymore.
I mean, we used to be a lot more open
with each other.
But now,
with all these secrets just piling up...
You know, I haven't even told him
that I'm adopted yet.
STEFAN : Maybe it's time you start
opening up to him again.
I'm not saying you should tell everything,
but try to find out what he does know...
...and be prepared for it.
- What about you? How are you doing?
- I'm much, much better.
You know, I'm still, you know, a little...
A little jittery, a little bit on edge...
...but I'm gonna be okay.
ELENA : I've been really worried about you.
And I've missed you.
I just needed to lay low for a little while
and let my body readjust.
It's only been a few days.
It feels like a lifetime.
I've missed you too.
Stefan, what's wrong?
(STEFAN PANTING)
Stefan.
(ELENA GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
- Oh, good. You're here.
- You ask, I come. I'm easy like that.
No, Elena, I will not go
to your bedroom with you.
(DAMON CHUCKLING)
- Ah. Just like I remembered.
- Stop messing around.
DAMON : Did you know that your uncle's been
kicking it with the Founder's Council?
- What?
- Yep.
ELENA : Perfect. We'll just add it to growing list
of how everything is falling apart.
What happened right there?
Nothing.
Look, Damon,
I'm worried about Stefan.
He says everything is okay,
but he's clearly struggling.
- How long before he's back to normal?
- A few days, give or take.
- It's been a few days.
- Give, then. I don't know.
What's the big deal?
He's not himself, Damon.
Well, maybe his problem is he's spent
too long not being himself.
Hm.
Please don't make me sorry
for asking you.
- It is what it is, Elena.
- Hey.
DAMON : The Stefan you know
was good-behavior Stefan.
Rein-it-in Stefan. Fight-against-his-nature
to-an-annoyingly-obsessive-level Stefan.
If you think there's not another part
to this, then you...
...have not been paying attention.
- He is not you. Not even close.
- Well, he doesn't wanna be me.
But that doesn't mean that deep down
that he's not.
Mm-hm.
(KNOCKING)
- Hey.
- What's up?
Do you have some time to talk?
Uh...
- Yeah, sure.
- Not here.
Come on. Let's get out of the house.
JEREMY : I just can't believe Mom and Dad
never told you that you were adopted.
I'm sure they would've eventually.
Why were you worried
about what I thought?
Because... I don't know, it's weird.
Going your whole life thinking
you're related by blood to someone.
- Does it bug you that we're not?
- No.
ELENA : Jer, you're my brother.
That's all that matters.
So Mr. Saltzman said you've been
doing great in history now.
Yeah, yeah.
He's really been helping me out.
Yeah, he gave me some extra credit
and stuff.
He loved your vampire paper.
He thought I had a clever angle.
What drew you to that subject matter?
I don't know. Boredom.
Or maybe I'm just as nuts
as the long line of Gilbert crazies.
- The Gilberts aren't crazy.
- Easy for you to say. You're not one.
Ouch.
Oh, God. I shouldn't be here.
DAMON : Come on. Don't be a downer.
It's a party for founding families.
That would be us.
It would be rude to skip it.
STEFAN : I really liked you a whole lot better
when you hated everybody.
DAMON : Oh, I still do.
I just love that they love me.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- How you feeling?
- I'm good. I'm fine.
No cravings, no urges?
Is that whiskey you've been
drinking all day doing its job?
We are who we are, Stefan.
Pretending doesn't change that.
STEFAN : Nothing would make you happier
than to see me give in, huh, Damon?
Whatever. It's inevitable.
- I'm gonna go find Elena.
- Don't embarrass me, young man.
MAN :
Here you go, miss.
(SIGHS)
LOCKWOOD : I'm so glad you can join us tonight.
- It was nice of you to reach out to us.
- This town is one big family.
When we lose a member,
we all have to come together.
- Matt.
- Mayor.
Kelly.
KELLY : Well, I guess dead kid rates
a special greeting from the mayor, huh?
God, Mom.
I need a drink.
Hey. Check it out.
MATT : Your dad is gonna beat you
if he catches you.
Yeah, let him try.
All right, screw it.
- Hey.
- Hey. How are you?
Are you drunk?
(CLEARS THROAT)
STEFAN : Okay, I know it's a little weird,
but it's really helping me.
Alcohol, it takes the edge off.
ELENA : You're totally that drunk high-school guy
at the party sneaking booze.
- I totally am. Yeah.
- How worried do I need to be?
STEFAN : Oh, no. You don't need to be worried.
It's just until the cravings go away.
Listen, I think we should enjoy it
while it lasts.
Would you like to dance with me?
ELENA : You hate dancing.
I usually have to beg you.
No, you have to beg the sober me. The
drunk me, there's no begging necessary.
MAN : Nice to see you again.
ELENA : There's really no one dancing.
That's because they need
something better to dance to.
Be right back.
Yeah, that's not gonna work.
I tried to bribe the guy
with 20 bucks and a date.
He said Carol Lockwood has
complete control over the music choices.
ELENA : You'd be surprised
what Stefan can accomplish...
...when he puts his mind to it.
(PHOENIX'S "1901" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
Thank God.
Counting all different ideas drifting away
DAMON : Have I entered an alternate universe
where Stefan is fun?
Is he gonna be okay?
WOMAN : Yeah.
- Eventually.
One way or another.
- Way too complicated
For a minute thought I couldn't tell
How to fall out
(OVER SPEAKERS)
I got a problem and it drains my soul
Don't tell, nobody knows
History teacher, 3 o'clock.
- How do I look?
- Beautiful.
- I've been looking for you.
- Here I am.
- I haven't seen you in a while.
- Yeah, well...
...things have been a little crazy.
But I'm here now.
Do you wanna get a drink?
- Sure.
- Okay. Great.
MATT : When did this happen?
DJ had a change of heart.
- You wanna dance?
- I don't know.
- Yes, yes.
- Matt. Matt. Ugh.
MATT :
Come on.
I got a problem and it drains my soul
DAMON : I love a woman in uniform,
but I have to side with this look.
You look... You look smashing.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you, Damon. Cheers.
I needed that.
You know,
I had my doubts about you at first.
But like everyone else on the council,
you've won me over.
Thanks, Liz.
It's really nice how welcoming
the council's been.
I like my life here in Mystic Falls.
It's starting to feel like home again.
FORBES : You're not gonna like what I have to tell.
Jonathan Gilbert's claims check out.
The blood banks, the missing people,
all of it's true.
- We might have a problem.
JEREMY : Excuse me, sheriff.
Um...
I was curious if there's been any more
information on Vicki Donovan.
It was an overdose, Jeremy.
Yeah, but her body was buried.
Somebody must've done that.
We're aware of that.
The investigation is ongoing.
But there's nothing more
I can tell you at this time.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
I don't wanna lose your love tonight
STEFAN : Please dance with your alcoholic
vampire boyfriend.
- To be found
They all split when I'm in trouble
- Whoa. Watch it.
- I'm sorry. My fault. I'm clumsy.
- Heh, heh. Then get off the dance floor.
- Excuse me.
- That's no way to talk to a lady.
- Whatever.
STEFAN :
I think you need to apologize.
MAN :
I'm sorry.
STEFAN :
Now say it like you mean it.
I'm really, really sorry.
- Stefan, it's fine.
- Now walk away.
You all right?
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Well, go get your shovel
BARTENDER : Bourbon.
- Thank you.
- You noticed what your brother's up to?
- No. I've been preoccupied with yours.
Jeremy's been asking
about Vicki Donovan's death.
He knows her death
was ruled an overdose.
Really? Oh, but, sheriff, someone
buried her. Who would do that?
I know. I know. Me. I mean, I could
compel him, but he's wearing vervain.
- I don't want you to compel him.
- If he keeps asking questions...
Damon, no, I'm serious. I'm not gonna
do that to him again. I'll handle it.
Okay.
DAMON : Don't say I didn't warn you.
Her prince finally came to save her
And the rest you can figure out
But it was a trick
And the clock struck...
I saw that.
KELLY : Shh. We'll keep that between you and me.
Where's the ladies' room?
- This way. I'll show you.
- Is that soda?
Um...
Vodka, thank God.
Well, go get your shovel
And we'll dig...
JOHN : Damon, right?
- John.
- We didn't get to meet at the meeting.
Yeah, it's a pleasure.
- Are you enjoying the kickoff?
- Oh, yeah.
I forgot how much fun these can be.
Yeah, yeah. When is the last time
you were here?
It hasn't been that long.
My brother's funeral.
- How long have you been in town?
- Not long at all.
So what do you think, Damon? You
know this vampire problem is real, right?
- It's a potential bloodbath.
- I wouldn't overreact, John.
Oh, I think it's like 1864
all over again.
Vampires running amuck.
We're gonna have to hunt them down,
throw them in church burn them to ash.
That is the story, huh?
Part of the story, yeah.
- Oh, there's more?
- Oh, there's a lot more.
You see, it seems
there was a tomb under the church...
...where the vampires were hidden away
waiting for someone to set them free.
But then you already knew that,
didn't you?
Being that you're the one that did it.
DAMON : And you're telling me this, why?
Get the introductions out of the way.
Look, well, you know that I could rip
your throat before anyone would notice.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
- But you probably ingest vervain, so...
- Why don't you take a bite, find out?
It's not worth my time.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Jer.
I... I heard about your conversation
with Sheriff Forbes.
No one is trying to figure out
what happened.
They're willing to believe she OD'd.
ELENA : The office confirmed it.
If that's what happened...
Is that what you believe?
What do you think happened?
I think somebody killed her
and buried her body.
I don't think we write it off
because it's easy.
They're doing what they can.
JEREMY : Truth is the only thing
that's gonna help people.
Jer, just let it go, okay?
Whatever it was, she's gone now.
Whatever it was?
So you don't think it was an overdose.
Yes, I do.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
- Why aren't you looking at me?
- Stop it. That didn't mean anything.
If there was something else,
you would tell me, right?
Of course I would.
Oh, God, I can't even walk.
TYLER : I know. Me neither.
- Oh, God, Matt's gonna kill me.
TYLER :
He won't even notice.
I think he's actually letting himself
have some fun for once.
I'm supposed to be on my best
behavior because of Vicki...
...but I don't wanna think about it.
I can't, because if I do...
Yeah, I was a dick to her.
I was really bad.
That's what I hate,
is I can't make any of it right.
It's like I don't deserve
to even miss her.
Um...
KELLY : You're nice to talk to me.
I don't have anyone to talk to.
I don't have anyone to talk to either.
MATT : Who knew I'd been missing
all the fun?
ELENA: This is rare, believe me.
Is it bad that I'm enjoying myself?
No, it's great
that you're enjoying yourself.
- Thanks for making me dance.
- Yeah, no problem.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Waitin' on a cold day
Air. Air. I need some air.
Come with me?
- Sure.
- You haven't seen my mom, have you?
Um...
No, not in a while.
All right.
We're the wild type
Oh, my God.
TYLER : What are you doing?
KELLY : Matt...
- Mom.
- Whoa, dude, calm down, man.
- Matt!
- No!
(GRUNTING)
ELENA :
Stop it.
Tyler. Stop it, you're hurting him.
Somebody help us.
ALARIC :
Stop. Tyler.
Hey, stop. All right, stop.
What the hell was that?
Huh?
ELENA :
Here, come on. Get up. Are you okay?
What was that?
I'll take it from here.
It's all right. It's okay.
You hurt? Okay.
Go get cleaned up.
It's okay. Go get cleaned up.
Thank you for your help.
Everything's fine.
Everything's fine. Back to the party.
Let's go. Come on, have a good time.
- Are you okay?
- Where is she?
I don't know.
Come on, put your head up.
(THE AIRBORNE TOXIC EVENT'S "DOES
THIS MEAN YOU'RE MOVING ON" PLAYING)
DAMON : Do you wanna hear the bad news
or the really bad news?
STEFAN : Actually I don't want any news,
Damon.
DAMON :
All right, let me rephrase.
Do you wanna hear how the council's
back in vampire mode...
...or how I just killed
Uncle John Gilbert?
- What?
- Great party, by the way, huh?
(OVER SPEAKERS) Your words so dry
Your face so wet
Damon.
(KELLY CRYING)
Is everything all right?
No.
I ruined it. I always ruin it.
What is wrong with me?
What are you doing?
Alone, alone, alone
And my heart sinks like a stone
A stone
I'm sorry.
I feel so numb
MAN :
All right. Well...
(OVER SPEAKERS)
No, not a guest to be seen
DAMON : You've gotta be kidding me.
Thank you all.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you all for joining us tonight.
In a few moments,
we will officially begin the countdown...
...to our Founder's Day celebration.
And it's a very special one this year.
The 150th birthday of our town.
And...
And I would like to welcome
back one of our town's favorite sons...
...to do the honors of ringing
our official charter bell.
John Gilbert,
would you please join me up here?
JOHN : One hundred and fifty years
of community, prosperity, family.
We take care of each other.
We look after each other.
We protect each other.
It's good to be home.
- Look at his right hand.
- Whose?
The town's favorite son.
Look at his ring.
(CROWD CHEERS)
- Well, looks like mine.
- Yeah, and that'd be a big coincidence...
...if he didn't just come back
from the dead five minutes ago.
- Where the hell did you get that ring?
- Isobel, my wife.
(DAMON CHUCKLES)
Who gave birth to Elena...
...under the medical care
of the esteemed Dr. Grayson Gilbert...
...John's brother.
ALARIC :
You think John knew Isobel?
I think John knows a lot of things.
MAN 1 :  Take care.
MAN 2 : Have a good night.
MAN 3 : Well, when's the last time
you were?
(MAN 1 GRUNTS)
Sorry about that, man.
I really am terribly sorry.
You don't wanna do this, man.
Sorry about that too.
God, all I can do is apologize.
What's that about?
Get out of my way, please.
No girl to show off for now?
I see how this is.
(GRUNTING)
What are you, man?
ELENA :
Stefan?
(MAN GROANING)
Hey. Hey, are you okay?
What happened?
My arm.
I lost my balance and fell.
I'm clumsy.
MAN :
Good to see you guys.
- Let's go.
- Dad, I'm sorry.
TYLER : I don't even know what happened.
I was drinking and I lost control.
I can't explain it.
That is the last time you ever embarrass
this family.
- What are you doing? Matt, don't.
- I can't do it anymore, Mom.
Just go, all right? You've done it before,
more times than I can count.
I'm not leaving you.
- Matty.
- Mom!
Don't you get it?
I'm better off without you.
(CRYING)
No.
Tonight was...
God, I'm so sorry.
I know I've failed you.
And I failed Vicki.
But I won't do it to you again.
I promise I'll get it together.
MATT : I want you out of the house...
...and my life by morning.
DAMON : Going somewhere, huh?
I never like to be the last one
to leave a party.
It's too desperate. Are you here to kill
me or are you gonna let Mr. Saltzman?
- Okay, you obviously know who I am.
- I do.
JOHN : Alaric Saltzman, the high school
history teacher with a secret.
Sure know a lot
for someone who just got to town.
More than you can imagine, Damon.
My knowledge of this town
goes beyond anything that you...
...or you or the council knows.
So if you were planning on some clever
high-speed-snatch-ring-vamp-kill move...
...know that if I die...
...everything I know
goes to the council...
...including a fascinating little tale
of the original Salvatore brothers...
...and their present-day return
to Mystic Falls.
ALARIC :
How'd you get that ring?
I inherited one.
My brother Gray, the other.
This was his. And I wouldn't
have given mine to Isobel...
...had I known she'd hand it to a guy.
- So you did know her.
Who sent her your way
when she wanted to become a vampire?
- You sent her?
- Guilty.
Why, did you think someone else
sent her? Maybe Katherine Pierce?
- How do you know about Katherine?
- How do I know anything?
What do you want?
So many questions.
It's a pleasure meeting you, Ric.
I've heard so much about you.
JENNA : I'm not so excited that we have another
month of these Founder's Day events.
Tell me about it.
- You okay?
- Fine.
- Are you sure?
- I'm fine, Elena.
(GASPS)
- Oh, my God, you scared me.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry that I ran off earlier.
What happened? Is everything okay?
No.
Talk to me.
Stefan, tell me.
STEFAN : I tried so hard to keep it together
tonight.
And it was working.
It was working, but...
But then Matt's mom,
she got hurt and she was bleeding.
And I had her blood on my hands.
- And then what happened?
- And then l...
That guy in the parking lot,
I wanted to feed on him.
It took everything inside of me
not to do it.
- But you didn't?
- No, but I wanted to.
Oh, God.
STEFAN : Elena, l... My head is pounding.
I feel like my skin is on... Is on fire.
I have this hunger inside of me
that I've never...
I've never felt before in my entire life.
All I keep thinking is how I promised
I would never keep anything from you.
- And so I'm telling you this.
- It's okay. I need you to tell me things.
But I don't want you
to see me like this.
I don't want you to know
that this side of me exists.
ELENA : Stefan, you're gonna get through this.
I'm gonna help you. It's gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
STEFAN : No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I can't, l...
I'm afraid of what I could do to you.
ELENA : I'm not.
Stefan. Stefan, I'm not.
I'm not, okay?
STEFAN : I love you so much.
ELENA : I love you too.
DAMON : We have a problem, Stefan.
And when I say problem,
I mean global crisis.
It seems Uncle John has...
You don't look so good.
It's different this time, isn't it?
The need is too strong.
Of course it would be
after all these years.
Have a good night, brother.