NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret. Until now.
I know the risk, but I have to know her.
JOHN : Johnathan Gilbert had an invention
that was stolen by a vampire.
- Her name was Pearl.
- I gave your device to Damon.
Why don't you ask him for it yourself?
(SQUISHES)
Mom! Mom! Mama!
ALARIC : My wife, Isobel, spent her life researching
paranormal activity in this area.
- What have you done?
- I turned her.
- Why do I look like Katherine?
- You were adopted.
JENNA : This girl showed up,
16 and about to give birth.
- What else do you know?
- Just her name: Isobel.
MAN : Stop looking.
She doesn't wanna know you.
ELENA : She's alive?
Does that mean that she's a...?
(HORN HONKS)
(ELENA SCREAMS)
ISOBEL :
Hello, Ric.
ALARIC : Isobel.
ISOBEL : It's good to see you.
You look good.
I hear that you're a high school
history teacher?
- How is that?
- Where have you been, Isobel?
I don't have any reasons
that are gonna comfort you.
I don't have any explanations
that are gonna satisfy you.
I wanted this.
- It's that simple?
- Yeah.
You were supposed to mourn me
and move on.
ALARIC : You were my wife.
And I loved you.
How could I not search for you?
ISOBEL : Because I wasn't lost, Ric.
I understand
that you know my daughter, Elena.
And I hear that she's been looking
for me.
So I want you to arrange
for a meeting with us.
ALARIC : You want me, ahem,
to deliver a message?
Yeah.
Screw you.
You selfish bitch.
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(WHOOSHING)
What do you want from me?
- I told you.
- I'm not gonna do anything for you.
(ALARIC GRUNTING)
You better tell Elena that I wanna meet.
Or I'm gonna start killing the citizens
of this town one by one.
And I'm gonna start
with your History students.
Got it?
ELENA : I'm supposed to help build the Miss Mystic
float for the Founder's Day Parade.
If I don't, I get the wrath of Caroline.
But I wanted to check in first.
- Well, I'm doing great. Thanks for asking.
- Check in on Stefan.
Oh, him? Oh, he's... He's terrible.
What's the matter?
DAMON : He's just back to boring, strait-laced,
off the junk.
You've successfully cured him of anything
that was interesting about his personality.
- Don't forget who helped me.
- I hate myself.
Hey, did Uncle John mention anything
to you about my field trip with the teacher?
No, I've still been avoiding him.
Why? What's he up to?
- I'd love it if you could find out for me.
- I gotta go. I'm late.
Have fun with the Mystic queen.
I know I did.
(SCOFFS)
Elena called.
ALARIC : So these are the specs for the History
Department's Founder's Day float.
We're gonna be re-creating
the Battle of Willow Creek.
Tyler's been nominated
to head up the design.
- By who?
- By me. I've seen your sketches.
- I'm not really into the whole...
- You just pick your team, be creative and...
And don't screw up.
TYLER :
Great.
You wanna help me out with this?
Not really, no.
- Hey, Mr. Saltzman.
- Come with me. We need to talk.
BONNIE :
All right, show me.
CAROLINE : Let's reference
last year's Miss Mystic Float.
This was what they did last year.
- And it's exactly what we don't want to do.
- Ew.
- Yeah.
- Okay. So, what are we doing?
- Southern classic elegance.
- Gone With the Wind?
- How'd you know?
- You channel Scarlett daily.
So true.
(CAROLINE CHUCKLES)
Ugh. Where's Elena?
She's supposed to be helping.
I don't know.
Okay, what's the deal?
- What do you mean?
- Don't play dumb.
You and Elena are fighting. Spill.
- It's nothing.
- It's not nothing.
You know, this whole float...
...is supposed to be about friends
creating something together...
...and everyone is fighting.
Matt and Tyler hate each other.
You and Elena are on the outs.
I just... I don't like it.
(SIGHS)
And I can't fix it
if I don't know what's wrong.
I can't talk about it, Caroline, I'm sorry.
Damon. Thanks for coming.
Sorry I'm late. The dog ate my, uh...
Never mind.
- What's with all the furrowed brows?
- I saw Isobel last night.
Isobel's here?
In town?
- You're late.
JOHN : Didn't realize I was on a schedule.
What's with the sideshow?
ISOBEL : Cherie is a little jazz singer
that I picked up in a blues bar in Brooklyn.
And I got the cowboy at a gay rodeo
in Amarillo.
- He's gay?
- Not right now.
He's very good to me. Hey, Cherie?
(ISOBEL SPEAKS IN FRENCH)
I'm teaching them French.
Ooh. I can smell the judgment
coming off of you.
Well, they're people,
and you're treating them like they're dolls.
If we're gonna be partners,
you really have to stop being such a hater.
We're in a partnership
because we share a goal.
Don't ever confuse that
for an acceptance of your lifestyle.
My lifestyle?
So I assume
that you still don't have the invention.
I'll get it. I said I would.
You threatened to expose Damon Salvatore.
That didn't work.
You killed that Pearl lady.
Still no invention.
I really don't think
that your plan is working, John.
Well, you being here
isn't going to help anything.
(JOHN GRUNTS)
You failed, John.
I'm gonna take it from here.
DAMON :
Did you ask about Uncle John?
- Are they working together?
ALARIC :  No.
- No, they're not?
- No, I didn't ask.
- What about the invention?
- Didn't ask.
- She know about the tomb vampires?
- I don't know.
Did words completely escape you?
I was a little too distracted by
my dead vampire wife to ask any questions.
- What's she want?
- She wants to see me, Damon.
STEFAN : Alaric is supposed to arrange a meeting.
We don't know why or what she wants.
DAMON : You don't have to see her
if you don't want to.
- I don't really have a choice.
- She's threatening to go on a killing spree.
Oh.
I take it that's not okay with you guys?
ELENA :
I wanna do it.
I wanna meet her.
If I don't, I know I'll regret it.
Thanks.
Can you hear me?
Thanks for coming.
I'm nervous.
But I'm happy that you're here.
I love you.
(MOUTHS)
ISOBEL : Hello, Elena.
You look just like her.
It's eerie.
ELENA : You've met Katherine?
ISOBEL : She found me after I turned.
Genetic curiosity, I suppose.
She would be fascinated by you.
Is that how you can walk in the day?
Katherine helped me obtain it.
- Who's my father?
- Not important.
- A teenage waste of space.
- A name would be nice.
It would, wouldn't it?
You ask a lot of questions.
ELENA : Why did you compel that man to kill himself
after he told me to stop looking for you?
Dramatic impact.
Wish it would've been more effective.
- Human life means that little to you?
- It means nothing to me.
It's just part of being what I am.
No, it's not. I know other vampires.
That's not true.
You mean your boyfriend over there
by the pool table?
Stefan Salvatore.
Why Stefan?
Why didn't you go for Damon?
Or do you enjoy them both...
...like Katherine did?
- We should be in there.
- No.
Isobel made it clear
we're not to step foot inside.
- I'm not gonna kill her in a restaurant.
- You're not gonna kill her, period.
She ruined your life.
You wanna protect her?
She's my wife.
Was. Was my wife.
I looked for the woman I married,
but she wasn't there. Whoever that is...
...is cold and detached.
- Yeah.
- She's given up her humanity.
- See, I don't get that.
Stefan has his humanity.
He's a good guy.
You kill people,
but I see something human in you.
But with her, there was...
There was nothing.
DAMON : You can turn it off.
It's like a button you can press.
I mean, Stefan's different.
He wants the human experience.
He wants to feel every episode
of How I Met Your Mother...
...so he shuts his feelings out.
The problem is, as a vampire,
your instinct is not to feel.
Isobel chose the easier road.
No guilt, no shame.
No regret. I mean, come on.
If you could turn it off, wouldn't you?
- You haven't.
- Of course I have, Ric.
That's why I'm so fun to be around.
ELENA : Why did you wanna meet me?
It can't be to just catch up.
ISOBEL : Because I'm curious about you.
But the real reason
is I want what your uncle wants:
Johnathan Gilbert's invention.
(CHUCKLES)
How do you know my uncle?
I used to spend a lot of time here
when I was younger.
John had a crush on me for years.
He was the first one
that told me about vampires.
So, what made you wanna be one?
It's a very long list of reasons, Elena...
...all of which
I'm sure you've thought about.
That was your first lie.
It's inevitable.
You're gonna get old, Stefan won't.
Forever doesn't last very long
when you're human.
I'm sorry, but I don't have
what you're looking for.
Sit down.
And tell your boyfriend to walk away.
- I want the invention.
- I don't have it.
I know that. But Damon does.
- And you're gonna get it for me.
- He's not gonna give it to me.
Then the blood will be on your hands.
It was nice meeting you, Elena.
ANNA : Hey, Anna. Uh, where are you?
What's up? Uh...
Give me a call when you get this.
JENNA : How is Anna?
I like that girl. She has fire.
Uh, I don't know.
- She won't return my calls.
- Girl trouble?
No, no trouble.
Anna just owes me a call, that's it.
Is that the girl that I saw you with
at the Founder's Pageant?
So you two are getting
pretty hot and heavy, huh?
When was the last time you saw her?
- Why?
- I'm just making conversation.
No one else in this house likes me.
At least I can talk to you.
- Especially if you need someone to talk to.
JENNA : Oh, please, I'm eating.
So seriously,
how well do you know Anna?
I know Anna extremely well.
Uh-huh.
Well, know that you can talk to me
about anything.
I'm here to answer any questions
that you have...
...to help you in any way I can.
Why?
Because your dad would want me to.
I'm, uh... I'm good.
Uh-oh, Cherie. You won again.
Hope I'm wearing my good underwear.
Tonight's just one blast from the past
after another.
- No, no, no.
DAMON : Mm.
(SPEAKS IN FRENCH)
DAMON :
Mm.
It's good to see you, Isobel.
Just having fun
with your naughty little minion.
ISOBEL :
Mm.
How'd you find me?
DAMON : I searched all the bank-owned foreclosures
and found the most expensive one.
Oh, I should have known.
You were the one that taught me that.
- Mm-hm.
- What are you really doing here?
You caused quite a stir.
You blew into town, saw everyone
except for the man who made you.
- I'm a little hurt.
- I'm so sorry.
Did you bring the device?
(CHUCKLES)
- Ow.
- Heh, heh.
- What are you doing with John Gilbert?
- We dated when we were young.
- He was a little bit in love with me.
- I'm sure, one of the many.
Now, this invention,
what do you want with it?
Oh, me personally?
I don't want anything with it.
I'm just doing what I'm told.
You know, Damon,
we're on the same side.
- Oh, yeah? Which side is that?
- Katherine's.
She wants John Gilbert
to have the device.
I think that you know that she's not happy
when she doesn't get what she wants.
- Why are you doing her dirty work?
- Don't kill the messenger.
We both know
that you can't control Katherine.
- She does what she wants.
- Pfff. And so do I.
- Oh, really, Damon?
- Yeah.
You do?
What should we do now?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Oh, yeah.
Memory serves.
Now that I have your attention, listen up.
You do not come into my town,
threaten people I care about.
Going after Elena? Bad move.
You leave her alone or I will rip you to bits.
Because I do believe
in killing the messenger.
You know why?
Because it sends a message.
(GASPS AND GRUNTS)
If Katherine wants something from me,
you tell that bitch to come get it herself.
(KNOCKS)
- Hi.
- Hey.
BONNIE : I couldn't sleep last night.
You were obviously upset about something,
and I just walked away.
That's not me.
That can't be us.
You're my friend, Elena.
If you need me, I'm here for you.
And I'm sorry
I couldn't show you that yesterday.
I met my birth mother.
Oh.
Was it?
Are you okay?
(GRUNTS)
TYLER :
Hey, man.
Yeah?
So Caroline tells me you've been
on your own the past two weeks.
Is everything okay?
MATT : You're asking me about my mom?
Seriously?
Why don't I have her give you a call
when she blows through?
Dude.
That's not what I meant, okay?
I'm just trying to...
- I don't know what to say.
- Good.
Don't say anything, because you're a dick,
end of story.
I know.
Yeah, whatever.
BONNIE :
Hey, thanks for meeting me.
- I wanted you to see this.
- Is that Emily's spell book?
I've been going through it
since Grams died.
Check this out.
- That's the vampire compass.
- Yeah.
According to Emily, Johnathan Gilbert
never succeeded in inventing anything.
Emily secretly spelled them all
with magic.
Compass.
Rings.
The mystery device you told me about.
ELENA :
Yeah, that's it.
Well, part of it.
Damon only has the one piece.
Emily pledged her loyalty to Katherine.
But she couldn't stand by
and watch innocent people get killed.
This was the only way
she could think of to help...
...to let Johnathan Gilbert believe
he'd actually invented these devices.
Does it say what it does?
- Are you sure this is what Isobel wants?
- Yeah, I'm sure. Why?
This is a weapon.
Against vampires.
Elena.
Hey. Um...
Have you seen Stefan? I need to find him.
No, not lately.
Listen, do you have a second?
- Yeah, what's up? What's going on?
- Well, it's Anna.
I've left her all these messages
and she hasn't gotten back to me.
- Not even a text.
- Anna?
I didn't know
that you guys were still friends.
Yeah, we're more than friends.
Look, something
could be seriously wrong.
And if you know anything,
you gotta tell me.
I haven't talked to her, Jer.
Are you lying to me right now?
- Why would you say that?
- That's what you do. You lie.
You lie about everything.
I know what Anna is,
and I know that you know.
So tell me,
do you have any idea where she is?
No.
But, Jer... Jeremy, wait.
Jeremy.
(SIGHS THEN GASPS)
Isobel.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm your mother, Elena.
I wanna be more involved in your life.
- I don't want you in my life.
- I understand that.
You already have a lot of people
you care about.
But I've been studying.
Let's see if I got this right.
There is the witchy best friend, Bonnie.
Gonna stay away from that one.
The sad little brother, Jeremy.
And there's Caroline. Obnoxious Caroline.
I got all of my info from her, by the way.
She had no idea who I was,
and she wouldn't stop yapping.
Aww.
And there's Matt.
Friend, ex, Yappy's future ex.
Lots of connections there.
- Matt's not involved in this.
- He's involved with you, isn't he?
Look, you shouldn't be here.
You need to leave.
No. I have some friends here too.
Look. See that man over there,
standing next to Matt by the float?
His name's Frank. He's very handsome.
And he's also quite handy.
And he noticed that the axle
is kind of rusted, which is very dangerous.
So all you have to do
is apply a little bit of pressure and...
No!
(MATT YELLING)
- Hey, pick this trailer up! Guys, lift it!
- Give me a hand.
MAN : Dude, come on.
- Come on, lift.
(MATT GRUNTING)
MAN:
Come on!
- Caroline, call an ambulance.
- Okay.
Why are you doing this?
I'm showing you how easy it is
to hurt people.
You're doing this just because
of Johnathan Gilbert's invention?
- Hand it over and the fun will stop.
- Damon's not gonna give it to me.
And I think that you underestimate
how much Damon cares about you.
He'll kill you before he gives it up.
Is that before or after I kill your brother,
Jeremy?
ELENA :
Jeremy!
The ambulance is saying
15 to 20 minutes.
- I can take him.
- Caroline can take me.
- No, I didn't drive.
- Then I'll wait.
You will not wait.
Okay, you need to see a doctor.
- Tyler's driving. End of story.
- Fine.
- Go.
- I'll bring my car around.
- I see you're packing. That's a good sign.
- It won't be long now.
- Did you get the missing piece? Where is it?
- I don't have it yet.
Then why did you call me here?
Because I have the next best thing.
FRANK :
No, sit down.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Getting what I want.
Yeah, but he's my nephew...
...and you're gonna let him go
right this second.
That gaudy ring on your finger?
It comes off.
Come on.
Come on, Isobel. I know you.
Okay? It's me, John. You can't hurt a kid.
- I'll kill him to prove you wrong.
- Really? Are you that far gone?
Look, I know you've changed, okay?
But the old Isobel
is in there somewhere still.
Isn't she?
Come on, let him go.
Okay.
(SPEAKS IN FRENCH)
- Unh!
JEREMY : John!
(JOHN GRUNTING)
Okay.
(JOHN COUGHING)
ISOBEL :
Nice try.
We'll see how you do without this.
Where's the device?
STEFAN : Damon has it.
He's gonna be difficult to reason with.
ELENA : Then we'll go to him. I'll talk to him.
STEFAN : He's not just gonna hand it over,
especially if it's harmful to vampires.
What if it's not?
DAMON : Absolutely not.
ELENA : Just hear me out.
DAMON : I'm not gonna give the device to Isobel
so she can give it to John, who's gonna turn around to kill me.
- I like being a living dead person.
ELENA : But it'll be useless.
- Bonnie can take its power away.
- I don't trust her.
I can remove the original spell.
- John and Isobel will never know.
- No. No, I'll get Jeremy my own way.
Really? How are you gonna do that? Hm?
Because Isobel is a vampire...
...and Jeremy could be dead
the second you walk in the door.
Are you even up for this?
I mean, no offense.
You're no Emily Bennett.
Emily knew what she was doing.
- I've been practicing.
- It's not piano lessons, honey.
What's your favorite book?
- What?
- Name a book. Any book.
Name a book.
How about Call of the Wild,
Jack London?
(BONNIE EXHALES)
Jack London.
- Great parlor trick.
ELENA : We're doing this, Damon.
And we're gonna do it my way.
Now give me the device.
We're wasting time.
I don't trust you. I tried to kill you.
- Mm. You're right. You can't trust me.
- But you can trust me.
Thank you.
(JOHN GROANING)
Here you go.
Thank you.
What is she after?
Your ancestor invented a weapon.
A device that's extremely harmful
to vampires.
- We've been trying to get it.
- Why?
Because there's a group of vampires
from a long time ago...
...that wants revenge on this town.
But why would a vampire
help you kill other vampires? Lt...
She has her own reasons
for wanting them dead.
Look, Jeremy...
...no one ever thought vampires
would return to this town.
Not in modern times.
But they have.
- And we have to destroy them.
- All of them? No.
- There are some good ones out there.
- There's no such thing.
- I don't believe that.
- Well, your dad did.
And as his son,
that should mean something to you.
How did my father know about all this?
JOHN : Who do you think taught me
about the family history?
Done.
- Great. Now what?
- Now we give it to Isobel.
(BELL TOLLING)
(WHOOSHING)
Where's the device?
- Where's my brother?
- This isn't a negotiation.
Where's the invention?
- Where's my brother?
- Do you really think that I came alone?
ELENA :
Do you really think that I came alone?
For God's sakes. Call home.
- What?
- Call home.
Ask to speak to your brother, Jeremy.
(PHONE RINGS)
- Hello?
- Jeremy. Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Uncle John hit his head.
- It was an accident.
- And we're all laughing.
(JEREMY CHUCKLES)
- Yeah, but I'm okay.
- I'll be home soon, all right?
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
- You were never gonna hurt him.
- No, I was gonna kill him.
ISOBEL : Don't look for any redeeming qualities
in me.
I don't have any.
ELENA : But you took a risk with Damon. How did
you know he was gonna give it to me?
Because he's in love with you.
Thank you.
For what?
For being such a monumental
disappointment.
It keeps the memory of my real mother
perfectly intact.
Goodbye, Elena.
As long as you have a Salvatore
on each arm, you're doomed.
Katherine was smart. She got out.
But we all know
that you're not Katherine.
Hey.
It's okay.
ANNA (ON RECORDING):
Hey, it's Anna. Leave a message.
- Jeremy, we have to talk about this.
- No, we really don't.
ELENA : I don't know what Anna told you,
but there are things that you need to know.
JEREMY : Yeah? Because I'm pretty sure
that your journal covered it.
You read my journal?
Save me the speech
about invasion of privacy.
I read a section about Damon erasing
my memory about what happened to Vicki.
Jeremy, please, you don't understand.
The night that Vicki died,
it was like Mom and Dad died all over again.
It was all over your face.
And it hurt so much to see you like that.
I just wanted to take away your pain.
I'm so sorry. I...
Just get out.
- No, Jeremy, let's just...
- Elena.
Just get out.
Please.
Jer, l...
ALARIC : What do you want?
ISOBEL : I totally get it.
You here as a history teacher.
- It's good.
- What the hell are you doing?
You act like you don't care,
and yet here you are hunting me down.
I'm leaving.
I just thought I'd say goodbye.
You couldn't be bothered the first time,
so why now?
- You hate me. Good.
- Does that make it easier for you?
What is the point of this exercise?
What did you expect? You spent
all this time trying to track me down.
- What did you think you would find?
- The woman who gave me this.
You act like you don't care, but you cared
enough to protect me after you left.
I was a different person back then.
Right, right, right,
and that person is gone.
The woman I married, the woman I loved,
she's just... She's gone.
You expect me to believe that?
- What are you doing?
- Well, I'm ring-free.
I'm vervain-free.
So either kill me or compel me, because...
...I don't believe it.
Not for a second.
(GRUNTS)
I wanted this.
I needed this.
And I'm gonna regret it forever.
This was my mistake.
Not yours.
You're not gonna remember this.
I loved you.
I did.
And when I think about what I gave up,
it hurts.
But now your heart's free of me.
It's easier this way.
Goodbye, Ric.
JEREMY : Anna? Hey, what are you doing here?
My mother.
She's dead.
What?
She was killed.
Oh, my God, Anna.
I'm so sorry.
ANNA : I know I'm not supposed to be here,
but I don't have anywhere else to go.
It's okay.
DAMON : Would you like one?
Say it, whatever it is. Purge. Get it out.
- It's about what Isobel said.
- What about it?
STEFAN : Well, I know that you and Elena bonded.
And I know that she cares about you
and I know you care about her.
DAMON : Well, this is going
in an interesting direction.
STEFAN : I'm just concerned about Elena being hurt.
She considers you a friend.
DAMON : Same here. Elena is a very good friend.
Actually, she might qualify
as my only friend.
Is that a problem?
STEFAN : So at the risk of sounding like a, um...
- Like a jealous boyfriend...
- Oh, there's no risk. You do.
History will not be repeating itself
where Elena's concerned.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Sure.
Do you understand?
Whatever you say, man.
I mean, honestly, we're just friends.
And I wasn't looking forward
to telling her the truth anyway.
So I'll let you do it.
- What truth?
- About John.
I know you guys don't like to keep secrets
from each other.
- What are you talking about?
- Am I the only one...
...who has the ability
to put two and two together? Isobel.
Hello?
She dated John when she was 15.
She gets pregnant and ends up
at the doctor's office of John's brother.
Now, what do you think John's role is?
I mean, go ahead, think about it. I'll wait.
Did you get it? You there yet? Hm?
- So you think that John is Elena's father?
- Ding-ding-ding-ding!
(SCOFFS)
- What proof do you have?
- I don't need any.
That's a DNA test for John and Elena
and Maury Povich to deal with.
But I know how well
you deal with these big bombshells, so...
Sleep tight.
Oh, and when you do tell Elena...
...and she needs a friend to talk to
about anything...
...l'm here for her.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
ISOBEL : On your doorstep...
...you'll find what you've been looking for.
- And my ring?
Don't screw this up.
You know what you have to do, John.
I got it. I won't fail.
You better not.
Katherine wants
all of those tomb vampires dead.
And I wanna add two more to that list.
- Let me guess.
- Stefan and Damon.
I don't want this life for her.
ISOBEL : Well, that was always part of the plan.
Consider them gone.
She's our daughter, John.
We owe that to her.
I know.
CAROLINE: So you're not gonna tell me
what happened?
BONNIE : I did something bad, Caroline.
And I lied about it.
To who?
To Elena.
I pretended to do something...
...I didn't really do.
What are you talking about?
I couldn't do what she wanted me to do.
It wasn't right.
Grams would have never done it,
so I couldn't either.
But when Elena finds out...
...she's never gonna forgive me.