NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
JOHN : As a founding family member, it's my
duty to report some distressing news.
- He's a Gilbert?
- Elena's uncle.
Mayor Lockwood, is it?
My name is Pearl.
- Hi.
- This is my daughter, Anna.
Maybe there is such a thing as vampires.
They're just different.
(JEREMY GASPS)
You got a problem with blood, Anna?
FORBES : The coroner's office has officially ruled
Vicki Donovan's death a drug overdose.
- You don't think it was an overdose.
- Let it go.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
ELENA : Take my wrist. You need blood.
STEFAN : I have this hunger inside of me
that I've never...
I've never felt before in my entire life.
I don't want you to see me like this.
I don't want you to know
that this side of me exists.
Nice car.
STEFAN : Well, it was a waste to leave it sitting
in the garage.
ELENA : I didn't know you were coming back
today.
You know, I woke up this morning
and I was feeling great...
...and I figured it was time for me
to get back into things.
Does that mean you're okay now?
- With all the cravings?
- Yeah, I mean the worst part is over.
So now all I wanna do is just spend
as much time with you as possible.
I'm okay with that.
Hey, thank you.
For helping me get through
the rough patch.
You're welcome.
- We're gonna be late.
- Okay. You know what?
STEFAN : I'll catch up. I'm gonna grab my stuff.
- I'll be right behind you.
- Okay.
FORBES : There was a disturbance at the hospital.
Some of the supply was compromised.
DAMON : Compromised. You mean, stolen?
We almost missed it.
The inventory records were altered.
When the manager was questioned,
he had no recollection of changing them.
Meaning the vampire
used mind control...
...to hide the theft.
- I know what you meant.
John alerted us to recent discrepancies
at other hospital blood banks...
...in the county.
- How lucky for us we have John.
FORBES : We're stepping up security,
giving the guards vervain...
...to prevent this
from happening again.
JOHN : Might I offer a suggestion? Why don't
Damon and I put our heads together?
We could track down
whoever's doing this.
Truthfully, I could use extra hands.
Is that something you'd be willing to do?
- Well, of course. I mean, if it will help.
JOHN :  I think we'll make a good team.
Don't you, Damon?
Whatever I can do
to keep this town safe.
Even if it means spending time
with you.
ALARIC :
Okay.
This week,
we're gonna set aside our curriculum...
...for a lesson in local history
as we approach Founder's Day.
The community leaders feel that's
more important than World War II.
But, hey, what do I know?
Sorry I'm late.
ALARIC :  Looks like we will be
at full occupancy.
Welcome home, Bonnie.
Right, Founder's Day.
What does it mean
to have a Founder's Day?
Well, if you turn your attention
to this exquisite diorama over here...
...that I spent all night
painstakingly...
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
DAMON : I suppose I should be grateful.
You learned to use the bell.
- I am here on behalf of my mother.
- On behalf of or in spite of?
ANNA : I'm sorry about what
the other vampires did to Stefan.
Abducting, torturing him.
It wasn't supposed to go like that.
You were playing house with half
of a tomb of really pissed-off vampires.
- What did you think was gonna happen?
- My mom is devastated.
They tried to overthrow her.
- Why isn't she here?
- She doesn't really do apologies.
Well, that's a coincidence.
I don't do forgiveness, so run along.
If you're gonna continue playing
house with your pets...
...you might wanna stop
robbing the blood bank dry...
...because they're on to it.
I haven't been to the local blood bank
in a week.
- It's the others.
- The others are gone.
- Well, where did they go?
- They weren't cut out for this town.
After what happened, my mom
kicked them out and they took off.
It's just us and Harper now.
ELENA : Bonnie.
- Hey.
I... I tried to grab you after class,
but you had already taken off.
- How are you? How's your family?
- We're dealing. It's been hard.
Everyone here missed you.
BONNIE : Yeah, I had so much to deal with
after Grams' funeral.
And after you told me
the tomb spell failed...
...I just didn't really
wanna come back.
I hope that you understand
why I called.
I wanted you to know
before you came home.
I understand why.
I just shouldn't know.
- I know it's been really hard.
CAROLINE : Bonnie.
CAROLINE : Bonnie, thank God you're home.
I know we talked every day.
I missed you.
- How are you doing?
- Better. It's better, you know?
Glad to be back.
And I'm trying to keep myself busy.
Well, I can help with that.
Major wardrobe confab needed, ASAP.
You need to help me pick the perfect
dress for the Founder's Court.
ELENA : The Founder's Court?
Did I miss something?
The Founder's Court.
You know, Miss Mystic Falls.
They announced it today.
And you and I are both on it.
Oh, my God, we signed up for that
so long ago. I completely forgot.
So are you dropping out, then?
I can't.
No?
BONNIE : Her mom is the one
who wanted her to enter.
DAMON : How was school?
Fine.
Yeah? Same old, same old?
Nothing new?
No stories to bring home?
STEFAN : You're making small talk, why?
You seem chipper lately.
Less doom and gloom.
Little more pep in your step.
And you think it's because
I drank human blood again.
DAMON : I mean, I don't wanna brag, but I would
definitely take responsibility...
...for this new and improved you.
STEFAN : Right. Well, I hate to burst your bubble,
but I'm clean.
Yeah, not possible.
Not only is it possible,
but it is quite true.
DAMON : Stefan, let's be serious for a second.
You've spent the last century and a half
being a poster child for Prozac.
And now you expect me to believe
this new you...
...has nothing to do with human blood.
Nothing.
I'm clean.
You're lying.
STEFAN : Believe what you want.
ELENA : I'm sorry for the short notice.
I didn't know the contest was
coming up, or that I would be in it.
STEFAN :
I'll be happy to escort you.
My mom was really into
this Founder's Day stuff.
She was even Miss Mystic in her day.
I kind of wanted do it for her.
Well, it'll be great. We'll have fun.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
DAMON :
Well, well.
He's a liar and a thief.
So when were you gonna share?
Go ahead. Help yourself.
No, I'm talking about the fact
that you're a closet blood junkie.
So I'm drinking blood again.
You're the one that shoved it on me.
What's your problem?
- I have it under control.
- Under control?
You robbed a hospital.
So, what's your point?
Fine. Whatever, man. Drink up.
Just remember,
we're trying to keep a low profile.
Why don't you walk up
to Sheriff Forbes, ask her to tap a vein?
Have my actions
negatively impacted you?
I can't imagine
what that must feel like.
DAMON : Yeah. What does Elena think
about the new you?
STEFAN : Nothing's changed.
I'm still the same person.
- Clearly.
- Elena doesn't need to know anything.
You've been off the human stuff
for years, Stefan.
- Lf you're having trouble...
- I'm not.
Who do you think you're talking to?
I know what it's like.
Jekyll and Hyde feeling. That switch.
Sometimes it goes off, you snap.
DAMON : Right now is not a good time for me
to be worried about you snapping.
- I know that it pains you to see this.
- Mm.
But I'm fine. Okay? I'm fine.
So please do me a favor...
...and back off.
CAROL : This year's queen will have the
special honor of taking center stage...
...at the 150th Founder's Day Gala.
Before we crown our winner, we'd like
to get to know a bit more about you.
CAROLINE : I'm on the MF beautification committee,
volunteer at the center's soup kitchen.
ELENA : I recognize that I haven't been
as involved this year as I used to be.
CAROLINE : I implemented this year's
Go Green Campaign.
ELENA : I've been distracted
and I let a lot of things slide.
I don't think it's wrong
to win twice in a row.
I was surprised to have been selected.
I'm not from the founding families.
I'm aware of what an honor this is.
I want you to know I take it seriously.
Worked with the recycling program,
in charge of the Yearly Raffle.
My DUI made my service mandatory.
Doesn't mean I was any less committed.
ELENA : This was really important
to my mother.
She believes in community,
family, honor and loyalty.
It's a legacy she left for me.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
- Hey, partner.
- What do you want?
You haven't returned any of my calls.
Most people would take that as a hint.
Where do we start looking
for vampires?
Why the act, John? You obviously
don't care about catching vampires.
- You're here talking to me.
- Actually, I care very much.
What did Isobel say about that?
I mean, considering that she is one.
- Isobel and I share a mutual interest.
- Mm.
JOHN : The original Johnathan Gilbert had an
invention that was stolen by a vampire.
That vampire was then burned alive
in Fell's Church, or so Johnathan thought.
- And the invention was lost forever.
- Mm.
But then the vampires weren't killed,
were they?
They were trapped.
And now they're free, thanks to you,
which means the invention is retrievable.
- Well, what is it?
- The thing that matters is I want it back.
And you're going to help me
if you want your secret safe.
DAMON : I mean, why bring me into it, John?
I don't know what you're talking about,
who has it.
JOHN : Oh, come on, Damon.
You were around back then.
You know who these people are,
what they look like.
He was friendly with a woman
who turned out to be a vampire.
Her name was Pearl.
Does that ring a bell?
DAMON : I'm not playing anymore.
Get out. Get out.
- I beg your pardon.
- I only entertained this whole blackmail scheme...
...because I thought you could lead me
to Katherine.
But see, now I know you have no idea
where Katherine is, because if you did...
...you would know that Katherine
and Pearl were best friends.
See, you don't know everything,
do you, John?
JOHN : I'll tell the entire Council
what you are.
DAMON : Go for it. I'll kill every last one,
and then I'll sever your hand...
...pull your ring off and I'll kill you too.
Do you understand that?
MRS. LOCKWOOD :
Honor your partner.
Let's focus. Right hand around.
(STRAUSS' "BLUE DANUBE"
PLAYING ON STEREO)
Flirt with your eyes.
(ELENA GIGGLING)
Left hand around.
- This is ridiculous.
MRS. LOCKWOOD : Both hands.
STEFAN : You're saying that
because you don't know how.
ELENA : Sorry only one of us was around
when the dance was invented.
- Ouch.
- Whoa! Ha-ha-ha!
No, no, no.
There's no touching during this part.
It's about the simple intimacy
of the near-touch.
- Very nice, Amber.
- Thank you, Mrs. Lockwood.
If you ask me,
the near-touch is overrated.
- You seem to be in a good mood.
- Is that a bad thing?
Would you prefer me brooding
and tortured?
- Hey, I'm not complaining.
- Oh, no touching.
CAROLINE :
The Fell cousins don't have a shot.
Amber Bradley is only on the court...
...so the pageant doesn't look like
it's founding families only, which it is.
So that leaves Elena.
And she totally has the sympathy vote
since her parents died.
- How can I compete with that?
- Very nice.
- Very sensitive.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
This must sound really unimportant
in light of everything.
It's okay. I get it. You wanna win.
My grandmother was Miss Mystic
and both of my aunts.
My mom is the only one
who didn't get the gene, and I want this.
And I actually deserve this.
ELENA :
Bonnie. Hey.
STEFAN : Hey, how are you?
CAROLINE : I begged Bonnie to fill in for Matt.
He had to work today.
Bonnie, do you have a minute?
We only have 30 minutes
for rehearsal.
It'll only take a minute.
Please.
- You have to tell me what's wrong.
- It's not worth talking about.
What do you mean, not worth it?
You've barely said 10 words to me
and you won't even look at Stefan.
Is that what it is? Is it Stefan?
Listen.
BONNIE : Elena, I can't just pretend
like everything is okay.
Everything my grams did was to protect
us from those vampires in the tomb.
And now they're out,
which means she died for nothing.
I'm so sorry, Bonnie.
- What can I do to make it better?
- That's just it.
There's nothing you can do.
I blame him, Elena. Him and Damon.
And I'm not gonna put you in a situation
where you have to choose sides.
I'm just having a hard time with it.
Okay?
PLAYER 1 :
Pass it.
Stay on your man!
PLAYER 2 :
Good defense.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, dude, are you okay?
You're bleeding.
PLAYER 3 : Yeah, I'm all right.
It's just a little blood.
It's cool.
(GRUNTS)
Aah! Stefan.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. I'm sorry.
(COUGHS)
I was just...
I was feeling a little sick. I'm fine.
(KNOCKS)
- Hey, I heard you're driving.
- Hi. Yeah, I am.
Let me get that for you.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
How, uh?
How is Stefan?
- What do you mean?
- You know, he seems on edge.
He went through a lot.
He was in bad shape for a while,
but he's bouncing back now.
Alaric? Hey, buddy.
- What are you doing here?
- Well, I'm the chauffeur.
I thought I was driving.
JENNA : No need. We're going with Ric.
ELENA : Are we ready?
- Mm-hm. Jeremy can ride with you.
DAMON : In the running for Miss Mystic Falls?
ANNA : Sometimes you have to wear
uncomfortable heels to blend in.
I remember this event from 1864.
I was supposed to enter
before everything happened.
Ahh. Nostalgia's a bitch.
If you're just gonna mock me,
can you move along, please?
DAMON : John Gilbert thinks your mom stole
an artifact...
...from Johnathan senior senior
back in 1864.
What are you, his errand boy?
I don't know what it is.
I don't want him to have it.
I could ask her.
You've made it pretty clear that you
don't trust us. So why should I bother?
Because you wanna stay in Mystic Falls.
John Gilbert's making that impossible.
Find out where it is. He leaves,
you can buy a welcome mat.
ELENA : Thanks for helping me.
Don't thank me until you're sure
your hair isn't gonna burn off.
You know, I remember when my mom
and I were first applying for this.
- She was so excited.
- So were you, if I recall.
I was. She just made it sound
like so much fun.
A lot's changed since then.
I hate to break it to you,
but it's late for cold feet.
I don't have cold feet. I just...
I think I'd be enjoying it a lot more
if she was here.
I'll tell you one thing. Your hair
would have a better chance if she was.
(ELENA CHUCKLES)
Okay. I should go put my dress on.
Be careful with that thing.
Don't hurt anybody.
JOHN :
You look miserable.
(JEREMY CHUCKLES)
JEREMY : Are there really a whole month of these
events that I'm supposed to show up at?
You can fight it if you want,
but it's part of being a Gilbert.
Yeah. You mentioned
you know a lot about the family.
You know anything about our ancestor,
Johnathan Gilbert?
Prolific writer, crazy inventor.
Why do you ask?
Well, I read his journal.
Is that right?
Yeah. I actually found it
in all Dad's stuff.
Well, that's surprising.
Most of them are locked away.
- There's more of them?
- Johnathan Gilbert journaled his life.
Right down to
the bitter, insane, drunken end.
- The guy had a lot of demons.
- And did you read them?
I've browsed. Yeah.
What did you think
about what he wrote?
Crazy ramblings of a madman,
of course.
She's very pretty.
Yeah. Yeah, she's a friend of mine.
Excuse me.
(AMBER BREATHES DEEPLY
THEN CHUCKLES)
ELENA : Are you okay, Amber?
AMBER : I hate being the center of attention.
I get panic attacks.
Do you need some privacy
so you can change?
Actually, I'm just gonna go
get some air.
Hey.
- You can't be back here.
- We need to talk.
Does it have to be right now?
Normally I would have a different outlook
on what I'm about to tell you...
...but since it could really
inconvenience me, I'll squeal.
What are you talking about?
Stefan's still drinking human blood.
- What?
- Yeah.
DAMON : A month ago, I would've rejoiced,
but with the Council back on the alert...
...it is not a good time
for Stefan to fly off the handle.
I know he's been a little edgy,
but he said that was normal.
DAMON : He has a fridge full of stolen
blood-bank contraband in the house.
Oh, my God.
He has no idea what normal is.
His entire existence isn't normal.
Normal to a vampire
is drinking human blood.
He spent this time fighting it, when he
should've been learning to control it.
And now it's controlling him instead.
ELENA : I can't believe this. I mean,
it's Stefan we're talking about here.
DAMON : Stefan on human blood, Elena.
He'll do anything, he'll say anything...
...because he's not gonna
wanna stop.
Trust me.
JEREMY :
Anna.
What is it?
- Oh, come on. Don't be like that.
- Why not?
You were basically using me to turn you
into a vampire...
...so you could be with someone else.
- I wasn't using you.
Really?
Then how would you like to define it?
I don't think it's worse
than becoming friends...
...so you could give your mother
my blood.
How do you know that?
It's not important.
Seriously, Jeremy.
- What do you know?
- Everything.
I know everything.
ELENA : This is all my fault. I'm the one
who fed him the blood in the first place.
Uh...
STEFAN : What's going on in here?
I'm just filling Elena in
on your extracurricular activities.
- What are you talking about?
- I know about the blood, Stefan.
I'm gonna... I'll be downstairs drinking.
(CHUCKLES)
STEFAN : I was gonna tell you.
When?
I'm fine.
The blood, it doesn't change anything.
ELENA : It's changing you.
Why? Because I kept it a secret
from you?
Come on, Elena, look.
STEFAN : Given the way that you're reacting now,
can you really blame me for doing that?
Are you hearing yourself right now?
You've been stealing blood and lying.
And you say that everything's fine?
Everything is not fine, Stefan.
So you and Damon
have everything figured out.
It's not about Damon.
It's about what's happening to you.
I know
and I'm telling you that I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Please, come on.
Elena, I thought you...
I thought you believed in me.
(KNOCKS)
CAROL : Elena, let's go. The lineup's starting.
- I just... I need a minute.
- You're not even dressed yet.
Escorts wait downstairs, Stefan.
(PANTING AND GRUNTING)
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
LOCKWOOD :
Miss Tina Fell...
...escorted by Bartholomew Whitmore.
(APPLAUSE)
Has anyone seen Amber?
Do you see Stefan down there?
Nope. Just my boring fill-in escort.
- What happened to Matt?
- They wouldn't let him out of work.
- What happened to Stefan?
- I don't know.
He just disappeared somewhere.
I don't know.
What am I doing?
I never should've gone through
with this.
- What do you mean?
- I need to find Stefan.
This isn't me.
I'm not this person anymore.
No, no, no. No way. No.
You had your chance to drop out.
And believe me, I was all for it.
Because there is no way
that I can beat you.
Elena, you're doing this
because it was important to your mom.
LOCKWOOD : Miss Caroline Forbes
and her escort, Jeffrey Lockwood Hamilton.
(APPLAUSE)
Elena, you're next.
(SIGHS)
- You're missing Elena's introduction.
JEREMY : I don't care.
So she has no idea
you read her journal?
She keeps things from me,
I'm gonna keep things from her.
What are you gonna do now?
Now that you know everything
that she's been hiding from you.
I don't know.
There's a part of me that's so angry.
I mean, she covered up
what happened to Vicki...
...and erased my memory...
...but there's also this other part of me
that's glad.
I...
I don't wanna remember Vicki
like that.
As a monster?
No, as someone who wanted
to hurt me.
When I met you...
...you were just a part of my plan
to get my mother back.
But then things changed.
All the time we spent together.
I would never do anything to hurt you.
Not now. You know that, right?
Yeah, I know that.
- Where are we going?
- I don't know.
I'm in the ceremony.
Not now you're not.
You're standing in the parking lot
with me.
AMBER :
I'm in the parking lot with you.
I'm sorry.
STEFAN : I'm not very good to be around
right now. I'm a little bit on edge.
I've been drinking the human stuff,
and it's really screwing with my head.
She knows now.
She wasn't supposed to find out. I didn't
want her to. Now everything's ruined.
You seem sad.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm not sad.
I'm freaking hungry.
LOCKWOOD :
Miss Elena Gilbert...
...escorted by Mr. Stefan Salvatore.
(APPLAUSE)
(WHISPERING)
Where's Stefan?
I don't know.
- What is she doing with Damon?
- I have no idea.
- What are we gonna do?
- Right now we have to get through this.
STEFAN : I don't hurt people. I don't do that.
I'm the good brother.
AMBER : Do you wanna hurt me?
I want to kill you.
I wanna rip into your skin.
And I wanna feed on your blood.
Under your skin.
Pulsating, flowing.
Your carotid artery right there.
If you puncture this right,
you can control the flow.
It takes practice...
...but it doesn't have to make a mess.
You don't have to waste any.
What's stopping you?
If I do this...
...if I give in, there's no going back.
Then don't.
I just want one taste.
That's all I need.
One taste.
(APPLAUSE)
(WHISPERS)
Where's Amber?
I don't know.
LOCKWOOD : Before I crown the winner,
I'd like to offer a personal thank you...
...to all of these young ladies
for their efforts to better our community.
So without further ado,
it is my honor...
...to announce our very own
Miss Mystic Falls, Miss Caroline Forbes.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
Congratulations.
I actually won.
JOHN :
There's blood on the glass.
Get me Damon Salvatore.
STEFAN :
I can't do this.
(STEFAN GRUNTING)
- What's the matter?
- I can't do this.
AMBER :
It's okay.
It doesn't hurt that much.
Just not so hard next time.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
I can't stop.
Why aren't you afraid of me, huh?
You told me not to be.
What's your name?
Amber.
Listen to me, Amber.
I need you to be afraid of me.
I need you to run like hell.
Do you understand me?
Run. Run. Now.
(AMBER WHIMPERING)
Did you find him?
There were signs of a struggle
in the bathroom.
There was blood.
- And that Amber girl is missing.
- Oh, my God.
No, he wouldn't hurt her. He won't.
Let's just find him, okay?
Let's get your coat. Come on.
(PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
(AMBER SCREAMS)
- You said to run.
- I changed my mind.
(AMBER SCREAMING)
Stefan!
DAMON :
Stefan.
Come on. Get control. Come on.
It's okay. Come on.
Breathe through it, man.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Stefan, stop it.
(GROANING)
It's okay.
Stefan.
She doesn't remember
what happened.
DAMON : It's a good thing the girls got here.
She lost a lot of blood.
You didn't see anything?
No, we just found her
and then called Damon.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- It looks like it, yeah.
You girls get back to the party.
Damon and I can take it from here.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- They didn't see the bite mark?
- No. I got here before they got close.
There was too much blood.
They couldn't see it clearly.
- Bonnie, can we talk about this?
- There's nothing to talk about.
Bonnie, please.
I told you
I wasn't gonna make you choose.
But I need to make the choice
for myself.
Please just leave me alone.
- Jer, you ready?
- Just a sec.
Who's that girl with Jeremy?
His friend Anna.
JOHN : What's her story?
JENNA : Why so nosy?
I'm just curious.
He really seems to like her.
She's new in town, I think.
She and her mom, Pearl.
The family you're so rudely trying to
prevent from buying Grayson's building.
Her mother's name is Pearl?
Yes. So?
I believe I already know all about her.
Oh, good. There you are.
Jenna wanted me to get the car.
What happened?
- All right, now this is getting weird.
- We're here to talk.
Not in the mood.
Today has been a no-good, very bad day.
Annabelle tells me you're looking for
something I took from Johnathan Gilbert.
I'm listening.
- What is it?
PEARL : Johnathan was passionate...
...about his inventions.
He confided in me...
...that he had created
a detection device...
...meant to track
the town's vampire element.
- That was the pocket watch.
PEARL : That's what it turned out to be, yes.
But that's not what I stole.
I discovered my mistake when I saw
the watch in Johnathan's hand.
The night they took us...
...its dial pointed at me.
- So, what is this?
PEARL : I have no idea.
But now it's yours.
- What's the catch?
- There is no catch.
My daughter wants to stay here.
I wanna stay here.
You refuse to trust us,
and for good reason.
Consider this an apology.
STEFAN :
You shouldn't be here.
I know.
Now you know.
That wasn't you.
Oh, it was absolutely me.
A monster, a predator.
It's who I am, Elena.
That's what the blood makes you.
The blood brings out
what's inside of me.
And if you think any differently,
then you're an idiot.
I know this isn't you, Stefan.
I wanted to drain every ounce of blood
from that girl's body.
- No.
- It's who I am, Elena.
No, you can't scare me off.
- Why would you risk it? Why come here?
- Because I did this.
This is my fault.
I made you drink the blood.
STEFAN : All you did was expose me
to who I really am.
- This isn't you.
- Stop saying that!
Don't get any closer.
- I'm gonna let this happen to you.
- Stop.
I'm not gonna give up on you.
I believe in you.
Stop! Stop!
I'm so sorry.
ELENA : It's okay.
It's okay.
(STEFAN SOBS)
- I don't know what's happening to me.
- It's okay, Stefan. Shh.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
DAMON : Are you sure you wanna do this?
I'm sure.
There's no guarantee
this is gonna work.
It has to.
Coming?
ELENA : I'm gonna stay here.