NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret, until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
DAMON : She's a dead ringer for Katherine.
- Hello, brother.
Damon.
DAMON : There's nothing about
that Logan guy I killed in here.
- Covering it up.
- It's a small circle.
- Founding families, a few city officials.
- I will do anything I can to help.
Alaric Saltzman.
I'm your new history teacher.
JEREMY : That's a cool ring.
- Thanks. It was my father's.
I have to leave.
Too many people have died.
- I can't be a part of your life anymore.
- Don't go, Stefan.
Goodbye, Elena.
You know what,
I'm not gonna invite you in.
- Some other time then.
- I was dumped.
Yeah, well, Logan's a jerk.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Hello, Jenna.
- Logan.
Aren't you gonna invite me in?
Why are you here, Logan?
I missed you. I was out of town.
Yeah, I got that e-mail.
You got an e-mail?
You didn't send an e-mail?
I can explain. Just invite me in
and I'll tell you everything.
I'm not gonna invite you in. Forget it.
Come on, Jenna, it's me.
- The answer is no.
- I know you.
You're always one step
from a "maybe."
A tiny nudge to "yes."
(SCOFFS)
You just pointed out
that I have no self-control.
Clever strategy.
(SIGHS)
LOGAN :
Evening.
Hey.
You're that guy from the news,
Logan Fell.
I watch you every night.
Well, I used to. I mean,
you've been missing from my TV.
- I took some time off.
- I noticed.
I'm Daphne.
- Hey, you know something, Daphne?
- No, what?
(DAPHNE SCREAMS)
JEREMY :
"I live in fear.
It consumes me.
In the early evening, when I see
the sun begin to fade, the fear comes.
Because I know
that the night brings death."
Jeremy's got his sketch pad out.
- You're kidding.
- Nope, but don't say a word.
The minute we encourage him,
he'll put it away.
Psychology major. Check that.
And you and Stefan?
- Update?
- He knows how I feel and where I stand.
And I know where he stands,
but it doesn't matter.
He's leaving, moving away.
- Where's he going?
- I've stopped asking questions.
- The answers get scary.
- Oh.
Yours leaves, mine returns.
Logan?
- He's back.
- Ugh.
- I didn't let him pass the front door.
- I hope you slammed it in his face.
- Ah, medium slam.
- Three-strike rule, Jenna.
You're not even allowed
to watch the news.
Exactly. No more Logan "Scum" Fell.
So any idea of where you'll go?
I don't know. London, maybe.
- See some friends.
- You don't have any friends, Damon.
You're right, Stefan. I only have you.
- So where are we going?
- "We" are not going anywhere.
I'm gonna live my life
as far away from you as possible.
But we're a team.
We could travel the world together.
We could try out
for The Amazing Race.
Mm. That's funny.
Seriously, where are you going?
Because we're not staying
in this town.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
FORBES :
I'm here to see Damon.
Uh, sure. Okay.
Sheriff. What a surprise.
Sorry to bother you,
but we need to talk.
Come in.
I hope you understand the secrecy.
Stefan doesn't know about this yet.
- I'd like to keep it that way.
- Of course.
- Kids are too young to be brought into this.
- So, what do you need?
There's been another attack.
A female victim, her throat torn out,
completely drained of blood.
- It fits the pattern.
- I'm sorry. I don't understand.
I thought we solved that problem
when I staked the blond one.
I'm thinking she must have turned
someone.
Or multiple someones, I don't know.
The story is another animal attack...
...but I'm not sure how long
we can keep lying to them.
The Council is in an uproar.
We thought we were past this.
So, uh, what do we do?
You're the only one
who's taken on a vampire.
We were hoping you could tell us.
MATT : And then the ballet dancer
and the crunker did the salsa.
I was awake for that part.
Well, I don't know
when you fell asleep.
Um, did you see the Celine Dion waltz
about cancer?
Those always make me cry.
Yeah.
Then the loud judge kept screaming
and I couldn't take it so I turned it off.
I sat through Family Guy,
so you owed me.
Did I miss something?
BONNIE :
They've been hanging out.
ELENA : Kind of weird, don't you think?
- She needs someone nice like him.
As opposed to a homicidal vampire
like Damon.
Yeah, how are you doing
with all that?
I'm freaked out.
Damon attacked me.
I could be dead right now.
- But I'm also grateful.
- Hmm?
- To Stefan. He saved my life.
- Mm.
Have you seen him?
Not since he told me he was leaving.
For all I know, he's already gone.
He wouldn't leave
without saying goodbye.
Yes, he would.
He thinks he's protecting me.
Clean break and all that.
So, what are you gonna do?
What am I supposed to do?
I already begged him not to go.
If I ask again, I'm being selfish.
- It is what it is.
- Oh. Maybe it's for the best.
What? Why?
I mean, what kind of future could you
have had with him, even if he stayed?
BOY : Let me tie it tighter.
GIRL : Sorry.
- Did you just...?
- No, I swear.
ELENA : Ah. God.
GIRL: How's that? You got it?
DAMON :
Thank you for stopping by.
FORBES : Let me know.
DAMON : Absolutely.
What is wrong with you?
You killed somebody?
DAMON : Get off of me.
A, don't touch me.
B, if I had, I wouldn't have been
so obvious about it.
And C,
there's another vampire in town.
- That's impossible.
- Obviously not.
Well, who could it be?
Ah, what do we care?
We're leaving anyway, right?
No, I can't leave now,
and you know that.
STEFAN :How are we supposed
to find this person?
Let the adults handle this stuff.
See you later, okay?
- Okay.
- Bye.
Hi.
We need to talk.
- So, what's up with you and Forbes?
- Nothing's up.
I saw you two in the hall today.
Don't even try and deny it, bro.
- You're tapping that.
- No. It's not like that.
Never is. Till you become we people.
- "We people"?
TYLER : Yeah.
"We can't make it to the party."
"We'll never miss a game."
"We don't like the color red."
We hung out, like, twice.
Like I said, "we."
So you have no idea who it could be?
None.
But it must be somebody new,
because leaving a body like that...
...they're either sloppy
or they're trying to send a message.
- And you're sure it's not Damon?
- Well, I'm never sure about Damon...
...but he's been trying to keep a low
profile so it doesn't make sense to me.
So, what are you gonna do?
Damon is tracking them right now.
Look.
I promised you the truth...
...so I wanted to tell you.
I want you to be careful.
(ELENA SIGHS)
When I saw you, I thought
you were coming to say goodbye.
Not yet.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
JEREMY : Hey, what do you think?
- Creepy.
I found this old journal in Dad's stuff.
Jonathan Gilbert, from the 1800's.
He's kind of a freak show.
He wrote about demons
and all these people getting slaughtered...
Yeah, he was a writer.
Short stories, horror stuff.
Oh, he wrote fiction?
Figured he was just a lunatic
or a drunk.
Well, he was a Gilbert.
Probably a little bit of both.
- So, what do I do now?
DAMON : Just wait. I'll be there in a minute.
Can you hurry? I have things to do.
You can give me that.
So why did you need me to do this?
Because I interfere with the signal.
Look, can I go now?
This has blown, like, half of my day.
You do that.
Get in your car, go home.
Forget I asked you to do this.
- Okay. Bye now.
- Bye.
(DAMON GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
LOGANN :I have tons of these wooden bullets,
so nothing funky.
You don't wanna do this, trust me.
(GROANING)
- That's what you get.
- For what?
- You made me like this.
- I killed you but I didn't turn you.
See, I know what you
and your brother are.
I've been watching the two of you.
I knew you'd show up here.
And I'm glad you did
because I have some questions.
Me first. Who turned you?
How should I know?
Last thing I remember
is I'm about to stake your brother...
...and then you grab me. That's it.
Until I wake up in the ground behind
a used-car dealership on Highway 4.
Somebody buried me.
It happens. Ow. Unh.
- You bit me. It had to be you.
- Damn it.
You have to have vampire blood
in your system when you die.
I didn't do that.
Some other vampire found you,
gave you their blood.
(DAMON GRUNTS)
- Who?
- That's what I wanna know.
It's not like the welcome wagon was waiting
with a Bundt cake and a handbook.
It's been a learn-as-you-go process.
One minute,
I'm a small-town, on-the-rise news guy...
...and next thing I know,
I can't get into my house.
Because my foot won't go through the door.
- You have to be invited in.
- I know.
- I live alone.
- Oh, that sucks.
Now, I'm at the Ramada,
watching pay-per-view all day...
...eating everything in sight,
including Housekeeping.
It could be worse.
All I can think about is blood.
And killing people.
I can't stop killing people.
I keep killing. Ha, ha.
And I like it.
I'm conflicted.
Welcome to the club.
Wait a minute.
The cops only found one body.
I left one. I was tired.
I've been hiding the rest of the bodies.
They're right back there.
- You're kidding.
- They're just piling up.
(ALL CHATTERING)
(THE FEATURES' "OFF TRACK"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Thank you, sir. Nice to see you.
Let's try to make something clear
So, what do we know?
Nothing new to report yet.
(LOCKWOOD SIGHS)
My highly reliable deputies
are all on alert.
But if you feel the need
to be more proactive...
...by all means,
grab a stake, and have at it.
What extra precautions can we take?
Right now there's nowhere safer
than a crowded public place.
And for once, mayor,
we actually know where our kids are.
(LOCKWOOD SIGHS)
- What do you want?
- Hey, uh, just surprised to see you here.
JEREMY :Art usually implies culture
and culture implies... Well, not you.
Go to hell.
Where we stand
What it means
And what has come between
- Still wanna be an astronaut?
- Ha, ha. I can't believe you remember that.
I remember the tinfoil
that you wore on your head.
I was 8.
How are you doing?
I've had it easier.
You?
I mean, I heard some things.
So it's true then, you and Stefan?
Yeah, it is.
What about you, Matt Donovan?
- I heard about Caroline.
- Uh, man, not you too.
- Hey.
- We're friends.
- It's not a big deal.
- No?
No.
LOGAN :Why am I so overly emotional?
All I can think about
is my ex-girlfriend.
I wanna be with her,
and bite her and stuff.
DAMON :Well, you probably love her.
Anything you felt before
will be magnified now.
You're gonna have to learn
how to control that.
What about walking in the sun?
I'm a morning person.
You can walk in the sun.
Which, by the way, is pretty cool.
The Council would never suspect you.
That's not in the journals.
- The journals?
- Yeah, the founding fathers...
...they passed down journals to
their kids. Come on, you gotta tell me.
How can you walk around in the sun?
- Who turned you?
- How do you walk in the sun?
Who turned you?
You know, I've been really nice so far.
But I will kill you.
Then you'll never know.
- You're not answering my question.
- You first.
It seems we're at
a bit of an impasse then, doesn't it?
I have things to do, people to kill.
I guess I'll be needing
a little head start.
(DAMON GROANS)
Ah. Damn it.
ELENA :I'm guessing you're not here
to plan the path for your future.
You're looking out for me.
STEFAN :I hope that's okay.
(SIGHS)
You know, I wanted to be a doctor...
...before everything happened.
But, uh, then I couldn't because...
The blood?
Yeah.
I've dabbled in a bunch
of different things though.
Didn't love anything enough
to stick to it?
No, I loved it all. I just...
I had to move on before anybody could
notice that I wasn't getting any older.
- How long before that would happen?
- A few years, usually.
Sometimes shorter.
And you always left?
I didn't have a choice.
So, what about...? What about you?
What are your, uh, plans for the future?
ELENA :I don't wanna talk
about my future, Stefan.
Because everything you're saying is
making it perfectly clear you're not gonna be in it.
Well, it's not that
I don't wanna be in it...
You can't. I get it.
I heard you the first time
and the second time.
And I appreciate you
looking out for me...
...but, please,
if you're gonna leave, then just go.
- Hide me.
- What's going on?
The "Scum" Fell has landed.
Logan's here?
Wait, Logan Fell?
(JENNA SIGHS)
ELENA :Stefan, what's going on?
Jenna, are you dodging me?
It's a form of self-preservation.
Um, Elena, why don't you and Jenna
go somewhere else.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
You know, your brother asked me
the same thing.
In fact, why don't we just skip past
all that "who turned me" stuff...
...and get the answer that I want.
How can I turn into a day-walker?
Damon and I
are the only two that I know of.
But you're both very cagey
on the how.
Which tells me that there is a way.
You know, in case you hadn't noticed,
I'm quite the celebrity in this town.
It would be very, very easy for me
to expose you.
You wanna know
how you can walk around in the sun?
I do.
You can't.
Don't ever threaten me again.
When Logan came to the house,
what did he say?
Oh. Fake flattery, stupid dimpled grin,
puppy-dog eyes.
I'm serious, Jenna.
- How did he act? What did he say?
- He was the usual Logan.
He was charming,
a little more manic than usual.
He kept trying to convince me
to let him in.
What?
Okay, listen to me very carefully.
Do not, under any circumstances,
talk to him again.
I'm serious, Jenna. Like, ever.
Hey, Elena. Jenna.
Hi, Mr. Saltzman.
- Yeah, I was hoping to see you here.
- Career Night is the new bowling.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Um, excuse me.
DAMON (OVER PHONE):
Logan Fell is a vampire.
And when I find him again,
I am gonna destroy him, limb by limb.
What happened? You okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I was ambushed.
I was shot.
Now I'm vengeful.
Just gotta find him.
Well, there's no need.
- He's here at the school.
- You're kidding me.
- Why the hell is he there?
- He's working the crowd.
Well, I'll be right there.
So?
Anything you'd like to share?
- What are you doing?
- Following my future.
- There it is.
- "Broadcast journalism"?
Yes. Broadcast journalism.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You don't even read the paper.
Liz.
Logan.
LOGAN :
What are you gonna do, stake me?
Bury me in another shallow grave.
What would the e-mail say this time?
I didn't have a choice.
You bitch.
I died for you.
For this town.
You've known me since I was 6.
And you swept me under the rug
like dirt.
- You knew what you were getting into.
- I was one of you.
And now you're one of them.
Watch your back, sheriff.
Get a backup team to the school.
Keep it within the circle. It's a V5.
JEREMY :
I didn't know you drew.
- It's an elective.
- It's good stuff.
You like graphics?
Because that's kind of my thing.
Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
Well, it's just something else
we have in common.
And what's the other thing? Vicki?
Let's hang out
because we did the same chick?
Go be friends with one of the many other
guys she screwed. There's no shortage.
Whoa, whoa. Hey, hey.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Break it up.
- All right, work it out, tough guy.
- You two, follow me.
Excuse me, mayor,
where are you taking them?
I'm gonna talk to them.
All fights should end in handshakes,
don't you think? Come on.
CAROLINE :Bonnie, where are you?
I'm ready to go.
I'll be outside.
Hey, damsel in distress, need a ride?
Oh, my God. Logan Fell,
Channel 9, is that you?
I used to babysit you, Caroline Forbes.
Don't mock me.
Well, I was supposed to go home
with Bonnie but I can't find her.
It's not a problem, really.
- It's on my way.
- Okay.
- You know, this is fate.
- And why is that?
Because I'm interested
in broadcast journalism.
So can I ask you a couple questions?
Anything you want.
But first, buckle up.
Okay.
MATT : Hey.
- Hey.
Have you seen Logan Fell,
the news guy?
Yeah. He just gave Caroline
a ride home.
Stay here.
Okay, let's get this
out of your system.
Go ahead. Fight.
You want us to what?
I'm not gonna fight him, Dad.
I don't think so, sir.
You don't fight in there like pansies.
You take it outside, fight your battles
like men, and move on.
That's the lesson my dad taught me.
So let's settle it. Fight.
- Come on, Dad.
- No, it's not gonna happen.
I said, fight.
Whoa. What's going on out here?
I'm just letting these two kids
work it out.
- We're good here. Go back inside.
- I don't wanna go back inside.
What I want is an answer
to my question.
What's going on out here?
Who do you think you're talking to?
- Do I look like a student?
ALARIC : No.
You look like a full-grown,
alpha-male douche bag.
You don't talk to me like that.
I could have your job like this:
(CHUCKLES)
You do that.
Then it'll be you and me
in this parking lot, working things out.
You cool with that?
- You just marked yourself.
- Okay.
You all right?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Where are you?
LOGAN : Your daughter has expressed
an interest in journalism.
I think it's important
to foster young minds.
What do you want?
The satisfaction of turning your daughter
into a vampire.
(LOGAN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
DAMON : Payback's a bitch, isn't it?
(GROANING)
Get her out of here.
FORBES :
Logan, what happened? Logan?
Sheriff, it's Damon.
- Where's Caroline?
DAMON : She's okay.
Uh, I'm on Elm Street.
(GROANING)
I'm gonna try this one more time.
- Who turned you?
- I told you, I don't know.
This tire iron here
could take your head clean off.
- Is that your final answer?
- How can you side with them?
I don't side with anyone.
You pissed me off, I want you dead.
- Who turned you?
- I don't know.
- Oh, well, then you're screwed.
- Wait!
- I do know.
- You're lying.
Think you're the only one
who wants in that tomb...
...underneath the old church?
If you are lying me, I will end you.
I am not lying. There's another way
to break the spell. We can help you.
Meet me at the old church.
(SIREN WAILING)
Take me down. Make it look real.
Make it look real.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
FORBES : Where is she?
- She's okay.
My brother is taking her home.
I'm sorry, sheriff.
I just wasn't strong enough.
MAN :
All right.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
- Caroline?
STEFAN : She's okay, I took her home.
She was shaken up, but all she knows
is Logan attacked her, nothing else.
- Where's Logan?
- Damon is...
...dealing with him.
- As in?
You saw what happened tonight,
right?
I mean, you understand
why we can't be together? You see it?
Yeah, I'm starting to see
a lot of things, Stefan.
Come on, I'll, uh...
I'll give you a ride.
Uh, I can get home.
I know.
All right, that would be nice.
Hey.
What do you want?
I don't know.
I, uh, thought that was weird
with your dad.
What he did.
Is he like that all the time?
Is that what you gotta go through?
Man, I get it.
I get it.
- What's your problem?
- Look, I don't need your pity.
You don't have to be like this.
- You don't.
- Just go.
JEREMY :
What is your problem, man?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know.
ELENA : What I said before,
about you leaving, it was harsh.
STEFANN : No, you had every right.
You asked me
what I want my future to be.
I wanted to be a writer.
My mom sort of pushed me
into that direction...
...from the time I was able to read.
She supported me, encouraged me,
bought me my first journal.
And then she died.
And I can't see myself
being a writer anymore.
That was something that we shared.
You think that you brought
all of this bad stuff into my life...
...but my life already had it.
I was buried in it.
This is different.
It doesn't make it any less painful.
I know that it's hard to understand...
...but I'm doing this for you.
No.
You don't get to make
that decision for me.
If you walk away, it's for you.
Because I know what I want.
Stefan, I love you.
Don't.
Elena, I can't.
Yes, you can.
Don't hide from me.
(METAL CLATTERING)
- Who are you?
- A friend of Jenna's.
Jenna sent you?
No, I came on my own.
Ah. I get it.
Well, I know you think this makes you
brave, but actually it makes you stupid.
Either way, here I am.
What do you want?
Jenna's a good person,
and she deserves the best.
I'm here to make sure she gets it.
Was that supposed to be a threat?
Couldn't you throw a punch
or maybe provoke me a little?
(ALARIC CHUCKLES)
I'm not a violent guy by design.
- You're not a very smart one, either.
- And how is that?
LOGAN : Because you have no idea
who you're talking to.
(YELLING)
(LOGAN GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
TYLER :
I need a ride.
Sure.
Look, I like Caroline.
She's got this thing, this way about her
and I like her, okay?
And I'm not gonna defend it
or apologize about it.
- Okay.
- So stop your little bromance bitch act.
Okay.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
I've never been in your room before.
STEFAN :
Hmm.
Well, it hasn't changed much
over the years.
Do you just leave everything here
when you come and go?
It's the only place
that has remained constant.
This room holds every memory...
...that I ever thought was important
enough to hold on to.
A lot of memories.
Yeah.
You thirsty or anything?
A little. You?
- Oh.
- Heh.
I'm fine.
I'm gonna get you something
to drink, okay?
Okay.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
DAMON : Hello?
FORBES : I just wanted to say thank you.
I don't know how you did it.
Uh, I'm not following.
We found Logan's body
by the old Fell warehouse.
It's been disposed of.
He was hoarding victims.
Innocent victims.
What?
This town owes you so much.
So do I.
Elena?
(SOBBING)
(ELENA GASPS THEN TIRES SCREECH)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS THEN GASPS)
(PANTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(ELENA SCREAMING)