NARRATOR:
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN : For over a century,
I have lived in secret. Until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
ELENA : I'm Elena.
STEFAN : I'm Stefan.
DAMON : I'm Damon.
ELENA : You didn't tell me you had a brother.
- It's complicated.
DAMON : Elena. Dead ringer for Katherine.
- Which one of you dated her first?
STEFAN : Katherine is dead.
And you hate me
because you loved her.
- I was hoping I'd see you again.
STEFAN : She's not a puppet.
She doesn't exist for you to feed on
whenever you want to.
- They're whatever I want them to be.
- Wear it for me for good luck.
DAMON :
You wanna kiss me.
Vervain in the necklace.
It's been a while since anyone
could resist my compulsion.
STEFAN :
There's nothing human left in Damon.
No good, no kindness. No love.
Only a monster who must be stopped.
(BANGING)
(GASPS)
ELENA :
Hello?
Jeremy?
LOGAN (ON TV): This is Logan Fell coming
to you live from Mystic Falls...
...with breaking news
of another deadly animal attack.
The wild animal terrorizing citizens
has claimed another victim...
...local high school student,
Elena Gilbert.
Police are certain that evidence will
confirm that this is the same animal...
...responsible for recent attacks.
DAMON :
You know what's coming next.
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
DAMON :
Bad dream?
Do you know how easy it was
to get into your head just now?
You really need some human blood.
It might even the playing field.
Football reference.
Too soon?
All right, I deserve that.
But I just wanted to let you know,
they caught the culprit.
The animal responsible for killing
Tanner and all those people.
- What are you talking about?
- A mountain lion. Really big one.
It attacked a hunter this morning.
It's all over the news.
"Deadly beast captured.
All's well in Mystic Falls."
Why would you cover your tracks?
I've decided to stay a while.
And I'm having fun here
with you and Elena.
- Can't touch her now.
- The vervain keeps me out of her head.
Maybe that's not my target.
Believe it or not, Stefan,
some girls don't need my persuasion.
Some girls just can't resist
my good looks...
...my style and my charm...
...and my unflinching ability
to listen to Taylor Swift.
(GRUNTS)
This is John Varvatos, dude.
Dick move.
I can confirm that a puma attacked
a hunter and was subsequently killed.
The hunter is in stable condition.
STEFAN : The real animal is still out there,
waiting for me...
...challenging me to fight back,
to stop him.
But how do I stop a monster
without becoming one myself?
To repeat, the animal terrorizing
Mystic Falls has been caught.
JENNA :
Scum ball.
Scum bucket.
Who are you talking to?
Him.
Including tomorrow night's...
ELENA : The news guy?
- Also known as Logan "Scum" Fell.
Did your mom tell you
why I moved away from Mystic Falls?
Oh, no way.
You and him?
Logan Fell...
He's cute.
He is not cute.
There's nothing cute about him.
- What are you doing with that?
- I got it from the safe deposit box.
Mom told Mrs. Lockwood
she would loan it...
...to the Founder's Council
for their heritage display.
Is that Grandma Beth's wedding ring?
Originally, it was Great-Great-Grandma
Mary's wedding ring.
How much do you think this stuff
is worth, like, on eBay?
You're not gonna find out.
That stuff is Mom and Dad's.
You can't give it away.
I'm not giving it away.
It's called a loan, Jeremy.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
- Sorry.
- Maybe we should press pause.
Yeah, you're probably right.
That was getting a bit...
- Yeah.
How do you look in a suit?
- I can pull one off.
- How about tomorrow night?
Will you be my date
to the Founder's Party?
- They still do that?
- Have you been before?
No, the Salvatores
don't get invited anymore.
Well, this year,
there's this heritage project...
...that meant a lot to my mom.
She was really involved
in the Founder's Council...
...and it was her favorite party.
I know it sounds really boring but...
I would be honored to accompany you,
Miss Gilbert.
The pleasure is all mine, Mr. Salvatore.
No yellow. Jaundice. Go for the blue.
- I don't like the blue.
- Well, I do.
- And if I'm gonna be your date...
- You cannot be my date.
My mother is going to be there
and she's a very proud gun owner.
I went through a lot to make sure
this party wasn't canceled.
It's very important I be there.
Please take me.
You should come
to the Founder's Party with me.
Not if you're wearing that dress.
What's so special about this Bella girl?
Edward's so whipped.
You gotta read the first book first.
It won't make sense if you don't.
- I miss Anne Rice. She was so on it.
- How come you don't sparkle?
I live in the real world
where vampires burn in the sun.
Yeah, but you go in the sun.
I have a ring. Protects me. Long story.
Will these bites
turn me into a vampire?
It's more complicated than that.
You have to feed on my blood,
then die, then feed on a human.
It's a whole ordeal.
This book, by the way, has it all wrong.
(CAROLINE CHUCKLES)
You can be very sweet
when you wanna be.
Yes, I can be sweet.
- Are you gonna kill me?
- Mm-hm.
- But not yet.
- Why not?
Because there's something
I need you to do for me.
Anything.
How good are you
at getting this nose...
...where it doesn't belong?
- Oh, I'm excellent.
Mmm.
LOCKWOOD :
So, what happens with the season?
One big forfeit?
Are they looking for a new coach?
I doubt anybody's thinking about that.
Charles, Founder's Party, focus.
VICKl :
How are we all doing over here?
We're doing great, sweetheart.
- Anything else I can get you?
- We're fine, thanks.
LOCKWOOD :
Just the check, honey.
- Here you go, Mayor Lockwood.
LOCKWOOD : Thanks.
You're taking Damon
to the Founder's Party? What about me?
- Go with Elena.
- She's asking Stefan.
- Okay, go by yourself.
- Gee, thanks.
What about your mom?
Is she okay with you bringing Damon?
And I'm supposed to care why?
He's Older, Sexy, Danger Guy.
Older, Sexy, Danger Guy?
Is that an official witch Twitter tweet?
No more witch jokes, okay?
That Mr. Tanner prediction thing
has me freaked.
Okay.
And Damon's not dangerous.
You know, he just has a lot of issues
with his brother.
You know, like major,
deep-rooted drama.
Like?
I'm not really supposed
to say anything.
Caroline Forbes, when have you ever
kept a secret in your life?
Okay. But you can't tell Elena.
No.
So, what you gonna buy me?
Some class.
Oh, your parents are gone.
I guess we can be close now.
TYLER :
Well, what the hell does that mean?
- You treat me like trash. I'm sick of it.
- I don't think you're trash.
Really? Then who are you taking
to the Founder's Party?
Vicki Donovan...
...do you want me to ask you
to the Founder's Party?
No. It'll be stupid and lame.
TYLER :
True.
But it'll be less stupid and lame
if you're there.
You realize you had to ask him
to ask you, right?
You figure if you dress
like a respectable lady...
...he'll finally treat you like one?
Screw you, Jeremy.
You know you're making wrong choice,
yet you make it anyway.
It's sad.
- Didn't know you were here.
- Going through Stefan's homework.
Boy, this country has dumbed down
in the last hundred years.
Why he wants to go to high school
is beyond me.
In the '70s, he went lvy League.
Harvard, I understood.
Actually, no. I didn't get that either.
Go ahead, purge.
Get it out. What's on your mind?
Why are you here, Damon?
To spend time with you, Zach.
Family's important.
I know you.
You always have a motive.
So tell me, what is it this time?
You are in no position to question me.
I didn't mean to upset you.
This is not upset, Zach.
STEFAN :
What's going on?
Having a family moment, Stefan.
Spending some quality time.
(ZACH PANTS)
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not and neither are you.
How many have to die
before you see that?
- I see it, all right.
- Then why aren't you doing anything?
I can't, Zach.
I can't.
It would take human blood.
It's the only way that I could stop him
and I can't do that.
Vervain could weaken him
if he ingested it.
It would help get you the upper hand.
Vervain hasn't grown here since 1865.
Damon saw to that.
The little I had, I gave to Elena.
What?
STEFAN :
You've been growing it.
It's just something that's been
passed down through the generations.
Blood only runs so deep
when you're related to vampires.
Damon would kill me
if he knew that I had it.
But you're telling me.
Why?
Because I trust you.
And you're gonna need it
if you wanna get rid of him.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I'm here for my mom.
- Supposed to pick up a box...
ELENA : It's right here.
Please be careful.
- Yeah, be careful with it, dick.
ELENA : Hey.
Not now, okay, guys? Please?
- I'm fine. He's being a punk.
- I got your punk.
Look, Tyler, maybe you should go.
Tell your mom that I'll see her tonight.
Hey, would it make a difference
if I told you I actually like Vicki?
Not even if you meant it.
Delicate Flower versus Naughty Vixen.
Tough call. Can we mix them?
Look at you,
getting all pretty for your date.
You seem happyish.
I am-ish.
Tonight's gonna be a good night.
Don't let that stop you from telling me
whatever it is you wanted to tell me.
What if I tell you in the morning?
I don't want to ruin the night.
Bonnie, out with it.
Okay, but it has to go in the vault
because Caroline will kill me...
...if it gets back to Damon
that she squealed.
Apparently, Stefan has
a very interesting back story.
Uh-huh.
Do you know what happened
with Katherine?
I know that they both dated her
and that's why they have issues.
Yeah, they both dated her,
only she chose Damon.
And that drove Stefan mad.
So he did horrible things to try
and break them up.
He manipulated Katherine.
He filled her head with all these lies
until it worked...
...and she turned against Damon.
Sounds like one person's side
of the story, meaning Damon's.
I just wanted you to know.
Anyway, his past relationships
are none of my business.
Unless he's a calculating,
manipulative liar.
That's your business.
- Stefan is none of those things.
- Yeah? How do you know?
They still wear ties at this thing?
- Why are you even going?
- It's fitting. We were at the first one.
It's better if we don't draw attention
to ourselves.
So you should stay here.
I'll see to it Elena has a good time.
My goodness, I've driven you to drink.
Can't seem to rid myself of you.
What else am I supposed to do,
besides go about living my life?
"Go about living my life."
See, therein lies your eternal struggle.
You're dead, dude. Get over it.
What do you think?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Hi, Ms. Lockwood.
What do you mean? It is?
Are you sure? Because I saw it.
Let me check. Mm-hm.
I will find it and bring it.
Okay. Bye.
What's wrong?
Ahh! God, what now?
The pocket watch. Where is it?
What watch?
The one you stole from Mom's box.
Look, Mrs. Lockwood just called me
freaking out.
It was on the list, Jeremy.
She can't find it and thinks she lost it.
And maybe she did.
Maybe Tyler took it.
Don't even play that card. You took it.
Am I gonna find it on eBay?
Is that how you pay for your pot?
Screw you.
- I would never sell this, okay?
- Then why did you take it?
Because it's supposed to be mine.
Dad said it goes to the firstborn son.
His father gave it to him and now what?
- And he was gonna give it to you.
- Yeah.
Look, Jeremy, it's still yours, okay?
Mom promised Mrs. Lockwood.
What do you want me to do?
Just take it and get out.
DAMON :
It's cool not growing old.
I like being the eternal stud.
Yes, being a 150-year-old teenager
has been the height of my happiness.
You cracked a funny, Stefan.
I should have a drink and celebrate.
1864. You and Katherine
were the perfect couple.
It was hell watching you
dance with her.
My happiness was short-lived,
as you well know.
I remember.
I left the party early,
I was waiting for her.
That night you dropped her off,
I was waiting inside.
You were such a gentleman,
gave her a kiss on the cheek.
When what she really wanted was...
Oh, well. Here's to history
repeating itself, huh?
I admire your effort, Stefan.
Pouring yourself a drink
then spiking the bottle with vervain.
I'm not some drunk sorority chick.
You can't roofie me.
But I can't help but feel a little used.
I thought we were having a moment.
I have to go to the party angry.
Who knows what I'll do?
MAN 1 : I think you'll enjoy it very much.
WOMAN 1 : Oh, really?
CAROL : Welcome.
LOCKWOOD : Great to see you, thank you.
WOMAN 2 : Hello, Mayor Lockwood.
CAROL : Hi. Nice to see you.
- Hi.
LOCKWOOD : Hi. Nice to see you.
MAN 2 : Hi, sir.
LOCKWOOD : Thank you so much for coming.
MAN 2 : Mrs. Lockwood.
LOCKWOOD : Have a great time.
- Bar's open.
MAN 3 : Mayor Lockwood.
You look sharp. It's nice.
WOMAN 3 : Mrs. Lockwood.
- Hi.
- Nice to see you.
TYLER : Hey.
LOCKWOOD :
Come on in.
- Let's go this way.
- Why?
Line's too long.
We can go around back.
Come on, party's in the back.
LOCKWOOD : Hey, thanks for coming.
Look at you, great.
That was his favorite Scotch.
I thought it would work.
I wasn't counting on it.
You knew it would fail.
Did what I wanted.
Lowered his guard.
He won't expect me
to try again so soon.
ZACH :
I doubled what I put in the Scotch.
(SIGHS)
MAN 1 : Hi, how are you?
WOMAN 1 :> We're gonna go in.
(CHATTERING)
Caroline. You look smashing.
Thank you, Mrs. Lockwood.
This is my boyfriend, Damon.
Oh, well, come on in.
Lovely to meet you.
I've been looking forward to this party.
Well, enjoy.
Let's get a drink.
Wait here.
Really, you couldn't even change
out of the badge for this?
I'm working, honey.
Who's the date
you just tried to sneak past me?
Just some guy.
A little old for you, don't you think?
Because otherwise you'd approve.
I doubt that.
- Hi, Mayor Lockwood.
- Hey, come on in.
- Thank you.
LOCKWOOD : Have fun.
Where's your dad?
- Memphis.
- Good.
With Stephen.
Your parents?
There's a lot of history here.
LOGAN :
Jenna.
JENNA :
Hello, Logan.
It's good to see you.
I thought I might see you here.
- You knew it.
- I dreaded.
But were secretly hoping.
And now that I have...
Whoa, hey, not so fast. I know you.
You have a lot more insults in you.
I can tell.
- Your hairline's receding.
- It's not.
- Wanna have lunch?
- Nope.
- You haven't changed a bit.
- Oh, yes, I have.
I'm meaner now.
ELENA : "The founding families
of Mystic Falls...
...welcomes you to the inaugural
Founder's Council Celebration."
Wow, look,
it's the original guest registry.
Look at all these familiar names:
Sheriff William Forbes,
Mayor Benjamin Lockwood.
Is that Damon Salvatore?
And Stefan Salvatore?
DAMON :
The original Salvatore brothers.
Our ancestors. Tragic story, actually.
We don't need to bore them
with stories of the past.
It's not boring, Stefan.
I'd love to hear more about your family.
Well, I'm bored. I wanna dance.
- And Damon won't dance with me.
- Mm-mm.
Could I just borrow your date?
Oh, uh...
- I don't really dance.
- He does. You should see him.
Waltz, the jitterbug, the moonwalk.
He does it all.
You wouldn't mind, would you, Elena?
It's up to Stefan.
Well, sorry, but I'm not gonna take no
for an answer.
DAMON :
I wanna apologize to you...
...for being such a world-class jerk
the other night when I tried to kiss you.
There's no excuse.
My therapist says I'm acting out,
trying to punish Stefan.
- For what?
- I don't wanna bring it up.
Let's just say that the men
in the Salvatore family...
...have been cursed
with sibling rivalry.
And it all started
with the original Salvatore brothers.
Damon told you to ask me to dance,
didn't he?
And why would he do that?
MAN :
Champagne, sir?
STEFAN :
Would you like one?
Thank you.
Just tell me if you see my mom.
The Salvatore name was practically
royalty in this town until the war.
- There was a battle here...
- The Battle of Willow Creek.
- Right.
- I know, we talked about it in class.
Confederate soldiers fired on a church
with civilians inside.
What the history books left out...
...was the people that were killed,
they weren't there by accident.
They were believed
to be union sympathizers.
So some of the founders
on the confederacy side back then...
...wanted them rounded up
and burned alive.
Stefan and Damon had someone
they loved very much in that church.
And when they went to rescue them,
they were shot.
Murdered in cold blood.
Who was in the church
that they wanted to save?
A woman, I guess.
Doesn't it always come down
to the love of a woman?
I'm sorry that you and Stefan
have this thing between you...
...but I can't get
in the middle of it, Damon.
I just...
I hope you two can work it out.
I hope so too.
So you wanna dance?
Me dancing? Not pretty.
Maybe you could show me around.
I mean, this place is amazing.
Yeah, if you like living in a museum.
Maybe I should just strip naked
and give Pastor Bill a lap dance.
That's why we're hiding
in a corner all night, isn't it?
You're scared of how I'm gonna act,
afraid of what your parents...
...are gonna think about your date?
I don't care about what they think.
Great. Let's go say hi.
Knock it off, Vick.
Or we could just
sneak up to your bedroom.
As long as nobody sees us, right?
- Vicki, I swear...
- What's the matter, Ty?
You scared to stand up to your mommy?
It's pathetic.
- Look, let go.
- Tyler.
We didn't get a chance
to say hello earlier.
It's Vicki, right? Matt's sister.
Yes, ma'am.
You'll have to forgive
my son's rudeness.
He gets it from his father.
Well, that's okay, Mrs. Lockwood.
Tyler and I
were just saying good night.
That's what you get
when you bring the trash into the party.
What'd we miss?
We were just chatting.
Drink, Damon?
No, thanks, I'll pass.
Stefan, do you have
another dance in you?
Absolutely.
They look so cute together.
Don't talk, please.
Don't shoot. Only need to refill.
- Shooting implies caring.
- Feigned indifference. I like it.
I'm over the banter, Logan.
I'd really rather you just left me alone.
I'm sorry, Jenna.
About your sister.
Thank you.
I came to the funeral.
I know. I saw you.
I didn't wanna push my way in,
but I wanted to be there for you.
And when I heard you were staying
in Mystic Falls, I thought maybe...
Well, maybe I could have
a second chance to make things right.
Her name was Monica, wasn't it?
I hope Damon
didn't drive you too crazy.
No, actually,
he was on good behavior.
He even apologized and explained
why he is the way he is.
That it all goes back to Katherine.
Hmm.
So tell me about her. What happened?
Not something I like to talk about.
I get that. I do.
I just want you to know that you can.
I mean, I burden you
with all of my drama...
...and I want you to do the same.
Um...
Thank you.
The truth is, Stefan, I don't really know
that much about you...
...and I'd really love it
if you would open up to me.
Damon said something, didn't he?
He likes to play games
and cause trouble, Elena.
This isn't about Damon,
it's about me trying to get to know you.
Look, you're the mystery guy
and I like that...
...but with mystery comes secrets,
and this thing with Katherine...
Let it go.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Say something about yourself.
Anything.
Otherwise, I'm left with nothing
but what other people tell me.
Don't you see
what Damon has done here?
He's trying to get you
to turn against me.
Well, then I guess it's working.
BONNIE :
This is my fault. I planted doubt.
- I'm a doubt-planter.
- It's not your fault.
I feel terrible.
I said I wouldn't get in the middle of it
and that's exactly what I did.
I got all snotty.
CAROL :
Elena, honey, there you are.
I notice the watch
still isn't in the collection.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Lockwood.
I couldn't find it.
I guess, it's still packed up
in my parents' stuff somewhere.
I see.
Please let me know if you do find it.
Okay.
CAROLINE :
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Your brother barely danced with me
for five minutes.
Okay, just a minute. Stand right there.
Uh... You're not supposed to touch.
What is that?
Very important crystal.
Well, how did you know
that it was there?
DAMON : Because I put it there.
- When?
A long time ago.
Tonight, I'm taking it back,
thanks to you.
Well, what's it for?
- Never you mind.
- You can't just steal it.
- It's not stealing if it's mine. Come on.
- Well...
Vodka tonic.
Okay, I know that this is probably
gonna be strike three...
...but I hope you can see it
for what it is.
- And what is it?
- Persistence.
Groveling, commitment.
Take your pick.
I fled town because of you. Fled.
I was young and stupid,
and then things changed.
Life got real.
You'd know that better than anyone.
Hypothetically speaking, if allowed,
how would you make things right?
Well, more groveling, of course.
A recap of the past few years
spent soul searching.
Cheese fries.
Obvious.
I know my audience.
Yes to lunch. Call me.
CAROL :
Look around. What's missing?
Flames, the candles.
Why aren't they lit?
There's matches in the kitchen.
Bitch.
- Hey.
So how are things with Stefan?
Great. Just great.
Really?
Well, my radar must be off...
...because I was getting all sorts
of other vibes.
What is that?
Don't.
- Caroline, what happened?
- Nothing, okay?
That is not nothing.
- Did somebody hurt you?
- No, okay, it...
Nothing, it just...
My mom would kill me.
- Did Damon hurt you?
- No.
Of course not.
Just leave me alone,
okay, Elena? God.
There is something
seriously wrong with you.
You stay away from Caroline
or I will go to her mother, the sheriff.
You got it? Stay away from her.
I'm sorry.
I take it all back.
- You're right about Damon.
- What did he do?
There are bruises
all over Caroline's body.
Bite marks. And he has her all confused
and messed up in the head.
You don't look surprised.
I'm handling it.
Handling it? Stefan, you should be
having him arrested.
Elena, please, l...
- I don't expect you to understand.
- I don't understand anything, Stefan.
So why don't you
just clear it up for me?
Look, there are things
that you don't know, okay?
Things that I want to tell you,
but I can't.
And I may never be able to.
And I just need you to trust me.
Trust is earned.
I can't just magically hand it over.
I'm so sorry. I have to go.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
You look amazing.
What are you doing here?
I was thinking maybe I could
make one more wrong choice today.
I still have 17 minutes.
Don't.
She took it off
and I got flustered, okay?
I didn't know what to say.
But I swear, I did not tell her.
I just told her
that you didn't mean to hurt me.
You make me crazy, you know that?
It's okay. I forgive you.
- I swear I didn't say...
- No, don't... Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay.
Unfortunately, I am so over you now.
What the hell?
I knew I couldn't spike your drink.
So I spiked hers.
(GRUNTING)
ELENA :
Caroline?
Oh, there you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Caroline, what happened?
I'm fine.
No, you're shaking. Caroline, what...?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- Caroline, come here, come here.
(SOBBING)
STEFAN :
I did what I had to do to protect Elena.
To protect everyone.
Yes, Damon, the headline reads:
"Deadly beast captured.
All is well in Mystic Falls."
Thank you for staying so late.
Did you get the Gilbert watch?
She claims it's packed away
in her parents' things.
I can get it.
Good, we're gonna need it.
- Are you sure?
- Five bodies all drained of blood.
I'm certain.
LOGAN :They've come back.