NARRATOR :
Previously on The Vampire Diaries:
STEFAN :
For over a century, I've lived in secret.
Until now. I know the risk.
But I have to know her.
DAMON :
Elena, she's a dead ringer for Katherine.
STEFAN : I want you all to myself.
KATHERINE : Just as he wants me.
I'm the one
who gets to make all rules.
- Get the sheriff. We have a vampire.
- Don't take her.
- You'll be killed.
- Then let me be killed.
- Damon, we'll get her back.
- Don't you think you've done enough?
DAMON :
Stefan's still drinking human blood.
(AMBER SCREAMS)
- Stefan.
DAMON : Stefan.
The blood brings out
what's inside of me.
I'm not gonna give up on you.
I believe in you.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN :
Be careful.
JONATHAN :
Get him in.
We have to get to church.
They're waiting.
Circle around that way.
I'll distract them. Go.
Over here. There's another one.
Quick. Help me.
Arm yourselves.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
We don't have long.
Katherine. Katherine.
We're gonna get you out of here.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Damon, hurry. Hurry.
(GUNSHOT)
No. No.
(GASPING)
(SIGHS)
STEFAN :
Damon.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
SOLDIER : Think we got one, sir.
I think we got one.
MAN :
Shoot him! Over here!
(GRUNTS)
We got him.
(GASPING)
Stefan. Stefan.
ELENA :
Stefan.
KATHERINE : I love you, Stefan.
ELENA : It's so hard to see him locked up
like this.
- You're the one who locked him up.
- You helped.
DAMON : I couldn't have him
chewing on people...
...while the town was looking
for vampires, could I?
Nothing to do with you
caring about him.
Your thing, not mine.
EMILY : Katherine had me make that for you
weeks ago.
- Where am I?
- The quarry, just north of town.
My brother and I brought you here
last night.
- We found you dead in the woods.
- Where's Damon?
- Am l...? Am I a...?
- Not yet. You're in transition.
But how? I...
- You had Katherine's blood in your system when you died.
- No. I never...
She's been compelling you to drink it
for weeks, Stefan.
- And Damon?
- No compulsion was necessary.
He drank from her willingly.
DAMON : I woke up last night.
I didn't know where I was.
I went to the church.
And I watched them drag her inside.
Then they set fire to it.
And the whole church
went up into flames.
They killed her, Stefan.
She's gone.
(SIGHS)
- Did you figure out what that is?
- Nope. Whatever it is, it doesn't work.
Pearl didn't say anything else?
DAMON : Thought she was stealing his vampire
compass, but it was a pocket watch.
That Johnathan Gilbert
was a crazy scientist.
- Have you spoken to your uncle lately?
- I've been avoiding him, actually.
- That, and I've been here most nights.
- So you'll be here again tonight?
- Is that a problem?
- Yes. You're a complete nuisance.
ELENA : I'll see you later.
- Okay, man.
- See you in a bit.
ANNA : Surprise.
- Heh.
- What are you doing here?
- Picking up this.
A class schedule?
Starting tomorrow,
I'm officially a student here.
- Wait, you're kidding me, right?
- No, I finally beat my mom down.
But why would you wanna go
to high school? It blows.
Do I really need to answer that?
You'd suffer through all this
just to hang out with me?
Yeah. I would.
- That's, um...
- Stupid?
Pathetic? Old lurky me?
It's awesome.
DAMON : Brought you something to eat,
100 percent Stefan-diet approved.
You know what'll happen if you don't
eat, you'll get all rotting and crusty.
- I'm not hungry.
- Pfff. Of course you are.
We're eternally hungry. Take it.
The human blood
should be gone now.
Wanna explain why you're still in here
feeling sorry for yourself?
Come on. Drink up.
Fine. Starve. What do I care?
(PHONE RINGS)
- Hello?
ALARIC :  It's Alaric Saltzman.
- How did you get this number?
- It's a mystery.
Listen, I've been doing some digging
on Elena's uncle. You interested?
- What kind of digging?
- An old friend from Duke...
...who studied criminology there.
Let's just say
he's become a very proficient digger.
Well, did he find anything?
Well, I had him run a track
on John's cell records.
Getting a call from a number.
The same number that Elena dialed
to get Isobel.
- And then the number was disconnected.
- Isobel knows John. We knew that.
He started getting calls
from a new number.
And I had my friend run a geo-track.
Got the address.
It's an apartment in Grove Hill.
- Isobel's in Grove Hill?
- I don't know.
- We could take a look, see what we find.
- Perfect. Give me the address.
So you can go without me?
No, I don't think so.
- I'm not going with you. Tried to kill me.
- You did kill me.
(CALL WAITING BEEPS)
Hold on. What?
ELENA : I'm grabbing some clothes,
then I'll be right over. How's Stefan?
Extra broody. Hold on.
- You drive. Pick me up in an hour.
- Done.
(PHONE BEEPS)
He won't eat anything.
He has to eat.
What's his favorite kind of, um?
- His favorite kind of what?
- Type of animal blood that he prefers?
- Ew. Gross.
- Your joking doesn't help.
Helps me. Now, hurry up.
I can't babysit all night.
I have things to do.
- I would say drop dead, but...
- Ha, ha, ha.
Stefan likes puppy blood.
Little golden retriever puppies,
cute, floppy ears.
That's his favorite.
(SCOFFING)
- Sorry.
- Uncle John.
I didn't see you there.
JOHN : I thought we could talk.
We haven't had a chance to catch up.
- I'm actually just heading out, so...
- Well, it won't take long.
ELENA : What did you wanna talk about?
I know you know.
- Know what?
- It's really silly to keep pretending.
What do you think
your mother would say...
...if she knew
you were dating a vampire?
Which mother?
STEFAN : I bet Johnathan Gilbert
has told Father by now.
Wonder how he took the news
that we're dead.
As if he cares. He betrayed us.
He thought he was protecting us, Damon.
He thought he was protecting this town.
DAMON : God, the sun hurts my eyes.
It's part of it.
The muscle aches, the sick feeling.
Emily says it's our bodies pushing us
to feed, to complete the transition.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Is that your choice then?
- To die instead?
- Isn't it yours?
DAMON : This was all to be with Katherine.
But she's gone.
I want it over.
ELENA : How you feeling?
Damon says you need to drink that.
You need it, Stefan.
- Can't survive without it.
- I don't wanna survive.
What?
- No, don't say that.
- I'm sorry, Elena.
No more.
After what I've done, it has to end.
I just want it over.
DAMON : He's being dramatic.
He's not gonna starve himself.
Why would he say that?
He feels bad about hurting that girl.
It's typical Stefan martyr stuff.
- It will pass.
- Will it?
Because he seemed to be
in a lot of pain.
That will pass, once he eats.
- I didn't mean physical pain.
- I know what you meant.
Are you okay if I have to run out?
I have an errand with the teacher.
The teacher? Alaric?
- Are you two friends now?
- I don't have any friends, Elena.
Right.
You should... You should stay up here.
- Shouldn't be down there by yourself.
- I'll be fine.
You know...
...you're very trusting of him,
given the circumstances.
ELENA :
So are you.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be leaving.
I won't be long.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
PEARL : Hello, Mr. Gilbert.
JOHN : Pearl. What a pleasure.
I must admit,
I'm surprised that you came.
Jenna tells me you wanted to discuss
the sale of the building in person.
Revealing yourself to me,
it took a risk.
I'm not stupid, Mr. Gilbert.
You knew who I was
when you requested the meeting.
Damon tells me you're looking for
the device I took from Johnathan.
I'm sure you realize I have no intention
of giving it to you.
That's why I wanted to meet you.
I'm planning on changing your mind.
Really? How so?
With my Gilbert charm.
I know that you have a weakness
for it.
May I buy you a drink?
JEREMY : Your mother was in love
with Johnathan Gilbert.
- And he betrayed her?
- Yup.
And now my Uncle John
wants this invention-device thing...
...that she gave to Damon.
That's pretty much it.
John mentioned more Gilbert journals.
I bet that's how he knows everything.
Do we have to talk about this all night?
I've told you everything.
I probably shouldn't have.
That could get us both in a lot of trouble.
(ANNA GIGGLES)
I'm not gonna say anything.
Your Uncle John wants us dead.
Oh, you don't know that.
Yes, I do.
- He's a hater, Jeremy.
- Well, I'm not.
No.
You're something else entirely.
Oh, yeah? What would that be?
My weakness.
- I don't want Jenna to walk in on us.
- Jenna's in the kitchen.
- She just opened the refrigerator.
- Wait. You can hear that?
That is so cool.
ALARIC : This is the one here. The records show
this was paid three months in advance.
DAMON : This is where it gets tricky.
I may or may not be able to get in.
ALARIC : How does that work?
You always have to be invited in?
DAMON : By the owner
or the person of entitlement.
Short-term rentals and hotels
are a bit of a gray area.
You gotta play it by ear.
(ALARIC SCOFFS)
- Could we not kill anyone tonight?
- Brought me along for my company?
It doesn't look like anyone's home.
Yeah. I'm good.
No permanent resident, apparently.
Uh, Ric, we have company.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Boys, boys, boys, that's enough.
I know you.
- Damon?
- Your name is Henry.
- You were in the tomb.
- Yes, sir.
What are you doing here?
GIUSEPPE :
May I offer you a drink, Mr. Gilbert?
JOHNATHAN :
Thank you, Mr. Salvatore.
This won't take much longer.
I wanna make sure
the archives are accurate.
Be sure you document
the loss of civilian life in the church.
They were hardly civilians,
Mr. Salvatore.
GIUSEPPE : As far as anyone
needs to know, they were.
As record keeper for council, what you
write will be passed through generations.
Details should be kept
between you and me.
- For example?
- My sons.
They'll be remembered as innocent
victims of the battle of Willow Creek...
...not for their shame.
Certainly, Mr. Salvatore.
STEFAN : You know,
Damon hasn't fed me vervain in a while.
I could be at those bars in a flash,
and you'd be dead.
ELENA :
Yeah, you could...
...but you won't.
- Please just go away.
I don't want you here.
- What are you doing? Get out of here.
- No.
- You're taking a risk. I could hurt you.
- Then I'm stupid.
You need to drink this.
- Elena, get out of here or you'll regret it.
- Drink.
I said get out!
No.
HENRY : So how do you know John Gilbert?
DAMON : Well, I've known him for years.
A good friend. How do you know him?
I met him right after I got out
of the tomb. He's been helping me out.
ALARIC : Helping you out how?
HENRY : Adapting.
It's a whole new world.
Cars, computers, match. Com.
There's so much to learn.
He helped me get this place.
ALARIC : So do you live here alone,
or is there someone else here?
DAMON : That's my friend's very
passive-aggressive way of asking...
...do you know a woman
named Isobel?
Uh, no. No, I don't know an Isobel.
I know John.
He's my only real friend.
He showed me the ropes.
How to use a microwave,
separate my whites.
- What else do you do?
- Keep an eye on things. With the others.
- The others?
- From the tomb.
Pissed at the founding families
for trying to burn them.
I'm cool, but those tomb boys,
they want revenge.
- What does John want with them?
- He's just keeping an eye on them.
- Make sure they stay out of trouble.
- Well, that's John.
He's such a do-gooder.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
That's John now.
- Hey, let me talk to him.
- All right. Yeah.
- Are you gonna answer that?
- Am I gonna answer that?
What's going on?
(HISSES)
(GRUNTING)
"Let's not kill anyone tonight."
Your words. Just pointing that out.
- My apologies.
- No apologies necessary.
PEARL : So tell me, Mr. Gilbert,
why should I let you have the device?
JOHN : Because I can help you.
I'm connected around here.
Town council's eating out of my hand.
They do whatever I say.
I know you just wanna live your life
with a picket fence, I can help you.
The device doesn't work.
Why would you want it?
It's a family heirloom.
Call me sentimental.
Johnathan was ahead of his time.
JOHN : I read his journals.
They're very extensive.
He actually wrote about you.
You were his one regret.
He loved you and he hated himself
for what he did to you.
- You're lying.
- No.
On his last days,
he wrote how sorry he was.
You were the only woman
he ever loved.
(LAUGHING)
Good God. You vampires,
you're so emotional.
Johnathan Gilbert hated you.
His only regret was he didn't drive
a stake through your heart himself.
- I gave it to Damon.
- What?
I gave your device to Damon.
Why don't you ask him for it yourself?
He'd be delighted to give it to you.
And then, Mr. Gilbert,
may you rot in hell.
ELENA : Talk to me, Stefan.
Why are you doing this?
I'm making the decision
I should have made years ago.
What are you talking about?
You have to feed to complete
the transition.
I know that.
It was a choice I shouldn't have made.
Dear God.
Even in our death,
you only feel shame?
- You're one of them now.
- No.
Father, I came to say goodbye.
I watched you die.
You were there when we were shot?
I pulled the trigger myself.
You killed your own sons?
You were dead to me the moment
you sided with the vampires.
I thank God your mother isn't alive
to see the disgrace.
STEFAN : I haven't turned yet. I don't want to.
I'm going to let myself die, Father.
Yes, you are.
(GRUNTS)
No. Oh, God, Father. I didn't mean to.
- Get away from me.
- No, let me help you. Please.
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, God. What's happening to me?
How can you even look at me
right now?
ELENA : You need to be able talk
about these things, Stefan.
I need to hear them.
Come upstairs.
We can talk about it more and we'll
keep talking as long as you need.
STEFAN : You're so sure I'm ready.
ELENA : And when you feel the same way...
...l'll be upstairs.
- Find anything yet?
ALARIC :  No, I looked everywhere.
The places is... The place is clean.
Well, I found this behind the blood,
in the fridge.
Oh, man, this was a real dead-end.
I wouldn't beat myself over it, man.
What'd you think you were gonna find,
huh?
Isobel with a cigar and slippers?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, man. I...
I gotta stop this. I can't...
I can't keep searching for her.
Really? After only two years?
That's actually...
...moderately healthy.
What are you going on?
A hundred and forty-six.
I figured the 200-mark is probably
a good stopping point.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
ALARIC : I mean, no answer is enough.
I keep thinking I wanna know why,
when, you know, the precise moment...
...when my wife decided
life with me wasn't enough.
DAMON : She charmed me, your wife, Isobel.
She talked a good game.
She was smart.
She had this excitement in her eyes.
Should have known there was something
different about her, tie to Katherine.
- Had to be some reason I didn't kill her.
- Enough. I don't wanna hear anymore.
I don't wanna waste any more of my life
searching for answers that I don't want.
I'm through with Isobel. I...
I'm done with all of this.
Yeah.
ANNA :
Hey.
- What's the matter?
- I need you to pack your things. We're leaving.
What? No.
PEARL : I was wrong to think
that we could make a home here.
It's time for us to move on.
But I don't wanna move on.
I wanna stay.
We can't stay. There's too many people
here who know the truth.
Too much history.
So, what, you're just gonna give up,
pack us up, and move us out?
It's not safe here. You know that.
Please.
- This is about Jeremy.
- No.
It's about me finally getting
to build a life for myself.
Please, Mama.
You gave me my life back.
I am just trying to protect yours.
I can't force you.
It's your decision.
DAMON : Ugh. God. You're still here?
- Were you expecting anything else?
- No.
(SIGHS)
So how was the errand?
Futile.
Although I think I witnessed the teacher
having an existential crisis.
- Has Stefan eaten yet?
- I thought you didn't care.
Chalk it up to morbid curiosity.
ELENA : I think he's getting there.
He's got a lot of guilt
that he has to deal with.
And it doesn't help that you've spent
the last 145 years...
...punishing him for Katherine
getting caught.
- This is my fault now?
- No, it's no one's fault, Damon.
I'm just saying
you're not exactly innocent.
You've made your life's mission
to make him miserable.
DAMON :
Let me ask you a question.
In this important soul-searching and
cleansing of demons of Stefan's past...
...did you ever manage
to get the story?
- He said there was more.
- Yeah. That's an understatement.
Damon.
Tell me.
What are you doing?
Who is that?
STEFAN : I brought her for you. She's a gift.
Have a seat, please.
- What have you done, Stefan?
- Damon, I've been to see Father.
He came at me.
I didn't know my own strength.
There was blood everywhere.
He was dying
and the blood was too strong.
I needed it.
- I had to have it.
- You fed.
Yes. And it's incredible.
My body is exploding with power,
Damon.
- No.
- I can hear things from far away.
I can see through the darkness.
I can move like it's magic.
And the guilt, the pain, Damon,
I can turn it off like a switch.
Katherine was right.
It's another world out there, Damon.
DAMON : Katherine is dead, Stefan.
- There's no world without her.
- No, but you can turn that off too.
You don't have to feel pain anymore.
I don't want it.
You're weak. You'll be dead soon.
You need this.
- You'll die.
- No. I can't.
Please.
- I won't let you die.
- No. I can't.
Don't fight it.
We can do this together.
The moment Stefan had his first taste of
human blood, he was a different person.
I suppose I should thank him.
It's been a hell of a ride.
Oh, my God.
He said he wanted to die.
That's why he won't feed.
Now I understand why, but...
DAMON :
His choice.
If he's stupid enough to make it,
so be it.
Don't do that, okay?
Don't pretend like you don't care.
Where are you going?
Hey.
It's getting impossible
to sneak up on you.
Nice try, though.
Sorry I woke you.
That's okay.
You only woke me halfway.
So listen.
- I...
- That feels good.
Goodbye.
STEFAN :
How do you feel?
DAMON : Whew. You were right.
It is a whole new world.
We can explore it together.
You got what you wanted.
You and me for all eternity.
But hear this, brother.
I will make it an eternity...
...of misery for you.
Damon.
You've transitioned.
You'd have rather found me dead?
EMILY :
Katherine saved my life once.
I owed her.
That doesn't mean
I'd wish her curse on anyone.
It feels more like a gift.
- That will change.
- Why is that?
Because even in death,
your heart is pure, Stefan.
I sense that about you.
That will be your curse.
Emily, wait.
ELENA :
Stefan.
Damon told me the rest of the story.
I thought I might find you here.
STEEFAN : I should have died that night...
...just like I had chosen.
- I should have let Damon die too.
- But you didn't.
And if you die now,
it's not gonna change what happened.
Every single person that's been hurt...
...every single life that's been lost,
it's because of me.
ELENA : The night that my parents died...
...I blew off family night
so that I could go to some party.
I ended up getting stranded,
and they had to come pick me up.
That's why we ended up in the car
at Wickery Bridge.
And that's why they died.
Our actions are what set things
in motion.
But we have to live with that.
STEFAN : I made a choice, Elena.
And because of that choice,
a lot of people were hurt.
You also made a choice to stop, to reject
the person that the blood made you.
- You made a choice to be good.
- No. Please don't do that.
That's the person who jumped
in the water to save the family...
...whose car had driven off the bridge.
- Don't make this okay.
That's the person who saved my life.
- You don't understand, Elena.
- Then tell me.
It hurts me.
It hurts me, knowing what I've done,
and that pain...
...that pain is with me all the time.
And every day, I think that if I just...
If I just give myself over to the blood,
I can make that pain stop.
It would be that easy,
and every day, I fight that.
And I am so terrified that one day...
...l'm not gonna wanna fight anymore,
Elena.
The next time I hurt somebody...
...it could be you.
- There will be no next time.
- You don't know that.
- Maybe I don't.
But what I do know...
...is that you can take this...
...throw it in the quarry,
and let the sun rise.
Or you could take this ring
and put it on.
And keep fighting.
It's your choice.
Elena.
- Thank you, Harper.
- You're welcome.
Annabel should be back in a minute.
You don't have to come with us
if you don't want to.
This was never my home, Miss Pearl.
I was just a soldier who was left to die.
You saved me. I'm coming with you.
Let me help you with these.
(SQUISH)
DAMON : Little boy lost.
- I'll be upstairs, okay?
- Okay.
Good night, Damon.
- Thank you.
- No, Stefan, thank you.
You're back on Bambi blood,
I'm the badass again.
- All is right in the world.
- I mean it.
Thank you.
For helping her take care of me.
You brood too much. Everything
on this planet's not your fault.
My actions, what I do, not your fault.
I own them.
They belong to me.
You are not allowed to feel my guilt.
Do you feel guilt?
If I wanted to, it's there.
Emily waited till I turned...
...to tell me she'd been successful
protecting Katherine with her spell.
She didn't want me to know
about the tomb.
She thought
it would impact my decision.
STEFAN : She didn't want either one of us
to turn.
She said it was a curse.
Witches. Judgy little things.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't want you to know.
Because I hated you, and I still do.
I know.
But not because you forced me
to turn.
Then why?
DAMON : Because she turned you.
It was just supposed to be me,
Stefan.
Just me.
ANNA : I'm back.
(YELPS)
Mama.
(WHIMPERING)
No, please don't leave me again.
No. Please wake up.
You have to wake up. No.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Sheriff Forbes, it's John Gilbert.
Sorry to call so late.
I have an update about the vampires.
ISOBEL :
Hello, Ric.
ALARIC : Isobel.