[English subtitles are available]
The Qixi monthly exam officially started.
I'm almost done with the look.
There's only one most important thing to do.
TikTok beauty blogger Chestnut here.
Welcome to the show.
Look at me.
Isn't my look unique today?
How is our often sold-out
pearlescent powder shadow
produced?
Aren't you curious?
Today,
I'll demonstrate
the process of making it.
With such a pearlescent eyeshadow pencil,
you can have big watery eyes.
Prince Xiu.
Guard Yun.
Where are you going in a hurry?
Your Highness,
Palace Makeup Service is having a monthly exam.
We are going there to judge.
Go on.
A group of men as makeup judges?
Interesting.
Let's check it out.
Here, the contestant
uses orange-centered makeup
to accentuate the cheekbones.
Thicker lip gloss is applied
to emphasize lip makeup.
As for her,
light purple is the base color.
Eye makeup is accentuated,
making her look sparkling,
charming,
sophisticated, and chic.
My wife
works in the kitchen.
She always smells greasy and smoky.
They smell nice.
I love it.
I can't tell if a woman
wears makeup or not,
but I like this.
It lightens them.
I think Jade's red lips
look good.
If she wears this makeup,
she'll love it.
The name sounds cool, too.
It's called "the romantic makeup."
My lord,
failing to replace the medicine
is my mistake.
That maid is for sure weird.
Shall we find a chance to get rid of her?
It's okay.
The master said
to keep her for other purposes.
You messed up big time.
If anything goes wrong,
we'll blame it on that maid
and make her a scapegoat.
Let's cast our vote.
The longer you look at them, the prettier.
First place.
How did Si Yan do?
Right here.
Neither good nor bad,
but yeah, I passed.
You seem over-joyed.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I cast my vote for you.
The pearlescent eyeshadow pencil
is interesting.
You have good eyes.
Thank you very much, Your Highness.
But I wonder where Yi
and Bao went.
Based on their taste,
they must like you...
...your design the best.
Please don't tease me, Your Highness.
I'm just a nobody
in those two nobles' eyes.
Miss Min, what brings you here?
Prince Yi rarely asks me out.
I want to look my best to impress him.
My lady,
the winner is HuYing's
romantic makeup look.
I want her to do my makeup.
What's going on?
She's got masters on her back again and again.
What a showoff!
Screw the eyeshadow pencil!
You are disparaging Si Yan again.
I'll take you to Lady Cui.
You have a big heart
to speak for your love rival.
Does Si Yan appreciate you?
Hu Ying!
Get up.
Are you okay?
Si Yan,
it's my fault.
I shouldn't have misunderstood you.
Stop crying.
If you ruin your makeup,
I'll have to redo it.
Do you forgive me?
Hey, you two.
It's okay
to play sisters in front of others.
But don't do that in front of me. It's disgusting.
You always go behind my back.
You're disgusting.
If it were not for Prince Yi's support,
how could you have participated in the contest
and entered the Makeup Service?
If it were not for Prince Bao,
how would you have convinced everyone?
You were a lowly maid
who fast-tracked your way up by kissing up.
You are the least qualified
to talk about fair and square.
Perhaps you've done many shameful deeds
behind the scenes.
Who knows what you did in exchange of
the eyeshadow pencil?
How dare you slap me?
Excuse me.
You deserve a beating.
Why don't you look at yourself
instead of staring at others all day?
Do you think no one knows
you bribed Director Hua?
I... I...
You what?
I haven't forgotten what you did to me last time.
How dare you come on at me again?
I guess I've been too nice for too long.
I am getting a bit rusty at slapping.
Bring it on.
Si Yan,
murder is punishable by death.
Help!
Stop screaming.
The well is not very deep at all.
Don't worry.
Someone will come for you in two hours.
Before that happens,
think about what you did.
Si Yan!
Let's leave.
Help me!
Help me out!
Si Yan,
pull me up.
How much is it?
What's going on?
Where's she?
Let's check inside.
Let's go.
The setting in the game is rigid indeed.
NPC characters
can't tell if a female is disguised as a male or not.
It seems that
I don't need to worry about exposing my identity.
Your Highness,
I've arranged everything.
If it goes well,
I'll reward you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You little brat,
I'll beat you to death today.
Get lost and go
as far as you can.
I'll kill you.
I must beat you to death today.
Mom...
I am not your mom.
Your mom died long ago.
Over the years,
and for the sake of the old master,
I've provided you with food and shelter.
But now that
the old master died,
I don't have food to spare for you.
Get lost.
Leave now.
Are you not going?
Today, I'll...
I'll beat you to death.
Stop it.
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
Come.
Who I am
is not important,
but...
Alright, alright.
Stop making a scene.
Let's go home.
May I treat you to a drink?
What do you say?
After you.
You first.
My girls,
tonight
is the night!
Once you claim the title in the Oiran election,
prosperity and wealth await.
Yes, Ma'am.
Who is she?
Why did she get it?
Miss,
you look so beautiful.
Are you also here for the Oiran election?
Why?
Miss,
you haven't told me your name.
Luna.
Who is she?
She finally showed up.
Go with the plan.
Si Yan,
This is the reward for clearing
the monthly exam task in the system.
The reward is pretty good.
The gold coins I earned earlier
can finally be put to use.
Wow! There are many beautiful outfits.
Insufficient fund?
Are you kidding me?
The hard-earned money
is only enough for a dudou.
If you can't buy it,
you can rent it.
But
you need to return it by midnight.
How do I look?
Do I look nice?
The powder is thin and translucent.
The lip gloss is just right.
Overall, it looks great.
Yet,
you might want to work on the details.
As a good butler,
all you need to say is that I look nice and gorgeous.
That's it.
By the way,
why don't you wear the makeup you designed,
the grape blossoms with sparkles?
This makeup look
is not permitted on anyone else.
Yes, my lady.
Today is the first time
Brother Yi and I are going out alone.
Do you think he'll like it?
Lowly maids like us have no way
of knowing what Prince Yi likes or dislikes.
Is that so?
I've heard some gossip
through the grapevine under this roof.
Take the advice.
You should know your place
so as not to stir up more rumors
and ruin the reputation of the princes.
Yes, my lady.
That is the makeup for
heart-broken girls.
If I put in on myself,
it'll bring bad luck.
Is there anything fun to do today?
I barely take a vacation.
Let's have an outing.
Qixi is the Chinese Valentine's Day.
There are games specially arranged
like riddles and setting off sky lanterns.
Sounds great.
I haven't gone shopping for so long.
I'll go shopping with Lan Miao later
and eat as I please.
Si Yan,
are you free tonight?
Why do you ask?
Actually,
I want to tell you something.
I'll wait for you
at the Lantern Festival tonight.
Your Highness,
can it not be tonight?
I have other plans tonight.
I'll be waiting
until you come.
Shouldn't you be pleased
when someone asks you out?
Why do you look like
you're having a dilemma?
I... I am not.
I get it.
Data shows that
you have
never had a boyfriend before.
Feeling awkward is normal.
Don't be afraid.
If you need help,
I can provide you
with references anytime.
I am a beauty blogger
who has over a million fans.
I have nothing to fear.
How can I be a relationship virgin
like you said?
Your database has a glitch.
Is that so?
Miss Min, your makeup looks very unique.
It's the look I put on just for the Lantern Festival,
the grape blossoms with sparkles.
You lost, Miss Min.
It's because you are so good at it.
Brother Teng used to always say that
since you were young, you've been good at chess.
Did you let me win on purpose today?
Prince Teng overrated my skills.
He never gave undeserved praises.
Prince Teng was always thoughtful.
Perhaps...
Perhaps he was worried that I would be humiliated
by my poor chess skills.
I met him when we were young.
When we met for the first time,
we both had feelings for each other.
We both enjoyed riding horses on the grassland,
reciting poems and singing duets,
and drinking tea while incense burned.
Every time I was with Prince Teng,
he was very caring for me.
We liked each other.
It sounds like
you have a deep affection for him.
It must be very tough on you
these days.
I will find a chance to explain to my father
and call off the engagement.
No!
I mean
the marriage between the East Mansion
and the Min family is of great importance,
so we can't break it off
because of our feelings.
Recently, many incidents took place
in the East Mansion.
I don't know
if it was the Northland
or someone else.
Please be cautious, Miss Min.
Don't get involved.
I lost the person.
You may leave.
How come your maid
is not with you today?
Peach, she...
May I ask you one thing, my lady?
Why don't you use your true identity
to meet Prince Da at Qixi Festival?
You don't know anything.
Prince Da is afraid of women.
He's hard to approach
even if I use my true identity.
Needless to say that
you shouldn't put all the eggs in one basket.
With the power of the First Lady,
I am bound to marry Prince Yi
and be restricted everywhere.
As a maid,
I have more freedom.
But my lady,
if I meet Prince Yi by myself,
I'm afraid that I might give myself away.
You just need to memorize what I taught you well
and make Prince Yi fall in love with you.
Today is Qixi.
It's her first time coming to East City,
so I gave her permission to look around town.
Brother Yi,
why did you ask about her?
Was she your maid
when she was little?
When she was seven,
she came to the Min family.
She's been accompanying me ever since.
On the day of the Flower Feast,
she seemed to have arrived late.
She went back to fetch
a set of changing clothes for me.
Miss Min, have you ever suspected
that she tampered with First Lady's reins?
Brother Yi, what did you just say?
It didn't matter.
I was just asking.
Let's go.
Shall we go and enjoy the view?
May I ask
what you said to the woman
to change her mind?
I just calculated the numbers for her.
A child eats 70 lbs of rice a year.
It'll be 700-900 lbs of rice in ten years.
He will be able to work in ten years.
He'll be able to pay back in one year.
It's better to keep him as a house dog
than to drive him out and come back
like a wolf to take revenge.
If she keeps the child,
he might take care of the house.
Doing that
is like pushing the child into the fire pit.
Who is the fire pit for whom?
It's hard to say.
That child is not simple.
He has fire in his eyes.
Even if he was raised like a dog,
he would still have desires.
As long he has desires,
he won't lose himself.
Sooner or later,
he will become his own master.
Your perspective
is very insightful.
I'm inspired.
It seems that getting the Oiran's Tear is
much harder than I thought.
Look over there.
What are we doing later?
Let's eat some delicious food.
Look here.
You startled me.
Let's go over there.
What is this?
Let's go.
Take a guess and take a look.
It's yours if you guess it right.
A spider hangs from the sky.
Guess an idiom.
Seven hands and eight feet?
No.
What is it then?
Joy falls from the sky.
Are you also here to have fun?
You changed your outfit!
It's my job to retrieve the necessary information
for Miss Si Yan.
How loyal you are!
But,
but why is it "joy falls from the sky?"
What's the joy of seeing spiders?
It's said that spiders can bring joy.
So, joy falls from the sky!
It's a pun, right?
Yes, you're right.
Here is a gift for you.
Here you go.
You won it.
I'm merely solving problems for you.
It's my job,
so I can't take credits.
If I tell you to take it, take it.
Stop the nonsense.
Oh, I forgot...
I'll give you a day off today.
You are not the butler.
You are Xiao Li.
I am not "Miss."
I'm just Si Yan.
Let's shop and eat together.
What do you say?
Xiao Li?
You see that those Misses and Masters
all have
a Xiao Wang or Xiao Bao by their side.
It sounds nice.
I also thought that
your name Jack
seems very strange at this time.
Do as the locals do.
Xiao Li.
Do you like it?
The name is just a code.
Whatever floats your boat.
Si Yan,
hurry over.
Come and help me with the riddle.
What is it?
This.
Come. Take a guess and have a look.
Here it is.
Beautiful lanterns.
What word becomes shorter when you add
two letters to it?
If you add the letters "er" to the word "short,"
it will become "shorter" indeed.
The answer is "short."
Congratulations, you're right.
Bravo.
Yeah, how could you have guessed it right?
Take it.
Please help us guess one.
Yes, please.
And this one.
Okay, okay.
Not to worry.
I'll solve it one by one.
Brother Bao.
Brother Xiu!
Are you looking for
Si Yan?
How do you know?
For the Qixi Festival,
are you only giving her this?
I saw that everyone is gifting this,
so I did the same thing.
When you choose a gift for a girl,
you have to know what she likes.
I can only help you this much.
Yun Li.
This lantern is so beautiful.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
I finally got it.
I've wanted a lantern badly.
Let's go.
Miss, please don't leave yet.
Since you're so good with riddles,
do you want to participate in our ultimate final?
Ultimate final?
Right.
What do we do?
You won all his lanterns.
Now he remembers you.
I am a straight-A student,
I have a secret weapon.
I'm in.
Alright.
Here you go.
Why is it these three pictures again?
This game is trying to trick me again.
I won't choose the auspicious green clouds.
The miniature version of the man in black
doesn't seem like a good thing.
This one.
Okay.
I chose this one.
Here.
I am a helping verb that gives people ability.
What am I?
I am the only pronoun that always capitalizes.
I am a four-letter verb that owns a lot.
What am I?
I am a possessive adjective that has four letters.
What can fill a room but take up no space?
It's too hard.
I have to guess a word for each sentence.
I only figured out that the first word is "can."
Am I right?
Si Yan,
this is a hidden task,
so I can't help you.
You must know the answer
and just aren't telling me.
Then I'll check out Forever Young first.
Let's go.
Sure.
So this is the famous Forever Young makeup shop.
Let's go inside.
I hate that we get paid so little monthly.
Otherwise,
I won't bother choosing.
I'll just buy all the lip gloss.
Back then,
I could buy the shop out
without a blink.
What nonsense was that?
Though I can't afford it,
I can at least try it on.
Si Yan.
Your Highness.
I knew you'd be here.
This system
has got everything planned for me.
What is the system?
It is guessing the riddles.
I am very good at riddles.
Really?
Then can you help me with the riddles?
I am a helping verb that gives people ability.
What am I?
It's the word "can."
I am the only pronoun that always capitalizes.
What am I?
It's "I."
I am a four-letter verb that owns a lot.
What am I?
It's the word "have."
Makes sense.
I am a possessive adjective that has four letters.
What am I?
It's the word "your."
What can fill a room but take up no space?
It's love.
"Can I have your love?"
Si Yan,
there's something I want to tell you.
Could you leave us for a moment?
Is there anything you like?
I like this one.
I think that one suits you.
Si Yan,
This is... for you.
What is this?
The spider of joy.
Thank you for watching the lanterns with me.
Brother Yi!
let's go over there.
Please leave the mask on and hear me out.
I...
Just a second.
I have been searching for someone
who I can see right away
in the vast crowd
and whose voice is all I hear
in the noisy world.
When we are happy,
we embrace at will.
When we are sad,
we hold each other's hands.
Not everyone
dares to pursue a girl.
You suddenly
walked into my life,
so dazzling that I dared not to approach,
just like now.
I want to tell you...
Don't tell me the next sentence
is "I like you!"
This must be the love letter
you wrote to Little Wan.
People who don't know you
might think you are confessing to someone.
I am not an indecisive person,
but when I am with you,
my brain goes blank.
So...
So I asked
Brother Xiu to help me write this.
Si Yan,
I like you.
Brother Yi!
Who is Si Yan?