♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[Written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Something's wrong.
You said to get there as soon as possible,
so I kept going straight at full speed.
But now we're in the Magic Whales' territory!
Are you crazy?
Do you want to die?
They say
that the Magic Whale is too strong,
so the Ocean Master blinded his left eye.
He's the Magic Whale King of the Deep Sea?
Brother San, we will fight him to the death!
[Episode 165]
Let me tell you about the new fishing net I bought...
Run!
Help!
We can't win!
Wu.
Even if I die,
I will let you and the others escape!
Brother San!
Fatty, Ao.
Take them away!
Purple God Light.
San!
Go!
Just go!
Even if I die,
I'm going to waste some of your vitality!
Wu.
Don't waste your soul power
on activating Nothingness.
It's pointless now.
What's happening?
Bastard beast.
Did you forget your lesson
from twenty-thousand years ago?
Do you
want your other eye to be blind as well?
Shut up.
Disappear forever!
What?
You think that just because you finished
transforming into a dragon
and broke the ten-thousand-year limit,
you could break my dignity?
I will let you go one more time
for the sake of your cultivation.
Scram.
Who knew that bastard
would really finish transforming into a dragon.
What a pity.
My power...
It's been twenty thousand years.
I hope that my choice this time
won't be let me down.
Don't run! Stop!
We'll fight him to death!
Even if we die...
We won't be able to win!
I will let you and the others escape!
Go!
No!
Bastard beast.
Did you forget your lesson
from twenty-thousand years ago?
I'm not dead?
The Vast Sea and Universe Shield is duller now.
I can't feel its special energy anymore.
Did it...
rescue me?
Mate.
Don't save him anymore.
If the Purple Pearl Pirates find out,
there might be trouble for us.
Why don't we
take his pretty belt
and leave him run his course?
[Soul Land]
Brother.
Even though we live on Purple Pearl Island,
we're not pirates.
We can't harm human life.
If the Purple Pearl Pirates make trouble,
they can come find me.
Fine.
Whatever you want.
But
you should still be careful.
Don't let them find you.
Okay, got it.
You're awake?
Who are you?
Why am I here?
My name is Ji Xiang.
I am the only doctor on Purple Pearl Island.
I found you
passed out on the beach yesterday,
so I brought you back here.
As for what happened before that,
do you not remember?
My friends and I
were attacked by the Purple Pearl Pirates.
Even though I'm alive,
I don't know if the others still are.
Even though I don't know what happened to you,
not all pirates are bad.
Besides, good people are blessed.
I believe that your friends
are still alive too.
Maybe
what you say is true.
No matter what,
thank you for saving me.
I owe you my life.
Alright.
Get some rest first.
Who knew that
after absorbing power from the
Magic Whale King of the Deep Sea,
the Eight Spider Bone evolved again.
But I've engulfed the power too much.
It's creating a huge burden for my body.
I need to quickly finish absorbing it
and go find the others.
Even the strongest ocean soul beasts
might not be able to recover like him.
It's done.
My soul power is at level 67 now.
Help,
Doctor Ji Xiang!
Please save my brother.
What should I do?
I don't have any soul power.
I can't insert the needle deep enough
to fully seal his vessels.
Let me try.
Who are you?
Scram, don't make trouble!
If you want your friend to live,
please move aside.
Let him try.
Amazing!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Even though he has no soul power,
every needle he's inserted is fast and sharp.
Seems that silver needle
should be his martial soul.
Look.
Doctor Ji Xiang.
Thank you for saving my younger brother.
If you want to thank me,
then bring some medicine for me
when you're back next time.
Of course.
Mate.
My apologies for earlier.
I'll treat you to a drink next time.
Sure.
Thank you for earlier.
It was easy. No trouble at all.
I'm really ashamed.
They call me a magic doctor,
but I can't even seal a blood vessel.
I'm really just an incompetent doctor.
Then do you
want to learn the method I used
to seal his vessel just now?
I can't.
Your method requires soul power,
but I was born with none.
No matter what martial soul I have,
I can't increase my soul power with cultivation.
What if
I could increase your soul power?
You...
What did you say?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 165 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1536 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2494]
[Total scene: 61032]
[Total CGI: 28233]
[Total plan of action scene: 12624]
[Total scene model: nearly 571]
[Total character model: nearly 1042]
[Total props model: 13399]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,
vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise, I have much
that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolors ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Ji Xiang. How is the head
of the Purple Pearl Pirates?
She's very nice.
She often helps the poor fishing villages.
Who tied you all here?
Where is Wu?
Go to hell.
Demon Snake Ghost!