{\move(400,10,190,270,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}sub_master-HD
Previously on AMC's
"The Walking Dead"...
And on this day,
we begin to reshape this world.
[Engine revs]
♪
Y'all can live
if you surrender right now.
♪
[Explosion]
No matter what comes next,
we've won.
We've already won!
Yeah! Yeah!
[Indistinct conversations]
Let's hurry it up, fishies.
We got our pants down out here.
It's only like a dozen.
Yeah, I mean --
Huck.
Relieve Todd
at the maintenance station.
- Hey, Mara --
- Shut up.
Give me your gun.
How's that feel?
It, uh, feels --
Shut up.
Go inside. Get the coolers.
Start packing up.
[Sighs]
Hey, genius.
Sorry.
Go.
[Static crackles]
Little Roy.
Little Roy, it's Mara.
You copy?
[Static crackles]
J-Top, it's Mara.
You copy?
[Static crackles]
Todd?
♪
Todd: Yeah?
[Static crackles]
Lock the stairwell, every floor.
Why?
[Rapid gunfire]
[Indistinct shouting]
(((( o ))))
[Walkers growling]
♪
Looks like
they made themselves a moat.
[Sighs] I guess we shouldn't be
surprised, considering.
We can do this.
We did before.
[Round chambers]
Yeah.
That's what I was considering.
I wasn't here before.
Just need a clear shot.
Right, Dianne?
Just a few seconds.
So we just need
to time it right.
They see us, they fire a gun,
we're not getting in.
Don't let them fire a gun,
Dianne.
♪
Morgan, do you need us
to cover you or something?
I do not.
Hey, we're here to help.
It shouldn't just be you.
I don't die.
[Growling continues]
♪
Woman: Your majesty!
Man: Where is he?
Find the King!
♪
[Walkers growling]
[Gun cocks]
♪
Ezekiel:
The damned are upon us!
Protect the King!
Protect yourselves!
[Gunfire]
[Grunts]
♪
Anyone see where he went?
He saw us.
If he tells them we're here,
it's over before it started.
It is not, and he won't,
for we together
will find him, end him,
and fulfill the promise
of what we have begun.
[Round chambers]
Trust the King.
Outpost is due north,
through the woods.
As that's surely his course,
so shall it be ours.
If our comrades had already
arrived, they'd have been here.
Return to the staging area.
Gather the others
when they land.
And if they haven't yet,
release Shiva from her cage.
Due north.
We'll leave a trail for you.
Ensure no enemies remain
in these environs,
and be not 10 minutes behind.
Go.
- Onward!
- Whoo!
To our foe,
then to his compound,
then to certain victory.
♪
[Rapid gunfire]
Spread out!
Watch for breaches!
We keep 'em locked in, they got
bigger problems than us.
♪
I can hear the shooting.
[Static crackles]
Mara: Stay where you are.
Do not say another word.
[Gunshots]
Ugh!
Ohh!
[Bodies thud]
♪
[Whistles]
[Gunfire continues in distance]
♪
You signal
if they're already inside.
We'll be there.
Come on.
Let's find them guns.
[Rapid gunfire]
♪
Dino, we need an opening.
Find one or make one.
[Bullets ricocheting,
glass breaking]
♪
[Walkers growling]
[Fence rattling]
♪
What the hell?
Hey!
[Muted gunshots]
[Growling continues]
♪
[Groans]
Ugh!
Ohh!
♪
[Fingers snap]
[Whistles rhythmically]
♪
[Door creaks]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
[Gasps]
Ain't on this floor.
Only option is up.
High ground.
Good cover.
Yeah, I'd put them
up there, too.
Stairs.
[Door rattling]
[Rapid gunfire]
♪
They're too chickenshit
to move in on us.
We push them back!
Go!
[Gunfire continues]
♪
[Glass shatters]
We got some coming up
on my right.
Stay on them!
Don't let them through!
We pin them in,
it takes care of itself!
That's the plan!
♪
[Scattered gunfire]
Tobin, move in!
I can take them!
Cover me!
No!
Wait for Tobin!
There's no time!
[Scattered gunfire]
Go!
I'll help cover you!
♪
[Scattered gunfire]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
[Rapid gunfire]
[Metal creaking]
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
[Rapid gunfire in distance]
[Both breathing heavily]
Last floor.
The guns have gotta be up here.
He said they'd be here.
Everything else he passed you
is checking out.
That guy's a piece of shit.
Those guns get to the Sanctuary,
they could cut through those
walkers and free up an exit.
We'll go faster if we split up.
I find the M2s,
you find 'em, we use them,
hit the courtyard
right then and there.
End this quick.
♪
Aah! Please!
Please don't shoot me!
[Crying] Shit.
Please don't shoot me.
Please don't...
Tara: Huh.
Oh, look, you pissed your pants.
I-I'm not one of them.
Uh, m-my name's Dean.
Why are you still talking?
Jesus:
Tara, wait.
Just wait.
Tara: For what?
He has his hands up, Tara.
We have a job to do.
[Rapid gunfire in distance]
You want to go check that out?
[Sighs]
[Rapid gunfire]
♪
We're missing some people
from the other team.
Morgan?
[Gunfire continues]
Come out.
♪
[Gunfire continues]
Just stay in there.
We're on top of each other here.
We'll signal you
when it's clear.
Just be ready.
[Gunfire continues]
I got it, Jesus.
Step aside.
Tara.
There's a firefight outside.
We don't even know
if Morgan's alive.
Dean: Please, lady.
I'm not one of them.
You're here. You had a gun.
You are one of them.
I'm not. I'm not.
You got to believe me.
Then what are you doing here?
I'm just a worker.
They brought me
from the Sanctuary
to cook, clean, whatever.
They did not give me a choice.
They made me leave
my wife and kids.
[Breathing heavily]
Your people do this
to the Sanctuary, too?
The families okay?
We don't want to hurt
the workers.
We're not going to.
You believe him?
It's not about him.
I'm not gonna shoot someone
with their hands up,
and I'm not letting you.
These medical supplies --
they're the Hilltop's, right?
Maggie's prenatals.
They took them
because they could,
because they don't give a shit.
So why should we?
I know they killed
your girlfriend...
Jesus --
...that you loved her.
This isn't you.
It is now.
We're not here for revenge.
It can't be about that.
It can.
[Gunshot]
Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
I wouldn't.
You know what's funny?
Normally I'd peg you
as the softie, not pretty boy.
You know how hard it is
to piss yourself on purpose?
I-It's like your dick knows
you're wearing pants.
♪
Aw, hell, look that.
Well, that shit is ruined.
Well, looks like that dumb bitch
Maggie and her kid
are just gonna die, anyway,
Just like you two.
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, honey, no, you're not.
Then someone else will.
There's too many of us.
See, that's where we differ.
If I take the two of you
with me,
then I've got one hell
of an insurance policy.
So why don't you put
that thing down
unless you're gonna shoot
through this beautiful man here.
I'm not gonna ask you again.
I think she's gonna shoot you.
I am.
Yeah.
She is.
Shut up!
Tara --
I can do it.
Tara, he has a gun to my head.
Not for long.
Wait. Wait.
Wait a second.
Go to hell.
Okay.
So [chuckles] you really
wanna risk it, huh?
Me for him?
Well, I can tell you right now
that I am not worth it.
We can work this out.
I-I may talk a big game
like I'm a tough guy,
but I'm not.
I really just want to...
[Gunshot]
[Coughs]
[Both breathing heavily]
You're not gonna do it.
Not you.
It's not about revenge.
It's about getting it done.
Ugh!
What the hell are you doing?
He tried to kill us.
I told you --
it's not about him.
So he gets to live?
What about Abraham?
Glenn? Denise?
This is different.
You're not Rick.
You're not Maggie.
No.
But she'll hear
what I have to say.
Man on walkie talkie:
Evac Sat 1! Evac Sat 1!
Dianne: Jesus! Tara!
♪
They're falling back!
Man: Go! Go! Go!
There another way out of here?
Yeah.
Follow my lead.
♪
[Groans]
[Rapid gunfire]
♪
Tobin!
Tobin: I'm okay!
Just keep going!
I'm okay!
[Gunfire continues]
♪
[Breathing heavily]
[Bullets ricocheting]
[Groaning]
♪
They didn't
have to move in on us.
Shit.
[Growling]
Aah!
♪
[Birds chirping]
Up ahead.
Carol: I see it.
This is me.
[Growling]
♪
[Grunts]
What befell this creature?
I mean before you.
Carol: We don't have time
to figure that out.
Compound's not far off.
If he made it,
if they know we're coming,
they're gonna be ready.
Two possibilities,
just one fact.
And what's that?
We shall be ready regardless.
What's about to happen,
it's not just a few walkers.
You know that, right?
Yes.
And yet I smile.
Why?
Do I feel the supreme
confidence?
Or is my lot, my job,
to simply protect
such certainty?
No and yes.
Yes and no.
And then finally yes to both.
Fake it till you make it, baby.
That's what I've done
and what I do.
I am King because
I-I have provided a light
to lead my people forward
through the darkness,
and they have made
my fictions realities.
So, with all this and everything
that's happened --
All of us may not make it.
We may not even win.
And yet I smile.
There will be no fantasies
of failure this day.
Daniel: Hey, guys.
Is this blood from the wasted?
No.
One of us hit him
when we fired on him.
Means he's moving slow.
Hells yeah.
We're back in business.
Ezekiel:
Well done, Daniel.
Well done to us all.
We move forward...
as we move
the very world forward.
♪
[Door bangs]
[Door creaks]
[Floorboard creaks]
[Door squeaks]
[Door creaks]
[Both grunting]
♪
[Objects clatter]
[Gasping]
The M2s.
Where are they?
No...guns!
[Gasps]
Grace--
[Breathing heavily]
They're in there?
No! No!
Ohh!
[Gasping]
♪
Aaaah!
[Breathing heavily]
♪
[Gunshots]
[Man grunts]
You sure we can do it?
We can beat 'em?
♪
What this group has done,
what we've learned,
what we've become, all of us --
yes, I'm sure.
♪
Ugh!
Circle the door, wide,
at least 20 feet.
Guns up, but hold your fire.
What?
They're gonna give up.
We only fire if they fire first.
They fire first, one of us dies.
Then let's hope, for my sake,
that they don't.
You can try to stop me.
[Clattering]
Man: Come on! Go! Move!
Jesus:
Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon and surrender.
Living sounds good to me.
[Gun clatters]
We're surrounded.
Don't be as dumb
as they think we are.
Put your guns down.
♪
[Breathing heavily]
It's okay.
We can do it the hard way.
Because even if Maggie
listens to you,
Rick will listen to me.
♪
[Guns clattering]
[Shell casings clattering]
[Magazine clicks]
[Door creaks]
Man: Ugh!
[Shell casing clinks]
♪
We have to come for them
before they come for us.
We can't leave them alive.
♪
Morgan: Where there's life,
there's possibility.
Of them hitting us.
Jared: Shit.
I know you.
You get transferred, too?
♪
Morgan!
Lower your gun.
[Breathing heavily]
We came here to kill them.
We're supposed to.
They surrendered.
It's not what we do.
♪
Then what do we do, huh?
[Floor creaks]
Rick: Hmm.
[Door creaks]
[ Waves crashing ]
[Breathes shakily]
♪
Gracie.
No.
♪
[Groans]
[Exhales sharply]
♪
[Groans]
[Birds chirping]
That way.
There!
♪
Save your munitions, Carol.
Our friends have arrived.
[Shiva roars]
[Screaming]
♪
[Shiva snarling]
[Rapid gunfire]
♪
Ugh!
Aah!
♪
Ahh.
Francine!
♪
[Gunfire continues,
glass breaking]
♪
[Keys clack]
[Engine starts]
[Gunfire continues]
♪
You okay? You okay?
I'm fine, but our people --
they need...
[Breathing heavily]
Oh, God.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
Eric, Eric.
Eric.
Let's go.
♪
Ezekiel: And there it is --
our certain victory.
[Shiva snarling]
This -- I am not glad
for his death.
For anyone's.
I know.
[Static crackles]
Man: Nelson, we're on the move,
taking active measures.
Just hole up, keep it elevated,
and if you see us,
stay out of the line of fire.
Jig's up.
Gonna have to break chocks.
No.
This journey will not end
in retreat.
But they know we're coming.
♪
Indeed they do.
[Chuckles]
♪
[Door creaks, thuds]
Damn it.
Keep your hands down.
Turn around slow.
♪
Hi, Rick.
Your name...
is Morales.
You were in Atlanta.
That was a long time ago.
It's over, Rick.
I called the Saviors back.
[Walkie talkie clacks]
And they're coming.
♪
[Gun cocks]
Cont..