{\move(400,10,190,270,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}sub_master-HD
I'm gonna kill you.
( Roars )
( People screaming )
( Man groaning )
Now!
Go! Go! Go!
We got your back!
( Gunfire )
We are going to war!
All : Yes, sir!
( Birds chirping )
( "Weird Al" Yankovic's "Another One
Rides the Bus" plays in distance )
♪
( Rhythmic clapping )
♪ Riding in the bus
down the boulevard ♪
♪ And the place
was pretty packed ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Couldn't find a seat,
so I had to stand ♪
♪ With the perverts
in the back ♪
♪ It was smelling like
a locker room... ♪
( Insects chirping )
( Birds chirping )
( Hammer clanging )
( Indistinct conversations )
( Clanging continues )
♪
( Conversations continue )
( Air hissing )
♪
10:28.
When I first met him...
Jesus said that my world was
gonna get a whole lot bigger.
♪
Well, we found that world.
We found each other.
That..."bigger world"
is ours by right.
That we've come together
for it, all of us...
it's that much more true --
it's ours by right.
( Walkers growling in distance )
Any person who would live
in peace and fairness,
who would find common ground...
it's their right, too.
♪
( Walkers growling in distance )
Down.
But those who use and take
and kill to carve out the world
and make it theirs alone --
we end them.
♪
We don't...celebrate it.
We don't have shame about it,
either.
♪
There's only one person
who has to die...
and I will kill him myself.
I will.
( Walkers growling in distance )
( Pen clicks )
♪
( Growling continues )
( Arrow fires )
♪
But if it's the others...
the others who prop him up,
stand by his side,
even those
who just look the other way --
so be it.
10:28.
( Walkers growling in distance )
Then...
we keep making the world bigger.
♪
Together.
Ezekiel : Together.
Bound forever!
To quote The Bard, "For he today
that sheds his blood with me
shall be my brother."
♪
For she today...
my sister.
( Shiva roars )
Maggie :
We've practiced.
We've been through it
over and over again.
We all know the plan
doesn't end this morning.
That we may have to live
in uncertainty for days,
maybe more.
That we have to keep our faith
in each other.
If we can hold on to that
with everything we have,
the future is ours.
The world is ours.
♪
( Walkers growling loudly
in distance )
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
♪ And another comes on
and another comes on ♪
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
♪ Hey, who's gonna sit by you? ♪
♪
♪ There's a suitcase
poking me in the ribs ♪
♪ There's an elbow in my ear ♪
♪ There's a smelly old bum
standing next to me ♪
♪ Hasn't showered in a year ♪
♪ Well, I think I'm missing
a contact lens ♪
♪ And I think my wallet's gone ♪
♪ And I think this bus
is stopping again ♪
♪ To let a couple more
freaks get on, look out! ♪
( Mid-tempo music plays )
♪
( Insects chirping )
( Brakes squeal )
( Engine shuts off )
( Door creaks )
( Chirping continues )
( Birds chirping )
Man : Hi.
( Can clatters )
Yeah.
I-I'm okay.
I mean...
I'm not, but...
I've been shot at.
Someone threw a microwave at me.
So I-I'm just gonna say
something my mom used to say
and hope for the best here.
"Whatever you have of good,
spend on
the traveler."
My mom said that --
that helping the traveler,
the person without a home --
that's everything.
I'm sure you've seen things,
been through things,
that you don't trust people.
I get it.
I don't, either.
I've been through things, too.
My mom --
she also said that,
"May my mercy prevail
over my wrath."
( Scoffs )
It's not all my mom.
That -- That one --
That's from the Quran.
Probably shouldn't have
said that.
I don't even know you,
but I ha-- I haven't eaten
in a few days.
You might not even be real.
♪
Hands up.
Listen.
I'm gone.
Huh?
It's cool.
I just --
I just wanted some --
e-even just some food.
( Gunshots )
♪
We were supposed to meet
at the intersection.
♪
I shot over his head.
I just wanted him gone.
He said
that he was --
I heard what he said.
Most of it.
But he could've been
one of them.
Like a spy?
( Gun drops in holster )
I shot above his head.
If he isn't one of them,
I hope he makes it.
It's not gonna be enough, Dad.
Enough what?
Hope.
( Sighs )
( Walker growling )
♪
( Silenced gunshot )
( Growling continues )
♪
( Thuds softly )
( Door rattling )
( Walkers growling )
♪
( Grunts )
( Body thuds )
♪
( Shuddering breath )
30 minutes.
Everyone's ready.
♪
Are you?
It's one person
who brought it to this.
One person.
It always starts
with one person.
This did.
What we're doing here now.
This --
This isn't about me.
Yes.
It isn't.
You made it like that.
♪
( Engine revs )
( Engine revving )
♪
( Engine shuts off )
( Engine starts )
Come here.
( Engine starts, revs )
( Brakes squeal )
This is the end of it.
♪
( Engine revs )
I know you wanted
to go with him.
♪
I did, too.
Everything hurts.
♪
But I'll help you
defend this place.
Help me?
Oh, yeah.
This is your show.
( Scoffs )
Okay...
♪
You'll see.
( Walker growling )
( Rick whistles )
( Groans )
( Body thuds )
♪
( Breathing heavily )
What are you up to, Rick?
( Coughs )
You think
you're gonna take us on?
( Coughs, groans )
I saw you...
beggin'.
Crying.
You're gonna beg again, Rick.
( Coughs )
( Breathing heavily )
Your --
Your boy's gonna die.
( Coughing )
♪
( Walker growling )
Aah!
( Flesh tearing )
No, no, no!
( Growling continues )
♪
( Indistinct conversations )
( Brakes squeal )
♪
Andy : Sure are
a lot of us here.
I got your back.
Really?
You just met me.
We all just met each other.
( Indistinct conversations )
Aaron:
Are you praying?
I always meant to start.
Better late than never.
♪
Jerry : Here.
Over your sternum.
No, I'm going back
with Maggie after.
Dude. Sternum.
Duuuuuude.
Rick :
You up to this?
Maggie : I got the Hilltop
to stand against the Saviors.
I need to be there.
At least for the first part.
They say you can wage war
through the second trimester.
( Chuckles )
I've been fighting
since the farm.
Can't stop now.
How about tomorrow?
You been thinking about
what that looks like?
Yes, I have.
I don't know
if I can wait for it.
Just one more fight.
And I'm gonna be there.
At least for the first part.
Ezekiel : I'm told the Hilltop
lost their doctor.
An obstetrician, no less.
We have a doctor in the Kingdom.
A woman of talent.
Join us.
We'll get ours back.
( Laughs )
Yes, Jesus.
Yes, you will.
As sure as the day
defeats the night.
And on this day,
we begin to reshape this world
for your child
and the children to come.
So let's get started.
♪
( Sighs )
What?
Hilltop's lucky to have you.
♪
You showed me how to be
someone worth following.
Good.
♪
After this...
I'm following you.
♪
Here we go.
10...
9...
8...
7...6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1.
♪
Shit.
( Wind whistling )
No. There.
Tara : Okay.
Close enough.
All right, let's go.
Got it?
Yeah.
( Engine starts, revs )
♪
( Walkers growling )
Woman :
It went up towards the herdway.
Dwight : Go big.
2 cars, 10 guns.
We're not messing around,
not now.
You take the Sister route.
It's locked down.
Do you think it was them?
Nah.
Probably something left over,
maybe under one of the bodies.
I want some bang bang, Dwighty.
I want some scream scream.
I want blood.
♪
Well...
maybe you'll get lucky.
♪
Carol:
How close are we?
Daryl : Close.
( Walkers growling in distance )
( Silenced gunshots )
( Walkers growling )
♪
( Brakes squeal )
( Engines shut off )
( Vehicle doors open )
( Growling continues )
♪
( Guns cock )
( Gunshots )
♪
( Doorknob creaks )
Well, shit.
I'm sorry.
♪
I was in a meeting.
( Insects chirping )
( Creaking softly )
( "Weird Al" Yankovic's "Another One
Rides the Bus" plays in distance )
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
♪ And another comes on
and another comes on ♪
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
♪ Hey, who's gonna sit by you? ♪
Mnh.
♪ Another one rides the bus,
hey, hey! ♪
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey-ey-ey-eyyyyyy ♪
You turned off the alarm.
They can manage without you
for one morning.
Carl:
We're all playing hooky.
All of us? ♪ The window doesn't
open, and the fan is broke ♪
Hey, I didn't put that song on.
Mm.
( Chuckles )
( Walkers growling in distance )
Negan : Well, shit.
I'm sorry.
I was in a meeting.
( Growling continues )
I see you got
your little mudflaps with you.
So I'm not exactly
feelin' a reason
for us to try throwin' lead
at each other.
I care about my people.
I don't want to just march them
into the line of fire
because I want play
"my dick is bigger than yours."
It is.
We both know it.
But I'm also comfortable enough
to accept the fact if it wasn't.
I'm certainly not gonna let
my people die over that shit...
...like you're about to.
♪
So, Rick,
what the hell can I do for you?
Dwight.
♪
Your name's Simon.
You're Gavin.
♪
And you...
Regina.
Rick, I'd feel remiss if --
Rick : No.
I know who you are.
♪
Listen, you five.
The Saviors inside.
All of you have a chance
to survive here.
To survive this.
You all can live
if you surrender.
Can't guarantee it
any time but now.
Right now.
( Walkers growling in distance )
♪
Tara : Shit.
Could that thing set it off?
Morgan:
I got it.
( Walkers growling )
♪
Negan :
So they surrender...
and you and your little
piss patrol doesn't kill them.
That sounds like a good deal!
♪
What about me, Rick?
I told you.
Twice.
You know what's going to happen.
I do.
I do know what's gonna happen.
You don't.
You have no idea the shit
that's about to go down.
Let me ask you something,
Rick --
Do you think you have
the numbers for this fight?
♪
You don't.
Simon?
♪
Of course that's where he went.
Negan : What do you
have to say
to the Rick
and the piss patrol, Gregory?
The Hilltop stands
with Negan and the Saviors.
Any resident of the Hilltop
who takes up arms
or who supports this ultimatum
against the Sanctuary
or any of the Saviors,
for that matter --
they will no longer be welcome
in the colony.
And?
Their families
will be thrown out
and will be left
to fend for themselves.
And?
Go home now.
Or you won't have a home
to go back to.
♪
You do what you need to do.
All I have at the Hilltop
are a bunch of books
and an old lobster bib.
♪
Negan :
You heard the man.
Go back
to separating wheat and shit
or whatever the hell it is
you people do.
Doesn't look like
anyone's goin', does it?
♪
Hilltop stands with --
The Hilltop stands with Maggie!
♪
( Walker growling )
I feel...
like I invested a lot in you,
and I am very,
very disappointed.
( Grunting )
( Body thudding )
♪
( Engine revs )
( Wire rattles )
( Explosions in distance )
♪
( Walkers growling in distance )
Sounds like
shit is goin' down, Rick.
♪
You "lieutenants..."
you're gonna have to
make up your minds.
Maybe we can take
a time-out here --
No.
This has to happen now.
This is the only way.
( Growling continues )
♪
You're gonna make me count.
( Chuckles )
Okay.
I'm counting.
10!
9!
8!
7!
( Gun cocks )
( Gunshots )
( Gunfire )
♪
( Walkers growling in distance )
Carol:
It's started.
Daryl : Yeah. It was always
gonna be that way.
( Walkers growling )
♪
Tara : Pleasure doing business
with you.
♪
Beat 'em.
We will.
♪
Be careful.
( Engine starts )
Shit, this is gonna be fun.
( Growling continues )
No, it isn't.
It's better than lettin'
things be, though, right?
♪
Yeah. It is.
( Growling continues )
♪
Now!
( Gunfire )
♪
( Walkers growling )
( Gunfire )
( Horn honks )
( Engine revs )
♪
( Gunshot, explosion )
( Gunfire continues )
♪
( Gunshot, explosion )
( Engine revs )
♪
( Gunshot, explosion )
( Gunfire )
( Gunshot )
Go!
( Gunfire )
( Gunshot, explosion )
( Gunfire continues )
♪
( Growling )
( Gunshot, explosion )
♪
( Walkers growling )
( Gunfire )
♪
( Explosion )
( Walkers growling, gunfire )
( Groans )
♪
Gabriel : Rick!
( Distorted gunfire )
♪
He's not going anywhere!
Rick!
We have to go!
He's not going anywhere!
We have to leave now!
It's not about you, right?
Not about you.
Come here.
( Gunfire continues )
♪
( Camera shutter clicks, whirs )
( Walkers growling )
♪
( Engine starts )
( Tires screech )
No, no.
Wait. Wait.
Whoa!
( Groans )
♪
Shit.
( Gun cocks )
( Gunfire )
♪
I'm gonna get you out of here.
We just have to wait
for our moment.
Thank you, Father.
Thank God.
Sure, whatever.
( Gunfire )
The -- The -- The shots --
they're too close!
Why are they firing at me?
( Gunshots )
♪
Wait.
( Gunfire continues )
Hey, hey!
Wait!
♪
( Groans )
( Engine starts )
( Walkers growling )
( Gunfire continues )
( Car door closes )
♪
We can wait some more.
We can't.
He stopped to get me.
How's that?
Negan. ( Sighs )
He was on the ground.
I was trying to kill him,
and Gabriel stopped to get me.
♪
We gotta start out.
You all right?
♪
( Chuckles )
This isn't about me.
Let's go.
Yeah.
( Whistles )
( Engine starts )
♪
We were gonna start with taking
out the guards with arrows.
You think you can still
hit them through that?
♪
I wouldn't bet on it.
( Arrow fires )
( Grunts )
♪
( Gates creaking )
( Gunfire )
♪
( Metal scrapes, clattering )
Down!
( Explosion )
( Walkers growling )
♪
( Growling continues )
( Breathing heavily )
Negan : I hope you got
your shitting pants on.
♪
What?
Your shittin' pants.
I hope you're wearing them
right now...
♪
...'cause you...
are about to shit your pants.
♪
( Growling continues )
Daddy!
( Chuckling ) Hey!
( Smooches )
They made a big owl
for the party!
What?
People are taking this festival
extremely seriously.
A big owl?
♪ Another one rides the bus ♪
It's outside.
( Gasps )
They're gonna get you.
Never.
Should we go see?
♪ Hey, who's gonna sit by you? ♪
I'm not afraid of a big owl.
How big is it?
( Indistinct conversation )
♪ Let's go! ♪
( Mid-tempo music plays )
♪
( Chuckles )
( Birds chirping )
My mercy...
prevails...
over my wrath.
( Chuckles )
♪
I don't want
to wait for it anymore.
You don't either --
Yeah, I know.
So we don't have to wait for it.
If we start tomorrow
right now...
with everything we've beaten,
everything we've endured,
everything we've risen above,
everything we've become...
If we start tomorrow
right now...
no matter what comes next...
we've won.
We've already won.
( Crowd cheers )
®  Cont..  ®