Previously on AMC's
"The Walking Dead"...
Save him. Like you saved me.
- Wait.
- I liked you, Ezekiel.
Your people are gonna look
up at the sanctuary fence,
and they're going to
see their king is dead.
We can't just let them have this place.
We can.
All we need to do is survive tonight.
"My mercy... prevails...
over my wrath."
Jerry!
S'up, Jude?!
Hey, Rick.
Everything okay?
Just came for some of
that butternut skillet cake
you guys make.
You rode out from the
Kingdom for dessert?
Hells yah.
You got roped into masonry duty.
Siddiq, man.
Dude's impossible to say no to.
Back to it.
Just go!
You don't have to do this.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's just 'til I can talk to my dad.
If he's not back soon,
we'll meet him there.
Hopefully, they'll be with him.
What about Michonne?
Ah.
You seeing this?
North copies. Got shots here.
West, too. What are they doing?
They'll run outta ammo
before they run outta walkers.
I got eyes on it.
South out.
They're trying to make a path.
Blocking out the walkers with bodies.
They're gonna get out.
Man, we need to tell everybody...
South down!
Get out! Everybody, get out now!
Hey! Hey!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I see it.
It got tripped up on my wire.
I got it.
The cottage is just ahead,
out of the tree-line.
It's got a wrought-iron fence.
There's food and water inside.
The Saviors don't know about it.
You'll be safe there
until I make it back with Ezekiel.
You versus all of them?
Yeah.
They don't stand a chance.
It's not just Carol.
I'm going, too.
No. You're not.
They killed my brother.
And I'm not gonna let 'em kill you.
I can do it.
I can help you.
Morgan taught me the stick.
You taught me the gun.
It's not happening.
Come on.
I-I don't...
Dad.
- How...
- Dad...
it's all right.
It's gotta be.
I wasn't sure if you'd
make it back before...
But just in case, you know...
I wanted to make sure I
was able to say goodbye.
No. It's them. It's them.
They... They don't...
It wasn't...
Carl.
No.
I got bit.
I was bringing someone back.
His name's Siddiq.
We saw him at that gas station,
before...
It wasn't the Saviors.
It just happened.
I got bit.
Negan's gonna kill you now.
I said he's gonna kill you.
And there's nothing
I can do to stop that.
Hey. You hear me?
I ferried my people to freedom.
What befalls me now matters not.
No. It matters, idiot.
I liked you, Ezekiel.
You got it.
You got that you couldn't do better
than you had it.
You accepted things for what they were,
and you didn't get any
big ideas in your head.
And then Rick went and
planted one right in there.
And here we are.
Shit's getting shittier.
And you're gonna die.
I made a choice I could live with.
Now it's your turn to do the same.
Henry!
Hey.
They don't have enough people
to guard all the walls.
No, but they do have people.
- And they have Ezekiel.
- I saw him.
They got him on the
other side of this place.
We can take them.
One by one.
No, if we hit one of them,
that could call them all.
It's better just to
avoid them until we can't.
Henry.
He's here, too.
Where?
Did you see him? Do they have him?
Yeah, I saw him run this
way, and then he was gone.
But he'll hide.
He won't take them on face-to-face.
We have to do this now.
So if we have to take
them, we take them.
Is that better?
Yeah...
Thanks.
I, um, I got these.
They're over-the-counter,
non-steroidal anti-inflammatories.
They'll, um...
They'll help a little with the fever.
They did for my mom and dad.
Please take them.
Your son...
he should have them.
You're a doctor?
I was a resident... before.
Yeah.
Your name is Siddiq?
Yes.
Did you know he was a doctor?
Is that why you brought him back?
He wasn't gonna make it alone.
He needed us.
That's why.
He was the one at the gas station.
Shh!
Water. Give him water.
Easy. You got it?
Slowly, slowly.
Make it stop.
Make them stop.
- I can't.
- You can.
You're one of them.
They'll listen to you.
Please.
You said that Hilltop's safe, right?
Yeah.
We need to get everybody there.
We can get Carl there.
And they think all of
you got away in the woods.
They're out there, looking.
They saw us go West,
so we won't go West.
Your best chance is to stay here
until they're gone.
No.
They find us here, we're dead.
They're almost done.
They gotta be.
It wasn't about destroying the place.
They don't have the ammo for that.
After they let up,
after they're gone,
that's when we go.
Okay.
We wait.
You sure going to
Hilltop's the best plan?
You got a better one?
All of you in one place, together...
All of us together...
We'll be their worst damn nightmare.
If we don't go through 'em,
we gotta go through the courtyard.
Exposed.
This is it.
You want me to just do it?
No.
No. No.
Got all of 'em.
They could've found Henry.
I know.
I'm not worried about them.
Come on, boys.
Get the damn gum off your shoes.
Let's go!
Is it gonna go bad, Ezekiel?
Is this going to turn
into something else?
You are the author of this night, Gavin.
Its close shall be
fashioned by your start.
You left.
You were supposed to be resting.
I'm not tired.
Yeah.
You look great.
It's gotta stop, Michonne.
It's not supposed to be like this.
I know it can be better.
Sounds like they're letting up.
Looks like you were right.
They're leaving.
Maybe.
Want me to go take a look?
Hey. Hey.
There.
sure as shit gonna beat
living in that chemical dump.
Hell, you want that room.
You're gonna have to fight me for it...
Leave it.
Hey.
Let's go.
Leave some room for Ezekiel.
Get him a pillow or something.
It's gonna be his last ride.
Let's at least try to
make him comfortable.
You try, and you try, and you try,
and you hope, and you
hope, and you hope.
Just wantin' things
to finally just settle.
Achieve some goddamn,
hard-fought equilibrium.
But, no.
It always comes down to this.
It always has to get dark and ugly...
and inhuman.
You know I don't like this, right?
It is not too late
to walk back from something decided.
You did,
and look where it got you.
Duke. Paulie. Where you at?
Stop pickin' dingles, grab your walkie,
and respond!
Gomez?
Gomez!
It is not too late to walk
back from something decided.
Shit. There it is.
Get him inside. Now!
I calibrate this cooker properly,
we'll be lousy with
baked apples ad infinitum.
It would be my honor
if you considered to
be the sous to my chef.
Or I could be said sous,
and you shall surely chef.
'Til then,
this Golden Delicious
has your name on it.
Thanks, Eugene.
Thanks.
The Saviors are gone.
We can get everyone to Hilltop.
We can get Carl there.
Carl? No.
Daryl can get one of the cars.
Carl won't make...
He can't leave here.
- I have to stay with him.
- Rick.
He can't.
I have to stay.
We'll both stay.
Will you...
Will you take Judith?
She needs to be there.
If she...
If...
happens...
I'll take her.
I'll get her there. I'll keep her safe.
I got this.
Let me say goodbye.
You be good, okay?
For Michonne.
For Dad.
You gotta honor him.
Listen when he tells you stuff.
You don't have to always.
Sometimes, kids got to
show their parents the way.
This was Dad's before it was mine.
Now it's yours.
I don't know... Just...
Just having it and...
It always kept Dad with me.
It made me feel as strong as him.
It helped me.
Maybe it'll help you, too.
Before Mom died...
she told me that I was
gonna beat this world.
I didn't.
But you will.
I know you will.
Here we go.
These people.
You saved them all.
That's all you, man.
You were helping me honor my mom...
Not just yours.
Mine, too.
You brought me here.
You gave me a chance.
I know I can never repay you...
but I can honor you
by showing your people, your f-friends,
your... your family
that what you did wasn't for nothing.
That it mattered.
That it... That it meant something.
Because it did.
So that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna honor you, Carl.
Congratulations.
You're stuck with us.
Okay.
There can't be a lot of 'em
'cause there aren't a lot left.
We got room for us
and controlled access.
Force projected on the doors, now!
We end this, whatever the hell it is.
I gotta settle this shit
under the penalty of that goddamn bat.
You don't.
Shut up about that, okay?
This is it!
It is too late.
I'm the "author," you're the dead man,
and that's how it's gonna be.
You think I can be someone else?
This is who I am.
I live, you die... This is what this is!
The petty compromises
I made to avoid conflict
were always done
in the name of saving my people's lives.
Now I realize...
I was saving yours.
No more.
Give up, or he's dead.
Aah!
Jesus.
Morgan, we should take our leave.
We don't need to go.
All of them are dead.
You okay?
I don't want you to be sad after this.
- Carl...
- Or angry.
You're gonna have to be strong.
For my dad.
For Judith.
For yourself.
I will.
Don't carry this.
Not this part.
You're my best friend, Michonne.
You're mine, too.
You're mine.
I need your help.
With what?
Getting him out of here.
We need to stop.
The house up ahead. We can make it.
It's okay. Just put me down here.
It's okay.
- No. We'll make it.
- Please.
There.
Thanks... for...
For getting me here.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I-I just...
I didn't... I didn't want you out there.
- I-I...
- No.
No... for getting me here.
For... For making it
so I could be who...
Who I wound up.
Back at the prison...
when we got attacked...
there was a kid,
a little older than me.
He had a gun.
He was...
He was starting to put it down,
and I-I s...
I shot him.
He was... He was giving it up,
and I... I just...
I shot him.
I think about him.
What I did to him
and how...
How easy it was to just... kill him.
You're sick!
Only a sick man would do it like this.
You think I wanted this?
There wasn't a lot on the menu.
I ran a good crew.
I kept my word.
You ask Ezekiel... I kept my word!
You... You could...
You could go back to the Hilltop.
It's still standing.
They're keeping them going.
Just turn around.
You think you can beat Negan?
You can't.
We can go back to how it was.
We can go back...
No.
Carl, no.
What happened...
what you'd lost...
All those things you had to...
All those thing you had to do...
You... You... You... You were just...
You were just a boy.
And you saw it.
What it did.
How... How easy it got.
You just killed all those
men because of the kid?!
Killing me won't make any of it go away.
You'll still wake up to
the same shit tomorrow.
Get up.
Up.
Ugh! Aah!
That's why you changed...
why you brought those
people from Woodbury in...
You brought them in, and
we all lived together.
We were enemies.
You put away your gun.
You did it so I could change,
so I could be who I am now.
What you did then...
How you... How you stopped fighting...
it was right.
It still is.
It can be like that again.
You can still be like that again.
Morgan.
Morgan, cease this.
Relent.
Ending him is the coward's way.
We've won.
We don't have to kill him.
He will see what he has wrought,
and all of it will be his to live with.
I can't be who I was.
It's different now.
You can't kill all of 'em, Dad.
There's gotta be something after.
For you... and for them.
Morgan, stop it.
You don't want to do
this. You don't have to.
You told me we can be better than them.
You said that to me.
You don't want to do this.
I know it. I can see it.
I have...
I have to.
I know... you can't see it yet...
how it could be.
But I have...
You have a beard.
It's... It's bigger...
and grayer...
Michonne's happy...
Judith is older,
and she's listening to the
songs that I used to before...
Alexandria's bigger.
There's...
There's new houses...
crops...
and people working.
Everybody living...
helping everybody else live.
If you can still be who you were...
that's how it could be.
It could.
Carl.
It was all for you.
Right from the start.
Back in Atlanta, the farm...
Everything I did, it was for you.
Then, at the prison, it
was for you and Judith.
It still is.
It's gonna be.
And nothing... Nothing
is gonna change that.
I want this for you, Dad.
I'm gonna make it real, Carl.
I promise.
I'm gonna make it real.
Henry.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Don't look at him. You look at me.
I had to.
You were supposed to
stay at the cottage.
This wasn't what you
were supposed to do.
This wasn't for you. Carol.
Henry.
All will be resolved.
Carl... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
A father's job is to protect his son.
Love.
It's just to love.
No. No.
Carl...
It... It... It... It should be...
I know. I know.
Somebody you love.
When you can't do it yourself.
But I still can.
I grew up.
I have to do this.
Me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, Carl.
I love you so much.
I'll make it real.
I will.
Good morning.
Well, good morning to you, darlin'.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --