{\move(400,10,190,270,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}sub_master-HD
Previously on
AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
[Gunfire]
Aah!
[Gunfire continues]
We will lose
not one of our ranks.
Ezekiel: Not one.
We move onward.
[Tiger growling]
[Roars]
[Man shouts indistinctly]
There! Go!
[Gunfire]
Scatter, now!
Cover the King!
[ Gunfire ]
Ezekiel: No!
[Sighs]
[Gate creaks lightly]
[Shiva growling softly]
Fear not, young master Henry.
You will be brave.
Because you are brave.
We face dire challenge
and chance.
Our lives...
our way of life...
it hangs in the balance,
a fragile glass
standing on a wire,
high above the asphalt,
as we pray for not one drop
of rain under an overcast sky.
And yet, I smile.
We will fight,
and we will bleed...
and yet I smile.
We shall face men,
some cornered into their roles
by circumstance,
some desperate murderers
thrilled by blood.
We shall end them all.
As is our charge this day.
As is our sorrow.
And yet, I smile.
We will leave our loved ones...
to traverse a dangerous road.
Rushing out of peace into war.
And yet, I smile.
For we will mine glory from
the rock of struggle this day.
We will honor and protect
this -- this bastion of life
in a land of the dead,
and we will win.
You trust the king --
we will win.
I smile...
I laugh...
I rejoice this day...
for on this day,
we are joined in purpose
and vision --
we are of a singular heart
and mind.
On this day, we are one!
Yeah!
‭[Crowd murmuring]
Woman: Yes.
‭Man: Yeah!
We are one!
[Indistinct shouting]
‭Yeah!
We are one!
Man #2: Yeah!
[Shouting continues]
We are one!
[Grunting]
[Gasping]
Aah!
[Grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
Aah!
[Grunting]
[Screams]
[Cries]
[Growling softly]
[Growling]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
(((( o ))))
[Grunting]
[Dramatic music playing]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
[Grunting, gasping]
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Walker growling]
[Gun clicking]
[Gun clicks]
[Grunting]
Oh!
[Groaning]
[Growls]
[Gunshot]
Your Majesty!
There are too many!
[Gunshots]
‭Just go!
Can you walk, Your Majesty?
With my cane.
I have to.
I got you.
‭[Grunts]
‭[Groans]
You cannot endanger yourself
for me.
Your Majesty...
I have to.
[Growling continues]
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Soft clattering]
[Indistinct conversation]
Rudy: Asshats,
get those guns,
and let's screw
the hell off now!
Man: We need
some help here!
What you need
is to hurry your asses up!
If you're not out of here
with those guns
by the time I round this corner,
I am gonna flay your asses!
It is real now!
We're almost done!
Jesus!
[Suspenseful music plays]
What the hell?
‭What?
Those are the only
.50-cal buckets we got?
Got the rest in the pool.
This was just to tear 'em up.
We got at least --
[Gunfire]
[Ceiling tile scraping]
[Gun clatters]
[Breathing heavily]
[Gurgling]
[Man speaks indistinctly]
[Door opens]
Let her go!
Grab the guns!
Shit has to be goin' down at HQ.
We gotta get
this shit there now.
Go!
[Walkers growling]
Have you seen Shiva?
Not since we were hit.
[Growling continues]
We can
get through them --
[Gunshot]
‭[Groans]
Hands up.
Let's move...
"Your Highness."
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
[Cane tapping]
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Breathing heavily]
Forgot about your blade.
Give it to me.
It's how I can walk.
You can keep the cane.
I'm gonna need your help.
We got a big trip ahead of us.
[Groans] Where?
‭Guess.
The Sanctuary?
That's right.
The gates are down.
It's surrounded by the dead.
They can't get out.
We can't get in.
Well, maybe you can help me
get our big guns over there
to help remedy that situation.
[Growling continues]
Yago:
Ammo's in the truck?
Man: There's another three up
at Sanctuary and then some.
[Walkers growling]
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
[Gunshot]
Hurry up. Come on!
‭Ohh! [Groaning]
You made it this long.
After pulling all
the crap you did,
you're gonna lie down now?
Better the dead be my end
than a despot's
meaningless foot soldier.
Tell me...
does Negan know your name?
I'm Negan.
Get up.
I will not let you use me
to hurt my people.
"Your people"?
You mean all those sheep
you rooked
into thinking you're a king?
Yeah, I heard your story.
We all did.
[Screaming]
Let's go.
Now. Move!
[Groaning]
You work at a circus?
No.
Yeah, I thought maybe, but nah.
They don't treat animals
too nice at the circus.
And that cat just loves you.
It gave you everything,
didn't it?
Gave you an angle, a story.
Got to hand it
to you --
you played your cards good.
You played "your people" good.
They ate that horseshit
right up.
[Laughs]
They grew food for you.
Built those walls for you.
Hell, look at that.
[Chuckles]
You got them all killed --
they're still following you.
But take away that tiger...
what's left?
Just some meaningless con man
in a costume.
[Grunts]
[Truck hatch creaks]
[Gunfire]
[Gunfire continues]
[Glass shatters]
[Gunfire continues in distance]
[Walkers growling]
You got people
still alive in there?
Let it be so.
We're getting into
something with wheels,
and we're getting out of here.
[Gunshot]
[Grunts]
Ohh!
[Groaning]
[Grunts]
It's over, okay?!
You took your shot --
it's over!
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
[Gunfire continues]
Delusions of grandeur.
[Grunts]
‭Come on.
[Gunfire continues]
[Gunfire continues in distance]
Dammit!
The dead are nearly upon us.
Give me my sword.
We can fight 'em together.
The hell are you doing?!
Gettin' out of here.
‭[Grunting]
I can't stand on my own.
I can't climb that.
You don't need to.
‭[Grunts]
[Groans]
Is what it is.
Negan was hoping
to have your ass
chained to
the Sanctuary fence...
You, the Widow...
Rick.
But your head on a pike
will do just fine.
Maybe break it up a little,
avoid the obvious symmetry.
[Man screaming]
[Screams]
[Axe thuds]
[Gunfire]
[Man whistles]
[Gunfire stops]
Carol: I can tell you
where the others are.
Just let me live!
They're hiding out,
waiting for
other Saviors to show up.
Nice and slow.
I'm unarmed.
Look.
Your Majesty, your leg!
[Groaning]
I'm okay.
[Grunting]
[Walkers growling]
Jerry...
I'm going to borrow this
for a sec.
Jerry, I can --
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
Your Majesty.
You don't need to call me that.
Dude...
yes, I do.
[Screams]
[Screaming]
Your people...
...where are they?
You can't tell them I told you.
You have to promise.
Please!
Hey, do you wanna die?
I asked you
where your people are --
Lower your guns now!
Yago, please, man.
Joey just pooched it.
Light 'em up.
[Gunfire]
[Screaming]
[Growling]
[Grunting]
Shitballs.
[Grunts]
Yah!
Get behind me, Your Majesty.
No.
[Gunfire]
[Groaning]
[Walkers growling]
[Both grunting]
[Gunfire continues in distance]
Thank you, Your Majesty.
For what?
For being such a cool dude.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Gunfire continues]
[Walkers growling]
[Gunfire stops]
Carol:
We need to end this.
You were lying to us
about your friends, huh?
Yeah. I was.
Now, we need to end this.
Okay.
Walk away, lady.
You're not going anywhere
with those guns.
[Scoffs]
Nah. We are.
They got someplace to be.
I've got your pal's ammo.
How many bullets you got left
after all those walkers?
Three? Four?
Why don't you come at us
and find out?
We're right here.
[Growling continues]
[Gunshots]
[Grunting]
Honey, let's keep talking
We got all the time
in the world.
[Music intensifies]
Have you ever fought before?
You've seen me fight.
Before this.
The dead.
A marauder in the woods once.
You fought him?
‭Yes.
Me...
then Shiva.
I have trained
for a very long time.
And I have continued,
from long before this till now.
And I have practiced
for days on end.
I am ready to become
what I must.
"To become"?
Yes.
To will myself
into what I must be.
I was a zookeeper.
I was...meek.
Those weekend matinees,
those nights.
And then, at work,
a 500-pound tiger
needed my help.
And as she bled...
I did not just leap
into her enclosure.
I was not seized by any...
deep-seated instinct.
They were only...
a few seconds that passed...
but I deliberated.
I thought about doing it,
weighing the risk
‭of approaching such a beast.
And I thought about
not doing it.
I stood there,
considering who I'd be
in either iteration.
And I decided I wanted to be
the one who leapt.
So, many years later...
Benjamin was the one who told me
what I already knew,
but couldn't hear...
"If you're asked
to be the hero...
be the hero."
I'm now ready.
Finally.
I've deliberated.
I've made the decision
on who I will be.
Was it easier for you?
Or have you always
been this way?
This strong?
This brave?
Or did you decide to be
who you are today?
I decided.
Just like you.
But life
‭decided some things, too.
It does.
It will.
[Grunting]
[Walkers growling]
[Gunfire]
[Grunts]
[Keys jingling]
Are you okay?
Did they get the guns?
Nothing we can do about it.
[Lock clicks]
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
I've got the King.
[Grunting]
We have to get word to Rick!
If they ferry those machine guns
to the Sanctuary...
[Engine revs in distance]
They're not getting them
to the Sanctuary.
[Engine revving]
[Gunfire]
[Tires screech]
[Engine revs]
Aah!
[Engine shuts off]
[Leaves rustling]
Rick: Hey.
[Grunting]
[Panting]
We got the guns.
You look like shit.
Let's go see
if this asshole's alive.
[Walkers growling distance]
[Ezekiel grunting]
Jerry:
Your Majesty!
This ain't gonna work.
You gotta leave me.
I'm slowing you down.
No. You don't
get to do that.
[Gunfire]
Come on.
I'm almost out of ammo.
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
[Suspenseful music plays]
I can't...
You can't.
Y-You two
have to just go.
[Grunts]
Lower him down to me.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
Carol: Ezekiel!
Just go!
I'll hold them off!
Ezekiel, we can get you away.
You can't!
[Grunting]
I can't leave you, Your Majesty.
[Grunts]
C'mon, man, just go!
You're my king!
No, I'm not!
I'm not your King!
I'm not "Your Majesty"!
[Grunts]
‭[Body thuds]
Look at what's in front of us!
That's what's real!
Go.
I ain't no king!
I ain't nothing.
I'm just some guy.
Some guy who found...
[Shiva growling]
Shiva...
C'mon.
[Growling]
[Grunting]
Shiva!
Run, girl!
No! No!
[Growling continues]
Please, Jerry!
Dammit, let me help her!
[Flesh tearing]
You can't.
[Walkers growling]
[Growling continues]
[Groans]
[Metal gate opens]
[Gate creaks softly]
[Gate thuds]
Cont..