[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 9]
Did you lose anything?
No, I didn't lose anything.
Rao Zhi.
Nothing suspicious is detected.
You guys are neglecting
what is right under your nose.
Could it be that before you left,
you opened the window
but you forgot about it?
Could it someone else in the house
have opened the window
but didn't inform you?
There's no way I could've forgotten
that I opened the window.
I'm not sure
if anyone else opened the window.
I think it's better to be cautious.
Please investigate for me, Mr Rao.
How about this?
I'll get someone to check the surveillance
of the surrounding streets.
I'll contact you if anything.
Sure.
Let's go back.
It's my...
Stop moving. Sit down and watch.
It's Er Miao.
Did it lose weight?
Do you have any other videos?
No.
That's the only video.
Please send it to me.
Xia Chu.
When you left home,
did you open the window
in the master room?
I can't remember.
Did I? I don't think so.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's my darling Er Miao.
I really miss it.
-You call it Er...
-Miao.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get changed and wash my hair.
Don't be dramatic.
You can barely stand.
How do you wash your hair?
My hair stinks!
Do you want to recover soon?
Of course, but I have to wash my hair.
Why don't...
you lend me a hand?
Do you expect me
to wait on you like a servant?
Isn't a soldier meant to serve the people?
Dream on!
♫ Romance makes little things feel warm ♫
♫ Warmth softens even a stubborn heart ♫
♫ Heart is filled
with your little company everyday ♫
Slow down!
The water is going into my ears!
It's burning!
You're so troublesome.
Why don't you do it on your own?
I'm sorry.
I forgot that
this is Captain Liang's place.
If I won't stop talking,
I'll be chased out of the place.
What are you doing?
I'm going to get a towel.
Don't move. Let me get it for you.
I can do it.
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
Don't move.
There's a piece of hair on your face.
What's wrong with you?
I enjoy having a strand of hair
sticking on my face.
It's none of your business!
Stop moving. It's to reduce the swelling.
My mum is calling.
What does it have to do with me?
Of course it has something to do with you.
Have you forgotten that
you're my girlfriend?
Mum.
Son.
Why didn't you reply to
my text messages on WeChat?
I just came back to the camp yesterday.
I've been busy at work.
What are you doing?
Xia Chu injured herself.
Xia Chu?
She's moved out, hasn't she?
She didn't move out. She decided to stay.
I brought her back to the military camp.
I have to take care of her.
Why would I lie to you? She's here.
I'll let her talk to you.
Hello.
Hello, Xia Chu.
It's me.
I heard
from Mu Ze that you injured yourself.
What happened?
It's nothing.
I injured my ankle.
I feel so much better today.
You must rest well.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of myself.
Does Liang Mu Ze treat you well?
Liang Mu Ze...
He...
treats me quite well.
Good to hear that.
When I'm free, I'll pay you a visit.
Sure. Please take care.
That's all for now.
Mum.
Are you at ease now?
Moving forward, stop sending
ridiculous photos to the camp.
I have to go. Bye.
Good acting.
As long as you're happy.
Otherwise, you will chase me out again.
Xia Chu.
What?
I have apologised to you, haven't I?
Put it on until the swelling is gone.
Listen.
Starting from next week,
it will rain every day.
Don't go anywhere.
If you're bored
and intrigued to check out
our training process,
you may use this.
No one wants to see it.
All right, take a nap
after you blow dry your hair.
Don't get a cold.
Health documentary?
It sounds great.
Now,
the relationship between doctors
and patients has become strained.
We can provide them a channel
so that they can understand
each other better.
I think it's quite meaningful.
I support the idea.
However, in order to execute the idea,
we need to get approval
from the management department
of the hospital.
How about this?
You should come out
with a specific proposal.
Let me deal with
the hospital.
I think it shouldn't be a problem.
It helps with digestion.
Thank you.
What is bothering you?
Dr Zhang.
I would like to
ask an irrelevant question.
What is it?
Is Zhuo Ran terminally ill?
How should I put it?
When the disease is under control,
he can live like a normal person.
Once the disease is at its onset,
it can be dangerous.
Is there any way to cure it?
Reduce his stress reaction.
For example,
who called him the other day?
What was the conversation about?
Try to avoid the same
from happening again.
It's quite impossible
to cure it once and for all.
What's wrong?
Something urgent came up.
Now?
I'm sorry, Dr Zhang.
Do you want to add on?
No need, I can't finish everything.
I'm so sorry. I'll pay for the bill.
No need.
Hello, sir.
Since your friend has left,
we purposely bring you
a toy bear.
Can we place it here?
You're being so considerate.
Thank you.
Sure, enjoy the food.
Sure.
Let's finish the meal
together.
Zhuo Ran.
Mi Gu?
Why are you here?
I'm here to check on you.
You were discharged
from the hospital so suddenly.
I couldn't reach you.
I'm a little worried.
How do you feel?
Have you recovered?
I've recovered.
Good to hear that.
Since you're ill,
you have to rest well.
Take good care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
Mi Gu.
Thank you for checking on me.
What on earth were you doing?
We almost got caught!
Why were you dilly-dallying?
Nothing happened, right?
Why are you scared?
Why am I scared?
We've been in China for so long.
You've been running around after Xia Chu.
I thought you're something
but we haven't even seen
her dad for once.
I'm talking to you!
Why did you go to his house
and install bugs?
Are you crazy?
Do you really think that
by wearing earphones all the time,
you can accomplish the mission
assigned to us by Old Master?
I know what I am doing.
Like hell you do!
Listen, don't put me in trouble.
I'll report everything that happened today
to Old Master.
You'll have to
bear the consequences alone.
Based on the analysis
of a jewellery expert,
the sapphire
on the deceased's walking stick
is the Cornflower Blue Sapphire
originated from Kashmir.
The mining activities
only went on for 28 years.
Therefore,
Kashmir Sapphires
that are available in the world
are really rare.
The last time
this sapphire appeared in public
was two years ago, at the world renowned
[Gem info: Cornflower Blue Sapphire
originated from Kashmir]
Sotheby's auction in Hong Kong.
A China Mainland merchant
by the name Liu Zheng Ming
won the bid
with 9,210,000 HKD.
Liu Zheng Ming
is the sugar-daddy
of the deceased, Zhou Lan
who killed herself
in the Jiao Tong University district.
His nickname is Xiong.
How much do we know about him?
In the early nineties,
he started off his business
by smuggling imported cigarettes.
He was arrested and sentenced
to prison for seven years.
After he's released,
he ventured into Chinese
herbal medicine business.
Now, he's dominated
the herbal medicine market
in the five provinces of Southeast China.
He also has business
in Thailand, Vietnam and so on.
[Gem info: Cornflower Blue Sapphire
originated from Kashmir]
Besides the sapphire
which was recorded two years ago,
we don't have any other records
about his gem collection.
It appears that
he is not a major gem collector.
As for how and why the sapphire
fell into the male deceased's hand,
we don't have any clue as for now.
A Chinese medicine merchant
is involved in two murders simultaneously.
It's not a coincidence for sure.
Judging from the situation,
to find out the identity
of the male deceased in the bungalow,
the breakthrough
is Xiong.
Put up with it.
Slow down.
All right.
you may move around.
That's great!
You're recovering fast.
Like I said,
I can remove the cast on my own.
But you insisted on coming here.
I have to do so.
I'm entrusted by someone.
Please thank
Brigade Commander Dong for me.
Brigade Commander didn't send me here.
It's been raining for a week.
It's not going to stop any sooner.
Yes, it'll rain non stop.
Therefore, every year, at this period,
we'll get ready for war.
Did you receive a new mission?
As the Buddha said, it's a secret.
All right, I have to go.
How about this?
I'll leave some medicine for you.
If I have to go on a mission,
you can apply the medicine
on your own.
Okay, thank you.
I'm leaving.
Is the entire Special Forces Brigade
getting ready for war?
Yes, we're preparing for war.
Team Lightning is getting ready too.
Captain Liang is included.
I'm leaving.
Brigade Commander!
I propose to pass through
the highland side.
It's pouring. I worry that
we might get struck by lightning.
What if we run into a mudslide?
We go through field battle training
on a daily basis.
It's okay.
No doubt it's safer
but how about the speed?
You might be okay with the route
but can the other units catch up with you?
Let's go!
Attention.
Speed up!
Let's take the lead
to pave the way for the other units.
Make sure all of you
take safeguard measures along the way.
Make sure all the units pass safely.
Reply if you receive my message.
Noted!
Hurry up. Stay safe. Hurry!
This is Team Lightning speaking.
Attention, all units.
Speed up and stay safe!
Before five o'clock,
all of you must reach the assembly point!
Go!
Be safe.
-Squad leader.
-Liang.
Are the stewed ribs ready?
It's ready.
As per the Brigade Commander's
instruction,
it's braised on low heat.
Take a sniff.
-It smells good.
-It smells good, right?
-Yes.
I'll take it with me.
Slow down. Don't burn yourself.
I haven't added salt in it.
It's okay. It's good.
It's all right.
-Slow down.
-I'm leaving.
-Don't burn yourself.
-Thank you.
Great. Slow down.
Let me check on
my saviour.
Are you okay?
You're so cool, Liang Mu Ze.
Of course.
Let's get ready for dinner.
Yes!
Our captain
is really something.
Listen, besides catching you,
he's also good at other things.
Not only is he good at diving,
parachuting, rock climbing, and skiing,
he's also good at close quarters combat
and emergency rescue communication.
He can speak three languages
and handle all kinds of vehicles.
He's the top soldier in the army.
He can do things that others cannot.
For example,
metamorphosing and lip reading.
No one in the army is his match.
Nobody can better him.
In that aspect,
he's definitely the best.
Are you writing a novel?
You're even more interesting
than a novel.
I didn't know that you can read lips.
Just a bit.
Anyone can mistake us for a couple
except for you.
For a long time,
I couldn't even stand it
when someone mentioned
the phrase, "special forces soldier."
Let alone start dating again.
Can you teach me?
No.
Dr Xia.
There's a long way to go.
Finish the soup.
Yes.
You too.
Finish it while it's still warm.
-It's quite flavourful.
-It's so bland.
It's so delicious, captain.
I've never had such delicious soup,
captain.
Well done.
I was being impatient.
Why did you bring out the case?
I'm leaving tomorrow.
My leg has recovered.
Has it been a week?
Yes.
Are you sure you've recovered?
Report!
Captain, I suddenly recall
I have to attend to something urgent.
I have to go.
Don't leave yet.
You haven't finished eating.
Dr Xia, it's quite urgent.
I have to leave now.
Continue eating.
You don't have to send me off.
I'm leaving, captain.
Continue eating.
Is Lieutenant Tian
trying to make space
for us to spend time alone?
Thank you for taking care of me
for the past few days.
I'll replace wine with soup.
Cheers!
That's all?
Don't you have anything else to say?
Like what?
You bought a bouquet in my name
and you haven't apologised to me.
Well,
I was being nosy.
However, I still don't get it.
Why did you get so angry?
Just because Xiao Jun's mum
doesn't like flowers?
She likes flowers.
However, it has nothing to do with me.
Both of you...
It's been so many years.
You've been taking care of them.
So what?
Does it have to involve a love affair?
Do I have to date her
and marry her?
What if I'm taking care of them
as Luo Liang's comrade?
I'm just pretending to be Xiao Jun's dad.
I'll take care of them and protect them
until Xiao Jun grows up,
until he's grown into
an independent adult,
until they don't need
my protection anymore,
until he can protect his own mum.
Is that not allowed?
I'm not avoiding it.
It's to the contrary.
I'm facing it.
I got it now.
Liang Mu Ze.
I didn't mean to
embarrass you on purpose.
Firstly,
as Xiao Jun's doctor in charge,
I don't want him to get
emotionally agitated.
It will affect his recovery.
More importantly,
I don't want you two to let
each other slip by.
I know the feeling.
I mean,
letting each other slip by
when the feeling is mutual.
It's
quite disheartening.
Therefore, I promised Xiao Jun
to buy a bouquet in your name.
However, I didn't expect
it would bother you that much.
I'm sorry.
I was full of myself.
That's why I misunderstood you two.
Have you experienced it?
Pick up the call.
I think so.
How about you, Liang Mu Ze?
Have you ever let anyone slip by?
Do you feel regret?
No.
I never let anything slip by.
That's why I don't have any regrets.
Eat up.
Have some pork ribs.
You are what you eat.
Listen.
I...
In that situation,
I felt as if
there was a huge bulb on my head.
Did you feel awkward?
It's so awkward.
Lieutenant Tian.
What is the relationship between
Captain Liang and Dr Xia?
What do you think?
If they are really a couple,
she seemed upset
when we called her Mrs Liang.
If there is nothing between them,
why did Captain Liang
bring her back to camp?
She stayed here for so many days.
Xiang Yang.
"The west is veiled in rain
while the east enjoys sunshine."
"My gallant is as deep in love
as the day is fine."
Xia Chu.
My mum wants to see our photo.
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
It's not going to work!
You promised me before.
No doubt I promised you before
but...
Look, this photo is so ugly.
You took the photo from the bottom.
That's the most tricky angle.
Furthermore,
my face looks huge in the photo.
It's also taken against the light!
I look at least three shades darker.
Captain Liang, look at yourself.
Would you smile?
What kind of expression is that?
We are so far apart.
We don't look like
a couple who are crazily in love.
If you send the photo
to your mum,
she won't believe in us.
What should we do?
Let me teach you a lesson, Captain Liang.
Liang Mu Ze, come forward.
My face looks huge. Hurry up.
One, two, three, cheese!
Captain Liang, can you put on a smile?
Stay still, don't move.
One, two...
Close your eyes and enjoy life.
This is not okay.
I look silly in this photo.
Be happy, okay?
You look happy.
My mum will think that I've gone crazy
if she sees this.
Do I look crazy?
Taking a photo is so tiring.
It's even more tiring
than going for training.
It's not that tiring.
Since we're pretending,
we have to put in more effort
to look real.
All right, it's done.
Send it to your mum.
♫ Romance makes little things feel warm ♫
♫ Warmth softens even a stubborn heart ♫
We look so real
even though we're pretending.
♫ Heart is filled
with your little company everyday ♫
What if it becomes true?
It's none of my business.
♫ Can't miss a thing about you,
hence there is no regrets ♫
♫ Getting used to your habits
from breakfast to dinner ♫
Do you really enjoy
working in the hospital?
Of course.
Just wait.
I'm so busy with training.
We need to get ready for war too.
I don't have the time to fetch you.
I have legs.
You mean, your broken leg?
I'm a military officer too!
I won't fall behind
even when I lose my flesh and skin.
I'm not as fragile as you think.
Here, let me show you something.
Come here.
See for yourself.
It's pouring.
It's difficult to travel.
How do you plan to go back?
I...
I can drive.
I have a driving licence.
Drive?
What are you doing?
How do you drive?
It's for the sake of your safety.
Be good, Da Miao.
Good girl.
Liang Mu Ze!
If you ever pinch my face again,
I'll chop the 27 bones in your hand
into pieces!
Brigade Commander.
Yes, I'm Liang Mu Ze.
I would like to get your permission
on something.
I'm coming. Stop knocking the door.
Change into the military uniform.
Ten minutes later,
go to the assembly point.
Why?
One, two, three, four.
What's wrong?
You have to run.
What?
Either you run
or you train with them.
Me?
Yes.
Liang Mu Ze, are you crazy?
Hurry up. Do it.
Why?
It's for your own good.
You're not my leader.
Why should I listen to you?
Brigade Commander said
it's just a minor accident
but you injured your leg.
That means you lack training.
Hence, he applied to your superior
to include you in the training
as a non-staff.
What?
It's to strengthen your stamina.
He doesn't want you to get into danger.
But...
Let's go.
I'm an injured person.
You've fully recovered, right?
Let's go.
I can walk on my own.
Here, run now.
Keep running.
Let go of me. I can run on my own.
Run on your own.
Keep running.
One, two, three, four.
Xia Chu, I'll beat you up if I catch you.
-I'm coming.
-I can run on my own!
Stop following me!
When you're in danger,
you should run at first instance, got it?
Watch your arms. Swing your arms.
Keep it low.
Don't stop. Keep running.
I can run on my own!
Try it.
I have to practice shooting too?
It's an order from Brigade Commander.
I've only used a rifle before
when I was in recruit company.
Stand here.
Hit the humanoid target at the front.
Here.
Aim carefully.
Liang Mu Ze, I've never used a gun before.
A gun is not much different from a rifle.
Adjust your breathing and relax.
♫ We'll have ups and downs ♫
♫ The journey to happiness is bound
to be filled with waves ♫
Don't be nervous.
♫ I'm glad we came through the
obstacles that time has brought upon us ♫
Hold the gun firmly.
♫ My hands are still eager
to hold you tight ♫
♫ Nothing matters as long as
our smiles outweigh our tears ♫
♫ Others can doubt me as long as
I have your trust ♫
What do you think?
Liang Mu Ze, look!
If you connect the bullet holes,
♫ Our souls cross paths
as our gaze meet ♫
you can see a heart shape!
♫ Some words you can understand
even if I don't say it ♫
Do it again.
♫ I promise I won't let you slip by ♫
♫ Exchanging everything, we'll become
each other's destiny ♫
Liang Mu Ze is a jerk.
He trained me as if I'm a soldier.
He claimed that he didn't shout at me.
♫ I'll make your heart my kingdom ♫
♫ You and I will make our dream
come true with our lives ♫
Assemble!
One, two, one!
Comrades.
Lately,
the Southeast region of our country
has been experiencing
heavy rain and flood disaster.
In order to protect
the people and their property,
we've been instructed
to aid the disaster areas.
The fighting is going to begin soon.
I only have one requirement.
Confront the danger.
Help and protect the dyke.
Before the rain stops, we won't give up!
Got it?
Yes!
Let's go!
Turn to the rear.
Start marching!
Captain!
Take care!
Take care, Liang Mu Ze.
I'm back.
-You're back.
-Come here.
-Has your leg recovered?
-Are you okay?
I'm okay. I've fully recovered.
-You've recovered.
-What are you doing?
-Reading the flood fighting news.
-Look.
They've been immersed
in the water for many days.
It's stated in the news that
many troops
are rushing to the areas.
Xia Chu.
Dr Zhang.
You're back.
How do you feel?
I've recovered.
I can start working anytime.
That's great.
Is my hairstyle all right?
Dr Zhang, you're...
I'm filming a show.
There is a lady by the name of Mi Gu
from the life channel.
Do you know her?
I know her. She's my best friend.
She wants to produce
a medicine related documentary.
I'll be the main character
in the documentary.
Please work with her.
Don't worry.
Is she single?
Dr Zhang!
Dean.
Allow me to introduce someone to you.
He is Deputy Dean Zhou.
Hello, Deputy Dean Zhou.
Thank you for
being interested in the hospital.
You're so kind, Dean.
We would like to thank you
for supporting our show.
That's our duty.
This is...
I don't think
there's a need to introduce him.
Hello.
We decided to film the signing ceremony
at the eleventh hour.
Sorry to have...
I'm sorry. I need to answer a phone call.
Xiao Wen, please communicate
with the other leaders
and Mr Zhuo
regarding the filming details.
Okay, Ms Gu.
Thank you.
[Xia Chu]
I changed Xiao Jun's dressing for you
and you promised
to prepare two weeks worth
of medical orders.
Please honour your words.
It's an honour
to set up a special fund
with the hospital.
We will develop 3D medicine production,
organ printing,
auxiliary instrument printing and so on
in full swing.
We believe that
following the rapid development
of 3D printing,
we will welcome
the new era
of personalised medicine.
Take some scenery shots
in the hospital later.
Sure.
I hope everything
goes according to plan.
-Goodbye.
I'll see you off.
How long will the filming take?
Let's go for dinner tonight.
Should I wait for you?
Are you not going to join
the photography session?
Why should I join?
He's young and talented.
I'm sorry.
Please hold on.
Mi Gu.
Let's go for dinner tonight.
I'll invite Xia Chu too.
Dr Zhang, please join us.
Sure.
I have something to do at night.
Well...
Dr Zhang, don't we have a date?
I'm sorry. I forgot that.
We have a discussion.
I'll not take up your time then.
I'm leaving.
Why did you do that?