[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 36]
He got high on anaesthesia.
He is talking nonsense.
But you feel happy after hearing it.
Who's talking nonsense?
I'm Sailor Moon.
In the name of the Moon, I'll punish you!
Oh my.
Isn't this Sailor Moon's catchphrase?
I can't believe
I'm hearing this
from a special forces soldier.
Did you teach him that?
No. I...
No.
Sailor Moon
is
a couple gift from her.
Liang Mu Ze.
A set of Sailor Moon bed sheet.
Liang Mu Ze, keep quiet.
Bed sheet?
No.
You don't need to explain it.
Your dad is here.
He's waiting at the door.
What are you doing? Just go.
Check his body temperature.
His face was hot just now.
Xia Chu.
I love you.
Stop it. Captain Liang.
Let me check
your body temperature.
Where did you come from?
I came from my mother's womb.
Why did you come here?
What do you think?
After receiving the call from your unit,
I was frightened.
So I asked your grandpa to contact
the leader at your war zone.
When I heard that you're safe
and have completed the exercise,
I came to see you immediately.
You asked Grandpa for help?
It's all because of you.
I can do everything
for you.
So...
Does Mum know about it?
I dare not tell her.
Although I normally do things slowly,
when a big problem occurs,
I am very clear-headed.
I've informed your grandpa.
So she won't know about this.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You have your own life.
I can't
make decisions for you.
But
you have to think carefully
about it.
I've thought about it.
However...
However?
If
I don't become
a great doctor
who makes history,
will you be disappointed?
I
have overcome
many difficulties in life.
So many.
To me,
I only have one most important
masterpiece.
And that is you.
So
since the day you were born,
no matter what job you do,
be it a success or failure,
my answer
remains the same.
I want to join Liang Mu Ze
at his outpost.
Life is short.
I hope
you will be happy.
Life can be long too.
So
you must find carefully
the one who will be your life partner.
But
don't worry about making mistakes.
Dad and Mum will always be with you.
Got it?
Yes.
Thank you, Dad.
I will be very happy.
The moon is lingering...
Brigade Commander.
Don't sit up.
Just lie down.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I had some allergies.
I'm fine now.
What about you?
I'm fine.
I just had a few stitches.
Good to hear that.
Actually
the command post told me
that the foreigner who got caught
mentioned about Tian Yong.
This is the photo
given by the police.
It's confirmed
that he is
the commander.
What's the matter?
Do you know him?
His name is
Zhuo Ran.
He's Xia Chu's first love.
He was missing since 18 years old.
He just came back
to the country this year.
You're right.
When he was missing,
he was using another identity.
He was in the military
and have been at war.
He's the most valuable mercenary
in the world right now.
One of the representatives
in the foreign armed forces
is a former comrade in arms.
What is his other name?
Pei Yu.
You're not the first one
who said that I'm lucky.
Who else?
He was not a comrade in arms.
Before you,
he was my only failure.
Who is this guy?
Pei Yu.
The higher-ups gave order
to have liaison between
the police and the military
for a full search.
Is there any news?
As of now,
we are stepping up the search.
Your mission
is to focus on recovery.
[Miss Mi Gu, I have received
the amended proposal.]
[What shall we do next?]
[Mi Gu.]
[Do you have 10 thousand RMB?]
[I'm doing a business with my friends.]
[I still need some money
to join the partnership.]
[You must help your brother.]
[Call him before weekend.]
[Help him to achieve his dream
to start a business.]
[Miss Mi Gu, are you feeling better?]
[Mi Gu.]
[I found someone else
to manage your programme.]
[You take a rest at home.]
I'm warning you.
Don't call me again!
[Mi Gu.]
Zhuo Ran?
Is that you?
[Yes, it's me.]
Did anyone follow you here?
No.
I have deleted
the address that you sent to me.
I've applied a long leave.
May I know the reason?
Let's go to the hospital.
Zhuo Ran.
I'm cold.
So cold.
♫ I'd like to find out ♫
♫ If my mask of foolishness ♫
♫ Could deceive you ♫
♫ I'm putting on my best performance ♫
I'm cold.
Mum.
Why did you only take my brother with you?
You're unfair.
Are you going to abandon me?
Don't leave me.
Don't go.
Don't leave me here.
I won't go.
I won't leave you here.
The Training Unit
and Public Security Bureau
has confirmed his identity.
According to their analysis,
it's highly possible
that he came back to the city.
They have asked us
to do a thorough investigation.
[Find out his whereabouts]
[as soon as possible.]
Yes, sir.
Unit One.
Continue to track Tian Yong.
Unit Two, follow me.
Yes, sir.
Xia Chu.
Xia Chu, there is a problem.
Liang Mu Ze's condition is not good.
Go have a look.
Sir.
How is he now?
He has high fever.
He also has indirect muscle spasms.
From my initial findings,
his wound is infected.
Infected?
I've taken his blood sample.
I will take it to the hospital
for testing.
Xia Chu.
Don't stand there. Hurry up.
What?
Send him back to the hospital.
The condition here is not ideal.
Yes.
Let's do it together.
Don't worry, Commander Dong.
I will report Captain Liang's condition
to you.
Thank you, Xia Chu.
Dad, I'll get going.
Go.
Be careful.
[According to the test results,]
[Rescue Room]
[it should be
Acinetobacter Baumannii infection.]
[We have sent Liang Mu Ze]
[to the emergency room.]
[After several consultations,]
[we put on high dosage of sulbactam]
[and combined with tigecycline.]
[We hope it can control]
[the bacteria in his body.]
Is it controlled?
We are unable to confirm that now.
After some time,
we will do an analysis
of the bacteria in his body.
Only then,
will we know if the medicine is effective.
So...
If it is not effective,
what will happen?
We have prepared several plans.
If this doesn't work,
we will try another plan.
He should have changed jobs.
If he hadn't joined the exercise,
he wouldn't be injured.
His wound wouldn't have been infected too.
Enough.
Don't have to say it.
Sir.
Madam.
I'm sorry.
I didn't
take care of Mu Ze.
It's not your fault.
He's an adult.
He should be responsible
for his decision.
Liang Ren Dong.
You're so heartless.
Director Song.
Can we visit him?
His body is very weak now.
It's better not to enter the ward.
I understand.
We won't enter the ward.
We will look from outside.
Sure.
Xiao Xiao.
Did I wash my hands
before stitching the wound?
I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
Of course, you don't remember it.
You don't have to remember it.
It's a classical conditioning
in every surgeon.
It's impossible that you will forget.
Please.
Don't be so paranoid.
They are still checking
why he was infected.
There is no conclusion yet.
Why do you take responsibility
for that?
Do you want more conflicts to happen?
I...
Hello.
[Xia Chu.]
[Director Chen wants you and Xiao Xiao]
[to come to the meeting room.]
Now?
[Yes.]
Sir, Xia Chu reports.
Come in.
Sir, are you looking for me?
Where is Xiao Xiao?
She was stopped by
the patient's family members.
She will be here soon.
Let's start.
Recently,
there have been
two surgical site infection cases.
It's caused by Acinetobacter Baumannii.
First patient, Liu Ran
has passed away.
And now, the patient
is Liang Mu Ze.
Currently,
he is in emergency intensive care unit.
We are not sure what will happen.
If
the first case was an accident,
then we have to
take the second case
very seriously.
Today,
I have invited
all the resident doctors here
not to criticise anyone
or
to hold someone accountable.
I just hope that we can gather
and listen
to other's experiences
in clinical treatment.
So that you may benefit
and improve yourself.
Xia Chu.
You go first.
You have dealt
with both patients.
Especially Liang Mu Ze.
You stitched his wound.
What's your opinion
about his infection?
Did you
overlook anything
when you were treating him?
Xia Chu.
Mr Zhou is talking to you.
To be honest,
I have been
asking myself this question
in the past two days.
Outdoor...
During war...
In that setting,
it may not be possible to achieve
a germ-free situation
like in the hospital.
I'm worried that this happened
because of my careless mistake.
But it wasn't.
When I was treating Liang Mu Ze,
I am certain
that I was very careful.
There wasn't any operational problem.
Sir, Xiao Xiao reports.
Come in.
Xiao Xiao.
You were at the site during the rescue.
What's your evaluation
on how Xia Chu treated the patient?
You witnessed the entire process.
You were the bystander.
Perhaps you saw other details.
All I can say is that
she was very serious
but she wasn't calm.
I don't think this is
how a professional doctor
should be when treating a patient.
So
about the prevention of
Acinetobacter Baumannii,
do you have any opinion?
We can discuss.
Okay?
[You knew what happened.]
We have been through
a life-and-death situation.
Of course, I know.
That's why I asked if you could do it.
You said you can.
You insisted to put the stitches for him.
I understand
that you wanted to save him.
But you weren't calm, were you?
[I thought we were friends.]
I don't know what
your definition of a friend is.
I treat you as my friend.
That's why I want to tell you that
when you're facing this patient,
you personal feelings have taken over
your professional ethics.
When Mr Zhou
asked me about my opinion,
I voiced out my intuition.
I didn't want to lie.
I didn't ask you to lie.
You just had to keep quiet.
Isn't this your forte?
I know you want to be
the chief resident doctor.
I never thought
that you would think that way.
[Xia Chu.]
Mr Zhang.
Are you busy now?
It's regarding Mu Ze's medical condition.
His condition is bad.
I really want to save him.
But I don't know
what else I can do.
Sir, please teach me.
Please teach me.
♫ Whatever evidence ♫
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I hang in there ♫
♫ I know love will surely come, someday ♫
[Dear Professor Ye Jun.]
[I apologise for contacting you
out of the blue]
[I'm a doctor from]
[Hospital 109 of
the People's Liberation Army.]
[I tried calling your office phone number
but couldn't get through.]
[I've sent you an SMS
but you didn't reply.]
[I wonder]
[if you've received my previous email.]
[The patient's condition
is deteriorating.]
[He is starting to have septic shock.]
[He is in coma]
[and has hallucinations.]
[These are signs of impending death.]
Stay calm. Let's just wait.
I don't understand.
It's just bacteria.
Bacteria are found everywhere.
It's impossible
that it will take my son's life.
It has mutated
and become drug resistant.
All the antibiotics that we could get
don't work on him anymore.
Must you use antibiotics?
Can't you think of other method?
Besides antibiotics,
I don't believe
there's no other method
that can kill the bacteria.
Lower your voice.
Say something.
Aren't you doctors?
I'm sure you have other methods, right?
-Calm down.
-I can't.
Bacteriophage.
What is it?
Bacteriophage
is bacteria's worst enemy.
It's a special group of virus
that parasites on
selectively target bacteria or fungus
and replicates within bacteria.
It eats
and kill bacteria from inside.
It uses physical attack
so there isn't
antibiotic resistance problem.
As long as we find
the relevant bacteriophage,
it can kill the Acinetobacter Baumannii
inside his body.
Impossible.
There are many types of bacteriophage.
How do we find it
in such a short period of time?
I've contacted Professor Ye Jun
from Ke Hua University's
Biology Lab Center.
His lab
is doing research on phage therapy.
They have collected
many types of bacteriophage.
Moreover,
Acinetobacter Baumannii
is on their research list.
He is willing to provide
the phage therapy plan.
Phage therapy?
We have thought about it too.
But it is not part of
mainstream medical practice.
The rise of antibiotics
has completely pushed it aside.
Even if you have
this treatment plan,
you won't be able to get approval
from the department in charge.
We may face the risk of breaking the law.
Brigade Commander, Mr Dong Zhi Gang,
has submitted a request
to the higher-ups.
They will try their best
to talk to the department in charge,
and get a special arrangement.
What is the progress of the phage therapy
in their lab?
There is a successful case study.
How many cases?
One.
If the phage therapy has problems,
are we going
to lose him forever?
Since he joined the military,
we have lost him.
It's not the same.
I know he is with the special forces.
Even though I didn't see him,
I felt ease.
I...
I dare not think about it.
I dare not.
Let's not
do the phage therapy.
It's too risky.
Believe in him.
He will make his own choice.
Braised Egg.
Can you put on a smile?
I've told you
that you look nice when you smile.
Now,
you must be suffering.
Memory cleared.
Do you feel better now?
Do you still remember?
When I was being held hostage,
I was so scared
and you said to me,
"Do you trust me?"
"I'm here"
"so you will be fine".
This time,
I ask you to trust me.
I'm here.
You will be fine.
As long as we are together,
there is no difficulty
that we can't overcome.
Liang Mu Ze, listen carefully.
During the treatment,
you might be in even more pain.
I'm afraid that this decision
is just my wishful thinking.
If
you want to give it a try,
please give me a sign.
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
I got it.
Don't worry.
I will make sure you're safe.
I've talked to my dad.
He will use his network
in the medical field
to convince
the heads of relevant department.
We hope to get the approval earlier.
How's the situation on your side?
Professor Ye Jun has successfully
grown phages.
The treatment is all set.
Once we get the approval,
we can carry out
the treatment immediately.
[Outpatient Department]
Noradrenaline.
Add 30mcg per minute.
Atropine, 0.5mg.
-Prepare CPR.
-Yes.
Zhi Gang.
How is it?
I got it.
Thank you for your hard work.
All right.
What did he say?
There is no result yet.
He plans to meet the higher-ups
to hurry them.
Sir, the first batch
of bacteriophage is here.
Leave it there.
Perhaps
we still have to wait a little longer.
We can't wait anymore.
The patient's blood pressure, pulse
and oxygen saturation level is low.
After the shock,
he is now unconscious.
If we wait longer,
he will suffer organ failure.
We must carry out the treatment now.
We have not received the approval yet.
Director Hao.
We have signed the consent form.
We stand firm on our decision.
No matter what the outcome is,
we will accept it.
We will not blame the hospital.
Look.
Shall we give him
the medicine first?
Yes,
I understand your feelings.
But this treatment
is special.
Without the approval from higher-ups.
I'm afraid...
Dr Hao.
Liang Mu Ze is having high fever again.
What?
Xia Chu.
Xia Chu, what are you doing?
Dr Xia.
Please leave for a moment.
Xia Chu.
Open the door.
Xia Chu, open the door.
Xia Chu.
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Xia Chu.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
I will bear the consequences.
You...
Wait for your suspension letter.
How is he?
♫ I had a quick glance at your eyes ♫
♫ It could be the destiny
but it is not practical ♫
♫ Your expression popped up on my mind ♫
♫ I learn to face the music
instead of evading it ♫
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
[Aunty.]
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫
[The phage therapy worked.]
[Liang Mu Ze's fever subsided.]
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫