[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 11]
Captain.
Captain Liang!
What are you doing here? Leave now!
I'm here to deliver the medicine
and to give you a checkup.
I'm alright. Leave now!
How can you be alright?
Xiao Teng said you haven't slept
for days.
I'm reminding you as a doctor.
You must take a break now!
No need to!
Just take a break for a few minutes.
Send her away.
Unless you take a break,
I'm not going anywhere.
Captain, why don't you listen to Dr Xia?
So you're aware that
I'm your captain?
Send her away!
Listen, Liang Mu Ze.
You should carry out the mission
on the premise that
you take care of yourself.
You're made of blood and flesh!
I'm an occupational military officer.
I know my own body's condition.
Send her away!
Yes!
Don't touch me! Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze!
Keep working! Stay safe!
Yes!
Liang Mu Ze, let go of me!
What are you doing?
Do you hear me?
Liang Mu Ze, let go of me!
I'm getting angry!
Brigade Commander Dong!
Help, Brigade Commander Dong!
Liang Mu Ze!
Brigade Commander.
What are you doing?
Xiao Teng!
Xiao Teng, what's wrong?
Xia Chu.
Have some water.
Cool down.
Thank you, Brigade Commander Dong.
He's not gentle at all.
You need to reflect upon yourself
for what has happened today.
As long as she stays away from the dyke,
I'll reflect upon myself on anything.
If I don't go to the dyke,
will you take a break?
Is it the right time for a break?
-As I said, your safety...
-Enough!
How are things going on on your side?
No doubt the water level
at the ten mission areas have reduced
but the water level at three other areas
are still above the warning line.
Mission area number two
is the most dangerous one.
What happened?
Don't move. Let me check on him.
He came down with a fever.
Report!
Brigade Commander!
Brigade Commander.
Something urgent came up
at Dr Wu's camp.
What?
Brigade Commander,
the three patients who caught a cold
came down with fevers
higher than 39 degrees Celsius.
They have sore throats,
stuffy noses and body aches.
They also suffer from
coughing and diarrhoea.
Report.
I need to use the outhouse.
-Tian Yong.
-Yes!
-Bring him to the outhouse.
-Yes.
Brigade Commander, I must not die.
I'm the only son in the family.
He is still waiting to hand over
the family business to me.
Cut the nonsense.
Stay in bed.
Yes.
Can't you confirm the diagnosis by now?
With the equipment that we have,
I can't confirm the diagnosis.
You can report it to the superior
since there are three patients.
It's four.
We have to include the staff officer
who has just passed out.
-What's wrong, Xiao Teng?
-I'm having a stomachache.
Don't go near him.
Stay back.
Yes.
Brigade Commander Dong.
Please arrange manpower
to isolate this tent.
Before the superior unit sends someone
who can confirm the diagnosis,
besides Dr Wu and me,
everyone else
has to leave the tent immediately.
Is it really so serious?
Plague always comes after a flood,
Brigade Commander.
Observe the patients closely.
Lower his body temperature.
Yes.
Do you feel better?
I'm still not feeling well.
You're still not feeling well?
-My body is burning.
-Okay.
Now, the doctors are doing their best
to save our comrades!
We have to hold on to our post
to protect their safety!
Got it?
Yes!
It's okay, don't worry.
Don't be scared.
Finally, it's sunny again.
It's finally sunny again.
Yes.
Will they recover?
Are you scared?
Have you ever met some people in life
where you completely trust them
and will take a bullet for each other?
Have you?
I trust all of them.
Every time I bring them out on a mission,
I only have one thought.
I will make sure they're intact
when they go home to their parents,
wives, and children.
The tears of a military officer's
family are too heavy.
I can't take it.
[Martyr Luo Liang]
Meng Zhen.
Don't worry.
We'll always keep you
and your son company.
If I had a choice,
I would rather be
the person in the casket.
I don't want anything
to happen to my comrades.
That's why when we were in Isaia,
when Lieutenant Tian injured himself,
you overreacted.
It's not only because
Tian Yong injured himself.
It's also because of
your reckless behaviour
when we're organising the rescue.
The moment you lifted the robber's gun,
it's no different from committing suicide.
Do you know that?
If I didn't give it a second thought
and fired the gun at you,
I think my career as a military officer
would have stopped then.
I bet the complaint
must have caused you so much trouble.
I was number one
in the Hunter Military School assessment.
Then, I dropped to number two.
Songpaisarn got the advantage for nothing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll take it back soon or later.
How about you?
Are you scared?
Back in 2003, Ms Lan,
who was my mum,
was the chief nurse
of the General Surgery Department
of the city's best hospital.
She contracted SARS
when she was taking care of the patients.
[Though she survived the disease,]
[her health deteriorated.]
[She had no choice but to retire early.]
[Because of my mum,]
[I decided to become a doctor.]
[In the beginning, she was against it.]
[When the admission letter
was sent to my house,]
[she looked at it for a long time.]
[Then, she said,]
["Daughter,"]
["there's no turning back."]
As a doctor,
fear
is one of the human natures
that we have to get over.
Instead of feeling scared,
my urge to play my role as a doctor
at disastrous times is stronger.
I don't want to live with regrets.
As such,
no matter what,
I'll guard the dyke.
I'll stay committed
and dedicated to my job.
I'll complete my duty.
Before my comrades give up,
I'll never give up.
Being committed doesn't mean
you don't have to take care of yourself.
Something bad will happen
if you don't rest well.
Are you worried about me?
Yes.
Why?
Why are you worried about me?
I'm a doctor, Liang Mu Ze.
I can't stand it when someone
doesn't take care of themselves.
Thank you, Dr Xia.
They're back.
Brigade Commander!
Sir.
It's the W4C9 virus.
No mutation is detected.
The vaccine is already on the way.
The isolation measures
were executed just in time.
We'll wait for the patients
to be vaccinated.
Then, conduct blood tests on the soldiers.
We'll give them a talk
on prevention and control
to prevent further infection.
Let's start working!
Yes!
-Liang Mu Ze!
-Yes!
Carry out full protection!
Yes!
Come with me!
See?
As usual, you hold us up again.
But,
well done!
-Report.
-Come in.
Captain, Xiao Teng's fever is gone.
How is he doing?
He's doing fine.
Xiang Yang is taking care of him.
He's still muddle-headed though.
He kept asking me,
"Where are the angels?"
What angels?
When he came down
with the fever, he thought
Dr Xia had a pair of wings.
Have the medical team left?
Not yet, they're on the dyke.
Brigade Commander wants to send them off.
Let's check it out.
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
-Don't mention it.
-Otherwise, god knows
what would happen to the soldiers.
It's our duty.
Thank you for the hard work.
Salute!
Take care.
I'll wait for you to come home.
All thanks to the doctors,
especially Dr Xia.
She looks fragile
but she takes her job so seriously.
Not only is she professional,
she is also kind-hearted.
She is such a nice lady.
What do you think, captain?
What's wrong? Are you having insomnia?
I'm exhausted physically
but my brain keeps me awake.
These are my first sleeping pills
since I came here.
Every medicine has its side effects.
Don't...
What's wrong?
Something is wrong with the pills.
It looks like an effervescent tablet.
It dissolves in the water right away.
It melts in water.
At ease! Attention!
Look to the left!
Eyes front! At Ease.
Attention!
Later, according
to the order from the superior,
besides the injured soldiers
who are recuperating,
the rest who are
from combat battalion and Special Forces
are going to Zone Four.
Team Nine of the Special Forces Brigade
will stay back
as the reserve team, just in case.
Got it?
Yes!
It's the same formula.
The smell is so familiar.
Are you done being sentimental?
Dr Zhang.
How does leading a surgery feel?
Just like a nightmare, it's exciting!
Great.
Get ready to enter the theatre.
Now?
The heart transplant
which was scheduled earlier
had been postponed.
Of course, if you're not keen
to take part in it,
you may skip it.
I want to join.
-Sure.
-Dr Zhang.
Yes?
Xiao Xiao performed well too.
So?
She would like to watch
the heart transplant surgery.
Can both of us
enter the theatre together?
It's full.
There's only one vacancy
for a houseman.
Is there any question?
No.
All right, hurry up.
-In the next round...
-I won't thank you.
Next time, it'll be me.
This place
is a battlefield for patients.
It's also a battlefield for doctors.
Everyone who enters this place
is fighting for survival.
For life,
dignity,
responsibility,
and the irreplaceable
sense of accomplishment at work,
we put ourselves in tight spots
over and over again.
We fight hard against the God of Death.
If I chose the path
because of youth's passion,
then being persistent
throughout the journey
is because I have faith in the profession.
As the saying goes,
"The one who wants to wear a crown"
"must bear the weight."
I'm looking for a birthday present
for our daughter.
You told me
she likes dolls, right?
She doesn't like it anymore?
All right, I got it.
What is it? Say it.
No, no way!
It's not the right time.
When I'm done with my work,
I'll pay her a visit.
I don't know when I can get it done.
Stop speaking in English!
I don't understand English.
Listen...
Li Lei.
Rao Zhi, we found something.
Okay, got it. I'm coming back.
How is it?
Rao Zhi.
The information is provided by
the Intelligence Bureau.
Xiong
has been scrutinised by the narcotics
squad for a long time.
They suspect that his business
is just a camouflage.
He supplies
a type of Chinese shrub, Ephedra
which is one of the ingredients
to produce crystal meth
to drug cartels abroad.
Have the narcotics squad taken any action?
Not yet.
They haven't figured out
the mode of communication
and the transaction channel
between Xiong and the purchasers.
Just like us,
they're monitoring him.
Channel?
The City of Desire?
[Completing invasion]
[Please send the information
to my mailbox.]
Xiao Xiao, let's hang out tonight.
I can't make it. I'm on duty.
How about Xiao Chu?
I'll pass. Something happened at home.
I heard that front line flood fighters
have left the disaster area.
I guess your beloved military officer
is coming home, right?
He's not mine.
As for his whereabouts,
you have to ask him.
Goodbye, everyone.
Have fun!
She's so impatient.
Welcome home, Captain Liang.
I left my key in the military camp.
Take it.
What is this?
Give me a hug.
You bought custard steamed buns!
Yes, I crave it.
That's why I bought an extra portion.
♫ Heart is filled
with your little company everyday ♫
Finally you're back.
I've missed you so much!
♫ Can't miss a thing about you,
hence there is no regrets ♫
♫ Getting used to your habits
from breakfast to dinner ♫
♫ Spending every minute to stay with you ♫
Liang Mu Ze.
You should smile more frequently.
You look quite handsome when you smile.
How shallow.
Come join me for dinner
after you have unpacked.
♫ Liking your habits,
remembering small moments ♫
♫ Infecting sorrows with smiles ♫
♫ Getting used to what you like,
trying to be brave ♫
♫ Liking becomes natural
and turns into a habit ♫
♫ Even though it's simple, my heart
still fills with deep emotion for you ♫
I do look quite handsome.
How long will it take?
Should I start cooking?
You may cook now! I'm almost done!
♫ We're trying to keep it natural
and romantic at the same time ♫
♫ Every time we slow down,
the whole world is filled with love ♫
♫ Can't miss a thing about you,
hence the path is simple yet dazzling ♫
♫ Liking your habits,
remembering small moments ♫
♫ Infecting sorrows with smiles ♫
♫ Getting used to what you like,
trying to be brave ♫
♫ Liking becomes natural
and turns into a habit ♫
By the way,
I prepared some pills for you.
Take one tablet
when you're having insomnia.
Don't overdose.
Every medicine has its side effects.
What's wrong?
Something is wrong with the medicine.
I'll leave Er Miao with you. Let's go.
Custard steamed bun will be ready soon.
Did you cook those dishes?
No, they're cooked by Ms Snail.
What a lame joke.
I love cooking.
Why?
Human heart is located above the stomach.
The way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
Is it scientifically proven?
Please trust the professional judgment
of a cardiac surgeon.
So much for professional judgment.
Have some soup.
[Have you taken the pills I gave you?]
[I took one.]
[You...]
[Did you notice anything?]
[What is it?]
You're indeed a straight guy.
Nothing.
How many days will you stay?
I'm going back to
the military camp tomorrow.
All your comrades are back, right?
Yes, they're back.
Good to hear that.
I was under the impression
doctors take life and death lightly.
I don't know about others
but I...
I don't have the talent
to take it lightly.
When I was undergoing rotation
at the Obstetrics Department,
there was an old pregnant woman.
She couldn't give birth to the baby.
She held my hand and said,
"Doctor, it's too painful."
"I don't want to do it anymore."
Two minutes later,
she passed away due to
amniotic fluid embolism.
Her husband
while carrying the newborn
burst into loud sobs.
I never knew
a man could cry for so long.
That was the first time
I witnessed the death of a patient.
Until now, I still vividly remember
the moment she lied
on the operating table.
I always feel that a hand
is holding me down.
No matter how difficult it is,
she motivates me to run forward.
[I'm sorry.]
Five years ago, I went to Yunnan
for residency training.
I received a phone call from home
informing me that
my grandma was terminally ill.
I applied for leave and rushed home.
When I reached home,
my grandma was already unable to talk.
However, when she saw me,
she got agitated. She cried non-stop.
I don't think I would ever
understand how she felt.
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what I could do.
I sat at the bedside.
I held her hand
and sang her a song.
So, my grandma passed away
as I sang.
Then, I could feel the warmth of her palm
slowly disappearing.
In the end, it turned completely cold.
But at that moment,
I was really calm.
Yes.
Calm.
[Why are we talking about this]
[all of a sudden?]
You started it first.
However,
it's okay to talk about it.
Military officers and doctors
are two occupations
that are close to death.
We understand death.
That's why we cherish the moment.
When we're alive,
we won't miss out on
any wonderful moments.
Am I right?
You are afraid of missing out.
Do you want some?
Does it go well with Chinese cuisine?
I like it.
We deserve to take a well-earned break.
We can have some liquor.
Just a sip.
Bourbon Whiskey.
It's Matthew's favourite drink.
Who is that?
He's a detective
in Lawrence Block's novel.
When I was in high school,
a new student joined our class.
He sat beside me.
Under his influence,
I started reading detective novels.
He said
he wanted to be a detective novelist.
However,
due to the harsh reality,
he didn't realise his dream.
He said he wanted to be
a National Defence Student
and contribute to society
by joining the special forces.
Back then,
no matter what he said or what he did,
I always thought that he was right.
However, one day,
he disappeared from school.
I couldn't find him anywhere.
I didn't know where to find him.
I couldn't do anything besides reading
the detective novels he got me one by one.
Then, I bought more novels from
the book store.
I even hoped that
one day,
in one of the detective novels,
I could see his name, Zhuo Ran.
He is now neither a novelist
nor a military officer.
He set up a 3D printing company.
He's now a business owner.
I have retained a habit of his
in my own life.
However, I was already 18
and our high school memories
were gone for good.
[How about you, Liang Mu Ze?]
Do you practice
someone else's habit?
No.
Your life
is so boring.
Because of his ambition,
you're not interested
in military officers, is that it?
What do you mean?
The other day,
you told him,
for a very long time,
you couldn't even stand the phrase,
"special forces soldier,"
let alone seeing one.
You eavesdropped on me?
No, I didn't.
I can read lips.
Just a bit.
However, I could understand what you said.
Cheers.
Good morning.
Did you stay awake
for the whole night again?
What say you?
You look energetic.
You have sharp eyes.
You're not humble at all, Braised Egg.
What?
I'm complimenting your head shape.
Thank you for the compliment.
What are you looking for?
"The Tokyo Zodiac Murders."
You're still reading it?
Didn't I tell you the ending?
I'll never get sick of reading you.
It feels like spring when I read you.
What are you saying?
I'm talking about the book.
What were you thinking?
It was on the shelf.
Where is it?
Do you have any plans later?
No, I don't have any plans.
I'm going to chill in the morning
before going to the hospital.
Let's take a stroll
at the furniture store.
I want to change some of the furniture.
Give me some suggestions.
Sure.
♫ The sky is smiling
and my heart is fluttering ♫
♫ Time stops as we're surrounded
by happiness ♫
♫ I always have the urge
to hold you in my arms ♫
♫ Though we argue at times ♫
♫ Though we fight at times ♫
♫ We chit-chat the whole night through ♫
♫ ​The sweetness is just right ♫
♫ We share the same taste in food ♫
♫ The sweetness is just right ♫
♫ No one knows
what triggered our first fight ♫
♫ When we think back, love is a wonder ♫
Xia Chu.
♫ Our encounter is not too old school ♫
♫ The amount of happiness is just right ♫
♫ Our connection is not too boring ♫
♫  The amount of happiness is just right ♫
♫ No one ever notices
your smiling lashes ♫
♫ We don't have to think about it
as we are destined to meet ♫
Slow down.
It's so comforting.
Finally it doesn't look like
a sample house.
Er Miao, come on, try out the new couch.
Er Miao!
You're not giving me face.
♫ The sky is smiling
and my heart is fluttering ♫
♫ Time stops as we're surrounded
by happiness ♫
♫ I always have the urge
to hold you in my arms ♫
♫ Though we argue at times ♫
I think I'm out of favour.
♫ Though we fight at times ♫
Like this?
-Like this?
-Yes.
♫ We chit-chat the whole night through ♫
♫ ​The sweetness is just right ♫
It's quite nice.
♫ We share the same taste in food ♫
♫ The sweetness is just right ♫
Come here.
♫ No one knows
what triggered our first fight ♫
One, two, three!
♫ When we think back, love is a wonder ♫
♫ Our encounter is not too old school ♫
♫  The amount of happiness is just right ♫
♫ Our connection is not too boring ♫
♫ No one ever notices
your smiling lashes ♫
♫ We don't have to think about it
as we are destined to meet ♫
What are you doing?
Do you want some?
You haven't lost all your conscience.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
You can't have it unless you tell me.
I suddenly recalled the first time
we had custard steamed bun in the store.
I had the urge to squeeze the custard
onto your face.
It's never crossed my mind.
Here.
Liang Mu Ze, that's inhumane!
Don't move!
Go back!
I didn't see anything.
The memory has been deleted.
I'll go get changed. Clean up the mess.
By the way,
don't forget to clean the litter.
Why?
Fine, I'll do it.