[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 5]
Have you seen Dr Zhang?
He's in the dressing room.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Dr Zhang!
I'm changing,
what are you doing?
Sorry! Sorry!
She's killing me.
How reckless!
Xia Chu, how inappropriate!
Just carry on and listen to me.
We might be able to use
interventional surgery
for Xiao Jun's ASD
but only if we can find a method
that is more intuitive than a CT scan
for understanding the condition
of his ASD.
I tell you what.
The most intuitive way is
to cut the heart open,
and it's the most accurate way.
And a 3D printed heart model.
3D printed heart model?
Do not take photos!
I just want to show
you the previous case.
Someone has succeeded before.
You get out first.
Get out!
[Dressing room]
Keep that in mind.
It's the men's dressing room.
I'm sorry, sir.
I was in a hurry.
Then...
Where's the case?
Look.
This is his echocardiography
and this.
Okay.
It's possible.
But I haven't done it before.
I might need to
consult with a company.
I have a classmate
who's in this line of work.
Then hurry up and contact him.
Okay.
Xia Chu?
It's me.
I have something to talk to you.
[Go ahead.]
There's a kid with
congenital heart disease.
His first operation failed.
We need your 3D printing technology
to print his heart model out
before we perform the second surgery.
To get a full overview
of the location and type of his ASD
and to practice the surgery in advance.
You may wait in there.
Boss will be right here soon.
Thank you.
Do you know the
origin of this sketch?
September 7, 2011.
It was my first day
transferring to a new school.
During recess,
someone invited me to play shuttlecock.
I was hesitant.
It wasn't that I don't want to.
Just that I was drawing
a girl with a
beautiful smile at that moment.
Hello, Xia Chu.
The CT scans and the data of
echocardiography of
the patient are all in here.
How long does it take
to complete the production?
About one week if everything goes well.
How about the fee?
It depends on the material you choose.
Will the quality of the
materials affect the
accuracy of the final model?
It won't affect much.
For preoperative purposes,
normal materials costing a few
hundred will do.
Okay, I'll wait for your call.
If you have any medical issues that
need to be communicated,
please feel free to contact me.
Xia Chu,
is it only medical
issues that I can ask?
I don't know about other questions.
And I have no time to answer that.
Are you still mad at me?
No.
That's it.
Zhuo Ran,
I am a resident.
My patients are
my first priority.
If it weren't for helping
my patients,
I wouldn't be standing here today
and have this conversation with you.
I want to spend my time
on the people and things
that are more meaningful to me.
Do you understand me?
With her attitude,
are you sure the plan
to approach Xia Guang Yuan
through her will work?
Xia Chu's attitude towards Zhuo Ran
would never change.
We just need time to rouse her.
I believe we can get what we need
through Xia Chu.
I hope so.
So far,
we can't identify
the male body in the villa.
We found an account
named Scary Pirate
in a confiscated laptop
but
it takes time to break the passcode.
So we can't confirm
whether this is related to
the founder who lurks in the drugs
trading platform.
Even if we break the passcode,
this can only mean that the person
logged into the account
named Scary Pirate in the villa.
It can't show who Scary Pirate is
or if he's related to that body.
This might be a
characteristic of a cybercrime.
Any progress on the
Jiao Tong University district case?
The name of the deceased is Zhou Lan,
22 years old,
born in Yibin, Sichuan.
She came here from
Chengdu three years ago.
She'd worked as a beverage promoter
in a club before.
She was later kept by
a man named Mr Bear.
After they broke up in March this year,
Mr Bear gave one of his properties
to the deceased,
which is the house where
the body was found
by the cleaning lady.
Has the autopsy report come out yet?
Yes.
According to the autopsy report,
basically, we can rule out
the possibility of homicide.
Zhou Lan's drowning
might be due to the
hallucination which was
caused by the consumption
of methamphetamine.
Where is the drugs' source?
We logged into an account
which she saved on the laptop.
We found that she had sent
a few posts requesting drugs in a
drug trading platform
called City of Desire.
How did a 20-year-old young lady
enter this
bottomless world?
Who is Mr Bear
exactly?
Hurry up! Keep going!
Hurry up!
Keep going! Keep going!
Hurry up! Keep going!
Hurry up! Run!
I'm a second faster
than your vice-captain.
Finish the remaining five kilometres.
Vice-captain,
are you an undercover
whom the captain sent here?
Are you a fun guy
whom the monkey sent here?
Wipe your drool.
Okay, stop hesitating!
Let's get started!
All tanks!
Five kilometres of trail running!
Double march!
Get your equipment.
I got it!
Brigade Commander.
In the last comprehensive assessment,
you set a new record
for Team Lightning.
Here's your citation.
Let's take a photo.
This isn't a first-class merit.
You're getting
greedy.
Even a field citation
can't satisfy you?
It was within our expectation.
We can get a better result
if Tian Yong hadn't cramped up.
Don't be proud!
Later on,
there will be a special combat training
for reserve officers.
By then,
all the experts will be here.
The more experts, the better.
It would be boring
if they were incompetent.
I'm quite cool.
What's the point that
I think you're cool?
You have to make the
ladies think you're cool.
Silly boy.
When it comes to girls,
I've had only one problem
since childhood.
Too many ladies are coming for me.
Are you sure about that?
Then why did your mother
send me the photos?
What photos?
No, Mother, you're a
knowledgeable lady
who has been working for years, right?
Why did you become ignorant
and old-fashioned
when it comes to your child's marriage?
Not that I don't like it.
Just that it's too many.
I need to work too.
Mother?
Now she is mad.
Report!
Come in.
Captain,
Brigade Commander said...
Here it comes again.
What did he say?
Brigade Commander asked you to
drive me to the hospital
for a re-inspection
and to visit Xiao Jun.
Noted.
You can take some.
No, Captain.
-Why did you ask me to take it?
-Don't be shy.
-No!
-Take it!
I didn't see it, really!
-Take a pick!
-I really didn't see it!
Captain!
Keep it...
Captain, I'll go change my clothes!
He was staring at it.
Captain,
You're really ungrateful.
How I wish my parents
could arrange my marriage.
And you?
You don't appreciate it
and you even keep
yourself away from girls like a monk.
What's wrong with you?
I just don't like it.
What do you dislike?
There's always a stack of photos.
Looking at the photos,
having blind dates.
It's so old-fashioned.
Why don't you just say
you don't like any of the girls
in the photos?
What's all this for?
What isn't old-fashioned?
Among tens of thousands of people,
in the boundless river
spanning tens of thousands of years,
there's such thing as being too
early or too late.
What a coincidence! You met
the one you wish to meet.
You can only ask her discreetly,
"So you're here?"
Shut up!
Do you think this will work, Captain?
Stop talking.
According to the 3D printed heart model
of the patient,
ASD runs obliquely between the lower
part of the right superior and inferior
pulmonary vein and the superior
part of the inferior vena cava.
If we use APMLATZ
septal occluder on the
model to simulate the occlusion,
the right superior
and inferior pulmonary vein
will be obstructed,
which is the same problem
on the first surgery.
If we use a PDA occluder
to occlude it,
there'll be no obstruction on the right
superior and inferior pulmonary vein
making for a tight and secure seal.
Above is the result
of the surgical trial
according to the 3D printed heart model.
I've finished the debrief.
Thank you.
Xia Chu,
prepare for the surgery.
Yes.
We don't need to cut the heart open?
But I heard Dr Zhang said
it's hard to process
with interventional surgery.
Yes, it is.
That's why we need to duplicate
Xiao Jun's heart and simulate
the occlusion on the heart model
before the surgery.
Duplicating the heart,
does it really work?
Of course.
Conventional ultrasonic imaging
with CT imaging
and 3D data test mode,
these are the latest technologies.
Have there been any
successful cases before?
Why are you here?
I'm with Tian Yong.
He's here for a re-inspection.
If this is the first attempt...
This is the first time
for our hospital.
But there's been successful cases
in other hospitals.
3D printing technology
can make a more
accurate surgical plan.
There are certain
risks in thoracotomy too.
As for the interventional surgery,
the damage it causes
is relatively minor.
Why don't you give it a try?
Trust her.
I'm in charge of tomorrow's operation.
You failed in the first operation.
Interventional surgery is
the field of cardiology.
Rest assured.
For a surgeon, an interventional surgery
is nothing new.
What about this?
It's more intuitive
with this.
What are you doing?
It's not our first time to kiss.
Enough.
We've broken up for years.
Why did you do that?
Did you do that to
your resident too?
Which resident?
Xia Chu.
How is that possible?
You're ridiculous!
Let me tell you,
I've stayed away
from all my colleagues
since we broke up.
I knew
you'd regret
breaking up with me.
Why don't
we get back together?
Stop! Stop! What are you doing?
I don't...
Don't tell me
it's all because of an operation.
It's a huge operation
that might
break new grounds for clinical medicine.
Li Juan,
you haven't changed a bit
after all these years.
Have you changed?
I am responsible for my patient.
I thought you would
oppose this operation.
A doctor told me.
When a patient is
on the operating table,
the person who wishes for
his safety the most
is the doctor.
True.
Is the 3D printed heart model reliable?
It should be performed
by a cardiologist if it has to be done.
One more time.
This operation won't work.
Why not?
We've studied the patient's
3D printed heart model thoroughly
and the surgical plan
is well-established.
What remains is
seriousness and patience.
There will be no problems.
Zhang Yi Chi is going
to perform the repair of ASD.
Notify the anesthesiologist
and extracorporeal circulation
to prepare for the repair of ASD.
Yes, Dr Zhang.
Dr Zhang,
use model 26 PDA occluder.
We've tried it many times.
Its umbrella is more stable.
You can't go wrong.
Sir,
please don't give up.
Try it again.
Open model 26 PDA occluder.
Yes.
Dr Zhang.
It's successful.
We had a little trouble while occluding
the ASD at first,
but then at her insistence,
we promptly
replaced it with a PDA occluder,
and it worked.
Thank you!
And Dr Xia.
Thank you very much!
You guys really
are angels, thank you.
Okay, you can rest assured now.
I have to drop by the emergency room.
Go on, you go on.
I'll get going.
Dr Xia
told you that, didn't she?
Yes.
You work this hard
just for an operation?
It's not about the operation,
it's for saving the patient.
Then how do you feel
about reclaiming the patient?
A patient is not a prize.
Don't use the word "claim."
I tell you what, Xia Chu.
Every resident in this hospital
wishes to take part in the surgery.
We work hard to show our strengths.
I finally got a chance
but you easily took it from me.
You took advantage of me.
I'm enough with your sweet-talk.
Do you know
how annoying you are?
Easily?
I only slept for
ten hours in seven days for this model.
I kept researching, practising
and recording data
during this period.
From the operation in the morning
to the handover,
I didn't even have time to eat.
I'm so sleepy and hungry
I could vomit,
but I keep going, why?
Because someone told me
not to give up on
my patient until the last minute.
I made it.
Now, I'm really happy.
Your likes and dislikes
are meaningless to me.
I didn't come to this hospital
to please you.
Why are you here?
You haven't eaten, right?
Laoyou noodles, without spices.
Your favourite taste.
You don't have to be like this.
Did the surgery go well?
Yes.
The model is useful.
Thank you.
That's great.
Eat the noodles.
I'll leave first.
How are things going?
Xiao Jun hasn't come out yet.
I'm in the middle of something.
Dr Xia, you're awake.
Dr Xia, you've worked hard.
Can I help you?
Nothing.
Have you
found a place to stay?
I'm still searching.
I've been working overtime recently.
I have no time for it.
Then stop looking.
Just live in my house.
What?
Really?
Yes.
You're not that generous, Liang Mu Ze.
There's a condition.
Okay.
You didn't even ask
what the condition is.
I'm fine with everything.
Nothing is more important
than one's life and death.
Okay then.
Date me.
What did you say?
To handle my mother.
Just faking it.
Liang Mu Ze, are you crazy?
How could we pretend to fall in love?
Definitely not.
Did you spread
the information about me having a son?
I...
I didn't mean to.
My mother forced me.
I had no choice.
She always tries to set us up.
If I don't get firm with her
and put a stop to it,
she'd never stop nagging me.
You did wipe it out of
your mother's mind.
But my mother is
dying to take girls to my unit.
What should I do?
Isn't that great?
No.
I really can't pretend to fall in love.
Moreover,
what if you really fall in love
with me?
Just worry about yourself.
Me? Why should I be worried?
I'll fall in love with you?
Are you kidding?
By your silence,
I assume you accept it.
I ate.
A dose of public display of affection.
Liang Mu Ze, don't be like this.
What if someone sees us?
You made me nervous.
Why are you so nervous, Dr Xia?
I...
I'm just shocked.
By the way,
why must you ask me
to trick your mother?
You live in my house.
And you refuse to help me?
It must be you.
Senior.
[Where are you?]
I'm in the hospital on
afternoon break.
[How about tomorrow?]
I have a night shift tomorrow.
What's wrong?
What's up?
[Professor Zhao of the
Military Medical University]
[had three consecutive
operations yesterday.]
[He died of acute myocardial
infarction on his way home.]
[Can you stop by?]
Okay.
Wait for me,
I'll be right over.
Deal?
What's wrong?
One of my professors
at the Military Medical University
died of acute myocardial infarction.
Where are you going?
To the airport.
I'll give you a ride.
I booked the 2 p.m. flight.
You don't have to pick me up.
Just send me the address.
I'll go there by myself.
Okay.
[Mr Zhang, I'm off.]
[Something's up, I'm
going back to my hometown.]
[I'll be back before
tomorrow's night shift.]
[Just a few days
before his retirement.]
His greatest wish
is to retire
to travel the world with his wife
to make up for the time
he's owed his family due to work.
Mrs Zhang is a high-school
geography teacher.
The farthest place they'd ever been to
was Yellow Mountain,
which they visited on their honeymoon.
Every time I go to Mr Zhang's house,
Mrs Zhang will take out
the photo and tell me
they would go to
Yellow Mountain again
after Mr Zhang retires
to see the clouds.
He's gone just like that.
Let's go.
I think it's stuck.
Let me take a look.
Done.
-Go.
-Thank you.
Do you have money?
I do.
Then
I'll get going.
Go.
About pretending to be your girlfriend,
I'll promise you
if it's a genuine need.
We'll talk about it when you're back.
Selling point!
It must have a selling point!
The reason why
the last issue became a hot topic...
3D printing company?
Mi Gu, what did you say?
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening.
So
you think
it's in a 3D printing company?
This is my way of thinking
about this problem.
This is the power of modern technology.
Good.
We'll do this.
Leave it to me.
[Mi Gu, please cover]
[the topic of 3D printing for this issue]
[as soon as possible.]
[I'm looking forward to it.]
[Hello, I am Mi Gu.]
[I'd like to meet up and]
[talk with you about 3D printing.]
[Are you free?]
[I'm sorry. The user you're calling]
[is not available.]
[Can you contact Zhuo Ran for me?]
[I'm looking for him.]
[I've met Mrs Zhang.]
[Everything is fine.]
[Thank you for giving me a ride.]
[Friend request]
[Special Forces: Accept]
[Set note and tag]
It's rare.
You proactively add a friend.
And it's a girl.
Can't I do that?
You can.
Is she extraordinary?
No.
But she is a doctor,
she saved Xiao Jun.
How long have you been living together?
Not even a ten-thousandth
of the time we've been together.
Well played.
Why do I feel that
you treat her differently?
What's the difference?
Look.
To send her to the airport,
you left me in the hospital
for so long.
You put off rejoining the unit
and
you have to take the risk of
being lectured by Brigade Commander.
Isn't the reason sufficient?
Isn't that obvious?
You're giving a reason
to scold you if you
don't drive faster.
Yes, sir!
It is hard to meet,
but hard to part too.
As the east wind wanes,
all the flowers fade.
Silkworms won’t stop spinning
silk till they die.
Sericulture is the new way to get rich.
Drive fast.
Xia, are you back?
I left the snow mushroom soup
on the table.
Drink it.
Miss Lan.
Girl, you're back. You scare me.
I thought it was your father.
Have you eaten?
I'll cook for you.
Never mind.
I've eaten.
You've eaten?
You didn't have your first meal
at home when you're back.
Where did you eat?
What did you eat?
Miss Lan,
I want to sleep with you tonight.
Silly girl,
you're past the age
to act like a baby.
Look at it.
How long since you've
cleaned your ear wax?
Don't move.
Home is the best, right?
Don't leave then.
No.
I still need to work.
You're
like your father.
You're a workaholic.
Has Father been busy recently?
Sure.
He's so busy that he's been gone
for three weeks.
Where did you two go
for your honeymoon?
No honeymoon.
Your father was summoned
by the research group the day
after our wedding.
Don't move!
Then you two must go on
a trip when father retires.
I'll pay for you.
You'll pay for us?
What can you do for us with your
starvation wage?
Just
take good care of yourself,
that would be enough for me.
I'm doing fine.
Right.
Why did you come back
all of a sudden?
Did someone bully you in the hospital?
No.
Were you not satisfied
with your new house?
No.
You've got a boyfriend?
Stop being ridiculous.
I'm sleepy, let's sleep.
You...
You stupid girl.
You always avoid me
when I talk about something important.
Avoid me, will you?
Why did you want to go that far?
I worry when you're away from home.
I worry when you're back home.
You think that I'm naggy
and you refuse to listen to me, don't you?
I can only worry by myself.
You'll know it one day.
You'll know it when
you become a mother.
That whether every mother
in the world is the same.
I'm fine.
I just missed you guys
and wanted to come home.
I shouldn't have
allowed you to study medicine.
You're right.
What's good to study medicine?
But I like it.
What should I do?
[Military University Professor died of
sudden heart attack due to overwork.]
I'm back!
Er Miao.
Do you miss me?
Look what I've got you.
Liang Mu Ze?
The combat zone is organizing
a special training for the reserve force.
It'll last for 20 days.
We're allowed to go home
during the weekends.