[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 38]
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Really, I'm fine.
I didn't expect
I'd be the one
to send him to the police station.
Right after he said
he wanted to take me to his mother.
Why did things end up like this?
Why?
It's not your fault, Mi Gu.
I know.
It's not my fault.
It was him who'd been lying to me.
He's guilty.
He deserves to die.
He should be punished.
But I'm very sad.
Xia Chu,
I'm envious that
you met the 18-year-old Zhuo Ran
instead of the current Pei Yu.
But they look alike.
They really do.
I think I'm dying.
You won't die, Mi Gu.
Life always has ways to hurt us
but these wounds
will eventually become
our strongest bit.
I pulled through.
I'm sure you'll make it.
♫ Let it be, I'm once again
close to tears ♫
♫ An unfamiliar street,
a cruel heartbeat ♫
♫ Time stops, tears are meaningless
in this moment ♫
♫ All I want is a hug ♫
♫ Drunk on your lips ♫
♫ It's the trickery played by hormones ♫
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
[Outpatient Department]
♫ We'll have ups and downs ♫
♫ The journey to happiness is bound
to be filled with waves ♫
♫ I'm glad we came through the
obstacles that time has brought upon us ♫
♫ My hands are still eager
to hold you tight ♫
♫ Nothing matters as long as
our smiles outweigh our tears ♫
♫ Others can doubt me as long as
I have your trust ♫
♫ Our souls cross paths
as our gaze meet ♫
Does it look nice?
A living person
killed himself while
killing others.
He can only live
as another person
for the rest of his life.
What kind of feeling is this?
No love and hatred,
no relief,
until time consumes him totally.
No one can really
understand this kind
of feeling except the person themselves.
Liang Mu Ze,
do you remember what you promised me?
It was on this same roof.
Never give me a chance to revive you.
Don't break your promise again,
Liang Mu Ze.
♫ It could be the destiny
but it is not practical ♫
♫ Your expression popped up on my mind ♫
♫ I learn to face the music
instead of evading it ♫
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
Liang Mu Ze,
what do you like about me?
I like you
when you sing off-key
but you're comfortable with it.
What about you?
What do you like about me?
I like how you're being fearless.
Actually, I'm afraid.
What are you afraid of?
Take a guess.
Being on a mission?
Getting hurt?
Killing people?
I'm afraid of...
I'm afraid of losing you.
We're made for each other.
Dr Xia,
thank you.
Thanks for letting me know
it's great to be alive.
Liang Mu Ze, I want to sing a song.
Go ahead.
But what if I sing out of tune?
I'll accompany you.
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ To relive the moment
my heart skipped a beat ♫
What's the time now?
He keeps asking the time.
We predict that
he might have a deal with Old Master
on when and how they make the drop.
Have anyone contacted him from
last night until now?
No.
But at the scene where we arrested him,
he was logging in to the City of Desire
and had posted on the forum.
What was the content?
"I've got the stuff,"
"waiting for the wind."
The stuff he meant
might be the information
he wants to get
or
the related clues.
What did he mean by
"waiting for the wind"?
Old Master.
Zhuo Ran succeeded.
But
he asked you to hand his mother
and Tian Yong over to him.
We got news from Dong'an,
It's impossible that he got
the information of the project.
The narrative of
"he got the stuff"
must be false.
Why did he lie
to Old Master?
For all I know,
his mother disappeared
with him back then.
I'd asked Xia Chu.
It's true that his mother is not well.
Looks like she's got a heart condition.
I'm thinking if it's possible that
Old Master forces him
to work for him
by threatening him with his mother.
The reason why he's refused to
denounce Old Master
is probably because
of his mother's safety.
He wants to wait for the wind.
Just let him wait and
send the video of Tian Yong going
through withdrawal to him.
Let's see who lasts longer.
-Yes.
-Let's go.
This is a video on City of Desire
our comrade at the technical team
had seized last night.
Upon initial analysis,
it's a reply to
Pei Yu's post from Old Master.
But it remains unclear
why they filmed Tian Yong.
Based on the image detail capturing
and the manor's floor
plan provided
by the local police,
we guess
Tian Yong might be detained in the
basement of the manor
and it's possible
that he's been injected with drugs.
Commander Dong,
listen to me.
We've reported the current situation
to our superiors and
we've intensified the
interrogation of the accomplices.
After we get the statements,
the orders from the superiors
and set up cooperation
with Willick's police,
we'll conduct the
extraction immediately.
I'll apply to my superiors
for joint operations too.
This is a debt
they can't ever repay.
This is
Tian Yong?
What's wrong with him?
He's being controlled
by the drug dealers.
Brigade Commander sent me this video.
The drug dealers drugged him.
Then
what now?
Waiting for the notice
of the superiors.
I can't do a thing!
Liang Mu Ze.
Calm down.
Morse code?
I'm wondering
if we should have some
unexpected
methods for communication.
You know, just in case
-you're taken captive someday.
-Get lost.
[Why aren't you the one taken captive?]
Okay.
I understand.
Xiao Qiang,
-contact the expert on telegraph now.
-Yes.
Play it again.
Slow down.
What did he mean?
Three Hundred Tang poems.
Rao Zhi, is the message
related to the Three Hundred Tang poems?
Three Hundred Tang poems.
Tian Yong is back!
What are you doing?
Tian Yong gave me this.
It's going to save Tian Yong's life.
[Rao Zhi,]
[I found the clue that
Tian Yong left in the book.]
These might be the
username and password.
Try typing them in.
I got the evidence.
Old Master's records.
He got the evidence.
Old Master,
Tian Yong is dying.
Any word from Zhuo Ran?
No.
Tell him
I'll kill every single one
he wished to protect
when the time comes.
Yes.
[You have to go.]
[No one can cover you.]
You sure?
[Yes.]
[They're coming for you.]
Understood.
How is it?
It has been decoded.
[That's great.]
Xia Chu, I'll park my
car at the hospital.
You drive it home after work.
What about you?
[I need to return to the unit.]
So soon?
You're still recovering.
You have a mission?
Time is running out, Xia Chu.
Just go.
I'll wait for you.
[Once again,]
[I lost track of Liang Mu Ze.]
[Just like every parting before,]
[I don't know where he was headed,]
[and I don't know when]
[we will meet again.]
[I didn't even have
energy left to feel sad.]
[While he's fighting for his comrades,]
[I'm fighting my own battles as well.]
[The border between China and Willick]
How is it going?
When we arrived,
Old Master had already run away.
Lieutenant!
Who did this?
Xiao Teng!
Tell me who did this!
Who did this?
Calm down!
I'd kill him myself
if I know who did this!
Lieutenant!
Willick's police said
Old Master was gone
when they arrived.
What do you think about
this treatment programme?
Sir.
There are two seriously wounded in
the Emergency Department.
We found a tumour on
the heart of one of them.
We need to you check on her.
Xia Chu!
Xia Chu.
Patient, Zhuo Mei Qin.
Her electrocardiogram shows
sinus rhythm,
ST-segment elevation
on V4 to V6 leads.
Class II to III on classification
of cardiac functional.
Combining with CT scan,
we found that she has
enlarged heart with
left ventricular aneurysm.
Have you had any treatment before?
Son.
I want to see my son.
Who is her son?
Is he here?
We haven't seen him.
Her son is Zhuo Ran.
Rao Zhi,
am I supposed to tell you
about Zhuo Mei Qin's condition?
Yes.
How is she?
The patient
has been diagnosed with
brain death.
What do you mean?
She is currently under
precarious conditions.
The initial diagnosis
might be ischemic cardiomyopathy.
It's the most serious stage
of coronary heart disease.
And she has old myocardial infarction
with left ventricular aneurysm.
She may die anytime.
We've used every
resuscitation methods
we have on him.
But he was
in shock for too long,
so his
advanced neural center
is gradually dying.
Next,
his brain stem function
is going to waste away
until irreversible termination
appears.
There's only one way now.
Heart transplantation.
Heart transplant?
She wants to see her son.
So it's
meaningless to
keep reviving him,
it would only make him suffer.
You need to decide
as soon as possible.
I...
I need to ask my leader.
[Is there no other way?]
[Does Tian Yong]
[have someone he wishes to see]
[or]
[does he have an unfulfilled wish?]
Mu Ze.
Mu Ze, what's wrong?
Who is that?
Tian Yong.
What's wrong with him?
Go in and take a look.
Where are you taking me?
To the hospital
to see your mother.
Tian Yong.
His heart is beating.
He is currently on life support.
Then just keep supporting him!
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
Get up.
I'll read you poetry.
I've finished memorizing
three hundred Tang poems
by using the method you taught me.
I memorize one poem each time
the sand in the
hourglass finish flowing.
The time really does pass quickly.
Guess what.
I like Bai Ju Yi the most.
His poems are very simple.
Even I can understand what he wrote.
What about you?
Who do you like the most?
I guess it must be Li Bai.
You are both passionate and sincere.
You're the reason I'm able to know
this many poets.
You must be joking with me,
right?
Mu Ze,
did I do something wrong?
It shouldn't be.
I did as you said.
I've been staying in the military camp!
Why is he still lying here?
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I hang in there ♫
♫ I know love will surely come, someday ♫
Currently, there has no
beds in the Cardiac Surgery ICU.
So we put the patient in here
to closely
monitor her condition.
Dad.
How could he be like this?
He didn't even say goodbye!
It's okay.
Dr Xia,
please get him changed.
Okay.
Follow me.
Mu Ze,
I'll take Xiao Xue outside.
Let's go.
What did he
experience along the way?
I don't dare to think about it.
Then stop thinking.
I'd rather you know nothing.
I can't do it, Dad.
I can't do it anymore.
You're lucky, Captain Liang.
The one lying in there
is not so lucky.
Liang Mu Ze!
I'm warning you.
Don't mess with my man
if you want to save your mother!
Sun Xiao Mo.
Are you all right?
Pull yourself together!
He deliberately provoked you
just to see you lose control.
It's a liberation for him
if you beat him to death.
Is it worth to commit a crime for
that kind of person?
I'm going back to the department.
Liang Mu Ze.
Just cry it out
if you're sad.
What does death feel like?
Does it hurt?
Or does it feel cold?
It's like
being sent off by the
people in the world
and picked up by the heavens.
It's a problem that
everyone of us has to face.
We've got to face it.
Just that we are
destined to face more of it
and be influenced by it
than others.
[Give me back my OK!]
-I have to go in and find OK!
-Stop your ruckus!
OK!
I'm here to pick you up!
I warn you. Do not make loud noises!
♫ Sadly, I always have delusions ♫
♫ Let it be, I'm once again
close to tears ♫
♫ An unfamiliar street,
a cruel heartbeat ♫
♫ Time stops, tears are meaningless
in this moment ♫
♫ All I want is a hug ♫
Tian Yong?
Are you all right?
♫ Drunk on your lips ♫
♫ It's the trickery played by hormones ♫
Will you kiss me within five minutes?
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
Absolutely not!
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
I guarantee it with
my ethic as a soldier.
Then do you
want to
try the taste of my lip balm?
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
It's a lead-based product.
I'll get poisoned if I eat it.
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
♫ Sadly, I always have delusions ♫
♫ Let it be, I'm once again
close to tears ♫
♫ An unfamiliar street,
a cruel heartbeat ♫
♫ Time stops, tears are meaningless
in this moment ♫
♫ All I want is a hug ♫
♫ Drunk on your lips ♫
♫ It's the trickery played by hormones ♫
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
[Let's take a photo.]
[Right here?]
Yes.
Or you want to go to
the Civil Administration?
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
Hold on.
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
[Are you home?]
Dad.
It looks like Tian Yong
has been sending me messages.