[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 39]
From the x-ray,
the bypass inserted into her heart
through the coronary artery bypass graft
is blocked again.
Her cardiac function is weak.
The ventricular wall is thin.
It may rupture at any time.
Heart transplant
is her only
and last resort.
[Forgo treatment]
The donor
is Tian Yong.
The available organs include
heart, lungs,
and two corneas.
As for the liver and kidneys,
as he's been injected with drugs
when he's alive,
it's led to
varying degrees of damage.
The other organs
have been
assigned to
the matching recipients.
Now,
the main issue is
the recipient of the heart.
The registered patients
waiting for heart implants
total seven people.
The most critical patient
is Zhuo Mei Qin who was admitted
on the day before yesterday.
However, based on
the information provided by the police,
she's the mother
of the suspect known as Pei Yu.
The latter
was one of the accomplices in the gang
which Tian Yong worked
as an undercover agent in.
Her son committed a crime.
It's nothing to do with the mother.
The police
want us to try our best
to cure his mother.
Organ donation is one thing,
donating the organ
to the mother of a criminal
is another thing.
To Tian Yong and his family,
it's too cruel.
He doesn't have a family.
I think
everyone should be rational
when we deal with the issue.
Zhuo Mei Qin is a patient.
I'm her doctor.
I want to save her.
It's as simple as that.
Let's vote.
Those who are agreeable
with the heart implant surgery,
please raise your hand.
Dr Zhang.
I'll serve as an external assistant today.
All the best.
Salute!
Let's pay tribute to Tian Yong.
Get ready to open the chest.
Pass me the scalpel.
First and second assistants,
get ready to hold retractors.
Get ready for the surgery.
Yes.
Do you know
who
will be receiving his heart?
I have no idea.
However, it must be someone
who is in dire need of his heart.
Someone needs his heart.
That's great.
However, he's gone.
In this world,
I can never find anyone else like him.
Be careful, pass it to
Dr Chen as soon as possible.
Get ready for the heart transplant.
Officer Rao.
We found this
in Tian Yong's body.
We assume
it's something you're looking for.
The surgery has ended.
Thank you for the hard work.
It's been eight hours.
Thank you for coming
to show us support.
That's my duty.
You've worked hard.
Many knives see blood
when they're used to murder a person.
However, only the scalpel
sees blood when it saves people.
Why do you come to the hospital?
Are you not feeling well?
No.
We're here to send Tian Yong off.
In that case,
where are you going?
Xiao Jun wants to pay Xia Chu a visit.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Well...
Xiao Jun.
You must be hungry, right?
I saw Xia Chu just now.
She's still busy at work.
I think it'll take a long time.
Why don't we find a place
for some food?
Mum.
I'm hungry.
This is the restaurant.
After entering the restaurant,
you guys may get a table first.
Okay.
Let me know what you'd like to eat.
I'll get the food.
Let me do it.
You have no idea what I like.
Let's go.
-Let's sit here.
-Sure.
Xiao Jun has grown taller.
Yes.
Kids grow really fast.
I heard from Xia Chu that
you're going to Beijing soon.
The first draft of my script
has been approved.
I enjoy working with
the company too.
Coincidentally,
a classmate of mine
went to the company.
He's in charge of production.
He wants to take me in.
I think
I can give it a try.
What about your bookstore?
My parents have just retired.
I'll leave the bookstore to them
so that they have something to do.
Will Xiao Jun go along?
Yes.
I've found a boarding school for him.
It's great.
As a script writer,
you'll get more opportunities in Beijing.
Yes.
How about you?
Are you all right?
I mean is your body all right?
I'm all right.
Well,
I won't die any sooner.
I met Dr Zhang today.
Which Dr Zhang?
Dr Zhang Yi Chi
who was initially a heart surgeon.
You mean the one
who contracted Hepatitis B, right?
That's a shame.
I think
he's not as handsome as before.
How about his former girlfriend?
Which girlfriend?
Who else?
I only know Li Juan.
Isn't their relationship
going on and off for a few years?
Then, a married lady with a son
ruined their relationship.
Are you serious?
Let me tell you.
I was under the impression
that they broke up
because Dr Li went abroad.
It's true.
For a short period of time,
that lady went to the Department
of Cardiothoracic Surgery very frequently.
She claimed that
the son was getting treatment
but she was actually going after Dr Zhang.
Later, when she found out Dr Zhang
contracted Hepatitis B,
she left immediately.
She's so materialistic.
No wonder Dr Li resigned.
If I were here,
I would leave too.
I think
it's not about falling out of love.
It's absolutely
a humiliation.
I'm sorry.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm Zhang Yi Chi.
I heard your conversation.
It seems that
all of you are quite concerned
with my love life.
Dr Zhang.
We...
You have nothing better to do.
If
your work life is going well
and your love life
is going smoothly,
I'll forget about it.
However, if your own life is a mess,
then please
don't pry into
other people's private lives, okay?
All of you are just my former colleagues.
You're not my mum!
Why are you worried for me?
Xiao Jun.
Here.
You're right.
No doubt she is
married.
Furthermore,
she has a son.
Her lover sacrificed eight years ago.
He's a martyr.
Listen.
It's because of
the sacrifices made by the martyrs,
we get to
live in peace.
That's why you have the privilege
to sit here
and gossip about others.
Compared to those martyrs,
I am nothing.
You're
even worse than nothing.
Keep your nose
out of someone else's business!
Let's go, Xiao Jun.
No, I haven't eaten.
I'll buy you a feast.
Xiao Jun, let's go.
Are you not going to wait for Xia Chu?
Send me a text message
when you reach home.
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
What is it?
Why Dr Li and you
didn't get together in the end?
How should I put it?
Perhaps both of us
thought that we were too smart.
We thought too much.
We were too cautious.
We were afraid of getting hurt.
We were afraid it might not work out.
And so,
it didn't work out.
I'm not afraid.
Our flight
is next Friday, at 3 p.m.
Have a safe journey.
Sure.
Come here.
Listen.
You're a man.
You should know what you should do.
[Outpatient Department]
Thank you.
Who received Tian Yong's heart?
You're still here.
I've just completed the procedure.
When the military truck is here,
we'll send him back.
Will there be a memorial service?
The organisation is making arrangements.
Where will he be buried?
The Martyrs' Cemetery.
He will be Luo Liang's neighbour.
You haven't answered my question.
I'm sorry.
I can't answer the question.
Organ donation
has to be carried out
in strict confidence.
The identity
of the donor and the recipient
should not be revealed.
Is it Zhuo Mei Qin?
I saw both of them
go into the theatre together.
All I can say is,
today's the first time
I feel upset
over a successful surgery.
You've worked hard, Dr Xia.
[We have mastered]
[the evidence
of Lu Wen Long's criminal activities.]
[There's nothing much you can say.]
If you insist on keeping quiet,
then you'll lose the chance.
How is my mum doing?
The surgery was a success.
A week later,
she will be discharged from the ICU.
How did you ascertain my identity?
We found out through
the clips from the TV station.
Later, when you barged
into the drill site,
a foreign military officer recognized you.
According to him,
when Pei Yu
served as a foreign military officer,
he had a heart attack
for unknown reasons.
It's such a coincidence.
When you came back
in Zhuo Ran's name,
you had a heart attack too.
Then, we obtained a report
from the hospital where Pei Yu was born.
We found that one of the pregnant ladies
was Zhuo Mei Qin.
She gave birth to a pair of twins.
Initially, we suspected
you're the twin brother
of the deceased, Pei Yu.
Later,
when we searched through
the underground of your company,
we found that the password to the door
was set as
910218.
That's Pei Yu's birth date.
Compared to Zhuo Ran
who was born at midnight
on February 29,
he was born three minutes earlier.
You can pretend all you want
but your subconscious
has betrayed yourself.
Hence, we assume that
in the crossfire
which happened eight years ago,
Zhuo Ran died
but you survived.
Pei Yu.
[I have told you everything]
[that you want to know.]
Now let me ask you a question.
You are the founder of City of Desire,
Scary Pirate.
Am I right?
Yes.
Why did you build the platform?
It's due to loneliness.
Loneliness?
It's unfair.
[I am the only person in the dark.]
[I'm drowning.]
The order in the world
ought to be changed.
The internet
is a fascinating soul.
However, inherent to it
is an ugly flaw.
I'm the person who found the flaw
and made good use of it.
If everyone is a criminal,
then committing crime
is not a lonely journey.
Just like you.
You eliminate sins
to get acknowledgment.
However, once the acknowledgment
ceases to exist,
you will become depraved too.
Becoming depraved together
is a wonderful experience.
Wonderful?
Yes.
Those people who died in the suicide game
must be
really thankful for me.
Turns out this is
how you hypnotise yourself.
I can tell you without hesitation.
To me,
I'm not eliminating sins
to get acknowledgment.
I'm doing it for my wife and daughter.
Even though everyone is against the idea,
even though they don't understand it,
I'll still do the same.
That's because I'm a husband
and a father.
I want them
to live a safe and peaceful life
under the sun.
Even if everyone commits crime,
it doesn't mean you have to do it.
It also doesn't mean that
I will tolerate criminals.
For a scum like you,
I'll arrest you every time I see you.
I won't let go of you.
I'm a scum.
[Have you ever thought about it?]
[One day soon,]
[when your mother wakes up]
[and find out about the things
that you have done,]
[how would she feel?]
You...
Don't agitate her.
Then tell me Lu Wen Long's whereabouts.
I'm not sure of that.
However, I know that
he has a hiding spot in the country.
Where is it?
I can bring you there.
Whale.
The target is approaching the port.
Got it. We're ready.
I don't believe that
he would work with us.
Boss is waiting for you.
Old Master.
I'm here.
What took you so long
since you have obtained the information?
I need to shake off the Chinese armed
forces who have been following me.
Have you done that?
I found a scapegoat.
Where is the thing?
How is my mum doing?
She's doing well.
She's waiting for you to go home.
Hu.
Don't do that.
I thought
you wouldn't give me the chance.
Am I so not reasonable?
As long as you listen to me...
I've always been obedient.
Let me do it.
After my dad died,
I've been treating you
as my spiritual father.
I risked my life for you.
I killed for you.
The list goes on.
I did everything
hoping to live a stable life in exchange.
I want my mum to live well.
The signal is gone.
Something is wrong.
They must have found out about us.
That's why they block the signal.
Attention!
Move!
I've been so careful.
I've been staying low to the ground.
I'm worse than a dog.
However, it's not enough for you.
You hope that I can be like my father
who died without a resting place.
Am I right?
I've told you many times.
Your father
was killed by the Chinese armed forces.
When the accident happened,
to be honest, I was very upset.
However,
the Chinese armed forces told me that
the person who shot my dad to death
was you.
The Chinese armed forces?
They told you that?
Why?
What do you think?
It's to instigate me for sure.
You're already surrounded by them.
Old Master.
You must be crazy.
If you kill me,
your mum won't live any longer.
Where is my mum?
Tell me!
All this while,
you've been controlling me with my mum.
I've had enough of it!
Let me tell you.
Without me,
you and your mum
would have died a hundred times!
Just like your scum of a father,
you're not being grateful!
Let me tell you.
All these years,
I treated your father like my own brother.
I brought wealth to him.
I shared prosperity with him.
However, behind my back,
he attempted to steal my goods!
I gave him a chance.
However, he refused to return the goods.
I really...
I really gave him a chance.
He pushed me too hard!
He deserved it!
Let me tell you.
If you kill me,
the Chinese armed forces
will not let you off.
So,
it's true that you killed my dad.
Zhuo Ran.
I'm getting old.
You're the only person who I can trust.
You're overly ambitious
but you've never let me down
in any way.
Am I right?
I've decided.
If we ever escape,
I'll pass everything to you.
Okay?
All mine?
Yes.