[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 29]
Go and get a CT scan.
You might get the result
in the morning at the soonest.
Okay, thanks, doctor.
Doctor.
Why did you push me?
I'm letting the doctor see my scans.
Well, get in line.
It's my turn.
Sir, wait outside.
After I'm done with him,
I'll talk to you.
Heard that?
The doctor told you to wait outside.
Doctor,
Director Yue introduced me
to come see you.
Who cares who introduced you?
I could say the hospital dean
introduced me.
Watch what you say, mister.
Are you a civilised human?
Are you even human?
What's this ruckus? Stop arguing!
Get out of here if you want to argue.
Doctor!
Please get me a number.
Are you the patient?
The patient is outside.
Get them in.
I can't. They can't walk.
I said, get the patient in here!
If they don't come in,
how am I supposed to check?
Argue here and there!
What is there to argue?
Doctor, are you okay?
Dr Zhang...
Doctor.
You have a nose bleed, doc.
A nose bleed.
Don't just stand there. Get help!
-Doctor.
-Dr Zhang.
Shut up.
Get help!
I'm a military man.
I won't give up.
Chen Meng Zhen.
I won't give up on you.
[Liang Mu Ze, are you free right now?]
[I need a favour.]
Meng Zhen.
Is it about Zhang Yi Chi?
I can't stay put.
Who are you kidding?
I still have to do my rounds.
I need to operate.
Patients are waiting for me to save them.
-You people are interrupting my work.
-Son!
Yi Chi, your condition is serious!
You need to rest.
-You hear me?
-That's right, son.
Listen to the doctor.
Take the medication first.
I am a doctor.
I'm the chief physician.
I believe in science.
I only believe in hard data.
What illness do I have?
You have acute hepatitis.
Acute hepatitis?
You must be kidding me.
Do you know what the symptoms are
for acute hepatitis?
Will a person with acute hepatitis
be as calm as me?
Acute hepatitis causes one
to lose judgement,
to be easily agitated!
They won't be able to think clearly.
The skin turns yellow.
Yellow like jaundice.
Do I look yellow?
-Is my face yellow?
-Take a look yourself.
Am I yellow? Am I?
Take a good look. I'm...
The mirror is yellow!
-Yi Chi.
-Son!
Ms Meng Zhen.
How is he?
He's not doing very well.
Dr Zhang cut himself during an operation
and was infected with Hepatitis B.
Despite getting an immunoglobulin shot
right after,
the virus is too toxic
and it caused the onset of severe
acute hepatitis just now.
There are signs of hepatic encephalopathy
and bleeding.
He's not thinking straight
and keeps resisting our help.
What do you need me to do?
Try and keep him calm.
Make him work with us.
Alright.
Will I be able to?
Of course.
When we were administering emergency care,
he kept calling your name.
Compared to others,
I'm sure he's more willing
to listen to you.
That's why I asked Liang Mu Ze
to go and get you.
Okay, I understand.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Yi Chi, you're now the patient.
You need to quiet down.
Don't get agitated!
-Dr Zhang.
-Dr Zhang!
You can't stop me.
I don't want this.
Stop holding me down.
Mr Zhang.
Look who's here.
Who asked you to come?
Xia Chu, get her out of here.
This is an infectious zone.
You, get out!
I'll keep you company.
I'll help you get treated.
No need to be scared.
I'm not scared.
I'll stay with you.
Lie down.
Yi Chi, listen to her.
Sir.
Do you have any other input
regarding Yi Chi's treatment?
No.
Well,
I've stopped practising a long time ago.
Besides,
internal medicine isn't my expertise.
We'll do as you see fit, all right?
Meng Zhen is here.
What about Xiao Jun?
He's with a neighbour.
He knows Dr Zhang is sick.
He told the mum
that he'll be good
and that he can take care of himself.
A mature boy.
When will Yi Chi
be able to wake up?
I don't know.
Acute hepatitis
has a survivability rate
of 50 to 70 percent.
Right now, we're using an artificial liver
to get rid of the toxins in his blood.
Currently, this is
the most effective method
to treat acute hepatitis.
But...
But what?
Each time, 50 percent of his plasma
has to be removed.
This means that
a series of allergic reactions
and potential risk of infection
are highly likely.
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I hang in there ♫
♫ I know love will surely come, someday ♫
♫ Whatever evidence ♫
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I hang in there ♫
♫ I know love will surely come, someday ♫
-Come in.
-Rao Zhi.
The chief wants you at the meeting room.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Xiao Xue.
I have work to do.
Wait here.
Mu Ze will send you home later.
Okay.
Dad.
All the best!
Thanks.
Tian Yong.
Assistance from
the Special Forces Brigade.
Rao Feng.
Captain of the Criminal Investigation
Division of Public Security Bureau.
An experienced officer on fieldwork.
He's currently in charge
of the task force.
Good day, sir.
You've read the materials?
Yes, sir.
I also did some extra research.
On what?
Reporting.
Triad rituals and social network.
From now on,
you may skip the 'reporting'
when speaking.
Yes, sir.
No need for the 'yes, sirs' too.
Where's your hometown?
I don't know.
I'm an orphan.
I grew up in an orphanage.
Are you married?
No.
A girlfriend?
Do you have one?
No.
The bait we left
on the City of Desire
has gotten a response.
The Scary Pirate
has accepted our proposal for a deal.
We've confirmed a date and venue.
Bear in mind.
The goal of this operation
is not an arrest.
It is to assist our internal operations
set the trap.
to determine
Scary Pirate's real identity
and find the mastermind
behind the ID,
Old Master.
Any questions?
No.
Yes.
I'd like a smartphone.
I'm so tired.
I shouldn't have come back with you.
I didn't ask you to come back.
You yourself didn't want
to go to the unit.
If Tian Yong isn't there,
there's no point for me to stay there.
By the way, Tian Yong
was shot, right?
How is he now?
Did he get it checked?
He hasn't been going to the hospital.
He wouldn't answer my calls too.
Has he gone back to the unit?
Is there a new mission?
Can't you call him
and help me get in touch?
Just worry about yourself.
Don't bother Tian Yong unnecessarily.
When did I bother him?
I'm just concerned about him.
When are you going back to the US?
I'm not.
Xiao Xue.
The explosion that happened
isn't as simple as it seemed.
The culprit dared
to do something so brazen.
It means they're prepared.
You get it?
Although the neighbourhood
is now under police watch,
but as long as you're here,
your dad must be worried.
So tell me where Tian Yong is.
I'll go to him.
No.
Why?
What why?
Why should you go to him?
I'm his girlfriend.
Has Tian Yong accepted you?
His girlfriend?
You're just a girl.
You can't decide on your own.
Well, has Xia Chu accepted you?
You're also pestering her.
Who said Xia Chu hasn't accepted me?
No need to pretend. I know the truth.
You two aren't really together.
You're just putting on a show for Aunt.
You guys live in one house
but sleep in separate rooms.
There's no tension either because
you're useless
or she's sick.
Listen up, Liang Shao Xue.
There are many types of love.
For Xia Chu and I,
we are...
the kind that love
with reason.
Well, Tian Yong and I are
the kind that doesn't need proclamation
to act on it.
He doesn't have to admit it.
I know I'm in his heart.
Where do you get the confidence from?
You're not
What's the matter with you?
Your love is real love,
but mine isn't?
It's my love, my feelings.
It doesn't concern you.
If you won't stop putting me down,
I might just tell Aunt
about your fake relationship.
I dare you to try.
I will. Try me.
Where are you going?
To the hospital.
Dr Zhang.
It's okay.
What do you need, Dr Zhang?
I want to check on the patients.
Dr Zhang, in your condition,
I don't think it's a good idea.
Don't worry.
I'll be careful.
I'll keep my distance.
What?
Face mask.
Here.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hello, Dr Zhang.
Is the director here?
Go and get him, quick!
Bed 21's patient's heart has stopped!
What's the situation?
Dr Zhang.
Doctor, he's in critical condition.
I've pressed the alarm.
Director Chen should be here.
Where do you feel unwell?
I'm having shortness of breath.
The pressing is making it worse.
Stop pressing.
I can't stop, sir.
His heart will stop if I stop.
Listen to me and stop pressing.
You see this?
The electrode sheet fell off.
Okay, keep calm.
Relax.
You're okay.
Okay.
The signal is back, right?
I... I thought...
Sorry, doctor.
Don't be so absent-minded next time.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Everything is fine.
I remember you.
You're the doctor with acute hepatitis.
What are you doing in our ward?
Acute hepatitis?
Hear me out.
Stay away from me!
Don't come close!
Is that true?
-Yes, it's him.
-Don't worry.
Don't come near. Stay away!
Stay away!
Don't come near.
Xia Chu.
Ms Meng Zhen.
Yi Chi is missing.
Isn't he in the room?
I fell asleep.
He was gone when I woke up.
Don't be alarmed.
Dr Zhang is in
a stable condition.
He should be all right.
He probably stepped out
for some fresh air.
Xia Chu.
What is it?
Dr Zhang is in a bit of trouble
at the cardiovascular ward.
Director Chen wanted me to come get you.
Let's go there.
Director Chen.
We are sick people.
Our immunity
is at its weakest.
How could he simply enter
our ward like that?
What if we got infected?
He has Hepatitis B.
That's an incurable disease!
Don't you know that?
Now, now. Please calm down
and let me speak.
Yes, Dr Zhang did
contract the hepatitis virus
during an operation.
But after receiving treatment,
all of his vital signs
have returned to normal.
So you guys need not worry.
Moreover,
Hepatitis B is usually spread through...
No need for the useless explanation.
Once you have Hepatitis B,
there's no way to remain normal.
We need to trust in science.
Are you speaking for him
because you're a doctor too?
Not at all.
You should be thinking about the patients.
You have to be responsible
for our health and safety.
Yes, okay.
But we must have faith in science, no?
Just now, his spit
got onto me.
What if I contracted Hepatitis B?
Listen, don't worry.
His vitals are back to normal.
-Stop it!
-All right?
Sirs.
I think you're mistaken.
Dr Zhang contracted Hepatitis B.
It doesn't make him a monster.
He went to the ward to treat patients,
not to spread the virus
to you and harm you.
If such simple contact
meant quarantine,
then my advice to you
is to just stay at home and
never go outside.
Or else you might get
into an accident on the road,
or get smashed to death
by a falling billboard.
The possibility of that
is higher than your chances
of getting infected by Dr Zhang.
Whatever!
You can stop your nonsense!
You guys are clearly accomplices.
You probably have Hepatitis B too.
Stay away from me!
What?
I'm going to sue you.
I'm going to sue you!
I'll get your license revoked!
Shut up!
Are you finished?
The doctor hit me!
Get lost with your nonsense!
You heard me?
They're doctors but I'm not.
One more word and I'll kick you out!
That patient
has been quite a handful.
Every time he's here for a check-up,
he wouldn't let resident doctors near him.
He always thinks the staff
are up to no good.
So the way he acted today
wasn't targetted at you specifically.
It was more
a purging of his emotions.
So don't take it personally.
No need to feel bad.
We should focus on your recovery instead.
Sir, can I still go back to operating?
With the proper treatment,
if the surface antigen
and E antigen are negative,
it means
there isn't inflammation
or infectiousness.
Then of course you can.
What if something like today
happens again?
Do patients know what E antigen is??
Or surface antigen?
Will they be able to trust me again?
Look.
Aside from cardiac surgery,
the hospital has the
administrative department.
I always believe that
a doctor's worth
isn't tied solely to doing surgery.
Right?
They can also...
You know I love the feeling
of holding the scalpel.
Straightforward.
Accurate.
Using the most direct way
to solve a problem.
Following a clear direction.
Be it good or bad,
there's always an answer at the end.
It's within my own control.
Of course,
the administrative department
plays an important role too.
But it's not what I want to do.
If it comes down to that,
I'd rather leave.
What are you talking about?
With the way you are now,
aside from the hospital,
where else can you get a similar job?
To me,
the doctor's coat
and the military uniform underneath
are not only
a representation of a job.
I mean it.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have slept so soundly.
Ms Meng Zhen,
don't say that.
Nobody expected
such a thing to happen.
Life is unpredictable.
Zhang Yi Chi went to see me
at the book store recently.
He sort of confessed his feelings to me.
But I turned him down.
Because I felt that it would be too hard
for us to be together.
Thinking back now,
aside from death,
what else matters?
What can be more important?
Sometimes in life,
we should really be more upfront
with ourselves.
Otherwise, you'd unknowingly
leave behind a whole bunch of regrets.
Ms Chen.
Uncle, aunty.
You went through an ordeal.
It's nothing.
Where is Zhang Yi Chi?
Director Chen is having a word with him.
I'll go find him.
Doctor Li.
I think you shouldn't go.
Let's wait for him here.
Right, we should wait for him here.
Yi Chi.
Yi Chi, how are you?
I'm fine, Mum.
-I'm going to be discharged.
-What? No.
Yi Chi, don't be hasty.
You've just recovered.
You should be monitored a while more.
No need.
I want to go home.
Yi Chi.
Zhang Yi Chi.
Mr Zhang, Mrs Zhang.
I'm truly sorry about what happened.
It's fine.
Director Chen,
we'd like to talk to
Yi Chi's supervising doctor.
Is that okay?
Sure, I'll arrange for it.
Okay.
Xia Chu.
You were the first doctor
to treat Dr Zhang.
Tag along.
Okay.
Meng Zhen.
Mu Ze.
Please go and buy some food for him.
He hasn't eaten anything all day.
Okay.
I was on leave for personal reasons.
I only just heard what happened.
What did I tell you?
If you had listened,
and waited for his test results
before you did the operation,
you wouldn't be in this situation now.
Now what.
You failed to save the patient
and put your health in jeopardy.
What was that for?
Nothing.
I'm just stupid.
Okay?
Yes, you're stupid.
I've told you many times.
A doctor
is just a profession after all.
You're not god.
Don't put all your hopes
on being able to change
the scheme of things.
Towards patients,
we can do our best to save them.
But we don't have to risk our lives.
Ms Li Juan.
Do you remember when
we were in our second year
and had our first dissection lesson?
What did Dr Su write on the blackboard?
What?
Those who don't know the past and present
and don't understand heaven and humanity
will not attain immortal skills
or the heart of Buddha.
Better to focus on working the land
and weaving to make a living
than to partake in medical care
and cause trouble.
Any recollection?
None.
Did he write that?
Yes.
You forgot.
You're right.
I am not god.
I even made
such a rudimentary mistake
during an operation.
I am not a good doctor, even.
The reason why I give my all
not because I wish to change
the circumstance
with my own power.
It's because I rather not
be easily influenced by the surrounding.
That's all.
What about now?
Do you still think so?
Of course.
And it isn't just me.
I got the permit.
Really?
That's good news.
Your dream is finally coming true.
Congrats.
If you want me to stay,
I'd consider it.
Even though I don't like
changing my plans for others,
but you're an exception.
I'm willing to do it for you.
As long as you're willing.
Li Juan.
I'm sincerely wishing you the best.
You are finally able
go to where you want,
do what you love.
I'm happy for you.
You take care.
♫ The best would be mutual affection,
having good feelings, hiding nothing ♫
♫ The best would be not answering,
anticipating, avoiding misery ♫
♫ Whether we argue or show love,
it does not matter ♫
You too.
I will.
Take care.
♫ The best would be
being on the same page ♫
♫ Occasionally romantic,
impervious to joy and sorrow ♫
♫ The best would be
getting along naturally ♫
♫ Sometimes curious, wanting
to learn about the word ♫
♫ Perhaps real happiness
is simple after all ♫
Chen Meng Zhen.
Do you have a minute?
I'd like a chat.
Come to my office.
Done packing?
You're here.
Meng Zhen asked me to get you porridge.
Where is she?
She went down to get some air.
Thank you.
What are you
planning to do now?
If this had happened
before I became ill,
I wouldn't care about her stance.
I'd press on.
But now...
Now you have a chance
to correct things, right?
We should always look at the bright side.
Do you know the consequences
of this illness?
Thanks.
I heard for the past days,
you had been the one looking after him.
Yes.
Back when you brought your son
here to seek treatment,
I never thought that
Zhang Yi Chi and you
would have an episode.
Do you think his parents
would accept you?
I get it.
For a single parent,
his career
and family background
are quite the draw.
Normally,
a person's judgement on others
directly reflect their own
inner thoughts.
Do you know my relationship with him?
I only care about
my relationship with him.
I must say you're more impressive
than I thought.
Zhang Yi Chi and I were together
for 10 years.
Aside from not having
a marriage certificate,
we were as good as a married couple.
No matter who ends up with him
in the future,
they will certainly find traces of me
on him.
It was I
who moulded him into who he is.
You were together for 10 years
but still ended up separating.
Aside from lack of love,
I can't think of any other reason.
He has Hepatitis B now.
Do you know what that means?
I mustn't be fatigued.
I have to always be careful
about my physical health.
Currently,
treatment of Hepatitis B
is much better than before.
But if it turns into chronic hepatitis,
that will be the end
of my clinical practice.
I have no idea what else I could do.
I'm afraid.
Dr Li.
You know what?
I've been the family of a soldier.
Do you know what being
a soldier's family entails?
No companionship,
no assurance.
No matter what happens,
you are alone in facing
whatever life throws at you.
From the moment I married a soldier,
until eight years after his demise,
I've been taking care of Xiao Jun alone.
Till I met Dr Zhang
and we had an episode.
Maybe in your eyes,
I have no strong suit.
But at least
I have what it takes
to take on whatever outcome
this episode gives me.
Be it love or separation,
joy or sorrow,
this is what I've decided.
I will not regret it
or be afraid.
I think I know
why it's you.
I'll go now, Dr Li.
Put it his way, buddy.
If it was you,
what would you do?
Knowing full well
that you can't give your all
in carrying out your duty
as a husband.
For instance, these dishes
might turn bad at any moment.
Will you still claim a free life
in the name of love?
I can't.
Thank you, Dr Hu.
Thank you.
Not at all. It's our duty.
Mr Zhang, don't worry too much.
Yi Chi is still young.
He has good bones.
Make sure he gets enough rest
when he gets back.
The condition shouldn't affect
his life and work too much.
How could it not?
Alright, now.
Let the doctors get back to work.
I'm going to the Inpatient Department
to process the discharge.
Go an check on Yi Chi at the ward.
Okay, we'll go now.
I'll accompany you.
Okay, thanks.
Goodbye.
I'm off, Director Chen.
Dr Zhang
is an only son, right?
Xia Chu.
What is it, sir?
Do you want to go back
to Cardiac Surgery?
Yi Chi told me that
you're one of
the best resident doctors
under his mentorship.
If you wish to return,
I can arrange it with ER.
What about Dr Zhang?
Is he coming back?
He...
He will be transferred to
the medical school to teach.
Think it over.
Tell me your decision later.
Aunty.
You came to get Dr Zhang?
Can he go home?
Yes.
Thanks a lot,
for the past few days.
Thank goodness for your company.
Otherwise, Yi Chi's treatment
couldn't have gone so well.
Previously,
regarding you two's relationship,
I admit
that I was against it.
I believed that in terms of credentials,
you two weren't compatible.
I was afraid...
I was afraid that
you were in it for something.
I'm sorry, Ms Chen.
I was wrong.
You're not wrong, aunty.
I am in it for something.
I am after him.
His intelligence,
his humour.
His bright and calm demeanour.
If my admiration for him
comes across
as a selfish desire in your eyes,
I admit it.
But frankly speaking, isn't love
a form of desire anyway?
So are you
still...
I'm not thinking so far.
I just want to take care of him.
Consider it as repaying him
for saving my son.
Don't say that.
Let's be real.
A doctor is responsible for the patient.
The patient's family has no responsibility
towards the doctor.
You don't owe me anything.
No need to repay.
I'm not asking for it either.
Yi Chi.
That will be all.
♫ I'd like to find out ♫
♫ If my mask of foolishness ♫
♫ Could deceive you ♫
Meng Zhen.
I'll take you home.
♫ I'm putting on my best performance ♫
♫ Is it a little too cruel? ♫
Yi Chi.
♫ The game of adults ♫
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Mum.
♫ The moments of joy
along the way ♫
♫ Do not bring them up ♫
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
♫ Whatever evidence ♫
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
♫ The embrace I long for ♫
♫ Comes up in my dreams often ♫
♫ If I hang in there ♫
♫ I know love will surely come, someday ♫
♫ Is it a little too cruel? ♫
♫ The game of adults ♫
♫ The moments of joy
along the way ♫
♫ Do not bring them up ♫
♫ Whatever evidence ♫
♫ Requires no validation ♫
♫ It is our shared secret ♫
♫ Keeping it close to the heart ♫
[Outpatient Department]
Dad.
Can we go now, son?
Okay.
Get in, Mum.
Mencius said,
a gentleman's happiness
lies in three things
Does anyone know
what those three are?
Parents are alive and well,
harmony amongst brothers.
First happiness.
Have nothing to be ashamed of
before God or man.
Second happiness.
Find the most talented individuals
and teach and nourish them.
Third happiness.
I was your teacher.
It's my little bit of happiness.
Now I'm going to teach those
who are younger
and have more potential than you.
This will be one big happiness.
You guys should be happy for me.
At the same time,
do even better
to stand
in front of the operating table
in place of me.
I hope that after every surgery,
you'd be able to calmly
inform the patient's family
that the operation was a success,
and not
"I've tried my best."
Alright, then.
All the best, comrades.
Salute!
Today, I enter the medical profession
and vow to dedicate my life
to serve others.
I thank and respect my teachers,
the same way I treat my parents.
I will practise medicine
with conscience and dignity.
The patient's well-being
is of my utmost priority.
[Outpatient Department]
I will uphold the doctor-patient
confidentiality.
I will do my best to honour
the reputation and noble tradition
of the medical profession.
My colleagues are my brethren.
I will be responsible for my patients.
I will not let difference in religion,
nationality,
race,
politics or status
affect my service and aid.
From its inception,
a life shall be given utmost dignity.
Even in the face of danger,
my medical knowledge
will not go against humanity.
I solemnly and autonomously
swear on my name
the above declaration.