[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 2]
Do you think I'm short on cash?
If you can't afford a moving company,
I can sponsor you.
Don't be afraid to ask.
Look at him being all obnoxious.
That one, two, three, four, too.
He can't wait to see me
fall into despair.
Who gave him that confidence?
How hard is it to get a new place?
I can't believe
that in the entire Ningjiang District,
there's not a place for me.
Where do you usually crash at night?
The whole world belongs to me.
But I really hate moving.
I've got to go to work, look for a place,
then pack up and clean up again.
I'll really go mad.
Calm down.
It's okay. I must remain calm.
As a modern lady,
I won't be defeated
by such a trivial matter.
Just focus on doing the laundry first.
He says a little pain in life
doesn't matter...
It's just moving to a new place, isn't it?
Anything on tonight?
Where did you come from?
You gave me a scare.
Do you have anything to do tonight?
I'll be looking for new places online
so I can move out soon.
I need you to come with me.
I'm not done hanging up my laundry yet.
It's for something more important
than this.
A kid was hurt,
but he refuses to go to the hospital.
I need a doctor.
So I'm needed only when something happens?
Isn't it a doctor's duty
to heal the wounded and save the dying?
Let's go.
Is that kid
-very important to you?
-Yes.
What if...
I'll do my best.
Xiao Jun.
Liang Mu Ze.
Alright, let me see it.
Now you're embarrassed?
I just asked you to wash up
but you didn't.
He insisted on waiting for you.
You got hit?
I brought this madam doctor
to look at your injury.
Madam doctor?
Just call me sister.
Pretty please, handsome boy?
Let me have a look.
It's too dark in here.
Do you have a torchlight?
Yes. Mu Ze.
On the table over there.
[Just give up, Mu Ze.]
[I know you're almost out.]
[How would you know that?]
[If you can, so can I.]
[I can't do this anymore.]
[I can't.]
-[You lost.]
-[I lost.]
[I lost.]
[There's always a bigger fish.]
-[Let's continue this tomorrow.]
-[Sure.]
[I'm always up for that.]
[Anytime.]
[Don't move.]
[Let me try out my new camera.]
[Go away.]
[Three, two, one. Look up.]
Mu Ze.
Now close your eyes.
Don't move. It's going to sting a little.
Hold on. It's almost done.
Hold on just a little bit more.
Xiao Jun is so brave.
Done.
Will there be a scar?
It probably won't.
A scar is nothing.
Am I right?
We're tough men.
Mu Ze, you two have a seat.
I need to head out for a while.
Where are you going?
Look after the kid.
Liang Mu Ze.
Liang Mu Ze, don't leave.
I'm not. I'll just go
to see where she's going.
You promise?
I promise. Don't worry.
Have some fun with madam doctor.
It's sister.
How dare he.
What's your relationship
with Liang Mu Ze?
To be precise, we actually
have just really known each other today.
What about you and him?
We've known each other for many years.
He's my father.
Where are you going?
I'm fine.
Please head back first.
Your friend's still there.
I... I'll be back soon.
It doesn't seem like you're fine.
What's the matter?
I...
Xiao Jun got bullied in class today.
He panicked and banged his head
against the door.
After that, he fainted.
Although his father is dead,
Xiao Jun has always been very obedient.
I've never hit him.
I went through a lot to raise him.
Who are they to bully him?
They won't give me an explanation
so I'm getting it myself.
Please don't stop me, Mu Ze.
I don't mean to stop you.
Xiao Jun...
How much longer can you
defend him like that?
And you're going with a torchlight?
What can it do?
Stop touching it.
There are germs on your hand.
Let it heal on its own.
Why are your lips purplish?
They've always been that way.
Do you usually feel dizzy
or experience chest tightness?
No.
No?
Well I... I've done my best.
The dressing isn't really that ugly,
is it?
Does it hurt?
Xiao Jun.
Listen to me.
In future,
if someone tries to bully you...
I was wrong.
Next time, I'll avoid it immediately.
No, it's not your fault.
You can't avoid it.
If someone bullies you,
you retaliate immediately.
You hear that?
You can't bully others,
but you can't let others bully you either.
Got it?
But I'm afraid.
What are you afraid of?
Your bully feels afraid too.
He only has two fists and two legs
just like you.
As long as you fight back,
he'll be afraid too.
And he won't come at you again.
Got it?
Really?
Let me show you a few tricks.
-Okay.
-Come here.
Thanks for talking
to Miss Meng Zhen all night.
It's fine.
Is Xiao Jun
really your son?
Yes.
Your personalities are different.
What do you mean?
He really cares for you.
I know.
He'll believe and do
whatever you tell him to.
Is that a problem?
Do you really think the fighting skills
you taught him
will make him untouchable?
I never meant it that way.
Why did you teach him to fight then?
It's called resistance.
When you're bullied,
you won't necessarily win with your fist.
But at least,
it'll make sure
you won't become
a target of bullies anymore.
Is there really no other tactful way
to resolve this?
Must it be an eye for an eye?
He will have
to face this world by himself.
Thanks for sending me to the hospital.
Go home and get some sleep.
I don't really need any sleep.
Sleep probably doesn't need you.
Is there a medical explanation for that?
Not that I know of.
But my woman's hunch says,
the body of a sleepless person
harbours
a battered and weary soul.
Did I get it right, Captain Liang?
Stop being conceited, Dr Xia.
Goodbye.
[Outpatient Department]
-Good morning.
You have dark circles under your eyes.
Where did you party last night?
I had a vocational study.
Get changed quickly.
Dr Zhang will be here soon.
[Miss Lan]
Miss Lan.
[Hey, girl.]
How's the place?
[I'm getting ready to move.]
Why?
I was thinking of...
Hold your thought.
He has a son. Do you know that?
What?
A son?
What son? I didn't know that.
And yet you were so eager to push
your daughter into relationship hell?
Are you even my biological mother?
I...
[Enough. I won't blame you for it.]
I need to work now. Talk again later.
Love you. Mwah!
Goodbye, Miss Lan.
Wait, girl.
A son?
Xiao Xiao, do you have
an extra pair of shoes?
Didn't you keep a pair here?
I forgot.
In that case, I can't help you.
To hell with it then.
A week ago, the patient did
a coronary artery bypass graft.
Since yesterday,
his fluid intake has been 2000 ml,
urine output has been 2100 ml.
Intake and output volumes are balanced.
The drainage tube was removed yesterday.
She is doing well so far.
You caught a cold?
No.
I'm just a little sensitive
to the perfume of this doctor.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
You're doing good.
Rest well now.
Why are you back here?
Liang Mu Ze.
This will count as a reward
for treating Xiao Jun yesterday.
Must you draw a line in everything?
Yes.
Fine, whatever you say.
Things like bangles, rings,
brooches and earrings
that interfere with your work
and affect the recovery of patients
must all be discarded.
Keep in mind.
You're either a good or bad doctor,
regardless of gender.
Xia Chu is working
without her military outfit.
Why am I the only one being scolded?
Xia Chu.
I'm here.
Why are you so smug?
Why aren't you wearing the military outfit
during working hours?
No.
I'm properly attired. Look.
I'm a professional military doctor.
How can I make
a rookie mistake?
Very good.
Correct mistakes if you've made any,
guard against them if you haven't.
Especially you.
By the way,
that young officer
who returned from Isaia with us,
how is he doing?
He was already discharged
from ICU yesterday.
According to the order of higher-ups,
he is now placed in the private wad.
Alright.
Let's check on him first.
Yes.
Captain Liang,
are you here to visit the patient?
I was initially here to deliver something.
I came to see Tian Yong since I'm here.
How are you feeling?
Is everything good?
Xia Chu.
Yes.
Describe the patient's condition.
Patient's name, Tian Yong.
Age, 32 years old.
Because he was shot
in the left thoracic cavity,
he was given a thoracotomy
by the Isaia Joint Medical Team.
The bullet was removed.
Two days after the surgery,
he was transferred from Isaia
to our ICU.
After receiving medical treatment,
his condition is good.
Currently,
his blood pressure is 120/80 mmHg,
heartbeat is stable.
Thoracic cavity and pericardium drainage
tube flow is steady.
The rate of drainage in 24 hours
is 100 ml.
What should be done next?
Conduct an echocardiography
and chest CT scan,
a blood routine and a full-set
blood coagulation examination.
Check if the thoracic cavity and
the pericardial drainage
flow rates have reduced
and whether the colour
has gradually turned clearer,
which will decide
if we can remove the tube soon.
In other words,
your recovery is going well.
Dr Zhang.
Will there be any medical repercussions?
Are you experiencing any yourself?
Xia Chu.
Let me introduce.
He
is the officer
I told you about in Isaia
who was injured even worse than Tian Yong.
You must be a major now, aren't you?
Chief, I've heard so much of you.
We know each other.
Really?
Why didn't you mention it?
We don't know each other too well.
We only crossed paths
back in Isaia
when I was held hostage.
Now I remember.
You were the one who saved the hostage,
weren't you?
Since you know each other,
why are you so discreet?
I don't know.
We even met a few times
upon returning.
Is there a cause for it?
No.
If she says so.
Alright then.
In that case,
if there's any problem
with Lieutenant Tian's condition,
you can look for Dr Xia in future.
No problem.
We're done here. Next wad.
What were you doing back there,
Liang Mu Ze?
What do you mean?
Do you know
that what you said just now
will bring me
a lot of troubles?
I only spoke the truth.
Are you a pretty little fool?
If you can't handle gossips,
that is your problem.
Liang Mu Ze.
You don't call me chief now, do you?
Listen, Dr Xia.
If you think it is right
to cast people away
after using them,
then continue with it.
I don't care.
But I've told you before.
I like simplicity
and straightforwardness.
It's not something honourable to know you.
So there's no point in lying about it.
If you like to act,
then suit yourself.
I have no obligation to play along.
Something is not right.
What is it?
Aren't you from the Special Forces?
So?
A person from the Special Forces
shouldn't be
arrogant, cool, inarticulate and tough?
Why is it different when it comes to you?
You're so talkative.
I bet if you were
on a prolonged ambush mission
where you can't speak nor move,
the silence could just kill you.
When you move out,
make sure you take all your stuff.
Captain Liang, join us.
I'm done.
I'm a pretty little fool?
I can't take this.
Has she lost her mind?
What a joke.
How am I a pretty little fool?
She called an officer
a pretty little fool.
Tell me, Tian Yong.
As the top-notch graduate
of military school,
your captain,
in my every aspect,
whether it's my physique,
or my military skills,
or my cognitive aptitudes,
aren't they all equally excellent?
How can she call me a blockhead?
This isn't the worst part.
What really pissed me off is that
she pretended not knowing me
in front of her colleagues.
What's wrong with knowing me?
Tell me what's wrong with that?
Does it embarrass her?
You're just sneering.
Why don't you say something?
Did I feed you too fast?
I'm asking you.
I've answered you.
What did you say?
Via Morse code?
I've been thinking
if we should have
some kind of secret way
of communication between us.
We should, shouldn't we?
If someday you are captured
by the enemy...
Nonsense.
Why isn't it you being captured?
I'm just saying.
You can't do that either.
Let's be clear that there's no way
for it to happen in my troop.
You're being too idealistic.
Major.
Without ideals, why are you
even a soldier?
Without ideals, how can you be a soldier?
Didn't you start off as a soldier
because of your ideals?
I did it for survival.
I grew up in an orphanage
with no parents.
I couldn't find a decent job
after graduating from high school.
What ideals did I have?
I was looking to survive.
Tian Yong.
Listen.
You're wrong.
Even if in the beginning,
you joined the forces
merely because of survival,
you've still managed to stay in it
for so long.
After so many years,
your ideals
have already transcended
the mere reason of surviving.
Am I right?
Don't you deny that.
It's pointless to deny it either.
Look at this.
This here
is the best proof.
What's that?
It was this?
Yes.
Hold on to it.
Keep it, so you'll always remember.
Thanks, captain.
Take it.
That's so kind of you.
Ouch.
It hurts.
That's good.
That way you'll remember.
Brace yourself.
My wound hurts.
Alright. I'll remove it.
[Somewhere in Southeast Asia,
Willick, T4 Headquarters]
Why did the mission fail?
The local police
hired help from Hunter Military School.
They were all top-notch special forces
from various countries.
What about the thing I wanted?
It's gone.
But we can find another one.
Listen.
I'm running out of time.
-I must have it as soon...
-Of course.
Just like the steak before us.
As long as one can afford it,
anyone can have a taste of it.
Money is not a problem.
Once I've received it
and confirmed that it's compatible,
you'll have the rest of the payment.
Again, just like this steak,
time determines its doneness.
Likewise,
its taste will vary accordingly too.
What are you trying to say?
The organ provider is from Country A.
This matter has now alerted
not only the Isaia police,
but the Interpol is watching closely too.
Trying to retrieve your goods
under such dire conditions
requires a higher price now,
don't you agree?
You're fooling with me.
Business is business.
Great.
So it is.
Fine.
You may be in power in China,
but over here,
I'm in charge.
Boss, don't move.
You must understand
that everything in this world
revolves around money,
except money itself.
Money is related to one's dreams.
And you seem to have belittled mine.
Therefore,
your opportunity is gone now.
What do you mean?
Have you forgotten whose fundings
T4 owes for its glory today?
There's an old Chinese saying.
Great kindness repaid with ingratitude.
No kindness needs a lifetime of repayment.
Furthermore,
while we were negotiating our ties,
your little brother, Gui,
struck a money deal with me.
He wants you dead.
Plus he has offered me
something I simply can't refuse.
You liar.
Tell Old Gui
that the job is done.
Have him come over
to negotiate the remaining terms
of the goods supply and market sharing
as soon as possible.
Yes.
Master.
People think my resources come from
T4 alone.
But they never know
my greatest asset is you,
Zhuo Ran.
I owe it to your cultivation, Master.
Here, have a sit.
Yes.
Try out my cooking.
Master.
How does it taste?
Zhuo Ran.
Hasn't it been eight years since you
last set foot on China?
It's been 8 years and 27 days.
Pack up.
You'll be heading there.
Can I bring my mother along?
Have you forgotten that
she needs to recuperate?
Don't worry.
Once you return,
I'll arrange a short reunion.
Sounds good?
Yes.
What's the mission?
Dong'an University of China recently
invented a new form of medical sedatives.
I need the formula
and its person-in-charge,
Xia Guang Yuan.
Perhaps his daughter rings a bell.
Xia Chu.
I got it.
We've already locked
onto this dark web platform called
City of Desires.
Many recent cases of drug trafficking
in the city
are connected to this platform.
After our technical team
hacked into the server,
they collected metadata
for further analysis and interpretation.
We gradually found
some basic information
about the mastermind behind the platform.
This person uses an online account named
Dreadful Pirate.
Just moments ago,
he published several images
mourning the death
of several T4 mercenaries.
Besides that,
he even initiated
a suicide mission game
using high monetary rewards as bait.
Various mission cards
are randomly published
to incite netizens
to commit suicide missions.
[Although the motive is unclear,]
[it has already caused
terrible ramifications.]
[Higher-ups have called for
a special task force]
[led by the chief
of Criminal Investigation Detachment Unit]
[Rao Feng,]
[along with Narcotics Divison,
Financial Investigation Division]
[Cyber Crime Division
and various other divisions]
[to identify the whereabouts]
[of Dreadful Pirate.]
[According to the latest intel,]
Dreadful Pirate is hiding somewhere
amidst our country's borders.
It's likely related
to the mercenaries hired by T4.
If we were to arrest them,
the police would need your help.
No problem.
I'll inform the Thunder Commando
to get ready immediately.
Once the mission is approved,
we'll assist in the operation.
Thank you.
She asked me to lend her
my pair of shoes.
But I didn't have an extra pair.
I think Army Officer Liang was the one
who brought her those.
How can I help you?
I bet
the shoes and military uniform
you're wearing now
were delivered by Army Officer Liang.
Of course not.
He's pursuing you?
Impossible.
Are you guys together?
Nope.
He seems to be close to Dr Zhang.
How should I know about that?
So the reason you were selected to attend
that international medical
training program in Isaia
was because he talked
to Dr Zhang about it?
Dr Zhang.
Why aren't you doing this in the office?
It's too noisy there.
You heard gossips?
You heard them too?
It's easy to guess.
You should know that
you're our first ever resident doctor
to have participated
in a foreign aid medical program.
You're also the first ever resident doctor
to stand in front of the operating table.
Others of the same age as you
are still busy practising how to stitch.
Hence comes the gossip.
You have to learn to handle them.
Why should I?
To wear the crown
is to bear its weight.
What you have to do now
is to work as hard as you can.
Let those who talk
feel hopeless.
Then, they'll stop talking.
Will they really stop?
Of course they will.
I'm certain of it.
It's because I
experienced it too.
Do you train like this all the time?
Of course. It's a must.
Ever since the day I first did stitching
and was kicked out of the operating room
by my teacher.
Every day.
But this time during the day,
isn't it bright enough already?
Why do you also need a candle?
They aren't for the training.
It's for those
who went on the operating table
but never made it back alive.
Because of them,
I remind myself
that I can't slack even for a moment.
Remember this, Xia Chu.
Nothing is more important
than a person's life and death.
I understand now.
Mi Gu.
Hey girl.
Do you miss me?
[I do.]
[I miss you a lot.]
How are you doing there?
Is your residency life
full of blood, sweat and tears?
[Not only that.]
It's an imperial court drama
here every day.
When I started medical school,
[I thought
I just needed skills to survive.]
Only now do I realise that
emotional intelligence is super important.
No matter how terrible it is,
at least you've got
a free mansion to live in.
Am I right?
Forget it.
The landlord is forcing me to move out.
[Mi Gu.]
[How I wish you were my landlady.]
Well, I'm always ready to share
half of my tatami bed with you.
Mi Gu.
You're the best.
I'll leave you with that thought.
I've got a cab to catch. Goodbye.
Bye.
What doesn't kill me
only makes me stronger.
Thunder Commando unit,
check your communication devices.
Once we're at the borders,
our orders
are to capture the target alive.
But if the target fires,
we won't hold back.
Yes, sir.
Alright, let's have a look.
Who knows?
We might find a better place
than this one.
[I don't want to go. I like it here.]
What a pity. This house is so exquisite.
I was almost getting used to it.
Stop thinking, stop thinking.
Delete that thought.
Look for a new place.
You can do it.
[Hi, Dr Xia.]
[I'm Chen Meng Zhen,
Luo Xiao Jun's mother.]
[Do you remember me?]
Yes. How can I help you?
Well...
Two days back,
Xiao Jun kept complaining
about tightness in his chest.
He even fainted in school earlier today.
I was wondering
[if it could be some kind of repercussion
from his previous head injury?]
Has he done a check-up?
I brought him to the community hospital
during the day.
But their equipment was broken.
So they couldn't do an X-ray.
How is he doing now?
[Right now]
[he's sleeping.]
Mum.
I feel terrible.
[I feel terrible.]
Don't worry. Just observe him for now.
If it gets worse,
come straight to the hospital
tomorrow morning.
I'll be there.
That'd be great. Thank you so much.
You're welcome. Goodbye.
Could it be that I didn't dress
the wound properly?
What's the point of raising
a lazy cat like you?
A holograph?
Looks like someone's messing with us.
Whale.
What's the situation?
The other party definitely
has ill intentions.
You have to be careful.
Yes, sir.
No matter what case this is,
or who the mastermind is,
I'll get to the bottom of it.