[English subtitles are available]
[My Dear Guardian]
[Episode 21]
Mi Gu.
Boss.
The...
The clip is almost ready.
I'll send it to your office
once I've reviewed the captions.
I'm not here for the clip.
This.
My nephew
studied documentary making
in Bristol.
He wants to do a project of his own.
If you're free in the
next couple of days,
get in touch with him.
He's a nice kid.
You two will get along well.
Think of it as making a new friend.
[Liu Song]
Thanks, boss.
That's right.
Friends and family
should look out for each other.
Contact the buyer.
[Okay.]
Alright, thanks.
Rao Zhi.
Do you know him?
No.
We found this in his phone.
Is this the dead man in the villa?
That's right.
Is he the killer?
We're not sure yet.
I've asked my colleagues
in the technical department
to do a DNA test on the body.
I've also contacted the
telecommunications operator.
We need to confirm his identity first.
If he's not the killer,
how do you explain the photo?
Ever heard of the City of Desire?
What's that?
It's a website.
But it's a little different
from the websites we're used to.
It's a trading platform hidden deep
within the Dark Web.
[The founder could be related]
[to an account named Scary Pirate.]
[It was Scary Pirate]
[who first posted this photo]
[on the City of Desire.]
[Before this, a female suicide victim]
[had downloaded the photo
onto her computer.]
Now, it seems
this photo
didn't pop up by pure chance.
I suspect it's
some form of invitation.
A means to identify
an in-group member.
Behind it all,
there may very well
be a deeper, darker secret.
The Scary Pirate,
what's his aim?
Our colleagues at the
Psychology Department
put together a profile
of the Scary Pirate.
We learned that he's probably
an anti-social militant anarchist.
Those types are characterised
by their aggression
and lack of remorse.
Their crimes
tend to appear coincidental.
How can we find him?
It's difficult.
The Dark Web is notorious
for its anonymity.
Those who dwell within it
are akin to masked men
moving in the shadows.
They're very hard to catch.
Perhaps this Scary Pirate
is the culprit behind the dead man
in the villa?
Not only that.
There's also Sang Kun's
borderland organ harvesting case
and his brother, Gui's death.
He may very well be a key lead.
All we can do now
is use the Scary Pirate's
online activity pattern
to perform a stake-out.
Hopefully, we'll get some clues
or his personal information.
But because of the Dark Web's
peculiarities,
even if we spend an inordinate amount
of manpower and money,
we might still lose track of him.
Progress will be slow.
Rao Zhi.
The Network Security Centre just called.
Gui's cargo has surfaced.
Lieutenant.
Come play with us.
If you don't,
Xiao Teng is going to wipe the floor
with me.
What are you saying?
Lieutenant.
You're holding the book upside down.
It's called being a proficient reader.
Lieutenant,
whose call are you waiting for?
I'm not waiting for anyone's call.
Even Xiang Yang could tell.
Quit being so secretive.
You must be waiting for a girl
to call you.
Last time, at the New Year dinner,
I overheard the Brigade Commander's
conversation with the chief of delegates.
He was asking him to
watch over a certain nurse
in the medical corps for you.
Could something have turned up?
Xiao Teng.
Your ears sure are sharp.
How come I didn't hear that?
I can't help it.
Collecting intel is my speciality.
Attention!
Commander!
Which ones of you
have been to a bar?
Commander.
You have?
I was going to say
I've never been to a bar.
Xiao Teng!
Yes, sir!
Have you?
Commander,
I've never set foot in one of those
cesspools of debauchery.
You haven't?
Then how do you know
they're cesspools of debauchery?
That's ancient history, way before
I joined the force.
Who else?
Commander!
Me.
There's no need to tell me
you haven't been to one.
I have.
Before I joined the force,
I worked in a bar.
Well I'll be.
You. And you.
Change into some civilian clothes
and follow me.
Yes, sir!
Once you've reached the destination,
go straight upstairs.
Someone will be waiting for you.
Commander, what's the mission?
You'll know when you get there.
Remember,
you must follow
our command.
Yes, sir.
Wipe the sweat.
Whale?
Aren't you supposed to be
on break?
Let's talk over there.
Well, Gopher?
Don't I look dashing?
Have you ever seen
a more dashing waiter?
I say,
what's with the heart armour?
I crafted it out of a used
bulletproof vest.
Seriously?
It's better than having nothing at all.
Impressive.
Tell me,
is there anything you can't do?
Once you've had your heart
pierced by a bullet,
let alone heart armour,
you'll learn how to crank out
chain mails.
I guess you're right.
Alright.
Have you suited up?
Yes.
Captain.
We've coordinated with the bar.
Let me remind you,
these aren't run-of-the-mill
drug dealers we're arresting.
They all have a long list
of murder charges
as well as T4's backing.
[They are the shadow.]
[And we're the shadow's shadow.]
[Our mission]
[is to apprehend the middleman]
[as soon as the deal takes place.]
[Try not to use bullets]
[or create a huge racket.]
[Wouldn't want to hurt the innocent.
Suspect spotted.
Fox.
Try to approach his backpack.
Sorry, sir.
Let me wipe that for you.
Whale, follow him.
[Calling all teams. This is a trap.]
What's going on?
The City of Desire has changed domains.
Into the deeper Dark Web.
[The Scary Pirate posted
a wanting-to-sell ad]
[the day after Gui was murdered.]
[Later, he got in touch]
[with a buyer called Franster]
[and agreed to deal in Yunshan Tunnel.]
[The bar is probably a diversion.]
Ask the City Bureau
to deploy its people
to set up blockades along
the roads connected to Yunshan Tunnel
and check all vehicles.
Okay.
[Have you checked the suspect]
[in the bar?]
[The stationed officers
have checked them.]
[The backpack contained only
some daily necessities.]
[Nothing suspicious was found.]
Criminals these days sure
are tricky.
What did you expect?
Why did you think we set up
such an elaborate stake-out?
Too bad we didn't catch him.
We will.
That's right.
Nothing is perfect.
Once something goes down,
there's nowhere to hide.
You should have confidence
and be brave.
No matter how many times you fail,
you must pick yourself up.
What are you talking about?
Aren't we talking about
busting crimes?
Why do I feel you're talking
about relationships?
Get out of here.
About your experience in
finding love.
I was talking about busting crime.
Do you understand?
Really?
Something's not right here.
What's going on, Gopher?
Don't touch me.
Look...
[Calling all teams.]
[You can pull back now.]
Roger that.
Let's change and get out of here.
Okay.
Sir.
What is it?
Thank you for letting me
observe the operation.
You're too kind.
You deserved it.
Remember,
even if they're off life support,
one in four patients
may still die of infections.
Understood.
Get some rest.
Sir.
Can I borrow your phone?
What about yours?
Mine is sodden.
I would like to use yours
to call Liang Mu Ze.
Thanks to him,
we were able to get
the replacement lung.
You ought to.
But I'm sorry to tell you,
look,
my battery's dead.
I was just about find a place
to make a phone call.
Never mind.
I'll charge it.
You can use mine.
Thanks.
Captain,
you had a long day.
Why don't you let me drive?
It's okay.
I'm good.
Letting my captain chauffeur me.
How is this appropriate?
With your driving speed? Forget it.
I want to live.
That was because
we were chased by enemies
during the drill.
A good soldier never falls back.
That's what Lieutenant taught me.
Right, Lieutenant?
What's on your mind?
What do you mean?
Look at you.
And you say it's not love?
Are you kidding me?
That's my phone.
I'm just checking the time.
[Liang Mu Ze.]
My phone is sodden.
I'm calling you from
my colleague's phone.
How come your phone
is working just fine?
Yeah, it's fine.
If your phone is wet,
you can try putting it
in a bag of rice.
[Got it.]
So is Liu Ran alright?
The surgery was a success.
Her lungs are starting
to function again.
Good.
[But there are more challenges
down the road.]
Rejection and infection
being the two major hurdles
to sustained lung function.
Under your care,
it shouldn't be a problem, right?
[Actually,]
I'm not that great.
It was the effort of the whole team.
Including you,
[Liang Mu Ze.]
[Today,]
[I can't thank you enough.]
Thank me for what?
[Thank you for recovering
the replacement lung.]
And
thank you for saving me underwater.
Because of the
incident with Zhuo Ran,
I was a little emotional
[and spoke harshly to you.]
[I'm sorry.]
[Actually...]
Actually, you're alright.
[More and more, I feel that]
[at the brink of life and death,]
as long as I have you,
I don't need to be afraid.
[It's quite reassuring.]
Who's with you?
It's just Tian Yong and Xiao Teng.
[I'm sending them back
to the camp.]
And
my phone is still connected
to the car's
[Bluetooth speaker.]
[Xia Chu.]
Xia Chu.
Liang Mu Ze, I hate you so much!
What's going on?
Is Dr Xia...
Is she that petty?
Now what, Lieutenant?
What should we do?
How would I know?
Captain, wait for me!
Me, too!
Rao Feng filled me in
on last night's situation.
You guys were responsible
for execution,
not strategy.
So the blame for the failure
doesn't rest with you.
Pull yourself together.
In the future,
we'll work on many more
missions together.
Yes, sir.
How many leave days do you have left?
Three days.
Do you want to spend them?
I do.
Good.
Are you spending it with your cousin?
With
Xia Chu.
Who?
Are you having so much fun here
that you forgot about your family?
Do your parents know?
It was my mother who arranged it.
I knew it.
That's wonderful.
Feel free to use my car
until yours is fixed.
You'll need it
for your date.
We haven't gotten that far, Commander.
Then get on with it.
Listen here,
Xia Chu is a good girl.
She's presentable
and cheerful.
She has the makings
of an officer's wife.
Hurry up. Make her your girlfriend.
It can wait.
What do you mean it can wait?
You can wait,
but the girl can't.
After you make her your girlfriend,
you'll have to wait at least
six months
before you can propose marriage.
Think of all the time
you're wasting.
Get to it.
But I don't know where I stand with her.
What have you been doing
throughout your long break?
Let me tell you, Liang Mu Ze,
with regards to your love life
and marriage,
I don't want
any screw-ups from you.
If you truly love Xia Chu
and want to share a life with her,
you should let her know
as soon as possible.
You want me to confess to her?
She should confess to me.
What are you on about?
Commander,
Xia Chu
is not like other girls.
Don't compare her to others.
She has an attitude.
I wonder who it was that bragged
about frequenting women's bedrooms
and having problems
saying no to their adoration?
Well?
Can't handle it
this time?
It's not that I can't handle it.
I just don't want to rush it.
Commander,
there are many ways
to a woman's heart.
Countless ways.
But on Xia Chu,
I can't use any of them.
Especially at a time like this.
What's wrong?
What are you hesitating for?
Have they decided who's
going to be transferred?
Captain!
Didn't the Brigade Commander
give you a half-day leave?
You're up early.
It's in my habit.
Didn't run enough yesterday?
Captain,
I'd like to ask you
a question,
but I'm not sure if I should.
You shouldn't.
Captain.
How is your sister?
Xiao Xue?
I'm so tired.
Er Miao,
I'm so tired, I can't even take a shower.
You chose this path.
You'll have to walk it
even if it's on your knees.
I must've been crazy when I decided
to study medicine.
Er Miao,
are doctors this miserable
or is it just the resident doctors?
All of them, of course.
Let me get my phone.
[Braised Egg]
[Is Xiao Xue there?]
Why should I tell you?
We haven't settled last night's score yet.
[She's not here.]
Liang Mu Ze, will you ever quit?
I told you she's not home.
Why must you call me?
Can't you call her phone?
I don't want to speak to you,
do you hear me?
Xia Chu.
It's me.
[Zhuo Ran]
Sorry.
What's up?
I'm at the hospital.
Can you come over?
[Why?]
Just come.
I'll be waiting.
[Do you know where she is?]
She was going to visit the parrot
at the Special Forces Brigade.
Didn't you see her?
That's right.
She took a ride around 1 p.m. yesterday.
The license plate number...
Bin C49058.
[She smiled at me
when she got into the car.]
[And then she cried.]
[She said she didn't want to
go home]
[and asked me to take her
to Yunshan Tunnel.]
[Then as soon as we reached
the coastal road,]
[she asked me to pull over,]
[telling me she changed her mind.]
[So I pulled over]
[to let her decide where
she wanted to go.]
[She stared blankly out of the window,]
[then told me to continue on
to Yunshan Tunnel.]
[This went on several times.]
[Finally,]
[I dropped her at the entrance
of the tunnel.]
[I'm telling you,]
[in all my years as a driver,]
[I've never come across such
a fussy customer.]
[She was erratic.]
[Is she mentally ill?]
Xiao Xue!
Xia Chu.
[Where are you?]
Yunshan Tunnel.
Is Xiao Xue back yet?
[No.]
[She's in the Emergency Department.
Please come right now.]
Xiao Xue.
Why are you with her?
I bumped into her.
Where?
Is this an interrogation?
I'm asking you, where?
Yunshan Tunnel.
Last night?
That's right.
I was on my night jog.
I thought it dangerous
for a girl to be sleeping there.
There was a case
at Yunshan Tunnel yesterday.
All the cops were there
and none of them saw you?
A case?
I have no idea.
Maybe I missed it.
How lucky for you.
Even if they saw me, so what?
I'm sure your country's policemen
will take good care
of a friendly foreigner's
rights and well-being.
We only protect allies.
The dress your sister is wearing
belonged to Xia Chu, isn't that right?
I remember the first time
Xia Chu and I kissed,
she was wearing this very dress.
After all these years,
she still kept it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have recognised
your sister and saved her.
I called Xia Chu, and it turned out
I was right.
You should thank me.
No.
You should thank that kiss.
Now that I think of it,
it kind of left me wanting more.
Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze, what are you doing?
Such a temper, Officer Liang.
Do all soldiers have such
violent tendencies?
Liang Mu Ze, let go.
Let go right now.
This is a hospital, Liang Mu Ze.
Liang Mu Ze.
Listen here,
no funny business.
Xiao Xue's report!
Xia Chu.
You're staying under one roof
with a guy like that.
Aren't you scared?
How did you know?
Know what?
I never told you
I'm staying in Liang Mu Ze's house.
How did you know?
Mi Gu.
She told me.
I'm really worried about you.
I apologise
for Liang Mu Ze's behaviour just now.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive him.
One more thing.
The Liang Mu Ze I know
isn't the Liang Mu Ze you know.
So
please don't say things like that again.
[Tang Lin]
[Hallo, Mr Zhuo,]
[are you in Dong'an?]
[Let's meet up.]
Sure.
Let's meet up.
Lower your head.
Drive.
Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze, who are you
throwing tantrums at?
I've just finished a 14-hour shift.
I was supposed to rest today.
But because of your sister,
I had to rush to the hospital
before I got one minute
of shut-eye.
If you don't want to thank me, fine.
But why are you
giving me the cold shoulder?
Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze, come out!
Come out, Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze!
Liang Mu Ze, open up.
Come out, Liang Mu Ze!
You really went off the rails today,
you know that?
Why did you hit him?
No matter how contemptible
you find him,
no matter how scornful you are,
you shouldn't have hit him
at a place like that.
You made a brute of yourself
when you're clearly not.
Liang Mu Ze, is something wrong
with your brain?
Say something, Liang Mu Ze.
He's jealous.
When did you wake up?
When we were at the hospital.
Your ex said you were wearing
this dress
when you first kissed him.
Your ex even said
the kiss left him wanting more.
Sure enough, my brother took offence
and gave him a punch.
But you, of all people, saw it.
You even pushed my brother aside
and stood in between
him and your ex.
That made my brother angrier.
He walked past me
as if his feet were on fire.
I thought he would knock me over.
Given the
complicated and dangerous
circumstance,
I decided to feign unconsciousness.
Until just now,
when I heard you reproach my brother,
I thought if didn't wake up
and tell his side of the story,
this argument would never end.
Arrogant guys like my brother
don't feel like they have
to explain anything.
Right, Mu Ze?
Is what
she said
true?
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ To relive the moment
my heart skipped a beat ♫
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
Children, please look away.
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ To relive the moment
my heart skipped a beat ♫
What was that about?
I'm feeling blue. Can't you see?
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ To relive the moment
my heart skipped a beat ♫
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
You're the one who dragged me along.
I don't feel like going anywhere.
I just want to sleep.
Let's go to the mall.
What for?
To buy dresses.
♫  The sky is smiling
and my heart is fluttering ♫
♫ Time stops as we're surrounded
by happiness ♫
Hey buddy, you're not married, are you?
How can you tell?
I could tell at a glance.
You're like me when I was younger.
Full of pep.
What about after marriage?
Observe.
Honey, what do you think of this dress?
Looks good.
At least take a look first.
Sure, it's nice.
Liang Mu Ze.
I'm sure you'll do better than
us after you get married.
♫  We don't have to think about it
as we are destined to meet ♫
♫ We chit-chat the whole night through ♫
♫  ​The sweetness is just right ♫
♫ We share the same taste in food ♫
♫  The sweetness is just right ♫
♫  No one knows what
triggered our first fight ♫
♫  When we think back, love is a wonder ♫
♫  Our encounter is not too old school ♫
♫  The amount of happiness is just right ♫
♫  Our connection is not too boring ♫
♫  No one ever notices
your smiling lashes ♫
♫  We don't have to think about it
as we are destined to meet ♫
Smells delicious.
Have another bite.
What's wrong?
I'll help myself.
Don't you want to eat?
I don't like sweets.
Then you're
missing out on the
great pleasures of life.
Try some.
I don't want to.
Just one bite.
Just try it.
Durian is delicious.
It smells a little funky, that's all.
It's really yummy.
Take a bite.
No, thanks. Save it for yourself.
-Just one bite.
-No.
-Liang Mu Ze.
-I don't want to.
Try some.
-No.
-Just one little bite.
I don't want to.
Seriously.
Just one bite, come on.
You actually ate durian?
Are you blind?
For the first time in his life,
Liang Mu Ze actually tasted durian.
Well?
How did it taste?
Nothing special.
That's beside the point.
What matters is you ate durian.
Liang Mu Ze ate durian!
Are you nuts?
The first taste of durian.
The first taste...
♫ Liking what you like,
sensitive to every detail ♫
♫ My heart is at peace when I'm near you ♫
♫ Liking your habits,
remembering small moments ♫
♫ Infecting sorrows with smiles ♫
♫ Getting used to what you like,
trying to be brave ♫
♫ Liking becomes natural
and turns into a habit ♫
I'm serious, Aunt.
They were kissing so passionately.
I was stunned.
My pictures
don't show a tenth of the passion.
They don't do it justice.
Yes.
At that moment, it felt as though
the house might've been set on fire.
[The house was on fire?]
No,
it wasn't on fire.
Not literally.
It was only a figure of speech.
[And now?]
[Are they gone?]
Now? I don't know.
[Where are they?]
Well,
they went out right after the kiss.
Who knows where they were off to?
Could they have gone to register
as a couple?
[What?]
Anyway Aunt,
your wish has finally come true.
Congratulations, your grandson
is on the way.
Just you wait. It's going to be awesome.
Are you sure, Lieutenant?
No backing out.
Just make the move.
Check mate!
Take it back.
Are you trying to weasel
your way out?
What's that for?
I'm not.
My hand slipped.
Honestly.
No backsies.
-Xiao Teng.
-"Xiao Xue"?
Xiao Teng.
Tian Yong!
Yes, it's me.
Attention!
Give me the phone.
[Give me the phone!]
Xiao Xue, are you alright?
[I'm fine.]
[I'm just calling to let you know
I'm safely back home.]
That's one day later than
I expected.
Were you waiting for me to call you?
That's right.
What if I didn't call?
I'd keep waiting.
[You idiot.]
Can't you call me?
I can?
Of course you can.
[Xiao Xue.]
What's this about?
I'm taking the initiative.
Are you some kind of dolt?
I'm glad you're okay.
Yes, I'm quite okay.
[Well, then...]
Don't hang up just yet.
Why don't you
recite a poem to me?
Okay.
Which one would you like
to hear?
Whatever you like.
It's not like I'd get it anyway.
[A promise for life.]
[A meeting under the bridge.]
[The tide came before the lady.]
[Hugging the pillar, the man died.]
[This is an excerpt from
Zhuangzi's "The Bandit".]
[It means...]
I like you.
Tian Yong!
[I like you! Do you hear me?]
I hear you.
This is so embarrassing.
Lieutenant.
We like you, too!