Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me
that you were going to die?
I'll... protect you.
I too... will protect you.
There are only 51 days left.
But today's not over yet.
So there are 52 days left.
You don't want the days to pass quickly?
It's because each day I get to
spend with you is so precious.
We can't let this precious day
pass just like this.
Let's go out.
Okay.
Let's go for a walk.
No.
To go on a date with you, Mi Ho, I've fought
obstacles and traveled a difficult road.
So go on a date with me.
Please.
Okay.
You said that if I were stabbed
with this knife,
I'd immediately die and fade away, right?
Because you found out...
are you now thinking of disappearing?
Um... this cow-colored one, and the
pig-colored one and the chicken-colored one.
Please mix them up well.
A lot of the cow-colored one.
A lot of the cow-colored one, please.
Wow!
Honey, you're tired, aren't you?
Yeah, a little.
Oh, I'm tired.
- Woong-ah!
- Oh, I'm tired.
Woong-ah, are you tired?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Mi Ho! You don't have to!
Mi Ho, let me down!
Woong-ah, if you're tired, feel free
to tell me anytime. I'll piggyback you.
O- okay.
You've lost some of your tails but I see
you haven't lost your strength.
I still have five of them left.
I'm an oh*-mi-ho.
[*Oh = five]
I want to eat the cow-colored one first!
All right, eat a lot!
Honey, say ah!
Ah!
Mi Ho, me too, ah!
I'm done!
Hey, you downed that in one shot?
Ah that was delicious!
I feel like I'm about to lose a tail!*
[*from happiness]
My Mi Ho has quite an appetite.
It figures the cow-colored one
is the most delicious out of these, too.
Aigoo, please. How childish.
Woong-ah, what are they doing?
That?
Well they put their hands together
like this...
...and show the other person
that they love them.
Ah, so it's similar to this then.
Hey, that's just cautiously
sending a small display of love.
There are ones that are this big too!
Do you like it?
Yeah!
Hey! I'm shooting you a heart of love
but you just imitate a cow yet again?
This isn't a cow!
This is something I learned from auntie.
These are my heart antennae that are always
pointing towards the one my heart is with.
Is that really what it means?
Yeah!
Ah so that's why Director Ban was
always doing this at the set every day.
Wow... Director's always telling me
to not focus on anything else...
...and just concentrate on the action!
But he's had his share of distractions!
Wait a second... this, this...
Does this mean that Director is going
to secretly come back to meet my aunt?
Min Sook!
I was so lonely
as I was filming in the desert.
Then I suddenly heard your voice.
So you did receive the signal
that my heart sent off.
Beep beep, beep beep.
That's right!
That's how I called for you.
Min Sook...
Oh...
I didn't have time to wash off the sweat...
...that I shed while I was in the desert.
I- it's okay.
Oh, Director!
Oh...
Why don't we...
Let's go sweat out the sweat
that you shed in the desert at the sauna!
Now that I see you, Min Sook,
I'm reminded of a cute lamb I saw
while I was in the desert.
You're like Lawrence of Arabia, Director.
If you have sunglasses on,
you look like Chow Yun Fat.
And with the towel on,
you look like Lawrence.
There's nothing that doesn't suit you.
When I grow a mustache,
I've been told I look like...
Now what kind of Gable was it?
Ah, I was told I resemble Clark Gable.
That's right, that's right!
Then I want to be Vivian Leigh.
What?
That's right!
Vivian Leigh.
Please drink some.
Ah yes.
Cheers.
Now this is called a sauna.
Since our stomachs are cold
from the ice cream...
...we can cover them
and just lay here.
Sauna*? That's a funny name.
[*literally, Heat Treatment Room]
They say people come here to get steamed!
If it were the old times...
...people would have to be cautious
about bringing you here because...
...you could have misunderstood and thought
this was a place for people to get steamed.
That's right, I almost assumed wrong!
Look, it says that they'll roast you there.
[We roast you until you're nice and brown!]
And there you can get heated.
[Please heat yourself moderately]
And there you can get chopped!
[You can chop your whole body here!]
You can steam, roast, heat and chop!
This place seems scarier than a gumiho
who eats people's livers!
Then shall we get a start on steaming,
roasting, heating, and chopping?
Should we?
Let's go there first!
[Please heat yourself moderately]
Since we've come in here,
you've become Steamed Fox.
Since you're Woong,
you're Steamed Bear.
Oh, you.
[Please heat yourself moderately]
Woong-ah! It's too hot!
It's so hot I feel like my tails
are going to catch on fire!
Really?
You don't even have that many tails left
so we can't have that.
Let's go cool your butt off.
Let's go!
Ah, it's so nice and cool!
- You're cool now?
- Yes!
Then does that mean your tails
have calmed down?
Wooooooonnnngggg-ahhhh.
Wow!
Why does he have sunglasses on
when we're at a sauna?
It's Director Ban!
Director Ban?!
I can't let him see that I'm here! Let's go.
Director!
It's my aunt!
Have some eggs!
Have some eggs.
Director, since you went through so much...
...your square jaw
has become as oval as this egg.
You need to take care of your health
so have all of these eggs.
You should leave your body in the hands
of these massage chairs, Min Sook.
It's quite good
at getting every square inch.
They must be a couple.
They look so sweet.
Although I'm not the type of person to speak
badly of someone within earshot,
I always want to tell off those young kids
glued to each other these days.
But it's a common tendency
of young people today...
...to disregard what others think and
openly express their love so passionately.
Look deeply into my eyes.
Although I don't express it as openly...
...the love inside my heart
is at bursting point.
So please don't envy them so much.
Oh, Director!
I didn't tell him I was home yet,
so I can't get caught.
Your aunt must have
kept her heart's antennae up...
...and called him every day
for him to have heard and come back.
You're probably right.
We shouldn't listen to any more.
Let's keep covered and go.
When we were apart,
the time didn't seem to pass at all.
But now that we're together,
several hours flew by.
Yeah, now that we're together,
the time is passing really quickly.
After about 50 years, we'll be like them.
What?
Becoming a shriveled grandma scares you?
No.
I, too, want to be with you for that long.
Wow, that's really cool!
Wow, it's so nice!
It really is.
Do you want to touch it?
Ah, does it still scare you a little?
No, it's fine.
Whoa!
Wow!
It's okay, try coming up!
Come up!
Here. Follow me and do what I do.
Wow!
If at the end of 100 days,
I take back the bead, they say you'll die.
In order to keep you safe,
I have to disappear.
Wow!
Mi Ho!
After I disappear...
- Mi Ho! - ... please don't be too shocked
and don't be in too much pain, okay?
Even then, please still call for me
once in a while like you are now.
Then I'll remain alive in you forever.
Right?
You'll remember me forever, right?
I found you!
You were here?
Yeah, I was here.
By your side.
So Dae Woong left also?
He was really worried because
he had left Mi Ho all by herself.
It was a big turn off seeing
Cha Dae Woong treat girls so poorly...
...but seeing the way he treats her now
makes him look so handsome.
When he has to go back,
he wants to bring Mi Ho with him.
He wants to bring Mi Ho with him?
I, the actress, have to go
in a few weeks...
...so why would the stand-in go now?
And also, how can she leave the country?
That's ridiculous.
Mi Ho has a passport.
What?
Dae Woong already paid for
the plane ticket too.
I always thought Mi Ho's name
was unique but...
...she has another name that's more normal.
What is it?
I think it was Park Sun Ju.
Anyway, it was an ordinary name.
Park Sun Ju?
Seon Nyeo, do you want to go
to the desert with me?
No, it'll mess with my complexion.
Hey, your complexion is so merong*.
[*sticking out tongue]
[Vegetables For A Day]
Drink this.
That monster...
...has the nerve to take a normal name,
get a passport and pretend to be human?
Park Sun Ju.
Park Dong Ju...
Did that person do this?
Did you make her a passport so that
she could follow Dae Woong wherever he went?
It wasn't so that she could go with him,
rather so that I could take her far away.
I won't let her go with him.
Dae Woong wants to go with her!
Grab onto her so that she won't
be able to go with him.
So it's all in Cha Dae Woong's hands.
We can't permit things to remain this way,
can we?
What are you talking about?
I thought you said you weren't
going to do anything to Dae Woong!
Go scare Cha Dae Woong
so I won't have to do anything to him.
Tell him he's in danger.
He must get away from her.
Why do I have to be stuck in
the middle of them and be so scared?
Do I have to get an amulet
against evil or something?
Should I get one each for Dae Woong and me?
Ah this is so annoying!
You saw it?
I've decided that in Mi Ho's Life Plan,
Dae Woong will be included as well.
Hey why are you taking that off?
I think we're going to have to
put this off for now.
Put it off?
I think I was too hasty.
Since this is going to happen
after I become a person, it'll be for later.
I'm going to have to start thinking about
what to do in my last 52 days as a gumiho.
It's not putting it off completely, right?
Woong-ah! I'm hungry. Let's eat!
Mi Ho, I think you've grown
accustomed to rice now.
I think I saw you eating vegetables
and fruit before too.
Yeah, I can eat a lot of plants now
and a lot of rice too!
I'm proud of you.
When I was looking at the album
I saw a lot of pictures too.
I think you're practicing a lot
at being human.
Yeah, I practiced a lot.
I really practiced a lot.
[Dae Woong and Mi Ho's Life Plan -
Mate with Dae Woong - Marry Dae Woong]
You filled it up to here while I was gone.
But let's fill the rest of it together.
Okay.
Should we go skiing this winter?
Ski?
I saw it on TV.
But it needs to snow for that.
I don't think it's going to snow
in the next 52 days.
Let's go as soon as the first snow falls.
This awesome Instructor Cha will teach you.
Skiing in the winter?
Wow, that'll be so cool!
Wow, now this is the ski range.
- All of this is it.
- Wow.
- And the snow is falling like this.
- Isn't this great?
- Yeah!
We're going to come down from up there.
- I'll teach you later.
- Yeah.
- Now should we take a picture first?
- Okay!
Look over there.
One, two, three!
And then, Christmas!
Do you know Grandfather Santa?
I don't know who that is.
He's a friend of my grandfather's,
and presents just come shooting out of him!
He wears this red suit
and his beard is down to here.
I'll introduce you.
Wow.
Yay!
Merry Christmas!
Now Mi Ho, hang it wherever you want to.
- This?
- Yeah!
It would look nice here.
That's right.
Wow it looks so cool!
- Now let's hang this too.
- Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
- Oh Grandfather Santa!
- Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Grandfather Santa, this is Mi Ho.
Mi Ho, this is Grandfather Claus.
Pleasure, pleasure.
Hi, Santa.
In the time I haven't seen you,
I think your beard got even longer!
Is he a foreigner?
Yeah but I think
you're around the same age.
Hi, BF.
Grandfather! Give us presents.
It's going to be so much fun!
Woong-ah, keep telling me more.
I'm having so much fun just listening.
Keep telling me what I can do with you.
Umm, then next spring we'll go
look at flowers by the Han River.
And when you're not afraid of water anymore,
we can go to the beach.
Haeundae, Gyeongpodae*...
[*names of islands]
No. We're going to have to go
straight down the Donghae coast.
More! Tell me more.
Our school's fall festival is really famous.
You know the dragon at my school, right?
The dragon. - Yeah
That dragon finds my school's festival
so fun that...
...there's a legend that he comes out
and plays at night.
Really?
If he really comes out,
I'd like for us to become friends.
Then isn't there anywhere you'd like to go?
Um... the zoo!
I saw it on TV and I could see
a lot of strange looking creatures.
Ah, the zoo?
Why don't we go to the aquarium instead?
The aquarium will probably be a lot cooler.
But I want to try going to the zoo.
The aquarium would be nice though!
Yes, anywhere will be nice.
Ah, we have so much we have to do together!
Yeah, there's so, so much.
So another day has passed.
Now that becoming a human is all wrong,
is there no reason for me to live?
Even sleeping is a waste of time. I'm going
to stay up all night watching him.
My Woong even has handsome eyebrows.
His goatee is cute too!
His hair grew a lot already.
Mi Ho's association registration
is all ready.
Thanks.
Hey, she's going to be going regardless.
Is it that great that you're taking her
just a little earlier?
Yeah. Mi Ho gets sick once in a while,
so I have to stay by her side all the time.
Anyway, thanks for this!
Dae Woong!
That bead of hers that you have in your...
...is it really safe?
Noona, I already told you not to interfere
in Mi Ho's and my business.
I'm not acting this way because of any
residual feelings I might have for you.
I'm truly worried about you, that's all.
That kid Mi Ho...
...I really believe she planned something
with Park Dong Ju and is hiding it from you.
You know that too, Noona?
Dae Woong, you're in danger.
I'm certain that you're stuck between
the two of them and that you're being used!
You're right.
Mi Ho is using me right now.
It's true, right?
Because she needs me,
I told her to use me as much as she wants.
That's everything, right?
Are you really going to follow
Cha Dae Woong and go?
It's because it hurts.
When my tails disappear, it hurts so much
that I have to be by Dae Woong and the bead.
So the pain is lessened
when you're with Cha Dae Woong, right?
That means I won't be able to stop you
from going.
You said that if you go tomorrow,
you'll be back in a month, right?
You need to come back no matter what, okay?
I know.
I have to go out for a little while.
Do you want to stay here?
Okay, I'll stay here. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Of course.
Don't touch it!
Just what are you trying to do?
Teacher Dong Ju, I need your knife.
So if I try to force the bead out of him...
...will you kill yourself with that knife?
Instead of becoming human,
you'd rather die?
To save Cha Dae Woong?
I need to keep Dae Woong safe.
We're going to have to buy another album.
A really big one.
That's quite a grand love you have...
...but it's too one-sided.
You're saying you love Cha Dae Woong enough
that you'd die for him,
but would he do the same?
From what I can see, it doesn't seem so.
Dae Woong loves me.
Then why don't you try asking him?
Would he be willing to die for you?
You're not certain of that, are you?
You're not certain of that...
... so isn't it unfair that
you're preparing yourself for death?
Since you're going to die
without him knowing,
he won't recognize the importance and since
you didn't leave a lasting impression...
...he'll forget about you in no time.
And once he forgets you...
...another woman will take your place.
He won't forget me that quickly,
and he'll long for me.
He won't ever forget me,
and he'll love me for the rest of his life.
You have such a fantasy of love.
That's probably why you made such
a ridiculous decision to die for love.
It seems to you that the person you love
would die for you, right?
But he won't ever be able
to give up his life.
It seems to you that
he'll remember you forever, right?
He'll be quick to forget about you.
It seems to you that he'll think about you
and only you, right?
He'll be immersed in another love.
It seems like you decided to die
because of a fantasy about love,
but you need to get over that.
Then you'll see it's unfair and
you won't be able to die after all.
It's not unfair to me at all.
Try finding out for sure.
Because regret won't mean anything
after death.
Why did Teacher Dong Ju have to go
and say something like that?
I had already made up my mind...
[China/Mongolia]
Woong-ah!
I have something I want to ask you.
Huh?
Imagine we're both drowning in the ocean
and there's only one piece of wood.
- Uh-huh...
- And neither of us can swim.
Then would you give me that piece of wood?
How big is that piece of wood, exactly?
It's so small that
only one person can hold onto it.
If I give it to you, then what about me?
You said I can't swim.
Then am I supposed to just die?
Then you wouldn't give it to me?
You have nothing to worry about,
I'm a good swimmer.
Dae Woong!
Imagine that...
...there was a fire here
and only one of us could escape.
Who would you have escape first?
Think about it carefully.
How would we have time to think in a fire?
We'd just run as fast as we could.
I'd make sure that you got out first though.
That's because you're a gumiho, of course,
you'd make sure the human was safe.
You have nothing to worry about;
there won't ever be a fire here.
Dae Woong!
Imagine that...
Another one?
If you and I were dangling off a cliff and
there's only one rope to climb to safety...
Then would you grab the rope first?
Or would you give it to me?
I don't like mountains so there's no reason
why I'd be dangling from a cliff.
Mi Ho, you've begun worrying about
pointless things, you know that?
Are you starting to worry
because your powers are ebbing away?
That's not it; I just want to know
who you'd give the rope to.
Would you give it to me?
All right, I'll give it to you then.
You can have it all to yourself.
Tell me the honest truth.
You don't really want to give it to me,
do you?
You want it for yourself, don't you?
I said I'd give it to you! You can have it!
Tell me the truth!
You wouldn't give it to me.
You don't care as long as
you're alive, right?
Of course I want to stay alive,
who in the world wants to die?
Mi Ho, you have no reason to worry about
such pointless things.
I'm going to take a short nap,
so you should go take one too.
I'm going to sleep now!
Aigoo.
Saying that he'd die in my place
isn't the only way he can show me his love.
That's just a fantasy.
That's right,
I'm not hoping for anything like that.
I just want him to keep remembering me.
That's it.
Let's go shopping for some things
to bring to China.
You're going to have to buy
another pair of sneakers, right?
Woong-ah, you bought me a pair
before you left. The white ones.
You don't remember?
Ah, did I?
It must have slipped my mind.
You don't remember?
You forgot?!
Even though it hasn't even been a month?
I'm sorry.
Then aside from sneakers,
is there anything else you need?
Woong-ah, do you remember what chased us
when you first saw me?
Umm... a boar!
Then do you remember what you said
when you first saw me?
I said you were a demon.
No, you said, "Wow, you're pretty. "
Hey that was said
in a moment of shameless ogling.
Okay, fine, I'll give that a pass.
Then do you remember what kind of tree
I perched you on?
Tree?
A tree is just a tree...
You don't remember if the tree's leaves
were pointy or round?
Hey, who in the world
can remember things like that?
I guess no one
would remember things like that.
What's going on with you?
Is your memory fading along
with your powers?
Man, that's not good...
No! I have a good memory.
I remember everything.
Mi Ho!
It's normal for him not to remember
every little thing.
But... he will start to forget
more and more, right?
Dae Woong said he has a punishable memory.
Do you know a good fortune teller?
Fortune teller?
I know a shaman that was in my dad's movie.
Will my place be filled by
The Hater or Merong?
Mi Ho! Let's go.
Woong-ah,
today let's go where I want to go...
...and have fun
and never forget anything, okay?
Let's do it.
Where do you want to go?
Ah, where I said I wanted to go yesterday.
W- where?
I said just yesterday.
You don't remember?
So where is that?
The zoo!
I said yesterday
that I wanted to go to the zoo!
A- ah, the z- zoo...
Of all the places I said yesterday,
I couldn't think of the zoo.
H- hey, but that's possible of me.
Why are you getting so mad?
If you can't even remember what I said
yesterday, what on earth will you remember?
Mi Ho...
You'll forget everything,
and not give me the rope.
And be with The Hater and Merong,
aren't you?
Then... then it'll be unfair for me!
Mi Ho!
Oh my, I guess they fight too.
I know, right?
Maybe it was good I backed off before
I got a charm to use against them.
Unni, were you going to use a charm
to force them to break up?
Even you aren't Jang Hee Bin*, Unni.
[*legendary femme fatale]
That's not it.
Ahjumma.
If someone passes away...
...do people forget about them completely
and continue living their lives?
Of course, people that are alive
have to keep living!
As I work hard in this chicken shop, I don't
think about the person who left before me.
Aigoo, if I wallowed in thoughts of him...
...do you think I'd be able to
get on with my life and survive?
Woong-ah!
Woong-ah, are you inside?
Don't come in!
Dae Woong, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I was wrong.
Don't come in yet!
Woong-ah, don't be mad anymore!
Let's talk face-to-face!
No!
You're really mad, aren't you?
Aish!
Man, I was almost done too!
What is this?
Kimbap.
We need some
if we're going to go to the zoo.
I bought some bubbly water too.
Woong-ah...
We went to the zoo.
Really?
To the zoo?
Yes. At the zoo,
we saw a big Dae Woong bear...
...a baby bear, another bear
that looked like Ddoong Ja, and a fox too.
Aigoo.
You were at the sauna yesterday,
weren't you?
It was you, wasn't it?!
How could-
Your grandfather
wanted so badly to see you.
How could you go see your girlfriend
as soon as you get back?
My word, they say that when a man falls
for a woman, he can't see anything else...
I don't think you should be one to talk.
From what I heard,
Seon Nyeo desperately missed her dad.
Y- you can't tell his daughter
that he came to me first, okay?
He was in such a hurry that
he came to see me and went back to China.
Aunt, I came to be a good grandson
to grandfather.
I brought Mi Ho so that grandfather
would help me make...
...progress on the life plan
we came up with.
Life plan?
We have one.
Ah, grandfather needs to be able
to help me a lot...
Really?
When I see that Dae Woong went to the zoo
because you said you wanted to,
I can see that you're very special to him.
Why?
Dae Woong was enjoying himself
at the zoo, too.
Dae Woong's mom and dad
were on their way back from there...
...when they got into their accident.
Then does Dae Woong dislike the zoo?
Of course.
Whenever they went on picnics at school...
...if he heard they'd be going near the zoo,
he always said he didn't want to go.
Of course it'd bother him.
But I guess its okay when he goes with you.
Dae Woong said that he couldn't really
remember his mom and dad well.
Since it happened when he was young...
he wouldn't be able to remember much.
Where should I put this, Aunt?
Put it right there.
We have to make sure they're arranged well.
I was only hoping you'd remember me.
I didn't think about whether
the memories might be painful for you.
Meat.
Now there's exactly half the time left.
Yeah, there are 50 days left.
You might even become a person
while we're in China.
No, no. It's a notable time in history
that a gumiho is becoming a human.
So of course you need to become a person
on Korean ground.
Wherever we are, it doesn't matter
as long as I'm next to you.
Woong-ah, during the 50 days we have left,
let's make as many good memories as we can.
Since you're only my gumiho girlfriend
until here.
Even though I'm really sorry about you
feeling pain...
...I want to give you a lot to
remember me by.
Then it won't be unfair for me at all.
Mi Ho.
Is it unfair to you that
you're giving up being a gumiho?
You're going to gain an incredible 50 years
by giving up 500.
By Cha Dae Woong's side.
Don't feel like it's unfair.
Yeah, it's not unfair at all.
More than 500 years or 50 years...
...if these next 50 days are that
much more beautiful, that's fine with me.
Since there's a lot of luggage,
we need to call a van.
Byung Soo, are these forms
all I need to take with me?
Yeah.
But when is Mi Ho coming?
She's going separately because
she has people she needs to see first.
We arranged to meet at the airport later.
Goodbye, Grandfather.
All right, go on.
Go and work hard before you come back,
all right?
No, don't work too hard.
Given the circumstances,
just do what you can.
Share this with Dae Woong...
...and give this
and this to Director Ban, okay?
Yes.
I'll give these to him on your behalf, too.
Aunt, take care.
Ddoong Ja, since you're
Dae Woong's best fried...
...take good care of him, okay?
Bye.
There. Since our chicken is fresh
before fried, it's tasty, isn't it?
Yes! It's very delicious.
Isn't it great?
Yes, it's so good.
Bye, Ahjumma.
Oh! The Hater.
Hey, don't go with Dae Woong.
If you're by his side, I feel like
something bad will happen to Dae Woong.
Tell him you can't go,
and stay here cleaning the action school.
I'm going to go.
Each day I get to spend with Dae Woong
is precious to me.
If you go, I'm going to tell everyone
that you're a gumiho.
Do whatever you want.
I have proof that I'm a citizen, a passport,
and a driver's license.
Even then if you go around telling people
that I'm a gumiho...
...they'll all say you're crazy.
The only one who's crazy is Dae Woong!
How in the world did you bewitch him?
Should I teach you?
Because I liked him.
Because I liked him so, so, so, so, so much,
he liked me back.
If you want to bewitch someone, just say
that you like him so, so, so, so, so much.
Like this.
What kind of sign is that?
I'm teaching you a really great sign
so you should use it too.
'Bye, Hater.
What the...?
Oh, Dae Woong.
I said my goodbyes and am all packed.
I'll go to where we get on the plane.
Are you with Byung Soo?
Okay.
I guess I won't be able to come back here.
Goodbye to this place, too, then.
I had something I wanted to tell you
if I saw you again, Teacher Dong Ju.
I'm glad.
By leaving this way, you're planning on
disappearing while you're there, right?
So does that mean that you've decided...
to die in Cha Dae Woong's place?
Teacher Dong Ju...
Does saying I'll die in Dae Woong's place
seem that pathetic to you?
Saying that you're going to...
...die for a worthless human
seems foolish to me.
But I think I'm cool!
Since I'm a gumiho
and can't become human after all,
I like that I can give all that I can
to the person I love.
I think you came all the way here
because you wanted to try and stop me,
but just leave me be.
I don't want you to try and stop me,
Teacher Dong Ju.
I...
...believed that love was doing what the
other person wanted me to, and once I did...
...I spent a thousand years regretting it.
I don't want to repeat
the same mistake again.
I'm not your Kil Dal, Teacher Dong Ju.
I'll go now.
Bye.
Dae Woong's probably getting ready
to leave right now.
I told you I wouldn't be able
to stop them.
She said that she was going to go
no matter what.
At this point the only thing left to do
is tell Cha Dae Woong.
Tell Dae Woong what?
You know that that person is in possession
of the fox bead, right?
I know.
I heard that thanks to the fox bead,
he can't be injured so he's completely safe.
If the fox bead remains in his body,
he'll be safe.
But Cha Dae Woong and the fox
made a promise to each other.
He'll keep the fox bead for a hundred days
and then return it to the fox.
That's the way a gumiho can become human.
She's going to become human?
But there's something that guy doesn't know.
If the fox bead that comes into possession
of a human is taken out of his body,
that person will die.
What do you mean by that?
Just like he promised the gumiho,
if he returns the bead after a hundred days,
it means Cha Dae Woong will die.
Dae Woong is going to die?
Those two haven't left yet.
Go stop Cha Dae Woong
so they won't leave together.
Is it heavy?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Driver, to Incheon Airport please.
All right.
I can't let you leave.
Dae Woong's going to come now.
I'm going to go with him.
You're waiting for Cha Dae Woong?
He won't come.
I told you to stop interfering
in our business.
I told you that you were being used
and tricked, didn't I?
I was right.
You need to leave that girl's side
and run away immediately!
What are you talking about?
I have to go and board the plane.
You can't go!
You can't be with her.
- Noona!
- You!
If you stay with her... you'll die.
What?
Since he found out that he's going to die...
...Cha Dae Woong will not appear
by your side again.
He'll probably run away from you
to somewhere far away.
Why did you do it, Teacher Dong Ju?
Why did you tell Dae Woong?
I was trying to prevent him
from finding out.
I didn't want to force him to choose...
...between life and death because of me.
But why did you do it?
Why?!
You can eventually catch a person
who runs away...
...but not someone's consciousness
if she throws it away.
You're in your love fantasy so deep...
...that you're about to make
a stupid choice.
I'm trying to break that fantasy.
Humans never risk their lives
for something like love.
That's enough.
You know that too,
that's why you can't ask Cha Dae Woong...
...if he's willing to die for you.
If he tells you the truth that
he wants you to die instead of him...
...that grand love will crack.
Cha Dae Woong won't come to you.
Even if he coolly comes now...
once he's actually facing death,
he'll double back and run away.
Lose this fantasy of love
and protect yourself.
Teacher Dong Ju, you're really cruel.
All I've done is shown you reality
instead of fantasy.
Through this situation
in which one of you must die.
Are you telling me that because
my love is all a lie and a fantasy...
...you want me to break it off
and run away to live?
Cha Dae Woong won't come.
If you realize this and accept it,
you'll be able to keep on living.
If Mi Ho takes the bead I'll die,
and if she doesn't, she'll die?
Dae Woong...
the fact that Park Dong Ju had me
tell you this,
didn't seem like it was because
he wanted to help you.
It's probably because he's telling me to
leave Mi Ho and run away if I want to live.
Dae Woong, where are you going?
To Mi Ho.
Are you crazy?!
Why are you going there?
He said you're going to die!
Are you saying you'll die
because of a worthless monster like her?!
I won't die!
I promise you I won't.
Cha Dae Woong isn't coming.
Just leave everything to me.
Go to Japan with me.
After that, getting the bead back
from Cha Dae Woong,
I will investigate how to do it.
Okay.
I'll do what you say, Teacher Dong Ju.
All right.
Since there are still 50 days left...
try and change the decision you made.
We can leave for Japan immediately.
There should be tickets available.
Excuse me.
Where is the ticketing office?
It's okay with me if Dae Woong doesn't come.
No. He shouldn't come.
Because my heart isn't a broken fantasy
but something real.
Mi Ho!
Dae Woong!
Are you just going to run away?!
Even though I'm here?!
So when a hundred days are up,
one of us has to die?
Since something so ridiculous is our fate,
we're supposed to calmly accept it
or run away from each other?
I can't do that.
I won't!
I won't wait for the day
that one of us has to die.
I don't want to either.
Today marks exactly half of
the hundred days that have passed.
Mi Ho.
Take the bead from me right now.
You want me to take the bead from you
right now?
Then what?
I don't know what's going to happen.
But that punk probably doesn't know either.
So we should make the decision
and go with it.
I'll lay my life on the line,
and you'll give up on becoming a human.
And we're going to go with it.
We don't know if we'll live or die.
Then...
the two of us are grabbing the one rope.
Mi Ho... I love you.
So I won't die in order to save you.
You shouldn't do it either.
Dae Woong... I love you.
I won't die on your behalf either.
So neither should you.
This is the decision I can make
as the person that loves you.
Even though I'm not sure of the outcome,
we're in it together.
If we live, we'll both live.
And if we die, we'll both die.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: soluna413
Spot Translators: serendipity, yOiTzO
Timer: dizzybugs
Editor/QC: reluctantbutaddicted
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com