Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Starting from now, I'm your girlfriend.
You and I are a couple.
That's right,
even though you're really unfortunate, and
really unlucky, we are indeed a couple.
But you agreed, only for 100 days.
Dae Woong, since we're a couple,
can you fulfill something
that I've always wanted to do?
We've already gone this far,
what is there we can't do?
What is it that you want to do?
Why are you holding a towel?
You even drew on your face.
Please receive a bow from a little miss.
Stop!
I've got the general idea
of what you're about to do.
You can't do this.
I've always wanted to do this!
Just let me finish!
No!
Because of the bead, I had no choice
but to be your boyfriend.
And now you're seizing the chance
for me to become your groom?
Wow, Gu Mi Ho is so shameless
that I'm speechless!
Gu Mi Ho is really so shameless
that nobody has anything to say.
I really wanted to do the whole thing.
What a pity.
Woong! Then let's mate!
What?
I think I heard wrong.
What did you say?
Mate!
You're that happy?
Ah, seriously. Seriously...
If I had to mate with a gumiho,
I'd much rather spit out the bead.
You think you can spit it out like that?
Until 100 days have passed, you
definitely won't be able to get it out.
During this period of time,
you belong to me.
Okay then. Come on.
What you wanted, is it this?
No, I was just joking.
Don't casually joke around.
I'm sorry.
Normal girls are all like this.
Okay then. Come on.
What you wanted, is it this?
Mi Ho, don't be like that!
I was just joking!
That won't do!
I really was only joking.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let go of me. Let go.
Was I too impulsive,
so I did something stupid?
No, thinking about the bead in
my stomach makes me feel better.
I just have to endure 100 days,
then I'll have reached the end.
He actually dares to joke
around with a gumiho.
Made me like him, but without fruition.
After 100 days, I will become human!
100 days starting from now.
After 100 days, one bulb will be empty.
The other bulb will be completely filled up.
We're not in a relationship,
we're just in a type of contract.
I'm in because of the bead, and you're
in because you want to stay here.
We're together because
of each others' needs.
But there's a boundary line between
human and gumiho...
that neither of us are able to cross.
Let's just cooperate with each other.
I know,
I won't do anything that you don't like.
If it's like that,
then you don't have to look at me with
an expression like you're going to eat me.
It looks like I'm going to eat you?
Strange, I haven't thought
about that recently.
Recently?
Ah, so sleepy.
You can't go to sleep like this!
Why? I'm really tired.
I need to address this.
I have to get it straight.
Did you have thoughts of
wanting to eat me before?
Why are you asking this type of question?
Even if it was just once.
"Wow, Dae Woong must definitely be tasty."
You never thought that before?
You're a gumiho!
Just in case you can't
control your instinct,
you still can't make a mistake.
I don't want to say it.
I'll be understanding, so just say it.
Did you or did you not have
these kinds of thoughts?
Just once.
Just once?
Actually it was twice!
It was actually twice?
What's wrong?
Didn't you say that you'd be understanding?
What kind of person can
understand these things?
I shouldn't have asked.
Let's maintain a distance between us.
Woong!
Right now...
I don't have the confidence to face you.
If I'd known this earlier,
I wouldn't have said it.
Twice?
Maybe three times, four times, who knows.
I love you, you fool
Do you want to go to the
delicious udon soup shop...
and drink a bowl of udon soup together?
The two of us should have
had some good udon soup...
I want to be with you
The way I'm like this is...
the fluttering of love
Please stay by my side
Please don't leave me
When I close my eyes
after time has passed...
I am a rough man, who smells like Icy Hot.
How pungent.
Eyes and heart are both very pungent.
You scared me!
What's wrong with you?
Are you crying?
It won't rub off.
The stuff on my face won't rub off.
What did you use to draw it?
This.
You used a permanent marker
to draw on your face?
I thought it was a regular blush.
Let me see. Lift up your head.
How can a gumiho like you be so stupid?
Let's find a solution.
Typing: Methods to remove
permanent marker stains
A lot of people replied.
Seems like there are many people
who are as stupid as you.
Then that means I've made a mistake
that many people make.
Glue.
Glue?
It's so comfortable.
Sit still!
Oh, it came off!
Really?
Yes.
It's your fault for insisting
on drawing this on your face.
I've always wanted to put blush on my
face and pretend to get married.
Before, I was going to get
married and live a human life.
But, once the rumor spread that
gumihos eat livers, nobody came.
So, I wasn't able to get married before
I was locked up in that painting.
Turns out you were the victim
of evil at that time.
What is evil?
Talking behind people's back,
harming intentionally, spreading rumors.
Seems like back then, there were also
these types of bad people.
I honestly never ate a person before.
But before, a tiger wanted to eat people.
I blocked it and told it to not eat people.
You blocked it?
That tiger listened to you?
Yeah.
"If you don't listen, I will eat you."
Ah...
so you mainly said that you'll
eat the opponent as a threat.
It's already been 500 years, but this
type of problem still arises.
From what I can see, this problem
is very difficult to overcome.
This prejudice is truly
very difficult to change.
Wait until I've become a famous actor.
I'll star together with my
friend Kim Byung Soo.
We'll film a movie that will shatter
people's perception of gumihos.
It'll wash away any accusations about you.
Really?
That's right.
If I can become an actor,
your bead gets some credit.
A small present like that
is quite necessary.
That's right, present!
Wait for me!
You'll definitely be greatly surprised!
Mi Ho, what is the thing
that you like the best?
Meat!
That's right.
This thing, regardless of
its appearance or size,
has, even at first glance,
obviously been made for you.
You can't show your tails or anything
just because you're too excited.
Okay.
Prepared especially for Miss Gu Mi Ho,
the super, king size, massive beyond
comparison, chicken drumstick!
Chicken drumstick!
Wow, that meat is really big!
Here, Mi Ho, I give you meat.
Catch it!
Mi Ho, are you okay?
Mi Ho, what's wrong? You don't like it?
Because it's not real meat,
are you disappointed?
No, it's because I'm too happy.
My tails aren't going to show,
but my tears are about to fall.
Next time, I'll look for
a beef ribs plushie.
This can't be bitten, otherwise
cotton will be come out.
But I still want to pretend
like I'm eating it.
If there are drumsticks this big, then
wouldn't the wings be as big as this room?
As big as the entire room.
If there really was a chicken this big,
my life's road would be a lot smoother.
What a pity.
Does the Director know that
Dae Woong got injured?
Not yet.
Didn't Hae In unni advise him to give up?
Was he planning to give up?
I did talk to him about it, but we
haven't been in contact since.
Dae Woong shouldn't be hurt
because of what I said, right?
I don't even have to see it to know,
she definitely hurt him.
When Hae In unni speaks, she always
likes to make herself sound innocent.
When she does that, she's very hateful.
She knew that Cha Dae Woong got into
an accident, she's just too much!
Dae Woong definitely can't say that he's
giving up face to face with the director.
Before he acts impulsively
and hurts himself even more,
looks like I'll have to tell the director.
Director!
Exactly what kind of person are you?
How did you do it?
It's simply perfect action.
Look into my eyes.
You don't have fear in your eyes.
What is fear? I do not know.
After doing three somersaults in the air,
and when landing on one foot,
you weren't scared?
Absolutely not.
Usually when you're landing on one foot,
your ankle will crack and break.
I won't be scared of getting injured.
I'm not the type of person who'd sacrifice
the seriousness of the moves out of fear.
Wow... too inspirational!
The moves you perform...
will let you be inspiring.
I will give you even greater inspiration.
Inspiration.
Ah, inspiration.
Are you really okay?
Have you been enduring
too much pain?
Look carefully into my eyes.
Do these eyes...
look like I've been going
through a hard time?
Didn't I say that I was okay?
It's all been resolved.
At one glance, it looks
exactly like a couple ring.
He was even wearing it proudly.
Cha Dae Woong... how can he
have another girlfriend already?
Who is it?
I reckon it should be Hae In noona.
Unni, let me see your hand.
This doesn't look like a couple ring.
Couple ring?
Unni, is this the couple ring that
you're wearing with Dae Woong?
It's not.
Then who is Cha Dae Woong
wearing a couple ring with?
What do you mean by that?
Cha Dae Woong is like lightning.
He has another girlfriend already!
Girlfriend?
Dae Woong has always been popular.
Plus this time, he even
started to film a movie.
Movie?
I thought that couldn't be filmed anymore.
They say that Dae Woong's
body has recovered a lot.
There don't seem to be any problems, so
they're still going to film the movie.
You didn't know?
It really isn't noona then.
Couple ring? Who with?
Dae Woong
I became Dae Woong's girlfriend.
Looks like he really did need the bead.
This type of ring is bought for
the person you like, right?
Cha Dae Woong doesn't show
affection towards you.
And doesn't consider you as a human.
I will become human.
Maybe in the future, he will like me.
Seems like you wish for
Cha Dae Woong to like you.
What does he like about you?
Dae Woong said before that I'm very special.
He said that I can run fast,
jump high, and am powerful.
There are cars that can go fast,
and planes that can fly high.
Those kinds of abilities aren't useful,
even if they are considered special.
Things that are far away,
I can see and hear them clearly.
Those kinds of abilities
can't compare with this.
He also praises me when I eat a lot.
That's going to cost more money.
Even if he likes a woman who
can make a lot of money,
he won't like a woman who only
knows how to spend money.
I'm very beautiful.
That... I admit.
But women who just go on their beauty,
cause very large side effects.
I strongly suggest that you don't talk about
mating with Cha Dae Woong in the future.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Don't be like before and threaten
him to get what you want.
Try and help him with what he wants to do.
What Dae Woong wants to do?
You like this, right?
Eat it while you're thinking it over.
Am I a dog?
I'm sorry, I was too careless.
Don't eat it on the road.
Miss, miss.
That sounds too disgusting.
That sounds too casual.
Dae Woong!
Yes?
Since you gave me a present like this,
I also want to help you with
what you want to do.
What should I do for you?
I wish that you can be a bit quieter.
I want to do something for you!
Say what you want. Woong, Woong!
- Woong! Woong! Woong! Woong!
- You're so noisy.
If you can't even be quiet
when I tell you to,
what else could you do for me?
Whatever you want, I will do it for you.
Really?
Then, if I tell you quit eating meat,
can you do it?
I'm not planning on giving Gu Mi Ho
any excessive requests.
You don't have to think about it.
Just be quiet.
I will be quiet.
In the future, you definitely
have to tell me.
And I will definitely help you fulfill it.
I'll think about it.
Someone's coming!
That's right.
May I ask, is there a problem?
Oh, the director asked us
to clean up this room.
Director, during this period of time
that I'm filming the movie,
please allow me to continue
living in the room up there.
That's a storage room. I was afraid that
you'd think living there is inconvenient.
Is it because you have some problems
that you're like this?
I want to concentrate all
my energy on the movie.
If I live here, I can practice
all the time.
Then I'll consider it and let you stay here.
I will manage this Action School well.
I'll keep watch of the door at night,
and I'll even clean when I have time.
I'll also wipe the equipment
so it's sparkling clean.
That house number is covered with dust.
I will clean that, too!
I cleaned that yesterday.
But if you're going to stay here,
your aunt will be coming in and out.
I'll call her and tell her
to stop coming in and out.
That's not it, that's not it!
I'm not a person who's picky about
someone coming in and out.
You can just live here.
Thank you!
Ah, that's right.
Have you seen a girl around here,
with long hair,
wearing a white dress who can jump
really high, and run really far?
Run far?
If you see her, ask for her phone number.
Mi Ho, by any chance...
did the director see you that day,
when you kicked down that wall?
I don't know.
Last time he saw me, he started chasing me!
Really?
Mi Ho, no matter what, don't ever
appear in front of the director.
If you see him, you have to run away.
Okay.
Real Action. My dream.
What's your name?
Don't even know her name.
Director, we're going to a shop that
makes the best udon soup for lunch.
Let's go.
Udon soup?
In the near future, don't mention
udon soup in front of me.
Then what do you want to eat?
Black food. Black bean noodles.
It's really great!
Only special people have it,
it's a very rare limited edition
that isn't sold anywhere.
Limited editions are good right?
Of course!
Once you wear that, you'll look
exactly like a fashionista.
That's good too, right?
It's saying that you're smart.
I'm already prepared...
Ahjumma!
My bag looks really smart, right?
Ban Do Hoon's Action School
Opening Souvenir
Yes.
Ahjumma's bag is really nice, too.
Ahjumma is also a fashionista.
Thanks.
Tonight I'm going to eat chicken.
Okay.
You and that ahjumma became friends?
Do we look like friends?
You greeted each other and
talked about a fashion topic.
And you even praised her.
Isn't that being friends?
So it's like that!
Then the chicken wing shop's
owner is my friend!
You're making friends on your own.
Good job.
Who is this?
This is Cha Dae Woong, right?
I'm Park Dong Ju.
Who?
If Mi Ho is with you,
please give her the phone.
Mi Ho?
Is it Mr. Dong Ju?
He told me to give you the phone.
Oh, Mr. Dong Ju. It's me.
I'm very curious about your progress.
You're doing well, right?
Yes. Wait a minute.
Hey, just talk over here.
I listened to what you said
and didn't mention mating.
Do you know what Cha Dae Woong
wants now?
He said that he'll tell me later.
Whatever Dae Woong wants,
I will definitely do it.
It seems like their relationship is good.
I'll go over and hang out another day.
Who was it?
Park Dong Ju.
Mr. Dong Ju is my friend.
Friend?
Mr. Dong Ju?
She said she'll come over and hang out?
Seems she thinks I'm her friend.
She doesn't even know
what I want her to do.
It ought to be like this.
You even have a friend who
you can hang out with?
He treats me very well
and we're very close.
That person doesn't know you're a gumiho,
so he's treating you well,
and you're very close?
Hiding your true identity and then
hanging out with him is wrong, isn't it?
What does he do?
How did you meet?
Woong.
Don't ask any questions
related to Mr. Dong Ju.
I'm not curious,
I'm just a bit worried about that guy.
Don't worry, I won't do anything bad to him.
What?
Won't do anything bad?
Threatening to eat me, tormenting
me to buy meat for her to eat,
But pretending to be kind
to her new friend.
If something happens to him, I'll feel bad.
Tell him to stop calling me in the future.
I understand.
I'll tell him to stop calling.
I'll just go and hang out with him.
It sounded like a young man.
Looks like he's enchanted by her looks.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk... how foolish.
Wow... so pretty.
There are a lot of people looking at her,
drooling with greed.
The bus is here, let's go.
Okay.
Didn't you tell me to keep
a distance from you?
Why are you sitting beside me?
I never thought much about it,
but I have the task of protecting
these foolish people.
I can't just not care.
My childhood dream was to become Batman,
but I've never thought of using
this way of protecting the world.
Ah, what a pain.
Excuse me.
What?
What do you want?
You're Cha Dae Woong sunbae, right?
I'm your high school junior,
do you remember?
Hoobae, you look kind of familiar.
Really?
Your name is...?
Mi Nyeo, Go Mi Nyeo.
That's right, it's Mi Nyeo!
Right, right, right!
I even wrote you a letter
at the graduation ceremony.
Did you?
You've gotten more handsome.
Mi Nyeo got prettier, too.
I have to get off at this stop.
Sunbae, you've changed phone numbers, right?
Yes, I changed numbers.
My number is...
I'm sorry for bothering you
and your girlfriend.
Mi Nyeo, bye.
This ring is amazing.
Just by showing it to them, they will leave.
That's right, they all left.
Woong, because I didn't let you continue
talking to that woman, are you angry?
She's my very close hoobae whom
I haven't seen in a long time.
Because of you, she left before
I even greeted her properly.
If I didn't intervene,
I was afraid that you'd want to mate
with her and run off with her.
What do you take me for?
Hey, I'm not that type of an easy man.
I'm popular,
but I've only had one person in
my heart and it has never changed.
Is that person the person from last time?
Yes, it's Hae In noona.
If you like her that much,
why didn't you make her
your girlfriend earlier?
I even had the rings prepared,
but it didn't work out.
By any chance, that ring
isn't this one, right?
You originally wanted to give it to her,
but she didn't want it,
so you gave it to me?
Noona never said that she didn't like me.
If I asked her now, she'd definitely
say she likes me.
You can't be like this!
I know, so it's okay.
I didn't give her the ring,
so you have the opportunity to wear it.
What?
I'm wearing it because of that?
Between you who's wearing noona's ring
and me who gave you that ring,
I'm the one more deserving of sympathy.
If you don't like it,
then give it back to me.
Okay, I'll take mine off too.
Wearing this makes me nervous.
Taking it off, of course,
makes me feel more relaxed.
Enough, just wear it.
Let's go.
Why?
Are we going somewhere where
only humans can enter again?
You're finally starting to
get the hang of things.
Wait here.
Sha la la la la la
As I sing a song
I will dream and sing your name
Sha la la la la la
As your woman,
Lovingly, I will only look at you.
Sha la la la la la
As I sing a song
I will dream and sing your name
Sha la la la la la
As your woman
Lovingly, I will only look at you.
Why don't you come in, too?
I can go in too?
Although I don't feel confident in you,
but I'll try and see.
But you have to observe quietly,
you definitely can't stir up trouble.
I know, I'll just observe obediently.
Go in!
Wait a minute!
This has dirt, wipe it off.
Don't touch anything without
permission, understand?
Let's go.
In here, you just have to listen seriously
and pay attention in class.
So you just have to listen?
Yes.
Occasionally the professor will
ask someone for a response.
You definitely can't make eye contact.
I understand.
There are too many extras
that have to be filmed.
The class's curriculum needs to be adjusted.
That's right.
You definitely can't make eye contact.
It's nice.
You look awkward if you sit there like that.
Open this.
What is this?
Are these words?
That's English, English.
This is a foreign language.
Can you read this?
Read a bit.
Mi Ho, I think you're too nervous.
I'm very nervous.
It feels like my tails are
going to stand up.
To relieve your pressure, I'll buy
some soda water. Wait for me.
You definitely can't let anyone else
know that you're not a student.
Yes.
It feels like I've really become human.
If I fall asleep in class,
I'll be really embarrassed.
I'll drink some coffee before going in.
Dae Woong!
You're going to drink coffee?
Yes.
Then get me a drink, too.
Coins...
What do you want to drink?
Oh, there's fruit beverages in here.
Fruit is beneficial to the skin
and the body.
Why don't you drink that?
Give me two bottles.
I'm going to eat sandwiches with a friend.
Two.
Did you come here to attend class?
Yes.
Where's the classroom?
Over there.
Here.
Thanks.
Also, I'm sorry, Dae Woong.
Last time I wanted to advise you,
so I said some ruthless words.
I think I overdid it.
You understand my heart, right?
Oh,
Noona. I'm doing pretty well.
Don't worry.
Pay attention in class. I'm leaving.
Noona, I'll call you.
Aish!
Ah, it went that far under?
Come quickly.
I'm going to take this to someone.
Wait a bit.
Noona!
How strange.
What's wrong?
Did I scare you?
Don't be scared anymore.
I just knew that you'd get scared.
Noona has been scared this thoroughly.
I really feel successful.
It's your evildoing again!
What were you doing,
coming to the classroom?
This sandwich... I came here
to give it to you.
Ah, sandwich.
Thanks, Noona.
It's time for you to go to class, right?
I don't have anything to do,
is it okay if I attend class with you?
I don't have a class.
I got it wrong.
I let Byung Soo help me choose classes.
I got some mixed up.
You don't have a class?
Then eat with me!
Okay.
I'll go get my bag.
Count to one hundred,
wait for me to get back.
Yes.
I have some administration problems,
and I have to go the department office.
Really? Let's go!
Mi Ho,
didn't you want to attend class?
You stay and listen to the class.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere, just stay here.
This is the teaching material, read this.
If you're bored, just jot down
what the professor is saying.
I'll be right back.
Noona!
In front of the school there's a newly-
opened Chinese restaurant, let's go there.
Oh?
Let's just eat sandwiches here.
I'm apologizing to you
along the way, it's on me.
Let's drive my car there.
Nothing should happen, right?
Regarding the classification
of normal behaviour,
there are a few points for discussion below.
That student. What's wrong?
The student with her hand raised,
what is it?
What?
A fly.
I want to know everything.
Dae Woong was right, I can't make
eye contact with him.
I'll wait for him outside.
I want black bean noodles.
No, I said that I'm inviting
you to eat something good.
We'll have two sets of meal A.
Yes.
Meal A?
Wow, it's really long.
Eat slowly.
Okay, slowly.
When is Dae Woong coming?
I'm starving to death.
I'll just go home by myself.
Dad, thank you!
Real Action.
Wow, she's faster than a car.
And it seems like she hasn't
even run that much.
Seriously, she's already so far ahead.
Oh, hurry.
Ah, what's wrong with me?
My body feels strange.
You will gradually die.
The fruits after the meal.
I'm finished, let's go!
Why are you eating so fast?
Be careful, you could get indigestion.
Oh, probably because I was too hungry.
I swallowed before I could chew.
Let's go, Noona.
Ah, I think I got indigestion.
What?
I thought that she'd be waiting for me here.
I wolfed down a meal, and ran
over flustered and confused.
But she went home by herself.
You really came over.
My body is acting strange.
Suddenly, there was something
thumping in my body.
My throat felt suffocated all at once.
And then my body started to heat up,
I couldn't move for awhile.
It's really uncomfortable.
That's called pain.
You've never experienced pain before,
so you'll feel alarmed.
But humans often get injured
and will feel pain.
Then that means I'm a bit
similar to humans now?
That could count.
You'll still feel like that in the future.
It'll get worse as time passes.
Can you bear it?
As long as I become human,
I'll have to bear it.
I thought you didn't eat meat.
You said that you'd come hang out,
so I prepared this.
Weren't you in pain? Eat lots.
Humans are all like this.
Originally today was chicken day.
If Mi Ho knew we're eating beef today,
she'd be even happier.
Today I'm specially giving you
Grade A Korean beef to eat.
After heating the grill,
we can eat right away.
It's very cold.
How did I come to meet you,
what kind of fate is this?
The more I see you,
my heartbeat seems to get stranger
Could it be love?
I'm starting to like you so much
It's late.
Does she know my heart feels like this?
Mr. Dong Ju, this is the place where I live.
Ohh.
That's Mr. Dong Ju?
He's not that good looking.
Let's hang out next time.
I will prepare lots of meat.
Meat?
Mr. Dong Ju, the meat you gave me
to eat today was really delicious.
Was it expensive?
Of course it's expensive. Very.
So it is.
Then Dae Woong definitely won't
buy it for me to eat.
That girl...
What is he doing?
You're fine now.
Next time you're uncomfortable,
come find me.
Okay.
Oh, it's Dae Woong!
There's something that I'm curious about.
Why do you call me Mr. Dong Ju?
Because you're my teacher who's
teaching me how to become human.
So of course it'll be Mr. Dong Ju.
Do you trust me completely?
Have you lied to me?
No. I've never lied to you before.
Although... I haven't told you everything.
Then I'll still find you
to continue learning.
Wait for me. Bye, bye!
Wait for you.
Making me wait for you.
Oh, it's beef!
Is it Korean beef?
What, this is cheap beef.
Why is the one who came back
after eating expensive beef,
still running over here to eat cheap beef?
Oh, so you heard what I said to Mr. Dong Ju.
Isn't your behaviour incorrect?
Hiding your true identity,
eating the expensive meat that a man bought
for you, riding in his expensive car.
You're a gumiho, not a seductress!
First you say I'm a dog.
Now you're saying I'm a seductress.
Hey, I'm a gumiho.
That's right, you're a gumiho.
A gumiho who can kick a wall into
pieces is pretending to be sick?
He's worried for you and
even touched your forehead.
"I'm a weak and helpless girl."
"I want to eat beef."
"Very expensive beef."
Is that what you did?
Where did you put the ring?
Ring.
That's right, ring!
Wow!
It's here, found it!
Mi Ho, you're still very powerful.
Three strong men couldn't even lift this up.
You really are special.
Why is the ring here?
It rolled under there and I had no
idea how to get it out by myself.
Look, Mi Ho, you already found
the ring, and even some coins.
This is enough to buy three
bottles of soda water.
I asked, why did the ring roll under there?
Why did the ring roll under there?
When I was taking it off, it fell down.
Why did you take it off?
I saw Hae In noona.
I didn't want her to see the ring.
So it fell while I was taking it off.
Turns out that you left me
by myself to see that noona.
Yes, I went to see Hae In noona
and ate with her.
But nothing happened,
the bead is still fine.
Isn't that all right?
Just like you concealed the
ring from that noona,
are you going to conceal me, too?
That's right. If I can do it, it'll
be best to hide it from her.
Is that your wish?
What if it is?
That's right. You said before,
whatever I wish for,
you're going to help me achieve it, right?
Then what if my wish is concealing it from
Hae In noona, will you help me achieve that?
No.
I knew you'd be like this.
Since you're not going to
help me do it anyway,
why did you ask me what I wish for?
Other than this, just say something else!
I don't have any other wishes.
Humans don't dare to mention
any wishes to gumihos.
Regarding you, I don't have anything I want.
Then you...
The only thing you want
from me is the bead?
Isn't that asking the obvious?
Why does she always run away
from me as soon as she sees me?
Look into my eyes.
Do I look like an abnormal person?
Honestly speaking, if there was a guy like
Director chasing me, I would run away too.
Stop chasing that girl away.
Just make do with Kim Hee Joon
as the female lead.
You little...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh, brother.
Brother, thank you.
Oh, he should've arrived.
At the bar on the 19th floor, right?
Okay, wait for me.
Thank you.
I love you, you fool
I want to be with you
Honestly, I only want to
send you all my heart
I stop in front of you
I become ice like a fool
Even like this, I love you
Why are you always avoiding me?
Please don't be like this.
Please let go of me.
Let go of me.
Please let go of me!
Let go!
Director Ban!
Are you making me carry you on my back?
I say...
Oh my God, Director Ban!
My dad's phone is off.
There's still no accurate news of who'll
be confirmed as the female lead?
Tomorrow I'll help you ask my dad.
But the girl my dad is looking for
seems to be a student at our school.
What?
That shouldn't be right.
My dad said the he saw her at school today.
You're saying that she was
at our school today?
Unni! What's with the couple ring
that Cha Dae Woong is wearing?
Did you ask him?
When we met today, he wasn't
wearing a couple ring.
Really?
Byung Soo didn't see it clearly then.
On my way home, I'll make a trip
to the Action School along the way.
To see Cha Dae Woong.
Dae Woong didn't go home?
He's living over there again.
Unni, you don't even know that?
Why does my heart feel so congested?
Is it indigestion?
Mi Ho, you're... oh!
Look at you, look at you.
You've spread out all your tails,
what are you doing?
Do you have a problem with a
gumiho letting her tails out?
In the future, I'm going to spread
out my tails and live diligently.
You're drunk.
You drank the whole box.
And soju?
Dae Woong, you're too much.
Because I'm not a human,
you look down on me.
Mi Ho, clear your head,
put away your tails first.
They're so bright,
they're visible from far away.
Extinguish the light from your tails.
Is that your wish?
Yes.
Okay, then I'll definitely do it.
That's good.
Spreading out your tails as
you please is very dangerous.
Don't do that anymore in the future.
What else? What other wishes do you have?
But you have to help me
with everything I wish for.
Oh, that nail is sticking out,
it'll poke someone.
Hammer it back in.
I got it.
Wow, good job!
What else?
Again?
What else...
Oh, they're too noisy.
You make them be quiet.
Wow, our Mi Ho's voice is really loud!
Really? What else, what else, what else?
What else... what else is there?
Oh, the mosquitoes flying around here,
kill all of them.
That's something I do every day.
Something you do every day?
I don't want mosquitoes to bite you,
so I kill mosquitoes every day.
So that's why I've never gotten
a mosquito bite here.
Ah, after I drink, I can't hit them anymore.
These stupid mosquitoes,
because our gumiho is drunk,
they're looking down on her.
Oh! I killed it!
I killed it!
There's another one!
Hey, you're scaring me on purpose, right?
Stretch out your hand, let me see.
Let me see!
Stretch out your hand, let me see!
Gumiho isn't any different from before,
even when she's drunk.
Let me see.
Oh, it's that woman.
What?
She's coming over here.
Who's coming?
Mi Ho!
Dae Woong!
Your true wish, I'm helping you fulfill it.
All of your wishes, I'll help you
fulfill all of them.
Because I like you.
Dae Woong?
I'll hide.
Mi Ho!
Mi Ho! Mi Ho!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tiggerlily93
Spot Translators: serendipity, SeMe
Timer: casajuve
Editor/QC: langdon813
Final QC: reluctantbutaddicted
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com