Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
It closed down.
Looks like they left together
to a faraway palce...
Thank you.
Oh, excuse me, Miss.
You didn't fill out the name.
My name is Park Sun Ju.
Miss Park Sun Ju!
Park Sun Ju...
I'm sorry.
She must've left
with Teacher Dong Ju.
How could she have been here?
Miss Park Sun Ju!
Wait.
You forgot the complimentary gift.
You're skin's so nice.
Would you mind trying one of our products,
and posting your picture on our website?
Was the name Park Sun Ju,
a very common name?
Mi Ho's probably living well
as Park Sun Ju, right?
You're early.
Good thing I came first and waited.
I walked around everywhere but it wasn't
very interesting so I came early.
Teacher Dong Ju,
you said that there was a lot to do today, right?
Yes. Afterwards, we have a lot of places to go
so eat a lot of delicious things.
You don't need my help with ordering now;
you can do it yourself, right?
Try ordering the dishes you want.
Teacher Dong Ju can pick. Anything's fine.
Looks like she didn't come here once.
She threw this away too.
That's good, she left behind everything.
Then she should be able
to stop at that state and live well.
Shalalalala, while singing a song.
Calling my name again and again.
Shalalalala, you belong to me.
It really suits you.
Only looking at you beautifully.
Teacher Dong Ju, they're not
putting on blush?
I don't get to wear the traditional headress?
Those are only used for
traditional weddings.
This wedding you'll wear a veil
and hold a bouquet of flowers.
Oh really?
Then we won't be riding on a
flowered carriage either?
If you like those things, should we
change to a traditional wedding?
No. Wearing this is fine.
Anything's fine.
These are the designs you prepared.
Which one do you like? Pick one.
If you don't like any of them,
we can make a special order.
Teacher Dong Ju can pick one.
It doesn't matter which one I wear.
Really? It's okay if you wear any of these?
Yes, You should pick whichever one
you like.
The invitation cards are ready.
What are invitation cards?
It's an invitation for the people you want
to come and congratulate you at the wedding.
I don't have anyone I want to invite.
Don't you have Cha Dae Woong?
He just came back from China today.
- You know that too right?
- Yes.
This wedding is for Cha Dae Woong to see
that you're living well.
So you have to ask him to come
and show him.
If I don't appear in front of Dae Woong,
get married with someone else,
and then leave for somewhere far away,
he should assume that, like you,
I'm living well amongst other people, right?
He probably would.
He said if I stayed by Teacher Dong Ju's side
and lived as Park Sun Ju,
he wouldn't feel bad about it anymore.
That's right, help him lighten his remorse
for leaving you.
He can forget you faster, too.
That way, you can quickly end
your attachment with him.
No, you'll definitely be able to stop it.
You HAVE to.
This is the only way,
you'll be able to live.
Teacher Dong Ju.
Are you worried that my tail
will disappear again today?
Tonight, if death returns once more...
you'll only have one last chance
to live.
How are you feeling right now?
I don't know.
I feel like I've forgotten him...
but at times I don't.
Right now, where your heart lies...
we'll know when we see the results tonight.
Whether he remains in your heart
and your tail disappears
Or if he's no longer there
and you've stopped...
I can't ever stop.
I will disappear.
Good thing, I took out the bead that's
holding Dae Woong's life.
This won't disappear...
Ddoong Ja, you've been walking
with aunt everyday...
You're happy you came out with
oppa today, right?
My friend Mi Ho,
is a cute gumi-
Ddoong Ja, you're thirsty, right?
Let's go.
Ddoong Ja, wait here for me.
Wait. Wait.
You came out a bit later today.
I worried I wouln't be able to
see you today.
Looks like aunt was busy.
Ddoong Ja, I wish you were a fox.
That way we could communicate
and I could find out about Dae Woong.
Did you understand what I said?
I'm going to leave.
You should go back to aunt.
Ddoong Ja, bye.
Ddoong Ja!
What are you doing over here?
What are you eating?
Let's go home.
We have to go home.
Ddoong Ja, get up quickly.
Ddoong Ja, after we go home,
I'll give something good to eat.
Let's go.
Ddoong Ja!
I love you,
words from the bottom of my heart.
words which I would say a thousand times.
You and her... a wedding?!
Give this to Cha Dae Woong for me.
Passing it through you will be better
than me giving it to him directly.
That Mi Ho...
No, now she's called Park Sun Ju, right?
She really gave up on Dae Woong?
Before she said she loved him to death
and stuck to his side...
How could she give up so fast
and leave him?
A person like you will never
be able to understand.
Even when you like someone, you
question and calculate.
When separating...
you have to find excuses
and ways to defend yourself.
But there's also a type of love
that can leave out those processes.
In this type of love,
you give everything to the other person.
So without giving up everything,
you can't end it.
Understanding, convincing, justification...
...these are all unnecessary.
I thought you left far away...
But you're still here.
I'm preparing to leave.
Teacher Dong Ju and I still have
a some things to do.
I see...
Do you want to drink this?
Isn't this what you like?
I don't like soda anymore.
Beyond this, there are so many fun
and amazing things in this world.
Looks like that you've been living well
with Teacher Dong Ju.
Then, have you given up
on becoming human and
are you living by Teacher Dong Ju's side
as a half human?
Yeah, I have to...
Because I'm among people
who don't know what I really am,
it's really comfortable and I like it.
And because I'm by Teacher Dong Ju's side,
who's just like me, I can get a lot of help.
I'm glad to hear that.
Right now, I really really really really
feel great.
Oh! Good.
I have something to give you.
Here, I thought I should give this to you.
What's this?
I figured you should know
I'm doing good,
so you won't feel bad for me.
That's why I'm giving you this.
By Teacher Dong Ju's side,
I'm doing very well as Park Sun Ju.
You're even giving me something like this.
Seems like you truly are doing well.
- But, there aren't many days left.
- Yeah.
You might be busy and have
a lot of things to do but...
I hope that you can take some time off for it.
Sure, I can take time off but...
I don't think I need to.
These cosmetics are for women.
[Cosmetics coupon]
Oh?! What's this?
You used to collect chicken coupons everyday...
Have you expanded to cosmetic coupons now?
You say you're living as Park Sun Ju,
but you're still acting like gumiho!
Where'd Ddoong Ja go?
- Ddoong Ja.
- Ddoong Ja!
Ddoong Ja!
Ddoong Ja?
She came back by herself and
just finished off her lunch.
Now she's getting ready for a nap.
Ddoong Ja!
Where'd she go?
It's good nothing happened.
Ok.
I'm hanging up.
I can't find her anywhere.
Where did she go?
Even if aunt let go of the leash,
she never ran out of the park.
Ah!
Ddoong Ja really likes this so...
If she smells this,
she'll come right back.
Let's take this and look for her together.
Were you the one who gave Ddoong Ja
soemthing to eat?
Then because
you wanted to see Ddoong Ja...
did you come to the park by my house frequently?
Ddoong Ja and I are best friends,
remember?
Then trace Ddoong Ja by her scent.
Even though your tails have been reduced
by half, you still have that ability right?
Scent?
Unless.. are your abilities so reduced
that you can't even tell if Ddoong Ja...
is in this park or not?
No, it's because there are too many
other dogs, I get confused.
You didn't hear the conversation
between me and grandpa, right?
You weren't even that far away.
You weren't able to hear that?
A month ago, you could hear
everything, right?
It's because it's too loud here.
Your abilities are continuing
to disappear, right?!
Then, you still haven't...
No... I want to look like an ordinary person...
So I'm just hiding my abilities on purpose.
I don't want to stand out as gumiho.
I'm just trying hard to live as Park Sun Ju.
I'm leaving.
Tell me everything and then leave.
Let go. I'm going to leave.
You don't even have the strength to
shake me off anymore?!
You don't have to conceal your
gumiho abilities to me!
So if your abilities really haven't
disappeared,
then push me away forcefully
and try to get away.
I don't want to.
Other people are watching!
I'm not doing it.
If I push a man down, other people
will think that I'm a monster.
Just like you said I'm a monster.
How many tails do you have left?
Just like a month ago,
you still have four tails left, right?!
If you're curious, then see for yourself.
Take a look yourself and count them!
I can't see them right now.
I can only see them when the moon comes out.
Even with the moon, you probably
can't see them! You'd be too scared.
Because you're so scared
you won't be able to run.
I don't want to force you by my side again.
I won't ever show you.
I need to confirm how many
tails she has left.
I have to hang onto her until the moon
comes out...
and confirm it.
As you can see, the schedule is full.
These days are needed for editing.
In the following week there's a premiere
so it'll be difficult...
Ah, this day is free.
Miss Min Sook, let's get married
on this day.
Director.
You have to set the wedding date and
move your schedule around!
How can you just choose a day that
you're not filming for the wedding?
But marriage and work have equal importance.
What do you want me to do?
Also, after our passionate meeting
at the sauna,
we must think about our Gae Lan* who
occurred after we ate boiled eggs. [*Egg]
Our... Gae Lan.
If she knew about the secret
of our Gae Lan's birth,
my daughter, Seon Nyeo, would tear me
into shreds and eat them one by one.
Then again, we DO have to
get married quickly.
so we can say it was a premature birth...
But, even if it's for our precious Gae Lan,
I didn't receive a formal proposal.
And just getting married off this way
is too unjust.
Miss Min Sook.
This is my heart.
This? This is just coffee...
I really like coffee.
Whenever I'm tired, sleepy or lonely,
drinking a cup of coffee,
makes me feel the happiest.
But ever since meeting Miss Min Sook,
The amount of coffee I drink everyday
is a lot less.
Why?
Because I'm happy 24 hours a day.
Miss Min Sook filled up the empty void
in my heart,
with the coffee of love.
Director.
Miss Min Sook.
Please become my expectant, 24 hour,
love's automatic vending machine.
Okay.
I'll become your cafe of happiness.
Director is getting married with
Dae Woong's aunt right?
Seems like they're in a hurry.
Did they cause some trouble?
Back when we thought Dae Woong
and Mi Ho caused trouble,
the atmosphere was pretty good too.
Even though they seemed like they're
gonna break up everyday, it always worked out...
They'll probably get back together.
I bet they won't...
What's this?
Park Sun Ju is Mi Ho?
Park Dong Ju, that veterinarian?
The two of them are getting married?
That's right.
You guys give this to Dae Woong.
I tired so I don't want to get involved.
What's going on between the
three of them?
It's something unimaginable for you guys...
So it's better if you don't know.
If you knew, you'd get hurt.
What's so unimaginable?!
If he finds out that Mi Ho's getting married,
he'll probably be shocked.
Should we tell him or not?
What if Cha Dae Woong runs into the
wedding like a movie?
Movie?
NO!
Hey, she said something unimaginable!
No, no. Dae Woong's not on that team!
NO!
Hyung, Mi Ho.
The three of us are siblings.
Siblings?
We have to get revenge for our parents.
That doesn't even make sense!
Then Dae Woong is Park Dae Woong?
And who's the enemy?
Ah, really.
What's the "unimaginable" thing?!
Why are you following me?
I...
Buy me lunch.
What?
Buy me some meat.
While I was filming in China,
I didn't meat at all!
I really want to eat meat.
Especially cow. I want to eat cow.
Why do I have to buy meat for you?
We're nothing now.
That's right,
We don't even know each others names anymore...
If you haven't changed, you'd be sa*-miho
(*sa = 4).
But are you sam*-miho? Ee*-miho?
I don't know your last name. (*sam=3, *Ee=2)
Tell me clearly.
You...
How many-tailed-fox are you?
I'm...
My name is Park Sun Ju.
Okay then.
I'll just regard you as Park Sun Ju so...
Buy me some meat.
Buy me cow.
Until you buy me a cow,
I'll never leave.
The meat's gonna burn!
Leave it alone!
I like to cook meat until it's burnt.
Let's put all of them so
we can cook it faster.
No.
I'm going to savor each piece one-by-one
and barbecue them slowly.
Then you eat slowly. I'm leaving first.
I don't know how much more I'm gonna eat!
You have to wait and pay the bill
before you leave!
This is the only meal you've ever
bought for me.
Stingy! Leaving before paying for everything!
There's a lot here.
You call this is a lot?!
I wasn't gonna say this cause
I sound petty but...
If you took all the meat I bought
and built a tower out of it,
it may not be as tall as Namsam Tower,
but it's probably as tall as Dabotap or Seokgatap!
Fine.
Go ahead, eat your heart out.
They're all cooked.
They're cooked perfectly.
Here, eat it.
What's wrong?
You can't eat any more?
Should we go?
No, I can still eat for awhile.
Check please!
We finished eating!
Why're you following me again?!
I was gonna drink beef bone soup
to rinse my mouth...
Instead, you just threw me away and left
while I went to the bathroom!
I could've eaten for another hour.
Anyways, in the past, I mooched a lot off you.
I'm glad I was able treat you out.
Go.
I'm leaving too.
Mi Ho!
What now?
Since you're buying me food,
buy me this too.
I ate meat so I have to drink this!
I wasn't gonna say this,
cause I'll sound stingy but...
If we collect the soda I bought you,
it might not fill a swimming pool, but
it's more than enough to fill a bathtub.
Fine.
Since I mooched a lot of these from you,
after I buy this for you, I'm leaving.
Why isn't it coming out?
It ate your coin!
It really knows perfect timing.
There's no other choice.
Until someone comes to fix this machine,
we're gonna have to wait here.
There's a bench here
and the weather's nice...
It's perfect for waiting for someone.
Has your strength dwindled?
Before you could lift up
an entire vending machine.
Where did all of your strength go?
I just did that so I won't stand out.
Get the drink yourself.
Dad, pass this invitation to Dae Woong.
We're not confident enough to face
Dae Woong's shocked face.
I'll take care of it.
The two of you leave.
Between my real action dream and Mr. Cha,
a major historical drama of love
and betrayal has started.
No... it's a melodramatic movie...
Dae Woong, I'm pregnant.
What?
But I had a miscarriage.
So let's break up.
What?
I'm getting married to another man.
What??
What? What? What?
I can't think of any other lines.
I'll just stick with action films.
Melodrama is not my genre.
What? What?
There's still a lot of time
before the moon rises.
Mi Ho, do you have any medicine on you?
Ah, you're a gumiho so you don't need any.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
I think I'm getting indigestion from
the meat.
It's so painful that I can't move.
Does it hurt a lot?
Let's go to the hospital.
I'll take you there.
No, No. If I stay like this for a bit
I'll be fine.
Speaking of which, your bead
is very effective.
I feel a lot better
just by being beside the bead.
You can feel the bead beside you?
Yeah! Because the bead's by me,
it hurts a lot less.
So until I get better,
stay with me for a while.
You're lying about the pain, huh?
Of course not, I'm really in pain!
My hands are cold, I'm sweating,
and my face is pale.
It's really serious.
Your hands are warm...
...you're not sweating,
your face colour is fine too.
You're not sick at all.
Don't follow me anymore.
If you keep on following me, I'll scream.
And tell people that you're a stalker.
What? Stalker?
That's right, always following someone
who doesn't like them back,
that's a stalker, right?
Who said I was following you?
After the moon comes out
and I've seen your tails,
I won't follow you anymore.
Then you're a pervert.
What? Pervert?
Yeah! Going up to a girl in the
middle of the night,
And saying "Let me see. Just once, let me see"
You said that's a pervert!
Ah, also, you're a parasite.
What? Parasite?
Yes, you said that always staying
at other people's places,
scrounging food, water,
and money from them. That's a parasite.
That's what you did to me today.
If you don't want to become a pervert,
parasite, or a stalker
then stop following me.
Even if I become a parasite, pervert
or stalker, I still have to confirm it.
Mi Ho! Mi Ho!
Ahjusshi, stop the bus.
Mi Ho!
You can't know my condition right now.
You have to think that I'm happy,
living somewhere far away.
The wedding invitation will be delivered
into Cha Dae Woong's hands tomorrow.
Yeah?
I don't know if he'll come to the wedding
and see for himself.
But he'll accept everything
that you've already sorted out,
and the fact that you'll
continue to live well.
Then he won't be worried about me
anymore, right?
This is the airplane ticket to Japan.
If we show him that we're leaving
to Japan right away,
he'll think you left happily,
the way you wanted it.
Teacher Dong Ju, I'm sorry.
Because of me, you've broken
your old routine.
Your old peaceful life has
become disorganized and noisy.
I said that I don't care.
As long as your feelings can stop...
As long as you continue to live...
I don't care about anything else.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
Today is the 88th day.
If the deaths haven't stopped,
then tonight, another tail will disappear.
Since Teacher Dong Ju is studying through books,
I'll watch the TV and study.
I'll study together with you.
What do you want to watch?
What's the most loudest thing?
Ah, something with singing and dancing.
Turn that on.
Teacher Dong Ju, I'm going to buy soda.
I'll go.
No, I'll go.
You watch the show. Don't turn it off.
If he knew that I took the bead out,
Teacher Dong Ju will so sad.
There's only one left.
What are you doing there?
I was looking in the mirror.
On my way out, my tail felt weird all of a sudden,
so I cam here.
Did it... disappear again?
Yeah, another tail disappeared.
Teacher Dong Ju,
it's time to let go of me.
No, I won't ever give up.
There's still one more left.
I'm going out for a bit.
Dae Woong.
Starting from today, follow your aunt,
and help prepare for the wedding.
I have something urgent so
I have to go out for a bit.
You punk!
So you want your aunt to go around
preparing for it, all by herself?!
What about the director?
He said that he's too busy
and can't help her.
Your aunt has grown horns THIS big.
How is old is she now?
She's finally getting married.
You should stay with her and help.
Aunt, after we book the hall in this hotel,
we're done right?
Yes! After we make the reservations, I'll let you go
so stop rushing me!
October 9th has been reserved for you.
You haven't seen a wedding hall yet, right?
Let's see it before we leave.
This way.
Since it's a weekday,
it's available for reservation.
That's great.
Then I'll book it for you immediately.
The name of your son
who's about to get married is...
He's not getting married, I am.
Oh, right.
Because there won't be many guests,
I reserved the smaller one.
Do you like it?
This one is simple and nice.
Ah yes. How about this?
Oh, this one's really good.
Because it's autumn,
there's a lot of weddings.
Park Sun Ju, Park Dong Ju?
There's another Park Sun Ju...
But the groom is Park Dong Ju?!
Why does it have to be Park Sun Ju
and Park Dong Ju getting married?
Then let's go look at the hall first.
- Okay.
- This way.
Should we go now?
This way.
Aunt, let me take this call. Go ahead.
Byung Soo, I'm out with aunt right now.
Am I ok?
About what?
Don't I know yet?
What are you talking about?
Bride, groom, the waiting room is over here.
I really couldn't have imagined this.
But it seems like you're really doing
perfectly fine.
I didn't know at all.
I was going to give this to you
when we met yesterday...
Here, we're leaving right after
the wedding ceremony.
We're busy today so I have to go.
See you at the wedding ceremony.
Do you think I'll go?
If you're not going to come,
then let's say goodbye here.
We'll probably never see each other again.
Yeah. Let's never see each other again.
Goodbye.
That's good.
Now I can be at ease.
When I saw them...
It seemed like that it wasn't Dae Woong
who dumped Mi Ho...
he was the one who got dumped.
What's wrong with our Dae Woong?
Since he's young, he'll get over it soon.
At that age you dump
and get dumped by love.
Oh yea...
Min Sook,
The first time that you were
dumped by a man...
was at Dae Woong's age right?
Every time that I got dumped,
I received a lot of comfort from Dae Woong.
Auntie, kiss.
Aunt, if you can't get married,
when I grow up, I'll marry you.
Dae Woong.
Who's this punk?!
Who dumped Aunt?
He's DEAD!
Dae Woong. Dae Woong, don't be like this.
Don't be like this.
This time, I should be the one
who comforts Dae Woong.
So this time...
Aunt, I'm hungry. Make some food for me.
- Food?
Eat a lot.
Grandpa, you eat some too.
It's the egg rolls that you like.
Eat.
Aunt, after you get married, I won't be able
to eat your delicious egg rolls anymore.
I'll come back often.
If there's something you want to eat,
call me any time.
Right, what do you want for your
wedding gift?
Forget it.
You probably don't even have the energy
to get me a wedding gift right now.
Just say it; I'll buy it for you.
Should I make some meat for you?
I ate so much meat yesterday,
I probably don't need to eat meat
for a while.
There's a small mountain behind here.
They say it's really beautiful in the fall.
- Aigoo.
- There's more here.
Sit.
You're Seon Nyeo*, right?
[*Fairy]
Yes.
She's my friend, Grandpa.
Like a fairy, you're so graceful
and pretty.
Director.
Do you want another cup of coffee?
You're giving me goosebumps.
I don't know what's going on,
but you should let it go.
Anyways,
the director went to clean up the action school
attic room where you used to stay.
I'll throw away everything in there
for you.
This woman was the stand-in
for unni in China?
Yeah.
Obviously she wasn't as good as Mi Ho.
You hated Mi Ho but...
You still miss her, right?
She could've left
after I finished filming my parts.
Oh! Isn't this Mi Ho?
What?
Why would she be there?
I'm right! Look at the long hair.
Is it?
It probably isn't.
She decided to get married to Park Dong Ju.
Why would she be there?
"Stalker, pervert and parasite,"
I learned these words from following you.
You can't be here!
Leave, leave, stalker. Stalker.
Stalker?
What are you trying to look at?!
You can't, you pervert. Pervert.
Pervert? Pervert...
You're a parasite.
Parasite?
You followed him all the way there...
Good thing you didn't get discovered
by Cha Dae Woong.
Just watching him from afar...
was so hard.
In the old photo album I had,
I only filled it with good memories...
Tomorrow we're going to hold
the wedding ceremony.
I know.
It was me who wanted to.
I know that we're only doing this
to get rid of Cha Dae Woong but,
I still hope,
that your heart
can be sorted out as well.
I left something at the attic.
I have to go get it.
Just leave it.
We're going to go far away.
When we leave, leave everything here,
including everything in your heart.
Right now your life
hasn't entirely disappeared yet.
There's still a chance.
No matter what kind of life
you want to live,
I can create it for you.
So...
everything that's here...
throw it away.
I'll only bring the things
I absolutely need.
I'll be right back.
To me, it really looks like Mi Ho.
Isn't it?
Even if it is, let's say it's not.
If Dae Woong see's this,
he'll get really upset so
Destroy it.
Destroy, destroy it.
What is it?
- Dae Woong.
- What's gonna make me so upset?
It's Mi Ho.
See, if Cha Dae Woong can recognize her
at once, it's gotta be her.
She doesn't look like Mi Ho to me.
All the girls we saw in China
had long hair.
I think it IS her!
Their faces are similar!
Yeah! It's probably not Mi Ho.
She had no reason to go there.
That's right! The wedding's tomorrow,
why would she go to China...
It's here.
I just need to take this.
Drumstick!
Woong! That's really a big piece of meat!
Mi Ho, catch the meat.
I can't leave this here either.
I'll just take this too.
I can't throw this away either.
It's really awesome right?
You really surprised me.
Dae Woong, it's really great right?
Really awesome right?
Yes, it's really awesome.
If I continue like this,
I won't be able to throw away anything.
We stopped here.
Now it's up to here.
Who left the lights on?
It's Dae Woong.
What do I do?
Where's the thing that was here?
Did someone clean it up already?
I'm sure the album was here...
Why are you here?
I needed to find something.
You came to find this?
It has nothing to do with you.
That's mine.
Forget it, I'll just leave.
Did you follow me to China?
Am I right?
No.
I definitely didn't.
Let go.
What condition are you in right now?
The moon's up so show me your tails!
You... your strength is disappearing,
and your tails are disappearing too, right?
It has nothing to do with you!
Let go!
Mi Ho. Mi Ho!
Mi Ho, wait for me! Mi Ho!
Stop running away!
Why are you running away?
Why are you hiding your tails from me?!
You...
haven't stopped, right?
Your tails are still disappearing right?!
My condition...
do you HAVE to know?
Yeah! I have to know.
Show me.
Then, open your eyes wide and look at me...
See how I am right now...
See how I feel right now...
I... couldn't stop.
Then you're...
still dying?
I will...
disappear.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tiggerlily93
Spot Translators: fore, yOitzO
Timer: dizzybugs
Editor/QC: reluctantbutaddicted
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com
A country that can't protect
the citizens lives,
what's the point of that?
Ha Doe Yah
When I was a child, I was a dance prodigy.
I was even on TV.
[Dae Mul]
Raise my level of popularity
and level of trust
So I can be elected
as a member of the national party?
Member of the National Party,
Didn't you know?
I became a prosecutor just to
capture members of the legislature?
We deal with political affairs.
Then it's to be like those trash-like guys
who clean up messes?
Did my father deal with political affairs
when I was in studying biology?
I bet on this presidency.
The nation of Korea can no longer leave
citizens unprotected by the country.
[For the citizens, I've risked everything]
[Because that's my reason
for becoming the President]