Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 14
After the 100 days have passed,
one of us has to die?
Since something so ridiculous is our fate,
I'm supposed to calmly accept it,
or run away and save myself?
I can't do that.
I WON'T!
I don't want to either.
Today marks exactly half of
the hundred days passed.
Mi Ho...
Take the bead from me... right now.
You want me to take the bead right now?
Then what?
This is the only decision I can make
as the person who loves you.
Even though I'm not sure of the outcome,
we're in it together.
Until the very end.
I love you,
words from the bottom of my heart
words I want to say a thousand times
Until now I haven't been able to tell you
So I want to start telling you more now
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
That's great, that's really great.
Dae Woong.
Dae Woong!
Mi Ho.
Dae Woong! Dae Woong!
Dae Woong!
Dae Woong, Dae Woong!
Dae Woong...
Oxygen.
You've really made a fearless choice.
Dae Woong will live, right?
He won't die like this, right?
I don't know either.
Are you really okay?
Dae Woong, Dae Woong...
Mi Ho.
Dae Woong.
It can't be like this.
I have to give the bead back.
It's too late.
There's no way to turn back.
Cha Dae Woong has already transferred half
of his life to you along with the bead.
Whether he'll die immediately
or still live for a few months or
a few years,
it all depends on the original length
of his life.
Right now, there's nothing you can do.
If Dae Woong doesn't wake up again,
then give me Teacher Dong Ju's knife.
Let go of that hand.
Woong.
I'm fine.
So let go of Mi Ho's hand
and get out of here.
Dae Woong.
Woong.
Wherever my grandfather took me
to get my fortune told,
they all said that I'd live to 120.
So for the next 50 years,
there definitely won't be any problem.
How exactly it'll turn out,
we'll wait and see.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness. You're okay?
I'm okay.
This is the only decision I can make
as the person who loves you.
Am I following...
the decision made by a fearless human?
I told you I'm okay.
A decision a person made for love...
What? Dae Woong fainted at the airport?
Okay, I'll go to the hospital immediately.
Father, Father!
You're really okay?
No. I'm REALLY hungry!
We have to get out of here quickly
and eat.
You're really okay too, right?
Yeah 'cause I have the bead.
But what if the bead
restores the tails that I lost?
How can something that's already
gone reappear again?
Ah, you said...
you still have five left?
Yeah...I wish the tails
keep disappearing,
and leave only the human chi
you gave me.
Yeah...
Since I'm safe and sound,
you'll definitely be fine too.
On the 55th day, whether or not
the fifth tail will disappear,
we'll find out then, right?
It'll be okay even if it doesn't disappear.
I was ok nine-tails so,
who cares if it's five-tails?
Woong.
Come this way.
Father.
Our Dae Woong...
Thank goodness the bead went
back you to safely.
Yeah.
I hope that it'll continue to be safe.
Your body's different from before...
Can you still go to China?
Honestly, I don't know what's gonna
happen to the bead, so I'm a bit worried.
Let's delay our trip to China.
I'm worried about your condition so
I can't go either.
Since we're at the hospital,
let's do a check up and
ask the director
to give us a bit more time.
Can we do that?
Right now, the condition of the bead
is the most important thing,
So we should avoid any risks.
Bead, you can't cause problems.
Grandpa, Aunt.
You said "bead", what do you mean by that?!
That's…
Explain it honestly!
You're gonna keep concealing from your grandpa
and lie?!
Because it's something that
Grandpa doesn't need to know.
What do you mean I don't need to know?
I already heard that the bead inside
Mi Ho being in danger, you punk.
Grandpa.
How can you conceal my great-grandson
from me?
What?
If you're having a child
then you should have told me.
"Bead" is the name?
Of course it's not!
So THAT'S why you did everything to
come back to Korea?!
No, it's not.
It's seriously not like that.
Cha Dae Woong.
You still want to conceal it until
the very end?
- Then let's get it confirmed immediately.
- What?
Min Sook, this hospital has a
gynecology department, right?
Yes.
Take Mi Ho and get her examined.
Examination? I can't.
Grandpa, she can't get an examination.
There's no need to get an examination.
This punk…
You're right.
Right now, in Mi Ho,
there's a bead.
Mi Ho, are you okay?
What?
This isn't right.
Min Sook, you take her,
and check if the mother and the child
are both healthy.
Grandpa, they're very healthy.
Our bead is totally healthy.
Right?
Yes, our bead is healthy.
Congratulations, Cha Dae Woong.
You're telling the truth?
Dae Woong gave up half of his life to her?
That's right.
I believed that he would never
return the bead to her.
Instead he stopped all my
carefully laid out plans and did it...
That's unbelievable...
The Dae Woong I knew wasn't
that kind of person.
He's not the kind of person
who throws his life away like that!
He must have changed.
Even though I can't become human in the end,
but to be able to give my all to
the person I love,
I really like myself like this.
He met a person who can give
everything to him,
so he also turned into a person
who can be like that.
Then right now between the two of them,
you were unable to intervene either?
I'm not sure.
Right now, the result is not out yet.
Because inside her body,
my blood still flows in her.
Eat a lot.
Today, we'll have Korean beef bone soup.
And tomorrow let's buy some fish
to grill and eat.
I just like beef soup...
Really?
Then I'll ask for more Korean beef bone
soup from my friend in the countryside.
Mi Ho, live at our house from today on.
Why?
You said there almost was an accident,
we can't let her live by herself!
Anyways, don't you have to leave in a few days
to film the movie?
During that time,
Mi Ho can stay at our house.
Since Grandpa has already
misunderstood the bead anyway,
Until you go to China,
let's stay here.
Then until that time,
we're going to live here together?
That's right.
Us two in one room?
In one room?
We can't.
Dae Woong, you already gave half
of your life to me.
We don't even know what will happen,
so I can't steal any more.
I've already given you half anyway,
it should be okay if I give you
a little more, right?
I think... that it'll be okay.
No.
After the 100 days have passed,
and after we comfirm everything's ok.
Dae Woong, we have to be careful
until then and bear with it.
Woong, you have to bear with it.
You can't be blinded by thought of mating
and give up life so easily!
How am I blind?
And the one who has to bear it is you.
Who's the one who takes the initiative
everyday?
I've never had those kinds of
thoughts before.
I'm just like this because
I'm worried about you.
Woong, I have those thoughts frequently.
So in order for me to bear with it,
you'll have to stay in another room.
What?
Hey, this is my room.
Where do you want me to go?
Didn't you hear what Grandpa said?
Because I have the bead in my womb,
I have to show that I'm living
comfortably.
I'm sorry.
Right, I already gave her half of my life,
what's one room?
Thank you for understanding Dae Woong's
situation, Director.
There's no way around this kind
of situation.
My dear real action Mi Ho's got a
baby, it's really too bad.
I can't see her action anymore.
Do you know what's more agonizing
and depressing than that?
Please tell me.
I, Cha Min Sook...
am about to become a grandaunt.
Min Sook.
I've never been a wife, nor a mother,
but I'm going to be a grandaunt!
If it's just that, then
don't be too worried about it.
You don't want me to worry too much
about it?
Min Sook, that round face of
yours is like a doll's face.
No one will call Miss Min Sook "Grandaunt".
You cutie!
Yes, a round doll's face.
That's very comforting.
I'm hanging up.
Can't you just say that you want me
to become your wife?
What's wrong? What are you looking for?
I keep getting thirsty.
Really?
Is everything else ok?
My stomach feels nauseous,
and my head feels dizzy.
Why am I like this?
When you're pregnant, that's how it is.
How great it must be, feeling nauseous
and dizzy.
There's nothing wrong, right?
Why am I burning up? It's hot.
Byung Soo,
How come Dae Woong's not
going to China?
After a few months,
you'll find out naturally.
Seon Nyeo, now, you have to
completely give up on Dae Woong.
I gave him up a long time ago!
He doesn't even like me!
You thought that I'd always have
an unrequited love?
Do I look like an idiot?
Is that right?
Being like that is being an idiot.
Always guessing whether
he really liked me or not,
Of course I would do that! It was
smart of me!
From the very beginning,
his heart and his ring were mine.
I was only measuring the time
to accept them...
But as a result, something squeezed
between us.
What?
He fell for her because
she followed him around
telling him she really, really,
really liked him?!
Hanging on with no pride,
sticking to him shamelessly,
Saying you can give up your life,
being so pitiful and idiotic!
Could you guys do it?
That's right.
Humans can't do that.
Because she's not a human,
she's able to do things
that humans aren't able to do.
And pretending to be a human...
I definitely won't let you go easily.
Who sent this?
Keep a close eye on Mi Ho.
You will see something like this.
Keep a close eye on Mi Ho?
What is it?
Now the human chi and the gumiho chi,
are half and half.
If they can mix together well,
It'll be half human, half monster.
Will she turn into the same as me?
How am I supposed to keep a close
watch on Mi Ho?
Mi Ho, what are you doing?
Give me your chi.
What's wrong with you, all of a sudden?
Didn't you say you'll bear it?
Mi Ho!
There isn't enough.
I have to quench this unbearable thirst.
Let's share our chi.
Mi Ho, what's wrong with you?
Be rational!
Dae Woong, Mi Ho.
It's Aunt.
Give me some chi. Let's share our chi.
Dae Woong.
Mi Ho, are you sleeping?
They're not here.
Where'd they go?
Dae Woong, is that you?
Mi Ho, calm down.
Come back.
Give me your chi.
Bear with it.
You have to bear with it, Mi Ho.
Right now, you're half human!
Half?
My tails have been reduced by half.
I had nine and it's been reduced to five.
If this continues, all my tails
will be gone.
You, didn't you say that you wanted
all your tails to disappear?
The one making my tails disappear and
infusing me with human chi is you, right?
Give me my tails.
Dae Woong, are you in here?
Dae Woong, Mi Ho.
That's right.
I'll give you tails.
What are you guys doing in here?
Just looking at things.
It's a tail.
It's a fox's tail.
Hey, that fox's tail is very expensive.
She's just looking.
Tail.
One,
two,
three,
four.
- You can't touch those carelessly!
- I'll take care of it, Aunt.
Aunt, you should go out now.
Go out quickly.
What are you doing?
- Go.
- Ok! Fine!
Mi Ho, Mi Ho.
She's sleeping...
Has she finally calmed down now?
The real fox saved me...
I'm speechless.
Why're they acting like a honeymoon couple!
She might as well just buy
nine sets of fox haired coats.
This looks like some sort of tail too...
Is there a blue tail?
Mi Ho, come back to your senses.
Mi Ho, are you okay?
Why are you here?
Are you okay now?
Woong, you can't be like this.
We agreed to bear with it.
You couldn't bear with it
for that short time?
Hey, what did I do?!
Even me, a gumiho, can bear it.
You, a human, can't do this.
Hey, it was you who pounced
on me with hungry eyes first.
I was sleeping, but you came in...
and said,
"Let's share our chi"
Me?
I was sleeping the entire time!
We were almost discovered by my aunt.
You really don't remember?
I don't remember.
Are these side effects?
I don't know.
Why am I like this?
Don't be too worried.
It looked like you had a lot of energy earlier.
Yeah! It's probably cause
you got back the bead,
So you have a lot of energy
and went a little overboard.
What if I keep going around like this?
I'll watch over you.
Don't worry.
Woong.
What are we going to do if I keep
changing like this everyday?
Then I'll just keep guarding you
like this everyday.
Then everyday you won't be able to
sleep and you'll be very tired.
But we can be together every day.
Woong.
Everything's going to be ok.
Everything's going to be ok, Mi Ho.
What's this?
Mi Ho likes eating meat,
why didn't you prepare some meat?
Why eat meat this early in the morning?
We'll eat meat at dinner.
Yeah, Mi Ho can eat
vegetables now, right?
Meat.
Give me meat.
Mi Ho, where's the meat?
The meat's over there, over there.
Let's go.
Grandpa, Aunt, we're finished eating.
I told you, you should've
prepared some meat!
Seriously.
Meat, where did we put the…
Mi Ho, why are you starting to change
again in the morning?
Isn't it a bit strange?
Meat.
Mi Ho, Ddoong Ja isn't meat.
Tail.
Mi Ho, this is Ddoong Ja's tail.
Then, let's go to the second floor
to look for meat.
Aunt, get some rest.
Ah, it's irritating my eyeballs, seriously.
Mi Ho's changing more frequently.
Mi Ho, again?
Give me your chi.
Mi Ho, guess where I am!
Of course I'm here.
Let's go upstairs quickly.
Grandpa, you worked hard.
Be careful of bead.
Woong.
Are you okay?
I changed again, didn't I?
Why am I always like this?
I don't want to be like this.
I keep praying that I won't be
like this but I'm still changing.
Is it becuase I'm changing
back into the gumiho?
It looks like we can't keep
living here.
If it goes on,
you'll be discovered.
Let's go back to the attic room.
But how about what grandpa's misunderstanding?
He's so happy.
We'll have to tell the truth.
It's better to tell the truth earlier.
I'm sorry, it's all because of me.
It's not because of you.
I really hate myself.
I thought that you would know more
about Mi Ho's condition.
So I came to ask you.
Gumiho's instincts are probably surfacing.
I don't care if Mi Ho turns back
completely.
But her life won't be threatened, right?
I don't know about that either.
I only know that right now, inside her body,
she has half gumiho chi and half human chi.
The thing that can kill these two chi,
my half human-half monster's blood,
is also in her body.
If the two types of chi blend properly,
she'll become the same as me,
half-human and half-monster.
The same… as you.
If only that will happen,
my blood will stop killing her.
If that doesn't happen?
The gumiho chi and the human chi
will both be killed and disappear.
Is there a way to find out now
if the two chi's are blending?
Soon, on the 55th day,
the fifth death will come.
If the fifth tail doesn't disappear,
that means my blood has stopped killing her.
If her tail doesn't disappear then
that means she can continue to live, right?
If it disappears,
she's destined to die after the 100 days.
Come quickly.
We're going to take a family portrait!
Family portrait?
That's right.
Grandpa said that we have to take a
family portrait together with the bead.
Hurry up and come in.
Come.
What do we do?
After we take the picture,
I'll tell Grandpa.
Ok, here we go.
Smile. 1, 2, 3.
What did you say?
Mi Ho... isn't pregnant.
Grandpa misunderstood the bead.
What? Misunderstood?
How dare you lie about something
like that?!
I was wrong, Grandpa.
No, Director.
I didn't lie because I wanted
to postpone filming the movie.
I'm really sorry but...
I might have to stay for a few
more days before going back.
I'm sorry.
Let me stay a few more days
in the action school attic room.
Why are you putting people in such
difficult situations?
My dad's really pissed off this time.
Please understand my situation, okay?
Wow, we've come back home!
Feels good, right?
Grandpa, the director and your friends...
They're all mad at you, huh?
It's not because of you.
It's all right.
Everything will get better.
Bead...
My poor little bead.
I got the picture but...
If I take it to grandpa,
he'll probably get angrier.
Usually at our age,
even if we had a bead,
most people would lie and deny it.
But why did you lie about
a bead that doesn't exist?
I had no choice.
Are you really planning on marrying
Mi Ho within this year?
Wasn't your dream to live a
glorious single life until you're 40,
And then have a child at 45 like Brad Pitt?
Wasn't it like that?
I have to live twice as fast
as other people.
I don't have any time to waste.
Today is the day the fifth tail
is supposed to disappear.
Even if you didn't come here to tell me,
I remember it clearly.
If her tail disappears tonight,
that means her death hasn't stopped
but is continuing.
Wow, it came out great!
Grandpa was so happy at that time.
It has to blend properly no matter what.
It has to blend properly.
And please...
Just stop like this.
Woong, what's wrong with you?
What do you want to stop?
Are you telling me to stop
changing into that weird thing?
Woong, I'm sorry.
I change unconsciously so...
I can't make it stop.
What if my tails start to change too?
No, that won't do.
You have to stop right now
at five tails!
Mi Ho.
There isn't much time left until
the 100th day.
Don't ever change and...
just persevere until
the end of the 100 days.
I'm so afraid that you'll change...
You can do it, right?
Looks like because of me,
he's really having a hard time.
There's still a lot of time until
the 100th day.
He can't get exhausted already.
As long as nothing happens tonight...
If it passes smoothly, it'll be good.
Please blend well.
And stop here.
My tail...
Mi Ho, what's wrong?
My tail's changed.
Did it start to hurt again?
No, it doesn't hurt.
I have the bead.
Then what's wrong?
Mi Ho, hurry up and come out!
Did something happen?
Dae Woong!
My tail has disappeared.
It's... gone?!
Yeah!
Recently I've been so weird
so I worried that my tails would grow back...
But one more disappeared, Woong.
I think I'm becoming a human!
Really?
Woong, you're not happy?
I said I'm becoming a human!
Whether you're becoming a
human or not, how do you know?
Woong.
Death isn't stopping.
What do I do?
I thought that he'd be happy
my tail disappeared.
Did I make him uneasy again?
Woong.
You go to sleep first.
I'll just be out for a bit.
Dae Woong.
Are you going out becuase you're afraid
that I might change back into my scary form?
If it's like that, stay here and
don't go.
I will stay outside.
If you're feeling uneasy,
then lock the door.
Oh right...
Because of me last time, the lock's broken.
I'm not uneasy because of that so
go inside.
I might be late so don't wait up
and go to sleep first.
To stop the death, we have to stop
the gumiho and human chi from fighting.
So how can we stop it?
I can't go inside Mi Ho and tell them
not to fight and pull them apart!
You CAN stop it.
If you leave her side, then it can happen.
What?
The main reason why the gumiho chi
can't combine with the human chi...
is because her determination
to become human is too powerful.
And the one pushing her to become human...
is you.
Then you're saying...I'm pushing
her to die?!
That's right.
I... it doesn't matter to me if
she's a gumiho.
Mi Ho knows it too.
But you were happy with her,
that she'll become human...
and didn't you plan your human lives
together?
As long as she continues planning
by your side,
death can NOT stop.
You can't be by her side.
When you are no longer by her side,
her desire to become human
will slowly disappear.
And she will be able to
accept her current condition.
Didn't you say that if one lives,
the other one has to die?
But now for both to live, we can't be
together and have to separate?
Your decision to be together
whether you lived or died,
Isn't it fortunate that we found a way
for both of you to live?
Once again, as the man who loves her,
think about what you can do...
choose carefully and decide.
If you leave, then I will stay by her side
so she can become like me
and exist in this world.
Only when I'm no longer by her side...
Mi Ho can live?
Dae Woong!
Why didn't you sleep and come out here?
Woong, I feel much better after
the tail disappeared.
My stomach doesn't feel nauseous
and my head isn't dizzy either.
Every time my tails disappear,
I'll get better, right?
You're really happy about that?
Of course! My tails HAVE to disappear so
we can start our life plan together...
And we can make grandpa truly happy.
Mi Ho, I like you just like this too.
Didn't I say that it's all right?
Can't you just give up those things
and stay by my side like this?
Woong, don't give up.
Teacher Dong Ju's blood that's in my body
will absorb all the gumiho chi,
and as long as the chi you gave me is safe,
I can become human.
What's so good about becoming human?
You'll feel pain, get old and die!
I want to do that.
I want to do all of that
by your side, with you.
While I'm by your side,
I probably won't be able to stop you...
As long as you're by my side,
everything will be all right.
If it just stops like this,
does that mean,
I too, will have a chance?
Back then, I didn't know about love
Staying by the side of someone
I feel unfamiliar and scared
by this kind of thing
Only now, I understand love
Saying that it wasn't love between us
Thanks for the trust you had in me
Looking back now,
there were a lot of memories
I really didn't know that
it was actually love
I love you
Words from the bottom of my heart
Words which I would say a thousand times
Until now I haven't given you anything
So I want to start telling you more now
Words that I would like to tell only you
I love you
Words from the bottom of my heart
Words which I would say a thousand times
Until now I haven't given you anything
So I want to start telling you more now
Words that I would like to tell only you
Woong, this is our first time
driving and going somewhere fun.
It's great!
But where are we going?
Are we going to the zoo again?
If we're going out, you
should've told me earlier.
I could've prepared a lunchbox.
I always wanted to roll kimbap.
We're not going out to play.
Then where are we going?
Are we going to Grandpa?
Did Grandpa call us over to eat?
No.
Then where are we going?
We're going to Teacher Dong Ju.
Why are we going there?
Mi Ho,
I can't go on any longer.
Woong.
Do I... have to be by your side?
What?
The way you keep strangely changing...
I can't bear it anymore.
I'm scared of what you'll turn into next.
I'm worried that we'll get caught by
other people.
I should be busy working but...
I have to be chained down by you.
It's frustrating and annoying.
I won't be like that.
I can stop being like that.
Go to Teacher Dong Ju.
What?
Right now,
I'm taking you to Teacher Dong Ju.
Dae Woong.
You've had a hard time because of me,
huh?
I'm sorry.
From now on, I won't make
you worried about me anymore.
I'm not going to Teacher Dong Ju.
Let's go home.
Get out.
Because I was with you for so long,
I lost it for a little bit...
But watching you keep changing,
I've suddenly woken up.
- Dae Woong...
- If you really can become human,
I might be able to bear it.
But right now, you can't guarantee
that you'll become like that.
I'm scared, uneasy, annoyed and frustrated so...
I can't look at you anymore.
So you leave.
When I told you to leave before,
you left quietly, right?
I'll ask you again,
Please leave.
Dae Woong, don't be like this.
I'm scared. Don't be like this.
Go to Teacher Dong Ju,
and live with the identity of
Park Sun Ju that he made for you.
That way, I won't feel bad about this either.
And don't you ever...
appear in front of me again.
Dae Woong.
I love you
Words from the bottom of my heart
Dae Woong really left.
He threw me away and left.
Dae Woong's like that
'cause he's tired.
I just have to be good again.
Dae Woong, what's wrong?
Stop drinking!
How many bottles has it been already?!
Right now, I have to go completely crazy.
She definitely won't leave at once.
She'll come back.
Then I'll have to go completely crazy.
And act like an insane person.
One moment.
Hey!
I was always curious what you were
trying to get from Dae Woong by enticing him.
I heard that you took
half of Dae Woong's life away.
I knew I was right...
your existence will harm Dae Woong.
You hate that I'm by Dae Woong's side
THAT much?
Yeah!
I regret so much not being able
to capture Dae Woong's heart.
Because if only I accepted his heart,
and the two us were dating...
You wouldn't have been able
to get involved and harm him.
You really believe that I'm only
harming Dae Woong when I'm by his side?
Then you're not?
Ah, you said that you don't have
a conscience or pride, right?
So that's why you can stick to him
without any shame.
When you said giving Dae Woong
the bead would be helpful to him,
I was able to bear with you.
But you weren't helping him...
You used him because you needed him.
You're really a monster.
Dae Woong!
Mi Ho, Dae Woong's really drunk.
I tried to stop him,
but he kept saying he has to go crazy
and wouldn't let me.
He wasn't the type to drink alcohol
to clear his anger.
But it seems like he's really having
a difficult time.
You should comfort him well.
I'm leaving.
Did I make it that difficult for you?
Woong, drink some water.
Why are you here?
Just because you tell me to leave,
do you think I'll leave so obediently?
I'm super strength instant glue.
If you're not leaving, then I'll leave.
Dae Woong.
I'll go with you.
Woong, if you're mad at me,
then you can get angry.
Lose your temper and pull
a long face, it's all right.
You can do whatever you want.
I will take all of it.
Until 100 days run out,
I can bear all of it.
You really…
You've already gave half of your life
to me, right?
Starting from now, you don't have
to do anything.
Until all my tails have disappeared
and I've become a human,
leave it all to me.
You just have to stay by my side.
I don't want to.
I don't like having you by my side.
Even if you somehow become human,
your essence is still gumiho.
Perhaps people who don't know
can see you as a human...
but in my eyes, it's not like that.
Then, what am I in your eyes?
Recently my eyes keep seeing you...
as a monster.
I still don't understand love
So I'm unable to get closer
But why does my silly heart keep pounding?
I come across you again and again
I just can't escape
Towards this helpless love,
my heart hurts endlessly
A day has passed, all I think about is you
The pitiful and foolish me
What should I do?
The heart following love
What am going to do?
My heart hurts so much
from this hopeless love
[One month later]
Thank you everyone, for your hard work.
Starting from next week, we'll start filming
at the studio.
Everyone go back and rest well.
Okay, everybody worked hard.
You've worked hard.
Miss Hae In, you've worked hard.
Director.
Yes, our Mr. Cha, you've worked hard too.
Director, you too.
Director!
Min Sook!
Dad!
Let go.
Oh, you're back.
Grandpa.
But, your face has gotten so thin in a month!
It probably 'cause I got so tanned.
I ate very well and lived very well too.
I didn't get injured either.
I've come back nice and healthy.
Really? Let's eat first.
Aunt made a lot of things that
you like.
I'm going to clean up and change first.
Okay.
Mi Ho didn't go to meet Dae Woong?
After Dae Woong went to China, she
moved out of the place they lived in,
and never even went back once.
It looks like they've completely broken up.
Today is the 88th day.
There aren't many days left.
She should be ok... right?
If you do this survey, we'll give you
a complimentary gift.
Please fill one out.
It closed down.
Looks like they left together for
a faraway place.
Back then, I didn't know about love
Staying by the side of someone,
I feel unfamiliar and scared
with this kind of thing
Thank you.
Oh, excuse me, miss.
You didn't fill out the name.
My name is Park Sun Ju.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tiggerlily93
Spot Translators: fore, yOiTzO
Timer: casajuve
Editor/QC: snoopyvkd
Final QC: relunctantbutaddicted
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
After I'm president...
[2010, October 6, tune in at 9:55 PM]
no one will be unprotected
by the Republic of Korea.
That's my reason for becoming President.
Game?
You thought it was because I have something
to gain that I intervened with this matter?
You didn't know that I became a prosecutor
to capture members of the legislature?
Crying towards the law,
crying towards the media.
An impossible to achieve objective,
has been agreed to at once but...
You want her political objectives
to be achieved as well?
This is a war infringing on
the boundaries of the country.
For that,
you're going to let 20 people be
buried alive at the bottom of the ocean?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com