Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Is it Mi Ho?
Why are you calling?
Where are you?
When are you coming back?
I want to see you.
Can you come back earlier today?
Well, I don't miss you that much.
And I never thought of going back earlier.
What's wrong?
Looks like you really don't miss me.
That's very fortunate.
Mi Ho, actually I...
Woong.
I have something to say to you.
Even if I'm not scaring you,
you will still protect my bead, right?
Yes.
Even if you don't need it,
you will protect it, right?
Yes.
You still don't trust me?
I trust you.
So,
even if I'm not by your side,
you still have to protect the bead well.
What?
Dae Woong.
I think I'm going to have to
disappear from your side
In the future,
I'll definitely find you
and ask for my bead.
You have to wait for me until then.
Don't come back!
Because I said that I don't miss you,
you're showing your strength?
Last time you disappeared without a word.
This time you want to
disappear after a call?
If you dare, then just disappear
like this and see.
Where are you right now?
Oh...
The hospital.
You even followed me to the hospital
where I had my checkup?
If you're like that, then where
do you want to disappear to?
Don't move! Wait for me!
I'm going to find you.
I have to disappear.
Otherwise The Hater will
force me to get a checkup.
And will also spread strange rumors.
What should I do?
I have to disappear.
I can't cry.
If I cry, it'll start to rain.
In the future, when I've become human,
and when I can get a checkup normally,
I can go back to Dae Woong's side again.
I don't want to disappear.
Don't want to disappear.
Mi Ho!
Turns out you were here.
Did Dae Woong get his check-up?
Is he all right?
Dae Woong will be fine.
You didn't see Dae Woong?
Then did you see Hae In unni?
Yes.
That's really strange.
She made us come with you.
Unless she's playing tricks on us.
Mi Ho, we were just about to go eat.
Let's go together.
Since you're not in a very good mood,
let's eat barbecue meat.
Meat?
Let's go, it's my treat.
Let's go.
I have to disappear.
Let's go, to eat barbecue meat!
Let's go.
Mi Ho, why are you eating so fast?
I have to disappear right
away after I eat meat.
Where are you?
The barbecue meat shop.
What?
Weren't you going to disappear?
Why did you start eating barbecue meat?
Where is the barbecue meat shop?
Is it Dae Woong?
Are you eating together with Byung Soo?
I have to disappear.
The two of you, take care.
What?
Where should I disappear to?
I just had a fight with Teacher Dong Ju.
I don't want to go find him.
Where should I go?
Oh, it's Mi Ho.
It's Grandpa.
You came to the hospital, too?
Really?
I misunderstood you.
I apologize.
Don't take it to heart.
Come to my house.
Have a talk with the family members.
I have to disappear.
Come here.
Mi Ho said that she had to
disappear and she left.
Make her stay!
Why did you guys only
care about eating meat?
Hey! All the meat here
has been eaten by her!
Thanks for believing in Dae
Woong and accompanying him.
You're truly amazing.
Eat lots.
You sure can eat a lot.
Min Sook, bring over the
Korean beef tenderloin.
[Dae Woong]
It's Dae Woong, right?
Pick up.
Dae Woong doesn't like
that you're not going back.
He's calling for you to hurry up.
Min Sook, pack some kimchi.
And also some other side dishes
for her to take along.
Take it back and eat it with Dae Woong.
Wait a minute.
There should be other things
for you to bring, too.
I have to disappear.
She's not picking up her phone.
She saw Hae In unni today, is
she feeling uncomfortable?
How could Mi Ho have seen Hae In noona?
Didn't Hae In noona's dad
give you your check-up?
That hospital belongs to Hae In noona's dad?
Hae In unni told us to bring Mi Ho there
while you were getting your check-up.
She said she'd take us out to eat.
But she wasn't even picking up her phone.
Turns out that we've been fooled.
We saw that Mi Ho's expression
didn't look too good.
Could it be that when she was with
Hae In noona, she became unhappy?
It's possible that she was
fooled as well.
Once I've taken this back,
I have to disappear.
Big eyes!
Ahjumma.
Why do you look so unenergetic?
This, this!
Do you want me to buy this for you to drink?
Ahjumma. Goodbye.
Why does she look so unenergetic?
Before she was always really energetic,
and she even helped me make deliveries.
Right now, I don't have any other excuse.
Do I really have to disappear?
Isn't she a monster?
So I made her disappear.
I thought it was a bit strange.
Because of a girl who suddenly appeared,
you started to drift away from me.
An injury that can only fully recover
in at least three to four months,
she healed in a couple of days.
I can't understand.
Afterward, I also saw this.
The video camera filmed it.
This is footage that I cut off.
This is...
She's... not a human, right?
I'm correct, right?
So did you tell her to disappear?
I originally wanted to find out
her true identity at the hospital.
But she said that if I let her go,
she'll disappear by herself.
She was a little scary,
and I was also hesitant.
I really couldn't continue talking with her.
She said that she'll disappear by herself?
That's right.
A monster that scary.
She's finally disappearing from your side.
It's really fortunate.
Mi Ho's not scary at all,
and she's not a monster.
What?
Also, unless Mi Ho deliberately
wanted to break up,
she definitely wouldn't leave me.
I don't want to disappear.
I really don't want to disappear.
Woong!
I don't want to leave!
I never wanted to chase her away.
You don't have to be troubled by it.
What is she exactly?
You don't have to mind that, either.
Just pretend that nothing has changed.
What's with you now?
A thing that dangerous and you're leaving
and don't care?
Have you gone crazy?
That's right.
Because of that I'm really
about to go crazy!
So, don't you mind it.
[Dae Woong]
It was sunny a while ago, why did
it start to rain so heavily?
I'm begging you, pick up the phone.
Woong.
Mi Ho, you're crying right now, right?
Yes.
It's raining so heavily.
I didn't even bring an umbrella.
Can you stop crying?
But...
I can't stop my tears.
I can't do anything about it.
I don't want to get drenched in the rain.
I can only go back if you stop crying.
If I want you to stop crying,
I only have this tactic left.
Mi Ho.
I... miss you.
What?
I really miss you.
I will go there right away.
Don't cry anymore.
The rain's stopping.
These are the things that you wanted.
With the identity of 23-year old
Park Sun Ju,
I created a passport and birth certificate.
Park Sun Ju, driver's licence.
Elementary school, middle school,
high school graduation certificate,
and also a university diploma.
It's all been completely prepared.
Very good.
In the suburbs of Tokyo, Japan,
I want to buy a house under her name.
It has to be quiet around there.
It's best if there's can be a spacious
courtyard where you can barbecue meat.
How much time can you give me?
I'll give you three month's time.
After three months,
there will be a girl called Park Sun Ju
who will arrive in Japan.
I even heard him say that he missed me.
I definitely can't disappear.
No matter what, I have to
finish off that woman.
At any rate, I still have to
make her receive a check-up.
Saying that she's a monster
just by using this...
It'll probably only make people
think that I've gone crazy.
Miss Hae In.
That girl, is she interested in my movie?
Director, if the action movie
meets the standards,
will you really start using new
people for the main roles?
Yes.
If it's like that, then please
give me an opportunity.
I have confidence.
No doubt, Miss Eun Hae In's
acting is pretty good.
But I already abandoned selected
stars who took on the role.
I really want to produce real action.
Miss Eun Hae In has not
reached that stage yet.
Regardless, if you see that girl,
just tell her that Ban Doo Hong
really wants to see her just once.
Please, you have to help
me pass on the message.
He wants me to bring that
kind of girl over here?
That's too unreasonable.
What?
Ah, I didn't even put down the hand brake.
So annoying!
Who parked their car in
the middle of the road?
What?
What are you doing?
I came to see you.
You're making me disappear.
But I am unable to.
So what are you going to do to me?
Are you threatening me?
There are a lot of people who pass by here.
There's no one here.
You... can you just let me go this once?
I don't want to disappear.
Because of my self-respect, I originally
didn't want to do this to humans.
Just let me go this once.
I'm begging you.
You gave the bead to Dae Woong,
so Dae Woong definitely won't feel
pain, and won't get injured?
That's right.
That bead won't be harmful
at all to Dae Woong.
It will only benefit him.
So that's why he can fearlessly
act in the movie.
Your bead... give me one too.
If you give one to me, I'll just
pretend not to know about it.
Dae Woong is helping cover
you up because of that, too.
I can't, I only have one bead.
Once I gave it to Dae Woong,
I can't take it back anymore.
If I had that, then I can act
like Dae Woong, too.
I can also perform well
in front of the Director.
I can threaten you to intimidate you.
I can also use strength to
make you unable to move.
But if I do that, I won't be like a human.
I'm not a monster.
Right now I'm like a human, begging you.
I won't cause any harm to you.
Can you just let me remain here?
If you want to beg other people,
you have to pay a price.
You'll be more like a human if you do that.
Will you do whatever I tell you to?
Mi Ho and Hae In noona are together.
The atmosphere is a bit strange.
[Dae Woong]
I finally met you.
I never knew that you were
this close to me all along.
This period of time,
I've been really troubled.
I'm very glad to meet you, Mi Ho.
Mi Ho said that she's shy around strangers.
When Director chased her,
she thought it was burdensome,
so she ran away.
I'm not the kind of person who
gives other people burdens.
I only saw Miss Mi Ho's ability that night,
and I just wanted to show my enthusiasm
about my brand-new action movie,
So I was following you.
How about it?
Have you ever thought about filming with me?
Then let's cooperate nicely this once.
I don't know how to act in action films.
I don't want to be famous.
Then you mean, you only
want to be a stuntwoman?
She's really shy.
Her acting skills are completely
below standard.
She also never thought
about becoming an actor.
So it's like that.
I clearly had confidence that I can
train you, Mi Ho, to become a star.
But if you don't want to, then I
can't help it either.
Then will the main actor choose the star?
The action part will be
covered by our Miss Mi Ho.
I will do it only if she acts.
Let her face be known,
I'll do the action parts.
What is this?
If it's like that...
I only know how to be her stuntwoman.
If she acts the lead role,
then I will be the stuntwoman.
If I want to film a movie with Mi Ho,
then I have to let Eun Hae In
take the lead role?
Is that what you mean?
Director, I will do it very well.
I thought that person was chasing
me because he was irritated with me.
Turns out that he was chasing
me because he liked me too much.
If the Director's side approves,
then during the three months of filming,
I won't mind you.
Then in the future, are you still
planning to do something to me?
It depends.
Forget it.
After three months, I'll become normal.
Noona, what did you do to her?
Didn't I tell you to stop minding her?
Dae Woong, you knew too?
You know that I've been discovered?
Are you confused with the current situation?
You should protect me on
behalf of humankind!
Let's go.
Cha Dae Woong.
According to what you said,
she's not very dangerous.
On the contrary, she's
actually quite useful.
You want her to stay by
your side because of what?
You understand it, too.
I heard that you already
started to use her bead.
Then I can only let her
be my stuntwoman...
to get the position of the lead role.
What?
Just like how you're using her,
I'm just copying you.
I need her anyway,
so I decided to leave her
alone and not mind.
That woman doesn't understand anything.
Dae Woong, you clearly don't need the bead,
and you're even helping me take care of it.
That woman is really mean.
I helped her push the truck to the
side for nothing a while ago.
Mi Ho.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to use you,
I'm really, really sorry.
No, at first... didn't I threaten you
by saying that I'm going to eat you?
Mi Ho.
I'm really sorry.
Woong, I'm sorry too.
Woong, they said that I'm
a stuntwoman.
Very cool, right?
That's very tiresome.
Will you be all right?
I'm a gumiho.
It's suitable for me.
I'm just worried that doing too well
will make you get discovered.
Even though you don't need them,
you have to use the steel wires.
Occasionally you have to
show a tired expression.
I can do it very well.
Ah, so tired.
I'm a weak woman.
It's not like that.
This time you should be like,
Ah, so tired.
Let's rest a bit.
That's right.
Wipe it like this.
Like this?
[Swordsman Under the Moon]
This is the script for your
part in the movie.
You have to look at this to learn.
You're the heroine, Full Moon.
The hero is New Moon.
Full Moon, New Moon.
Then that's Round Moon and Crescent Moon.
It symbolizes the two heroes' love and fate.
Full Moon dedicated everything
to the hero before disappearing.
And the empty man, New Moon,
becomes full because of Full Moon.
But it's a sad story where he ends up alone.
Ah, so it's a love story between two people.
Then, since I'm Full Moon, you be New Moon.
No, I'm playing Black Rain, Hyun Woo.
Then should I say I won't be Full Moon
unless they make you New Moon?
That doesn't work.
Just study the script some more.
Here's Full Moon's part.
It's here!
Rose petals fall scattered into the bathtub.
The belt is being untied lightly,
revealing a pale white shoulder.
Wait!
You're not the one acting this.
You don't even need to look at this.
What? I like taking baths.
You're only doing the action scenes.
You're not supposed to do romantic films.
I know.
I think Full Moon has a fighting scene
further back where her clothes fall off.
It's here.
Hanging from a tree branch,
revealing white skin.
These parts aren't what you're acting!
Just say that you definitely
won't act these. Understand?
I know.
Dae Woong, there's Black Rain,
Hyun Woo, here too!
You act the part where you gaze
lovingly at a virtuous girl.
The plot hasn't developed much yet.
At first, when your tears
drenched my clothes,
I thought to just wait and let it dry.
But those tears became
bigger clouds and wind,
and fell as rain that
held back my footsteps.
While rain that can't be stopped,
can't be avoided, falls down on me,
where am I supposed to go?
I lost my way.
Even though I want to run far away,
you stay on my mind,
and I keep coming back.
I want to protect you,
and I want to treat you well.
While getting rained on,
I must have lost my mind.
What are you doing?
Showing the virtuous girl's feelings.
This isn't in the script.
Don't be like this from today on.
The last sentence you said
isn't in here either.
That's because I said the wrong lines.
I was wrong.
Being at Cha Dae Woong's side,
your identity will be exposed.
I said that he definitely won't tell anyone.
If other people know,
at that time, what are you going to do?
I will become human in three months.
Until then, I just have to
not get discovered.
Only your body is becoming human.
But the gumiho in the past
will be exposed again.
I'm definitely a bit worried about that.
That woman said I'm a monster.
If another person found out,
they'd say that too, right?
Thoroughly erase your gumiho past.
I will help build you into
a complete human being.
What's that?
Use Park Sun Ju's name.
I've prepared everything
that a human being needs.
Wow, it's so complete!
I have these, so I can
live like human beings.
Yes, you can live like a real human.
But, using Park Sun Ju's name to live,
you can't remain by Cha Dae Woong's side.
The people around Cha Dae Woong all
know that you're called Mi Ho.
Also, there's somebody who
already knows your true identity.
In the future, you'll be associated
with even more people.
You'll be revealed, sooner or later.
To become human, you have to go to
a place where nobody recognizes you.
If you agree to that,
I can help you become a complete person.
Park Sun Ju. The name sounds really nice.
Park Sun Ju has this, too?
I'm the driving Park Sun Ju.
Park Sun Ju even attended university?
I'm smart Park Sun Ju.
Wow, Park Sun Ju even has a lot of money!
I'm rich Park Sun Ju.
Being Park Sun Ju is so cool!
What meaning does that have?
Dae Woong won't be by my side.
[Swordsman Under the Moon
Line Rehearsal Room]
Introducing the movie's actors.
First, it's the female lead,
Miss Eun Hae In.
I'm Full Moon, Eun Hae In.
Please take care of me.
New Moon, Baek Chang Hyung.
Black Rain, Cha Dae Woong.
New Moon, listen to the rhythm.
How can she be Unni's co-star?
She can't act any roles.
Miss Min Sook, can we meet today?
Be more energetic!
Hello.
- They made the roof like that over here?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Where's the director?
Director!
Miss Min Sook, please don't hang up.
Also, don't be jealous
of brother Chow Yun Fat.
He doesn't know anything.
Okay, action!
Good.
Good!
Miss Min Sook,
You won't do, even if I give
up brother Chow Yun Fat?
Min Sook...
Why aren't there any calls today?
Was I a bit too much?
Tonight at the Korean Film Festival,
I will receive a special award.
I'm really sorry. I wasn't able
to put you in first place.
When you receive this,
please watch the acceptance speech.
I want you to see my sincerity.
Brother, I am sorry.
I am sorry.
Director Ban.
If my father receives an award tonight,
we're going to have a party
at my dad's friend's place.
We'll have a dinner together
with all the workers, too.
Can I go too?
Okay, you can come.
Woong, what's a party?
It's just when everybody eats, drinks,
plays and is happy together.
It's like a get-together.
Ah, is it like this?
When did you learn that?
This is the same as the ones
five hundred years ago.
Five hundred years ago is too outdated.
Then, like this.
Where did you learn that from?
I saw the ahjumma at the fried chicken
shop and her friends go like this.
It's not like that.
The moves are all kind of like,
Like this, like this,
like, more variety...
- Like this.
You really don't have a
feel for rhythm.
[Dae Woong! Let's make up!]
You try it.
You don't even blink an eye.
You're indeed different from humans.
I blinked.
You think that you can just pretend?
Today, don't attend the director's
congratulations party.
Why?
It's supposed to be a happy occasion.
Dangerous people are not allowed to mingle.
If you get mixed up in a group of people,
I will feel frightened and I really
don't know what you'll be saying.
Dae Woong will also be distracted
and unable to enjoy himself.
After he started being with you, he
drifted farther away from his old friends.
You know that too, right?
A day like today, just let him go.
Miss Mi Ho, drink this.
- Also this.
- Do you like to eat sandwiches?
Mi Ho.
Drink this.
Wow! This is my favorite.
Miss Mi Ho.
You have to come to the director's
congratulations party.
I really can't be at ease for even a moment.
Woong, if I'm together with
humans, will it bother you?
Worry you?
I'm not being worried on purpose,
it's because you're too beau-
Haven't seen the world.
Don't casually talk with other people.
Change upstairs and let's go.
I'll let you experience the so-called party.
You go first.
I'll go after I see the fried
chicken shop's ahjumma.
Do you know the address?
Will you be able to find it?
Yes, you go and have fun.
The 21st Korean Film Festival
special award winner is...
Director Ban Doo Hong.
I truly thank everyone.
I truly thank everyone for
giving me this award.
Thank you.
Oh, my!
I'm going to take this
honor and share it with...
everyone who likes my movies.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
The one who's looking at me right now,
I believe that you definitely...
understand my sincerity now.
You made me able to receive this honor.
Thank you! Thank you!
I understand.
Director's sincerity...
I understand!
That Ban Doo Hong or Ban Du Hoon,
seems like he really meant it.
Here.
- Cheers!
Speaking of which,
what happened to my father?
What was that? He acted like an idiot.
When is Mi Ho coming?
She said that she went to see a
friend. She'll be here in a minute.
Mi Ho has friends?
Hey, our Mi Ho is okay.
Her popularity is very high
in our neighborhood.
They're all cheering her
to become community president.
I want to go to the party too.
Oh, it's Teacher Dong Ju.
Teacher Dong Ju?
They say it's some party,
but it's actually not much.
You're that sad about it?
Teacher Dong Ju, you've been to
many, so you think it's not much.
It's because I've never
been to one, so I'm curious.
Gumiho still can't enjoy
it to her heart's content.
Have you thought about
becoming Park Sun Ju?
Becoming her, of course, is good.
But no matter how good it is,
if Dae Woong's not at my side,
it's not meaningful.
It's because you've never been there before,
so you're saying that it's not meaningful.
Do you want to go there once?
For the remainder of the day,
become Park Sun Ju.
Are you okay, Miss Park Sun Ju?
What are we doing here?
You have to have outfits
that suit Park Sun Ju.
I don't have money.
Even though you don't have any,
Park Sun Ju does.
Try this one on.
The style on this side is pretty too.
I like this color. It's the color of cows.
How many?
Where did Miss Park Sun Ju
attend university?
What major? How many years?
You've remembered them clearly, right?
Yes. Korea University.
Asian Studies major, Class of 07.
That's right.
Today your classmates are having
a gathering. A university reunion.
It's a type of party.
Party?
I can go into that type of place?
Of course.
Miss Park Sun Ju has the
qualifications to go in.
I won't be discovered by
other people as a fake, right?
It might cause a bit of suspicion.
Wait a moment.
Why isn't she here yet?
Cha Dae Woong!
In my heart, you're completely defeated.
Defeated!
Hey, Byung Soo, Seon Nyeo is drunk!
Seon Nyeo definitely drank too much!
Lastly, I'm going to give
you a farewell kiss.
Seon Nyeo!
You didn't kiss Seon Nyeo?!
Ah, so close.
I almost caused big trouble.
I was very fortunate.
Cha Dae Woong, it's very fortunate
that nothing happened.
Because Seon Nyeo likes you, she went a
bit too far while the liquor was strong.
You made it sound as if it was
a big deal, just grumbling here.
You really ruined my appetite.
Hey, I almost caused big trouble!
Abusing me once, I can bear it.
But if by accident something happens,
Mi Ho will be in big trouble!
You're Cha "Chun Hyang"*! Cha Chun Hyang!
*Korean folk tale heroine known for loyalty
Even if there's a sword resting on my neck,
I still have to guard my chastity.
So take Seon Nyeo farther away.
It should be okay, right?
Why? Let's go together.
Our Dae Woong is so great.
So, is it because of that girl?
It'll cause trouble?
Right now this is more suitable for you.
Did Park Sun Ju buy this, too?
This is a present that I'm giving you.
Give that one to me.
There are a lot of precious things in here.
It doesn't suit you.
This is more suitable for you.
Okay, let's go in.
Miss Park Sun Ju.
Please come in.
Don't be nervous.
Just follow what the other people are doing.
Please show your name.
Park Sun Ju.
Okay, please come in.
She shouldn't have caused
any trouble, right?
I'll call the fried chicken
shop's ahjumma and ask.
Dae Woong.
Are you still angry at me?
Noona, I understand why you think that way.
At first I was like you, too.
I'm really very worried about you.
- It's the truth.
- Noona.
The one I'm worried for now is her.
That's what I truly feel.
I'm leaving first.
There are still a lot of friends left.
Why did you come out so early?
Everybody really did treat
me as Park Sun Ju.
Although it's very new, I feel a bit shy.
There's still ample time
for you to get used to it.
Becoming human with Park Sun Ju's identity,
I won't ever be discovered by anyone, right?
But, when I'm with Dae Woong,
it'll be better if we can naturally
become more comfortable.
The two of us are both lying,
and it's very tiring.
If you're by Dae Woong's side,
you have to tell lies and work hard.
Cha Dae Woong will do it even more.
Isn't he hiding the truth from his
family and friends right now?
Because of me, Dae Woong both
worries and tells lies.
He must be really exhausted.
If you have this, you can go anywhere.
After one hundred days, leave Cha Dae Woong,
and this place, by yourself.
I will help you.
Min Sook really did see it.
Who are you?
This is also what I feel.
I like everything about you.
You definitely can't give up.
Min Sook.
Oh, my!
What am I going to do?
What?
Chow Yun Fat.
I'm sorry.
She's not at the fried
chicken shop or at home.
Where exactly is she?
Where did you go?
Where did you go dressed like that?
Hmm?
My clothes, my bag!
You left your things in my car.
It's too late today,
I'll take them over some other time.
It's good if she just forgets
everything one by one like this.
It's fortunate that I didn't
leave them somewhere else.
I left them in Teacher Dong Ju's car.
Dae Woong, your cell phone.
Dae Woong, did you have fun at the party?
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
Looks like you had a good time, too.
You look like you really
went to a real party.
Yes.
You really dressed for the occasion, too.
This outfit I borrowed from
a person called Park Sun Ju.
Who's Park Sun Ju?
Is she Park Dong Ju's relative?
You even met Park Dong Ju's family members?
What kind of relationship do you have?
Dae Woong,
how did you introduce me
to your relatives and friends?
What did you say about me?
Say what? Of course I couldn't say anything.
Then what will you say if they ask?
I said something before.
But we'll have to find a day to clearly say
what happened between you and me before.
Dae Woong, I'm sorry that because of me,
you have to lie.
It's okay.
Lying is my instinct, don't worry about it.
But Mi Ho.
Yes?
There's something that
I'm a bit worried about.
The bead in my chest... there
seems to be some side effects.
What's wrong?
When I become intimate with another woman,
the bead will shatter
and I'll be hurt, right?
Yes.
Following the same principle,
when I'm wearing the bead,
and you meet with another man, there
are some side effects on me, too.
Really?
There shouldn't be any.
No, no, no.
The bead has a reaction.
Especially when you meet
with Teacher Dong Ju.
The pressure over my chest
is getting more serious.
Since it affects my health, I hope you'll
try not to see Teacher Dong Ju anymore.
So, if I do meet with Teacher
Dong Ju in the future,
I'll stay farther away from him.
Before I was too close.
You two were really close together?!
So that's why my body's like this!
At least five meters away.
No, ten meters' distance.
I understand.
Why is the bead like this?
Are you still uncomfortable now?
I think there's still a bit, over here.
Seems like the bead has calmed down
because the owner is at its side.
Here.
If she's always looking for him,
it'll be very difficult for her to forget.
Dong Ba, make this movie
into a big event this time!
- Yes!
- Okay!
- I understand!
- Work diligently!
Preparations for the dress
rehearsal are finished!
Okay, the first scene!
Camera!
Let start with the action, got it?
Gong Pal!
- Yes, I understand!
- Let's go!
- Everyone, fighting!
- Fighting!
Director.
I came here to greet you
before the first scene.
Mmm, yes.
Watch attentively at the side.
Please go over there.
Yes, Mi Ho is at the filming location.
Mi Ho?
Okay, I got it.
Tell her that I'll come
over to return her bag.
Park Dong Ju?
Why did you tell that person Mi Ho is here?
Just tell him to drop off
the bag at our house.
Cha Chun Hyang, you're
getting way too jealous.
You're going to stay here again today,
even though you're not filming?
Yes, I'm going to stay until the end.
Take off the ring.
Why?
Is it right to wear a ring like
that in a historical drama?
Mi Ho.
Come out for a moment.
It fits me perfectly.
Look at this.
Compared to a monster like you wearing
this ring, it fits me perfectly, too.
That isn't yours right now.
It's mine, give it to me.
It's not mine right now?
Then you're saying it was mine before?
It's mine! Give me back my ring!
Speak clearly.
Was this originally mine?
You can't win against me.
If you don't want to get injured,
return it to me immediately.
I got it, I'll give it to you.
My strength definitely
can't beat a monster's.
As a result, I can't possibly
take that ring away from you.
You gave Dae Woong the bead and
then took away my ring, right?
Is the bead that extraordinary?
By chance, if that bead got into an
accident, it would cause you trouble?
You don't need to know.
Dae Woong said that just touching
him will cause big trouble.
Wait and see.
I will make you get hurt.
Dae Woong, you hold onto this.
Okay.
Don't perform too enthusiastically, to keep
people from seeing that you're a gumiho.
Be more delicate. What did you I teach you?
Ah, so tired. Let's rest a bit.
Good job.
Our Mi Ho, fighting!
What's fighting?
That's right, I have to speak
language that you can understand.
Win!
Miss Mi Ho, you have to
take the ladder outside...
onto a smooth platform and jump down.
How about it? Will it be okay?
Don't be too uneasy.
The safety facilities have
all been readily prepared.
It could be a bit difficult,
but I'll try it.
Before filming starts,
she should drink a soda.
Byung Soo, are they about to film now?
I'll tell you later, later.
Hey!
Ah, really...
Are they starting to film from this side?
Slowly, slowly.
A bit higher.
Take off, landing, understand?
Mi Ho.
Dae Woong,
- Ah, yeah...
- You don't have any scenes today,
why did you come over?
Because it's the start of the movie,
so I came over to greet the director.
Mi Ho.
Drink some soda.
What are you doing?!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tiggerlily93
Spot Translators: meju, serendipity
Timer: casajuve
Editor/QC: langdon813
Final QC: reluctantbutaddicted
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com