Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 4
Why did it start moving?
Dae Woong! Dae Woong!
Dae Woong!
Dae Woong! Woong!
Woong!
Woong.
Rain on a clear day
is called fox rain.
It's the rain that
will fall when I'm sad.
How's that possible?
As if it snows when she gets a runny nose,
or there's a typhoon when she sneezes.
That's impossible.
I'm very happy that I became
friends with you!
What friend?
I'm her source of food and I finally
managed to escape from danger.
Promise me, don't let it get damaged,
protect it well.
Why is it raining on a clear day?
Grasping people without letting go?
Why? Why?
Because of the water, my aura
is getting weaker and weaker.
Plus the bead isn't beside me.
I can't keep on crying.
It's quite strange, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
So scary!
That noona is scary.
What's wrong with her?
So scary!
Customer, are you alright?
I say, Miss!
Oh, what to do?
With my aura weakened, my face
has already started to change.
Terrible, terrible.
Hey!
Hey! What exactly did you do to my child?
Customer, did something happen?
The girl who went in there just
now made my child cry.
Hey, open the door!
I say, you make someone else's child
cry but you don't utter a single word?
You said that she looked like a monster?
Yes, it really was scary.
What exactly did she look like to be
able to scare a child to this degree?
I didn't see her. She was hiding the
entire time and wouldn't come out.
I saw. She didn't look like a human.
She became really scary.
Monster? Change?
Is it Mi Ho?
It can't be... Mi Ho?
Mi Ho.
Why are you staying down there?
How did you change into this?
Pretty!
I almost forgot about you and left you here.
Let's go.
Oh, so it's Pretty.
Then, where exactly is Mi Ho?
Mi Ho!
Oh, it's Dae Woong!
Customer, if you still won't open
the door, we're just going to enter.
Go get the key.
Who is it exactly?
I don't know. There's a woman who
went inside but won't come out.
- Is it Mi Ho? Is Mi Ho in here?
- Dae Woong!
What are you doing here?
Come out quickly.
Is it because you're angry at me?
Well, didn't I come back?
Come out quickly!
I can't go outside right now.
Once you see what I look like,
you'll definitely be frightened.
Why?
It can't be that your tails came out.
It's okay, I've already
seen them a couple times.
I'm already used to it.
I won't get scared.
It's not the tails.
My aura has been weakened,
which caused the change.
What part changed?
Open the door first. I'm the only one
here right now so it's okay.
You will definitely get scared.
What is there to be scared of...
See, I told you that you'd get scared.
You're right, it is kind of scary.
It's this key, right?
It should be. Let's go.
Before the other people rush over,
let's leave this place.
Here, we'll drape this over you.
Come out quickly.
Wrap it more tightly, tighter.
But how did you transform into this?
Why did you drag me here and leave?
I didn't, I just left temporarily.
It's the boat that left me.
Even if I did leave temporarily,
you should've eaten your fill of grilled
meat on the boat. Be more courageous.
But you ended up crying and transforming
into something this scary.
Don't let other people see. Wrap it tightly.
Is it because I cried that you came back?
Rain on a clear day,
it ruined the moods of all
the people out on excursions.
So that means you can't cry.
Let's find a place with no people first.
Customer! Customer! Customer!
Customer!
You can't take that away with you!
Mi Ho, are you okay?
Yes.
It'll be okay if I walk holding you
like this for the entire way.
Let's go.
Woong!
You changed back?
Yes! Because you've returned to my side!
So I was able to change back!
It's good that you're back.
No.
Stay like this for a little longer.
My aura is too weak.
I have to hold the bead for a little longer.
Ah...
how wonderful.
Okay now?
No, just a little more.
How much longer?
Just a little more.
I want to stay like this for awhile.
Helping me fix this, and even delivering
to a far-away place like here,
I am so thankful, Park Dong Ju.
I looked into it some more. It should be
possible to restore this picture.
You're saying...
that the fox in the picture
can be recovered?
Yes. Wait patiently.
I will bring the fox back into that picture.
You have to succeed.
Before that happens, the new disciples
will start to arrive and swarm together.
The third grandmother won't be
lonely anymore, either.
After waiting for a while, we will
be able to see it, right?
Yes, it has to return to its original form.
Child, this is Dae Woong's luggage.
Take this to him.
Dae Woong's independent mind is
currently ready to cause trouble.
If the seedling is that girl,
just add some fertilizer to
allow it to grow up quickly.
Let them be together.
What independent mind?
Making me run such a long distance.
At least the arguments
have stopped for now.
Why can't Dae Woong just stay independent
forever and I stay in love forever?
Don't know if Director Ban will
like the lunchbox I made.
I stayed up all night to make this
lunchbox, so I didn't get any sleep.
The sun is practically gone.
I can't be sleepy.
When will the director come?
I still have to ask Dae Woong about
how the results turned out today.
Dae Woong didn't make it
to the audition in time.
It's all that girl's fault by causing an
incident and messing it up.
For this audition,
he even prepared seriously.
That woman is the embodiment of misfortune!
He was late because he was buying
the outfit for Hae In sunbae.
Why did you start blaming Mi Ho?
Seon Nyeo,
I heard that Director Ban already
picked someone for the female lead.
Do you know who it is?
He saw a mysterious woman,
and has been obsessed ever since.
I clearly saw her here at this garbage can.
That figure who flew towards
the sky with nothing.
Could it really just be a dream?
Real Action, my dream.
Where... where is it?
Chicken again?
When are we going to eat beef?
Things didn't go very smoothly today.
Within this short period of time,
we can only live eating this.
Hey, you're still asking me to buy beef
for you to eat in this type of situation.
That's really shameless.
Didn't you say that I'm not human,
so it's okay for me to be shameless?
You can be shameless, but you
should still use your eyes.
I have no money, my dreams have been
shattered, how am I supposed to have beef?
Your dreams have been shattered?
Yes.
The first gate I have to pass in becoming
a big international action star,
has been closed right in front of my eyes.
Action?
Then what is it?
There is such a thing.
It's something I'm very skilled at.
Ah, so it's running away!
Even though in your eyes,
I'm the type of person who only knows
how to run away,
how to buy you meat to eat
all the time, and seems feeble.
But in women's eyes, I'm pretty handsome.
Speeding on a motorcycle,
running when I'm exercising,
when I'm about to fly with suspensions,
the women will all faint.
Woong, not only humans,
but even I can be put in a trance.
Really?
So, that means scholarly people's
insights are the same.
I mean, even when our dog Ddong Ja sees me,
the sound of her bark is different.
Dae Woong, if you start
practicing martial arts,
you will definitely be really handsome.
Of course.
Shall I show you?
Action.
Before I can continue looking for that
woman, I need to find a washroom.
It's very serious.
My name in the movie is Hyun Woo.
He's a chivalrous swordsman
nicknamed Black Rain.
Chase me. You've chased me to here.
I really took on a lot of trouble.
So this is... this is your final outcome.
Dae Woong! You were so great!
It's really amusing!
This was originally supposed to
be performed for the audition.
It's all in the past now.
- Eh, what a pity
- Eh, what a pity.
How depressing.
How... depressing.
So infuriating!
Forget it, tweh tweh tweh!
What a bunch of crap! Crap, crap, crap!
Don't care anymore, just leave it as it is.
Oh my God, what to do?
Woong, the wall is cracking.
Don't touch it.
What to do about this?
Someone's coming.
No matter where I turn,
I can't find a washroom.
I have no choice.
What to do? I feel a bit uneasy.
The crack in the wall is really severe.
I'm sorry.
So, Trench Coat Hero,
let's straighten things out.
You ruined their wall, and then you took
your pants off in front of that woman?
Is that right?
I'm not that type of a person.
I just peed at the foot of that wall.
Hey you,
so you're saying that you used your super,
invincible pee to knock over their wall?
Then why aren't you saying that your fart
can blow a bunny into the sky?
It probably can.
Are you trying to joke with me now!? You!
You're just wearing a trench coat,
but you made their wall collapse!
And you even took your pants off
in front of that woman, didn't you?
You're a typical complete whacko.
Please look carefully into my eyes.
I'm definitely not that type of person.
I can accept the accusation of
peeing in inappropriate places.
If you demand compensation because
I peed in an inappropriate place,
and caused a wall to collapse,
any amount is okay.
But you calling me a whacko.
I definitely will not accept that.
You really aren't explaining truthfully!
Honestly, I only peed.
And it wasn't even pee
I held in for a long time,
but only a normal amount of time.
How am I supposed to believe that? Huh?
Well...
I saw it.
It's true that this gentleman
only peed.
If you hadn't seen me today,
I would've been in big trouble.
Thank you.
As long as you're fine,
I'll be at ease, Director Ban.
Director Ban?
Do you know me?
Yes, I'm Cha Dae Woong.
I'm Ban Seon Nyeo's friend.
Cha Dae Woong. Cha...
Ahh...
So, that really popular person
at the action school is you.
Yes.
Originally I should've met you at
the Moonlight Swordsman audition.
Unexpectedly, I met you here.
I heard that you weren't able to participate
in the audition because you were late.
Saying this in a place
like this is kind of...
I really respect you, Director.
I feel extremely honored
to be able to meet you.
Letting you see me in such
an embarrassing state,
and hearing you say that you respect me,
I haven't lived for nothing.
Look carefully into my eyes.
This meeting today is a secret
between the two of us.
Can you swear on your name as a man?
Okay.
I will contact you.
Give you another opportunity.
I'll give you a call.
Thank you! Thank you!
- Leave safely!
- You should go back too.
Mi Ho, let's go!
Wait a moment.
What are you doing?
What are you doing with
something that dirty?!
I told you before that you can't just
pick up something and eat it!
Spit it out and throw it away!
Fine, if you throw that away,
I will buy you beef.
I always make you buy meat for me to eat.
I feel embarrassed.
You said that you'd buy meat for me.
It seems that things have
made good progress.
I can tell.
That's right.
Before, I never wanted to care,
but you really look too distressed.
When gumiho doesn't have the bead,
she'll be exhausted,
become weak and also become dirty.
Let's go, buy meat for me!
Buy meat and also something else.
Mi Ho,
we'll buy meat on the way back.
I'm going to buy what you need
the most first. Let's go.
This, dip it in water first.
Then squeeze this on it.
Here, hold it.
It's not edible!
It's delicious!
First go like this. Then go up and down.
Up down, up down, like this, like this.
Okay?
Use water.
Spit it out.
It's not supposed to be eaten!
It's delicious!
Use this, like this, wipe it like this.
Use this one or that one? Just come out
when you're finished washing.
Hey! You can't eat this.
It tastes good!
It tastes really good.
Here, open your hands.
Pat like this.
Oh, it tastes good!
I beg you, don't eat any more!
Seeing her like this almost makes
her seem like a normal person.
Today, because of you, I truly want
to become a real person.
It seems like you're in a good mood,
Miss Gu Mi Ho.
Then why don't you say when you're going
to take that bead inside me away?
I feel that my body's great.
How long do I still need to
keep that bead inside of me?
You should know.
Well, that...
it should've healed a lot.
Then I'll come there to
be properly examined.
How much longer until I
can take the bead out?
Today I did too much work,
I'm a little tired.
Ah, I'm sleepy, I want to rest.
Hey, what about the meat?
Leave it there, I'll eat it later.
Eat it later?
Seems like you're really tired.
I don't want to harm you.
I hope you can return obediently.
Can the fox really return to the picture?
He's almost fully recovered.
But if I tell him that, he'll let me
take the bead and go back.
Run! The boar's coming!
If I said that I'm going to stay here
and catch mosquitoes,
he'll think that I'm annoying, right?
Because I'm not human.
Hae In! Congratulations!
You got the role as Lady Seo In!
That's good.
But the person who'll play the lead
role hasn't been decided yet?
Ah, not yet.
Director,
before filming starts, I want to practice
a bit at Director Ban's Action School.
You don't have any fighting scenes,
there's no need.
You still want to act the lead role?
Well, it hasn't been decided yet.
In the last advertisement I filmed,
I did kung fu moves.
Also, I practiced fencing
for a period of time.
I want the director to see my strong points.
It's good that you're putting in effort,
but don't strain yourself.
That's too much!
I tried out for role of my dreams
but it ended up in Hae In unni's hands.
And I'm just playing
some maid or servant.
It wouldn't matter if I didn't want it,
but isn't my old dad being way too
harsh on his daughter?
After all, it's the job in which
Director Ban exerts all his effort.
He can't ruin it.
What?
Of course, you're prettier
than Hae In noona,
but your acting skills aren't that good.
Hey, even still... Maid Number One?
I'll get you into as many scenes as possible,
and also give you lots of screen time.
Stop joking. You're youngest rank in the production.
What can you possibly do?
But during action scenes,
the youngest power is the best.
At least...
I'm better than Dae Woong, who wasn't
even able to participate in the audition.
If you're not going to use my abilities,
let the Director give him another chance.
My old dad makes decisions quickly,
he won't show any mercy.
That Cha Dae Woong,
I wanted to see him today.
You changed your plan? Did something happen?
Ah, did you receive care from someone?
Do you know, in this action movie,
who will die first?
It's the type of people
who cause disturbances,
meddle in other people's business,
and spread rumors.
Five minutes after the movie
starts, that person will die.
So you just go and prepare well.
Oh my, oh my!
Why is he getting himself involved?
He'll definitely be the first to get shot.
Min Sook,
recently you're always watching movies
with waving swords and firing guns.
Are you dating a person
who likes to fight?
What are you talking about?
When dating a person who loved fishing,
you watched the fishing channel every day.
When you dated a baduk* player, you
watched the baduk channel. [*Korean chess]
Are you dating a person who fights,
so you're watching fighting movies?
Father, it's not fighting.
It's action, action.
Don't even know the difference.
So the man who Min Sook is obsessed
with recently is related to action.
Hmm, action. If only Dae Woong was here...
Maybe I'll discuss it with Dae Woong.
"My reliable child, Dae Woong."
I need to talk with you.
Come home just once.
This... What is this?
Reliable? Talk?
What's wrong with Grandpa suddenly?
Is he sick?
Woong!
Today, you have to perform what
you've been practicing well.
Of course I will.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
Don't let me mess it up again.
I'm not going with you.
You're letting me go by myself?
Yes.
Yesterday you said that
you're not eating meat,
and today you're saying
that you're not coming,
are you feeling sick anywhere?
If I wait for you, you will
definitely come back.
Right?
Yes.
Thanks for letting me go.
Then, I'm leaving.
Okay.
Mi Ho, if you're hungry, don't search
in the garbage cans.
Use this and buy some chicken or something.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Mi Ho, if something happens, you
know my phone number right?
Remember to call me.
Okay.
If today goes smoothly,
I'll buy beef for you.
Wait for me.
Okay.
I'm really leaving.
A couple days before, she was sticking
to me like gum,
now she suddenly wants to be separated.
Feels like I lost something.
What am I doing?
I think I've been influenced by her.
This won't do! Have to be clear-minded,
clear-minded!
Dae Woong, you should be fully recovered.
The bead can be removed.
Afterward, can I continue to stay here?
When you come back tonight,
I'll have to ask.
I probably won't be going
to the hospital today.
For now, let Mr Tae Jun store it for me.
Okay. Are you going to meet someone?
I'm going to send someone
to a far-away place.
Before that, I'll buy her good food to eat.
Then you're going on a date!
Have a good time.
Date?
I'm going to trick the fox over here.
That could count as a date.
Last night, my house's wall collapsed.
Did you see it? Did you see it?
Although it was pretty dark, but who am I?
My eyesight, how worse can it be?
That man was a serious specimen!
Who was it? Tell me too!
Also, recently there seems to be a cat.
Turning the garbage outside
into a huge mess.
My nephew's friend works for municipal
government, so I have some connections.
So typical of you, Madam Kang!
Who's that girl? Never seen her before.
Miss! What are you doing over there?
Miss, why are you looking
through my garbage?
Ah, found it!
I've collected 10!
Miss.
You can't take the free coupons you find
in the fried chicken shop's garbage can!
A young girl like you,
how can you be so shameless?
Give it to me. It's mine.
Quite a young age, but not
using formal language.
You lived overseas, right?
Give it to me! I finally found it with
great difficulty.
Give it to me! It's mine!
What? Found from other people's
garbage cans, how can it be yours?
A beggar so early in the morning,
how disappointing.
Leave quickly! Get far away from here!
Give it to me!
I finally collected 10 of these and I
can soon exchange them for chicken.
You're going to take the last one away?
Let go.
Okay! I'll give it to you!
Omo! She seemed so weak,
and you lost like this?
Weak Miss? You go try it!
Looking into her eyes,
I almost peed my pants!
She's not a normal person.
Using this, I can eat chicken
with Dae Woong!
Oh, that person.
He really did come find me.
Don't even know to be scared when fighting
with a human. You really can bear it.
You're more powerful, you have everything.
You have a name, an address,
and even a credit card.
Ah, your name is Park Dong Ju.
Right now, it's Park Dong Ju.
Oh! You even have one of these.
Nowadays everybody has one.
We're not people, though.
We may be inspected at any time,
so you should fasten your seatbelt.
What?
We can't risk being investigated,
because we're not human.
What exactly are you?
I'm Park Dong Ju, also the President
of the veterinarian clinic.
Do you want to see where I live?
It filmed pretty well.
We've already inspected the
video camera carefully.
What does Director think about it?
Tomorrow, since there are some difficulties
with filming, can you come along?
Yes, I can do that.
Then, let's start tomorrow. Just drop by.
Then... that means I've been accepted?
Why, you don't want to?
How could I not?
I'll try hard! Thanks!
Hey, congratulations!
No, now it's the rising star of the
next generation, Star Cha!
Thanks.
Of course, even Director Kim was
accepted into a performing troupe.
That's right, in the future, this drama's
leading actor is celebrity Cha.
Of course, isn't it one of
Director Kim's films?
And then what?
Okay then, newcomer, go buy some drinks.
Do you want to die? Do you
even know who my father is?
Yes, Seon Nyeo, what do you want to eat?
I'll see and buy every single one for you.
Tonight is beef dinner.
I'm coming right now, Gu Mi Ho.
Is it possible that Mi Ho ran out again?
What's running out?
Oh, Noona!
Dae Woong, congratulations!
I heard that you've been accepted.
I knew you could do it.
Actually, I didn't really want
to come, but they called me.
Maybe because they saw the others, but
none of them had the same talent as me.
Ah, how great! My Dae Woong.
Noona, drink this.
Now that you've really became an actor,
you're not letting me touch you?
It's because of summer and sweat.
I'm afraid that you'll get dirty.
Drink something cold.
Tonight, let's go celebrate each
other and eat supper together.
Supper?
If today goes smoothly,
I'll buy beef for you.
Wait for me.
Okay.
What?
Other than me, is there someone else
you have to celebrate with first?
Oh... My grandpa!
My grandpa said that there's
something he needs to discuss.
Because he's getting older,
he's relying on his grandson more.
And I can also tell him this good news.
Well, since it's celebrating with
the family, then I'll just make way.
Noona, definitely next time.
We'll celebrate next time.
Wow, you're really living
just like a human!
How did you get here like this?
Not caring about human matters,
not making friendships,
not staying too long in any one place...
switching jobs and names constantly.
For how long?
A long, long time.
Compared to the time you've been
in the picture, even longer than that.
I have to be like you and live
in the human world.
Why don't you tell me what's
best for me to do?
But don't you want to merge with humans?
Isn't that why you came to live out here?
If you want to live like me, you can't have
any relationships with humans at all.
You can't become friends. You can't even
have a family or a loved one.
But...
I can still be together with humans.
No.
People who are living splendidly,
and you who live using the bead,
can't be together. Definitely not.
Living like me, and living at the
Three God's Pavilion, like you...
is completely different.
Why don't you just go back?
I wanted to live here.
I really... I really really
don't want to go back.
You're that unwilling?
Even if you die?
If you don't have to go back anymore,
are you willing to die?
There aren't many days left where
I still have to stay with Mi Ho.
She's about to leave soon.
Why?
She and I can't truly be together.
If I have to say why,
although I became very
good friends with her,
in the end I still feel that
we're not suitable.
What does that mean?
The worlds that we're living in
aren't the same.
Living...
Is Miss Mi Ho... rich?
If she's Gu... perhaps the family
makes these sort of things?
It can't be, otherwise Cha Dae Woong
wouldn't let her go like this.
She didn't give me a call. Seems
like she didn't get into trouble.
I wonder if there're still ribs or beef
tenderloin in the fridge at home?
That means you're going to be
an actor in that movie?
Didn't I say that already?
Didn't I tell you that I can do it?
Director Ban said that he
had his eye on you.
Aunt, how did you get acquainted
with Director Ban?
I mean,
it's because he's the director
of many famous action films.
Also, he's directing your
drama, so that's how I know.
Action?
Why?
It's nothing, it's nothing.
Right now, movies have brought
our family back to life.
After a few more days, I can come home.
I can come back, right Grandpa?
No problem, no problem.
This type of circumstance is called
returning into welcoming arms.
Come back together with that woman.
Grandpa, she...
We'll decide on something.
What?
Grandpa, is there still meat in the fridge?
Can I take some with me?
If you, in the body of a gumiho, can
collect a human's spirit when you die,
you can become a human.
Can become human?
If you want that, first...
you must have something that can
kill your gumiho body,
and also a person who is willing
to share their spirit with you.
You have to meet these two conditions.
Something that can kill me?
My blood can kill you.
This dagger can also kill you.
After drinking my blood, the process
is very slow. It's a very slow death.
You can kill me?
Your fox bead can absorb a human's spirit.
I know that.
Drinking my blood,
with the fox bead that has been
tainted with hundreds of people's spirits,
you will be able to turn into a person.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I remember a girl named Kil Dal
who looked like you.
Kil Dal wanted the same thing as you.
She once had the same wish as you.
Did she turn into a human?
The part where you need to die,
I can help with that.
But is there a human who could hold
your fox bead for you...
for 100 days?
Well, that...
Right now, the person beside
you called Cha Dae Woong,
will he help you?
Humans are untrustworthy.
So forget what I said just now and go back.
Go back to the place you came from.
Dying...
Is that like disappearing?
I just want to remain at his side.
Unni's role is a girl sideline defender,
why are you practicing martial arts
moves with us?
Regardless of why,
it's always good to learn.
You have your eyes on that
still-up-for-grabs female lead, right?
If Hae In Unni becomes the female lead,
then I can get your role!
That'd be great!
This is the director's enormous
and ambitious breakout!
When is the director coming back?
He should almost be done warming up.
Let's start practicing with this.
Wait a minute. I'll practice later.
Looks like she wants to practice
in front of the director.
I have a headache. It feels stuffy.
That woman is Real Action.
My Dream.
Oh, it's Director Ban.
Miss, excuse me, did you see me
a couple of nights ago?
There's definitely no mistake.
Wearing a white dress, and with long hair.
That person... is her?
Miss, have a chat with me.
Miss!
Real Action.
Ah, she's really fast.
A person like her... how is it possible?
When Mi Ho sees this still freshly
frozen beef, she'll jump for joy.
Oh, Noona!
Dae Woong, let's meet up.
I have something to ask you.
Right now?
You're at your grandpa's house, right?
I'll come over immediately.
You're coming over?
It's too inconvenient.
It's inconvenient for me
to go out right now.
Really?
Why?
Are you in the middle of supper
with your grandpa?
Yes, we're just preparing to eat.
And it's inconvenient to go out.
When it's nighttime I'll come find you.
I'll see you then.
No need, let's just meet now.
I'm here.
What?
Noona...
Is this place your grandpa's house?
What is that?
Ah, you were planning on holding a
celebration supper with your girlfriend?
Why was that person chasing me?
He sounds very important to Dae Woong.
Good thing I didn't get discovered.
Oh, Dae Woong told me to call him
if something happened.
Ahjumma! Can I use your phone?
Don't call for too long.
Dae Woong,
I know very well that you
don't think of her that way,
but I still feel that I'm
being dragged down.
About her always being intertwined
with you, and not letting go,
I tried to be understanding.
But I really can't take it anymore.
Noona, I owe her a huge debt.
So I promised her that I'd be together
with her for a short period of time.
Also, there aren't many days left.
Dae Woong...
You...
like me, right?
Did I misunderstand?
No, you didn't.
These kinds of words,
I've always longed for the day when you'd
officially say them to me of your own will.
I already thought of an answer.
But seeing you recently,
I started to question whether
I should believe you.
I don't know if my answer
is still the correct one.
Don't make me continue to waver like this.
Break up cleanly with her.
And then hold onto me.
If you keep putting it off,
I won't continue to wait for you.
Then your answer will be gone.
He even brought back meat.
Seems like things went smoothly,
he didn't mess it up.
Where did Dae Woong go?
Ah, it'll definitely be delicious.
No, I have to endure it.
I have to wait to eat it together with
Dae Woong once he gets back.
Where did he go?
I even called him and left a
message a while ago.
Did he not hear it?
One new message.
Dae Woong,
that director was chasing me just
now, but I ran away from him.
Oh, also,
I have an extremely important
thing to ask you today.
If I were to remain here forever,
would you be okay with it?
If you're okay with that,
I have a method which will
allow me to stay here forever.
I'll wait for you.
Dae Woong, come back quickly as
soon as you've bought the meat!
Oh! It's Dae Woong's scent!
Dae Woong!
Why are you here?
Are you feeling uncomfortable somewhere?
It's Mi Ho.
Mi Ho, I drank liquor.
Ah, you really drank a lot.
The moon has risen already.
Why don't you spread out all your tails?
Let's play hoy hoy, okay?
Woong...
Hoy hoy.
Mi Ho.
You remember the time you agreed
to be friends with me?
Then,
can you do me a favor?
What favor?
Mi Ho,
I'm begging you...
disappear, okay?
I'm begging you, Mi Ho.
I really feel like I'm about to die.
So I'm begging you,
disappear from my sight.
Leave now.
Dae Woong...
Actually, you have already fully recovered.
I won't let you suffer.
I'm leaving.
Ah, my stomach hurts.
When did I get back?
Mi Ho!
Was it you who put me on the bed?
Mi Ho, where are you?
Mi Ho!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: Tiggerlily93
Spot Translators: serendipity, munchinghippo, SeMe
Timer: hitomi83
Editor/QC: langdon813
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Dae Woong said that he's friends with me.
Looks like because I'm a gumiho,
he still doesn't like me.
Gu Mi Ho has finally left my side!
This day has finally arrived.
Before she changes her mind and comes back,
I have to hide myself.
If you drink the contents in the red bottle,
It means that you've chosen to
become human and stay here.
If you drink the contents
in the blue bottle,
You will return to the Three Gods Pavilion.
But why does it feel so empty?
Like I've lost something?
Apart from the bead, did she take
something else from my body?
Do you feel sad?
How could I be sad?
Before I would have been happy to die.
My friend, Gu Mi Ho,
is a scary gumiho.
Dae Woong won't ever come here again, right?
Don't tell Cha Dae Woong that
you're going to become human.
You're only taking in my bead
with the thought...
of being together with me?
A gumiho became human.
I was going crazy!
Although I needed the bead, how
could I be Gu Mi Ho's boyfriend?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com