Gu Yiye, you were wounded
during the training?
I just chipped my skin. It's all right now.
[Carry every red flag]
Commander Lu, may I ask you a question?
If we want to damage the enemy's equipment,
and fire special bullets
that burn through shells
we must shorten the twist rate of rifling.
But once it's shortened,
the precision of firing ordinary bullets
will decline.
When the twist rate is shortened,
the spinning of bullets will be reduced
and the precision will decline by 25%.
Is there any chance
we can produce a gun with two twist rates
that can shoot at different targets?
Sorry, it's a silly question.
It will put severe stress
on logistic work.
Gains cannot make up for losses.
Military engineering is systematic.
Most of the time,
we have to abandon and sacrifice something.
With the same cost,
shall we produce an excellent weapon
or ten good weapons?
As a soldier,
you're too inexperienced to understand.
But if one day,
you can consider
as a coordinator,
you'll understand more.
Warfare is a science.
To win a war,
we don't need the best weapons,
but the most suitable ones.
All unsuitable ones
will be eliminated.
However,
a strategic and far-sighted troop
will collect
the most beautiful flowers
as its storage for various possibilities
and directions for exploration.
Once the situation changes,
they will have the chance
to bloom in other forms.
Thank you for your encouragement.
Well,
it's not the time to celebrate yet.
No one knows
how long they will be stored.
Many people were impatient, so they left.
I will not leave.
It's getting late.
Go back to your dorm.
Wait.
When I passed by division headquarters,
the female soldier Jiang Nanzheng
asked me to bring it to you.
Thank you.
[Monthly Publication of Accounts]
You've got yours.
Let me have a look. Don't be stingy.
No.
Let me have a look.
Stop. Stop.
I'll give it to you.
Why do you have two packs?
The other one is for Niu.
For him?
Why?
Don't you remember you bought perfume for him
because of his stinking feet?
Now, everybody in our regiment
knows he has stinking feet.
The socks she bought
are too thin. They don't fit Niu.
I'd like to keep them.
I'll exchange my army socks for them.
It's a deal between you and Niu.
I don't care.
But it's the kindness of Jiang.
You can't hide it.
Who would do that?
I'll go tell Niu later.
Hey, you two.
The lights have been off for a long while.
Come back for sleep!
[Chloromycetin Eyedrop]
Niu.
What?
Do you need socks?
Why?
Someone bought some socks for you.
Now that you have such stinking feet,
don't wear socks.
Give them to me.
Let's discuss it tomorrow morning.
No. Let's do it now.
Do you want the socks?
Why do I not?
They're good socks.
Come on.
I'll exchange my rubber shoes for them.
Give the socks to me.
Rubber shoes... Much more practical.
Are you sure?
Yes, yes. It's a deal.
Get back to sleep.
Don't bother me anymore.
There's too much training to take.
I've bought some socks for you.
One pack for Gao Liang
and one pack for Niu Mancang.
Comrades-in-arms should help each other.
I begged the doctor several times
before he gave me the eye drop.
It has a special effect
for soothing tired eyes.
Hope you'll do a good job
in the shooting practice.
Come on.
Left, right, left.
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
One, two, three, four.
Hold them for me.
Commander.
The battalion commander
is waiting for you in the company.
Okay.
I'm coming.
What book of martial arts was he reading?
Eighteen moves of the Black Dragon?
[Eighteen moves of the Black Dragon]
It's the lost martial arts.
[Start 1 The Claws of the Azure Dragon (Empty-handed Punch)]
[2 Looking in the Mirror (Sweep Kick)
3 Wicked Turning (Buttock)]
[4 Under-arm Attack (Forward Punch)
5 Kick and Chokehold]
Who's making noises here
instead of having an afternoon nap?
If you don't want to sleep, go running!
[Carry every red flag]
Tactical competition between recruits
and elder soldiers
now starts!
Next.
Get set!
Recruits are watching. What are you doing?
Next!
[Strict training]
Two minutes and forty-eight seconds.
Two minutes and fifty seconds.
Two minutes and fifty-eight seconds.
Next!
Get set!
Good! Get faster!
One minute and forty-eight seconds!
Next.
Report. I'm Gu Yiye.
Sergeant, the balance, please.
Next.
I first use the balance to find out bullets
with average ammunition weight
to guarantee the uniformity of bullets.
Bullets are different.
- I only picked out the bullets
- Next.
with better accuracy.
Next.
There's a production line
for prototyped guns of the Soviet Union,
manufacturing high-precision bullets.
Why must they make new bullets
instead of using the existing ones?
It is because
bullets are different.
Take up your rifles!
Besides screening the bullets,
there's another skill.
I load the rifle by hand
- in case the bullets
- Ready to shoot.
get stuck by the clip
or get scratched in the chamber throat.
It can ensure the accuracy of the bullet
during the flight.
What's Gu Yiye doing?
If he were in a real war,
would his enemies let him waste the time?
The shooting is over. Inspect your rifles.
All right.
I won't read the result.
Go and count it by yourselves.
Remember, tonight
recruits will compete with elder soldiers.
Gu got two rings better than me.
How come even you got one ring better?
What do you mean even?
Why can't I be better than you?
It was just your luck.
I did a better job than you,
not only because of my skills.
It was just a shooting competition.
You used tricks.
Why didn't you shoot like us?
I only compete with my own limits.
What do you mean?
I'm not good enough to be your opponent?
We don't win a real victory
unless we compete with ourselves.
Another question.
Think about it.
Even if I defeat you,
will Jiang Nanzheng still think
you're better than me?
Boring.
Attention!
Eyes right.
Eyes front.
Extra competition for tonight.
Firing practice.
The result will count.
You'll compete with elder soldiers.
Report.
We've never practiced night shooting.
But I'm not scared.
The competition should be flexible.
We'll test what you haven't practiced.
In the daytime, think about
how to shoot at night.
In peace,
think about how to shoot in a war.
Gao Liang and Gu Yiye
are the most hard-working recruits
during the training.
But they use quite different ways.
Let me put it this way.
One uses strength
while the other uses knacks.
Oh, you realized that?
[Company]
Gu Yiye
does scientific training.
Gao Liang
focuses on hard work.
So what do you think?
Which one is right
or which one is more effective?
Well,
victory is my only standard.
As long as a man can win,
I only care for the result,
not the process.
A commander
should care about the process,
as well as the result.
Division commander.
Qin Hanyong,
the division commander thinks highly of you.
During his inspection this time,
he especially comes here to see you.
I don't want to visit him.
But I have to.
He rubbed my back
and prepared water for my footbath.
He keeps speaking ill of me.
Everyone in the division knows
how many scars I have on my back
and how many corns I have on my feet.
Division commander, please sit down.
No. No. I've got something else to attend to.
Your colonel told me
that you were busy with the training.
How's the training going?
Be brief.
And I'm leaving after you finish.
Your regiment is quite stingy.
You only offered noodles and I'm not full.
I noticed
that Gao Liang has been training hard.
He doesn't even stop in the dorm.
He's still standing upside down.
He's making up by hard work.
He does more than hard training.
You know what?
He even reads secretly in his quilt.
Come on.
I sleep next to him and I'm certainly award.
He keeps whispering in his quilt.
I can't even fall asleep.
[It's everybody's duty to save water]
I sleep on your top bunk
but why do I not know that?
Are you sleepless, Jiang?
Shall we go running for 20 laps?
I'm not going. Go with Gu Yiye.
It's your standard.
I've already increased my running standard
to 30 kilometers.
Look.
With weights!
Gu Yiye,
no wonder you win first place in every item.
You're not training, but risking your life.
Jiang, let's have a private training
and work hard tonight.
No one shall go out tonight.
[It's everybody's duty to save water]
Cadres of the regiment are here.
Why?
When I came out of the company,
I saw our colonel
go there with the division commander.
Your company is the backward company in the division.
Right?
Right.
Some of my soldiers are unruly.
Some of them are disobedient, too.
But there are soldiers with potential.
For example?
Report.
I'm Gu Yiye from the Ninth Squad,
the Ninth Company.
I ask to see the division commander.
Qin Hanyong,
what's going on?
Gu Yiye, what are you doing?
Can't you see
we're in the middle of something?
I have something
to report to the division commander.
Gu Yiye, go back first.
Why do you try to stop him?
Let him in. Come on.
Come on in.
What do you want me for?
For your information,
before I met you,
I've heard about your heroic deeds.
I really admired you.
I first visited you
because of the withdrawal.
But I failed to see you.
Here I apply
to be transferred
to Night Tiger Company of Regiment 700.
Please approve.
What's your name again?
I didn't hear it clearly.
Gu Yiye.
What a special way to ask for a transfer.
Do you know what sort of company
Night Tiger Company is?
I do.
It's an ace troop of Troop A.
As early as there was the Red Army,
Night Tiger Company was
a famous model company.
They have won
countless battles.
I joined the army for this company.
I don't want to stay in Regiment 720.
Gu Yiye!
Why do you yell at him?
Let him finish.
A lot of soldiers
want to join Night Tiger Company.
Why do you think
I should transfer you?
I was born in a military family.
I love the army.
I have common military knowledge.
I have good military accomplishments, too.
Speaking of the training,
I'm No.1 in integrated training
in our platoon
and No.1 in shooting of the company.
When we have some more items,
I'll do as well as now.
How's your shooting?
48 rings.
When I'm not in a good condition.
When I am,
I can hit all the bull's-eyes.
You sound arrogant.
You're daring, too.
You knew I was here
and then you came to block me?
There are very few chances
in a grass-root company.
I just want to seize the chance.
Honestly,
I like the way you're doing this.
I hate it a little bit, either.
But now that you applied,
I have to reply.
Chan Dashan.
See?
This is an unnoticed talent of yours.
He's more ambitious than you.
You'll have a shooting tonight?
Yes, chief.
Do the best you can do.
I don't decide
how far you can go.
It depends on you.
Yes.
Division commander,
I have another request.
You're greedy. Speak.
I want to confirm something.
Is the bullet in your body
a 9mm bullet
from Parabellum Pistol?
Come on, boy.
Don't try to get in good with me.
I won't tell you until you finish shooting.
Yes.
Chen Dashan,
I'll forgive you
for the noodles.
Go arrange it.
I'm going to watch their shooting tonight.
Yes.
Wait.
Don't tell them in advance.
By the way,
ask Gao Liang
to take part, too.
Yes.
Subject, night shooting.
How can we shoot when we can't see anything?
Unit,
in squads.
- Isn't it supposed to be a night shooting?
- Shoot at fixed targets.
It's too bright to see anything.
They're making it more difficult.
Close your eyes.
The blaze will cause visual errors.
If you get spots in your eyes,
there'll be trouble.
Participants
shall determine the shooting target
within ten seconds
after the light beams
begin to move.
When the light beams fade away,
participants shall shoot
within ten seconds.
Remember.
Don't look at the light beams.
When they move,
cover your eyes with your hand
and look through your fingers.
What did you say? Louder. I...
On your marks.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start!
Stop shooting.
Inspect your rifles.
Target one, Gao Liang,
45 rings.
Target two, Zhao Hongliu,
18 rings.
Target three, Niu Mancang,
36 rings.
Target four, Lin Beihai,
42 rings.
Target five, Jiang Weixing,
39 rings.
Target six, Gu Yiye,
47 rings.
Today, the division commander
requested to watch your night shooting.
You haven't practiced it before.
Just try your best.
You should relax.
Don't be stressed out.
It's okay if you don't do a good job.
It won't be recorded
in your daily performance.
Let me emphasize one thing.
Your performance
will be directly related
to the honor of our regiment.
I hope
you'll do a good job.
Remain calm
and try
to shoot better than we expect.
Report!
Speak.
I'm not nervous!
The more stress I'm under,
the better I'll do!
I'll shoot exceedingly well!
Division commander,
how about not watching the Ninth Company?
Let me transfer several soldiers
from Lu Pingfan's First Company to perform for you.
They start from high bases,
and work very hard.
They will definitely
get in.
Your model company?
Knock it off.
I also started from the battalion,
and worked all my way to this position.
I know it too well.
Units only show their pacesetters to leaders.
I want to see the ninth company.
Am I not allowed?
Of course not.
Then cut the nonsense. Let them shoot by turn.
[Learn to fight wars from the range]
Gao.
The light was too bright.
Now,
I can't see anything.
If you can't see anything,
neither can they.
It's too dark to see anything.
Before hearing the scoring,
we can only rely on our ears.
I thought we are going to practice with the old soldiers.
Where is sergeant Mao?
Target six,
prepare to shoot.
It really feels like the last few minutes
before the rifle squad's ambush.
Sir,
it seems that
you even enjoy fighting battles more than drinking.
Report! Shooting is completed!
-That was quick.
-Target seven.
-A “hot head”.
-Prepare to shoot.
All at once.
Quick and neat.
He shot too fast.
That doesn't sound good to me.
Such fast shooting may work during the day.
But in such a night, there's no time for aiming,
unless he can see things in the dark.
You mentioned the first company, right?
Yes.
Bring them, wait for orders.
Yes!
Target eight, prepare to shoot.
[Learn to fight wars from the range]
This shooting sounds good.
Sir, I don't quite understand.
His shooting speed is not even.
Why is he better than the previous one?
Normally, aiming, shooing,
back-moving, resetting and shooting again,
the more consistent of these actions
-the more accurate you shoot, right?
-Target five.
Prepare to shoot.
Actually, as an experienced shooter,
you'll notice that
the first one or two bullets
have different trajectories.
Because when the first bullet is shot,
the barrel is still cold.
That is the cold gun accuracy.
Therefore,
the aiming and resetting intervals
of the first two bullets
is different.
Sweet mother of God.
You must have shot numerous bullets, sir.
Left, right, left.
Sir, the first company is here.
One, two, three, four.
After the ninth company finishes, let them start.
Yes.
Halt!
Fall in!
Report your score.
Target five, Niu Mancang.
Ten shots, six hits.
Target six, Gao Liang.
Ten shots, seven hits.
Target seven, Zhao Hongliu
Ten shots, four hits.
Target eight, Gu Yiye.
Ten shots, eight hits.
Did you really get so many hits, Gao?
Did you get it wrong?
Maybe you just got lucky.
Nonsense,
I got sharp eyes,
alright?
Gao Liang,
it's perfectly normal for Gu Yiye to score high.
He's just playing his normal role.
But you really outdid yourself.
Don't talk nonsense.
Why can't I score high?
[Strict requirements]
You are…
Good to see you again.
Si…sir!
You are target six, right?
Yes.
Your shooting speed was very fast.
Don't you need to aim?
Sir,
I was a miner,
used to work in the dark.
so I'm used to it.
See?
That's a good lesson for us.
Soldiers are not born good,
they need practice.
We have good soldiers,
but also bad ones,
you know?
You are target eight, right?
Yes.
Pretty good.
Tell your colonel,
how can you see things clearly in the dark?
Sir, I…
Just say it.
Yes.
It's dark in the night,
so you can't stare at the target with the center of your eyes.
The wider your eyes open,
the fuzzier the target is.
Retina consists of rod cells
and pyramidal cells.
Pyramidal cells
are concentrated in the middle of eyes,
mainly used for the day.
While rod cells
are distributed around eyes,
and are photosensitive,
mainly used for the night.
Gao Liang,
you and Gu Yiye will definitely get in.
Don't be so sure.
Why would we work so hard?
Gao has eyes of the owl.
Gu…
Gu, what's that thing you were talking about?
I have no idea,
don't understand a word.
You see, the rest of us
compete with each other.
But Gu, he can only compete with himself.
So unfair.
Unfair.
That's the way it is.
Ever since childhood,
there's always someone better than you,
and stronger than you.
Even if you try your best
to surpass him,
- Halt!
- But in the end,
- Eyes right!
- You are still behind him.
Eyes front!
The first company is here.
Division commander.
Where's Sergeant Mao?
Regiment 720, first company, first squad
is ready for shooting.
Please advise!
Commander Lu Pingfan.
Prepare to shoot.
Yes!
[Learn to fight wars from the range]
Rise.
[Strict requirements]
Report your score.
Target one, ten shots, nine hits.
Target two, ten shots, ten hits.
Target three, ten shots, eight hits.
Target four, ten shots, nine hits.
Target five, ten shots, nine hits.
Target six, ten shots, ten hits.
How many bullets have they shot?
[Strict requirements]
It looks like
you still need more practice.
You should know that
you are not qualified for the Night Tiger Company.
What's more,
the bullet in my body
is the 9mm Parabellum,
just as your guess.
Come on.
You use the same gun,
aim at the same target,
both are normal people,
besides,
you work very hard,
and you can see clearly in the dark.
Yet,
your score is just mediocre,
can't compare with Gu Yiye,
let alone
the pacesetters in the first company.
Feel frustrated, right?
Don't just stand there, sit down.
Yes.
Tonight,
though you have shown us that
you can see clearly in the dark.
But your daily practice
is not clever enough.
Just like farm works,
you can't just use brute force,
you see?
If you want to be the best of the best,
you have to find your own strength.
Use your brain.
How can I use my brain?
Unlike Gu Yiye, I don't have a good father.
He already knows everything when he joins the army.
But I have to learn everything from the beginning.
Yes,
I understand.
Sometimes, fate is not fair.
But in the end, it will be fair.
What we need to do,
is to work extra hard.
You see,
there are three roads
in front of you.
First,
you can stay put, do nothing.
At any time, in any community,
this kind of people is in majority.
Second,
keep using your brute power,
keep practicing,
not afraid of hard work.
Until one day, you can't continue anymore.
You get tired,
and go back to the first road.
You'll never surpass
Gu Yiye with his good talents given by his father.
Neither will you surpass
all those pacesetters
with every resource in their hands.
Well,
what about the last road?
Compete with yourself,
and every competitor
that you can't see.
Never stop.
Defeat them, beat them.
Leave them far behind you.
What are you writing?
I think your points are very good.
I want to write them down,
and learn from them.
That's a good habit, keep on to it.
Practice hard, and work hard.
[Dormitory]
Bros,
I heard that you got beat by the first company.
Have some sense of group honor, will you?
Our company is defeated by the first company, alright?
Just go take the bath.
Come on.
I'm gone take a bath.
Tomorrow is another day.
Hurry up, you guys.
The water will run out soon.
Just leave him alone.
It looks like
you still need more practice.
You should know that
you are not qualified for the Night Tiger Company.
Section Chief,
I really like the army,
I like being here.
It's warm and lively here.
The army makes me
feel like home.
It's just that…there are too many rules.
I can't get them straight.
So I'm always in trouble.
I know that you don't like me.
Nonsense.
Let me tell you this.
When you join the army,
it looks like you are all the same,
but,
you are all very different.
If you think of the military service
as a tower.
Gu Yiye is already on the second floor
or even the third floor
when he joined the army.
While those on the first floor
need to work harder,
and practice harder
to get to the upper floors.
What can I do? I'm on the first floor.
No, you are not.
You are in the basement.
People like you,
most of them
have little talents,
and were born in a poor family.
Just like someone
who's lax in discipline
and makes trouble everywhere he goes.
You see, for the army that takes disciplines seriously,
people like this is the worst kind,
habit like this is the worst kind.
This kind of people will make mistakes.
Therefore,
if you want to change your fate,
you'll have to get rid of your bad habits.
Everyone needs to grow up,
and discipline himself.
Yes.
You can't do whatever you want.
Oh, no.
My waist starts to hurt.
Come on, sir.
Come on, get up here.
- What are you doing?
- I'll carry you.
You'll carry me?
No need.
It's okay.
I've heard about it.
In the previous battle,
you got shot and a shrapnel was stuck in your waist.
So every cloudy and rainy day, your waist hurts.
It's alright, just get up here.
Come on.
No, no, no.
Stand up.
Rise!
I'll walk by myself.
The army
has its own rules.
There's no military rank
on our uniforms.
That's very rare
all over the world.
This is because we need to remember
that officers and soldiers are equal.
Do you understand?
Yes.
There are four pockets on the officer's uniform,
but only two on the soldier's uniform.
The extra two pockets
represent for responsibility.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You want to carry me.
If we were on the battleground, you can carry me.
But now you can't.
That's discipline.
For the next minute,
I'm not your section Chief,
and you are not a recruit.
From the bottom of my heart,
between you and Gu Yiye,
if I have to choose one to stay,
I'll choose you.
Because he's too excellent,
he has so many chances.
But you,
you need this place.
Do you understand?
Alright,
welcome,
comrade Gao Liang.
-Keep it up.
-Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Bro, I have this strange feeling.
From militaries
like Lu Pingfan,
Qin Hanyong, and Song Jianshe,
I see you.
Sometimes,
I feel like they are you.
They make me feel the warmth of family,
lead me out of confusion
and loneliness.
[Public Bath]
To hell with your advanced company.
Man to man, I dare you!
Gao!
Why such a hurry?
Where are you rushing to?
Gao.
The first company insulted us.
They called us rubbish.
So we got into a fight with them in the bathhouse.
Got into a fight?
Come on.
Stop it!
Save your energy for the practice!
Eighteen moves of the Black Dragon!
The palm of the Azure Dragon!
Tripping over by the Jade Dragon!
The Dragon shows!
This is outrageous!
How dare you start the fight?
You are really out of control!
You sure know how to make me proud, huh?
Qin Hanyong.
The ninth company of yours
wants to be the backward company forever, right?
Not so good at practice, but excellent in picking up fights!
And you, Lu Pingfan.
Does your advanced company
have to take shower first?
Is your advanced company
the father of the backward company?
Dashan,
how about letting them go back first,
and deal with the soldiers?
Song Jianshe.
Here.
Find out exactly what happened.
Who started this fight,
who stirred up the trouble.
Find it out!
Find some negative examples
and punish them hard!
Unbelievable!
Just a few new recruits,
are they going to ruin the whole Regiment 720?
Yes.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Wait for your punishment!
Company Commander already knew about this.
He will definitely punish you hard!
You look like you're not convinced.
Niu,
why did you start fighting?
Because of the bathwater.
What…just because of the bathwater?
And started a fight?