Hinatsuru!
I'm sorry, Lord Tengen.
It's okay. Just stop talking.
I realized that
Warabihime Oiran is a demon,
but she was suspicious of me, too.
I drank some poison,
so I could get out of the brothel.
However, Warabihime Oiran gave me this obi
to observe and kill me
if something happens.
That's why I couldn't contact you.
Lord Tengen, don't mind me, just go.
You must have heard the sound a while ago.
The demon is going on a rampage.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
I'm very sorry for not being of any use.
You don't have to do anything anymore.
Once the antidote takes effect,
get out of Yoshiwara.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The battle has begun.
Where is it?
Search for their presence.
It's here. Underground.
I hear the sound of fighting.
The reverberations sound very clear.
There's something in here.
Sound Breathing,
First Form: Roar!
UPPER RANK SIX
Those bugs are noisy.
What was that sound? What are they doing?
Where is it coming from?
Ogimoto House, huh?
And Hinatsuru has escaped?
How many of you came here? Four hunters?
I won't tell.
If you tell me the truth,
I will let you live.
We just clashed a little,
and your sword is already chipped.
Whoever forged that sword
must be a crappy swordsmith.
You're wrong!
The one who forged this
is an amazing person!
He's a skilled swordsmith!
Then why is it chipped, you fool?
You're beginning to rattle
all over the place.
Since you pissed me off,
I'll kill you with my next blow.
It's chipped because of its user.
It's my fault.
I…
As I thought, I…
I really can't master Water Breathing.
I'm not suited to be
a Water Breathing user.
The users must be like
Sir Urokodaki or Tomioka.
In my case,
Hinokami Kagura is inevitably stronger
in terms of powerful strikes.
It's compatible with my body.
But…
Take it easy, you idiot!
That won't make this a training!
Hinokami Kagura:
Dance!
Clear Blue--
Tanjiro!
Are you hurt, Tanjiro?
Are you hungry?
Stupid!
-You stupid boar!
-It was so powerful that…
-I couldn't use it consecutively.
-Hold on! I'll call Shinobu.
It's different now.
I should be able to do it.
No. I have to do it!
That's why I've trained.
Don't lose.
Ablaze…
Be ablaze. Set it ablaze.
Set your heart ablaze!
Hinokami Kagura:
Raging Sun!
He changed his style.
It's sharper than before.
What is this sound?
What an unpleasant sound.
Breathing sound?
Flame Dance!
Flame Dance is a two-strike combo.
If she dodged,
I still have the second strike.
This is nothing.
Is this…
all you've got?
Where is he?
Hinokami Kagura: Fake Rainbow.
It's an opening! An opening thread!
I can do this!
Hinokami Kagura: Fire Wheel!
You're so slow, I even have time to yawn.
Take a safe landing!
Safe landing…
It's the repercussions of doing
Hinokami Kagura techniques in a row.
My muscles are stiff
from the built-up fatigue.
So you're still alive.
Calm down. I need to take a steady breath.
Recover!
Hurry!
Do a recovery breathing!
Her obi is like a tough blade.
Even though I see the opening threads,
they immediately break.
My attacks are too slow.
Raise the temperature!
Raise the temperature more!
I'll tell Miss Shinobu
that your fever isn't going down.
Kiyo, I beg you. Please keep it a secret.
I'll be fine.
But…
I'm healthy.
I'm fine. I'm totally okay.
Look at this thermometer.
It's 38 degrees.
It's the same as yesterday
and the day before it.
It hasn't changed this whole time.
The fact that you continue
to have this fever is abnormal.
I don't know what to do myself.
It has to be Miss Shinobu.
To be honest,
I'm actually fine when I have this fever.
With this, I can use
Hinokami Kagura techniques consecutively.
I might get even stronger.
Could you please hold off
on telling Shinobu a little longer?
Please, just a little longer.
I understand.
But just a little longer.
I can feel my body temperature rising.
I can fight an Upper Rank demon.
He's more persistent than I thought.
This is interesting.
I can do it!
Hinokami Kagura is working against her.
No. It's not enough.
I have to win!
I have to use all my strength
and win for sure!
To protect someone.
To protect lives.
I won't let unjust fate rob something
from me ever again.
I won't let anyone…
go through the same sadness as we did.
The uglies are always ugly,
no matter how hard they try.
A LITTLE WHILE AGO
BACK AT THE OGIMOTO HOUSE
What happened?
Monster!
There's a monster!
Just do your work.
A boar monster is breaking
the ceiling and the floor!
-What?
-There's no such thing.
Then come--
This demon presence makes me tingle.
Here it is.
I found it!
I found the hole leading
to the demon's lair!
Brace yourself!
Only my head can get in.
How naive.
Nothing can withstand the Great Inosuke.
I'm the man who can dislodge
every joint in his body.
In other words, I can go anywhere
as long as my head can get in.
Pig assault! Nobody can stop me.
This is so far deep.
This isn't an animal trail.
It must be a demon.
There's a demon in here!
What is this place?
A human-patterned cloth?
What's with all of this?
No. This sensation…
These are living humans.
So the demon trapped humans
within a woman's bellyband.
Then it can eat them whenever it likes.
What a vore.
What's this guy doing here?
And what are you doing here?
You've entered my food storehouse.
Dirty.
So dirty.
You are dirty, stinky little shit!
What's with this worm? It's so creepy!
You little shit!
Keep squirming all over the place!
You're creeping me out, damned obi worm!
Your movement is so slow!
Looks like you got greedy
and captured too many humans.
Some attacks of a big, fat worm…
are not going to hit the Great Inosuke!
Get your ass up and come at me again!
He's cautiously avoiding the humans
when he cuts.
Though I went to the trouble
of preserving such fresh food…
His instincts are sharp.
Especially his ability
to feel bloodlust is abnormal.
No matter which direction I attack from,
he can sense and evade them.
I never expected a demon hunter
to enter my food storehouse.
What should I do?
Capture him alive.
UPPER RANK
That's the guy who got in
when you captured Makio.
He was beautiful.
You can kill all the preserved humans
except the ten prettiest ones.
Although it may be harder to catch him
alive rather than to just kill him.
Eat some humans there
and strengthen your own power.
Take this!
I can't cut it?
Is it because of its wriggling?
Beast Breathing, Sixth Fang:
Palisade Bite!
There's no point in cutting me.
I'm not the main body after all.
But more importantly, are you sure
it's okay to neglect the girls you saved?
I can regain the strength I lost
from getting hit by you in no time.
Crap! I have to fight
while protecting people!
Shit! I won't make it!
You damned obi worm!
Calling it "obi worm"
is a good way of putting it!
That thing is really disgusting!
You're right!
I'm going to tell Lord Tengen!
We'll back you up,
so good luck there, Boar Head!
Who the hell are you?
We're Uzui's wives!
Since I can't fight very well…
don't expect too much from me!
Suma, don't be a wimp!
But…
You know that
I'm a worthless loser, right?
I got captured right away.
I can't protect all these captured people!
I'm probably going to die first!
That's right. You get it.
Who should I eat first?
That bastard is not the main body?
If that's true, this is bad.
This fight is never going to end.
Thunder Breathing,
First Form:
Thunderclap and Flash, Sixfold.
You'd better be sleeping forever, man.
THEY CARRIED ZENITSU'S SWORD
Is that kid a Corps member, too?
Why is that kid dressed so ridiculously?
I have no idea!
-Hey, come on!
-What's with that guy?
-Get ready, man!
-That was so quick.
But more importantly,
were there two noises just now?
There were two thunder-like sounds.
One was from this guy.
And one more was from above!
Wind is blowing? Was a tunnel opened up?
How did someone manage to dig a hole
from above ground?
What was that?
There's someone.
Someone's entering this place.
DESTROYER OF DEMONS
This presence…
is of a Hashira!
Lord Tengen…
SLAYER
Makio. Suma.
Sorry for being late.
I'm relieved you two are safe.
It wasn't like this before.
We didn't mind dying
because that's what we were taught.
Because we're ninjas.
Especially the kunoichi,
who is inferior to a male ninja
in terms of strength.
Putting our lives on the line
was the least we could do.
You must only think about your own lives.
Whatever else you leave behind,
you must come back to my place first.
Your lives are more important
than a mission.
I know that what I'm saying
doesn't make sense in this line of work.
But I'll allow it.
I'll decide a clear,
flamboyant life priority.
First, you three.
Then, respectable people.
Lastly, myself.
As demon hunters,
we naturally protect the ordinary people
who are living a plain life.
But frankly, you are precious to me.
So don't die.
Is it okay to say that?
If we put our lives on priority,
we can't do our jobs properly.
Is it really okay?
Why not?
Lord Tengen said he's okay with it.
Not wanting to die
and choosing to live aren't bad.
As long as you don't mind,
that's all that matters.
I'm sure of it.
You're right.
Looks like you did
some flamboyant work here.
I expect nothing less from my wives.
All right!
From now on,
things are going to get really flamboyant!
-Nin-nin!
I can't believe that
Sound Hashira has three wives.
Why don't you go for it too, Zenitsu?
What? Can I?
-Maybe I'll go for Yoshiko, Sanae, and--
-I'm telling Nezuko.
Tanjiro!
It's time for the Taisho-era secret.
Uzui's family is polygamous.
When you turn 15, the head of the family
chooses 3 wives based on compatibility.
But I've heard
that Suma volunteered herself.
Maybe I'll become a ninja too.
Then you'll be training to be
a ninja starting today.
What?
No!
Next, episode 6, "Overlapping Memories."
TO BE CONTINUED