Since you pissed me off,
I'll kill you with my next blow.
Hinokami Kagura:
Raging Sun!
Flame Dance!
This is nothing.
Is this…
all you've got?
Where is he?
Hinokami Kagura: Fake Rainbow.
I can do this!
Hinokami Kagura: Fire Wheel!
Do a recovery breathing!
I can fight an Upper Rank demon.
Damn ugly, you're pissing me off!
What's happening?
The obi's entering her body.
No.
The parts she detached before
are coming back?
UPPER RANK SIX
Don't be afraid. Take a steady breath.
Now!
I was right.
She disappeared?
A Hashira…
A Hashira came.
Good.
My Lord will be pleased.
Her appearance has changed.
What a sinister smell.
It makes my throat feel numb and painful.
She's more powerful than before.
Wait. Is Uzui with Inosuke and Zenitsu?
If so, I'm relieved.
You guys are so noisy!
What's with that sword?
Don't quarrel in front of someone's door!
What kind of harassment is this?
Crap! We made a ruckus.
In this district,
everyone, including the customers,
must obey the rules!
We don't want people like you in here!
Get out of this district!
Look who's noisy now.
This is bad.
No! Get away from here!
Please step back!
Don't leave the building!
Hiro! No!
Stay calm.
You will be okay.
Bind your arm with a cord.
Wait.
I won't forgive you
after you have done all of this.
Jeez. You're still talking?
I've had enough of your ugliness.
Because hideous humans
don't deserve to live.
Get on with it and rot in death.
Hiro!
Please, someone, help us!
Don't come out, everyone!
It's dangerous! Go hide!
Kamado, I'm sorry for what I did.
Thank you for crying over Kyojuro.
I heard you've been exchanging letters
with Senjuro these past four months.
He's got a lot better.
I'm ashamed that our first meeting
turned out like that.
I was devastated by my own incompetence
when my beloved wife died of illness.
I went drinking and cowering.
What an unbelievable fool I am.
Unlike me, Kyojuro was an amazing son.
Even after I gave up on teaching him,
he read the manual of Flame Breathing,
trained himself, and became a Hashira.
With only three volumes of books.
It must be the traits from Ruka,
his mother.
Both Kyojuro and Senjuro
are wonderful sons.
And for you, Kamado,
you have more amazing power.
They say the chosen users
of the Sun Breathing
are born with a red birthmark
on their forehead, just like you.
So I'm sure, you're…
You're wrong, Mr. Shinjuro.
This isn't a birthmark.
Originally, this is a burn scar I got
when I covered my brother
after he knocked over the brazier.
It got wounded even more
during the Final Selection,
and that's how it ended up like this.
My father was born
with a thin birthmark on his forehead.
But not me.
I'm sure I'm not one of the chosen users.
Still…
But still…
Even though I'm not the chosen user,
even though I'm not strong enough,
there are times
when I just can't back down.
Because there are beings in this world
who do not have a human heart.
They take lives irrationally
without remorse or regret.
I will never tolerate their cruelty!
Lives that have been lost
will never return.
They are never coming back.
Our flesh and blood bodies
are unlike the demons'.
Why do you rob it?
Why do you trample on lives?
I feel like I've heard those words
somewhere before.
What is fun about it?
What is enjoyable about it?
What do you think lives are?
Who's that? I don't know him.
How could you not understand?
How could you forget?
These are not mine.
These aren't my memories.
These are from the cells.
The memories of…
Lord Muzan's cells.
Hey!
The obi worms scattered
and fled through the hole!
Shut up!
It's a good thing we saved
all these captured people!
Worship me first!
We'll talk about that later!
Sir Tengen, if you don't go after it,
it will cause more damage!
Don't worry about us, just go ahead!
Let's go after it, rascals!
Keep up with me!
Go faster!
Get out of the way!
The Great Uzui is coming through!
He's so damn fast!
What are you implying?
You were a human too, weren't you?
You used to shed tears because
you struggled with pain and suffering.
You just won't shut up, will you?
Why would I remember my past?
I'm a demon now, so it doesn't matter.
Demons never grow old.
We don't even need money to eat.
We never get sick.
And we won't die.
We have nothing to lose.
Furthermore,
the beautiful, strong demons
can do everything they want!
Very well.
Enough.
Blood Demon Art:
Eight Layered Obi Slash!
You can't stop it, can you?
Because you're a fool.
This crossing blow has no way out.
I've been splitting my body to rule over
the entertainment district,
and when it becomes one with me,
its speed is unmatched.
You've had your hands full
with my normal attacks,
so it's impossible for you to parry it.
It's over for you. Farewell.
I'm going to slice you
along with your dull sword.
I'll go to the Hashira's whereabout.
Hinokami Kagura:
Burning Bones, Summer Sun.
It hurts!
What's with this pain?
The sections he cut hurt like hell.
I can't regenerate it well.
His wounds are supposedly deep.
Normally, his body would tear apart
if he made such intense moves.
To begin with, why can he cut my obi?
I've increased its hardness too.
My fingertips are trembling?
Is this me?
Lord Muzan's?
He's faster than before.
This is strange. This is wrong.
Does he not feel any pain?
Is he even a human?
There's no way someone like you
can sever my head.
It's elastic.
Too elastic to sever.
Its elasticity loosened up my slash.
You're not getting away,
you ugly little shit!
She's using more obi. Thirteen of them.
If I dodge them,
the damage could spread again.
But somehow,
they're very slow.
I won't let you cut them this time!
It was just a pure coincidence
that you reached my neck earlier!
He parried them with the sword ridge
and gathered them in one place.
Is that supposed to stop me?
I'll send you flying!
Is he planning to cut my obi
by not letting them loosen up?
But I can extend them
in the blink of an eye.
As if he can do anything
from that distance in a split second--
What? Did he cut them?
So fast.
It's simple.
I just have to swing my sword and sever
her head faster than it can loosen up.
I can do it this time. I can sever it.
Tanjiro!
Tanjiro, breathe! Please!
It's miserable to be a human, isn't it?
No matter how desperate you are,
it's sad you can only go this far.
I can't stop coughing.
It's painful to breathe.
I already passed my physical limit
a while ago.
My vision is going dark.
I can only hear my own heartbeat.
Oh, well, your wounds won't heal easily.
Of course, that's how it goes.
Hold up your sword.
In return, I'll cut your head off.
How dare you kick me?
You…
It was you, wasn't it?
You are the one my Lord talked about!
Daki, there's a demon
who has escaped my control.
Just like Tamayo.
Find and kill her.
You're the only one I can ask.
She's wearing a kimono
with hemp leaf pattern and checkered obi.
Of course, as you wish.
I'll torture her to death, my Lord.
All you can do is kick, huh?
You small-fry demon!
So weak.
I bet you didn't eat humans.
How can you escape from my Lord's control?
What a poor thing.
Your torso is torn apart, you see.
You'd better not move.
A half-assed like you can't regenerate
those severe wounds immediately.
Since we're of the same demon kin,
I won't bully you anymore.
I'll trap you within my obi, and let
the sunlight burn you when morning comes.
It would be a waste of time
if the demons tried to kill each other.
What?
Wait a minute. What the hell?
Her legs had already regenerated.
Not only that, but how can she stand?
I cut her body in half a little while ago.
She resisted my attack.
I'm sure I've torn it apart.
The speed of her regeneration just now
is even comparable
to the Upper Rank Demons.
What's with this pressure?
She suddenly got more menacing.
Tanjiro…
Both you and Nezuko are really similar.
You both are gentle, but scary when mad.
A long time ago,
Nezuko got mad at a rude adult
who bumped and injured a little child.
She was angry
and told the adult to apologize.
It's a good thing there were
a lot of adults around back then.
But I was scared.
People who get angry
for the sake of others
often lack concern for themselves.
I'm scared that one day she might lose
something precious because of it.
Another kick?
Fools always repeat what they do!
Next is your head!
-Nin-nin!
Monjiro!
We're coming to save you right now,
so don't die before we arrive!
How can you run in your sleep?
Can you see what's ahead?
How about this?
Man, you've never done this before.
And where's the God of Festivals?
You're so slow!
God of Festivals!
We don't have time
for the Taisho-era secret.
Next, episode 7, "Transfiguration."
Don't waste time here! Let's go!
TO BE CONTINUED