♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 5=
Let's go.
OK.
OK. Let's go.
(Qian Xiu Workshop)
Is this the place?
Mr. Rong,
this shop seems too small
to offer us the 500kg
dyestuff that we asked for.
You are right.
Let's check out another store.
Dear customers,
wait up.
I heard that you need 500kg dyestuff.
This store seems too small.
Let's check out another one.
Customer, you were wrong.
Although this store seems small,
Qian Xiu Workshop can rank
top 3 or 4 throughout the whole
Ruo Shui Kingdom.
There's no problem to place
the order of 500kg dyestuff with us.
Really?
Mr. Rong is really
the top unscrupulous...
silk merchant in the North Desert.
We have very strict rules for
the partners we work with.
How about this?
I will send someone to
show you two around.
You can decide after knowing more
about the store.
How does that sound?
Alright.
Waiter.
Boss.
Show these two customers
around the backyard.
OK.
This way, please.
This is our dyehouse.
We do all
the clothes dying here.
That is our warehouse over there.
Our warehouse is very large.
We put all the dry clothes
inside the warehouse.
It is our accountant house here.
We have finished the touring.
Please follow me to the front hall.
What's wrong, Mr. Rong?
My jade pendant fell somewhere.
My father gave it to me.
It is a family heirloom.
I will send some people
to help you look for it.
It's OK.
I remember that it fell
somewhere in the front hall.
You can go to the front hall first,
and we will meet you there soon.
Sounds good.
Then I will go there first.
My god. Look at these.
The boss was telling the truth.
It is a top 3 or 4 dyestuff workshop.
How to search for it?
The number of accounts is so huge.
Even they might have
difficulty looking for it.
But these seem to be arranged
in a certain order.
(Stock-In)
Like the library?
Library?
The book storage room.
Let's look for it.
You take a look first.
(Stock-Out Account Book)
Can you tell anything?
Too many.
I still need some time.
Boss,
I will bring it to you right away.
This way.
Your heartbeat is so fast.
Someone's coming.
I'm afraid that we get exposed.
So, I'm nervous.
(Stock-Out)
It was so scary.
Let's go.
(Stock-Out Account Book)
There's not enough time.
Could you tell anything?
I can remember everything I saw?
Did Mr. System add
this new skill for me?
(Ping Shan Bamboo Forest)
We finally made it back.
I wonder if Xiao Ai is worried.
I told Chang Kong to bring
Xiao Ai to the pavilion
and wait for you.
Let's go.
Watch out.
- Catch them.
- Stop running.
Stay there.
- Catch them.
- Stop running.
Hurry up.
- Stay there.
- Don't run.
No, no.
It's useless to keep running like this.
They all know Kung Fu
and we cannot run away.
Let's do this.
I will run along the main road
and lure them away.
So, you can hide here.
Then what about you?
Do you really think I will
give up my life for you?
You run away and call others
to come save me.
But...
There's no "But".
Believe in yourself.
I gotta go.
Help! Someone's trying to kill me.
Go after her.
Help!
What took them so long?
They would not run into anything, right?
It's getting late.
How about this?
You can go back to the gate.
I will find the 5th prince
and the 9th princess.
Alright.
Murong Chen, you will be widowed
if you don't show up soon.
(Is he...?)
Fighting!
He threw a punch.
Our hero hit the vital
part of the enemy.
Such a pity.
The enemy escaped it.
But it's OK.
Right way.
That's too bad.
The 3 enemies started
fighting our hero back.
Can the situation be
changed in 10 seconds?
Oh, my god.
He did it.
Our hero successfully escaped.
Yes, that's right.
Move out, move out. Nice!
Left, right.
Save the princess now.
(I finally met the real hero.)
(Will the game end here?)
♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
How are you doing?
You are…
(Young Murong Chen)
Wake up.
Uncle Qi,
(Young Jiang Mengmeng)
I found someone.
(Yun Qi)
Last month,
I found you by the river,
and I found another person this month.
I almost became a
professional life saver.
Xiaomeng,
do you really want him to stay?
Uncle Qi,
please let him stay.
If we don't let him stay,
he will die.
If you're afraid that the money
is not enough to cover our living costs,
I can share my buns
and porridge with him.
It's fine.
Little guy,
you can stay.
But there's something
I have to say first.
This place is not for unoccupied people.
After your injury gets better,
come beg with us.
Thank you, master.
Don't call me master.
I can't teach you anything.
Well,
you can call me Uncle Qi
as Xiaomeng does.
Yes.
Uncle Qi.
What is your name?
My name is Mu…
My name is A Mu.
A Mu.
Then I will call you A Mu
from now on.
A Mu, this will be
your home now.
Don't run away again.
If you get lost again,
there's no one who's as kind as me.
Game over?
This is not my home.
You awake?
You saved me?
(Falling into water.)
(Shabby house.)
(Fire pit.)
(This story...)
He is a swordsman.
So, I cannot use what I learned
in the royal court dramas.
Right.
Knight-errant dramas.
A weak girl in a knight-errant
drama should be like this.
If you didn't show up and save me,
I would've died already.
May I know your name?
My name is Yun Ya.
Swordsman Yun.
If you hadn't saved me…
There's nothing I can pay you back,
but to marry...
Excuse me,
have you been to Liang City?
Liang City?
I've never heard of it.
(She did forget everything.)
(Why did he suddenly mention
Liang City?)
(Don't tell me it's some
vulgar story about substitute lover.)
(Is he going to say that)
(I look like someone he used to know?)
You look like someone I used to know.
(Sure enough!)
(This is the kind of story
I hate the most.)
(Although I like
Yun Ya's character setting,)
(I don't like the storyline.)
Swordsman Yun,
well,
I have nothing to pay you
back for saving my life now,
but I will be at your
service in my next life.
I gotta go.
Xiaomeng.
Come on, Mr. System.
I don't want to follow this storyline.
Are you going to chop me or what?
Fine.
Come, strike me.
I'm not leaving.
Strike me now.
You win.
Well...
It was lightning and I'd better...
Are you OK?
Your hands are so cold.
I'm fine.
It's just a small wound.
You call this small wound?
Did you get hurt when you saved me?
Small wound might have triggered
my previous illness.
Don't worry.
Ah, right,
why are you back?
It's all this system's fault.
You heard it?
It seems like
we have to spend the night here.
Are you really OK?
Miss,
you should have some rest.
I...
You...
Don't worry about me.
Since you said that.
Take care.
I'm telling you.
I do this because I don't want to
be called ungrateful.
Don't misunderstand me.
I don't like you at all.
And I'm definitely not
the person you knew in Liang City.
Fell asleep?
No, no.
What if he's a wanted criminal?
If I see his face...
Jiang Mengmeng,
keep your life for relationship.
Why are the hands so cold?
♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
Murong Chen.
Murong Chen, run.
Xiaomeng,
from now on,
no matter it's Murong Chen
or Yun Ya,
I will never let anyone hurt you.
Did you figure it out?
Yes, I did.
Those men in black were
sent by the 4th princess.
It's her?
I don't have any resentment with her.
Why does she want me dead?
The 4th princess is not trying to
kill you.
Instead,
she fell in love with you.
What?
Ah, right,
how is the 9th princess?
She's fine.
But...
I don't want to break off
the engagement any more.
Why?
You know what?
Jiang Mengmeng
is Xiaomeng, the one I've been
searching for years?
It's her?
I've been looking for her for so long,
and I finally found her.
This time,
I will not let go.
Your Highness.
As expected,
you used your inner power again,
and it triggered the
cold poison in your body.
It's fine.
It was urgent
to save Jiang Mengmeng,
and I couldn't care that much.
Your Highness,
it's not because of emergency.
It is because of love.
You knew that you may get killed
if the cold poison is triggered
too many times.
Is it worth it?
As long as it's for her,
it's all worth it.
Swordsman Yun?
Swordsman?
He left without saying goodbye
as expected.
Typical!
Cheer up, Jiang Mengmeng.
He's just a non-player character.
Yes.
I should just run off.
After I go back, I have to spend so much
effort on looking for
the blood night-blooming cereus.
Rather than breaking off the engagement,
it's easier to just run off.
No.
Xiao Ai is still in the palace.
Whatever. I already know
everything anyway.
But all my money...
Money in the game is all fake.
Fake.
Murong Chen came out together with me.
Damn Murong Chen.
He will be accused.
He can explain it.
No, no.
Even if he does, no one would listen.
No one would believe either.
Such damn sense of justice.
Go.
Did you see a girl who is
short with big eyes
and who looks cute?
No, no, no.
No, I haven't seen one.
Hi,
did you see a girl who is
short with big eyes
and who looks cute?
No, I haven't.
Song Che.
Mengmeng.
Are you OK?
Did you get hurt?
I was OK,
but now I'm a little dizzy.
Sorry.
I was too worried about you.
You don't know.
During the day you went missing,
the whole palace
became a mess.
Really?
Let's go.
Let's go home.
OK.
5th prince,
you and the 9th princess
were in danger by the river.
As the queen's son-in-law,
you not only let dangerous thing happen,
but also left her there.
She fell into the water, got hurt,
and stayed outside for a night.
You cannot get away from it.
Since Mengmeng is now back,
she will decide how
you should be punished.
Break off the engagement.
(This is a good chance
to break off the engagement for sure.)
Sister queen, there is
no need to punish him.
No punishment?
Since the 5th prince did nothing wrong,
he doesn't deserve any punishment.
On that day,
I asked him to run first.
Sister queen, I, as the 9th princess
of Ruo Shui Kingdom,
should undertake the responsibility
to protect the country and the people.
The 5th prince is not only
the queen's son-in-law,
but also my man.
How can I protect the country
if I can't even protect my man?
5th prince, you can see yourself out.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Mengmeng.
If I didn't sacrifice myself
and save you this time,
your life would be in danger.
How is it?
Am I generous?
It is a big favor,
and I have to repay it.
How do you want to repay it?
I will repay it
by marrying you.
Your Highness.
Chang Kong,
let's go.
You are biting the hand that feeds you.
What are you laughing at?
(Ling Xi Palace)
The 9th princess is not here.
It doesn't matter
whether she's here or not.
I'm here to send the stuff
from the 5th prince.
The 9th princess said that
she would not see anyone
or take anything.
Whatever.
I've delivered the stuff anyway.
Why are you so obedient?
You are totally...
well...
a simp.
I will leave the stuff here.
I will not see anyone.
I'm not at Ling Xi Palace.
Your Highness,
I've sent the person away.
But
he left the food here.
What?
This shall not happen again.
Your Highness,
you cannot hide from
the 5th prince like this forever.
You will meet sooner or later.
I'd hide as long as possible.
Let me tell you.
That Murong Chen
has been constantly
showing his affection.
He's bought me all kinds of stuff.
Xiao Ai, you really don't know
how scary it is
when a bad dog becomes
a simp.
Tell me,
did his brain get injured
the other day when we
were chased after?
I think
he was attracted by how you were
defending him bravely
in front of the queen last time.
So, he fell in love with you.
Wait,
are men in this game
that easy to take down?
Take down?
Well, this does taste good though.
What's wrong?
Why are you so mad
after delivering the stuff?
It's all because of
the maid of the 9th princess.
She said that I am
a dog.
[*simp means flattering dog in Chinese]
Dog?
What's wrong with dog?
Isn't it adorable?
Your Highness,
why are you also...
Fine.
Xiao Ai is not that kind of girl.
It must be taught by her master.
Speaking of which,
the 9th princess is treating
you as a stranger,
and not responding
anything to your affection.
Why don't you tell her directly
about the past between you two?
That memory is
not a good memory.
It's better be forgotten.
There're too many things
that I'm bearing.
I don't want her to get involved.
It is OK that she doesn't know anything.
I just want her to be happy.
I trust our fate.
Even if she doesn't remember anything,
I can still make her
fall in love with me again.
Your Highness,
you do have high confidence.
But now, the 9th princess doesn't
even want to see you.
How is it possible for her
to fall in love with you?
If she doesn't want to see me,
I will go to see her.
If she doesn't walk towards me,
I will walk towards her.
Your Highness,
is this...
sort of...
simp?
Simp?
Simp.
What does it mean?
Murong Chen went out of the palace.
The guard saw it by himself.
The 5th prince left the palace
with Chang Kong since morning.
Great.
I've been staying in the room for days
just to avoid him.
I'm about to go crazy.
(Jin Xiu Gate)
No way.
Your Highness.
Is there anything we can help?
Nothing.
I'm just walking around.
You can go.
Yes.
No way.
Picking up money
right after coming outside?
Even more?
What kind of luck am I having today?
Didn't you get out of the palace?
Yeah.
I took a walk outside.
But somehow
nothing is more attractive than you.
So, I came back.
Then what about these?
You didn't accept any of the
gifts I gave you before.
So, I thought about it
and figured that you must not like them.
Then, I will give you
something you will like.
You do know me well.
Otherwise,
how can we be a perfect couple?
Since you have already led me here,
I will make it clear to you.
The account book of Qian Xiu Workshop?
You remember them all?
I told you that I can
remember everything I saw.
You don't believe it.
(Account Book of Qian Xiu Workshop)
But
the handwriting is too bad.
Is my handwriting bad?
The handwriting on that
account book was this bad.
What are you trying to tell me
by showing me this?
I want to tell you that,
a few days ago,
we were still partners who look for
the blood night-blooming cereus.
Why can't we continue to be like that?
We find the blood night-blooming cereus
and then get separated.
Isn't it good?
No.
I want the flower,
and the marriage.
Do you know why I need to find
the blood night-blooming cereus?
I think...
I don't know.
I want to find it and
give it to my sister queen,
so that
I can break off the engagement.
Although we are engaged,
I don't like you.
Not to mention marrying you.
I thought it was something big.
It's okay that
you don't like me.
As long as I like you,
everything will be fine.
Relationship should be
mutual and equal.
Others might be like that,
but I'm different.
It's enough for me to like you.
Such a crooked thought.
Do you have any childhood trauma?
No, I don't.
Then,
what do you like about me?
Tell me,
so that I can change it.
Look at you.
You are a princess.
Pureness,
beauty,
dignity,
elegance,
and demureness.
These good qualities
have nothing to do with you.
You don't
look like a princess all over.
You're more like
a palace maid.
If you stand among the palace maids,
Xiao Ai would be more like
a princess than you.
And...
And the other one around you.
What is he called?
A Liang!
If he puts on female makeup,
he would look more like
a princess than you.
Is that enough?
But...
You are frank, righteous
and smart when in danger.
I'm very happy being with you.
I feel safe.
You feel
very happy
and safe with me,
right?
Are you sure you want to
wait for the sunrise here?
Aren't you cold?
Of course I have to wait.
(It seems that I underestimated
the cold night in late spring.)
(It's so cold.)
(Look at Murong Chen's
spoiled little body.)
(I guess he'll cry for
going back in a minute.)
It's so cold.
Now you know you were wrong?
Jiang Mengmeng! You…
I'll never watch the sunrise
with you again!
Don't you feel cold?
It's not that cold.
Are you really not cold?
Yeah.
I even feel warm.
Xiaomeng,
you know what?
I…
I hope that
in the whole life,
I can always have you
lying on my shoulder.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪