[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 2]
What are you doing?
It's you again?
Aren't you supposed to be in Zhao's Mansion?
This is my house.
Why should I be in Zhao's Mansion?
Did you lose money in gamble
and sneak in to steal, right?
I don't think Miss Zhao
will find you attractive.
Wait.
Did you say this is your house?
Are you...
How is that possible?
So,
you know Li Qingfeng?
Forget it.
Come with me.
My Lady.
I didn't mean it.
I know how hard it is to make a wooden kite.
That's why I have to make up for it.
Are you Li Qingfeng’s apprentice?
Can you help me fix it?
Do you think it can be fixed?
I checked.
It looks fine from the outside.
But we need to open its body,
and figure out the tenon and mortise structure inside.
Get out.
You can ask for anything you need.
How much will it cost?
I'll pay it.
Get out!
You...
Why are you so mean?
When I see Senior Li Qingfeng later,
I'll apologize to him.
He won't be as rude and unreasonable as you.
Luo, let’s go.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Why is he so mean to me?
It’s my fault. I shouldn't have been so curious.
Please punish me.
Luo, it’s not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Li Qingfeng and his apprentice went to take the embroidered ball.
They must be short of money.
Whatever Mr. Li asks,
I'll pay for it.
I'm sure Mr. Li can fix it.
Fix it.
Inside the wooden kite, besides the tenon and mortise structure,
there are 17 bronze cogs
of different sizes.
Each cog has been specially remoulded.
It's not as simple as you think.
Of course you can't fix it.
But Senior Li certainly can.
OK.
Ladies and gentlemen,
dear friends and neighbors,
Wood Feather House is reopened today.
I hereby announce that
from today on, our door is open
to talents.
Don't go.
[Wood Feather House]
Maybe you are not talents in this area.
But recommendation will also be rewarded.
If we hire the one you recommend,
you can get three taels of silver.
[Wood Feather House]
Three!
One tael.
When you beg on the street,
spread the news for us.
Luo.
What are you doing?
Qingfeng.
They look familiar.
Qingfeng?
You are Li Qingfeng?
No way.
He's like an old tortoise
that can't be found in Qiantang Lake in 300 years.
Why are you looking for him?
The old tortoise that can't be found in Qiantang Lake in 300 years.
He doesn't do well as a gambler,
but he's really good at cursing.
So the wooden kite is made by you.
I want to apologize to you.
Is the wooden kite destroyed?
Miss.
The kite is an amazing gadget
that took Qingfeng half a year to finish.
You just destroyed it.
He didn't even allow me to touch it.
Tell me.
Was the wooden kite fun?
Did it fly?
How could it be fun?
It was not finished.
There were still problems that I couldn't fix.
That's why it would be out of control due to excessive twists
if the mechanism was triggered after three laps.
It...
How many laps did you turn?
Five laps?
I think it was six.
Seven?
Maybe eight.
Nine?
Nine.
How did it fly?
It seemed to whiz through the air.
Yes.
That's it.
The main reason was the screen over there.
If it weren't for the screen,
it could...
But it crashed in the end.
That's enough.
You can leave.
Calm down. Calm down.
Ladies,
I want to ask
if you have any work for us.
To be honest,
we're not here for any worker.
We're here for a job.
For a job?
Good.
We are recruiting people.
I'm the owner of Wood Feather House.
Luo Ye.
Mr. Luo.
I wonder if you two want to be the supervisors
or the secretaries?
I'm an architect.
It's the first time I've seen a female architect.
It's a pity that
in our Wood Feather House,
there's already an architect.
It's him.
There can't be two architects in the House?
No way.
Even if it's possible,
you are not qualified to be an architect here.
It's just because
-I destroyed your wooden kite. -My lady.
Stop beating around the bush.
We are so sincere.
We apologized to you and offered to pay for it.
What else do you want?
I don't want to waste my time.
See them out.
You...
Calm down.
Wait a minute.
Wait a moment.
Qingfeng.
Come here.
Bro, let me tell you.
Wood Feather House has such a bad reputation
that no one wants to work for us.
That's why I'm so anxious to recruit people.
Understand?
Didn't you say we'll have new people if we have money?
I just did it
because of them.
But how can she work as an architect?
You need an assistant right now.
Her?
What are they talking about?
Why haven't they finished yet?
Let's see what they're talking about.
I'd rather not.
You might as well employ her first.
We'll replace her after we find a better one.
That's it.
This is too unfair.
She destroyed your wooden kite.
Why do you have to be fair to her?
Miss, what's the matter?
It's a bit cold over there.
So I moved here.
Well, Miss.
The vacant positions in Wood Feather House
include the secretary, the supervisor,
the chief executive and the general director.
Since you are full of sincerity,
I'll let you be...
The supervisor?
The deputy architect.
The deputy architect?
Do you ask me to be the assistant of Li Qingfeng?
Miss, guess what?
Just now Qingfeng told me
he very much appreciates
your frankness and honesty.
However, one team of craftsmen
can't have two architects.
That's why I let you be the deputy architect.
It's reasonable,
and can satisfy everyone.
You try to please everyone, huh?
I don't care what he said.
As long as you agree to let me participate in the design
and drafting,
I'll work as the deputy architect then.
OK.
From now on,
you two are members of Wood Feather House.
What should we do now?
[Recruiting craftsmen] [Recruiting stonemasons]
Patterned cloth.
Look at the beautiful patterned cloth.
Come and have a look.
[Recruiting craftsmen]
We're recruiting people here. You should shout it out loud.
Otherwise who would know we’re recruiting here?
I think there are no blind people on this street.
You're good at quarreling.
If you think shouting works,
you can do it yourself.
Who's good at quarreling?
You're so mean.
As expected, in this world,
it's hard to get both talent and nice character.
I think you have neither talent
nor nice character.
Your arrogance
is unbelievable.
In that case,
buy me some pear soup.
I've waste a lot of energy on you,
and now I'm a little thirsty.
Architect Li.
You can't talk to her like that.
You don't know she is...
Deputy architect, huh?
Okay, I'll buy it for you.
My Lady, you can't do that.
Architect Li, I’ll buy you pear soup.
[Recruiting craftsmen] [Recruiting stonemasons]
Please move out of the way.
What's wrong?
I feel dizzy. I need a rest.
[Recruiting stonemasons]
Did His Majesty send them to look for me?
Are you feeling better now?
Yes.
How about this?
When Luo brings back the pear soup,
let me drink some for you.
Thank you.
Are you recruiting a supervisor?
Yes. Yes.
Where are you from?
Wood Feather House.
Wood Feather?
Is it Li Qingfeng's team?
Li Qingfeng.
He's famous for being picky.
Forget it.
Sir,
what do you mean?
It seems that you just joined them.
I'll tell you something in one sentence:
stay away from Li Qingfeng.
He is talented but not virtuous.
He has a terrible personality.
Anyone who worked with him
was scolded by him.
When he got angry, he even scolded the employer.
He also likes to act on his own when working.
Wood Feather House went bust because of him.
Wait.
Didn't Wood Feather go bust?
Is this one sentence?
Never mind about that.
Anyway,
stay away from Li Qingfeng.
What's your name?
If you want to find another employer,
I can give you a hand.
I’m Li Qingfeng.
I knew it.
Architect Li is indeed famous in Lin'an.
Mr. Luo.
You're back.
How is it?
Great. That's great.
We didn't recruit anyone.
How come?
Actually, there were a lot of people coming to us.
However,
when they heard the name of Li Qingfeng, they all went away.
I think
they admire Architect Li's talents so much
and are afraid of not being qualified to work for Wood Feather House.
Mr. Luo,
I think you'd better prepare for the worst.
We may fail to
recruit any craftsman this year.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
I feel dizzy. I need a rest.
[Zhongsheng Drugstore]
[Silk Cloth Store]
Sir, it's not raining now.
Why should we take an umbrella?
Right, it's not raining now.
But what if it rains later?
What if my clothes get wet?
You're right.
I patrol for my father,
to maintain the order and justice of Lin'an City.
Ladies and gentlemen,
anyone who is wronged
can come to me.
I serve the country and the people.
I'm a hero
who will bring justice back to you,
and prove your innocence.
Do you have any questions?
You!
What's wrong with me?
You touched her.
What did I touch?
This is my new stall.
Don't cry here.
Why are you bullying a kid?
She lied.
You did touch me just now.
I touched you? Who saw it?
Who saw me touching you?
We all saw it.
I saw it too.
You dared to do that
in broad daylight
but doesn't have the guts to admit it.
Shame on you?
You bitch!
What did you just say?!
You...
What happened?
Prin...
What?
Mr. Meng.
What's going on?
The butcher harassed this lady in public.
My Lady and I both saw it,
but he didn't admit it.
Nonsense!
You!
You don't look like a good person.
Arrest him!
Sir.
We need evidence to arrest people.
Tell us.
How did I harass you?
You touched her.
I saw you kiss me.
I...
Sir, you should arrest her.
How dare you!
Don't be afraid. Tell me.
What happened?
I will help you,
but you must tell the truth.
Is what they said true?
Don't worry.
Did you hear that?
She said it.
You really brought people here.
You look like a martial artist.
Which position do you want to take?
The chief executive.
Being the chief executive
indeed requires excellent martial arts.
You indeed look like a master.
But I still want to give you a test.
Then I can decide how much I will pay you.
I don't care about my salary.
But I care about your skills.
Why didn't you fight back?
I'm afraid I might hurt you.
Alright. Alright.
Bro, you're good.
I'll give you 10 taels per month.
What's your name?
Wang Sheng.
Take care.
Here.
Waiter, we'll have some tea.
Got it. Sit here please.
Slow down.
We had no evidence.
So we had to let him go for now.
Miss, don't worry.
[Righteousness]
I will punish him severely someday.
We can't let him do evil again.
That butcher has done many evil things.
He has bullied
this kid repeatedly.
Please enjoy.
If you can stop him from doing harming,
it'll benefit the people here.
Of course I will.
Miss,
did you want to tell me something?
Did you post it?
[Recruitment]
Are you going to ask for a job?
No.
I want to ask you
whether you can do a small job for me.
Since we are a craftsman team,
of course we will do the job.
Wait.
What’s going on with you?
Are you working for Wood Feather?
Yes.
I'm the deputy architect now.
Luo is the secretary.
Thank you.
Tongtong.
Come here.
What secret task did the palace give you?
You think I'll let you know the secret task?
That's right.
But you're the noble prin...
Don't call me Princess.
Then what should I call you?
Master.
Master?
What are you looking at?
I think he can protect me.
All of us will protect you.
Do you remember that
when we were young, in the Ministry of Works,
I taught you how to carve swords with wood?
How could I forget?
Those were my happiest days.
Exactly.
So it's fair to say I'm your master.
You should call me master.
OK.
Master.
My good apprentice.
But you have to
keep it a secret.
All right.
Master,
how about
taking me to Wood Feather too?
As you know, I like you.
Stop, stop, stop.
That's what happened when we were little. Stop it.
Alright.
But you know it.
I don't have anything serious to do
and wander around all day long.
If I can work with you,
it must be much more interesting.
Mr. Luo.
You're back, Miss Chen.
Have a seat.
We are about to eat.
You look familiar.
His name is Meng Yuanxu.
He's looking for a job.
[Righteousness]
Who is this gentleman?
Wang Sheng.
The new chief executive of Wood Feather craftsman team.
Chief executive?
Why haven't I heard of this position?
Miss Chen, you don't know it.
Normally, craftsman teams in the Ministry of works
don't need a chief executive.
But private craftsman teams
usually have all kinds of complicated matters.
We need a chief executive like Wang Sheng
who can use force
to solve problems.
I see.
Wait.
He's the chief executive.
Then what do I, an official, do here?
So you're an official.
No wonder you look familiar.
Nice to meet you. Wait.
We've never met before. Don't cotton up to me.
You're right.
Please have a seat.
Since you're an official,
why do you look for a job in Wood Feather House?
I do it for a reason.
Just tell me if you want me or not.
A talent like you
is exactly what we are looking for.
You're the best employee we can have.
It's just that
we can only pay you very little salary.
I'm afraid you won't be happy with that.
You think I want your money?
Of course not.
But,
I don't get it.
Why do you want to work here?
I just...
He wants to be a carpenter.
Yes.
I've always liked cutting wood,
whittling wood and carving wood.
I've made a lot of wood carvings.
I really admire that.
But
why do you want to be the chief executive?
To be honest,
I just think it's an easy job.
I'm good at easy work.
Sir, you're really straightforward.
But we've already had Wang Sheng
as the chief executive in Wood Feather.
Do you want to be our general director?
It's a powerful position
and it's a perfect job for you,
who's strong and powerful.
Stop it.
The general director is in charge of other directors,
and has to manage the work on site.
It's both annoying and tiring.
I don't think this job suits me.
Wood Feather House doesn't hire slackers.
Who did you just say?
He doesn't mean it.
You're good at both civil and martial matters.
You're courageous and prudent.
But our Wood Feather is so small
that it's not worth your while to work for us.
Sir, please eat this.
Let's eat.
What do you mean?
I...
You want me to be the general director?
I'll do it.
I really appreciate how straightforward you are.
Now with you as the general director,
we only need a supervisor
before we can fill all the vacancies
in Wood Feather.
I believe before long,
the work will come to us.
Mr. Luo, how did you know that? We do have new work.
Tomorrow morning,
the employer will come here and discuss with us.
Miss Chen is indeed a lucky star of Wood Feather House.
All right.
Let's eat.
[Wood Feather House]
Who? Who are you?
Come out!
Is it this way?
Take a look here. Let's go.
[Wood Feather House]
Where did she go?
Where is she? Bro.
That way. Go.
Did a woman enter your yard?
Our Wood Feather craftsmen team
will answer your question before you pay two taels of silver.
You...
I mean, did you see a beautiful woman
in pink, and about this tall.
I see.
So many of you.
You must have a big project to consult us, right?
Well,
if you ask ten questions,
I'll answer another two for free.
No...
Come in. Come in.
Come in.
Let's go.
Don't go.
I can give you a discount.
Come out. They're all gone.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Those people are...
May I have your name?
My name is Han Niaoniao.
I met Miss Chen yesterday.
I have a job for you.
It's you.
I wonder
what exactly you want us to do.
I want you to renovate a shanty.
A shanty?
It's fine.
Miss Han. You can tell us in detail.
Yesterday, Miss Chen and Mr. Meng met Tongtong.
Yes.
That kid is so cute.
I want to ask you
to renovate the shanty of Tongtong's family.
Tongtong is living with her grandma.
They're impoverished.
Now their shanty is crumbling.
It can't even protect them from the wind and rain.
Miss,
how much is the budget of materials
and construction?
To be honest,
we don't have money.
I saw Miss Chen post a recruitment notice yesterday.
I also heard something about your craftsman team.
So I thought you may need a job
to restore your reputation.
The renovation of Tongtong's house is a very small project
without any complex design and construction.
If you take this kind deed as your first protect,
your reputation will surely be restored.
That makes sense.
What makes sense?
She wants us to work for free.
Miss.
Please wait a moment.
Qingfeng, come with me.
Just say it to her.
Why do you have to talk here?
Forget it.
Just tell me whether you want to take this job or not.
The renovation of the shanty
doesn't interest me at all.
So you don't want to take it?
If you have any ideas,
you can tell me.
Look at you.
You can't do this.
You should stick to your ambitions.
Though we have acquired
considerable financial support from the Zhao family,
and we're more confident now,
if we take this kind of unpaid job,
the reopening of Wood Feather House will be a joke.
It makes sense.
You can just tell her that.
I won't object.
Wait.
I think
it's better for you to tell her.
You're the decision-maker, aren't you?
Why do you ask me to tell her instead?
I want you to tell her not because
I'm worried about Miss Han.
Miss Han, you are not from Lin'an, are you?
What are you talking about?
I was asking Miss Han about herself.
My parents are not in Lin'an.
I'm a maid of a lady.
I have very little income
but I manage to support myself.
I'm sorry.
Since Master likes you,
how about working for my family?
I will be a good boss.
Meng Yuanxu. Don't interrupt us.
Mr. Luo. Architect Li.
Miss Han is a poor girl,
but she is willing to help Tongtong.
This is the right thing to do.
Now what she asks us to do them a favor,
we must help them.
Miss Han.
We understand your difficulty.
But now the Wood Feather has just reopened,
we need to take projects that can prove our capabilities.
This is also our difficulty.
Therefore,
I'm really sorry.
I see.
Sorry to bother you.
Architect Li.
Miss Han is making a living in Lin'an alone
but she's still kind enough to help those in need.
You are a man.
Why don't you show your kindness as well?
Everyone has their own difficulties.
The chance for Wood Feather to reopen
was also hard to come by.
If we make any mistake again, who will take the consequences?
You don't have to argue because of me.
I was too abrupt.
Architect Li.
Wood Feather House is not just yours.
I'm the architect.
Yes, you're just an architect.
Mr. Luo, you are the boss.
What do you think?
Guys.
Calm down. Calm down.
Let's sit down and talk.
Miss Han, please sit down.
We'll help.
Of course we'll help.
What I appreciate the most
is kindness.
Among other things,
just for your kindness,
we'll help you.
Great.
Thank you, Mr. Luo.
Architect Li, did you hear that?
Not everyone of Wood Feather House
is as cold-blooded as you.
Li Qingfeng, even your best friend agreed.
What else do you want to say?
Qingfeng, if you have any concerns,
you can tell me.
Even if you agree,
our team is still short of a supervisor.
In any case,
you can't start the work without a supervisor.
You're right.
How could I forget that?
It's true.
I can be the supervisor for now.
Miss Han, this is a serious matter.
Supervisor is different from other workers.
Only when you have very professional knowledge
can you be qualified.
I know. I'm not joking.
Please trust me, Architect Li.
According to the national rules of construction,
The size of the house is measured by cai.
Cai has eight levels.
We should choose different level of cai
according to the size and level of the house.
Therefore, how many materials are needed
for the pillars of Palaces, Halls and Remaining Rooms?
The Palaces use materials from 2 cai 2 qi to 3 cai.
The Halls use materials of 2 cai 1 qi.
The Remaining Rooms use materials from 1 cai 1 qi to 2 cai.
How about the size of pillars?
In terms of the size of pillars,
the corner pillar stands when it reaches the corner and it depends on the number of rooms.
If there are 13 rooms,
the corner pillar is 1 chi 2 cun taller than the flat pillar.
If there are 11 rooms, 8 cun taller.
7 rooms, 6 cun taller.
5 rooms, 4 cun taller.
3 rooms, 2 cun taller.
You have experience as a supervisor?
I worked with my father since I was young.
So I know a thing or two,
about architecture supervision.
I also worked as a supervisor for three years.
So I know how to do it.
Great! Miss Han.
Architect Li.
You won't disapprove now, will you?
It's like that people who want to cross the river meet a boat.
What a coincidence!
I didn't expect that
Miss Han is so talented.
You are destined to
meet us in the Wood Feather House.
In that case, this work...
We'll go and take a look first.
If everything goes well,
we'll take the job.
Thank you, Mr. Luo. Thank you, Miss Chen.
Thank you, everyone.
Tongtong?
Tongtong.
Sister Han.
Grandma.
Sister Han is here!
Niaoniao.
Who are these people?
They are from Wood Feather craftsman team.
Craftsman team?
What are they doing here?
Miss Han said she would show us around
to help renovate the house.
So we come here.
Niaoniao.
This house is pretty nice.
No need to fix it.
Let them have a look. It's fine.
We just want to have a look.
We won't do anything else.
May I?
Sure. Sure. Please.
[Three Character Classic]
The window is broken.
How do you sleep?
It's stuffy.
With some fresh air, we can sleep.
OK guys. This is their home.
Can you renovate it?
Qingfeng.
What do you think?
Why are you pulling me out?
When you see them,
don't you feel sorry for them?
I do feel sorry for them.
But there are so many poor people out there.
I'm just an architect.
I should only do my job.
Tell me now.
What should you do now?
I've checked this place.
I'm not interested in the renovation.
Its renovation won't benefit
Wood Feather House at all.
You have no heart.
If I show off my kindness everywhere,
Wood Feather House will close soon.
What do you mean?
Do you think I'm showing off kindness?
Li Qingfeng.
You don't deserve to be an architect.
You promise Miss Han to come and have a look before making the decision.
Since you entered the door,
you looked bored and aloof.
How would Miss Han, grandma
and Mr. Luo feel about that?
It doesn't matter how I looked like.
What matters is I've seen this house
and thought
Wood Feather House doesn't need to take this job.
Have you really seen it carefully?
You only saw the leakage on the roof,
but you didn't see that blooming flower.
You only saw the broken room,
but you didn't see the desk under the sun.
You only see the broken window,
but you didn't see that
even under such a circumstance,
they're still trying to live a good life.
You only saw this shoddy shanty,
but you didn't see that
it's all they have.
She's the greatest architect
in the world.
But you
don't deserve to be an architect.
Qingfeng.
Don't argue anymore.
We don't have to take this job.
I’ll tell Miss Han now.
We'll take it.
What?
Tell them that
Wood Feather House
will take the work.
OK, I’ll tell them now.
Well...
Mr. Luo.
I understand.
Let me see you off.
Let's go.
Miss Han, you don’t understand.
We're going to take this job.
Really?
Since everyone is here,
let me introduce her.
This is the benefactor
of our Wood Feathe House.
Zhao Yining. Miss Zhao.
She is also the co-owner of Wood Feather.
From now on, we are a family.
That's why you look familiar.
You’re Zhao Xian’s daughter, right?
Hello, Mr. Meng.
Well,
I'm not in charge of any of your projects.
So you don't have to be cautious with me around.
Just treat me as your friend.
But
I have another identity.
My second identity is
Li Qingfeng’s admirer.
Li Qingfeng, you are really something.
Do you have to tell them that?
Of course yes.
I'll come and see you often.
If I don't make it clear,
it will cause many misunderstandings.
Am I right?
All right.
Mr. Luo will take care of the rest.
I won't talk.
The first thing is done.
Let me tell you the second one.
Grandma.
Grandma. Grandma.
What happened?
Get up. Be careful, grandma.
Come on.
Slow down.
Grandma, come here.
Grandma. Sit here. Slow down.
Don't cry.
What happened?
That butcher
robbed our ten taels of silver.
What?!
He's such a bully!
He bosses people around in the South City,
who picks on peddlers
and trades by coercion.
His pork shop
was seized from Mr. Liu by force.
And he broke one leg of Mr. Liu
because of that.
But no one can do anything about him.
Why don't you report it to the court?
He doesn't care.
It's useless to report it.
This is ridiculous.
Tongtong, take good care of grandma.
I'll be back soon.
Luo, let’s go.
Where are you going?
I can't stand it anymore.
It's too dangerous.
[Zhang's Butcher Shop]
[Feng's Tearoom]
[Silk Cloth Store]
Take care.
Come and have a look.
[Feng's Tearoom]
Excuse me.
Is the meat you sell bacon, right?
Are you blind?
I sell fresh pork.
You really have a bad temper.
You looks familiar.
So what?
I'll sell this to you.
Ten taels.
When did I say I would buy it?
Are you trying to make fun of me?
Don't be mad.
But you charge me ten taels of silver for this small piece of meat.
It's too expensive.
The meat is worth one tael.
[Feng's Tearoom]
The other 9 is charged because you smelled my meat.
You took all meaty smell.
Now I have to sell the rest of the meat at a low price.
How low will it be?
Three cents per catty.
OK, I want two catties of your cheap meat then.
How dare you fool me! Are you going to buy it or not?
OK. I’ll buy it.
[Feng's Tearoom]
But my money
is kept by my wife.
I really don't have much money with me now.
How about this?
I'll write a promissory note for you before go back and get the money.
Then even if my wife is to hit me
or scold me,
she'll have to give me the money.
What do you think?
Then write it.
All right.
You can go.
Alright.
Since the note is ready,
I’ll take my leave.
You're trying to fool me! Sign it.
You hurt me.
You must sign here.
Anyway,
you must give me 10 taels today.
You're making it difficult for me.
I almost forgot I have this!
Well,
I'll pawn it.
Then I'll be able to pay you. How about that?
OK. OK.
I'll go with you.
No problem.
Let's go.
Don't worry. No one will take your meat.
This one is really precious.
Let me tell you.
[Yongchang Pawnshop]
[Pawnshop]
What's the matter?
To be honest,
I'm not pawning the jade.
How can you change your mind all of a sudden?
Are you making fun of me?
No, no, sir.
[Silk Cloth Store]
[Yongchang Pawnshop]
OK.
I don't care about you wife and mother.
I don't care about filial piety.
Let me ask you again.
You won't change your mind again?
OK.
If you dare to fool me again,
I'll kill you!
Let's go.
[Silk Cloth Store]
Go!
Sir,
you know what.
I don't know how to explain to my wife.
[Feng's Tearoom]
If my wife knows
I spend ten taels to buy your...
bacon...
Cut the crap.
Sign it.
I'll do it myself.
[Buyer Chen Langyue] [Seller Zhang Ganglie]
It's your turn.
All right.
Good.
I pay you ten taels of silver to buy your shop.
Are you crazy? You want my shop?
See for yourself.
It's written on it.
You sold this shop to me with ten taels of silver.
[Feng's Tearoom]
You signed it yourself. Did you see it?
How dare you!
So what? I'll kill you!
My Lady.
Help!
[Zhang's Butcher Shop]
[Bai Fu Chi Pastry]
I told you it's dangerous here.
Stay here.
Stop. Stop.
You won.
I don't want those ten taels, either.
That's not right.
You must take the money.
Your shop will be mine.
The contract is here. You can't deny it.
You've gone too far!
How can you talk to her like that?
Luo.
Shame on you!