come help me organize the books
Your Highness
Inventory of the world's military and civilian Yamen warehouse grain
Check the number of cashiers handed over by year
It's a tedious task.
Our department is understaffed
sudden edict
Free at kisskh.me
Isn't it a crab in soup
What a mess
Of course
His Highness's order
sir, it must be done
It's just that the end of the year
Please also grant your Highness a grace period
Rong Chen went back to draw up the charter
Report to His Highness again
Your Highness
In fact, this government grain warehouse
There are performances everywhere
Statistics can be reported
If you really want to send personnel to check on the spot
It's just the selection of this person
need to reconsider
scrutiny after scrutiny
Be cautious
Yichen's opinion
Why don't you put it on hold
Think long term
Master Song is right.
It's a pity that I saw your majesty yesterday
He said eight months is too long
Only for half a year
So
Lord Song
tired
adult
Please
resign
What laughing
Is the book organized?
Your Highness
The maid has doubts
dare to ask
Your Highness, what is this painting?
This is the fruit of the tribute from Sumatra
it's called gambler
Grandpa didn't like the smell of it
but i tried it once
taste very sweet
Dare to ask your highness
Where are the overseas countries
What kind of customs?
This is the homework of the Food Bureau
To make a menu for overseas envoys
listen to you
Seems like I can't wait to find a boat
fled overseas
There is no shortage of strange people in all dynasties
Passionate about finding immortals overseas
Xian did not find
But there are a few logbooks
if you are interested
find yourself
Maybe on the side of the travelogue
Your Highness
Concubine Taisun has invited someone again
take it
Your Highness won't be here tonight
Yes
Yuan Gonggong
Grand Concubine
Your Highness is afraid that you will be empty
The special servants came to report
so
he's not coming
The emperor has recently detained his master to discuss political affairs
So His Highness he is too busy
After Your Highness is free
The first to think of you
Go ahead
Free at kisskh.me
Grand Concubine
Brocade book
It's my fault
I broke his heart
walk with me
if someone disappoints you
She wants to regret now
will you forgive her
why not answer
Your Highness
no one
can be changed
goodness is great
You are really weird
You have done so much
see me but say nothing
You know I'm talking about her
But let me go see her
I let you go
because you want to go
His Highness is in doubt
can not be released for a long time
How can this be happy
It's better to be open and honest and ask for peace of mind
isn't it?
in the royal
Don't ask for a life-and-death love
But ask for a wife who is respectful
But I sat with her
both feel uncomfortable
you say this world
Is there such a strange couple?
Your heart is so sincere
Who in the world will not cherish
As long as your Highness treats you with sincerity
There will be a day when the clouds will see the sun
i go see her
you are really happy
As King's Worry
worry about oneself
Your Highness Showing Your Face
We are Xinyue
His Highness is in doubt
can not be released for a long time
How can this be happy
It's better to be open and honest and ask for peace of mind
Let's go to Hongqing Palace
Yes
The people's daughter greets Her Royal Highness the Crown Prince
Your Highness
Concubine Taisun greets Princess Concubine
will be back soon
Your Highness, please take a seat
This is Miss Hu Fuqi
Entering the palace to visit the concubine Taisun
Your Highness is back
why didn't you tell me sooner
you are talking to the princess
How dare a slave to disturb
Seven Sisters
How did you come
Shanyuan greets the concubine Taisun
No one reported it before
what happened
why not answer
The previous crown princess gave her mother
The favor of visiting the palace
Now the concubine is ill
mother often misses
But the legs are not flexible
So he sent the seventh sister into the palace to visit the sick.
I am sick
what's wrong with me
The concubine and the grandson have been married for a long time
but no offspring
Not only the princess misses
Parents are often worried
elder sister
I have always thought of family
No matter how much I blame you or hate you
I also regard you as the only support in the palace
You are the only person I can trust
But only because I have no children
Can't win more honor for the Hu family
you
you one by one
Why are you so cruel to me
why
speak
Sanjie
No wonder His Highness just came
Left without looking back
He thought I was a wife
for my own selfish desires
to dedicate my sister to my husband
So flattering for my mother-in-law
OK
Since you don't care about your face
Then I will complete you
come
drag this bitch down
Thirty
banished from the palace
Grand Concubine
This
master
Grand Concubine
please forgive the slave
master
The eldest lady saves the slave
The slaves also obey your orders
Slaves are obeying orders
Master Jinshu has followed you since childhood
But the closest maid by your side
Such a one for the Hu family
The servant girl who can betray and deceive her master at any time
I will never keep her
Free at kisskh.me
you take her out of the palace immediately
from today
without my orders
No one from the Hu family is allowed to enter the palace again.
you listen
from today
I want to live by my own will
either you
still father
If you go against my will
Don't blame me for being ruthless
elder sister
Sanjie
Why does the third sister seem like a different person?
It's better to change
If she was still
hazy look
I can't live in this palace
now so
She looks like a grandson
let's go
I will send you out of the palace
Your Highness
Concubine Taisun is still waiting outside
There is no need to report her news in the future.
Yes, I understand
wait
The slaves are going to invite the concubine Taisun now.
Your Highness
I am past
tell her
the book is messed up
call her to rearrange
Your Highness
I know
you go to report again
I have an urgent matter to meet with Your Highness
Grand Concubine
You know the temper of Your Highness
The more you clamor to see him
The more angry he is
otherwise
you go back first
Wait until the day when His Highness will be relieved
Are you here to make amends?
This is over
master
It's windy here
let's go back
I can't find a book I'm looking for
how did you organize
I'm asking you
Your Highness
asking me
Still asking a slave
What's the difference
His Highness said
I am a slave
What did you say
I persuaded the Highness to go down to see the Taisun Concubine
Your Highness vented his anger on me
I think Your Highness should know
everything i do for you
Not a slave would do it for a master
you
i love you
what i did for you
A woman does it for a man she admires
To make His Highness happy
I can endure the loss
even heartache
persuade you to see the concubine Taisun
but you
But the books I organized
Just give up like this
Your Highness did not lose a book
but my heart
you
How dare you talk to me like this
Your Highness
You treat me the way a master treats a slave
from now on
I will also use
Treat you the way a slave treats a master
It wasn't my job to organize the study
It is only natural that His Highness is dissatisfied
But the punishment is
Your Highness, if you have no other orders
The maid quit
what did she just say
she
she said she likes you
She said she was going to be a slave
to treat her master
get her back
go
roll roll roll
Your Highness asks you to come back
let you go back
you are finished
Your Highness
It is better to use Tibetan pig or mullet roe
no no no
Someone also used
What else can I use?
I have my own way
real
Go ahead
You get busy
hurry hurry hurry
go
look
how is she cutting cucumbers
It's not giving up
come yet
I'm coming
Grandson, please take a seat
Father
I heard you are sick
Have you ever called a doctor?
What is the disease
Headache
no
is here
cut out the heart
messed up
At once
both hurt
Father is sick
should be healed in peace
any mission
Although I told my son
really
Free at kisskh.me
Okay
You adult
don't have to be so serious
Today I'm not here to look for the ballast
Lord Liu enters the palace for an audience
I'm here to see the menu for the embassy
I'm just leading the way
Meng Shang food
Last year's meal list at Guanglu Temple was due to the different tastes
almost cause trouble
This year's Prince's decree
to supervise
Not a little sloppy
Mr. You has had a lot of dealings with those Fan people.
That's why I asked him to take a look
two adults
please come with me
succulent
but not greasy
Completely different from the usual pork
Tibetan fragrant pig sent by Wusi Zangdusi
what the adults say is good
This pig grows in the forest
drink natural spring
It is eaten by wild people participating in pine mushrooms
So the meat is delicate and mellow
fresh and tender
slaves want
Most of the guests come from the sea
I have never tasted the delicacy of Tibet
This is how to make soup with the backbone of Tibetan pig
The front legs are made of a lion's head
such pork
No matter how it is cooked
will not disappoint
well said
I am the only one in the world
Where to find this ginseng pig
It's so delicious
good
Garnish with ginger and cinnamon
unripe fragrant nose
Pufferfish are poisonous
Jiang perch is ashamed
Saury is indeed the first of Jiang Xian
But now the spring flood has not come
I even used dried fish to pass it off
Also used gold foil
It's ordinary color
Wrapped in arabesque satin
She's an absolute beauty
self-deception
back off
Why do you add pepper to it?
in my hometown
Pepper all the way from Sumatra
Shipped from Guri
The price is more precious than gold
adult
This is the tribute girl who just arrived
my country's Kunei pepper piles up like a mountain
you save others
Treat such a cheap thing as a treasure
Wouldn't it be rude
The slaves have little knowledge
please forgive me
What's the disrespect
Unknown His Royal Highness arrives
Please forgive me if I miss you
It's a small disqualification for entertaining guests
It is a great thing to lose the national body and talent
I heard everything you just said
under the sky
Could it be the king's land
The Shore of the Land
Could it be that the prince
I am China since the Qin and Han Dynasties
Then there is no end to the source of foreign
As for me even more so
Grandpa the Emperor
where is the caravan
Whether by sea or land
Can't bully the widow, can't bully the weak
Some places don't know the time
give the calendar
church farming
In some places, banana leaves are used as food.
People can only eat cold food
to open a ceramic market
Administer acupuncture herbs
It's unethical in some places
Killing
We're going to put an end to the war
brought by our fleet
More than just gorgeous silk and china
Chinese herbal medicine
Acupuncture weaving
Architectural Navigation
and a large number of Chinese classics
stay in overseas countries
why we do this
only because of widowhood
followed by chaos
Only the world is peaceful
Then the people of the world can enjoy happiness
so
She doesn't understand what you're going to tell her
and treat them equally
Your Highness, please forgive me
These children are confined to the deep palace with limited vision
The lessons of His Highness are better than my ten years of work
Remember today's words
One must have a broad mind and vision
good for your life
Yes
back off
A Red Shrimp is mentioned in the Supplements of Materia Medica in the Tang Dynasty
Born in Linhai Kuaiji
The big one is one foot long
must be a hairpin
Just in time with Taiping County Chronicle
The colorful giant shrimp with burly and unusual
same
Therefore, it is also called the god shrimp in Quanzhou Prefecture.
Today, the traditional practice of local fishermen is specially used
Cook Splendid Shrimp Rice
Please taste
where is the meal
Your Highness does not know
fishermen's food
often refers to fish
Shrimp dipped in sauce with unique flavor
Makes people feel like they are back in the bow
The moment the sea breeze blows
indescribably delightful
Fragrant and chewy
the smell of the sea
Free at kisskh.me
Your Highness, what do you say?
Flour glutinous sweet and endless aftertaste
Needless to say, betel nut and taro
Taro again
Crunchy and sweet
Far better than steamed taro
One taro and two
common food
make an unusual taste
That's the craft
no matter how delicious
Just some sliced ​​cucumbers
Fennel Broad Beans
add taro
Not even a piece of meat
Why be so stingy
Are you going to win by quantity?
Grandpa Huang asked his father to do errands
Father fell ill
But the emperor's order is the emperor's order
he is sick
I'm the only one here
Your Highness
Do you still need to ask the prince for the meal list?
call the cook
Why use ordinary food
Back to His Highness
ancients cloud
Have friends come from afar
entertain guests
should make them feel at home
But the people of our country are the most precious people
All the products of this land
It is a gift from God to the hard-working people
They are the ones who should taste the most
and
Zhang Qian was on a mission to the Western Regions
Bring back the ingredients you used today
precious seeds
Rooted and sprouted in my Chinese land
cultivated from generation to generation
In order to change the ever-changing taste
vote me with peach
Report it to Qiong Yao
Prepare meals for the envoys
In addition to mountain delicacies
Add these too
the rice I just ate
It's very soft and delicious.
Jingshan Bridge Rice
Huguang suffered a natural disaster last year
If this rice is supplied to the embassy
Then the wealthy businessmen in Beijing
will compete
so that
People's life will be much better
Just a little chef
How to have so much mind
But it's just a coincidence
Why is he back
adult
Please
thousands of miles
Opal brought back from Khurmus
see if you like it
Thank you for the reward
The slaves are ashamed and dare not accept
line line
Yao girl
you haven't been looking for
Is this logbook?
I sent it to you
no use
Take it all
take it
On behalf of the slaves and maids, thank the imperial grandson for the reward
Okay
you tell her
someday
brought back by our fleet
will be more than jewelry and spices
There will be more products that benefit the Chinese people
completion
Forgot the most important sentence
walk, walk, walk
reward
that's what she said
How dare that servant dare to talk nonsense?
That's what Yao girl said
hurry up
come quickly
quick
hurry up
Yuan Gonggong
thank you
Go in by yourself
go
Open
Yes
what did you do today
Back to His Highness
by convention
Meal list from Guanglu Temple
Cooked according to the order by the Food Bureau
Yao Zijin
Slaves are guilty, please punish Your Highness
what are you guilty of
The slaves are stupid, please express your highness
get out
The slaves retire
you go get her back
If you can't persuade you to come back, don't come back
Your Highness
Why is this called persuasion to come back?
I can't stand her yin and yang look
Your Highness
Yao girl is not yin and yang strange
This is how slaves serve their masters
Q&A
cautiously
no arrogance
What's wrong
what's wrong
I never treated her as a slave
go quickly
go
Your Highness
you see
is the month
Her Royal Highness takes tonic
Hot things that cannot be baited
Eat early
Into barley lotus seed duck soup
Substitute hibiscus meat with chub tofu
Apricot Blossom Goose Mixed Gorse
cut roe
go get her back
this time
go for me
Yes
Pinellia
three spoons
Gold Fang San
Zijin
look at my craft
do you look good
it's too expensive
The pattern is too dense
But still much better
make persistent efforts
Meng Shang food
Mr. Chen
Meng Shang food is polite
sir
ashamed
I vaguely remember when Hanying entered the palace for training
you have taught
It's right to call you Mr.
I didn't know you were visiting today
But what did the grandson command?
Lord Yang entered the palace today
Occasionally taste Miss Yao's Suzhou pastry
quite elegant
I want to call the kitchen cook in the house to copy it
I came here specially to ask for a recipe.
this little thing
I asked Zijin to write it out and send it over
He Lao, come to the door yourself
Then thank you Meng Shang for eating
I'll send someone to pick it up later
Okay
Mr. Chen walk slowly
Lord Shang Shi please forgive me
I'm also afraid of missing Zijin's good future
servant of israel
what a good future
Young and ignorant is a good thing
save a lot of worries
There are rules in the palace
Female officials have the dignity of female officials
People are in my food bureau all day
Take my shelter for a day
There is no reason to forcibly take it away
Don't do this stupid thing next time
I will not forgive
Yes
doesn't taste right
Your Highness
today's dish
Same as yesterday
what's wrong
try it yourself
How dare a slave
can't taste
Your Highness please express
Not the food is wrong
Your Highness is in a bad mood
Your Highness
same food
Diners have different moods
taste will be different
I think it's because the cooks don't care