(Is It Possible to Buy
Someone's Feelings?)
(Episode 8)
The moon is bright tonight.
It's the streetlamp.
Oh, I see.
- Goodbye.
- Right. Goodbye.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
To take the bus.
Are you telling me...
to send a woman home alone
on a bus at this hour?
Furthermore, just a few moments ago,
you had something huge
happen to you.
What do you mean by that?
Get in my car.
Don't make me into a bad person.
I'm more comfortable taking the bus.
I'll just take the bus.
No!
The bus station is right in front,
so you don't have to worry...
I drank.
What?
Are you going to let someone
who drank drive?
If you do,
you'll be charged for
aiding and abetting.
I was turning on the navigation.
Oh, right.
What's the address of the friend
you've been staying with?
- Why?
- My gosh.
Let's go to
your friend's house first.
I can call a chauffeur from there.
Oh, right.
- What's the address?
- You don't have to put it in!
I know how to get there.
It's not like I'm going to hurt you.
- Hey...
You can go first.
No. You can go first.
It's ladies bust.
What?
No, I meant "ladies first."
Ladies first.
First.
You can go first.
Your lips...
My lips?
What about them?
Wipe them off
because you have lipstick on them.
We're here. You can get off.
Thank you.
- What?
Wait...
How did you know I lived here?
You said you lived with Won Tak.
You said you didn't know
where he lived.
Well...
Oh, Won Tak!
Hi!
Did you come out
to throw out the trash?
What's going on?
Mr. Jin drank, so I drove.
What?
No. It's not that.
I wanted to take her home
because it's dangerous.
While we're on that topic,
can you drive me home?
I have a friend
that I've been staying with.
My friend's house.
Forget it.
Won Tak, you can go home and rest.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
No, Mr. Jin. You drank,
so you should go in and rest.
Won Tak will take me home.
Right?
Right.
Goodbye.
My gosh.
Gosh.
"My Won Tak."
"My Won Tak!"
After kissing me just a while ago,
how dare she go home
arm in arm with another guy?
I wasn't going to brush
my teeth today.
Why did I do it?
Why?
Hormones?
Time of ovulation?
Did his tears...
pull at my heartstrings?
No, that's not why.
Then could I be...
Can I go in?
Sure. You can.
Are you going somewhere?
It's an emergency,
so I need to go right now.
I see.
Are you sure everything's fine?
Yes, it is.
If something is bothering you,
just tell me.
That time at the police station
and even just a while ago...
I'm suspicious of you two.
What do you mean?
Are you...
Am I...
Are you being threatened by him?
What?
A threat doesn't have to be
that complicated.
Whether it's physical or emotional,
it's a threat if you feel afraid.
As your creditor,
he has the right to his money.
But he still can't mistreat you
like this.
Why would you drive
for that drunk scumbag?
Right. He's my creditor,
and I'm his debtor.
- What?
- You're right.
Hey. Are you even listening to me?
What?
Yes, I am.
Anyway,
even if he's your creditor,
don't let him walk all over you.
Do you need my help?
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
I'll let you know
if anything happens.
Get it together, Da Li.
I can't believe this.
Are they seriously in line
to see our exhibition?
They're not our creditors?
I even slapped my face...
to check if this was a dream.
My gosh. What's the matter with you?
This isn't a dream, right?
Hello, everyone.
Ms. Kim.
Congratulations.
Yes!
Gosh. This is a celebration!
By the way,
who do you think invited
the celebrities and influencers?
I'm sure they heard about it.
Right, they probably did.
She has become very famous
after the press conference.
Tell me about it.
Everyone was looking up
the jewelry and dress she wore.
- I had never seen a star before.
- Me neither.
They must've had a reason
why they came.
If they wear a certain dress
or carry a certain bag,
the sales for that brand
will skyrocket.
It's all related to money. Money.
Was it Tae Jin?
Look. As someone
who's working in the arts,
you shouldn't obsess
over money too much.
It's true that money is important,
but there are many precious things
in this world that can't be bought.
Remember that. Okay?
In any case, the press conference
made them come to our exhibition...
without our having to pay them.
Gosh, she must be worth
her weight in gold.
You are...
our lucky charm.
Please don't say that.
- Kim Da Li!
Please stop.
You guys did most of the work.
If you're going
to be humble like that,
we have no choice
but to cheer even more.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
- Kim Da Li!
Hello.
- Why...
- Let's have our meeting.
We're having a meeting today?
- Let's go.
- Seriously?
Hold on.
Where's my notebook?
Hey.
Why would you push me?
Then we'll plan
the Cheongsong Art Camp...
with Dondon F and B.
I'll send the materials
over to them as soon as I'm done.
I'll visit the orphanage myself.
What's next?
I'd like to offer
a certain service to our visitors.
In order to help parents
appreciate the pieces...
without having to worry
about their kids,
how about we make our own kids cafe?
That won't do.
Society may have become
more liberal now,
but what did you say? A kiss cafe?
Why do they need
to come here to kiss?
He meant kids cafe. Kids.
Was my pronunciation that bad?
That was a D. A kids cafe.
Not a kiss cafe. A kids cafe.
Next to contact is Keith Haring...
How can you kiss
without some contact?
Is that possible?
That's the artist's name.
Keith Haring.
Keith Haring?
What kind of name is that?
Are you sure it's his real name?
The Cheongsong workshop
that'll begin starting next week...
will be about poems
and famous paintings.
Romantic poets
such as Wordsworth, Byron...
And Keats.
Keats. Not kiss.
Keats.
- His name is Keats.
- Keats.
Gosh. I'm sorry.
Keats.
Keats. I got it.
Go on.
Did you get home safe yesterday?
What's wrong?
What is it this time?
Mr. Jin.
I'm listening.
Why are you doing this?
Doing what?
If you're uncomfortable
about what happened yesterday...
What's there to feel
uncomfortable about?
It's not like...
we're teenagers.
We're two grown adults.
After the exhibition,
I was exhausted.
And due to the vibe,
I made a mistake.
A mistake?
- Discourtesy?
- An incident?
Call it whatever you want,
but I'd like to apologize.
Let's pretend
like it never happened.
Can we go back to being
a friendly creditor and debtor?
Like you said, we're grown adults.
Let's be mature about it.
We have workers here...
and a ton of things to do.
Do you kiss men by mistake?
I never make mistakes with anything
that involves my mouth.
Eating, talking,
and the thing we did yesterday.
And what kind of mistake
is that intense...
It wasn't intense.
It wasn't a mistake for me.
So I want you...
to think it over again...
if the moment we shared yesterday...
was truly a mistake or not.
Goodness.
I'm sorry, sir.
This is quite a rough path.
I'm good.
This way, sir.
It's that house.
That's the house?
The rooftop of this building?
Yes.
That's where Joo Won Tak lives.
And Da Li is staying with him?
Yes.
- And...
- There's more?
The building owner is Jin Moo Hak.
The gamjatang guy?
Seeing how he's been living here
for a long time,
he probably had nothing
to do with how it turned out.
It seems to be a coincidence.
A coincidence?
He has a lot of ways
to get on my nerves.
(Art Galleries in Seoul)
No way.
Society may have become
more liberal now,
but what did you say? A kiss cafe?
Why do they need
to come here to kiss?
How can you kiss
without some contact?
It wasn't a mistake for me.
So I want you...
to think it over again...
if the moment we shared yesterday...
was truly a mistake or not.
Tae Jin?
Why are you here, Tae Jin?
I think I have
more questions than you.
Come on! When your dog poops,
you ought to clean that up!
- What is it?
- Get in.
- Come on! Goodness.
- What's wrong?
What is it?
Sir, please drive.
Go ahead.
Come on!
You can sit up now.
We turned the corner.
How did you know I was here?
Which would be harder for me?
To understand this situation...
or finding Won Tak's house?
A sponsorship association?
Young entrepreneurs meet up
when they have some spare time.
We go on yachts and play golf.
It's a social club.
And you know that social clubs
love a reason to get together.
They loved the idea of a sponsorship party
for Cheongsong.
As long as there's a good occasion,
they are willing to open up
their checkbooks.
Come up with a nice program.
It was really tough for me.
To prepare for this exhibition,
I visited a lot of people
to get sponsorships.
And they were
all my father's connections.
But all of them said
the economy was tough...
and they didn't have time.
It was hard
to even get a meeting with them.
To them, supporting
the artists wasn't the reason.
Your father was.
And after he passed away,
they saw no reason
to open their checkbooks.
There have been a lot of new players
while you were away.
I'll introduce them to you
one at a time.
Right. You're available
this weekend, right?
This weekend?
Yes. Come to our meeting
this weekend.
It will be a good way to meet them.
This is good.
What is it?
Do you already have plans?
I feel so pathetic.
I keep wondering
if I have always been this incompetent...
and if there's nothing
I can do on my own.
I keep getting help from you.
I hate myself.
Your father's death must have been
the hardest thing for you,
and you had to shoulder everything.
So you're not incompetent.
You gave up on your studies
which you loved...
and liquidated your assets.
You gave up so many things
not to give up the gallery.
Not everyone can do what you did.
You're doing a good job.
But where are we going now?
What is this?
It's the same passcode.
But I'm not sure if you remember it.
Let's talk inside.
I couldn't get rid of this house
because we picked it together.
But I couldn't live here either.
Nobody knows about this place
except for my secretary and me.
Which means it can be kept a secret.
Kept a secret?
Don't think too much about it.
It's just an empty house.
You can come and stay
whenever you need to...
and leave whenever you want.
Or even better, don't.
Da Li.
What do you want me to do?
Just do nothing...
after seeing you live somewhere
that can barely be called a house?
I'm not buying you a house.
I can't even do this for you?
Even if everyone else can,
you shouldn't.
What?
You left me in the rain...
as if I were some contagious person
a few days before our wedding.
Now that I have nowhere to go,
you bring me here out of sympathy?
To the house we were to live in?
Are you being considerate?
Did you think I would be touched
if the password hadn't changed?
How are you so cool about this?
Did it mean nothing to you?
If it meant nothing,
I would never have let you
be in this position to begin with.
When I saw you at the funeral,
I wanted to stay by your side.
Don't you understand?
I've been nervous and cautious...
to make sure that you wouldn't
get hurt or run away.
Not because I don't
have feelings for you,
but because I didn't want to use
the situation to my advantage.
Let's start over.
What?
For the past five years,
I have never forgotten you.
Every day was painful...
because of a choice I made.
You haven't gotten over me either,
am I wrong?
You're right.
I haven't.
How could I, when I heard
something like that?
But...
what you couldn't do five years ago,
you sure you can do it now?
Isn't the museum
different at this hour?
The pictures shine more brightly
after a good night's sleep.
Does that mean...
our dates will be here at this time
every day once we get married?
Every day?
You'll come here with me every day?
Of course.
I'll stick to you wherever you go,
like a piece of gum.
No matter what happens.
I'll follow you to the ends
of the earth, forever.
(Da Li)
Hey. I'm about to...
I'm about to head home.
Can I get anything on the way?
Where?
Just like when you were young.
What are you doing out here?
I just like this neighborhood.
It has a playground
and a convenience store nearby...
The night view
from the rooftop rocks.
Aren't all neighborhoods like that?
So come home and sleep.
You always sleep at the station
saying you have to work late.
I know it's because of me.
If you continue to do that,
I can't stay here.
Who said I was doing it for you?
That's what detectives do.
Did something happen today?
Nope.
For the first time in a while,
some guy kind of asked me out.
It felt good.
Kim Da Li's still got it.
And also...
some other guy...
proposed that I go live
somewhere really fancy.
Just a regular day.
One that can happen to anyone.
Did you see Jang Tae Jin?
Did that jerk ask you
to get back together with him?
To come live in his house?
What kind of...
So what did you say?
You didn't say yes, did you?
If he thinks less of you and thinks
it's easier to manipulate you...
now that Director Kim has passed,
I won't keep still.
Do you still have feelings for him?
People can't change. He's a no.
Tae Jin and I are over.
He's someone from my past.
When things get hard...
people say, "This too shall pass."
Pain, sadness...
That they'll all go away with time.
But if you think about it the other way,
that's a sad saying.
It means that the happiness...
and love you had...
will all disappear eventually.
Mom...
Dad...
Tae Jin...
Nothing is forever, right?
Won Tak.
Can you promise me you'll stay
for as long as you can?
Don't go away too fast.
If not, I might get too lonely.
Hey. Hold on.
Whenever I see you, you're quite...
friendly.
Maybe it's because you're
a police officer.
About Kim Da Li.
When you took her home,
- did she say anything?
- What would she say?
For example,
- something about me.
- No.
Don't answer me right away.
- Think about it for a second...
- She didn't.
Won Tak,
you always give such short answers.
You use water and electricity
in excess,
but I guess you don't like
to talk excessively.
What? Why? I'm just saying that
you seem friendly when you do that.
That's what I meant.
If you make Da Li
chauffeur you around again,
you're dead meat.
Why you...
What do you take
the Majang-dong Fighter for?
If you weren't Da Li's friend...
The night air is nice.
We see each other in the office
every day.
Did you have to tell me to come over
on the weekend too?
This is against labor laws.
Then move back in.
Right.
You should eat at home
at least once a week.
Ma'am. Your meal is ready.
Okay. Let's go.
Eat at home? Right.
Eating at home doesn't mean
it's homemade.
Do we have to taste test the food
at home too?
Who said this was a taste test?
I'm eating this because it's good.
We're not working.
With flavors like this,
we don't have to test it.
We can just go ahead
and open branches.
Gosh, this is incredible.
About the party.
When I heard it was
being hosted by Cheongsong,
I thought it would be incredible,
but I could've made better art
with my foot than what they had. Right?
I've never seen such a large group
of lunatics...
gathered in once place before.
A crazy brat kept screaming,
and they put a living person
in a coffin.
And people watched that
and clapped for them...
and drank.
It was quite a spectacle.
That's what art is like.
It's when people
who have nothing better to do...
show off their money.
Why would they show off their money?
My gosh!
You didn't feel anything...
upon seeing those masterpieces?
- What? Masterpiece?
Didn't you feel...
something burning up in here?
Something that can't be expressed
in words...
Something catches right here...
Get ready to catch this bone.
- Do you have indigestion?
- Want me to prick your fingers?
I have some medicine for GERD.
Go ahead and keep eating.
Whether I'm eating alone at home
or eating with you,
I'm still alone and lonely.
Why did I bother coming here?
My gosh.
If you're lonely, get married.
Married? With whom?
An Sang Tae's daughter?
An assemblyman is no big deal.
The one with money
has the upper hand.
- Oh, my. It's like Hawaii.
- Goodness.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- What is this?
- Just like this...
It's summer.
- You have something on your face.
- Gosh, stop.
Hold on.
Okay. I'll do it. I will.
Happy? I will.
The thing about marriage is...
you must marry someone you like.
Not someone that likes you.
What are you talking about?
What do you think?
He's talking nonsense.
Hey!
Take this with you.
(Jokbal Night Market)
We bought another one,
so you can have it at home.
This too.
Is it doenjang?
It's 100-year-old doenjang
from a head family.
Go home and make soup with it.
You should've wrapped it up
in a cloth.
This is cramping my style.
Hey.
How long are you going to leave
the gallery like that?
What?
If you keep hesitating like that,
someone might show up
and say they'll pay the two million.
What will you do then?
Kim Da Li won't be able
to keep the gallery.
Don't wear the poor girl down...
by giving her false hope.
Just tell her that Dondon
will take over.
What are you talking about?
You're not planning on breaking
even with the two million.
If you want the gallery,
take it from her now.
Do it before someone comes
and takes it first.
There's something on your jacket.
Bye.
Ms. Yeo. I need you
to look into something for me.
My brother?
He bought this land? Why?
You didn't know?
It's quite big.
Are they planning to
develop the area?
This is a limited development district.
You can say that it will
never get sold.
Or at least that's what I thought,
but it turned out I was wrong.
About 5 to 6 years ago, people
started selling and buying secretly.
But recently,
that has become more active.
Do you know when that started?
After Director Kim Nak Chun
passed away.
Right. You said that one time.
That there were many players
eyeing Cheongsong Gallery.
Where did you hear that from?
I guess Director Kim
was a pain in the neck...
for everyone who wanted
to develop the area.
The land for the museum
is located...
in the most important
part of the district,
and he had a lot of
social influence.
He even teamed up with NGOs
to make clear that...
he wouldn't let the area
get developed.
Apparently, he was very obstinate.
Kim Da Li won't be able to
keep the gallery.
If you want the gallery,
take it from her now.
Do it before someone comes
and takes it first.
But...
I did some further research
and looked at the land registers.
Do you remember the VIPs
at the opening party?
Their names came up often
on the list.
- You must've worked hard.
- Yes, of course.
It looks lovely.
- A goshiwon?
- Yes.
Why would you be interested in that?
I'm just curious about the cost.
It may vary
depending on the goshiwon.
But if you sell your scarf,
you could live there
for three months.
Ms. Na.
Did I ever offend you?
Why does it seem like
you always dislike me?
Have you ever thought...
that maybe the people around you...
were just overly friendly?
What?
Think about it.
Everyone's dying to help you out.
They brown-nose you
and act obsequiously.
Take the exhibition for example.
We pretty much prepared everything,
but only you were appreciated.
I envy you.
Thanks to your family name,
you have it easy.
I'm truly sorry
if that's how you feel.
But Ms. Na,
there's always more to everything
than meets the eye.
You're right.
There is.
Hello, you're here.
Mr. Jin and his secretary
are slightly running late,
so they'll join you later.
Okay.
This way.
Three Frogs of Sandro
and Leonardo...
isn't just a program
where we feed the kids.
We aim to help them understand
Leonardo da Vinci's work...
by experiencing it themselves.
That's our aim.
We want a more realistic...
Hello, Ms. Song. What is it?
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
They said we didn't pay
for Ham Yon Ji's appearance.
I looked into it.
They're a PR company
that invites celebrities...
to launch parties or opening events...
then uploads the photos on social media.
Apparently, Dondon had hired them.
What should I do?
- This area is a green belt.
- Come in.
This area is the most important.
- I...
- Sir.
Yes?
Is the meeting already over?
I was just about to join you guys.
Would you like some tea?
It's okay. You guys can leave.
Yes, sir.
Sit down.
What is it?
What has drained you like this?
Mr. Jin.
I'm listening.
Did you hire a PR company...
during our opening event?
Did you invite idol members,
YouTubers,
and influencers that we didn't?
That's true. Yes. I invited them.
What?
Gosh, I thought something horrible
had happened.
Gosh.
Opening events have more impact
than you think.
If you're launching a new product
or opening a new business,
the place should be teeming
with people.
And you should tell everyone
about it.
Although it wasn't cheap,
I hired them so that
we'd be off to a good start.
We actually benefited from that.
Look. People are lining up
to see the exhibition.
Did you also hire
the visitors on that day?
Yes, I did. That didn't cost much.
So what if people hear the news?
You need to leave
behind solid proof.
Just line a few of them
and take some good photos,
and it'll look like
the place is teeming with people.
Why are you doing this?
Isn't it obvious?
To make money, of course.
Do you think I had money to waste?
Also, this is a business tactic...
that even vendors use to lure kids.
It's Business 101.
You make it sound like
it's some incredible tactic.
An art gallery isn't a business.
Why not? The visitors have
to purchase their tickets.
What's wrong? Does "business"
sound too lowly and vulgar?
Is your pride hurt...
since it's not sophisticated
or refined?
That's not what I mean.
You're deceiving the visitors.
- What a load of garbage.
- Mr. Jin.
I thought you had learned your lesson,
but I was wrong.
Fine, then.
Let's forget about the profit
since you always had...
more than enough money.
But what about those art pieces
that you cherish so much?
Would you be content
with appreciating the pieces...
while having a party
and drinking wine?
Are you okay
not having any visitors?
Is it all right
if no one else sees them?
Didn't you say the artists
worked on those pieces for years?
Didn't you guys prepare...
for the exhibition
while pulling all-nighters?
Then shouldn't you gather
as many people as possible?
This work is by Ms. Choi Jung Hwa.
If you look here,
she used everyday garbage...
to create art.
And this one...
A dark and vacant art gallery...
is no different
from a charnel house.
I am aware that everything
you're saying is right.
But why don't I want to accept it?
It's true...
that we should do everything
in our power...
to show these great pieces
to everyone.
And sure. Money is important.
However,
I refuse to give money
that much power.
And it's neither
because of my pride...
nor because I'm sophisticated.
I just hate the fact that all
the hard work my workers...
have put in was disregarded
because of money.
It's also a shameless act
to all the other galleries.
If you were truly proud
of what you did,
then you would've told me about it.
Am I right?
What if that wasn't why?
What if I just wanted
to see you happy?
What if I wanted...
to see you smiling from ear to ear
like you did in the Netherlands?
Then you should've found
another way to do it.
Hey.
- Come here, you scumbag!
- Darn it!
- Hey!
- Hey, you scumbag!
Hey!
You little...
Let me go!
You scumbag!
Hey, don't you know who I am?
I'm Kim Si Hyung,
the eldest son
of the Cheongsong family!
Exactly.
Why would someone so well-off...
borrow money then hide?
Why would you enrage
poor commoners like us?
Darn it.
It's not even that much money.
I could easily get that money
from selling the gallery's land.
Poor commoners like us
wouldn't know that.
But one thing we know
is that you're dirt poor.
What did you say?
I'll give you one week.
Bring me my money, goods,
or a goodbye letter.
Make sure you prepare
one of these three by then.
Let's go.
Hey, move aside.
What?
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
Is this it?
Hey, don't we need to order
more beans and other materials?
Have they not given us
the money yet?
The gallery is going
to be in charge...
of the orders and sales.
They took the ledger
and the card statement.
Who?
What? The new director.
Has she gone crazy?
What about...
Where is it?
Where did you hide it?
Where in the world is it?
Hey.
Who are you to take the ledger?
Answer me.
How dare you try to run
the cafe yourself?
Mr. Kim, that's enough!
Stay out of this, old lady.
This has nothing to do with you!
Watch your mouth.
What did you say?
You can go. I'll be fine.
Okay.
Legally speaking,
the cafe belongs to the gallery.
I'll take care of your dwindling cafe.
Why is that a problem?
Your father...
gave me that cafe,
so I could learn
how to run the gallery.
Over you, who ran away
from your father and the gallery...
because a guy dumped you!
I guess you don't know
the full story.
But this gallery
was supposed to be mine!
It's very different
from what he told me.
You got expelled from school
because of a drug problem.
And your father disowned you.
As you had no money
or nothing to live for,
he wanted you to run the cafe,
so you'd turn over a new leaf.
That's what he told me.
- What?
- You get funds...
to run the cafe every month.
But I don't know where you spend
the funds or how much you make.
The ledger is a mess,
and there are no reports on this.
My father probably...
overlooked this because you were
his nephew, but not anymore.
If you don't want that,
you can pack up and leave.
- How dare you?
- Si Hyung.
The gallery is in bad shape.
This isn't just my problem.
It's also yours.
And our family's as well.
You have to help me.
Who can I trust right now,
if not my family?
Exactly.
Hand over the gallery to me,
and just leave. Go ahead.
I'll make sure you get your cut
once I sell this off.
- What?
- Hey. Let's be honest.
You think it makes sense
for a girl to inherit the assets?
What else did you do
other than having him as your dad?
Let me warn you.
Don't provoke me.
If you do,
I don't know what I'll do next!
Got that?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Before your father passed away,
he at least pretended to work.
Now, he's just lost it.
Some people express
their sadness through rage.
I'm sure Si Hyung was just upset.
If he was decent enough...
Fine. He must be.
I'll take care of this.
It's all right.
Okay.
Did he say he was off duty today?
Won Tak, was today your day off?
Did he go to the convenience store?
(Won Tak)
- Hey.
- Are you home?
Yes.
I can't go home tonight.
Make sure to lock up.
Ms. Kim?
(Dali and Cocky Prince)
You're letting me crash here
for the night.
I should earn my keep.
It'll make me feel better.
How can I not worry about you?
Are you two living together?
Thank you for your service today.
You got that wrong.
I'm with the gallery.
And you're the sponsor.
I found out that Dondon F and B...
has been buying a lot of land
around the gallery.
It is suspicious.
Shouldn't you give me an excuse
or explain what happened?
Consider it a warning.
Stay away from Da Li
when I'm still being civil.