(What's Thicker Than Blood?)
(Episode 11)
Well,
when will your friend, Won Tak,
come back to Seoul?
I think it will take
two or three more days,
seeing how Si Hyung doesn't know
anyone down there.
Oh, no.
I can clear this.
I'll put it in the recycle bin over there.
Then...
do you want to sleep over...
at my place tonight?
What?
No. I don't have any ulterior motive.
Just like the other night,
I will sleep in the living room
where the TV is.
And you can sleep in my bed.
I just want to be with you.
I'm serious. I won't try anything.
I won't even touch you.
So you don't have to worry about it.
Why must I sleep over at your place
if you're not going to try anything?
- What?
- Why won't you even touch me?
What?
You must be quite conservative
in that area.
What? I didn't mean it like that.
It's okay. We don't have to rush.
Just let me know
when you are ready and comfortable.
I can wait.
Who said I wasn't ready?
I'm totally ready.
Both physically and mentally.
I'm totally comfortable with it.
So we don't have to wait.
Hold on!
I need more time.
Chak Hee.
What happened to your face?
Did something happen?
You live in a terrible neighborhood.
The cab driver
couldn't find his way.
What?
What is she doing here?
Are you two living together?
Don't be absurd.
She's temporarily staying upstairs
due to personal matters.
Which is?
That's none of your business.
What happened to you?
Did someone beat you up?
Can I stay here for a few days?
Where do you think you're going?
Gosh.
Do you have ramyeon? I'm famished.
Unbelievable.
You barge in here
in the middle of the night,
and now, you want ramyeon?
What happened to you?
Who did that?
Tell me.
I got in a fight with some chick
at the grocery store.
I grabbed the last grapefruit,
but she claimed that it was hers.
How ridiculous.
What?
Don't worry. I won.
I gave her a bloody nose.
You went grocery shopping
in that outfit?
Then did you expect me
to wear something formal?
Where's the grapefruit?
Well...
I gave it to her in exchange
for giving her a bloody nose.
I yielded.
What is all this?
Is today a special day?
No.
What?
Come on. What special day?
For me?
For us? I mean...
I mean... For me.
I don't know!
I wasn't going to do anything!
Why are you here?
This is his house.
I was just worried.
About whom? Me or him?
Of course, him...
It's you, of course.
It's getting late.
Don't you think your parents will worry?
You should give them a call.
- Right.
- Didn't you hear what I said?
I'm going to stay here for a few days
until my wound heals.
After all,
I don't want my parents to worry.
I'm not sure if you should stay
at a young man's house.
Your parents will be worried sick
if they find out.
That's none of your business.
I don't know
what's going on with you,
but how about you come with me
to the rooftop?
We're both girls.
I think that'll be better.
No, thanks.
I'm going to stay with him.
That's why I came here.
Chak Hee, get out.
I've put up with you enough.
Get out!
What? Why do I need
to sleep upstairs...
when this is my house?
Gosh. But I was so ready.
- Ready for what?
- My gosh.
I don't want to see your face
when I lie down.
So you should sleep
in the living room,
and I'll sleep...
over there.
Do you want to die?
Look. As you can see,
I was spoiled, growing up.
I can't sleep on this hard floor.
Okay?
Darn it!
Do you really want to die?
Oh, come on!
Sleep here?
What is this?
I smell his scent.
Isn't it rude to do that
on someone else's bed?
What's it to you?
He's not even yours.
What are you doing?
Didn't you just say
that it was rude to do that?
I have a herniated disc.
Gosh, she's so annoying.
Gosh.
For the past two days,
I got up on the wrong side
of the bed.
It was worse for me.
I want to grab
a stranger by the collar...
and get in a fight right now.
I want to do worse.
So be quiet and go to bed.
I don't even want
to hear you breathing.
If I hear you snoring, I'll...
What? What will you do?
How can anyone sleep that quietly?
Gosh.
Do you want to die?
Fine.
Goodnight.
This is all because of Jin Moo Hak.
If it wasn't your brother,
then who could it have been?
How in the world
did that wench find out?
I heard he was the one
who helped out...
with the exhibition
and the supplies.
Maybe they fell for each other.
In any case,
I won't let this slide.
I put in so much effort
and spent a hefty sum on this.
How dare he ruin my plan?
What's it to you
what happens to him?
You guys aren't even related!
What was that about?
What about Moo Hak?
What will you do to him?
You idiot.
How could you call yourself
my daughter?
I introduced you to Jang Tae Jin,
but you couldn't even seduce him.
You fell for that idiot,
so I let you be.
But you also failed to seduce him,
and look what you've done.
I enrolled you
in a prestigious school,
gave you a good job,
and helped your sales.
In exchange
for helping you become...
a decent human being,
you should've at least
found yourself a good man!
None of that was for me.
What?
You were just using me.
It wasn't about me.
You wanted to satisfy your clients.
It was all out of greed!
How dare you?
What kind of guy would like me?
Even my own dad mistreats me,
so who in the world would love me?
How dare you?
Darn it!
Are you really not going to work?
Then at least call them
that you are sick or something.
You can't just skip work
without any notice.
They will be worried about you.
It's fine. My dad got me that job.
No one will care.
She has it easy, doesn't she?
Stop it.
Then get up. I'll drop you off.
No.
Chak Hee.
I'm not going back now.
I told you I wanted to stay here
for a few days.
Can't you at least let me do that
after what you did to my dad?
(Fifty dollars)
Did you get that bruise
because of what I did?
Did your father hit you?
- Chak Hee.
- Moo Hak.
I know that my dad is awful,
a corrupt politician,
and a hypocrite.
That's all true about him.
I don't deny that.
But he is still my father.
Did you think about me even once?
Were you reminded of me
even for a moment?
That's how insignificant
I am to you.
I feel so pathetic.
Blood is thicker than water indeed.
She's An Sang Tae's daughter?
Anyway, I doubt he will
just sit back and take the hit.
I'm talking about An Sang Tae.
I knew what I was getting into.
I at least bought some time.
Oh, right. What happened
to Si Hyung? He disappeared?
He just disappeared.
He somehow knew
we were coming and vanished.
He left behind all of his belongings
at the lodging.
He is okay, right?
- Hey. Wake up.
- Hey.
- Come on.
- What?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
Hey. It's too early for this.
Hey. Let go of me. What is this?
I'm Kim Si Hyung, the oldest son
of the Cheongsong family!
What?
Who is this?
This is An Sang Tae.
I see.
You came here to get me out of here.
"A hard worker for my district,
always jolly around the year!"
"Vote for me, An Sang Tae!"
You are not in your right mind.
- What?
- Kim Si Hyung. You.
Did you know your stuff turned up?
It turned up? Where? Who found it?
The police are out there,
trying to catch you.
They are looking for you
with their eyes peeled.
Of course,
I don't plan on
handing you over to them.
Hey. Do you want to disappear
from the face of the earth...
quietly?
Or...
will you do what I tell you to do?
Expect a call by 2 p.m.
Get him to wash up
and be on standby.
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
With this, we can get
the public on our side.
And we'll be able to get the gallery
to shut down quickly.
There is a top priority
throughout all this.
It's that Da Li cannot get hurt from this.
Find another way.
You can see what's in front of you,
but not the whole picture.
To deepen a relationship
between lovers,
they need obstacles and hardships.
Use this opportunity...
to show her clearly...
how scary this world is.
And show her that the person...
who can protect her
in this scary world...
is you, Jang Tae Jin.
Only you.
Only then,
she will not take you for granted.
That arrogant wench.
How dare she come after me?
(Jokbal Night Market)
People's desperate wishes such as
longevity, wealth, and honor...
are often the subjects
of our folk paintings.
So depending on the subjects,
the interpretation can differ.
Peonies represent wealth and honor.
Pomegranates represent fertility
in families.
Then what about ducks?
They represent good marriages.
Marriages?
Marriages...
Birds in our folk art...
mostly represent peace
and happiness of marriages.
They always include a pair
of male and female birds.
Then...
does she want me to die as a bachelor?
All good now. Right?
Moo Hak is inside, right?
- Sir.
- Let go of me!
Sir.
Hey.
How could you do this to me?
How?
I... Darn it.
I begged you.
How could you stab me
in the back, you jerk?
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
You handed over the files.
You don't think I know that?
You got your secretary...
to check the land registers!
Is this because you lost your chance
at this green belt deal?
How dare you keep
playing dumb with me?
I should be furious with you!
Sir.
I told her to get me
the land registers.
So what?
We invested a boatload of money
into that.
Don't I get to look into
how things are going?
I handed over the files to Kim Da Li?
Who said that?
Why must I do that for her?
Don't forget who I am.
I only care about making money!
You are the one who drove this deal
to the drain along with our land...
and the construction company.
How dare you put that on me?
- You're not going to drop the act?
- It really wasn't you?
- No.
- He's lying.
He's the only one
who could have leaked it.
Assemblyman An looked into it.
But he was the only one...
Jang Tae Jin knew it too.
You two bought land behind my back.
And you bought
a construction company.
I heard everything from Jang Tae Jin.
Are you sure the green belt deal
was confidential?
Otherwise, how would
Jang Tae Jin know that?
Dad.
You cannot believe what he says.
I'm serious.
He came to our restaurant
and grabbed me by my collar.
What more do you need to believe me?
He told me to quit dreaming...
about that woman and the gallery.
You still think I did it?
And not him?
What's going on?
Dad, he's not telling the truth!
Jang Tae Jin
couldn't have done that.
Who's ordering An Sang Tae around?
- What?
- Who's the mastermind behind this?
You have to know that
to determine how to handle this.
That...
- You sure it wasn't you?
- It wasn't!
If it turns out to be you,
I will kick you out with nothing.
You will be saying goodbye
to Dondon forever.
Can you promise me that?
Do whatever you want.
Jin Ki Chul.
Yes, Father.
Do you really...
have a card in your hand?
Yes, of course.
An Sang Tae said he could
handle this soon.
The green belt isn't over.
If something goes wrong again,
I'll be saying goodbye to not just Dondon
but also you.
You'll go back to being Oh Ki Chul.
Understood?
Yes.
Darn it.
Jang Tae Jin, that jerk...
What the heck is he thinking?
How are you going to deal
with this later?
You should've just told the truth.
Find out who An Sang Tae
has been meeting with.
- What?
- And just in case,
find out whether
there is some sort of connection...
between Jang Tae Jin
and An Sang Tae.
Between Jang Tae Jin
and An Sang Tae?
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
The petition bulletin board
on the Blue House website...
That must have been Ms. Kim, right?
How can she reject
such a golden opportunity?
The land itself must cost
tens of millions of dollars.
Then do you want an apartment
to take place of our gallery?
You can always build the gallery
somewhere else.
Somewhere else.
Where?
Where do you think would be good?
Somewhere you can go
only on holidays or weekends?
Somewhere with
a famous restaurant nearby...
so that you can drop by
on your way to the restaurant?
Somewhere the subway doesn't run...
so that there are more
squirrels and birds than visitors?
I'm just saying,
from Ms. Kim's perspective,
that option could have been better.
Frankly, with that money,
an entire generation
wouldn't have to work.
Can you understand that decision?
I honestly can't.
That's why they say
blood is thicker than water.
Like father, like daughter.
She is just like the late Director.
You know...
she might be holding out.
Land doesn't rot.
The longer you hold out,
the more expensive the land gets.
What?
If not that,
maybe she'll marry Jang Tae Jin...
and build a Segi Tower?
I think Ms. Kim likes Mr. Jin
more than Jang Tae Jin.
Jin Sang?
- That Jin Sang?
- Mr. Jin.
Listen. During the event
with the Three Frogs Restaurant,
didn't you see some sort of spark
between those two?
You could see it in their eyes.
Their eyes...
How dare you?
Ms. Kim would suit
literally anyone else better.
Sometimes you're so funny.
Come on.
I swear they go well together.
In what way?
They go well together.
Stop.
Is that so?
Do you think I go well with Mr. Jin?
Well...
These are some ideas about
some profit-generating projects.
And this is my feedback on
the exhibition plan.
I changed the overall direction.
Please take a look.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Hwang was just being funny.
You're not upset, are you?
Why would I be?
To hear that I go well
with someone so decent?
I think she's upset.
Mr. Jin is knowledgeable,
handsome, gentle.
He's also popular among women.
I'm a lot inferior, compared to him.
Ms. Kim.
Being too humble is the worst.
If Mr. Jin were to hear that,
he would call you Jin Sang.
- It was right there.
- Don't.
I can upload the recruitment ad
for the new intern today, right?
Of course. Please, do.
(Lawyer Cha)
Lawyer Cha.
(Notice of permission
to pay inheritance tax)
(Amount of tax to be paid:
285,673 dollars)
I proofread everything,
but you should read it again.
It's more money
than you imagined, isn't it?
Yes.
You have a way of getting it?
I'll find one.
Why did you mess with
the green belt case?
That was rash.
This will make it even harder
to get a loan from the bank.
If you don't do anything,
it might be auctioned off.
- Excuse me?
- I'll look for all other options,
but you should also go see
the adults in your family...
and ask for help whatever it takes.
It's better than asking strangers.
(International arrivals)
(Thank you for being born.)
Write your celebrity fashion article
next time and follow me.
Are you Kim Hong Chun?
I heard your relationship
with your brother went sour enough...
for you not to attend his funeral.
What are you doing here?
Is it about the museum site
development rights?
The new director Kim Da Li
did something big this time.
No wonder she's the heiress
of the Cheongsong family.
The heiress of the Cheongsong family.
I'm Song Chang Wook
from Jeil Newspaper's Cultural Bureau.
I'm also well acquainted
with Kim Si Hyung.
I'm sure you have a lot to say.
Feel free to speak your mind.
He left half an hour ago,
so he should be there any minute.
I've already called the journalists,
so the media will side with him
in no time,
and we can go back to our real job.
Who is this?
Kim Hong Chun?
Kim Da Li of Cheongsong Gallery...
(Kim Da Li of Cheongsong Gallery
is an adopted child?)
(Will an inheritance fight
begin for the Cheongsong family?)
is not a biological child...
of the late Kim Nak Chun.
She doesn't have a single drop
of Cheongsong's blood.
Kim Da Li was adopted.
Are you watching this video right now?
I knew it. Fate is on our side.
It never abandoned me.
How dare that adopted kid
get so cheeky with me?
You need to stop this now.
What do you mean, stop?
She needs to take a good blow now.
That way, she'll never dare
to get cheeky again.
Wait, did you know...
she had been adopted all along,
yet you helped that girl...
Don't you understand?
You need to stop Kim Si Hyung now!
- Stop the car.
- Why?
Why? We're almost there.
He told us to turn back.
What?
Man, what is this?
Tell them
to take the articles down now.
Upload another provocative article
or expose a scandal!
Do whatever it takes.
Yes, sir.
Where is Mr. Kim Hong Chun now?
When did he return to Korea?
Well, he...
(Tae Jin)
You can't find
Hamilton's "Smoke Series"...
even if you wanted to find them.
Let's pack up
all of Mr. Moon's works too.
All right.
The market isn't doing very well
so that can't be anywhere enough.
I need to pay the inheritance tax
and pay Mr. Jin back too.
Where are Mr. Shin Sang Woo's works?
You're selling
Mr. Shin Sang Woo's works too?
Over there.
My precious babies.
- Please be very cautious.
- Of course.
You have to be
extra careful with this one.
- This one.
- Please take this.
- Okay.
- That's it. Please be careful.
Yes, please don't
let it get scratched.
Please watch the edges.
The edges, please.
They took all of our best artworks.
These works are priceless.
Hey, you need to stop this now!
Uncle.
I'm not your uncle!
How dare a lowly girl like you...
try to sell off Cheongsong's assets?
What are you doing?
Put those back where they belong.
Now!
This one.
These are under seizure now.
If you take these,
it'll be considered theft.
I made myself clear.
Nothing that belongs
to Cheongsong will leave this place,
not even a pencil.
Ms. Song, did you know
Ms. Kim was adopted?
My gosh, how did she manage
to keep this so quiet?
So what will happen to us now?
Who should we put our faith in?
Good grief.
Can you hear anything?
Please! Keep it down.
You kicked Si Hyung out...
and became the director
of the gallery.
Does this make you feel like
you've become a part of the family?
Even beasts out in nature know...
how to be grateful
when someone saves them.
It hasn't been long
since my brother passed.
You sold off the house first,
didn't you?
And now you dare
to get into the storage...
of the gallery.
Where did you learn
to show such cheeky behavior?
Uncle, it's not like that...
If he took in
a lowly girl like you...
and brought you up to this day,
the least you can do is
behave like a decent human.
Everything you did overseas
wasn't anything important,
yet you didn't care
how sick your dad had been.
You let him be found dead
on that icy cold floor.
How do you call yourself a human?
This is...
why bloodlines are important.
This is why I was against it...
when he wanted to adopt you.
Even when we adopt a dog,
we make sure we find out
everything we can about it.
How unlucky do you have to be...
for your own parents to abandon you?
Ever since you became
a part of this family,
nothing went well for Cheongsong.
Right? My sister-in-law
suddenly passed away.
Then my loving brother and I...
became more distant
than two strangers.
And all those assets we had!
All we have now is this gallery.
Did you know...
my brother...
had to kneel down...
before Tae Jin?
Over his entire life,
that man never asked anyone for help.
But he did that before a man
who's young enough to be his son...
in front of a huge crowd.
He had to kneel down. He knelt!
It's all because
of someone useless like you.
I'll never forgive you.
If you have a speck of conscience,
you need to resign.
Don't bring more shame
to our family...
as you bring us
into the center of their gossip.
My gosh, I can't believe that man.
Is he really our director's brother?
People say words can kill.
How can he say that to her face?
This is why money is frightening.
Why do you think this happened?
It's because of money.
Do you think Ms. Kim is okay?
- Wait, give her a minute.
- Hello?
Who?
- Yes, right. Reporter Kang.
- Hello?
Yes, hello.
I'm sorry. Ms. Kim isn't here.
- She's out of her office.
- Yes.
- Please call again later.
- Yes, right.
Tae Jin, don't do this.
Please look at me. I beg you.
Please...
Can you really do as I ask?
I can.
And you'll do anything?
Anything.
Then...
be reborn...
as the real daughter
of the Cheongsong family.
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message.
Your call will be charged
after the beep.
It's me. Don't worry about anything.
I'm figuring everything out.
This will die down soon.
Da Li.
No matter what anyone says,
you're your father's daughter,
a member of the Cheongsong family.
I'll make it so.
I'll right this wrong
no matter what it takes.
So please don't hide
and pick up the phone.
I see. A van?
(Kim Si Hyung)
I see.
(A van)
And the license plate number?
I see.
Then could you send me
the CCTV footage right now?
Thank you. Goodbye.
That scumbag.
Where are you?
Did you hear?
- Did you?
- What is it this time?
The Cheongsong family...
is going to have
a huge inheritance feud.
- What?
- Did you know...
that Kim Da Li was adopted?
Gosh. She didn't look like...
someone from the orphanage.
Do people from the orphanage
need to have a mark or something?
Hey, I'm sorry.
Darn it.
I made a mistake.
What's so bad about that?
(Uncorrupted Police)
Pick up.
She's not at the gallery.
She also left her phone.
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
(Kim Nak Chun)
I didn't want to come here.
Because it'd feel like
I really lost you.
But I had nowhere else to go.
Did you meet...
Mom?
- Me too!
- I'll give you two.
I'll give you two.
Gosh, there you were.
Here we go.
Hey, kid. Have a bite, will you?
You need to eat.
You haven't eaten in days.
You can read again in a bit.
Goodness.
You should never take her books,
or she'll go mad.
Are you okay?
- Hop in.
- See you again.
- Three, four.
- Hurry up.
Did you have fun? Go in.
We're missing a kid.
- What?
- You are?
What's wrong?
Does the one-eyed monster scare you?
Should I hit him for you?
No!
Don't do that!
I feel sorry for him.
No one...
loves him.
Just like me.
So she knows how to talk.
(Kim Nak Chun)
All right.
I looked through the reviews.
And many of them complimented...
on how fresh and non-smelly
the meat was.
I think replacing
the broth regularly helped a ton.
Let's come up with a side dish...
that's suitable
for families who eat out.
- Okay.
Gosh, I should wear a diaper
to my meetings from now on.
They talk so much.
That's rich coming from you.
She's still not picking up.
Sir.
("Will the Cheongsong Family
Have an Inheritance Feud?")
(It's been revealed that Kim Da Li,
the only daughter...)
(of the late Kim Nak Chun,
was adopted.)
She was adopted?
I knew it.
Rumor had it that...
her family rejected Jang Tae Jin.
But it was actually the opposite.
She was rejected
for having been adopted.
Right.
Who'd want a daughter-in-law
who was adopted?
Exactly.
This is really sweet.
Are you serious?
Don't point that knife at me!
Gosh. You shouldn't be picky
and just eat what I give you.
Don't be so upset, Father.
Then how will this pan out?
Will she lose the suit?
Of course not. She may be adopted,
but she's still his daughter.
It's legally acceptable.
Of course.
Even though we're not related,
I consider Moo Hak my son.
I consider myself his mother.
Still...
I'm not sure if I want
my daughter-in-law to be adopted.
Isn't she better than Moo Hak?
Oh, please.
He never mentioned wanting
to get married,
so don't get ahead of yourself.
Darn it.
Hello, Mother. I was wondering...
if Da Li visited
the orphanage today.
I see.
Could you give me a call
if you find her?
Bye.
What are you doing here?
Is Da Li in there?
And why do you ask?
I couldn't get in touch with her...
ever since she left the gallery
this afternoon.
If she's not here, forget it.
Don't act like you care.
What did you say?
You dumped her all those years ago.
What are you doing here now?
Why? Did you realize
that there was no one like her?
Do you want her back now
because you dumped her?
Did you think...
she would welcome you
with arms open when you came back?
Don't fool yourself.
We'll take care of ourselves.
- You can just get lost.
- Stick to what you have to do.
I'll do what I have to do.
And Da Li is my business.
That jerk.
Should I escort you home?
Let's go back to the gallery
one last time.
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
(Mr. Jin)
Ms. Kim!
I know that you're here.
Come on out now.
Ms. Kim.
Where is she?
Where is she hiding?
What is this?
I couldn't reach you today.
I get that you are angry.
But were you trying to drive me mad?
Chak Hee is just a friend.
I don't see her as a woman.
She just barged in
because something happened.
I can't tell you right now.
But I'll tell you everything later.
I'm not telling you
not because I'm hiding something.
It's just her privacy. I'm serious.
I swear. I am telling you the truth.
Did you not see the news today?
The news?
Oh, that. The one about inheritance.
You don't have to worry about that.
You are his daughter.
Your uncle has no right to claim...
the inheritance should be voided.
It will just take some time
and be a hassle. That's all.
You won't lose your inheritance.
Don't worry.
It's not that.
I...
Was there something else?
I was adopted.
Did you not hear that?
I did.
That doesn't matter to you?
Should it?
Well, my brother isn't
biologically related either.
He's the son of the woman
my father is living with.
Well, he's still my brother.
But so what?
Just because you are adopted,
does that change who you are?
Did you not answer my calls
because of that?
Are you a kid?
What is this nonsense?
You got me all worried and anxious.
Ms. Kim.
When I was young,
I prayed every single day
my dad would die, not my mom.
Come here.
- Sir, how much longer must I wait?
- What?
Let's go to Mount Nam
for some fresh air after work today.
Watch your hands!
- I know you like it.
- Stop it.
I'll buy you a bag.
A designer handbag at that.
(Dondon Gamjatang)
A certain father
who is considered...
successful and respected
by society...
hits his daughter.
What was that about?
What about Moo Hak?
What will you do to him?
And a certain son...
changed his last name
to become a son of a rich man...
when his birth father
was alive and well.
I...
You know how hard I tried
to be Dad's real son.
I submitted the application for
permission to change remittance...
as soon as family law changed.
Do you think it was easy going from
Oh Ki Chul to Jin Ki Chul?
That...
was denying my identity.
And a certain daughter...
is risking everything she has...
for her late father.
Can you...
sell your father?
I get that you love money.
So will you sell your father?
The gallery is my father.
That's my father.
In our world, the relationships
with our parents...
are as diverse as the paintings.
That's my point.
Blood doesn't make our relationships
with our parents ideal and normal...
unlike our preconceptions.
Besides,
I sort of knew.
How?
Well,
I'm really sorry...
to say this about your late father.
You look nothing like your father.
I didn't see any resemblance at all.
Even if you were to take after your mom,
this just didn't add up.
Gosh. Come on.
You look nothing like him.
Gosh.
Oh, boy.
You're still a kid.
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
It's fine.
Wait, your crying face...
does resemble him a little.
Continue with everything...
as planned.
(Dali and Cocky Prince)
This exhibition was that big of a hit?
- What are you doing?
- How do you call yourself a human?
I just...
He's just a puppet boss
of the gallery's cafe.
Don't you think he has someone
with great power behind him?
I'm more than capable...
of turning this situation around.
Who do you think you are
to ruin my son's future?
I warned you, didn't I?
Wake up from your dream.
What can I say...
to console you?