(Does Everyone Become a Grown-Up?)
(Episode 9)
Goodness gracious.
Who was that?
What's all this?
Ms. Kim?
What are you...
My gosh, are you all right?
You startled me.
You can't walk into someone's house
without making a noise.
I'm sorry. The door was opened,
so I thought...
Anyway, what is it?
Why are you here?
And why is the house a mess?
I thought the thief came back.
It's all right.
Everything is okay now.
Why did the thief make a mess
without taking anything?
Maybe someone just pulled a prank.
It's hardly a prank.
The tenant came back,
so the thief ran off.
We'll get going.
Goodbye, then.
No.
A cat jumped at me. I mean it.
All right.
I'll make sure
I lock the doors well.
Bye.
Are you all right?
Yes.
They said they would investigate,
but I'm not sure if it'll go well
because nothing is gone.
Does anybody know
that you're staying here?
Among the staff in the gallery, I mean.
Among the staff in the gallery?
No, no one knows.
Is that so?
Why?
No, it's nothing.
Take another look.
See if anything went missing.
I don't think so...
Why did they make a huge effort
to go through everything?
What about my tenant?
Isn't he going to come?
He's on emergency duty,
so I didn't tell Won Tak.
I didn't want him to worry.
I see.
Then you should clean up
and come to my place.
You should eat dinner too.
Pack up what you need and come.
No, I'm fine now,
so you should go home, Mr. Jin.
No crazy man would
leave a woman he likes alone...
in a house with a broken lock.
You can be unbelievably selfish.
Don't be so stubborn
and come with me.
How did it go?
- It's not there.
- What?
I can't do this anymore.
Da Li almost caught me!
You said she'd be
out of the city on a meeting!
I'm guessing it got canceled.
Why are you taking things this far
to get that thing?
If it looks like a stamp,
I doubt it's a lump of gold.
Is it...
Uncle.
If you committed a crime,
you should pay for it.
No, Uncle.
I don't care what happens to me.
But what about the gallery?
What about my family?
Darn it, this is driving me insane.
She couldn't have thrown that away.
You've gone crazy.
Wait.
Why are you looking for that
in Ms. Kim's place?
What did you do to her?
What did I do?
My uncle brought this
upon his family.
He shouldn't have been
that stubborn!
(Mr. Ha)
Darn it, this is driving me insane.
- Darn it!
- What are you doing? Pick up!
(Mr. Ha)
(Power Off)
Hey, do you have any money?
- You're a psycho.
- What?
Let me make this clear.
I don't know what you did,
but it has nothing to do with me.
Don't ever call me again.
If you do,
I'm going straight to the police.
Gong Ju. Hey!
Has she gone crazy?
Hey. You!
What did you just say?
You're going where?
I was way too nice, wasn't I?
Why?
Do you think I'm just saying that?
Should I go there now?
Let's find out
if they'll trust the barmaid...
or the druggie.
Be quiet.
I can't believe
he considered you his nephew.
You are...
less than human.
What do you expect from me?
What the heck do you expect from me?
Darn it.
You can put these on.
What are you doing? Come in.
Then please excuse me.
Sure.
Right. The repairman will come
to fix the door in the morning,
so don't worry.
You're not a picky eater, right?
No.
It's quite late,
so I'll cook a simple meal.
(Fifty dollars)
I have a painting in my living room too.
It's nice and big.
And I admire it every day.
Morning and night.
(Fifty dollars)
That's it.
The painting I told you about.
I see.
Sit down. The chair won't bite.
That's just a pot for doenjang.
It's not some fancy porcelain
from the past.
I don't have such things here.
But the wallpaper and the curtains
are top-notch.
Art is nothing special.
Then why did Cheongsong Gallery
send you a chamber pot?
When I asked, they said it was
a token of gratitude for the loan.
A chamber pot!
Gosh.
- What?
It's a pot for doenjang.
I'm just worried it'll stink.
Gosh, that's hot.
Here we go.
Didn't you say you were going
to cook something simple?
It's simple.
I see no gujeolpan,
braised short ribs,
or octopus sticks.
Dig in before it gets cold.
This is because of the promise
you made to your mom, right?
What?
You said she was worried sick...
about leaving you behind.
She was worried
you'd skip your meals.
That's why you make sure to eat.
I didn't expect you
to remember that.
It must've been so difficult...
for a ten-year-old
to grow up so suddenly.
My dad always said...
a true adult never skipped meals...
or lost sleep.
I had to say goodbye to him
before I became a true adult.
And that...
breaks my heart the most.
We are...
just kids in front of our parents.
We're all...
just young children.
But you're doing your best...
to become an adult.
I'm sure he's cheering you on.
You said they're always watching us.
The food's getting cold.
Dig in.
Look. Mr. Jin.
I'm sorry for not telling you
in advance...
about living with Won Tak.
I know very well
what you're worried about.
- I'll make sure you don't...
- What am I worried about?
- What?
- So what am I worried about?
You're worried about the electricity...
and water bills.
That's correct.
You better not waste my money.
Make sure you turn off your lights.
Of course. Don't worry.
Tell me.
Has anyone ever called you
tactless before?
No.
Gosh.
I told you that cooking
also includes washing the dishes.
I should earn my keep.
It'll make me feel better.
You can sleep...
I'll sleep in the bedroom.
It's only right for the owner
to sleep in the living room.
Sure. Let's do that.
I refuse to be
an even bigger inconvenience...
by watching TV
while I spend the night here.
I know the TV space
is the most important.
How considerate of you.
I'm truly thankful.
Right. I changed the bedsheets
and pillow covers today so...
Have you ever washed
the dishes before?
Of course. This is a simple task.
You just scrub them
with some dishwashing liquid...
and rinse them.
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry.
I think...
we need a towel.
How can I not worry about you?
And yet, you still have no idea
what I'm saying.
You should take that.
It's been ringing for a while.
Yes, I ate.
I'm really fine.
Don't worry about me
and focus on work.
Bye.
To celebrate Dondon Cart Bar's
one-year anniversary,
everything will be 50-percent off!
Today is Dondon Gamjatang's
one-year anniversary!
Everything will be 50-percent off!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- We should eat out today!
Sure!
- Let's have something tasty!
- Let's go!
- I'm not going to miss it.
- One, two, three!
Who was that?
Do I know her?
Right. Why would she do that?
Is today Valentine's Day
or something?
Gosh.
Mom? It's not you, right?
Mom...
Ms. Kim.
- Ms. Kim.
- Mom.
Ms. Kim.
What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
I'm sorry. I knocked,
but I kept hearing you crying.
I'm sorry.
I must have woken you up.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm not.
I'm not okay.
I'd like to apologize again
for what I did the other day.
I'm flattered, but I can't accept
your feelings for me.
I'm sorry.
Do you not like me
because I'm not knowledgeable?
You are very wise.
Do you not like me
because I'm a money-grubber?
You are helping my gallery.
I'm grateful to you.
You're not a money-grubber.
Then what am I to you?
Is it...
because of Jang Tae Jin?
I can't deny that.
I don't know how much you know
about our history.
But I'm scared to love again,
make myself vulnerable,
and plan a future with someone.
Being in love...
comes with a risk
for your love not being returned.
And I don't think
I can take that kind of risk again.
I don't know much about
this difficult concept of love.
But anyway,
at least,
you're not seeing someone else.
And you're not going to start
over with Jang Tae Jin either.
So you don't hate me,
find me creepy, or disgusting, right?
- Mr. Jin.
- That's all I needed to know.
This is quite simple.
I just like you.
I don't know what kind of risk
liking someone entails.
But okay.
It just means you are still hurting.
I won't rush someone who's in pain.
What was that?
The thing you told me before.
We are a friendly creditor
and debtor.
Let's go back to that for now.
Mr. Jin.
It's a long way until morning.
You should sleep some more.
This time, don't have a nightmare.
Oh, right.
I want you to know something.
You are...
much braver than
you give yourself credit for.
In other words, you don't give up
on something because you're scared.
That's what I know about you.
But if you're not even trying
because of someone who hurt you,
that doesn't sound like you even more.
Goodnight.
Love comes with a risk...
Love...
Love... Risk...
(Fifty dollars)
Have this sandwich at work.
No, I'm good.
Gosh, come on.
You didn't get any sleep last night.
You can't skip breakfast.
I don't feel good about that.
Won Tak.
What's going on here?
Oh, no.
No. It's not what you think.
So nothing happened?
- Right.
- Are you hurt?
No.
She's lucky that
I showed up at the right time.
If I didn't...
Goodness.
You call this a door?
Anyone can break in.
Will you take responsibility
if someone breaks in?
Why would anyone want to break
in here?
There's nothing to take.
They'd be wasting their time.
What did you say?
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
Your face works as security.
Well,
who knew that Ms. Kim
was going to move in here?
Besides, how come
you never stick to something?
If your demand wasn't met
the first time, try again.
And if that didn't work,
you should try again.
You should have pestered me
until I changed the door for you.
Why didn't you insist?
Consider yourself lucky.
If there was a scratch on Da Li,
we would have been holding
your funeral by now.
Hey, why are you being
so hostile to him?
He helped me last night.
Let's go inside.
This isn't a simple burglary case.
What?
You should know.
You've been working as a detective.
The owner of Dondon F and B
lives right downstairs. Okay?
But the thief went
to the rooftop house over mine?
And it was like the thief was
looking for something specific.
The thief raided the entire room.
But not one thing went missing.
Look at this shabby, dirty,
and poor-looking house.
Wait. I'm not done yet.
The only valuables were the laptop
and designer handbags.
But they weren't stolen.
Do you think this makes sense?
Then what is it
if not a simple burglary case?
I think...
it's a grudge.
A grudge?
You must get a lot of resentment
for being a cop, no?
- Me?
- Try to find out...
if there are any recently released
female ex-convicts who hate you.
I bumped into someone,
and it seemed like a woman.
It could be a crime of passion.
What?
Is he insane?
I swear this house... I should move.
Darn it.
Can't you take the day off?
You must have been shocked.
You said you couldn't sleep.
I have an important meeting.
Oh, right. My phone.
What's this?
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
Gong Ju, what happened to your ear?
I had an infection from an earring.
You should have been more careful.
You have to take good care of it.
Are you okay, Gong Ju?
Yes. Thank you.
White bouquet.
Right?
Excuse me?
It seems you only use this perfume.
It's a common one.
It's not that common. It's niche.
I tried to buy one but gave up.
It was too expensive.
I can buy one for you.
Something that suits you.
It was a joke.
I'm fine.
I should go print the materials
for the meeting.
What's wrong?
What's Na Gong Ju like?
Pardon?
I have everyone else's HR profile,
but not hers.
Right.
About that...
My dad?
He personally hired Na Gong Ju?
We've had open recruitment
for all positions.
It was quite unusual.
And when I told him her education
and experience were all made up,
he said he'd take care of it...
and that the information should stay
between the two of us.
He even asked me
to take good care of her...
because she seemed to have a lot
of potential.
When the kids arrive,
they will tour the exhibition
with a docent...
and do activities that
Mr. Han has prepared.
For the activities,
we have origami and clay craft...
Are these yours?
This event will be at a park
for about two hours.
The agenda will come to an end...
with the Three Frogs Restaurant program.
The agenda does seem a bit tight...
since we cut it to just one day...
instead of the usual two.
The kids might also be tired.
What if we put up some tents
in the museum garden...
and let the kids sleep there?
It could feel like camping.
Spending a night at a museum
is easier said than done.
I agree. With children,
it can be dangerous.
You never know where
they might run off to.
Are you okay, Gong Ju?
Sorry?
About what?
The children,
spending the night at the museum.
I think you might have some opinions
as the project manager.
I see.
About that...
Unfortunately, I think we
might have to pass this year...
for security and financial reasons.
Then what about a staycation?
Please, sit.
I want to put Segi's name on
something you've already done.
Does that make me a jerk?
By staycation,
do you mean staying at a hotel...
I thought it might be nice to give
the children a tour of Seoul.
Segi will pay for
all the extra cost, of course.
What do you say,
Ms. Kim Da Li?
You have to go through the official
steps to make suggestions like that.
You can't just come into the meeting room.
It's not just anybody. It's Segi.
I thought that would be the only way
for you to say yes.
Why would I say no?
What?
- Because...
- Last time was a personal matter.
Did you think I wouldn't be able
to separate that from work?
You also...
didn't suggest this hoping for
something else, I assume.
My bad.
I apologize if it made
you feel uncomfortable.
That's the drawing case, right?
The one that you've carried around
since you were a child.
Are there still brushes inside?
Drink your tea.
I don't have the ceremonial grade,
which I know you like.
But a blend is okay, right?
Of course.
I like whatever you brew.
Smells good.
My thoughts haven't changed.
We're over.
Sure. I'll control my pace.
I was too rushed,
skipping over the part...
- where we actually bonded.
- Tae Jin.
But I at least want you to get out
of Won Tak's house.
Or should I move in?
You're not laughing.
I was joking.
What?
Kim Si Hyung has disappeared?
What about the thing?
It seemed he borrowed money
from Mr. Ha. Maybe it's him.
Then where could he have gone?
It'd be better if he turned up dead.
But if...
he is alive and says something
that he shouldn't,
we're done for.
Everything's done with!
Find him
before he messes everything up.
No matter what!
Sorry about that.
Did you get bad news?
Exactly.
You look like you ate poop...
Or stepped on it
You look unwell.
It's a lot of work
to take care of your district.
People call you up...
just because their dogs disappeared.
What? For their dogs?
Congressmen have so much work.
Mom.
Forget that. Please continue
with what you were saying.
Right.
The government will
make the announcement...
a little faster than expected.
The public interest
in real estate policies is...
higher than it has ever been.
She can demand any number she wants
once the announcement is made.
Do you think Da Li will hand
the gallery over for a few pennies?
That's why I, An Sang Tae,
came to visit the chairman myself.
Let's file a lawsuit.
- A lawsuit?
You can sue her
and make her pay her loans back.
Send her certified mails,
have her properties seized,
and nitpick over everything
you can find to get her in trouble.
She'll have to pay
her inheritance tax soon too.
Shake her around
and make her lose her senses.
And that's when...
we offer her
to take the gallery over.
Do you have...
enough resources?
Yes, well, if you're sure
this will go well.
Of course, this is your order.
We're done getting the money ready!
Here.
(Ilum Construction)
This is...
a construction company
operated by my distant relative.
Once the announcement is made,
you'll have to put in money
for the business.
You won't have enough time to start
a company, create a portfolio,
and take part in the bidding.
You should take that company over...
and split the shares by six to four.
Shouldn't we have
something like this...
to build trust between us?
There are...
too many traitors these days.
Of course.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
That thief.
He wants to take 40 percent
even though we paid for everything.
Thanks to Assemblyman An,
we got to take part
in this project, Dad.
Just be glad it wasn't five to five.
He's a very reasonable man.
Reasonable, my foot.
He's gone. Let's go back inside.
Do you really...
not have the money?
Sorry?
I mean...
It's just so hard to understand.
You're right.
There is more than meets the eye.
And it was like the thief was
looking for something specific.
The thief raided the entire room.
Something specific?
What could it be?
(Cheongsong Art Camp)
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Goodness, welcome.
- Hello.
- This way, please.
- Come on in.
- Hello.
The kids are coming, so let's hurry.
Hurry up and fill these up.
Please keep it safe.
Who's working on this?
Gong Ju, ask me if you aren't sure.
Thank you for taking part
in this goodwill event.
Many want to help,
but only a few can actually do it.
Thank you in advance
for your hard work.
I think you're mistaken.
I'm the host,
and you're the sponsor.
(Hosted by: Dondon F and B,
Sponsored by: Segi Group)
(Hosted by: Dondon F and B)
(Sponsored by: Segi Group)
I should be the one to thank you.
Thank you for your money.
You're a funny man.
I'm a pretty humorous guy.
You're here.
Hey, Da Li.
Thankfully, the weather is nice.
Yes.
- You're here, Mr. Jin.
- I am.
That's a cute hat.
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Don't mention it.
Let me know if you need anything.
We have everything here.
The kids are
looking forward to this.
Welcome to Three Frogs Restaurant.
Do you see
the silver platter before you?
- Yes.
In there, you'll find
this fantastic and artistic dish...
created by Leonardo Da Vinci.
I wonder what it'll be.
Do you want to know?
- Yes!
- Do you want to know?
If you're curious, give me 50 cents!
Good grief.
Let's find out.
Once I count to three,
you can all open it up.
- Okay?
- Okay.
One, two, three!
- Ta-da!
- What's this?
What is this?
It's weird.
Those are called anchovies,
Italian picked anchovies.
It may smell weird,
but it tastes great.
If you're curious,
feel free to taste it.
How is it?
- It's good.
- Is it?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
- Is it good? Really?
- Really?
- He says it's good.
- It's good.
It tastes like anchovies.
Goodness, but this is too harsh.
How could he serve only one anchovy...
to his guests who came hungry?
If he was born in this day,
he'd get stars deducted online,
forget Leonardo or whoever.
His business will go down.
Now, you won't get filled up...
by eating one anchovy.
Why don't we make
a delicious and hearty dish...
with our two hands
and eat that instead?
Does that sound good?
- Yes!
This is a list
of Leonardo Da Vinci's recipes.
Please modernize those dishes
and make them suitable for kids.
They'll love it
if it's made by a famous chef.
Let's not do that.
Why don't we let the kids cook?
- What?
It would be great to eat a dish
made by a famous chef,
but wouldn't it be better
to help them make their own food?
Like it or not,
there will come a day in your life
when you'll have to cook.
All right, in order to cook,
I'll need an assistant.
Let's see who looks like
the worst cook in this room.
Director Kim Da Li! You're it.
- Go, Ms. Kim!
- Give her a hand!
- Kim Da Li!
Goodness, what are you waiting for?
You're keeping the cooks
of Three Frogs Restaurant waiting!
- Kim Da Li!
Pour a little bit of oil
into the pan.
Let's stir-fry the potato first.
Put in the potato.
Let's put in onion and bacon too.
While your teachers
help you stir-fry everything,
you can each get the egg ready.
I have some eggs for you.
I brought some delicious
and fresh eggs.
Shake it.
- And drain everything.
- Okay.
- Mix it with the egg.
Mix it well.
- All right. Like this.
- Done!
We did it!
- Yes!
Let's go!
Ta-da.
It's a frog!
All right.
Goodness! It's so pretty!
- Look at that.
- Great job.
Guys.
We're all bound...
to be adults one day.
For some people,
it'll happen sooner.
For others, it'll take some time.
One day,
you'll have to face this world...
all by yourself.
Then what should you do?
Eat.
Make sure you eat on time...
even if that means
you'll be eating alone.
A true adult never skips meals.
All right, my little chefs.
Great job cooking today.
Well done.
- Good job!
- Well done!
All right. Now, leave.
Leave? Without eating this?
Just kidding! Dig in!
- What was that?
- Okay!
Yes! Let's eat!
- Let's eat!
- Try it.
- It looks scrumptious.
It looks tasty.
Try some.
- Goodbye.
- Was it fun?
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
- Have fun.
We should get going.
What?
We can't send them to the hotel
all by themselves.
We should escort them.
Right.
Then let me just say goodbye.
They're waiting.
It's rush hour,
so we should go now. Let's go.
Go first. I'll catch up.
Thank you for today.
- Good work.
Do you need any help?
Can you clean these?
These?
Do you need my help?
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
Ms. Na isn't here?
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
She isn't the type not to show up
to work all of a sudden.
Did planning for this project
take a toll on her?
She'll come.
Thanks to her wealthy parents,
she's lived a comfortable life.
She's not hardworking at all.
Gosh. Someone from Dondon
must've left this.
There are kitchen knives
and sauce containers.
Give it to me.
They'll come if they need to.
They'll certainly need that
for work.
Gosh. It's heavy.
Assemblyman An?
Why did he come over?
I'm not sure,
but those working with the director
have been quite busy.
I have no idea
what the legal team is doing either.
The legal team?
(An Chak Hee)
Watch out.
Someone's going to stab you
in the back.
Watch out?
- My gosh!
- Oh my!
Gosh, look at you.
I'm loving your suit and color.
Gosh. I'm sorry,
but there's someone I like.
- Could it be Kim Da Li?
- Yes.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
You're wrong.
What a shame.
She seems to like you.
Really?
Of course not.
It was a lie,
darling.
I can't believe that woman.
Gosh.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
Then why haven't you been
picking up?
You also disappeared
during the opening event.
Do you know how many times I called?
Do you know how worried I was?
I've been a bit busy lately.
You're here to eat, right?
Let's go.
I'll treat you to something good.
Do you want to sleep with me?
I... I'm sorry.
I was just startled
by what you said.
Are you okay?
Why would you be so startled
when we're dating?
Were we in a relationship?
Since when?
I confessed my love to you...
and introduced you to my dad.
Hey, if that was the case,
my nickname would've been
Casa Blanca.
It's Casanova.
Exactly.
I'm sure you know this already,
but I have a killer body.
I'm not interested.
Everyone will say
that I deserve better.
That's why you shouldn't date me.
Why have you been seeing me?
Have you never had
the urge to touch, kiss, or sleep...
with me?
No. Not even once.
We're talking about us here.
Didn't you say there was a line
we couldn't cross?
What's gotten into you?
Then...
is there someone else...
No. I don't want to hear it.
You better not answer that.
Leave five minutes later.
Don't you dare follow me.
Gosh.
Chak Hee. Hey.
I don't know how...
I caused this misunderstanding.
But I'd like to apologize.
I'm sorry.
I don't want
any more misunderstandings,
so let's make this clear.
There's someone I like.
So let's not...
You scumbag.
Did you have to tell me that?
I told you not to answer
and to leave five minutes later.
Don't you know
that was why I left first?
How could you be stupid and dull?
And since when did you like
to make things clear?
Did you have to make
a fool out of me?
Are you really that great? Are you?
Come on.
Who was I fooling?
Who?
Right.
Who was I fooling?
(Tae Jin)
Hey.
Today?
You're funding our gallery.
Of course, I should go.
(Dondon Gamjatang)
What? You like food like this too.
"Food like this?"
I thought we could dine
at a different restaurant...
instead of our usual type
of restaurant.
I hear their food is good.
What about the other people?
Something came up out of the blue.
So we'll reschedule
when they are available.
Besides, I just have to give you this.
So I came on their behalf.
That's the sponsorship application form.
We have eight people for now,
but I think two more will join.
Here's your food.
- We're out of potatoes.
- This is for table two.
Tell them I gave them a lot of food.
Wait. Shouldn't you be inside?
Inside where?
The gallery director is here.
Who was that?
With that annoying jerk.
You know, the guy from Segi.
Did you know that the name,
gamjatang, comes...
from the name of the bones,
not the potatoes that we know of?
Is that so? I didn't know.
When meat was rare in Korea,
people took pork backbones...
the US military threw out
and started to cook with the bones.
I see.
This dish truly suits that guy,
Jin Moo Hak.
What?
The ingredient
could have been garbage,
but he made a great dish out of it.
He's truly amazing.
I have a lot to learn from him.
To be able to be this successful...
from the bottom,
he must have made
numerous hard decisions...
and gone through many hardships
beyond our imagination.
Whether he wanted to or not,
he probably had to hurt people
to get what he wanted.
What are you getting at?
Dondon F and B...
has been buying the land
surrounding the gallery.
Did you know?
What?
They have been buying
every piece of land...
regardless of the location or the price
after your father's death.
I've been hearing that they plan
to buy a construction company.
Da Li.
You must think...
because you treat them
with good intentions,
they will treat you the same.
How much do you know
about this man, Jin Moo Hak?
Is he trustworthy?
Is he...
a good person?
Your fried rice is here.
(Dali and Cocky Prince)
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Are you saying that I did something
so dirty that I must make excuses?
Are you saying
you're giving up the money?
Ms. Na just didn't go AWOL.
What are you doing to Ms. Na?
What were you looking for
that desperately?
This is all I can tell you.
Let me just stay like this for a bit.
You still don't see
who is on your side?
Why won't you even touch?
Tell me when you're ready.
Who said I wasn't ready?
I'm totally ready now.
I feel great physically and mentally.