(Episode 7)
(Does Death Mean the End?)
Be quiet.
How dare you raise your voice here?
Stop lying through your teeth.
- Hey.
- Who are you?
- Hey!
- You scumbag!
- Hey.
- Get off me!
- Calm down.
- You almost punched me.
- What?
- Be quiet!
- What did you say?
- I'd love to get...
settlement money
and live a comfortable life.
Seriously. She'd better watch out.
Once I find the girl
that reported me,
I'm going to punch...
What...
Say that again. What did you say?
- What did you say?
- Mr. Jin, no!
Don't do that.
I should've...
just killed her back then.
Please don't do anything. Please.
Darn it, man. Good grief.
Darn it.
Darn it. What a load of bull.
Did you all just see that?
I'm never going to settle!
There are security cameras here,
so you all better make this right.
- Call the police again.
- You need to shut your mouth!
Let me make this clear.
Your sentence will go up
whenever you speak another word.
- That brat...
- Special robbery and injury...
gets you over 3 years 6 months,
up to 7 years.
On top of that,
you were released last year.
If you're convicted again...
after your previous crime
within three years,
you're sentenced to up to ten years
or for life.
The act of your crime was
taken on these cameras you love.
Throw in footprints,
fingerprints, and DNA.
There are millions of reasons
to throw you in prison.
However, you must know my witness
as the victim is the most essential.
Thankfully, I am acquainted
with millions of doctors.
Depending on your attitude,
the diagnosis will look
worlds different.
Let me explain it to you once again
in case you didn't understand.
Every single word I say will decide...
if you ever see the sunlight again
outside of prison.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Where's my money?
I'm sure you have some left.
- Well, the thing is...
- Did you use everything?
I mean, yes.
Only if the detective came
just a minute later.
I had the Eight Bright card.
You saw the Three Bright
in my hand, right?
Once you put them together,
you get 3-8 Brights.
That's the strongest hand.
I told you to be quiet.
- You! How dare you blow my money?
- Hold her back!
I had to pay my staff with that!
How dare you?
Hey, let go. Get off of me!
Let go of me!
You, come here!
(Episode 7)
No matter how angry you are,
you can't do that here.
If things go haywire,
you can be charged with assault.
If this gets reported
to the Human Rights Commission,
it'll get really messy.
I'm sorry.
The same goes for you
and your boyfriend.
Try to tone it down a little.
My boyfriend?
That guy who did fly kicks.
He's not my boyfriend.
- Is he your older brother?
- No.
If he's not your boyfriend
or older brother,
then why did he make a huge scene
in the middle of a police station?
You people will
get in serious trouble.
I'm sorry.
Try to lose your temper, okay?
All right, then. Goodbye.
Look at this.
You were a police officer?
It's unbelievably nice
to see you here.
What's your relationship with her?
Do you ask questions
that randomly...
out of habit
or because of your vocation?
What relationship?
What's your relationship with Da Li?
Da Li?
Yes, famous people are our friends.
Think about it. I'm friends
with Byung Hun, Woo Sung,
and Bin too.
I wonder when Son will come back.
We should grab a meal sometime.
Aren't you going to answer me?
Look at you.
She's not someone you can talk about
whenever you want.
Won Tak.
- Hey, are you done?
- Yes.
How do you know my dear Won Tak?
My...
My dear Won Tak?
Do you two know each other?
Not really.
- He's just...
- He's my tenant.
He lives on the rooftop
of my building.
I thought you were living alone.
What's it to you
if I live alone or not?
It's because...
my upstairs neighbor was
way too loud.
I see. I heard noise issues were
very serious here.
I hear there are people who aren't
considerate in their communities.
I told you that my landlord
is a crazy...
You have something dirty
around your mouth.
I see.
You're my dear Won Tak's landlord.
I hope you treat him well.
He's a vigorous, young man.
I hope he hasn't been too noisy.
I told you. He has been.
And that's why I couldn't sleep.
What are you talking about?
That's because the house is...
He says he's sorry
and that he'll be more careful.
When did I say that?
Are we done introducing ourselves?
Let's go home.
Thank you for everything, Mr. Jin.
Goodbye.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Who is he?
Be quiet. I'll explain back home.
Don't tell anyone that we're living
together for the time being.
- That we're living...
- Be quiet.
Where do you think you're going?
Sorry?
Shouldn't you go to the gallery?
What about the exhibit?
You have several matters
to take care of.
Right.
It was nice seeing you.
I should go now.
I don't know where you live,
but until we meet again,
watch your mouth...
Watch the amount of noise you make.
What?
Hey, Da Li...
Later.
What's your relationship...
with your dear Won Tak?
What?
You two seem
to have a special relationship.
Well... I guess that's true.
It's a long story.
You must've gone through
more than 3,000 geops.
How much? 5,000 geops?
Or 6,000 geops? 7,000 geops?
Look.
My dear Won Tak
is a kindhearted and decent guy.
He has a sense of justice,
is law-abiding,
honest...
And most of all, he's part
of the Violent Crimes Unit,
so thieves tend to avoid him.
So in a way, you have yourself
a free security service.
He's a great fighter too.
It's so reassuring
to have him by your side.
What is he? A bodyguard?
I'm just saying that
there's no better tenant than him.
He's often on duty or stakeouts.
He's so easygoing
that he rarely takes showers.
How great is that?
You'll save on utilities.
You talk as if you live with him.
Sorry?
You're such a hilarious man,
Mr. Jin.
I'll also warn him
about the noise issues so...
I get it.
I can take care of my own tenant,
so can you please stop talking
about your dear Won Tak?
My ears are about to bleed.
I'm sorry.
How are your knuckles?
They're fine.
I should've beaten him to a pulp.
But you hugged me from behind.
- What?
- You startled me.
People were watching, you know?
I was merely trying to stop you
from causing bigger trouble.
I see.
You were being quite passionate.
That's why
you should've just left...
instead of causing
a misunderstanding.
That's because...
I was... I was going to ask
about a rice soup restaurant.
- Sorry?
- There's a tasty rice soup place...
near the police station.
I was just doing some research.
Did you think
I went there because of you?
Also, you should never talk
like you did back there...
even if you're surrounded
by police officers.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous those men can be?
- I know very well.
- What?
You may not believe it
since he's turned into a great guy.
But when my dear Won Tak
used to be a troublemaker,
my dad and I popped by
the police station quite often.
You and your dear Won Tak...
We met all kinds of criminals
from petty pickpockets...
to gang leaders.
I probably know more
about them than you do.
I'm aware that I have a pretty face,
but don't let it fool you.
Did you forget the tiger tattoo
I had all over my body?
My nickname is Majang-dong...
Those were stickers.
Who said that?
A few of its fangs and claws
were erased.
Did you forget what happened
in the Netherlands? During...
During the blackout?
You said
you had forgotten everything,
but I guess you still remember
every little detail.
Right. How could you ever forget?
I had a killer body.
A killer body?
Why are you laughing?
I'm not.
I definitely heard you laughing.
You're mistaken.
A killer body?
A killer...
I think you went
a bit overboard there.
A killer body?
I think that's enough.
I'm sorry.
(Copy of Register)
(Debtor: Kim Nak Chun)
(Jang Tae Jin)
(Dondon F and B Organization Chart)
(Director Jin Moo Hak)
He's oddly annoying me.
Dondon F and B may be a company now,
but he's a nouveau riche
who started from a marketplace.
The same goes for his father
and stepmother.
They're just low,
money-hungry individuals.
Once he gets his money,
he'll be out of her hair.
There's nothing to worry about.
How much is the debt?
I heard it was two million dollars.
Two million?
Is he trying to seduce Da Li?
He may be ignorant,
but I'm sure
he knows better than that.
It's none of your business.
And we don't have that relationship.
Mr. Jin?
Why are you standing there?
You need to pay for this.
(Cheongsong Museum of Art)
Why did they bother
to invest in the gallery...
and cause this much trouble for her?
Not only is he conceited...
but narrow-minded as well.
I'd like to meet him once.
You want to meet with him?
Please handle it with care.
There was a problem
with the electrical wires,
so it took some time to fix them.
I'm afraid
we'll have to pull an all-nighter.
Is everything going as planned
with the catering service?
About that, we've yet to figure out
the number of guests we're having.
You haven't checked
with our VIPs yet?
Well...
Hello.
Will Mr. Jang be attending
the opening ceremony?
I see. His schedule isn't out yet?
Sorry?
Minister Choi?
I was wondering
if Minister Choi would be attending.
He's out right now?
Then when do you think
you can get back to us?
It must be
because of that news article.
They asked us
about who would be attending.
They would attend
if the other was attending.
They are just feeling us out
for the guest list.
At times like this, it'd be great
if an important figure...
like Director Jang would
encourage them to attend.
But he has a business trip
on the day of our opening.
Well, I meant...
we need celebrities to attend
the opening to get the word out,
so that way, a lot of people
would come after the opening.
Proceed with the number of guests
we planned initially.
- We can't disrespect our guests.
- Okay.
- Move out of my way.
- Goodness. Mr. Kim!
Gosh. What are you doing?
I called dibs on it first!
- Seriously?
- Gosh.
- This spot was empty.
- Come on.
You can just call dibs
to make it yours?
- I told you to move!
- Goodness.
- Wait. What's going on?
- Gosh.
This section belongs
to Ms. Hong Ja Young.
- I heard she pulled out.
- What? No, she didn't.
- Hey, can't I take this spot?
- Yes?
This is the main spot.
A piece deserving of the spotlight
ought to be displayed.
Besides, mine is
about the same size as hers.
- The size?
- Yes.
So only the size matters?
Not the actual artwork?
The artwork must represent
the group exhibition.
Exactly. That's why it must be mine.
Given my international fame
and well-received artistic quality.
- Everyone's artwork is great.
- Artistic quality?
Artistic quality?
Ms. Yang, how many solo exhibitions
have you opened so far?
Who cares about solo exhibitions
where the artist sponsors himself?
What about you, Mr. Kim?
Were you invited to the Biennale
this year?
- What?
- Goodness.
- Ms. Yang.
- My gosh.
- I guess you weren't.
- Everyone was invited.
- You really weren't invited.
- Your artwork is famous.
Are you guys sure...
you want this spot?
Yes.
Well, we'd love to install
your piece, Mr. Kim.
But the color of the wall
and your piece have the same color.
So your artwork might not stand out.
Well, you should repaint the wall.
Tomorrow is the opening.
There isn't enough time for that.
Then, why don't you display mine?
We'd be grateful
to install your artwork too.
But right next to this spot...
Right?
You'll go back
to your initial spots, right?
That section is the best
for your art.
They are usually very polite.
But they get sensitive
right before the exhibitions.
So we haven't heard
from Ms. Hong yet?
Ms. Song went to see her
but seeing how she didn't call...
Shouldn't we look for
another artist now?
Where is her studio?
- Her studio?
- Yes.
What brings trash here?
(Dondon Gamjatang)
I'm here to clean up my mess.
What nonsense is this?
"My mess is my duty."
What?
Since I made this mess,
I will clean it up.
That's my principle.
What a load of garbage.
Mr. Jin.
My goodness.
What on earth is happening?
She needs to let me in first
for me to offer her anything.
Gosh. I've been waiting
by her house for three hours.
I'm just taking a break.
But I realized that
I came here empty-handed.
So I'm going to buy some fruit...
What?
You're coming here now?
We must fix this in two hours.
We are literally running out of time
and don't have another alternative.
Okay.
Actually,
there was a reason behind her anger.
The first piece
in "The Living and The Dead" series...
was inspired
by alienating her late mother.
And that stupid man called
her precious art...
trash and garbage.
Gosh. You guys are
such a nuisance to no end.
Ms. Hong.
As for the incident this morning...
I bet you're sorry,
feel awful about it,
have nothing to say, and so on.
I got it. Let's cut to the chase.
What did you bring me?
- Pardon?
After all,
this is your first exhibition...
as the new director.
But there was a disaster.
So I doubt that
you would come here empty-handed.
I'm curious to find out
what you are going...
to offer me.
We'll handsomely compensate
for the damage we caused.
The insurance company
will take care of that.
You said you were interested...
in the artist-in-residence program...
sponsored by Hamilton Foundation
in New York.
I'm fully booked until next year.
I'm not sure
if I'll be available for that.
I see. Okay.
Then...
What about a solo exhibition?
We'll prepare
your solo exhibition...
as soon as we're done
with this group exhibition.
We can't purchase
your artwork right away,
but we'll make sure that we do.
And we'll put our best people
for the private showings.
Will there be a next time with you?
I thought this would be your last.
Ms. Hong.
We will hold an exhibition
within a year.
As long as you're happy with us,
I'd like to prepare...
your future exhibitions myself...
at Cheongsong Gallery.
I see.
I read it from somewhere...
that people even kneel
to get what they want.
I see. But you are a lady
from high society,
so kneeling in front of others
comes at a great price.
Ms. Hong.
If I kneel,
will you agree to our term?
If you make demands,
it's a compromise, not begging.
Ms. Hong. You don't like
this kind of behavior.
Why are you so harsh today?
If this can help you feel better,
I don't mind kneeling
in front of you.
I'm really sorry...
about today's incident.
Ms. Kim, please don't do that.
- Come on, Ms. Hong.
- Forget it.
I was just joking.
Don't take it so seriously.
Right. It must've arrived by now.
What kind of spell
did you put her under?
What made her come around?
This is amazing.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Sir, let me carry that.
Sorry.
No. Don't worry.
Everything is good.
- Gosh. Go help him.
- What?
The third piece of...
"The Living and The Dead" series
has arrived.
Shouldn't you get going?
Thank you so much, Ms. Hong.
I didn't do it to get a thank-you.
If the gallery closes,
it'll be bad news for the artists.
So you must keep your promise. Okay?
You promised to hold...
my exhibitions next year,
the year after that, and so on.
It would be an honor.
Ms. Hong.
You're the best.
Let's hurry.
If we want to finish setting up
before the opening,
we are short on time.
- Let's go.
- By the way.
Who was that trashy character
this morning?
He's not well-versed in art,
but he's not a bad person.
Actually, Cheongsong is
indebted to him.
How funny.
I asked who he was,
not whether he was a good person.
Well...
Congruity within incongruity.
You two go well together.
Wait up!
This is Mr. Jin's office
from Dondon F and B.
Where?
Jang Tae Jin?
He said he would grant you
the chance to meet him...
if you call him
whenever you're available.
Grant me?
He wants to talk about the debt
that Cheongsong owes.
Don't you think I nailed it
with my expectations this time?
What was it that you expected?
I told you before.
I said I thought Segi Group
would pay Cheongsong's debt.
Who does he think he is?
He's dying to pay.
He wants to flex.
Two million dollars means
nothing to Segi Group.
Especially now that their biggest
obstacle Kim Nak Chun has died,
two million is less than nothing.
That means we don't have
to do anything either.
Isn't it great?
When do you want to meet him?
As early as possible, I assume?
Tonight?
I'm busy.
Tomorrow night?
I'm busy tomorrow as well.
The day after tomorrow?
I said I was busy!
I don't have time to meet that dude!
And if he wants to see me,
make him come here.
Who is he to order me to come?
I have money too!
But an opportunity like this
doesn't come often.
Understood.
- What's that?
- Right.
It's the first piece
of Hong Ja Young's...
"The Living and The Dead" series
you purchased.
This is it? Just this?
They say inside are
explanations of her artwork...
and a description
of how the piece came to be.
They also said the first piece
of "The Living and the Dead" series...
would be unavailable for exhibition,
publication, or photography...
anywhere without your consent.
Now you're a real collector.
You're throwing it away?
That's a lot of money.
I...
can't believe I bought
a 100,000-dollar piece of trash!
What's wrong with him?
Someone's calling you.
Aren't you going to answer?
Who is it?
Extremity.
(Eternity)
Wait, it's eternity.
Give it.
Jin Moo Hak speaking.
Put it here!
Everything worked out well.
I know you've been worried.
Well... A bit.
You have many things to worry about.
You shouldn't be worried about
me worrying.
That makes me worried.
That shouldn't go there.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry,
even though it's late.
Are you coming
to the opening ceremony tomorrow?
Of course!
I'll be there no matter what,
so you just wait.
Okay.
I'm not sure what harmony that is.
I thought she would
never change her mind.
By the way, will Ms. Hong be doing
the opening ceremony performance?
I think so. We can't get anyone
since we're short on time.
Sir.
Why are all the plastic bags...
- Come down.
- Oh my.
Goodness.
Is everything alright?
This is way too crumpled!
Make it stay exactly like this.
No, I mean...
We have issues with the direction
of the monitors.
I was following the design...
You read it wrong.
- I didn't...
- Look.
Please stay within the line.
No, it's too close.
Move it slightly this way. Good.
Who's in charge of this?
Hurry up!
Three per table, please.
Over there.
This is wrong.
This one has to face that way.
Let's put it back down.
Ms. Kim?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Hello.
Are the VIP customers not here yet?
They all got the invitation,
so they will surely send someone
even if they can't make it.
Don't worry too much.
Everything will be fine.
The fact that we opened
is already incredible.
Honestly, I didn't think
we could make it.
It has to go well.
We've all been through so much
since Director Kim's passing.
Here we are.
Did you even advertise the event?
Where is everyone?
Can you really lose your momentum
to such an extent?
Isn't this too odd?
Let's go home. We did our part.
Where is everyone?
How is it possible that
not a single person showed up?
Where is that idiot?
The one time we need him,
he's not here.
Where is he?
We have to do something.
Everyone call who you can.
Wait.
There!
What?
What are you waiting for?
Places, everyone!
Let's go.
They're coming.
Look here, please.
Over here.
Welcome.
Look here, please.
Can you look here one more time?
Over here.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
- Oh my.
- Look here.
- Look over here, please.
- Thank you.
- Over here.
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
- This way, please.
Could you please wave your hand?
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
- Over here.
- Please look over here.
- Hello.
- Please wave your hands.
- Look over here.
- Thank you for coming. Hello.
- Thank you.
- Please look here.
- Please look over here.
- Hello.
Please show them the way.
Please look over here.
- Please show us a smile.
- Look over here.
- Wave your hand.
Could you make hearts?
- All right!
- Thank you.
- Could you wave again?
You can go in this way.
- You should say hi to him too.
- Thank you.
Darn it, where are
all these people coming from?
Darn it.
Hey, get me a straw.
Get me a straw!
Look over here.
You'll see works by Choi Jung Hwa.
As you can see here,
she made this...
by using household items.
You can see the philosophy
behind this artist's work.
Look, that's ELRIS. An idol group.
Ham Yon Ji is here too.
She has over a million followers.
Anyway, did we send an invitation
to ELRIS and Ms. Ham?
- Invitations get around.
- You're right.
Look, I've seen him on TV.
Who was he again?
- I don't know his name.
- He's an actor.
- Is he?
- He's not a singer?
This is the fanciest opening day
ever since I started here.
I guess Ms. Kim's marketing strategy
worked like magic.
Sounds great.
In my opinion, I think this is
Director Jang Tae Jin's power.
He's young, handsome,
and he's the possible successor
of Segi Group.
He's a divorcee too.
Anyone big in politics and business
would drool all over him,
as well as anyone with a daughter.
I get it. She's doing this again.
- She's so negative.
- Let's say hi to her.
- Hello.
We're curators
here at Cheongsong Gallery.
- Hello.
- It's nice to have you here.
- It's a lot of fun.
- You're so pretty.
- Yes.
- Goodness, thank you.
Hello, these are
the curators of the gallery.
Yes, hello.
- Hello.
- Weren't you going abroad for work?
How did you find the time?
It was postponed to next week.
It was postponed
because of their situation.
Did you think
I postponed it for you?
No.
I may be smitten with you,
but work is still work for me.
Let's head over there.
These are the people
we'll have to deal with.
Make sure you meet them.
- Chairman Choi.
- Hey.
"We"?
The new director, Ms. Kim Da Li.
Chairman Choi Young Man
of C and C Ventures and his wife.
Thank you for your time.
They're well-versed
in culture and arts,
so they'll be good sponsors.
Goodness, you threatened me saying
you'll never see me again...
unless I come here.
And you're now asking me to donate?
Goodness, you're like
a highway robber.
He's not a robber.
He's a romanticist.
I heard you postponed
your business trip to be here.
- Sorry?
- No, ma'am.
I didn't postpone it.
They postponed it first...
because of their situation.
Goodness, I must've made a mistake.
Chairman Kim!
That's Chairman Kim of Lux Hotel.
Let us go say hello. Let's go.
- Look at him.
- Chairman Kim.
What are you doing?
- Please meet Director Kim.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
This is Chairman Kim of Lux Hotel.
So did you have a nice chat?
- Yes.
- We did.
- They're here.
- Good grief.
Goodness.
Why? Why do you do this?
Since when did our family
visit exhibitions and art galleries?
Why is my entire family here?
Think of all the money we spent.
We have to come and look.
Also, I should start
attending parties to get used to it.
It's not a party.
It's their opening event.
It's their grand opening?
It's not a party?
Who cares if this is
the opening event or a party?
We can use this chance
to meet new people.
Father, I saw on social media...
that all kinds
of famous people came.
Even the successor
of Segi Group is here.
That sounds wonderful.
It's time. We should go.
Anyway...
Once you get in there,
pretend like we're strangers.
We're all on our own.
- Let's go.
- Yes, I just arrived.
I told you. I made this mess,
so I'll clean it up.
All right, then.
Goodness.
- Stick together.
- What have you been doing?
They're all wonderful people.
- Do you enjoy wine?
- Wine sounds great.
How's your artwork coming along?
- Well, did you see it in there?
- I did.
- What did you think?
- I thought...
What are you doing?
Why are you so late?
I've been waiting for you.
Chak Hee, why are you here?
Why would a gallerist be here?
Of course, I should be here.
Oh, you work at a gallery, right?
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Stay with me.
I have to introduce you to someone.
Introduce me? To whom?
- This is excellent.
- It is.
- I'll get going, then.
- Yes, goodbye.
- All right.
- See you.
This is Director Kim.
Hey...
You know that you seem the coolest
when you don't say a word, right?
That's enough. What are you doing?
Just greet them,
then don't say a word.
I'll manage the rest. Let's go.
Where are we... Where are we going?
Just come.
- Where did he go?
- Calm down.
Goodness. Thank you.
- Here.
- Okay.
How do you hit so well
with your driver?
You're really strong.
- Dad.
- Hey, Chak Hee.
A hard worker for my district,
always jolly around the year,
my name is An Sang Tae.
So who is he?
- I'm Jin Moo Hak...
- You know him too.
He's with Dondon F and B,
a company that makes
big political contributions for you.
I see.
Assemblyman An, hello.
- Goodness.
- He's my father.
Yes, right. Goodness.
Yes, it's an honor to meet you.
- Ma'am!
- This is fraud!
Get back here!
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Mr. Jin Moo Hak.
Yes?
Right.
I'm Jang Tae Jin of Segi Group.
I wanted to meet with you,
but you declined the offer.
Your people don't report properly.
I didn't decline it.
If you have business with me,
come to me...
instead of telling me
to come to you.
That's what I said.
I see. I just wanted
to suit your schedule.
I'm sorry if I sounded rude.
Suit me?
Sure.
So what is this about?
I heard that Da Li
is indebted to you.
I should've taken care of it
as soon as possible.
But we had a personal issue,
so it took longer than expected.
We?
Personal?
So?
I'll pay in Cheongsong's stead.
What's it to you?
Tell me.
Who are you to meddle in our affair?
I refuse to watch her
being treated...
like a doormat anymore.
Men covered in tattoos
lied in her gallery.
The art pieces were broken.
And you're always keeping
an eye on her.
She spent all her life...
reading books
and learning about art.
She's not like you.
She has a strong sense
of responsibility,
so she doesn't show it.
But can't you see? She's struggling.
You should stop here.
Did she say...
that I was giving her a tough time?
Because she never told me so.
And Da Li...
isn't some naive kid.
Can't you see how well she's doing?
Don't make a fool
out of an intelligent woman.
It's only money.
And excessive nosiness means...
you have an ulterior motive.
What is it?
Are things not going your way?
Gosh. Hello?
Fine. I'm leaving right now. Bye.
I'm a bit busy.
I heard you liked money.
Isn't that all you want?
It's true that I love money.
But I don't accept donations.
I may get indigestion.
This is the third piece...
of Ms. Hong Ja Young's
"The Living and The Dead" series.
As you can see,
everything is made...
with garbage left behind
by the living.
The dead can no longer leave
behind garbage.
Does life always bring happiness?
Is death always horrible?
What differentiates these two?
Ms. Hong only learned...
about her mother's death
one month after she passed away.
Her late mother
didn't want to bother her...
while she was preparing
for an important exhibit.
During that one month,
was her mom alive...
or dead to her?
The aim of this artwork
was to make...
the audience think
through this experience.
- My gosh!
- What's going on?
Ma'am!
You lunatic!
Why in the world
are you in the coffin?
You're teasing me, aren't you?
Why would you do
something like this to me!
What's the matter with you?
This is what I'm supposed to do.
The artist told me to do this.
- You little...
- He's right.
The artist had planned to do this.
He was handpicked today.
But starting from tomorrow on,
any of you can volunteer...
for this experience.
I see.
Go back inside.
Shall we move on?
All right.
Goodbye, sir. This way.
Let's go.
What?
You know nothing about art.
I thought no one would come,
but everyone came.
Gosh.
You were squealing when you saw KNK.
That's rich coming from you.
I saw what you did.
Since Ms. Hong had
to quickly change her artwork,
I thought we wouldn't have a model.
Me too. I was shocked
to see him in the coffin.
He didn't strike me
as the type to do that.
He just cleaned up the mess he made.
It's not that big of a deal.
Goodness.
Where's Ms. Kim?
She told us to leave first.
Today was her first exhibit
after her father's death.
Despite being hectic all day,
he popped into my head
every now and then.
Imagine how she felt.
Dad!
Remember I told you
that a gallery was timid yet chatty?
It has so many things to say,
but it's too timid to talk.
So when you're in a gallery,
you need to walk around quietly...
and listen
to what the pieces are saying.
Mr. Jin.
Look. My forehead is busted, right?
Don't exaggerate it now.
I'm serious!
Didn't you hear it crack?
All of a sudden,
everything went white.
When this happens,
the lack of blood can be more dangerous.
Let me see.
Do you feel dizzy or nauseous?
Do you feel like throwing up?
Do I?
Anyway,
you kind of hurt my feelings.
You put me in the coffin
and forgot all about me.
Who knew that you would
fall asleep in the coffin?
- What? Seriously?
- Sorry.
You must've bought good wine.
I always fall asleep
when I drink expensive liquor.
Good work today.
It was tough, wasn't it?
Well,
it wasn't so bad.
Actually, going into the coffin...
didn't feel good.
It was cold, dark,
humid, and scary.
But when I lay down,
it was warm, soft,
and warm.
They might've sprayed perfume.
It smelled good too.
For some reason,
it made me feel relieved.
It was comforting.
My mother passed away
on a very cold day.
Gosh. This is ridiculous.
I know that
you just lost your father.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask you how old you were
when she passed away?
It's not some big secret.
She passed away when I was ten.
You must've been heartbroken.
I'm sure she will be proud to see
how kind and successful you are.
No.
I hope she doesn't.
People...
talk about how the deceased watch
over us to the end of time,
protect us as our guardian angels,
and how we'll get to see them again.
But I want death to be
the end of everything.
The end of life.
The end.
That's what I want.
My mother...
suffered way too much.
She went through so much pain
her entire life.
From what I remember,
she was in pain every single day.
She was sick.
Because
she couldn't be there for me,
she was heartbroken too.
- I washed the strawberries.
- Yes.
They look delicious.
Try it.
Hurry and eat.
Did you eat?
Yes.
Don't skip your meals. Okay?
Even when I'm not here,
you must eat no matter what. Okay?
Eat.
Out of all days,
she passed away on the coldest day.
When we were burying her,
the ground was frozen.
The workers kept cursing.
She never had a ray of sunshine
in her life.
Her life was tough as it was.
She doesn't have to worry about me
even after her death.
Let's go.
She was probably watching
over you...
the whole time.
She was probably there
for every moment of your life,
rooted for you,
and worried about you.
And after seeing
how you stayed on the right path...
and have become a great man,
she must be happy.
(Dali and Cocky Prince)
No. Do what at the gallery?
Cheese cafe?
Why did I do that?
There's this magic
of an opening day.
You are our gallery's
true lucky charm.
What? How did you know
this was my house?
Your dog pooped!
You ought to clean it up!
- Hey. What is it?
- Sir, please drive. Let's go.
I've never stopped thinking about you.
Let's start over.
A mistake?
I never make mistakes
when it involves my mouth.