=Episode 5=
(Dr. Gu, come on!)
See, I said
you've met too few setbacks.
In fact,
when you stride over the barrier
and look back,
you'll find it's not a big deal.
Each setback is the impetus to move on.
Come on, Dr. Gu.
Dr. Gu,
you're really a very good doctor
in my eyes.
Don't give up
even if you don't do the surgery
for Mr. Lin.
Wei, could you come out for a while?
Here's an emergency.
My son is suffering so much.
You don't even care about it.
You call yourself doctors?
But it's normal to bleed
after the surgery.
Dr. Gu has dealt with it.
- It's not...
- Get away.
I'm talking to him.
None of your business.
Please calm down.
I see, you're Gu Wei.
You just caused an accident
and killed your teacher.
Mind your words.
How unfortunate
my son is to be here
- when you're on duty.
- Honey.
Honey, our son is fainted out of pain.
Find a way out for my son.
- Stop shouting. Stop shouting.
- Listen,
- I'm gonna complain.
- Sir.
- Could you please calm down?
Stop it.
Watch out.
I won't let you go.
Lin Zhixiao.
Dr. Gu, are you alright?
Gosh!
Blood.
Dr. Gu, please be gentle.
I haven't started.
Don't move.
Gently, gently, gently.
You know it's painful now?
I don't know
whether I should appreciate you
or scold you.
It was so dangerous.
But you rushed in recklessly.
It's lucky that the cut is not deep.
I saved you anyway,
OK?
Who is responsible for the wound?
I wish someone
can do the surgery for my dad
for the sake of my injury.
Done.
Does it hurt?
It's OK.
When I was little,
my dad treated me as a boy.
The other girls,
if they fell, for example,
their parents would hold them up
and coax.
My dad was like,
Lin Zhixiao,
get up where you fall.
Just like he did in the office.
Does it hurt
when stitching?
Are you so afraid of pain?
How's it?
It's cute.
This pig is so cute.
It's a chicken actually.
The nurses of children's ward
taught me when I rotated there.
I felt it looked like a chicken just now,
but I was embarrassed to say it.
It's a lovely chicken.
You get stitched then.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
I'll start now.
Ready.
Hold on, Dr. Gu.
Don't you have to anesthetize me
before stitching?
Lin Zhixiao,
you make the choice.
If you get anesthesia,
it would be four stitches.
And two stitches without anesthesia.
Make the choice.
Two stitches.
Come here.
I'll be as gentle as I can.
It will be a little hurt. Hang in there.
OK.
It's almost done.
Hang in there.
Dr. Gu.
Your eyes are so beautiful.
It's not painful, right?
Don't misunderstand. I didn't mean it.
It's just out of aesthetics.
Anything I should mind?
Keep wound out of water
in three days.
Change the medicine every other day.
Come to me to take out the stitches
five days later.
Don't eat spicy food.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It's done.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
Mm.
I'm gonna leave.
Bye-bye.
Mind your wound.
OK.
Bye-bye.
The chicken balloon.
I see, you're Gu Wei.
I heard that
you just caused an accident
and killed your teacher.
You're an irresponsible doctor.
Mind your words.
Dr. Gu.
Are you off duty?
Yes.
Let me take you somewhere.
Well, I'm not going…
- Come on.
- I…
I've saved you.
Do me an honor.
Say it again.
What did you ask me to do?
Climbing through the window.
Climbing through the window?
Take it ease.
This is the tradition
of our Department of Music.
Almost every student has climbed in
through the window to rehearse.
No way, Dr. Gu.
Haven't you ever done something wrong
when you were a student?
I think it's because
there're too little homework
for you students of Department of Music.
Old fogey. Wait here.
Look at me.
Come in.
Dr. Gu.
You're really interesting.
You can get in with one step.
Why are you being so stable outside?
Forget it.
I don't understand
the good students like you.
Wait for me in the front door.
I'll open the door for you.
(Huaqing University)
Lin Zhixiao.
The door is unlocked.
I don't know it's unlocked today.
Don't you lose your mind by the hurt?
No.
Get in?
How's it?
No one's here.
Is it super atmospheric?
When I was in high school,
I was with poor grades.
I had no idea what I could do
and whether I could
enter the university.
I almost gave up
until a senior
encouraged me
and pointed the direction for me.
I remember that day,
he took me
to climb in through the window.
He stood up here
and had an agreement with me.
Zhixiao,
when you entered Huaqing University,
we'll cooperate here.
So, you really entered it.
Yes.
From then on, I'll come here
when I come across
any difficulty.
And I will be relieved.
So, Dr. Gu,
I want to share it with you.
OK.
Are you going to play for me?
Hold on.
Thank you, Dr. Gu,
for curing Mr. Lin on time.
I specially chose
this song for you.
Listen to it carefully.
Ready.
How's it? Is it good?
Good.
Dr. Gu.
Do you know
what my impression on you is?
At first,
I greatly misunderstood you.
Now I don't understand
you very comprehensively,
but I'm sure for one thing,
that
you're a very good doctor.
A doctor heals the wounded
and rescues the dying.
Since I was an intern,
totally 15 patients have died,
regardless of my treatment.
I still remember
what they look like.
But now,
I even failed to save
my most respected teacher.
Do you still think I'm a good doctor?
Of course.
My grandfather was a doctor
of traditional Chinese medicine.
He told us
that many people think
doctors can remain indifferent
to death.
But actually, no one
can be indifferent to death.
When ordinary guys like us
see a dying man,
our first reaction is sympathy.
But when a doctor sees the man,
he thinks of whether he can save him
and how he can save him.
The doctor fulfills his duty
if he saves lives.
He also fulfills his duty if he fails.
So, Dr. Gu,
you've tried your best.
Like I just said,
in my heart,
you're a very good doctor.
However...
I guess
you want to be a better doctor.
Before you become a better doctor,
don't break down.
Come on.
Lin Zhixiao.
Mm?
Many people tried to comfort me
with many reasons.
But no one talked like you.
They did?
I'm quite outstanding
and unique, aren't I?
A little bit.
Who's there?
Run, run.
Didn't you say
climbing through the window
can be a tradition of the Music Academy?
If I'm caught, I'll receive
a disciplinary record.
I haven't graduated yet.
Stop, stop!
Lin Zhixiao,
you were just wounded.
Could you walk more carefully?
It's for you.
Dr. Gu,
you're off work, okay?
Besides, even though I was wounded,
I climbed through the window
and even ran today.
Never mind.
Come on. Let me be happy.
Have some Pepsi.
Cheers.
You don't want it?
I'll drink it first, then.
Tastes great.
Just taste it.
Come on, Dr. Gu.
Doesn't it feel great?
Just so-so.
Would you like some music?
Oh, dear.
Dr. Gu,
a big twist.
My teacher just texted me
that I could return to the orchestra
and continue as a cellist.
As long as I keep practicing hard,
I will be able to join the concert.
The wound on my head is indeed useful.
Lin Zhixiao,
what does your wound
have anything to do
with your teacher's decision?
It has a lot to do with it.
It's heaven-sent compensation.
It's like magic. You don't understand.
I indeed don't understand.
Why not let go of me?
Sorry.
I was just too excited.
It's okay.
If you want to disinfect...
...your hands,
just do it.
I won't think
you're discriminating against me.
Look at you.
How can you be in a relationship?
You can't even hold a girl's hands.
What did you say?
No... nothing.
I said nothing.
Actually,
in a relationship,
there are solutions.
There's a crack in everything.
That's how the light gets in.
See?
As long as you don't give up,
there's always a miracle.
Right?
Are you sure you want another round?
I never give in
on two things.
First, my charm.
Second, my capacity for liquor.
Don't regret it, idiot.
I won't.
Wait.
Let me taste it.
Why does it taste different?
Let me taste it again.
Isn't it sparkling water?
Should I complain about it
to China Consumers Association?
Let's challenge the real wine.
Do you dare?
A bottle of whisky, please.
Wei?
Madam.
Here. Have some tea.
Thank you.
Wei,
it's been long since you last came in.
I know
you often come
and see me from outside.
You just didn't come in.
Wei,
there was nothing wrong
with your operation proposal.
It was just an accident.
If your teacher
wanted to tell you something,
he would ask you
not to blame yourself or feel sad
for that accident.
Madam,
may I read my teacher's books?
Go ahead.
(The Ternary Therapy
proposed by Dr. Liang Zhou)
(has been regarded
as one of the top therapies.)
(Liang Zhou, professor
and deputy Party secretary)
(of Gastroenterology Center)
(Never forget why you started.)
I swear
I'll try my best
to take medical measures
that I believe are beneficial to patients.
I won't bring pain or damage to them.
(Never forget why you started.)
I'll work and live blamelessly.
From now on,
you must keep in mind
that you decide
the lives and health of many people.
However,
don't forget
that medicine isn't a perfect science,
but a changeable
and elusive knowledge system.
There's always a gap
between our pursuits and goals.
Make the gap encourage you,
instead of crushing you.
Because doctors
don't fight alone.
Instead, they keep making
human-centered progress.
I hope you'll never forget
why you started
and your mission will be accomplished.
Mr. Lin.
Mm?
Time for lunch.
Oh.
I hear you were wounded.
Just a flesh wound. No big deal.
No big deal.
Where were you wounded?
It's not a big problem.
Just a hit on the head.
Let me check.
That's not necessary.
Fine. Fine.
See?
Just this. It's okay.
Put your fringe down.
What?
You revealed your imperfect face.
Mr. Lin,
I'm your daughter, all right?
It's all because of your genes.
We both have imperfect faces.
Let's not complain
about each other, okay?
You've got good genes, too.
Did you get your dimples by yourself?
Fine, I got them from you.
Dr. Gu.
I came to check on Qiuqiu.
Mm.
Dr. Gu.
Come on, Qiuqiu.
Let me check your wound.
Does it still hurt?
No.
The wound heals well.
The operation was successful, too.
When he actively accepts our treatment,
he can have the stitches removed
and leave hospital in two weeks.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
We're indeed grateful to you.
It's my duty.
Qiuqiu,
you will leave hospital in good health.
Are you happy about it?
However,
have you finished your homework?
Son, don't be a coward.
I'll take my leave.
Okay. See you.
Have some more. You ate so little.
Have some more. Here.
Let me play with you.
How do you feel?
Does it still hurt?
No. I'm rough.
It doesn't hurt at all now.
In a couple of weeks,
if I pass the test
and can join the concert,
may I invite you to watch it?
Mm.
In a couple of days,
come to me
and have the stitches removed.
Okay.
Deal.
I gotta go.
Wait a second.
I have something to tell you.
What... what is it?
I've decided
to give an operation to my father.
To...
To my father?
But you...
What about your psychological disorder?
I never joke about a patient's life.
Thank... Thank you, Dr. Gu.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
Oh, you...
You want me to check your hand?
It's very steady.
Very steady. It doesn't shake at all.
Good.
I've been confirming this
over the days.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best.
Dr. Gu,
I trust you.
And,
thank you.
Qiuqiu, look at your grandpa.
Qiuqiu.
I'll arrange the distal gastrectomy
as soon as possible.
The tissues to be removed
will be adjusted
according to the operation condition.
But don't worry.
I'll reserve as many body tissues
as I can.
I understand.
But it's a cancer operation, after all.
Will it be risky
for my father's health?
Any kind of operation can be risky,
not to mention such a big one.
During the operation,
there are all kinds of emergencies, too.
As a doctor, I can't
assure you anything.
But please rest assured.
I'll do my best.
Dr. Gu,
I'll count on you
for my father's operation.
I've checked the gastroscopy report.
The stomach ulcer looks special.
In my experience,
you'd better take another checkup.
Be careful. Don't cut your hand.
I won't.
It was you
who said those frightening things
to my family
or they wouldn't be in a panic.
If something happens to you one day,
your family will feel guilty
for the rest of their lives.
I know my condition very well.
I'm all right.
Right, right.
We're just too worried.
I just saw your daughter crying.
The apple looks funny.
Lin,
why don't you eat the apple?
Eat it.
Or you can't have the second one.
We're like two psychos.
The tissues to be removed
will be adjusted
according to the operation condition.
But don't worry.
I'll reserve as many body tissues
as I can.
Here. Get your Ultraman.
Huijuan.
Lin Zhixiao.
Lin Zhixiao?
He's awake.
Honey, you're awake?
What's wrong with you?
When I woke up,
no one was around!
When you were asleep,
I went out for only a few minutes.
I went home to make soup for you.
I was held up in traffic
on my way back here.
When you were away,
what if something happened to me?
Who would take care of me?
What's wrong? Why are you so angry?
Do you think
you're having a hard time
accompanying me in the hospital?
Go back home, then!
We would never think like that.
All right. All right.
I'll then tell you
wherever I go.
Zhixiao made some soup for you.
Try a drop.
I have no appetite. I won't want any.
Have some.
You haven't had anything to eat today.
- I said no. Don't annoy me!
- Just have some.
What are you doing, honey?
Clean... Clean it up.
Lie there and cool down.
I'll go get the mop
and clean the floor.
Go, Ms. Li.
Go, go.
Zhixiao,
don't be angry with your father.
Why would I be angry with him?
He's sick and in a bad mood.
I won't be angry with him.
Why was he acting so weirdly
without a reason?
Did he know it already?
You mean his real problem?
Mm.
No, no. He wouldn't know.
Dr. Gu promised me
that he would keep the secret.
Dr. Gao agreed, too.
The doctors will say
it's just an operation for stomach ulcer.
Everything will be all right.
Don't worry.
Don't you know it's harmful
to your stomach and the other organs?
Don't you know that?
I just...
I'm gonna turn this place upside down.
If I find one more cigarette,
you're dead!
But it's a cancer operation, after all.
Will it
be risky
for my father's health?
Any kind of operation can be risky.
During the operation,
there are all kinds of emergencies, too.
As a doctor, I can't
assure you anything.
But please rest assured.
I'll do my best.
Xiaowei,
- how's it going with the patient file?
- Oh, Dr. Gu.
Here's the operation consent
of the patient in Bed 9.
Thanks.
She hung up on me again.
She's even more heartless than me.
I haven't touched anything.
I was just too tired of standing.
I couldn't hold it
and then sat for a while.
If you're not okay with it,
disinfect your chair.
Forget it.
What brings you here?
Do you really think I wanted to come?
Your mother,
namely my dear aunt,
said you didn't go home for days
and no one could get you home.
I have to take you back home today,
no matter what.
In recent days,
I've indeed been busy.
But what meal can we have
at this time of day?
Dinner or midnight snack?
That's not my concern.
You know your mother's temper.
If you don't go home, she'll kill me.
Go, go, go.
Go back home quickly.
Go, go.
After you.
Fine.
Let me get changed first.
I have to follow you.
Honey, get to sleep early.
You'll have the operation tomorrow.
You can't eat anything
after 9:00 PM.
Got it.
His family shall come
to the nurse station with me.
I'll tell you some dos and don'ts
for tomorrow's operation.
Oh.
Mom, you go with her.
Okay.
Lin Zhixiao,
go with your mother.
Don't miss anything.
Fine. Fine.
I'll go. I will.
Qiuqiu, have fun by yourself.