[English subtitles are available]
[Director Yoo Seon Dong]
[Writer Kim Sae Bom]
[Lee Dong Wook]
[Wi Ha Jun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Hak Yeon]
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Bad and Crazy]
[All characters, places, groups, events,
and organizations are fictional.]
I'll join you.
Hui Gyeom.
Kick on my count of two.
One, two.
Su Yeol!
Hey, Hui Gyeom. Hold on tight!
What's going on?
Where did these rats go?
Peekaboo.
-How far are you going?
-What?
You don't have a destination?
Then do you want to bite the dust?
I'm going to the reservoir,
Munyang Reservoir.
-Goodbye.
-Hey, wait!
So you're saying
you've been tailing us all along,
[and you guys were the ones
who killed that junkie at the reservoir?]
Keep your thank-you note short and sweet.
This is way too wordy.
What an awful way to build trust.
Jeez, why do we have to dig so deep?
When can we finish this and eat something?
Darn it.
-Hey!
-Jeez.
-Goodness.
-Hey! What are you doing...
-You punk.
-Stop it!
-Did you just laugh at me?
-You little...
Hey, the truck is here!
-Oh, there it is.
-What took him so long?
Let's go!
-What?
-What's the matter? Is he drunk?
-You're all dead meat.
-Let's go! Step on it!
Hey, step on it! Show them!
-Yes!
-Let's go!
-Fire!
-Nice!
-Hey, run!
-What's going on?
-Let's go!
-Yes!
Gosh, hold on.
-Darn it!
-Hey! Go away!
-Hey!
-Darn you! What are you doing?
Hey, hold tight!
-Hey!
-Go to the other side!
-You little...
-Hey!
Darn it!
-Get lost!
-Darn you!
-Hey! Get lost!
-Stop the car, you piece of...
No!
Hey, hold tight!
-No!
-Run!
-Shoot!
-Darn it!
Hey!
Help! Get us out!
Step on it, Su Yeol!
You idiot!
Hey, that's... Isn't that Su Yeol?
Looks like Captain has lost his mind.
Hey, that's...
No, this is not good. Stop Su Yeol.
Hey, Su Yeol. Ryu Su Yeol!
Ryu Su Yeol! Stop!
Hey!
Stop!
[Yeol Yeol Pizza]
Yeol Yeol Pizza for the passionate you!
[Episode 7]
Forget it.
Why did you lie to me all this time?
[Yeol Yeol Pizza]
-Because it's dangerous.
-But unfortunately, we're sold out today.
And I didn't really lie to you.
It's the same thing!
Since when did you volunteer
to do all the dangerous stuff?
Do you have a burning sense of justice?
No, you don't!
I did the dangerous stuff.
He's the one who hates injustice.
All you used to do was take credit
for our hard work!
-You punk. You're talking as if--
-That was so dangerous.
What if you got hurt
while doing it all on your own?
Did you think I'd say,
"Thanks for sparing me from getting hurt"?
Did you think I'd appreciate it?
That's why you didn't tell me?
This is so frustrating!
-Jeez, my ears.
-Hey, come on.
Then what should we do first?
[About the Eye...
It's coming from Russia.]
Up until a while ago,
only the people from Russia knew about it.
[To get them, you had to
go to where Korean Russians lived.]
["Do Yu Gon Visits Scholarship Foundation
Ceremony for Goryeo Descendants"]
[But I heard]
[they recently seized Munyang.]
[The Establishment Ceremony
of Scholarship Foundation]
[And the quaintly is top-notch.]
This punk is...
This guy was with Do Yu Gon
at the time of his arrest.
-Yes.
-Correct, his name is Andrei Kang.
Bring it on.
We're guessing he deals the Eye.
It looks like Andrei has become
Kim Gye Sik's new partner for now.
But it's all just a speculation
at the moment.
There's someone who can confirm it for us.
Inmate 2023, you have a visitor.
Hey.
Goodness. You look awfully upset.
You must've heard
what happened at the junkyard.
I'm surprised that you're still alive.
Jeez.
Hey, you're arrogant
on top of being stupid.
I heard your attorney rarely visits you.
I suppose you still don't see
that you're totally doomed now.
Take it from me, an experienced cop.
You'll never get out of here.
Even if you do, you'll have nowhere to go
with the junkyard gone.
Look at you acting all tough.
I know you came here
to beg me to rat out Captain Kim.
To beg you? Are you insane?
Hey, even if you rat him out now,
who'd believe you?
No one would believe a dirtbag like you.
Kim Gye Sik just used you
to clean up his mess. You fool.
How dare you? Are you crazy?
Jeez, that startled me.
You think it's unfair, right?
You must be angry.
All you did was follow the orders.
Hey!
You don't need to rat out Kim Gye Sik.
Just tell us this.
The one who makes the Eye.
Kim Gye Sik's new partner.
It's got to be one of these people.
You'd better tell us.
We should catch his new friend
so he'd no longer neglect his old pal,
you know?
Or you could think of it
as your golden opportunity
to get back at Kim Gye Sik
for what he did to you.
Think wisely.
Kim Gye Sik did a good job
getting things organized for us.
Our numbers have improved a lot.
Good job.
But you know, he even shot
and killed his own colleagues.
Can we really trust him?
I never trusted him.
We needed him, that's all.
For how much longer?
I don't know.
[Your cooperation will be appreciated.]
Have you seen this man before?
I'm not sure.
So about Andrei Kang.
It doesn't seem like anyone in the area
or at the center knows him.
In any case, we did receive a tip
that he was recently seen
near Yeonbu-dong,
[so let's search the area.]
[Yeonbu Intersection,
Munyang Foreign School]
[And it looks like Do Yu Gon sold
a courier company that was once owned]
[by his wife.]
[Can you look into that too?]
Okay, I got Yeonbu-dong. All right.
♫ Kungtari shabara ♫
-♫ Kungtari ♫
-Are you here to play?
I'm just trying to cheer you on, Yeol.
You? Cheer me on? Funny.
Okay, I'll be honest.
I get to see Hui Gyeom every day.
Unbelievable.
Don't you see
that I'm having such a hard time?
Shouldn't you have bonded with me more
by now?
You heartless jerk.
All you do is talk about Hui Gyeom.
Hey, Su Yeol. Are you jealous now?
What?
"Jealous"?
Hey, I don't have time to be jealous.
-I'm--
-We just passed him.
-Who?
-Andrei.
What?
-Where? Where is he?
-You believed that?
Darn you.
That's not funny! You little...
Jeez, what is wrong with that jerk?
What? Hold on.
[He was with Andrei
when we caught Do Yu Gon.]
[Y Courier]
-Hey!
-Hey, let's go.
Hurry! Turn the car around.
[You're so dead.]
[Focus, Su Yeol. Calm down.]
[Y Courier]
Darn it.
-Su Yeol.
-Jeez! You scared me.
Let's go in there.
Again? Are you insane?
Come on. It's okay.
It's a different truck.
Let's hide in there and find out
whether it really is him or not.
-Go! Quick.
-Darn it.
-Go!
-Okay! All right.
Are you scared?
Scared, my foot!
You are scared.
[Y Courier]
Why...
Why won't this go in?
Darn it.
[Y Courier]
Again?
[Eyes Candy]
Hello.
Hello. I'm Inspector Lee Hui Gyeom
from Munyang Police Agency.
[Eyes Candy]
We're trying to track down
an important suspect at the moment.
May I check the footage
from your outdoor security camera?
That camera has been broken
for a long time.
At the moment,
we only have cameras inside.
Is that right?
[Eyes Candy]
Well...
Then by any chance...
Have you ever seen this man?
I'm not sure.
Excuse me.
Can you please take a good look?
I'm really not sure.
[Y Courier]
Hey. Get off of me, you fool.
I want to, you fool.
No, not like that. Move your butt.
-Hey...
-Move it, will you?
-I did!
-It's so hot in here.
Hey.
This is not looking good.
Should we ask him to let us out?
Hey, do you want to advertise
that we're looking for that scumbag?
You're so dumb.
-Breathe quietly, will you?
-Darn you.
I can't do this.
I'm sweating like a pig too, you idiot.
Don't move.
I'm going to take this off.
What? Take off what?
-I need to...
-Why? Why would you take that off?
I'm boiling! I'm so hot right now!
You freak! Anybody in their right mind
would take their top off.
Who takes their pants off?
You crazy idiot!
I'm boiling right now, you jerk!
Idiot! If you take that off
in this situation right now,
it'll look so weird.
Think about that, you twerp!
Is there water here? Water...
No. No way. Don't.
-I need some water.
-No, don't.
My bladder is about to burst.
Please don't.
-I need water.
-No.
-If you drink water...
-Water.
[Water]
Hey, you know what will happen to me
if you drink water. Don't.
-Hold on.
-No, don't.
No! Please, no...
Why is it right there?
Nice!
No, don't.
-Su Yeol.
-No.
-Water!
-No, don't.
Please, no...
No!
Don't! Please don't...
I feel so much better now!
No! You idiot. Can you please stop?
Hey.
If you're done, hand over the bottle.
-What?
-Now! Hand over the bottle!
You mean, this?
Darn it.
What are you doing, Su Yeol?
What do you think? You idiot.
-Look at you, a full-fledged adult.
-What are you looking at?
Obviously, I'm an adult.
[Y Courier]
Move. I said, move!
My legs fell asleep.
What's he doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Do you want to get locked up again?
Come on!
It's the Eye.
Darn it.
Go back in. We have to hide again.
He's coming.
[Y Courier]
You're all dead meat.
Hey!
Hey, be safe. And get Andrei first.
You be safe too!
-You punk!
-Come here!
-Come at me!
-You're so dead!
Hey! Let go of me!
Are you all right?
-Come on.
-You should go to the hospital.
Okay.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
You scumbag!
Hey, Jae Seon.
Jae Seon. Yang Jae Seon.
-Stay with me.
-Hey!
Hey, open your eyes.
-Sir.
-Jae Seon. Hey!
-Darn it.
-Sir.
-Hey, call an ambulance first.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Hurry. Do it now!
-Okay.
You scumbag!
[Long time no see.]
Darn you...
I should've arrested you a long time ago.
It took me a little too long,
[didn't it?]
You got your hands on the courier company
through Do Yu Gon.
Who did you partner up with after that?
Somehow, your products always manage
to avoid regulation, without fail.
Are you not going to talk?
Will you keep pretending
that you don't understand Korean?
Talk, you jerk!
Did you just smirk?
Right. Of course, you wouldn't talk.
All the scumbags who end up in this room
exhibit the same pattern.
But you see, because you're not talking,
I can't help but think
that there's someone else above you.
Were you relieved
because you swallowed your USIM card?
You see,
the cops in this country aren't idiots.
Have you heard of "digital forensics"?
Be it your boss or watchman.
We'll catch them all in no time,
so don't waste your energy.
Tell me already.
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, you idiot! Hey!
Hey!
-Stay still.
-Don't move!
Hey, Gyeong Tae. The key!
This jerk, seriously!
Handling drug offenders
is certainly not an easy task, right?
What do you want?
As of this moment,
the Narcotics Unit will be investigating
this case involving Andrei Kang.
What did you say?
I know that your team went through a lot
to catch him,
but my team has been trying
to track him down for a long time.
We had to keep it confidential,
so we couldn't share the info.
Captain.
Officer O,
make sure this guy doesn't go anywhere.
-I'll go talk to the Commissioner.
-No need.
I'm here as per the Commissioner's order.
Take him.
Hey, wait!
Darn you. Hey.
-We're not done yet.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Hey!
-I said, we're not done with him yet!
-Darn it!
-Let go.
-I said, let go!
-What are you doing?
-Back off.
-Where are you going? Hey!
-Let go!
-Jeong Chan Gi!
Darn it.
This is how you're going to
get out of it yet again?
Yes.
Thanks, Ryu Su Yeol.
You helped me decide that
I should perhaps stop being so greedy
and just live an easier life now.
Seeing you act out like this
has been really getting on my nerves.
What I'm saying is...
You can't catch me now.
[Munyang General Hospital]
We may not be able to find a way
to catch Kim Gye Sik.
[Police]
[Captain Kim Gye Sik]
-Is that for me?
-You're back. Yes.
You never get stuff delivered
to the office.
I've never seen you get a package
delivered to your desk.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
[Y Courier]
[Captain Kim Gye Sik]
How's Andrei doing? Is he okay?
You made the right decision.
He's already been exposed anyway.
He could've gotten all of us killed.
Put a hold on your distribution
and lie low.
Hey, let's do some math.
What?
Why do you think I'm keeping you alive
when I suffered huge losses
because of you?
Protecting my stuff is your job, isn't it?
I got my products stolen
and even had to give up on one of my boys,
so I need to charge interest.
I know you've been building
your personal stash.
You'll have to bring them all to me
so we can be even.
My personal stash?
What are you talking about?
You mean...
The seized goods?
Are you asking me to rob the police's
storage facility for seized goods?
Are you crazy?
Yes. Didn't you know?
[Get to work.]
When you're driving through a tunnel,
you see those signs
that tell you how many meters to go to the left
and how many to the right.
They're there to help you escape
in case you get trapped in a collapse.
But you know, I always wondered this
from time to time.
What if I have rotten luck
and get trapped right in the middle?
Then,
I'd have no idea which way to go
to escape.
Captain.
I feel so lost right now.
Have we come too far?
Indeed,
we have come too far.
So we must keep going.
That way, we can get closer to the exit.
Are you crying?
No, it's just a runny nose.
"No, it's just a runny nose."
Liar. You must've been scared.
First time seeing someone get stabbed?
This will haunt you for a long time.
When I was a rookie, I saw Su Yeol
get stabbed by some thugs and cried.
My gosh. When I think about
getting teased about that,
I still get so angry.
I can feel my anger rising.
-It's rising, like this...
-Sir.
You must rest,
or your wound will get infected.
Hey, I know how to take care of my body.
I need to do this. The muscles will help
speed up the recovery time.
Sir, please!
If you keep this up...
-I'm going to cry.
-"I'm going to cry."
Just eat this, okay?
It's good.
You two look like a couple.
-Let me... I'll do it.
-It's okay.
-Isn't she pretty?
-Your wife is too good for you.
Hey, Ryu Su Yeol.
Hey.
Hey, I told you that I'd kill you
if Jae Seon ever got hurt.
Don't you know that he has three kids?
I'm sorry.
This is why I said
I'd never go on a blind date with a cop.
Did you really have to do this
to your high school friend?
Hold on. Let's get the facts straight.
You two started seeing each other
in secret and had Ji U--
-I'm sorry.
-You don't need to look so sad.
Jae Seon will live a long life.
Apparently, his birth chart is filled
with signs of longevity.
Go inside.
Jae Seon's wife is inside too.
-Stop eating.
-Why?
You've already had too much. Lie down.
Hello, Captain.
Are you Jae Seon's wife?
Pardon me?
Officer O, can you put the knife away?
Whenever I see that...
It's making the pain worse.
It's been here the whole time.
-Su Yeol, help me up.
-Okay.
Hold on. Does it hurt? Careful.
-It hurts.
-Okay.
-Is it that bad?
-Yes, it's not looking good.
He was working out with water bottles
until a moment ago--
Officer O, I think I have a fever.
Can you get me a wet towel?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
For what? It's not like you stabbed me.
Well, I do understand why you feel bad.
I'm not going to lie.
You really hurt my feelings.
When you told me that you were going
to deal with Kim Gye Sik by yourself,
I thought, "Does he not need me anymore?"
I felt useless.
I see. I'm sorry.
And Gyeong Tae is...
He's awfully slow-witted.
Maybe that's why
I feel exhausted.
Right, I'm sorry.
I guess you feel really bad.
Su Yeol.
On that note,
do you have about 30 million won
that you can spare?
My landlord jacked up the rent deposit.
No, I do not.
You don't?
You don't feel bad enough
to lend me the money?
I do want to help you out, but I really
don't have that kind of money.
I'm sorry for that too.
Then what about Kim Gye Sik?
-What?
-Why won't you catch him?
Now that I'm hurt,
you need to cover for me too.
Hey, Hui Gyeom.
Kim Gye Sik and Jeong Chan Gi.
They're going somewhere together
in an unregistered vehicle.
So?
Are you tailing them by yourself
right now?
Yes.
But I don't have a good feeling
about where they're headed.
The storage facility for seized items
is also this way.
And I know that the seized drugs
have not yet been disposed of.
Okay.
I'll meet you there shortly.
Don't move in alone!
That scumbag...
I'm ready, sir.
Darn it.
Kim Gye Sik, Jeong Chan Gi. Get out!
Freeze!
Can you shoot me?
You don't think I can do it?
Then do it.
I said, freeze!
Hui Gyeom!
Drop your gun.
Are we just going to stand around?
Chan Gi, hand it over.
Captain.
Kim Gye Sik.
I can kill a person
without even batting an eye.
Put the gun down.
Hui Gyeom.
I'll explain everything later,
so drop your gun first.
Put the gun down, Hui Gyeom!
Put it down, please!
Kim Gye Sik.
How low will you stoop?
You should have shot me, Hui Gyeom.
You said you'd arrest me.
Just know that...
you chose not to stop me.
Darn it!
Boss Yong,
things got a little complicated.
I don't think I can meet you there.
If you want the stuff,
get the money and your passport ready
and meet me.
As for where to meet...
There's a derelict building
in Samgyeong-dong.
Munyang Metro.
Meet me there. I won't wait long.
It's funny how that was the first place
that came to my mind.
-Which way did he go?
-Where did he go?
Which way did he go?
Captain, look.
[Munyang Metro]
"Munyang Metro"?
Hey, throw the bag over.
The rest of you, back off.
I said, back off!
[Evidence No. 2]
[We got the stuff.]
[Kill him.]
We're good now, right?
You think it's over?
Back off, you jerks.
I knew this would happen.
Hey.
Tell Boss Yong that I'm sorry
I couldn't return them in good condition.
Hey!
Darn it. Talk about bad timing.
Goodbye, you punks.
-No!
-Hey, you scumbag! Get back here!
Captain, I got this.
Drop your weapons and step forward!
Come on, now!
Darn it.
This is why
you should've just kept your old ways.
Darn it.
Jeez.
Hey, I'm a wimp.
Of course, I came wearing this
because I knew you'd be here.
Darn you...
So this is it.
I was so close...
Do you know
what I had to put up with
to come this far?
Do you think I'll get caught?
At a place like this?
You think I'll let you catch me?
Darn it!
Ryu Su Yeol.
No!
-Su Yeol, help me!
-No!
Hui Gyeom!
No!
Bring it back! No!
-Darn it.
-No!
No!
-So this was what it was all about?
-No!
Just for this?
-You killed all your colleagues
-Su Yeol!
just for this?
You shouldn't even call yourself human!
No! Make it stop! No!
My money! It's my money!
My money!
No!
[Police]
Hey, you...
You... Where have you been?
I went up there alone and...
-I've been here the whole time.
-What?
-Where?
Right by your side.
Look at you, Su Yeol. You can handle
these things pretty well on your own now.
[Police]
All right.
-Go inside.
-Okay.
-Thanks for today.
-No problem.
Go in and get some rest.
-All right, bye.
-Bye.
Hey, actually...
Do you want to come in for a bit?
What?
Well, for that wound.
You could probably use some ointment.
Oh, is it deep?
-No wonder it was all sore earlier.
-Right? I knew it.
-Come on in.
-Thanks.
Goodness.
What? You still remember that?
Yes. Well, it's hard to forget.
-My gosh.
-Hey, come in.
Come on in.
-Come in. It's all good now.
-I can keep my shoes on, right?
Jeez, my goodness.
Look at all this dust
in every nook and cranny.
Shouldn't you hire professional cleaners?
Why am I doing this?
-Gosh.
-Stop nagging me.
Come here. Let me dress your wound.
Come on. Sit here, please.
I even got shot today.
Hey, you're strong enough
to throw people over and around,
yet you don't have the energy
to pick up your garbage?
Look at that, all the food waste.
That's how you get maggots.
Just don't eat anything at home.
Jeez, you're such a nagger.
That's enough. Just sit here.
Let me dress your wound.
-Come on. Sit down.
-Seriously...
-Stop nagging.
-Hey, look at that.
How can I not nag after seeing that?
In the past, I could clean your place...
[3 times a day, after food, From Su Yeol]
for you, but...
I didn't know you had left these notes.
[You have to disinfect your wounds.
Don't get hurt.]
You didn't even touch them.
Adhesive bandages are in this box, right?
[Sigh. Will you stop getting hurt?
Su Yeol]
-Come here.
-Okay.
-This will do.
-This one here, right?
-Careful. Be gentle.
-There. Done.
Now, go home.
What?
Don't hit me.
That was mutual.
I know.
[Munyang Police Agency]
Sorry I'm late.
Thank you.
What? Is he sleeping?
I think he can finally sleep now.
What do you mean?
[You were at the scene when
Kim Gye Sik killed Inspector Tak Min Su]
and Sim Sang Ho, right?
It's all true.
The person who had Do Yu Gon killed
and devised a plan to rob
the storage facility for the seized items
was Kim Gye Sik.
Do you also admit that
you were an accomplice to his crimes?
Yes.
I admit to all charges.
[When Mr. Jeong Chan Gi said that,]
he seemed relieved.
I managed to drag you here in the end.
Come on. This isn't my first time here.
Wasn't it the same room before?
When you tried everything you could
to get me suspended?
The truth never mattered to you
from the get-go
when you tried to take me down.
Ryu Su Yeol.
Do you think
you and I are that different?
No.
But
I had to hit the brakes
pretty hard recently.
So I gave it some thought
since I couldn't go anywhere.
And I did realize that
I was heading the wrong way.
I'm sure you had
a few chances to do the same.
Tak Min Su, Jeong Chan Gi,
and Lee Hui Gyeom.
They all tried to stop you at least once.
It's you who ignored
those chances, Kim Gye Sik.
Isn't that right?
-Good job.
-Thanks.
Are you sure you're okay?
You bet I am. We're having a get-together.
I ought to be okay even if I'm not.
Gosh. Are we really done
with this case now?
Almost. But we still have
one more person to catch.
We do?
Kim Gye Sik, Jeong Chan Gi...
We caught all of them.
[Civil Servant ID Card, Ryu Su Yeol]
Do you even understand
what you're telling me?
I perjured myself.
And even if I was threatened,
I still obstructed the investigation.
I also had a part
in fabricating and concealing the case.
You're not asking me to cover that up?
You want to be punished?
You of all people?
Are you not yourself right now?
Did you do drugs again?
Gosh, take me seriously.
Anyway, go through the protocol.
Let me know when there's
a disciplinary committee meeting.
Even if I get fired,
I will pay for what I did.
[Civil Servant ID Card, Ryu Su Yeol]
Hurry. Bring it.
Gosh. It all says "beef."
-Great.
-All right.
[Beef]
Of course, it's beef.
-Okay.
-Nice.
Can we all vote for beef?
Why not? Do you want something else?
No. I only want beef.
-Yes.
-Right.
[Beef]
-Okay.
-Let's do this.
Wait.
This is my present for you.
-What?
-A present?
It's not my birthday yet.
What?
Is that cowhide?
Hey, you. Give me back my wallet.
Where did it go?
What the heck are you talking about?
You took it earlier.
Sir! What are you doing?
Sir, are you suspecting me now?
I wanted to check just in case.
Just in case I took it?
It's not like my wallet
can walk away on its own.
I put some money in it too.
Why did you put money in here?
You don't even have a lot of money. Gosh.
Live long and prosper, sir.
Hey.
Sure. He's going to get rich
with 1,000 won.
Sir, are you crying?
No. I'm not crying, you jerk.
Right. You are crying.
-Don't cry.
-I'm not crying. Come on!
-Hold on.
-Come with me.
-Gosh. Hey.
You just eat your food.
I can get it myself.
-This is tasty, Mom.
-Yes.
You always seem to get hurt these days.
And why are you whimpering at night?
Are you not well?
Didn't you say that you were going
to stop working in the field?
Mom, I'm the one who's not well.
I have protein deficiency.
And I'm losing hair too.
Look. My nails are chipping away.
I won't work on dangerous cases now.
Don't worry.
Mom, should I quit my job
and run the pizzeria with him?
Su Yeol.
My proud brother, Su Yeol.
What can you possibly do
at that small pizzeria?
You can't do that. It's a disservice
to our people. No way.
Why not? Is it because you're secretly
stealing money from the pizzeria?
This is so tasty. You should have it.
Just eat it.
When will you move out, Su Yeol?
You said you would be
out of here in a month.
Come on, Mom.
I don't even spend a lot of time at home.
It's like less than five hours.
Gosh. Fine. I'll move out soon.
Should I move out with you too?
I can prepare meals for you.
It'll be nice.
What's that? What's this smell?
You smell it too, right?
Mom, you owe me 10,000 won.
You owe me 100,000 in total now.
-Oh, no.
-We have a little bet going.
Hey, it's pretty good money.
Mom, go home and rest up.
I'll wrap it up here.
What did the owner say?
The water leaked to the basement.
They have to remove the flooring
and fix the leak too.
On top of that,
they have to redo the renovation.
Is he trying to use this chance
to remodel the building?
Exactly.
Why didn't you turn the tap close?
No. I definitely remember closing the tap.
Mom. Weren't you the last one
to leave the kitchen yesterday?
Stop blaming Mom.
How much? How much is the damage?
About 20 million won.
You mean 20 million won?
-Exactly. He's totally ripping us off!
-Darn it.
Gosh.
[Document for Approval]
Come on! You little...
Sir, I was totally sleep-deprived,
so my judgment was clouded.
I was completely out of my mind.
Please find generosity in your heart
and let me have my ID and gun back.
Hey, come here.
Hey, Su Yeol.
Yes?
Goodness. Look at you.
[Civil Servant ID Card, Ryu Su Yeol]
[Subsection Chief Gwak Bong Pil]
I was worried that you had changed.
I was super worried.
Changed? Not possible. I never change.
You little...
Right.
Hey, we should never change.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best to serve you.
[Gwak Bong Pil]
Salute.
I already smoothed out everything.
Don't worry about a thing.
Just go. You'll be fine.
-You're the best, Future Commissioner.
-Hey.
Hey. Commissioner? No way.
You're the best.
Hey.
Hey. By the way,
you need to get some counseling.
Pardon? Counseling?
Your story of getting drugged and
threatened was corroborated by a witness.
So luckily, you could dodge that one.
But they need to check your condition
to see if you can perform
My condition?
Our agency has a designated therapist.
You know the shelter
that takes care of teenage runaways?
It's called Dream Youth Shelter.
He works there.
Gosh. From what I heard,
he's the best therapist. Okay?
Go see the therapist. And don't
be late for the appointment. Go.
Wait. A therapist?
[Subsection Chief Gwak Bong Pil]
Dream Youth Shelter...
You made a donation there.
Hey, I bet he'll be
super nice with you. Right?
Hey, that little...
What? What is it this time?
Nothing.
[Bar]
[Evidence No. 2]
We got the stuff.
You lost my money and stuff.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Not to worry.
[No Smoking]
[Ministry of Justice]
[Emergency Transport]
No...
[Dream Youth Shelter]
Hello.
I'm Superintendent Ryu Su Yeol
of Munyang Police Agency.
Right. I got the call. Please come on in.
Okay.
[Contribution Award,
With Our Deepest Appreciation]
[In Appreciation for Your Service]
Are you going to film our session?
Yes. Recording it
helps me treat my patients.
It won't bother you
once you get used to it.
I see.
You went through a lot of incidents
for the past couple of months,
Mr. Ryu.
Yes. Well, it just happened that way.
It's common in my line of work.
Are you getting good-quality sleep?
Well,
only a few police officers in Korea
get to sleep well at night.
You have
beautiful eyes.
Pardon?
Then shall we talk about the most
recent incident you went through?
You were drugged against your will.
And you saw a man die in front of you.
And you were forced
to participate in the crime.
How did you feel then?
What do you mean? Feel about what?
You were in a situation that was
beyond your control for a long time.
Didn't you feel a sense of shame
toward yourself
or lethargic about life?
Well,
did I have to?
I go through all sorts of things
when I work on cases.
Then how about now?
Is everything under your control?
Yes. Sure.
I can control myself just like everyone.
I'm doing okay.
But why do you keep
looking at other places?
Pardon?
Do you see anyone else here
other than us?
No.
-Let's stop here for today.
-Okay.
For today? You want me to come back here?
I want to talk about your childhood
in our next session.
My childhood?
[It was Jae Hui.]
[In Jae Hui. My real name.]
[I was beaten up
more days than I had food.]
[After my father died,]
[I was adopted right away.]
[Like the day of my father's death,]
[six months prior to his death]
[are nothing but blank memories.]
[I don't know
why I can't remember those six months.]
[Why did I only lose
my memories from those months?]
[I don't know why.]
[How did you...]
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Bad and Crazy]
Why is your face getting red
like you're aroused?
No. It's not.
I'm working as your team's backup for now.
Something happened between you two, right?
[You and Lee Hui Gyeom
started this whole mess!]
Get rid of all the Eyes, Eyeballs,
or whatever it's called.
My father died.
[Police]
Stay away from me!
[She filed a report of
possible domestic abuse.]
Could that have been a motive?
So what's next?
So you're saying
someone manipulated her to commit murder?
[For what though?]
[I think I'm the target.]