Our Secret
EP06
I'm ready.
Come on, Ding Xian.
How many have I done, bro?
Are you counting?
You are free
after the physical fitness test.
Come on, let's play in groups.
In groups.
Okay, I'm the first.
Pass it to me.
Are you tired, Ding Xian?
Not at all. I'm OK.
I quit.
Why?
You don't play?
Oh, let him go. Game starts.
Come on,
pass the ball to me.
The last thing before you leaving.
The sports meeting
is coming next month.
In usual, you have many complaints
when the PE class
is occupied by other subjects.
Now it's the time to
release your passion for it.
Don't worry,
only one requirement.
I want to see my students
in every event.
It's better for you to have good performance.
Song Ziqi, you are in charge of sports activities.
Collect the signing up results
and put the entry form on my desk.
Yes, sir.
Classes are over.
Hey, you can
compete in the shot put.
Song Ziqi, are you crazy?
Hey, it's rude.
I'm serious. I reckon that you can do it.
Your punch is so hard.
You may win a prize.
Think it over.
Little Monster
Forget it.
You are too thin
to compete in the sports meeting.
Siyue
Do you wanna join the long-distance running?
Do it as you see fit.
Okay, it's up to me.
Short-distance running, shot put,
high jump and long jump... oh you are so busy.
Can you tell me, except this game,
do we have other entertainments?
What do you like?
Um, like basketball
or billiards.
You've promised to me that
you would concede me points.
When will you do it?
Answer me.
Ding Xian, do you remember me?
You Keke
One thing to give you.
Please help me
to give it to Zhou Siyue tomorrow.
-I, or you... -It took me
one morning to finish it.
Just be careful.
Thank you.
Why should I do that again?
It's for you.
Thank you, but I'm good.
I read your letter.
I've forgiven you.
Well,
that's not my letter.
Don't defend it.
It's from You Keke, a girl in Class Ten.
And what's this?
This is...
Come outside with me.
The class is beginning.
Come out.
Delivered the letter. Now the gift.
Are you a courier?
I'm just helping her.
Why not deny it?
I apologize.
It's my fault.
I won't ask you to do my mission anymore.
I'm not so mean.
So why are you unhappy?
You are close to Liu Xiaofeng
and never mind others' comments.
We all are schoolmates. Anything different?
Tell me.
Ding Xian
Can you tell me
what you are thinking?
Or you just reckon that
it's interesting that we were not on speaking terms?
I don't see it that way.
Just tell me please,
what's your worry?
Don't put these rubbish
into my desk.
The playground is bathed in the warm sunshine.
The male Group B of high jump of Grade Two will begin.
On the playground, athletes' robust posture
shot across the sky.
The ocean is mighty
and the drumming is splendid.
Dear athletes,
you're mighty as the ocean today.
We will cheer for you.
What are you doing?
I'm writing the composition.
That's not my point.
Is your deskmate in any race?
Yes.
Now male long-distance running of Grade One will begin.
All participants please gather at the starting line.
Zhou Siyue, our race will begin.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I should check the composition for me.
Just a minute.
Ding Xian, have you finished it?
My race will begin.
Almost done. I'll hand it in.
It's for me, isn't it?
I have to go, see ya.
Let's go.
I found him
was special to you.
You are kidding me.
I'm handing in the composition.
Though athletes running on the playground
can't receive flowers,
you'll embrace the rainbow after rains.
Athletes from Class Three,
we feel proud of you.
Liu Xiaofeng, you can make it!
Come on, Class Three!
That's your work?
Much better than my letter.
You can be my ghost writer next time.
Sorry, your letter...
What did you say just now?
What's wrong?
Your letter...
You didn't give it to him?
I did give it to him.
Just a joke. Take it easy.
What's wrong?
I tore it by accident
but I made a transcript.
You've read my letter to Zhou Siyue.
How about it?
Oh, don't worry.
I didn't write it by myself.
I know you don't care
but I should apologize.
It was an accident.
If you feel sorry,
you can do me another favour.
What's it?
Come on, Class Three!
Shadi, look at this.
I bought it, too.
Now we have the same earphone,
but its quality seems to be worse
than my old one.
I want to
have lunch with you every day.
Have lunch with me?
Yep.
Why not eat with girls in your class?
I don't like being with them.
Okay, it's a deal.
We are lunch pals.
See you.
I...
The male long-distance running
is coming to the end.
With perseverance,
athletes are approaching the end now.
Let's cheer them on!
Come on! Come on!
Here you are. Good job.
It's for me?
I knew it.
The final exam of this year is coming.
I haven't sent
the picture I drew for Zhou Siyue
to him.
And I haven't been reconciled with Kong Shadi.
I don't know
how to say no to You Keke.
I may admit
that I'm just a timid girl
who can't say no.
The final exam of your first year
is very important.
It's linked to
your class dividing in Grade Two, arts or sciences.
If you've made up your mind,
you should be well prepared.
If you have no idea,
this exam is a chance
to examine yourself.
Which one do you like?
Which one is suitable?
At last, I wish you have good performance!
Come on!
You can make it!
Make it!
Why did you hit me?
Can you be girlish?
Oh you deserve it.
Any question?
I have to go, bye.
How is it going with your robot contest in the summer holiday?
Got a prize?
Have a guess.
Well done.
You could go to the Huaqing University with so many prizes.
It's not as easy as you thought.
And you'll have the birthday party tonight.
Good things come in pairs.
Good.
That's Little Monster.
Did you ask her to join us?
Sister, I don't want to stay here.
It's so boring.
I'm going there.
Okay.
Why are you guys so weird?
It really bothers me.
The thing between she and she is not the one
between she and me.
Is that a tongue twister?
I can't get it.
I only knew you made me embarrassed.
Girls are difficult to understand.
Don't like us, simple and innocent.
You're innocent, not me.
Let me go!
Really fierce, boy.
You two, leave me alone.
Hey, hurry up
or she'll go.
Come on, she's gone.
Piss off!
What are you doing?
Get away!
Stand here! I'll pummel you!
Are you OK?
It's none of your business.
Okay, come back home.
Don't run around anymore.
Hurry up.
Be rebellious at home
and be bullied outside.
Why not fight against them?
It's not your business.
Not my business.
I'm your sister, so it's my business.
Keep still.
Now it hurts?
Two-faced, are you?
Oh, stop it.
You're the same as me.
Be fierce in front of me
and be a lady in school.
Ding Juncong
It looks delicious!
Shall we begin now?
Wait a minute.
Be patient.
How long are we going to have to wait?
Don't complain.
Why not?
Okay.
Let's start, guys.
Here you come.
Sorry,
I'm late.
Where are the others?
They went to the Karaoke.
Why are you here?
I've had enough of the regular activities.
A bit boring.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For your
having quarrel with me?
Or for the absence of my birthday party?
Both of them.
Okay,
I've forgiven you,
but how can you compensate me?
Well,
I'll come to your next birthday party,
I promise.
Why should it be the next one?
It's still my birthday now.
Zhou Siyue
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
It's for you.
My gift?
Let me see.
It's the nebula picture on your birthday.
It's beautiful.
Good.
I like it.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you.
Blow out the candle.
I hope your birthday wish will come true.
It came true.
What's your wish?
It's my secret.
Here,
I have a gift for you, too.
Oh, it's too expensive.
I can't take it.
It's not so expensive.
It's free.
Free?
I participated in a contest days ago.
That's my prize.
I can't take this.
Or you sell me the picture,
and this is paid for it.
My picture is valueless.
I don't think so.
It may appreciate someday.
Okay,
Take it easy.
Now I lend it to you,
you can return it when you get a new one.
I don't want to lose contact with you anymore.
Hello?
Hey, Ding Xian.
I... pressed the wrong button.
Silly girl.
Xianxian, you should get up.
Dad
It's holiday. Let me sleep in.
Wake up, my girl.
Your holiday was over.
Today you should go to school.
Hurry up. The meal is on the table.
I'm going to work.
What's the sound?
Alarm clock, dad.
I'm changing clothes.
Okay, don't be late.
Go to school together. I'm downstairs.
Good morning.
We would skip the morning self-study course
if you were later.
Sorry, I overslept.
Did you forget that it's a school day?
Just feel that the summer hasn't finished.
It's silly.
It's our second year.
The division of arts and sciences is coming.
Why are there so many choices in our life?
Hurry up
or we'll be late.
My hairs...
Siyue, can I copy your math homework?
Ding Xian
Give him yours.
You are reconciled.
I've said that
we had to maintain the friendship with deskmates.
-Or you... -Song Ziqi
Take your breakfast or I'll dump it.
I'm here, madam. Don't dump it.
Why is she mad at you?
Because of the letter.
How dare you mention it?
It's an accident.
It's so typical of you.
I'm sorry.
I promise it won't happen again.
What's the probability that
the times you get red balls
is more than the times
you get the white ones?
What's the probability?
You have to apply this formula.
Okay, keep sleeping.
No one cares.
We'll continue when all of you
wake up.
Why do you know the knowledge of Grade Two?
I've seen it in a Mathematical Olympiad problem.
So I learned it in advance.
Wake up, guys!
The exam of class dividing is coming.
You are in the second year now.
It's as important as the last year.
Do you understand?
Song Ziqi
Stand up!
If you are still sleepy,
you can stand up.
What are you thinking?
Don't like taking lessons?
These are extra lessons
but not teachers' compulsory obligation.
We want to help you
finish the courses of high school sooner,
so in the last year
you can have enough time to revise.
What do you think
why I don't take the summer holiday
but stand here to give your extra lessons.
Am I crazy?
Well, next class is Physics.
Wake up, guys.
Wash your face if you feel drowsy.
Okay?
Okay.
Um,
Deng Wanwan,
remember to hand out the
application forms of the class dividing.
Yes, sir.
Take this period
to think it over.
Give me before this Friday.
Zhou Siyue
Come here.
Shadi
Wanwan
I want to drink water, too.
Let's go together.
Okay.
Little Monster
Don't mind.
That's how she usually is.
Can you help me hand out the homework?
Nature calls.
Thank you.
I've put your name down on the list
of participants of the municipal math competition.
I'll give you some exam papers in a few days.
You should prepare for it.
If you can win a prize this time,
you can take the national college entrance exam next year.
Thank you, sir.
Though you've taken municipal contests at junior high school,
the contests of high school is more difficult.
All in all, you can make your schedule now.
Okay, sir.
I trust you.
Come on.
You're done.
It's Shadi's favorite diary.
Sorry, Shadi.
It's an accident.
Why are you here?
I didn't mean to.
I can buy you a new one.
How can you get it?
It's bought by my dad in Japan.
I'll figure it out.
How?
Buy a same one
and transcribe the content
like you do to You Keke's letter?
What do you mean?
That's typical of you, Ding Xian.
I've had enough, Kong Shadi.
Sorry, Shadi.
Don't cry.
Leave me alone.
Don't bother me.
How dare you.
I didn't mean it that day.
I'm so sorry.
Don't cry.
Forgive me.
Stop crying
or I want to cry, too.
You are heartless.
You're right.
Why don't you go to You Keke?
She's your friend.
Why did you come to me?
You are my friend, too.
Listen, Shadi.
Because of the letter
I've made such a mess of my life.
You are mad at me,
so is Zhou Siyue.
It reminds me
of my early days
in this high school.
And I realized that
I was a yea and nay
coward.
You are so brave and confident.
That's why
I really like being friends with you.
Can you forgive me? Please.
It's stinking.
It's ugly.
Okay,
let's go.
Don't cry.
You're so ugly after crying.
You're ugly.
Let's have lunch together.
Have something good.
You two
are reconciled?
Oh you shut up.
You are reconciled.
It took a long time to beg her pardon.
You know how to beg one's pardon.
Good job.
You can beg her pardon
but refuse to coax me.
I've spoiled you.
It's different.
What's the difference?
I want the same treatment
if we have a quarrel next time.
Okay.
Hey.
Siyue
Have you handed in the application form?
Not yet.
No need to be hurried.
You've handed it in?
There's no need to hesitate
since I'm sure to learn sciences.
You chose sciences.
Of course.
Do you think I can learn arts?
I'll choose sciences, too.
Are you serious?
You wanna follow me?
Stop being narcissistic.
What if Yang Chunzi and I
enter the same class if I learn arts?
I can't stand that.
Right,
I think girls will prefer liberal arts.
Yang Chunzi is too far-sighted
to choose the liberal arts. It's easier.
If you learn sciences,
you'll be apart with Little Monster.
Xianxian, will you learn arts?
If you choose arts,
we can't see each other in class.
It's sad.
I'm not sure.
I may choose arts.
Really?
Then Zhou Siyue
can continue to be your tutor.
Trust me,
I can depend on myself.
I won't trouble him.
I knew you would forget.
Keke
Why are you here?
Ding Xian's promised me to have lunch together.
I'm sorry.
Or you
eat with us.
Um,
who can introduce
this lady...
Why did you step on my foot?
Again?
Are you insane, Kong Shadi?
You are insane. Eat your food.
Hello, Zhou Siyue.
Nice to see you.
I'm from Class Ten,
the girl who sent you the letter.
I know you.
Take it easy.
I did send you the letter,
but I won't pester you.
Your deskmate
is more interesting than you.
Little Monster now is
popular with others.
Can you stop it?
Just focus on your food.
I've had enough.
Help yourself.
You are annoying.
Why are you always around us?
I'm here for Ding Xian, not you.
Just leave here if you don't like me.
Why should I leave?
Why don't you leave?
Kong Shadi
Do you hate me
just because
I'm more beautiful than you?
Scared of feeling small?
Are you kidding?
Don't pester us anymore.
Oh, no way.
I'll keep pester you and Zhou Siyue.
I'll also go to the boy called Qi.
You...
Xianxian, I wanna pummel her.
Okay, Shasha,
you go back to the classroom.
I'll have a talk with her.
Don't promise her anything.
I don't like her.
Keke
Let's have a talk.
Okay.
There are only us. What do you want to say?
Sorry, Keke.
Why do you apologize?
For what?
Come on.
Actually,
I should apologize to you.
At the beginning,
I made use of you to approach Zhou Siyue.
Because I
don't like being with girls,
I always make friends with boys.
But I found that
you were more interesting than them.
And this time I found
Zhou Siyue
had a special charm,
but I don't like to
make friends with one boring like him.
He's an interesting man,
not as boring as you said.
Don't mind.
I may prefer boys like Song Ziqi
who is more outgoing.
No, you can't.
You can't approach him.
I've promised not to pester Zhou Siyue
but I didn't make any promise about Song Ziqi.
Please,
you'll provoke Shadi.
Okay,
take it easy.
You'll look better with bangs.
Shadi once said the same words.
Really?
I think
you two can be good friends.
Okay, I should have my lesson.
What's going on with that You Keke?
She's my friend.
A letter makes you be friends?
It's complex.
Hard to explain.
I never found that
you were keen on helping others build relationships.
But listen,
I'm not interested in You Keke.
Don't play tricks.
Why?
You Keke is so popular.
If I were keen to make friends with those who are popular,
and there are many such people here,
I would be as busy as a bee.
Good point.
It's my fault this time.
I apologize.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Nice.
Better than before.