[English subtitles are available]
I'm saved.
Mr. Ai, are you OK?
I'm fine.
Go and check-in to your room.
Why aren't you returning to your room?
Now that I've brought you here,
I should go back now.
Go back? Where are you going?
Dongshan Recuperation Center.
Dongshan Recuperation Center?
It's in the opposite direction
from where we alighted just now.
Mr. Ai, you should've said so earlier.
Doesn't matter.
It's faster for me to walk alone.
Go quickly.
I'm going back.
Wait.
No need. This...
Put this on.
And also this.
Wait here.
I'm going upstairs to take something.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me. Don't go.
Wait for me.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 4]
Double 6.
Chen Chen,
time to sleep.
No, no. There's none.
A pair of K.
You... You're on your own now.
Sister Chen,
where's your treasure chest?
Sister Chen!
There. It's over there.
Did you fall ill?
Zeng Li, where were you just now?
You didn't pick up my calls.
What did I tell you?
Return the phone to Aunt.
Return it.
Zeng Li.
Be good.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Hurry up. Are you playing or not?
Is it warm?
Yes, it is.
I need to use it.
Zeng Li!
Hurry up.
Where is he?
Sorry, just now, there was a
tall man here, where did he go?
He's already left.
He told me to give this to you.
Thank you.
[He shouldn't have walked far.]
Just now, it took us an hour
to walk from the car to the hotel.
Now, it's only been 20 minutes
since Mr. Ai left.
It doesn't make sense.
He should be around here.
Where did he go?
It's fine. It's fine.
It's just an owl.
An owl.
[The mountain road is covered with snow.]
[Everywhere I see is a vast
expanse of whiteness.]
[The cold wind roared,]
[such that I could barely
keep my eyes open.]
My goodness,
can't I think of something else?
[Within the mountain, I saw a]
[black object moving.]
[It seems to be a human.]
[I thought, could it be
he's the same as me,]
[having also lost his way?]
[When I was about to walk over,]
[he suddenly opened his mouth.]
[Liu Bao Chang.]
Go away!
Don't come over!
Don't come over! Go away!
Go away!
It's me, Ai Jing Chu.
It really is me.
Ai Jing Chu?
You almost scared me to death.
Forgive me.
What are you doing here?
I came to look for you.
Look for me?
You're having a fever,
yet you purposely saw me to the hotel.
I'll worry
if you walk back alone,
so I brought you some medicine.
Here, I'll place them inside.
Remember to take it when you go back.
There's a heat pack as well.
Carry it.
And also, this umbrella.
Here.
You walked so far in the night,
just to bring me these stuff?
Yes. Now that I've brought these to you,
I'll go back first.
When you arrive,
message me
to tell me you arrived safely.
I'll get going.
Zeng Li,
the hotel
should have rooms available still, right?
That we have to find out from the staff.
Let's go.
No, you don't have to see me off.
It's troublesome enough as it is.
I couldn't walk any further.
Really.
I don't think I can make it
to Dongshan Recuperation Center.
OK, let's go.
I'd better give you a hand.
Thank you.
Mr. Ai,
when you walked alone just now,
weren't you scared?
It was all right.
Just that it's a little cold.
Mr. Ai, hang in there.
We're almost there.
OK.
Oh, right, Mr. Ai.
Did you see the owl just now?
No.
I saw it just now.
It's so scary.
The face of that owl
resembled "Liu Bao Chang."
Who's "Liu Bao Chang"?
There's no room left?
Two companies having staff bonding event.
There really is no room left.
What do we do now?
Hello, Hi.
This is Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel.
How can I help you?
[He seems to be feeling unwell.]
[What to do?]
[It can't be helped. The only way is....]
Luckily no one was in
the corridor just now.
Thank you.
Why not, tonight,
you'll just sleep here,
and we'll decide what to do when
we wake up tomorrow morning.
I still think
it isn't ideal.
Why don't
I lie here for a while,
and when the fever's subsided a little,
I'll leave right away.
It's midnight now,
and I'll worry if you go out
alone this late at night.
Besides, I feel bad.
Don't worry.
I'm a righteous person.
I won't do anything to you.
Don't worry.
Are you a righteous person?
Of course.
I'm also down with a fever.
OK.
I believe in you.
[Those gossipy colleagues of mine]
[must never find out.]
Zeng Li, are you in?
[Just what
I'm most afraid about right now.]
[Could it be we were discovered just now?]
Oh no.
It's Wu Wan Xia.
She loves to gossip.
Let's pretend we're not in.
Zeng Li, I heard your phone ringing.
Why didn't you answer me?
What's going on?
Did you faint?
Or maybe fell ill?
Don't tell me she's dead.
Even if you don't open the door,
she'll open it anyway.
Zeng Li!
Stay still.
I'm going to get someone to open the door.
[This is bad. It's over.]
What do I do?
Sorry.
Wan Xia.
I've been knocking for a long time.
Why didn't you answer me even once?
What were you doing?
I was taking a bath just now.
I didn't hear you.
You're wearing so many layers
for someone who was bathing.
Just now, you took from us
so much stuff.
Did you hide them in your blanket?
I took a nap after bathing,
that's why the blanket is messy.
So, just now,
you took so much stuff,
what were those for?
I... I...
I left my mobile phone in the courtyard,
and I went to search for it.
But I'm asking you,
you took so much stuff just now.
What were those for?
Zeng Li, you...
I caught a cold.
Go back quickly.
I don't want you to catch it.
Isn't your friend going to come?
You're going to sleep already?
My friend...
She couldn't come tonight
because something happened.
Go back and sleep quickly.
OK, fine. I'll go.
I'm taking back the heat pack.
It really does feel warm.
Zeng Li, listen to me.
Wearing these clothes to go to sleep,
you'll only feel more and
more uncomfortable later.
Leave
quickly.
Fine,
I'll go.
I'll just go.
What's the big deal?
Mr. Ai, it's fine now.
Mr. Ai!
Mr. Ai, what happened to you?
Why isn't he breathing?
Mr. Ai!
Mr. Ai, don't scare me!
CPR.
Right here.
Mr. Ai!
You gave me such a fright.
It's true that I almost
suffocated to death.
I didn't do it on purpose.
As you know,
that colleague of mine
loves to gossip.
If she sees me sleeping...
Sees both of us in the same room,
I'd be dead meat.
I feel you.
It does you no good.
You should sleep.
I'm going to take a bath.
Zeng Li,
with your CPR technique,
I wouldn't have survived just now.
Zeng Li, are you asleep?
You can answer me if you're asleep?
I ran out of water, but I'm still thirsty.
You can drink mine.
Thank you.
[What should I do? Let's count sheep.]
[One sheep, two sheep,]
[roast lamb leg, mutton hot pot...]
Mr. Ai, are you asleep?
I think he's asleep.
I'm awake. What's wrong?
I thought you've fallen asleep.
I was about to,
and I heard you calling for me.
I just, all of a sudden,
I couldn't fall asleep.
Do you still have the
earpiece I gave you earlier?
It's in the pocket of my coat.
I'll take it for you.
No need.
I'll do it.
[Seems like I'm becoming
more and more awake.]
[What should I eat for breakfast?]
Zeng Li,
I suddenly remembered.
What is it?
I remembered
who "Liu Bao Chang"  is.
I...
What's wrong with you?
Why bring up this name?
So, what happened to him in the end?
Don't ask me. I have no idea.
Zeng Li,
good night.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Fried chicken,
french fries,
coke.
Brother,
do you think these are the food I can eat?
Sister,
where am I going to find
salad for you at this hour?
Besides,
Uncle fell ill,
yet you're still going on diet.
Where's your conscience?
What's the relationship
between those two matters?
The relationship is,
when you're feeling down,
having food with high calories
will increase your level of happiness.
Come on, eat.
You'll have energy to look
after Uncle when you're full.
No.
Even if it's the end of the world,
I'm also going to say no to calorie.
These sweet and sour chicken wings,
coated with a thin layer of
peanut butter on the outside.
Why are Koreans
so skilled at making chicken wings?
The cheese is still warm.
Stuff like ketchup
are outdated.
French fries with cheese
is truly a fragrant combo.
Look.
Is this just a coke?
No, this is coke with lemon.
A cup of coke
with two slices of lemon,
it gives soul to the coke.
It's great.
Deng Hao Ran!
I hate you.
It's fine.
No need to refrain
yourself in front of me.
I'm not going to marry you anyway.
Thanks for that.
You feel much better now, right?
That's good.
Dr. Hao, how's my father?
The diagnostic report is out.
Your father's fine.
After taking antihypertensive drugs
and IV drips overnight, he should be fine.
I'm going to get a nurse to
ready the prescription medicine.
Wait here for awhile.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a look at my father.
Deng Hao Ran!
I ate 2,000 kcals for nothing.
You didn't.
You enjoyed it.
So...
So, why didn't you eat it?
I'm on diet.
You're on diet?
-You're on diet?
-It hurts.
We're in the hospital.
Stop fooling around.
I'll give you serious injuries
so you could get hospitalized directly.
[He looks quite handsome]
[when he's asleep.]
[Is he dreaming?]
[What am I doing, staring at him?]
[I was almost scared to death last night.]
[Share blessings or withdraw from group]
[Ma Yi Yi：I was so scared last night.]
[Luckily my father was just having
an episode of hypertension.]
[Ma Yi Yi：Luckily my father was just
having an episode of hypertension.]
[Zeng Li, I'm going to visit
Dongshan Temple later.]
[Ma Yi Yi：Zeng Li, I'm going to
visit Dongshan Temple later.]
[On my way there,]
[Ma Yi Yi：I'll look for you at
Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel on the way.]
[I'll go look for you at
Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel.]
[Wu Yin：Yi Yi, the temperature's
dropped recently.]
[Yi Yi, the weather's turned cold lately.]
[Wu Yin：Hypertensive patient
must keep themselves warm,]
[Patients with hypertension
[Wu Yin：especially their
limbs and the head]
[especially their limbs and the head.]
[Wu Yin：Tell Uncle not to eat food
items with high cholesterol.]
[Tell Uncle to stop eating]
[food items with high cholesterol.]
[Ma Yi Yi]
[Zeng Li, is my bed still there?]
[It's not taken over]
[by your lover, right?]
[If I take photo of Ai Jing Chu sleeping]
[and send to the group,]
[I'm sure it'll catch the
two of them off guard.]
[It's a skew.]
[So hot.]
[Outpatient Building]
Next, No. 34.
Who is No. 34?
I'm No. 34.
I'll see you outside.
Come in first.
-Wait here for a minute.
-Thank you.
Sister, I'm here.
Your wound was treated yesterday.
What are you doing here?
Sister, look.
The feeling of redness, swelling,
heat and pain are present.
I think it's inflamed.
Xiaoya,
bring him to the next room,
remove his dressing and check.
Wait a second. Wait.
Sister, aren't you going
to examine it yourself?
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
The dressing is so white.
There's no suppuration.
I don't think it's inflamed.
She'll just examine it for you.
If it is,
can I come and see you?
Can you not come if it isn't?
Follow me.
In that case, goodbye, Sister.
Next.
I'll take some of these,
this.
Zeng Li,
since when did you stoop so low
to be stealing eggs?
This is takeaway.
You can't do that in a buffet.
Put it back.
Vietnamese pho.
What are you? A robber?
It's not rice noodles at all.
Zeng Li, something's up with you.
There isn't.
Be honest.
Are you hiding someone?
I know. You must've watched
too many spy movies.
Are you hiding a handsome guy?
Seems like it's idol dramas
you've watched one too many.
I don't believe you. Show me.
No.
Show me.
Who's there?
Zeng Li, you...
You must be hiding a man.
My eggs!
Chen Chen!
Help!
My son is injured. Can someone help?
A nail...
A nail got inside his mouth.
My son.
Whose client is it?
Call the ambulance, quick.
I'll... I'll do it. I'll do it.
Is any doctor around?
Go get us a doctor, quick.
Make a phone call.
How did this happen?
Help get us a doctor, quick.
Doctor.
Mr. Ai.
What's wrong?
Here's what happened.
My colleague's son accidentally fell
and a steel nail pierced
through his mouth.
There's so much blood.
Can you please help to examine him?
OK, one second.
I'll come out right away.
OK.
Then I'll wait for you outside.
Mr. Ai.
Let's go.
Aren't you dressed
too little?
You have a fever still.
Mr. Ai, wait.
They say the mountain roads
are sealed due to heavy snow.
The ambulance couldn't
come for the time being.
What do we do?
I'm a doctor.
That's right.
The doctor is here.
Is the ambulance here?
Doctor.
The mountain roads are
sealed due to heavy snow.
Ambulance couldn't come.
Here, child, open your mouth.
Let me have a look.
Let doctor have a look.
It'll be OK. It won't take long.
How is it?
One of his tooth was knocked out.
Also, a steel nail
punctured through his lower jaw.
Luckily the wound isn't deep.
We just have to remove it,
but it won't be easy to stop the
bleeding on the inside of his mouth,
that's why he'll need stitches.
If we couldn't go to the hospital,
we could only do it here.
OK.
We have an infirmary.
Carry the child to the infirmary first.
Come on. OK.
Come on, slowly.
That settles it.
Mr. Ai.
That's right, come on.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It'll be OK.
Chen Chen is a good boy.
That's right. Good boy.
Lie still.
Chen Chen.
Can this doctor handle the surgery?
He's an attending physician
from Donghu University
Hospital's dental department,
Ai Jing Chu.
He's very skilled.
If you don't believe me, look.
The straightening of my teeth
was done by him.
You have to queue for few
days for his consultation.
Don't be ridiculous.
Wearing braces and surgeries,
how can it be the same?
It hurts.
What I studied
was oral and maxillofacial surgery.
I only switched to orthodontics later.
I'm very skilled at suturing techniques
involved in dental surgery.
Don't worry.
I won't joke around
with things concerning children.
Sorry, doctor.
I'm just too worried, that's all.
I'm sorry.
Then, let's begin.
Thank you.
Be good, Chen Chen.
Chen Chen.
Chen Chen, be good.
Chen Chen is doing so well.
You're really doing very well.
Stay still, Chen Chen.
Hold him down.
All right.
Be good.
See? It's cleared now.
Look.
OK.
It'll be over soon.
Good boy, Chen Chen.
Chen Chen, here, bear with me.
OK.
Come on, Chen Chen.
Only this injection will hurt.
It won't hurt after that.
You're a man.
I guarantee,
if you don't cry or move around,
your mouth will recover
to look completely the same as before.
OK?
Endure for a while.
It'll be over soon.
OK, good boy.
Done.
Chen Chen is such a good boy.
Chen Chen, it doesn't hurt anymore, right?
It's OK, right?
All right,
three, two, one.
-Hang in there just a while more.
-Chen Chen.
We'll get ready for stitching now.
OK.
Hang in there just a while more.
It doesn't hurt now, right?
The surgery will be over soon.
Come on.
We aren't going to see it.
It'll be over very soon.
Chen Chen, hang in there.
Mr. Ai, let me wipe your sweat for you.
Thank you.
You're having something different today
instead of your usual cup noodles.
It makes you hungry, doesn't it?
It doesn't look appetitizing at all,
but it's better than eating
cup noodles everyday.
I'm just giving it a try.
If it isn't tasty,
I'll switch back to cup
noodles starting tomorrow.
Just now, that really handsome
young man with injured leg
obviously came here to see you.
Why were you so cold to him?
To me, even queuing up at
the canteen is tiring.
If I have the time for that,
I might as well lie on the table
and take a nap.
In that case, I'll go eat my lunch.
Should I bring you something?
I'm lazy to queue up,
but I also dislike troubling people.
Go ahead.
See you.
[Break room]
Sister.
Why are you still here?
You can't come in.
Why are you having this for lunch?
This kind of ready-to-eat meals
are salty, spicy and has
preservatives, to top it all off.
It's really unhealthy for your body.
The way you say it,
seems like you're the doctor,
and I'm the patient?
I'm studying Chinese medicine.
The first step to nourishment
is nourishing the stomach,
and also less oil,
less sugar, salt,
and fresh food.
Got it.
Go now.
Wait 10 minutes for me.
I'll buy you freshly made food.
What are you doing?
[Laotan Sauerkraut Beef Noodle]
Sister,
why did you eat this?
I've finished it.
I packed many dishes for you.
Though it's a bit oily,
but it's much better than what you eat.
Thank you.
I don't have so much time to eat.
I have to do hospital rounds.
Eat two more mouthful.
Boy, don't you have to attend lectures?
You've been here for so long.
You may not need to attend lectures,
but I have work to do.
I'll throw it for you.
Hold this.
Eat it when you have time.
Thanks for your kind intentions,
but please don't decide
on your own in future.
I don't even have time to sleep everyday.
You ask so many questions
when you're here,
and chat aimlessly,
when in fact I could use
those time to sleep.
I'm really sorry.
[Laotan Sauerkraut Beef Noodle]
You're still here?
What are you doing?
Don't eat cup noodles anymore.
I'll deliver food to you
everyday from now on.
Don't worry, I'll register when I visit.
It won't interfere with your break time.
[Ma Yi Yi：I'm praying for my
father at Dongshan Temple.]
[I'm at Dongshan Temple]
[praying for my father.]
Does anyone need my help to
pray for an ideal relationship?
Register quickly.
Can this kind of thing be done by others?
Me.
Whether it'll work or not,
let's do it first.
OK.
I'll help you to ask for suitors.
Hi, one ticket please.
RMB20.
Will you scan my QR code
or I'll scan yours?
We only take cash.
I didn't bring any.
What about this?
Can I transfer to you via WeChat?
[Dongshan Temple]
Mobile phones are prohibited when we work.
Why don't you go to the shop
and exchange some money?
The line's so long.
So, when I come back later,
do I have to queue all over again?
Yes.
I'll buy the ticket for you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll transfer the money to you.
No need. It isn't a lot of money anyway.
Hi, have you finished buying tickets?
Please move aside if you have.
Sorry.
How is he?
He's fine now.
Dr. Ai, my son's saved.
Thank you.
My son's saved.
Thank you for saving my son.
Thank you.
It isn't a huge deal.
It's just a minor surgery.
Of course it is.
I must treat you to a meal.
All the restaurants in Donghu,
you can choose any.
Abalone, lobster, shark fins,
or any fine delicacy.
Anything is fine.
Dr. Ai,
when are you available?
[Cousin：Gosh, he's too handsome.]
[He's too good-looking.]
[Eldest Aunt：Zeng Li is finally dating,
and with such a good man too.]
[Zeng Li's finally in a relationship,]
[and it's with such a good man as well.]
[Second Aunt：He's Donghu University
Hospital's attending physician, too.]
[He's the attending physician of
Donghu University Hospital too.]
[Cousin：Wow, he became an attending
physician at such a young age?]
[He became an attending
physician at such a young age.]
[Eldest Uncle：Oh my, when Xiao Zeng said
to pick up a friend, it's her boyfriend.]
[So, when Xiao Zeng said
to pick up her friend,
[it's her boyfriend?]
[What are you all talking about?]
[Zeng Li：What are you all talking about]
[Group name: No work, gossip only]
[Zeng Li, remove from group]
[Who added Zeng Li into the group?]
[Hurry.]
[You were removed from
group by "Second Cousin"]
Xiao Zeng.
Let's have a meal together
with Dr. Ai some time.
My treat.
No need.
You don't have to go to such trouble.
These few days, when are you available?
You can choose any restaurant you want.
Director Li, if you really want to
repay Dr. Ai's kindness,
you just have to look after
Zeng Li well.
What are you talking about?
I get it.
I get it now.
Someone's calling.
OK. I won't disturb your work.
You all can carry on.
Hello.
How is the child?
He's fine.
We just coaxed him to sleep.
There was such a large wound in his mouth,
and it doesn't hurt at all now.
Stitching of the wound was done so well.
Your skill level
is too impressive.
If Xiao Zeng marries you in future,
she's guaranteed to lead an easy life.
Sister Chen, you misunderstood.
There's nothing between me and Mr. Ai.
I didn't. You don't have
to explain any further.
I'm sorry.
I'll answer this call first.
Sure. Go ahead.
I'm telling you,
you have to lecture her for me.
-I've told her many times.
-Brother-in-law.
She just won't listen to me.
I'm still at the hotel.
Xiao Zeng.
Keep driving inwards.
Just listen. That's right.
-Walk to the end and you'll arrive.
-Just listen.
Dr. Ai will be such an ideal boyfriend.
He's kind, good-looking,
and a skilled doctor at that.
-Make sure you grab this opportunity.
-Zeng Li.
My family is here.
Your family is here?
See you, Mr. Ai.
My
coat.
Coat?
He left his coat in your room.
Coat.
What's this?
Dr. Ai spent the night
in her room last night?
Sister Chen, that's not it.
Dr. Ai,
our Zeng Li is single still.
Look, you're also single.
You two...
It's a misunderstanding.
There was no room available last night,
so we had no choice.
-You had no choice?
That's not it.
Yesterday afternoon,
we met at the base of the mountain,
and we had no other choice.
No, that's not it.
It's because he was having a fever.
I know.
Understood.
We understand.
We're not the type of
people who like to gossip.
No, we're not.
So, no need to be anxious.
Things between you youngsters,
are up to you youngsters to decide.
We won't talk anymore.
Take more photos.
Zeng Li.
You're leaving already?
We haven't finished taking photos.
He's leaving already?
Dr. Ai.
They're indeed quite compatible.
This... Why is he leaving?
The prettiest girl in our library
finally has a boyfriend.
Are we going to have
wedding candy to eat soon?
Anyway, Dr. Ai and our
Zeng Li are really compatible.
After he bought me a ticket,
he left.
I looked everywhere for him.
He might've left by now.
You didn't ask for his WeChat?
That isn't your style.
[After what happened with Zhang Teng,]
I daren't take initiative anymore.
It's too bad.
Such a handsome guy
and so kind too.
He's exactly my ideal type.
You should stop thinking about him then.
It means you two
aren't meant to be.
Go look for Zeng Li, quick.
[Who knows what she's doing?]
[She hasn't picked up calls.]
-Dr. Wu, you've got a patient.
-Coming.
I'll talk to you again.
My patient's here. I'm hanging up.
I'm not done yet. Wu Yingg!
Hello?
I'll just give this a try.
I ask for your blessing.
Grant me a good relationship.
Also, grant my two good friends,
Zeng Li and Wu Yingg the same.
Please.
[A peaceful life]
Wait.
[My wish was heard.]