Neptune
not sleeping so late
I have been disturbed in Quanxian during this time.
thanks to you too
My body can gradually recover
I have something to ask you
You said
Free watch at kisskh.me
i know i forgot something
But these things should be about you
Sister Hongyuan and His Royal Highness the Prince
They are all speechless
So I had to ask you
what happened to me
and
Is this bead related to you?
the things you can't remember
do you still care
I've been trying to piece together
memory left in mind
Free watch at kisskh.me
But I can't remember
even if i tell you
That's just a story
Why are you obsessed with this?
Maybe these memories are important to me
doesn't it matter
As long as you live it's more important than anything
I plan to leave the Quanxian camp tomorrow.
Before my brother came back from Taoyuan County
I will take care of Na Sheng in the hut
if you have something to do
If there is anything you can come to me anytime
I can no longer protect you
I don't want you and me in the next danger
It's best if you live
It doesn't matter if you can't remember me
as long as you live
more important than anything
Why does he look so sad
how do i remember this
Neptune
Si Shi
Bai Ying, she forgot her past with me
Is this forcibly opening the five rhymes and six senses?
the result in exchange?
Bai Ying and I are destined to never be together
She unlocked the seal of the Dragon God for me
But I can't carry the power of the Dragon God
I saved her life
She forgot her relationship with me
you have tried your best
no self-blame
Si Shi
I decided to practice cracking again to fight the prey
absolutely not
The art of cracking is even worse than the art of mirror
I know
But apart from the fissure
there is no other way
can defeat the prey
if there is another way
Obtain the power of the Dragon God
I won't take the risk of practicing fission
Master this thing
I don't want people to know
I sometimes think
Does the Dragon God think
I'm not a real sea king
Dragon God seems to have another meaning
Yes, some time ago
has a mysterious power
call me with ice crystals
call you
It seems to be the blood of the emperor
Bloodline of the Emperor
Since the Dragon God's seal was lifted
Everything just got more chaotic
maybe clean up the mess
possible to find
Free watch at kisskh.me
How to get the power of the dragon god
correct
I saw someone enter the ice room today
I thought it was you
But when I got in, there was no one there
Who is it
Nasheng
Yanxi
Yanxi, you are awake
Great, great, you're finally awake
you're scaring me
I thought I'd never see you again
Nasheng
you overwhelmed me
I'm sorry I'm so excited
I didn't hurt you
Did you suffer a lot in prison?
It's my fault
is my problem
I shouldn't have left you back alone
made you suffer so much
good thing you're all right
If the spirit of tranquility is in the sky
see you awake
She should be happy
Yanxi, don't get up
Zhixiu said
Your body just needs rest
you drink first
I'll come by myself
You just woke up and your body is still weak
I'll come
what to see
nothing
You just woke up and you are still very weak
I'm right here with you
to wipe
Little Lord
You've been getting worse over the past two days
Do you want me to check it for you
i'm fine
I still don't understand
Now that the young master has unlocked the seal of the Dragon God
Obtained the power of the Dragon God
Why is it still being attacked?
I'm just a little sick
Just take a few days off
Little Lord
no matter what happens
You should take your body first
If you have something that needs to be repaired
Anything can be repaired
Thank you Zhixiu
ice cube brother ice cube brother
What is Sheng looking at?
why haven't you left
I will go back to the wooden house with my sister Bai Ying in a while.
do you want to send us
someone should escort you
Be careful on the road
Si Shi
What's the matter with you, why are you so weak
I've been feeling worse and worse these days
It's because of the cracking technique
Neptune
Sir, I know what you're going to say
there is something i want to ask you
You guarded the spring for thousands of years
I believe you will never lie to me
I would like to know
Am I the King of the Sea?
of course you are
You have the mark of the Dragon God behind you
You can also call me through ice crystals
you are the emperor
Maybe the dragon god is not looking for me at all
seven thousand years ago
I keep the blood of the sea emperor in the spirit bead
Yuji swallowed and gave birth to you
You have the blood of the Emperor of the Sea running through you.
born at the same time
And my brother Suno
Suno is dead
what if he hadn't died
Maybe he can carry the power of the Dragon God
Maybe he's the real King of the Sea
The Dragon God may be testing you
You shouldn't have doubts about your identity
Si Shi
I doubt my own ability
if i can't
Bring spring back to Biluohai first
How should I face you
The poison has already entered Su G's body
Now is the time to kill him
Little Lord
Elder Quan
what's wrong with me
It's been some time since the young master returned from the trapped Longyuan.
Zuo Quanshi was successfully rescued
Bai Wang has also left after recovering from his injury
Dare to ask the young master
The incident of attacking Cangliu and returning to Biluohai
have plans
Quan Xian's generals and soldiers are all looking forward to it
Little Lord
The young master may be in trouble
In addition to the five divisions of Cangliu
the real master
is the prey on the mirror tower
The young master has obtained the power of the dragon god
Can't beat the prey?
Attackers should not act rashly
I don't want to see Quan Xian
more casualties
is the lord
However, Quan Xian's generals and soldiers are not afraid of sacrifice
After all, we waited seven thousand years
to return to the blue sea
I finally see hope
Sir, are you going out?
Jixiu has something to do with me
How are you feeling these two days?
already much better
I don't need to worry about repairs.
I'll check again for you
no need
I feel like my body is about to recover.
Repair, don't worry
something else
that's all right
By the way, the white king left in a hurry that day.
I didn't get the medicine that I made for her
give her
Just finished today
I'm going to send her to the cabin
are you
Is there anything you need me to greet
Just give me the medicine
how did you come
I'll bring you medicine
Are you used to living here?
Habit
correct
Did you give me this light shield?
That's right
really you
What happens when you knock three times?
i will appear
That's why you came here
this medicine for you
Did you give me medicine before?
Can't remember the past
don't force it
I go first
A Ying
Your Highness
what are you waiting for
no
I am coming
are you disappointed
Your Highness
What about Sheng who is joking with you?
She hasn't troubled you lately, has she?
She said she went to catch the rabbit
Should be back soon
This is the light-shielding pearl that Su G gave me
you know
About Sunshine Pearl About Him
what he told you
he told me
If you can't remember, don't force it
I agreed
It wasn't your intention, was it?
Otherwise, how could you be so sad?
I thought I had a chance
Maybe you're lying to yourself
because
Even if you don't remember the past
you won't change me
Sorry
i don't want to hurt you
No need to say sorry
you didn't hurt me
you never owe me
Aying if you ask me
I don't want you to remember your past with him
i will answer i hope
Because only remember those
You will be the complete Aying
Aying, you forgot
you love su g
open the door
Feather magic
Major General
Why are you acting like a lost dog now?
dying
Do you still like my cell?
And something fresher and more exciting
Would you like to try it?
not talking
I have a way to make you speak
see how long you can endure
i can be here now
It's because the trapped Longyuan mission failed.
I deserve to be punished as a soldier
not because i'm afraid of you
As expected of General Yu Huan
The bones are hard enough
what are you laughing at
a mere blacksmith
designed some unheard of cruelty
I want to do whatever I want in this prison
It's just a dog raised by Shi Peng.
I am a dog raised by Master Shi Peng
You, General Feather
Not even a dog
You are not even qualified to be a dog for Master Shi Peng
you say your holy sister
If I see you being tortured
what will happen
to save you
Is she willing to do anything?
scent on her
it's me
me me me
How did you come
I should ask you this
I'm here to save you
how did you come out
help me
are you going to jail
I'm not that stupid
i have token
you can do this kind of thing
It didn't help anyway.
how did you get out
Fei Lian, help me with something
I'm here to help you
Help me find a place to stay temporarily
good
But you have to come with me
thanks
Elder Quan
Zuo Quan, why did you come out?
body recovered
Why is the elder so sad?
What happened
left power
I've been thinking about some things for a long time
don't feel right
What's wrong
I suspect
Young Master is hiding something from us
What's up
I suspect that the young master has not obtained the power of the dragon god
Reasonably, the young master unlocks the seal of the Dragon God
Gain the power of the Dragon God
Take us to attack Cangliu as soon as possible
Take us back to Biluohai
But the young master not only did not act
His body is getting weaker and weaker.
If the young master really did not get the power of the dragon god
He shouldn't hide anything from us
But now he's silent
does he have any secrets
This is about the safety of Quan Xian
If the young master really did not get the power of the dragon god
does it mean
He's not the king
He's not a sea king
then we
No, I'm going to ask him
elders wait
split
I didn't expect it
You thought you could beat me with a split
poison in your body
It's designed to deal with cracking.
The more you use the more pain
who are you
lock him up
lock him in
you go in
lock the door
i can't cry
Suno, I'm here to save you
You said we can't cry easily
I did it
someone bullied you
I must be stronger than others
don't let anyone bully me
i will do it
who do you say i am
you are suno
I didn't expect you to remember the name Su Nuo
you are not dead
why am i not dead
why kill you
Although we were born of a mother
But it was completely different
if it is possible
I'd rather not Suno
As your Su G's younger brother
Born with only pain
In order to secure the throne of the Sea King
practice mirror split
The pain of backlash has to be endured by me
how to ask
Is this fair to me
how is this possible
I've obviously been beaten
when you're being attacked
I also suffer
funny
I've never asked for any power
But
But I have to bear the pain of backlash for you in vain
why
Back then I rescued you under the nine-headed bird
Why did I get it
but this consequence
what should i do then
can ease your pain
I want you to give up the mirror split
or you die
I can stop pain
You come
just want me to die
if not
Do you think I'm here to meet you?
what exactly do you want
I'm going to take all your power
i want you to die now
I should pay off what I owe
Sir, are you there?
Little Lord
what's the matter
The old minister has something important to ask
you came right
There was an assassin trying to kill me just now
But I've been subdued
who's that person
how he got into the camp
my half-brother Suno
Then why did he assassinate the young master?
because of hate
How should the young master deal with him now?
leave him alone
He won't wake up for a while
Call everyone to the meeting room and wait for me
Young Master has something important to announce
Why are you asking so much?
don't do it soon
Yes Yes
Si Shi
Why do I always feel uneasy
Did something happen to Su Mo?
Bai Ying
no respond
should i go find him
Neptune
Si Shi
where is this
You were injured by Suno
I can only protect you here
Sir, I must go out
I'm afraid that Su Nuo will be bad for Quanxian
I have to stop him
Sea Emperor, your poison penetrates deep into your spiritual consciousness
If you forcibly wake up, you will be in danger of life
anyway
I'm going out to stop him
i figured it out
ok i'll take you out
but please remember
you are the king
anyway
You have to bring Quan back to Biluohai first
don't hesitate don't be afraid
Thank you Mr. Si
I will give you the strength to take you back
Why can't I summon the arrogant master?
Si Shi
what happened to you
Little Lord
Lord, call us here
What is there to announce?
Summon all the soldiers of Quan Xianjun
leave now
Attack Cangliu
Lord, leave now
Have an attack plan
How should we attack
Don't you want to go back to Biluohai?
How can I go back without attacking Cangliu?
But if you attack rashly, I am afraid there is no chance of victory.
you don't believe me
Of course we believe in the young master
But compared with the Cangliu Army
Our Quan Xianjun is from the military
It's not an advantage
Keep saying that you want to go back to Biluohai
As a result, no one was willing to contribute
good
From today onwards, don't go back to Biluohai again.
Little Lord
what's wrong with you today
Why did you make such a big decision all of a sudden?
Why don't we discuss it again
Yes, my lord
let's discuss
what to discuss
I am the emperor of the sea, I have the final say
Suno
Stop messing around with Suno
what nonsense are you talking about
take him down
How can there be two sea emperors?
What the hell is going on here?
This is his illusion
take him down
don't do it
before getting to the truth
Quan Xianjun could not fight internally
Isn't that the big brother who was healed by us?
How did he get into a fight with the sea emperor?
You recovered much faster than I expected
why do it
you are not thinking
Do you want to bring Quan back to Biluohai first?
i'm doing this
Su Nuo, who are you controlled by?
control
no one can control me
You are not inherently bad
Stop being obsessed
Come back to Biluohai with me
Ever since you abandoned me
I have nothing to do with Quan Xian anymore.
The prey saved me
prey
It's me you're dealing with
you let go of my brother
Su Nuo, do you want to be the emperor of the sea
just kill him
don't listen to him
Don't be under his control
Only you have absolute power
to control your own destiny
Arnold
only i can help you
become the new emperor
Useless things
Arnold
Why is the young master on fire?
Master, will it be alright?
Master, what's the matter
His backlash has dissipated
past life
The young master is under the help of the Dragon God
Inherit all the memory and power of the sea emperors of the past dynasties
The young master can obtain the power of the dragon god
The young master has obtained the power of the Dragon God
Great we can finally go home
Yes
Blood of the Dragon God
finally reconciled
It's so good
Great we are saved
we can go home
Very good
The young master has inherited the power of the Dragon God
and the golden body of the emperor of the sea
Meet the King of the Sea Meet the King of the Sea
see you safe and sound
I'm relieved
get up
congratulations, sea emperor, congratulations, sea emperor
Congratulations to Haihuang for getting the power of the Dragon God
Congratulations to Haihuang
Is this the price I get power for?
lose brother
Losing you
why did you bring me to your room
The most dangerous place is the safest place
No one thought you'd hide here
It's a hell of a lot out there
where can you escape
I'm only here to hurt you
If Master Shi Lang knew about it
I won't let you go
implicated in my feather fantasy
Is this the first time you implicated me?
You must listen to me this time