[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 26]
Welcome!
Yiye,
as the former
- commander of the Night Tiger Company,
- Left, right, left.
this is my first handshake with you,
the current Night Tiger Company commander.
To be exact,
it's the first handshake between
the 28th company commander
and the 32nd company commander.
Couldn't be more accurate.
This time your opponent is Gao Liang.
This should be interesting.
But I think that's why Army Commander Zheng
made such deployment.
Don't worry, sir.
Gao Liang just took office
and he was still not familiar with the situation.
Now the Ninth Company is bluffing.
However, we are
in a very good shape.
I will not show any mercy.
It's good to be confident.
But do not forget
you came from the Ninth Company.
Others may be afraid
of hurting feelings,
but I am not one of them.
And according to my knowledge of
Gao Liang, he isn’t, either.
It's good to be that way.
But I must remind you
that the Ninth Company has a solid foundation.
You need to take them seriously.
Sure.
You two company commanders,
let's catch up later.
What?
I am the colonel, he is the company commander.
Here is the thing.
The comrades
of the rapid response experiment group
of the military artillery will arrive soon.
They want to use the exercise as a chance
to test their previous research accomplishments.
This time the exercise arranged
by our army commander has a great influence
and brought them here.
You seem to feel extra cordial
seeing your old company commander.
Have you forgotten how I trained you?
When I was a new recruit,
I was with my old company commander.
We have a special relationship.
Fine.
Turn right.
Run!
Commissar Han!
Hello, Company Commander Gu!
Welcome!
Section Chief Zhao.
Hello!
Hello, Chief of Staff Li!
Let me introduce,
this is our newly appointed colonel,
Qin Hanyong.
Mr. Zhao.
Hello, sir.
Hello, sir!
Han, nice to meet you.
Long time no see.
Hello.
Chunyu, the equipment just arrived.
Let's check it out.
Sure.
Your… Your tent is there,
I'll show you the way.
Section Chief Zhao is the wife of Colonel Qin,
they are having a strained relationship recently.
Let's be more careful
and not bother them.
How's Xiu?
She's fine.
She attends the evening college
and takes cooking lessons.
Your choice back then
has influenced many people.
At least
you inspired me.
It's said love is priceless.
I am lucky enough
to see that.
That's it. Enough talking about me.
How are you and Battalion Commander Xia?
He's quite lucky to have you.
You do think highly of me.
In fact,
Xia Lin is also excellent.
Of course,
back then he was one
of the scout models of the whole division.
He makes his way to today's position
by hard work.
We are getting married.
Congratulations!
How about you?
Sometime later,
when the exercise is over,
I will settle things down
and bring them here.
Nanzheng
has made great progress these two years.
That's quite admirable.
Sure.
I often see her in the newspaper.
She is making greater progress and
getting further away from us.
Battalion Commander Xia,
here to pick up your girlfriend?
Company Commander Gu,
a little kindness won’t hurt.
We've only seen each other once for a long time.
Hurry up and give me back my girlfriend!
I'll remind you
she's the expert of artillery rapid reaction.
If you can't keep up,
you will be immediately covered by artillery fire.
Don't worry.
I got
an artillery reconnaissance
and positioning radar.
We are leaving.
Get in the car, Chief.
Bye.
Take care.
[Red Arrow Exercise Regiment 720 Command]
Colonel,
Chief of Staff,
Highland 501 was taken by us!
- Great!
- Well done!
Just as expected.
Highland 501 is the key strong point
for the other positions.
If it's taken by us,
Regiment 700's defense will be
wide open.
How's our casualty?
They shot down one of our companies,
but they had a lot of casualties, too.
In these two rounds of battle,
Regiment 700 failed to
take any advantage of us.
Nice job!
Colonel,
shall we
work even harder,
launch continuous attacks
and beat them to pieces?
From now on,
the positions of the two regiments
in Division 234 will
be reversed completely.
Chief of Staff,
order
our artillery positions
to move forward.
Commander of Third Battalion!
Yes!
Send one of your platoons
to hold on to Position 501.
The Eighth Company,
and the Ninth Company,
search forward!
Yes!
Regiment 720 is at the north
[Red Arrow Exercise Regiment 700 Command]
and we are at the south.
The south is mountainous.
And our biggest threat is
their synergistic strike system
of infantry and artillery.
If we launch the attack
north from the Greenstone Gorge
without the artillery's assistance,
we have to use infantry
to face the superior firepower by
the synergistic strike of infantry and artillery
of Regiment 720.
It's a war
we are deemed to lose.
That's why we have to do whatever it takes
to shoot down the long-range artillery of Regiment 720
by abandoning Highland 501
and opening the defense at Greenstone Gorge.
If they get in,
once the artillery positions of Regiment 720 moves,
we will have a chance to spot it
and shoot it down.
Hold on,
our troops have traveled long distance
and it's too hard to
launch continuous attack.
Can we still hold on?
No problem!
We just had a victory,
the morale is high
and we don't feel tired at all.
Well,
gather our main force,
alongside the opening of their defense
on Position 501,
take Position 502 in one fell swoop
and aim at
the command of Regiment 700.
Yes!
Sir,
are you going to give Regiment 720 up?
In my opinion, Position 501
was given to us by Regiment 700.
We got this position not because
the Ninth Company have destroyed
their defense.
It's a trap they set up.
A trap?
Report!
Information from the Front-line Command.
After our Highland 501
was taken by Regiment 720,
they did not continue their attack.
If they won't
fall into the trap,
it could be a problem.
So the bait is not big enough.
Is the supply convoy ready?
Yes,
they are ready to depart.
Send them now,
going from the East Mountain side
to Highland 502.
Yes!
[Army A Red Arrow Exercise Conducting Department]
What's wrong with Qin Hanyong?
How could he
lose Highland 501
at the beginning of the exercise?
In this case,
Regiment 720 can aim directly
at their company command at the East Mountain.
If he's that stupid,
that's my fault.
He’s forgotten what I’ve taught him.
Before the exercise,
I did some field survey.
If we want to strike Highland 502,
our artillery positions must move forward.
The speed of the 152 Gun-Howitzer
assigned to reinforce us
by the division,
when it’s moved in the mountainous environment,
will be extremely slow.
Now is dawn,
once the artillery is left
behind the Greenstone Gorge,
the risk will be multiplied by several times.
If we continue our assault forward,
the battlefront will be stretched.
The battle just began,
if we lose our artillery support,
how will we continue?
If we lose our artillery support,
so will Regiment 700.
Isn’t it the same situation for
their artillery?
Have some self-awareness, okay?
If we are both without our reinforced
artillery support,
we are no match
for them.
We are absolutely not at the same level.
What's wrong with you?
At this moment,
how can you puff up the enemy
and lower our morale?
I agree, sir.
Either an army or a person,
we should know who we are,
and know what our strength
and limits are.
Only then can we respond
to the battle accurately.
Yes, the experience of Regiment 720
is more than all the other units
in the division combined.
But it doesn’t mean we’re good at battling.
You can’t win on the battlefield
with fancy skills
or words.
Based on the actual training level of both sides,
if we are having a
head-to-head,
it’s possible that Regiment 700 can
beat three Regiment 720 combined.
A head-to-head?
Lu,
what do you mean by saying this?
Report!
Sir?
Speak!
The enemy's transport convoy was found
on No. 4 Highway west of Highland 502.
Amount?
More than 20.
Speed?
Estimated that within one hour
they will arrive at Highland 502.
Keep scouting!
Yes!
It's clear
that they want to defend Position 502
and delay our final attack.
Sir,
speed is the most precious in war.
Just give the order.
We must get to Highland 502
before the arrival of their convoy.
Shut up!
Order!
Gather our main force
and move forward alongside
the opening of their defense
on Position 501.
The 122 Cannon Battalion
assigned to our company,
move
[Greenstone Gorge]
at the fastest speed
towards the Greenstone Gorge.
Yes!
I'd like to see
whether we are a match for
them or not.
Sir.
If this was a real battle,
thousands of people's lives
would have been lost.
I know.
The Chief of Staff has a point indeed.
How about this, Lu?
I'll put the artillery battalion
under your command.
No matter what method you use,
within one hour,
the Position 502
must be included
in our artillery fire range.
Remember,
more than a thousand lives are
in your hand.
If the artillery is lost,
you'll take full responsibility.
Let's go!
[Cow Slope]
[Blue Ridge Exercise Ground]
Report!
[Regiment 700 Blue Ridge Area Defense Battle Chief’s Map]
Largescale movement of Regiment 720
towards Highland 501 is found.
All right,
they finally bite the bait.
It’s not that I’m looking down on Song Jianshe,
he’s just not very insightful.
Now if we take
their artillery,
we'll win.
Order Gu Yiye to
wait for chances.
Yes!
Sir, this battle is becoming more interesting.
[Blue Ridge Area Red vs Blue Posture Map]
The East Mountain is
steep in the south and gentle in the north.
It's easier to attack than to defend.
Now the main forces of Regiment 720
are all gathered on No. 7 Highway.
They have the mobility advantage
when launching their attack.
It seems
that Regiment 720 is likely to win.
The key point is that
everyone of Regiment 720
is longing to win.
I’ve heard
that high morale will increase
their battle power by 50% at least.
It's nice to have high morale.
But if the operational principle is wrong,
the high morale may become
a recipe for failure.
Why?
Sir,
what do you mean?
Qin is not that stupid
by welcoming the enemy.
[Blue Ridge Area Red vs Blue Posture Map]
If Song Jianshe prepares a deep strike,
the troops will be stretched longer.
Too many battle points and longer battlefront
will become the weak point for Regiment 720.
Qin Hanyong
has given up all the positions,
defends by attack
and gathers his main force
to
concentrate fire
on
Song Jianshe's stretched troops.
As they have the same
amount of soldiers,
then the decider will be
the quality of their daily training.
So there will be a tough fight.
Report!
The main force of Regiment 720 is
attacking forward towards Highland 502.
Regiment 700 has given up all the positions
and started to encircle and defeat
the main force of Regiment 720 step by step.
The forward troops of the Regiment 720
are already trapped.
Now we'll see
the resilience of Regiment 720.
They've had so many models
and so much experience.
Whether it works or not,
this exercise
is the test.
Messenger?
Yes!
The First Battalion?
What's happening up there?
Sir,
we are surrounded.
They've got 7 positions to defend.
How can they encircle you?
As we observed,
they gathered all their force in the forests
alongside both sides of Highland 502
and ambushed us.
Commander of the Second Battalion,
how's your situation?
We are blocked at the Greenstone Gorge.
Speed up!
Listen,
the Second Battalion is right behind you.
You must hold on
for support.
Their fire is extremely strong,
we are not able to hold on.
Sir,
Sir!
Hold on. Hold on.
Don't panic.
Yes!
What's the matter?
The troops are moving too slowly.
The Second Battalion hasn't passed
the Greenstone Gorge yet.
Where is Gao Liang's Ninth Company?
Report!
I don't know.
And where did Lu Pingfan
take my artillery position to?
Sir,
no worries,
hold on.
Sir,
reported by scout from the upfront,
8 cannons of the enemy were found
on No. 5 Highway.
The amount doesn't match.
The division assigned an artillery battalion
to Regiment 720.
There should be at least 15 cannons.
Shall we wait longer
and keep scouting?
There's not enough time.
Control the cannons
and we can question them afterwards.
Move!
Have we got in contact
with the artillery battalion?
Sir,
they suddenly lost contact
on No. 5 Highway.
The situation is unclear.
Report!
Speak!
The First Company was surrounded and annihilated
by Regiment 700.
And the Exercise Conducting Department determined
that they shall exit the exercise.
Sir,
maybe we shall retreat.
If we keep holding on,
we may lose the Second Battalion as well.
Hold on,
what about Gao Liang?
After the Ninth Company took Highland 501
and the order of assault forward,
Chief of Staff Lu sent them to
cover the movement of the artillery battalion.
Lu Pingfan
really has got me into a fix.
Order!
Yes!
The front troops all
retreat to Highland 501.
Since we couldn't take Regiment 700,
we can't let them
beat us all.
Yes!
Commander of the Second Company?
You are from the artillery battalion
of Regiment 720.
Where are your other cannons?
Forget about that.
You won’t get it.
Bro,
stay alert.
When the enemy is unknown,
you moved your artillery positions at will
without a plan of what to do when attacked.
And you just lost like that.
Gu,
today you are my enemy.
Don't try to be matey with me.
Since the commander sent the order
of attack,
all that we need is to follow without hesitation.
As for the plan,
it's none of your business.
So, there is one.
I said nothing.
You’ve already
told me everything.
Report to the command,
the eight cannons of the enemy
were taken by us.
Request all these staff
to exit the exercise.
Leader of the First Platoon.
Yes!
Arrange a squad to
look out for the cannons we captured.
Yes!
Hurry up!
Get out! Get out!
What's wrong, sir?
My waist hurts.
Ah…
This time we may be captured.
Nonsense!
After the incident of the Zhangmu Train Station,
I swore I’d never be captured again
all my life.
Hurry up!
Run faster!
Run!
Stop!
Drop your weapons,
and stop!
Regiment 700, stop your pursuit and attack.
Why?
How could the Guidance Department
be so biased?
You already entered the coverage of
their artillery.
What kind of cannon can shoot this far?
The 122 Cannon.
I don't believe this.
Their 122 Cannon is still
blocked on No. 6 Highway.
They've already laid
their artillery positions upfront
and launched a simulated artillery fire
on your route forward.
Now you are separated from
Regiment 720 by cannon fire.
They are right in front.
How could this happen?
Lu Pingfan,
well done!
Fifteen minutes ago,
the Second Battalion of the Divisional Artillery Regiment
assigned to Regiment 720
blocked the pursuit route of Regiment 700
with intensive simulated artillery fire
on the newly constructed artillery positions
in the area of Sandouping,
covering Regiment 720 to retreat from the battlefield.
Now
Regiment 720 has begun to
collect and organize the retreated troops,
adjust their deployment
and prepare for counterattack.
What did you say?
The Second Battalion of
Artillery Regiment has arrived in Sandouping?
Yes.
Gosh!
It's a bit surprising.
Yeya Lake is between
[Regiment 720 Artillery Positions Data-Flow Diagram Regiment 700]
Sandouping and No. 7 Highway.
Cannons are so heavy.
Can they swim across the lake?
In the northeast corner of Yeya Lake,
there is a part
where the surface is narrow.
The water level is very low in this season.
[Regiment 720 Artillery Positions Data-Flow Diagram Regiment 700]
The bottom of the lake is flat and solid.
They're able to fill the lake
with a few trucks of soil.
Song Jianshe was supposed
to lose.
But with the cover of the artillery,
the situation may change.
Who did this?
He's a genius.
Lu!
Colonel.
It has been proved that
your tactic
did work.
We have
joined forces triumphantly.
Welcome back, Colonel.
Thank you for that.
You brought the cannon here?
This is the best place.
You crossed the Xiaotuo River?
Yep.
How did you cross it?
How did I cross it?
Drove through it, of course.
Lu.
This batch of equipment
was just distributed.
It's a brand-new batch.
I didn't even remove the oiled paper.
But you just crossed the river
with the equipment.
Colonel.
The equipment was distributed
to us to use.
Shall we put it aside
and exhibit it?
If you're a woman,
I believe you'll be a big spender.
Oh, please.
Colonel.
We can only test the performance
and combat effectiveness
of the equipment
in real battles.
But you have to cherish it.
The army is not rich.
Save something for the days
after the exercise.
It's an actual combat exercise.
Yes.
An actual combat exercise.
We have to treat it as an actual combat.
But
there's a huge difference
between the exercise and the actual combat.
If it had been
an actual combat,
why would those soldiers
chase me just now?
They would have shot me
and I would have been dead.
There should have been a gravestone
in front of you.
Why did you laugh?
You won the bet this time.
He really didn't say thank you.
I wanted to say it
but you stopped me.
Colonel Song.
If you don't listen to me,
you'll be in trouble again.
Did you hear me?
Gao Liang,
did you hear him?
How could you talk to your supervisor
in this way?
I think now you know
why Qin Hanyong
became an acting colonel
but you're still my chief of staff.
According to the current situation,
[Highland 3 Highland 4]
if the infantry doesn't have artillery,
they'll have to suffer.
A quick battle
is our key to winning.
[Blue Ridge Area Red vs Blue Posture Map]
It's still morning. Gu Yiye,
lead a company
to penetrate through
[Highland 4 Highland 3]
the gap between Highland 3
and Highland 4.
Find the artillery positions of Regiment 720,
destroy their Command
and stop them from using the artillery.
Meanwhile,
I'll launch an attack, too.
Tell me your next
operation plan.
Colonel.
Two hours ago,
we entered enemies' ambush.
We lost almost half of our soldiers.
Now we have to rely on those cannons.
Hope they can help us defend against
Colonel Qin's attack.
Their heavy artillery
cannot pass the Greenstone Gorge.
Their gunfire will not reach
this artillery position
but the infantry can come here.
Niudu Outpost lies
on the west of this place.
There's a high mountain and a dense forest.
The weather is bad today.
It's very easy for them to
dispatch two squads to this area.
If we don't stop this,
our artillery position
will be destroyed sooner or later.
Colonel,
there is
nothing special
about your plan.
Even if you're going
to keep glaring at me today,
I'll still say it.
I'm sure
Lu Pingfan will expect
you to send people to deal with it.
I believe he'll have a countermeasure
and strengthen the protection
of the artillery.
If, at this moment,
we still only order a company
to launch an attack,
they'll be captured.
Come on.
Let's listen to
Gu Yiye's idea.
Come on.
Let's follow your plan.
Send a company
to penetrate.
But...
Let me lead a squad of twenty people
to carry out a raid.
What a dirty trick!
What if you can't find them?
Then we’ll left him
with a company of cannon fodders.
Company Commander really understands me.
Thank you for trusting me, Colonel.
Gao Liang.
Just be straightforward.
The artillery is performing
simulated shooting.
According to the exercise rules,
they can only learn the general direction
of our artillery
from the Guidance Department.
They cannot rely on this
to ascertain
the specific location
of our artillery position.
They can't even ascertain the location.
How can they destroy the artillery position?
It's all about math.
What will you get if you
add Qin Dapao's ambition,
Li Shaobing's craftiness,
and Gu Yiye's raid ability together?
You'll lose if you think you're lucky.
Commissar Han.
[Blue Ridge Exercise Ground]
The data-flow diagram of the artillery
of Regiment 720 has already been made.
Encrypt it.
Yes.
Commissar Han.
Commander Gu?
What are you doing here?
Can I ask you
a question?
The war is going to break out.
We can't violate the rules.
Why are your clothes covered in dirt?
Learning from an old comrade
is not a violation of rules, right?
Listen.
I'll only answer technical questions.
I'll never provide you
with any war information.
Got it.
As a front-line commanding officer,
I'll give you battle reports
to help you instantly store data
and analyze it.
That's the reason why your group
came here, right?
At dawn,
when our army chased Regiment 720,
[Blue Ridge Exercise Ground]
we were stopped by gunfire.
Here's the location.
Take this as the origin point.
There are three open grounds
in the range of Position 122.
The enemy gunfire
came from the northwest.
Position 122
needs open terrain.
Therefore, we can tell
that the enemy
artillery position
is likely to
be on the open ground
at the right rear of Niudu Outpost.
My speculation is right, isn't it?
No, but...
The data is confidential.
It's the exercise rule.
If Qin Hanyong attacks my base camp,
I'll let him pay for it.
Let's take our time to surround him.
Gao Liang.
Yes.
Lead the Ninth Company
to reach Niudu Outpost
within an hour.
If you let anyone of Regiment 700 go,
I'll punish you.
Yes.
Make sure
both the equipment and soldiers are safe.
Make sure of their safety.
Yes.
He Dazhuang!
Keep going.
Yes. Keep going!
What happened?
Sir!
There’s a venomous snake.
Wang Xiaolei was so scared
that he threw away a grenade.
However, the distance was short.
The grenade exploded and someone got hurt.
How could you throw away
a grenade so carelessly?
Even the fake grenade can hurt people.
Don't you know that?
Send him to the Combat Medic now!
Hurry up!
Chief of staff.
Come on.
Take a rest.
Sir!
Say it.
We found that a company
of Regiment 700
is penetrating into
our Position 3 and Position 4.
I didn't expect that our prey
arrived at our door so fast.
Commander of the Third Battalion.
Yes.
We're going to have a big meal.
How's your appetite today?
I promise I'll finish all of the food.
If anyone flees,
dismiss me from my post.
Good.
Let's get started!
Yes!
The First Contingent,
outflank enemies on the left.
Gunners, cover them.
The Second Contingent,
outflank enemies on the right.
Mortars,
fire!
Fire!
Battalion Commander,
the Colonel wants to talk to you.
Hello.
This is Xia Lin.
How's everything with you?
They entered our ambush.
We're attacking them from two flanks.
Now they’ve been cornered.
Good.
Do you need support?
No!
The battle is going to end soon!
Wonderful!
Listen.
This time
if you annihilate one of his companies,
it's like
extracting one of Qin Hanyong's teeth.
I'll give you the highest Merit.
I promise I'll complete the task!
Gao Liang! Go!
Go!
Hurry up!
Yes.
Colonel.
According to the Guidance Department,
the Second Company
of our First Battalion were annihilated.
What did I say?
Gu Yiye played such a dirty trick.
The whole company
became cannon fodders because of him.
We were ordered
to try our best to attack the position.
There's nothing else.
Take him away.
How's it going?
They were ordered
to go full force.
They have no idea why they need to attack us.
What's your opinion?
I think
it's a feint attack.
They have other goals.
They were attracting our attention.
Gao Liang.
Think about it.
They wouldn't waste
a company.
The Ninth Company has already
won a victory.
Besides, we have artillery.
Obviously,
the result is certain.
Obviously, it's a trap.
Where's Gu Yiye now?
Half an hour ago, he told us
he found the location
of the enemy artillery position.
He was going to go deep in Regiment 720.
He's a little cruel
but he knows to focus on the essentials.
He's a good commander.
As long as he destroys the command system
of the artillery of Regiment 720
before the attack,
no matter how big the price is,
it’s worth it.
Gao Liang, listen.
Your primary task
is to make sure the Ninth Company
keeps the advantage
and wins
instead of
turning victories
into casualties.
Xia Lin.
You are being penny-wise.
If you do that,
the Ninth Company will be ruined.
Gao Liang.
If you do anything rash,
the Ninth Company will be ruined for real!
Obey my order.
What will happen if I don't obey it?
If you don't obey it,
I'll tell the Conducting Department
that you disobeyed my order
and ask them to
punish you.
He Dazhuang!
Yes!
Lead the Third Platoon. Follow me.
All of them are here.
The eight cannons are all here.
You're amazing, Company Commander.
We just reached here
without even firing once.
Outflank them at the rear
with the First Contingent.
Make sure you destroy
their artillery's command system.
OK.
Guys, follow me.
Don't move!
Commander Gao.
You ran so fast.
I have a question for you.
Did you join Regiment 720?
No.
But Gao,
soon we'll
annihilate Regiment 720.
You're not that good.
According to the exercise rules,
you've already lost.
Really?
Put the guns down.
If it was the real battlefield,
now
I should capture all of you.
But today I'll be a traitor
to Regiment 720
because we'll have to
fight on the real battlefield one day.
Why?
Regiment 720 needs a crushing defeat.
Only in this way, can it be a real exercise.
If it was a real exercise,
you should kill me now.
What I pursue is not the authenticity
or the exercise.
What I pursue
is the thing behind the real exercise.
So now my best solution
is to let you go.
Got it.
I use my blood
to show my deep love for my country.
Gao is going to
be a tragic hero this time.
You don't get it!
To be a traitor.
Do you know how hard it is for me?
Gao.
Let's have a talk.
There are more ways to
make a change.
Even if I can't change it,
I promise you
the reality will never change me.
Their fraud really made me
angry.
Gao Liang.
Enough. Time is running out.
Blue Army, attention, please!
Today I'll let you go.
Before the deadline,
make sure
you occupy Red Army's artillery position.
Help Regiment 720. It's your former regiment.
You can go.
Everyone,
follow me!
[Regiment 720 Artillery Positions Data-Flow Diagram Regiment 700]
Sir!
The command system of the artillery position
of Regiment 720
was destroyed
by Qin Hanyong's small contingent.
The Conducting Department considers it
a valid attack.
Then why the artillery of Regiment 720
is still firing?
We received a notification.
Regiment 720
created the second command system
a long time ago.
Qin Hanyong's small contingent
only destroyed one of the stand-ins.
Go and check.
Who came up with this idea?
Good job.
Yes!
It's time to launch an attack.
What's wrong with Gu Yiye?
He's nothing
but eye candy.
It's really hard
to deal with Lu Pingfan.
He's smarter than me.
We need not only the interception
but also a countermeasure.
Countermeasure?
Yes, countermeasure.
Our infantry
cannot beat theirs.
Soldiers and canons’ synergy
is our advantage.
Gao Liang’s strategy is superior.
When they're on their way
to the place of departure,
he thought
there might be many accidents
in the real battle
so he brought a company's
100-mm mortars.
Colonel.
Our attacker army
was attacked by the gunfire of Regiment 720.
Order the army
to hang in there,
separate
and head for the front-line position.
Fight against Song Jianshe.
If we have to die, die with him!
Yes!
Company Commander!
The ammunition dump is at the front
of this place.
They're prepared.
We can't blow it up in a short time.
Don't worry.
They don't have a lot of people.
The gunfire on the left flank is powerful.
Lead two soldiers,
carry out a raid from the left flank
to attract the gunfire of our enemies.
Rest of you
carry out a raid
from the right flank with me.
Blow their ammunition dump
at any price.
Destroy their
cannons!
Sergeant of the First Squad, follow me!
Let's go!
Company Commander!
Enemies on the left
outflanked us from the rear.
Now there are enemies
at both the front and the rear.
What should we do?
Time is running out.
If we don't hurry up,
Colonel and his people will be annihilated.
Company Commander.
Hurry up.
Give orders.
I did that.
Am I wrong?
No, you're not.
We don't care about the defeat.
What we care is how we can win
in the future.
Stop hesitating.
Cease fire!
Let them go.
Stop them!
Don't let them run away!
Stop them.
What are you doing?
Your artillery's ammunition dump
has already been blown up by us.
Just a few
of you?
No.
Gao Liang helped us.
He betrayed Regiment 720.
If he didn't put the weapon down,
we would never win.
He's brave.
Don't you feel ashamed?
If he didn't do that,
Regiment 720
would keep dreaming
in their fantasy world.
Wake them up in a harsh way.
It's worth it.
It's a fraud.
My victory is disgraceful.
Victory?
You just won the trophy.
We got
more than you.
Left, right, left.
Leave some water for me.
Three, four.
I let you win the exercise.
Why can't I drink your water?
Enough.
Don't take it for granted.
I have a question for you.
Have you ever thought of the consequence?
Forget about the distant future.
I had to save the Ninth Company, right?
I'm a company commander.
I have to be responsible
for the whole company.
They all said as soldiers,
we have to make sacrifices.
But I can't let my soldiers
sacrifice
for some useless people.
That's not their goal.
As members of a Training Company,
they’ve never practiced
throwing real grenades.
I just returned from the hospital.
Two of my soldiers got injured.
One has an injured leg
and the other has an injured arm.
That’s the result of cheating
so we had to lose once.
Destroy the team and rebuild it.
Am I right?
No making without breaking.
In the future,
I'll be strict with the training.
Do you know what's the biggest problem
of the Ninth Company now?
They don't know who they are now.
They became overconfident
after being praised by others.
Thinking that my old company is like this now,
I feel bad.
I'm sorry for
the seniors who have passed away.
It's not too late
to change.
I can help you
make Night Tiger Company
better.
Just try to
catch up with us.
What are you gonna do?
You're the light
that will never be swallowed by the darkness.
What can I do for you?
Cows and sheep flock
but beasts
live alone.
Are you going to wait?
I'll observe
and think.
I'll make changes
in my way.
What you did
is heroically tragic
but it would affect a lot of things.
Are you scared?
No, I'm not.
But I know
what reverence and respect are.
If I really want to make changes,
I'll carry out a plan step by step.
I won't make a drastic change
like you.
[Gulf War Materials]
The onslaught on Saddam's line of defense
prevented Iraq from knowing
the real intention
of the Multinational Force.
When Saddam finally realized,
it's too late.
Kuwait was liberated.
Iraq had surrendered.
The Gulf War has ended.
Did you see it?
What were they doing?
What were you doing?
Before today's meeting,
someone talked to me.
He said someone cheated
in the exercise.