(The Devil Judge)
(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Episode 3)
Are you looking for this?
You knew.
(Safe Korea, it is now a reality.)
Why are you doing this?
Why am I doing this?
Yes.
Because I can.
What?
Possibility is like a drug.
Get down!
(Your judgment brings justice.)
Is he dead?
No.
Did you kill him?
Look. He's not dead.
It's not fun at all.
Why is it not fun?
Where am I?
It's not paradise.
I wouldn't push it if I were you.
(Do not enter, Investigation in progress)
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
Alpha, check in.
(Stop)
The nation's in shock after a bomb went off in a judge's office.
The public's main focus is the safety...
of Judge Kang Yo Han.
When the case was reported,
the police started an investigation...
and collected the security footage and the visitors' log.
- He's coming out! - It's Kang Yo Han.
He's here!
- Let's get a photo. - Excuse me.
- He's coming out. - There he is.
Judge Kang, are you badly injured?
How are you?
- Are you all right? - Are you safe?
I am, thanks to the public's concern.
Are you not badly wounded?
It's bearable.
Who's behind it?
We haven't concluded that yet.
Could we say it's an act of terror from a party who was...
- upset with the live court show? - That's possible.
Will the live court show be stopped?
I have something to say to you.
It looks like someone is very scared.
An act of cowardly terror cannot halt the public's judgment.
(I will not give in to terror.)
The live court show will go on as planned.
What case will you handle this time?
I'll sentence the child of someone influential...
who continuously abused the weak and unfortunate.
The defendant is...
the VP of Joongwon FNB, Lee Young Min.
- Lee Young Min? - Lee Young Min?
Isn't VP Lee Young Min the son of Minister Cha Kyung Hee?
- What's he saying? - Yes, that's correct.
If you put the Minister of Justice's son on trial,
won't the prosecution retaliate?
Everyone is equal before the law.
To me, everyone is just a defendant.
Kang Yo Han, that punk.
Still, there will be a lot of retaliation.
Even if a dog barks, the train moves on.
A dog?
Judge, I have a question!
Good for you!
Young Min.
Minister. Minister.
Let's have a look.
I'm with the police.
Judge!
Is Judge Kim Ga On okay?
Who are you?
I'm Yoon Soo Hyun with the RIU in charge of this case.
I see. Do your best, please.
- Is Judge Kim Ga On okay? - Yes, he's okay.
Do you know him personally?
Are you two dating?
No. We're friends.
I didn't know Judge Kim had a cop friend.
Where is Ga On?
- I'm sorry, but I cannot tell you. - What?
His safety is of utmost importance.
There could be another attack,
so it's best he focuses on his treatment somewhere safe.
Where is he? Let me see him.
Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun.
I apologize.
Catch the culprit.
Leave Judge Kim to me.
Who are you?
I apologize.
Why are you so surprised?
Did Master Yo Han not say anything?
What do you mean?
Then I have nothing to tell you.
I will bring you a fresh tray of food.
What's going on?
Rich people...
It looks really old. How much is it?
It's a national treasure. Put it down.
It was a joke.
You're so stupid.
Don't go prying and stay in bed.
Who are you that you're talking to me like that?
Elijah.
Eli? Is that your name?
The name's Elijah, stupid.
Didn't you even read the bible?
Okay, Elijah.
By the way, have I done something to upset you?
- Your face. - What?
I don't like your face.
How dare you...
"How dare you"? How can you say that about a person's face?
I don't understand why Yo Han brought you here.
You're just a fake.
Hold on. Wait up!
Hey.
What on earth is this place?
Dad, what do I do?
What did I ever do to be tried in that people's court? Crazy jerk.
I know. He's a complete psycho.
What kind of judge is that?
Don't worry, Young Min.
Your mom will protect you.
How dare he come after my son?
Dad.
There's something I haven't told you.
Okay.
Kang Yo Han, that psycho, might be coming after me on purpose.
What do you mean?
What I mean is...
Young Min.
Oh, hi, honey.
Mom.
How can you disappoint me like this?
What is this? Answer me!
I'm sorry.
Look me in the eyes.
Right now. Come on.
Look me in the eyes. Look.
Don't worry. Everything will be fine.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Honey, are you sure everything will be fine?
How could you let this happen to the kid?
Well, I've taken care of everything,
but there was just one case...
that went a little wrong.
Will it be okay?
Don't worry.
There will be no trial.
Are you going to sit back and watch?
Oh, welcome.
Hello, Minister Cha.
What were you saying?
Am I going to sit back and watch? Watch what?
I'll be going then.
Already?
Considering my position, it's inappropriate for me...
to come in contact with the defendant's family.
This is nothing personal, Minister Cha.
We should keep personal feelings separate from work, right?
Same here. It's nothing personal...
no matter what I'll do from now on.
Judge Kang?
Ms. Jung.
Are you here with a message from the foundation or something?
I have many messages to deliver here and there.
Anyway, are you okay? Are you hurt?
There's something interesting about the terror attack.
Pardon?
It wasn't serious enough to kill anyone,
but it wasn't trivial enough to be ignored.
It was just at that perfect level.
As if to warn somebody.
My goodness. That sure is very interesting.
Maybe I'm being too imaginative.
Then again, there are people who are wise enough to heed warnings...
and people who do not, only to regret later.
That's my observation.
I totally agree.
There certainly are people who do not heed warnings.
Many sponsors of our foundation seem concerned.
With the announcement of the Dream Home plan coming up,
they don't want this case to provoke the people.
I'm sorry to say this, Minister Cha.
The privileged class abusing their power...
is a topic that the public feels strongly against.
In these important times, you should've kept a closer eye.
Does your son have trouble controlling his emotions?
Does he have mood swings?
Is that because his mom is so aggressive?
Does that stress him out and...
Minister Cha, there's something I've been meaning to mention.
You tend to have this intense look in your eyes.
It's not really a quality appreciated in a woman.
You're out of line, sir.
Should the next live court show handle another case...
It's over a million.
The number of people who signed the petition.
"Please find out who's behind the attack against Judge Kang."
Isn't it scary?
It took just one day. A million people in one day.
If we mess with Kang Yo Han,
there will be a riot.
I understand.
If the government feels uncomfortable stepping in,
I'll take care of it myself.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'll do it.
It's not like I want to do this. Stay still.
- I can do it... - I said, stay still.
Let me get you up.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Where's that lady?
Who? The nanny?
She went home.
A nanny?
What's this?
I got it when I was immature.
I'm surprised.
- Are you an old fart? - What?
Judging others without knowing them. That's what an old fart does.
That hurts.
Exaggerating. That's what a kid does.
"Exaggerating"?
Hello, everyone.
I'm Judge Oh Jin Joo of the live court.
Recently, there was a terror attack at the Supreme Court.
I'm sure it left all of you worried.
But Judge Kang Yo Han...
will never give in to a threat of this sort.
As you all know,
Judge Kang Yo Han is an extremely strong person.
Until Judge Kang Yo Han and Judge Kim Ga On...
come back safely to the court, please show support...
Who's this woman?
She's Judge Oh. We work together...
- Are you two together? - What are you talking about?
She's an associate judge...
- Are you together? - No, we're not.
She is just overly dramatic and cries easily, that's all.
- So you're not together? - No.
Are you serious?
Yes.
You're boring.
Why did you bring that idiot here?
Who? Ga On?
Even his name is pathetic.
Send him away.
Why? Is he bothering you?
Send him away, or I'll kill him.
When you can't even walk?
You said, if you can walk again, you'll kill me first.
Don't get ahead of yourself. One at a time, okay?
Aren't you going to follow her?
No?
Stay put. Don't wander around.
Is there something I shouldn't see?
Curiosity killed the cat.
I'm feeling okay now. I'll go home.
It's safer here. The terrorist hasn't been caught yet.
By the way, what about the trial?
I'll find a substitute judge. Don't worry.
Substitute judge?
This is Judge Jung In Seok.
He's going to fill in for Judge Kim until he fully recovers.
It's nice to meet you, Judge Oh.
Gosh, you totally look like a judge.
- Excuse me? - What? Never mind.
- It's nice to meet you. - Oh, right.
- Good to see you. - Thank you...
for being brave enough to join us in a crisis like this.
It's an honor to be a part of the live court show.
I'll do my best.
We're lucky to have you.
Now if you'll excuse me.
- You said you'll do your best. - Excuse me?
Then go do your best.
No, wait.
That's Judge Kim's desk.
Then where should I sit?
You can sit over there.
Oh, okay.
(Associate Judge Oh Jin Joo)
We don't have much time until the next live show.
So we should start working.
Yes, ma'am.
I believe Master Yo Han told you to stay put in bed.
I can't stay put anymore. I'm bored.
I'm not Sleeping Beauty, you know.
I can make you stay asleep if you want me to.
Like Sleeping Beauty.
- Excuse me? - It was a joke.
That was a creepy joke.
People in this house don't listen to you.
(Supreme Court Control Center)
We looked through it, and there was no visitor.
You are so persistent, Detective.
No one from outside visited his office.
Do you think someone from the inside could've done this?
Someone from the inside.
That's possible.
Right?
Judge Kang is doing too well.
Maybe one of the judges has a grudge against him.
The explosive went off near the painting on the wall.
Yes.
So what if someone didn't sneak in to place it?
What if it was planted in the painting from the beginning?
From the beginning?
Which company was in charge of the interior design of the office?
May I have the number?
I think Detective Yoon got a lead.
Follow her.
We should find who's behind before the police do.
(Se Eol City)
Sir, may I speak with you?
Sir?
No, what are you doing!
- No, wait! - Let go of him.
Where are you from?
We're from the Regional Investigation Unit.
Did you install all the office equipment for the judges...
- on the live court show? - I don't know.
Let me see your account book.
Is that the office?
Let me see your warrant first.
Gosh, maybe you were too busy to get a warrant.
Come back with a warrant.
I'll be waiting for you.
You're in a good mood.
What the heck.
This is an interesting place.
This is a furniture plant.
But how come you make small bombs like this?
You little...
You almost got me killed.
You have a death wish.
Don't hurt me. I'll tell you everything.
But you know what?
I don't want anything from you.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you everything.
My gosh, you talk too much.
I'll... I'll tell you everything.
The foundation...
Someone from the foundation made me do it.
They wanted to scare you off.
That's enough.
Judge.
Go back to your master...
and tell him to deal with me himself.
Are you doing this because of Judge Kim?
So you've been behaving yourself.
You did what I asked so here's a present for you.
Did you get hurt?
It's nothing.
How's the preparation for Lee Young Min's trial going?
What is there to prepare?
It's a simple case.
I understand you like to prepare for trials thoroughly...
- in every aspect. - Do I?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You said that justice doesn't exist in reality, right?
You said that all that exists is a terribly unfair game.
So?
What is the reason you got involved...
in that terribly unfair game?
The reason...
Do I need to have a reason?
Is there something you want to make right?
Or perhaps something you regret?
- Are you an old fart? - Pardon?
You said that judging other people was a characteristic of an old fart.
- No, it's not that... - Hurry up and get better.
Stop imagining uncomfortable things.
(Search, Seizure, and Verification Warrant Request, Name: Kim Man Ho)
Hey, Ga On!
My ears are perfectly fine.
How could you say...
Are you okay?
What about your injury? Are your limbs okay?
Am I supposed to have 2 arms and 2 legs?
You must've hurt your head.
Is your face okay?
You have a terrible personality, but your face is nice to look at.
Soo Hyun.
Yes?
I'm fine. Were you worried?
Soo Hyun, are you okay?
Where are you right now?
- I'm at Kang Yo Han's place. - Where?
How could you trust him and stay at his place?
It looks safe.
It seems he has all sorts of security equipment installed.
The person who lives there is the most dangerous. What are you saying?
That explosion could've been self-fabricated.
You're right.
He did try to scare me by telling me I shouldn't roam around.
Leave right now.
I'm in the lion's den, so I should at least look around.
We don't have much information on Kang Yo Han.
His family, background, how he grew up... Things like that.
Ga On. I'll look into it.
I'll look into everything, so don't do anything.
Again. You're acting like my mom again, Soo Hyun.
It's not that...
But...
my body must be in shock, I've been tired all day.
But I can't just sleep.
I'll be careful, so don't worry.
How long will you leave our neighbors...
on the streets?
(A Dream Home Filled with Happiness, Social Responsibility Foundation)
For Korea to rise up again,
we must first shine a light on the lowest parts.
(A Dream Home Filled with Happiness, Social Responsibility Foundation)
We, at Social Responsibility Foundation,
are constructing the Dream Home Village with 30,000 units for...
those who are weak and ill on the outskirts of Seoul.
It is a rehabilitation community that provides...
free health care and free housing.
If we all join forces together,
this beautiful dream will become a reality.
Thank you
(Social Responsibility Foundation, Sponsorship inquiry at 080-369-1136)
Gosh, that a look at that.
Bravo!
It was great.
That was exactly what I was talking about!
That is what I wanted it to look like.
It's amazing.
- It's very nice. - It really is.
Who came up with the concept?
Mr. Seo. I was so moved.
You did a great thing this time.
At this rate, we should receive some good news from Sweden!
Of course.
How vulgar.
Do you think I'm doing this for a mere Noble Prize?
This is all for the sake of our country.
Please forgive him.
Chairman Park was being superficial.
You're right. This is all for the sake of our country.
That is why I would like to say,
isn't it time to start moving people to the Dream Home Village?
You're right. Myeong-dong and Hannam-dong...
are filled with homeless people. Many people need help.
Is that why your hotels have been suffering a severe loss?
I heard foreign tourists stopped staying there. Am I right?
When it comes to severity,
Chairman Yoon and Minister Cha are in a worse position than me.
His duty free shops have suffered a loss,
and Minister Cha's son is on the brink of going on trial.
In any case, Seoul must return to the way it used to be,
for our national status to rise up and to get more foreign investments.
Of course.
That way both your fortunes will return as well, right?
I'm sure your approval ratings will return as well, Mr. President.
Nevertheless, Mr. President.
It seems like cooperation from the departments related to...
the Dream Home business is being delayed.
I guess they don't really listen to what you say.
We have just managed to finish our first building.
There's still so much to do.
How would we manage if the administration...
keeps getting in our way?
It's probably because you want so many things.
You want us to undo the greenbelt zone...
and kick out all the residents and demolish all the homes...
in the shantytowns near the construction site.
Those are all things that were agreed on in advance!
This business will save the country.
Stop with the wordplay.
How does this save our country?
Also, why are you raising your voice?
I became president because the people chose me.
The people in the shantytowns are also my precious citizens!
- Honey, that's... - My gosh. Hey!
Why are you getting involved? How dare you try to speak...
Gosh. That's cold! What is this?
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
Ms. Jung. Are you crazy? Everything is wet! What is this?
I'm sorry.
I think my underwear is wet too. Honey.
- Darn it. - Where are the napkins?
My gosh!
Gosh! I'm so annoyed! Seriously.
Why do those punks keep acting up?
I'm not the same Heo Joong Se I used to be!
I'm the commander-in-chief!
Do they think the commander-in-chief is a fool?
Those stupid businessmen. Darn it!
- Are you okay? - I'm not.
You seem really agitated right now.
Why don't you get a massage and some rest?
Darn it. Should I?
Yes.
My goodness.
Gosh, the muscles in the back of your neck are stiff.
Ms. Jung?
Hold on.
Let me relax your muscles a bit before I speak.
Right, but what are you doing here?
Do you know anything about spinal manipulation or manual therapy?
I grew up dirt poor.
Before I met Mr. Seo, there was nothing I didn't do.
I worked as an acupressure masseuse for some time too.
Gosh, you're so unexpected.
I was moved earlier.
How you understood how weak citizens and displaced people felt.
Gosh. That's a given.
Will your mind change if you got...
20 percent of the Dream Home profits?
You're quite sensible, Ms. Jung.
I'm just a mere errand girl.
Mr. Seo was the one who arranged everything.
Who can run errands as well as you do?
You're really incredible.
Every time I see you, I...
Are you happy?
What did you just say to me?
You should massage your face too.
Oh, my face?
Should I?
By the way, how did you get in here?
This place...
This isn't a place that just anyone...
can come into.
[VIU Ver] tvN E03 'The Devil Judge'
"The Quiet Mansion"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Master.
I will protect you.
Poor young master.
"Master"?
Kang Yo Han's not home right now.
This house belongs to you.
It doesn't belong to him.
(Request for Summary Order)
"Victim Lee Ji Hoon asked defendant Lee Young Min to park."
"The defendant slapped the victim's cheek and hit his abdomen."
Does Lee Young Min have anger management issues?
Why would he do this at a restaurant?
I guess he didn't have to curb his anger.
Why would he?
Kim Yeon Hae? Hello.
Thanks for waiting.
(Menu)
Why did we come to this dirty place?
This place was on TV for being an alley gourmet diner.
It's really famous.
It's a hotspot.
Sure. You eat all you want.
He can't park here.
Who owns car number 0615?
(Menu)
- Is 0615 your car? - No.
- Is 0615 your car? - It's ours.
It's your car.
Do you own the car outside?
- So what? - Do you mind moving it?
- Why? - It's in the way,
and people complain.
I apologize.
Here.
You move it.
- Pardon? - I gave you the key.
You move my car.
I can't drive a customer's car...
Hey. Don't you see I'm drinking?
Will you take the blame if I'm caught drunk driving?
- Then can you... - Darn it.
Hey. Are you kidding me?
What place doesn't have valet parking these days?
You ruined my mood by doing business in a rundown place like this!
- Oh, dear. - Stop it!
My goodness.
You can't do this.
Sir, you can't just hit someone.
Oh, can't I?
Oh, dear.
Darn you.
You can't do this.
Can you hit me? Hit me, then.
One of the victims, the chef, had a record for assault.
That's why he held back.
Don't do this. Please stop.
Why? Do you need money too?
Then I'll hit you.
Stop it already.
Why?
Why should I stop?
Why do you keep telling me to stop?
Aren't we having fun?
Aren't we? Isn't this fun? Isn't it?
Please stop it.
They were so angry, he tried to settle a few times,
but they refused.
They won't settle.
The three victims have each other's backs.
Yes, Minister.
(Cha Kyung Hee, Minister of Justice)
Hello, Chief Justice.
- Hello? - Are you Kim Sung Ho?
Yes.
This is the Prosecutors' Office.
I need you to come over.
What for?
You were investigated for assault before, weren't you?
I paid the price for that.
We decide whether it's over or not.
We got a tip that your investigation wasn't thorough.
Come over, okay?
Kang Yo Han's Certificate of Family Relations?
Yes. There's something to it.
Can you find out?
Well, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if it's doable because he's not a suspect.
Right?
Still, I'll have a look.
- Thank you, Soo Hyun. - Sure.
Bye.
- Here's the paperwork. - Thank you.
What's this?
Not again.
There's another signed agreement?
Yesterday, we got the male server's.
Today it's the female part-timer.
"We settled amicably,"
"and I don't want the assailant to be criminally punished."
What?
This person petitioned that Lee Young Min be punished severely.
And the day before the trial,
he signs a settlement?
I guess the defendant really showed remorse this time.
How sincerely did he apologize that they changed their mind?
- Hey. Young master. - Yes?
Do you think the world is full of flowers?
What do you mean?
The powerful don't show remorse.
That's something the powerless do.
Do you get that?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. Why should you apologize?
I'll deal with it.
Will you attend the trial tomorrow?
I should.
To be honest,
I wouldn't feel this wronged if I had punched him at least.
If I had, I'd give up.
But I can't go on like this.
The anger might kill me.
Chef.
Leave it. It's not your fault.
I say this out of concern for you.
At a time like this,
- going against the Prosecution... - Chief Justice.
Do you believe everyone is equal before the law?
I don't know. Why do you ask?
I don't believe that.
It's a sweet story, just like Santa Claus.
But sometimes, don't you want to believe...
such a sweet story?
Listen, Judge Kang.
Consider this trial a movie, a Christmas special.
Also,
please pass on the message that they don't have to worry about me.
(Chief Justice Ji Yoon Sik)
Why are you up so early?
You usually sleep until midday.
It's Lee Young Min's trial today, right?
Do you want to show support or what?
There must not be enough evidence.
If you need a witness...
Did you see something?
I saw him driving in an aggressive way.
You did?
Anything else?
Hey! Stop it!
Don't worry about the trial. Stay put and get some good rest.
This is the day you've all been waiting for.
The live court show, which was postponed by an unexpected incident,
is finally back.
I can't wait for another refreshing trial.
Let's welcome the second live court show...
with a round of applause!
Before we start the trial, I have an announcement to make.
Sadly, Judge Kim Ga On could not be with us for today's trial.
- What's that? - Please pray for Judge Kim...
so that he can return to the courtroom in good health.
Judge Kim needs your prayers.
Why is he going overboard?
There might be people...
who don't want these trials to go on.
And some of them might be in positions of power.
The only thing that can protect us...
is you, the public.
- We support you! - We're here for you!
- We'll protect you! - We root for you!
- Let's do this! - Keep going!
- We root for you! - We're here for you!
Let's do this!
(Defendant)
(Live Court Show)
Now, let's begin today's trial.
(Defendant Lee Young Min)
The defendant has been accused...
of committing verbal and physical assault against a server, chef,
and part-timer of a restaurant.
Defendant Lee Young Min, please come forward.
Defendant Lee Young Min.
- Why doesn't he come forward? - What's wrong?
Please come forward.
Why?
(Prosecution)
Your Honor.
Yes, Mr. Prosecutor?
Before we begin the trial, I'd like to point something out.
Is that right? Please go ahead.
As you already know, this is a simple assault case.
If the victims don't want the defendant punished,
the defendant can't be punished.
If all the victims settle with the defendant,
the prosecution is forced to withdraw all charges.
But there's one victim who hasn't settled yet.
Do you mean him?
(Witness Kim Sung Hoon)
Please have a seat at the witness stand.
Please have a seat.
(Witness)
Is there something you'd like to say?
I don't want...
the defendant punished.
(Petitioner: Kim Sung Hoon)
- Mr. Kim Sung Hoon? - Yes, Your Honor.
You've filed a petition many times,
asking the court to severely punish the defendant.
I have.
May I ask why you've changed your mind?
I just...
wanted to end it all.
Why?
Ma'am, you know you can tell me anything.
Just tell me. Did something happen?
- The building has been sold. - What?
This entire building has been sold to a company.
Why would anyone want this run-down building on the outskirts?
They're going to tear it down.
What? Are they going to build a new building or something?
They just want to tear it down.
The land will be left empty.
They want us to move out before the contract is up.
Are they kicking us out without any compensation?
Gosh.
Could it be...
Come on. I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
In life, all kinds of things happen.
It's not like I got injured. I'll just pretend nothing happened.
Is that so?
As none of the victims want the defendant punished,
the prosecution is forced to withdraw all charges,
Your Honor.
Excuse me, Your Honor.
Could you give me a second?
Well...
I'm sorry.
(Witness Kim Sung Hoon)
My goodness.
I'm sorry.
This concludes today's trial.
Mr. Prosecutor.
Yes?
What do you call it when someone repeats the same thing?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Didn't you learn about cases where the same crime is repeated?
By any chance,
are you talking about repeat offenders?
If this were a normal assault case, the defendant wouldn't be punished.
But what if this were a repeat case?
Then it'd be different.
But there's no evidence he is a repeat offender...
How many times has he assaulted someone and settled?
Twelve times in total.
- But that's... - Not enough?
The prosecution seems to take human rights very seriously.
That's wonderful.
Please go back to your seat.
(Live Court Show)
Then I'd like to ask the public a question.
- Pardon? - All viewers of this trial,
don't you find the defendant's face familiar?
Zoom in on Lee Young Min's face. Zoom all the way in.
Your Honor, I don't understand where this is going.
On your DIKE app, you can send a video to the court.
If you find the defendant's face familiar, please let us know.
(Live Court Show)
I'll give you 10 dollars.
- I'm giving you a lot. - How's it going?
- Hey, you're here. - Yes.
- Be careful. - I'll weigh it.
- Okay. - Hi.
Thanks.
- Get some rest. - Okay.
(Live Court Show)
Isn't that...
Hey, what's going on?
Well...
Director, a video call came in. Should we connect?
Okay. Go.
Oh, it's connected.
What is this? Is it really being broadcast all over the country?
Yes, it is. Please go ahead.
Hello, Your Honor.
I'm a huge fan of yours. You're incredible.
All my friends are going crazy too.
Thank you.
So...
do you find the defendant's face familiar?
Of course. That crazy jerk...
Oh, I'm on the air, right?
He's a complete psycho.
I used to work part-time at a department store parking lot.
Doing this.
I see. And?
One day, that jerk got out of his car and threw a tantrum,
complaining about the congestion. He even kicked an attendant.
I was so shocked and stared at him.
Then he slapped me in the face.
The department store told me to let it go,
saying he was a VVIP customer.
I felt so upset and frustrated.
Hey, have you lost your...
Will you be okay after saying this?
Yes. I got fired anyway.
Do something.
Objection, Your Honor. This hasn't been officially investigated.
Are you willing to make an official statement of what happened?
Yes, of course. I'm so glad I can finally talk about this.
Please punish him. I beg you.
He's a regular at our restaurant.
He beats someone every time he comes.
Waiters, bartenders, parking attendants...
He beats anyone who he thinks is below him.
It's just not okay.
He once even beat a new female employee.
She cried, and I had to comfort her.
Do I have to work like this?
Plus, if something bothers him,
he hits people here and there every time something bothers him.
He doesn't even give us money to get treatment,
nor do we have insurance.
I don't care if I get fired.
I'll tell you everything!
There is so much more.
- His car... - That punk...
That man is quite old too.
He was old enough to be his father,
but he kicked him in the leg.
All because his car had a small scratch.
Last month, he came into our store and demanded we change the video.
I told him we couldn't do that,
and he pushed me out of nowhere and tried to step on me.
I was surprised and told him to stop...
when he began to break all the screens in our store.
- He said how dare I stop him. - I was very...
- I regretted it so much. - A few days ago,
- a yellow sports car hit me. - I own a business, and...
He appeared out of nowhere and almost hit me!
I was crossing the street on a bicycle...
- He's the worst! - He's terrible!
Was this the reason why?
The reason why he sent it to be an open trial?
What kind of game are you playing right now?
You little...
It's like a Christmas tree?
My fellow citizens.
How would you like a person like this to be punished?
It's like playing a game.
And if you can't prove anything, you lose the game.
(National Vote Status)
(Severe Punishment, In Opposition To, In Favor Of)
We got it.
Yes!
- We got 3,000,000! We got it! - Yes!
We got it! We did!
Is this not enough for you?
Isn't this plenty of evidence of recidivism?
This Bench...
would like to ask the prosecution to modify the indictment.
This case isn't a simple assault.
It is habitual assault.
In order to modify the indictment,
we will resume our trial.
(Severe punishment, In Favor Of)
You should hurry.
If it takes too long, this anger could be pointed at the prosecution.
(Prosecution)
- Mr. Kim Sung Hoon. - Yes, Your Honor.
Habitual assault can be punishable even after a settlement.
Your case will also be but on trial.
Thank you.
I will not allow any case to be buried.
You can't buy justice with money.
(Live Court Show)
Capture the audience's reaction.
What is the reason you got involved...
in that terribly unfair game?
The reason...
Do I need to have a reason?
Is there something you want to make right?
Or perhaps something you regret?
("Eichmann in Jerusalem: A Report on the Banality of Evil")
You are a very curious person.
Who is this person?
Who is this?
It's Master Isaac.
- Isaac? - Master Yo Han's older brother,
Master Isaac.
The true heir to this mansion.
He's Kang Yo Han's older brother?
Does this mean that this man lived in this basement?
- No. - Then?
This place...
This place is Master Yo Han's bedroom.
Pardon?
Master Yo Han was an abandoned child.
He was a child nobody wanted.
Kang Yo Han was an abandoned child?
Then he's not blood related to this family?
Please be more specific. Please?
The person I suspect is Kang Yo Han.
I know that he's someone who can do whatever he sets his mind on.
I heard he already did something incredible in elementary school.
I knew it wasn't just simple curiosity.
Then you should look into it yourself.
This house belongs to Master Isaac.
It doesn't belong to him.
I'm sure the person named Isaac was missing something.
What did you say?
There's no way...
that a family like this would give their entire fortune...
to someone who isn't blood related to them.
Perhaps Kang Yo Han was more qualified.
What do you know?
I'm sorry.
If it's hard for you to talk about it, you don't have to say anything.
You resemble him a lot.
Especially his eyes.
Master Isaac lost his mother at a young age.
All of this trouble started when Chairman Kang's friends took him...
to a bar after he locked himself up in his home after losing his wife.
He was completely drunk and slept with a woman who worked at the bar.
She showed up pregnant...
and demanded that she be given money.
The woman who was rejected...
Dad.
Yes.
("Crime and Punishment")
Dad!
Sir. Why do you hate Master Yo Han so much?
You can kick me out.
What did the child do wrong?
He's a lookalike.
He looks...
too much like me.
But Isaac...
Isaac's different.
Yo Han will kill his brother one day.
Why do you...
suspect Kang Yo Han too?
What do you mean?
You said Master Isaac is the rightful heir.
Doesn't that mean Kang Yo Han took his place unjustifiably?
Is there evidence that makes you suspect him?
There's no such thing.
If what you said is right,
Kang Yo Han's just a victim of his father's abuse.
He is also a child I raised with my own milk.
But Master Yo Han was already capable...
of doing something dreadful.
Like you said.
So why...
A servant girl had a crush on him,
and he made her jump from the second floor.
He also fed weed killer...
to the Chairman's favorite hunting dog.
We, at Social Responsibility Foundation,
are constructing the Dream Home Village with 30,000 units for...
those who are weak and ill on the outskirts of Seoul.
Was there a reason for that?
Something could've irked him,
or he could've just been having fun.
But...
what child could go that far...
without hesitation?
Who are you?
It's been a long time.
Don't you remember me?
You... You're...
You're...
the church...
fire...
Still, you said his brother Isaac was good to him.
And they got along. Did they not?
Master Yo Han's the survivor of a fire.
Don't come closer.
Did you hear of that?
Yes.
It happened just one month after the Chairman died.
Master Isaac died in that fire.
Go away!
You didn't sell this.
Did you like it?
Please save me.
Hey. Wait.
Yo Han? Kang Yo Han?
(The Devil Judge)
Does it have to be Cha Kyung Hee?
Why her?
The next president.
What are you saying?
Tell me. What happened in this house?
How do you think Yo Han became the owner?
Do you know about the church fire that happened 10 years ago?
Kim Ga On, what did you find out?
What do you want from me?
Strength? Power.
How can you be so cruel?
It's fun.
Is that why you killed your brother too?
Say that again. Say that again!