(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Live Court Show)
Get us justice!
Kang Yo Han was an abandoned child?
Still, you said his brother Isaac was good to him.
And they got along. Did they not?
Master Yo Han's the survivor of a fire.
Did you hear of that?
Yes.
It happened just one month after the Chairman died.
Master Isaac died in that fire.
Judge! You were awesome today!
You got the public to provide the twist.
Do you have the rating of that very moment? Look.
Sir, your blood pressure might spike.
Chief Kang. When the agreement came in yesterday,
I thought it was all over.
I'm ashamed, as a judge.
Don't be ashamed.
Look up.
We are a team.
Do you get that?
Yes, Chief Kang.
"We are a team."
That's the perfect ending to the show.
I got that too.
We are a team.
- Well done, kiddo. - Do you get that?
Our ratings will skyrocket.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Secretary Jang...
Don't worry too much, Young Min.
What is going on?
Will I get 100 or 200 years...
and go to prison?
For something like this,
do they think they can take down the Minister of Justice's son?
Do you think that crazy judge cares about that?
He's doing all he can to gain popularity with commoners.
There will be a way.
There's still time until the next trial.
So calm down, Young Min. Please.
I'll call your mom.
Give me my phone.
Darn it.
Let's go.
(Minister of Justice)
Hello?
Oh, this is surprising, Minister.
Why are you going this far?
I believe you should ask your son that.
Why did he treat all those people like that?
He has been through a lot.
And he failed to control his temper.
He's not a bad person.
Did you accept such excuses when you were a prosecutor?
Listen, Judge Kang.
I'm hanging up.
Let's meet.
It won't take long.
Thanks for coming.
Isn't this obviously inappropriate?
What do you want?
What must I do?
What do you mean?
What must I do to make you let my son go?
Your son is only being sentenced by the law.
Don't lie.
You targeted him from the start just to get to me.
Is that what you think?
What do you want from me?
Don't say something obvious like justice.
Isn't it strength?
Power.
You're doing this to gain popularity.
What if I give you a bigger prey?
A rich businessman? The president?
19 years ago,
you investigated a young politician with a bright future.
For bribery.
- What does that... - At the time,
you knew for a fact that he hadn't taken any bribes,
but you investigated him and got a guilty verdict.
It was impressive.
Even those who ordered it said as much.
What are you talking about?
That man was the trademark of morals.
He took his own life.
Leaving behind a son who was in middle school.
During the 19 successful years of your career,
did you...
never think about that even once?
Don't talk nonsense. The investigation was legal.
It was legal? As if.
This is my condition.
Tell the media the truth behind that case.
If you do that, I'll let your son go.
Give it some thought.
People don't change easily,
don't you think?
Thank you.
Get out.
- I'm sorry. - Get out!
- Butler. - Yes, Master.
I'm hungry. Is there something to eat?
- The ingredients you have are... - I'm not going to cook.
Is there something I can heat up and eat?
You can choose between pizza and beef and rice.
Beef and rice sounds good.
It's in the freezer.
Did Elijah have dinner?
Yes, she had beef and rice.
Do we have similar tastes?
Do you eat alone every day?
Does eating with someone change anything?
All alone in this huge house?
The most dangerous and harmful things in the world are humans.
Do you have something to say?
No, sir.
It was a surprise.
What do you mean?
It was pretty good. The toast.
You've never made it for me before.
I just arrived.
What?
I'm glad you liked it.
What are you looking at?
Maybe you should ask him for help.
- Who? That old man? - Yes.
What can he possibly do in this situation?
Minister, the entire country is in chaos,
but two organizations are trusted by 90 percent of the population.
Social Responsibility Foundation.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Who would say no to handouts?
What a bunch of beggars.
The other organization is the live court.
Ignorant pigs.
I'm sorry to say this, but the prosecution is trusted by...
only 12 percent of the population.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
(Minister Cha Kyung Hee)
Hello, Minister Cha.
I'm sorry.
He is meditating and can't talk right now.
Could you call again later?
Pardon?
If you tell me what this is about, I'll relay it to him.
I see. Of course.
Any mom would do the same.
I do understand.
Yes.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Minister, let's put things right together.
Okay.
My ear hurts. She talks too much, seriously.
I think it's time for us to meet, Judge Kang.
(Judge Kang Yo Han)
Are you hurt?
I'm sorry.
I'm surprised.
Not by you.
The cat doesn't like being around strangers.
I'm very popular with stray cats.
They must be able to tell that I'm a good person. Right?
As if.
Only the slow ones can't tell.
What?
I mean cats.
That cat was once a stray cat too.
It was?
But it looks so expensive.
Yo Han picked it up.
It's out of character, but he keeps doing it.
What makes you think it's out of character?
Don't tell me you think he is the person...
the people on TV make him out to be.
The fighter for justice who loves the powerless,
the great Judge Kang Yo Han.
He isn't?
You're just as stupid as I thought.
We feed this cat every day, but it still hunts mice.
Can you guess why?
- I'm not sure. - It's because it's fun.
The cat hunts for fun because it's bored.
How do you think Yo Han became the owner of this house?
What do you mean?
It's...
the only thing I think about...
every day.
Hey, Soo Hyun.
Could I meet the officer who investigated the fire 10 years ago?
Well, the thing is...
Was it an important call?
Don't you know you should knock when you go into someone's room?
In case you forgot, this is my house.
When are you planning to leave?
I want to stay here and take it easy for a few days.
I feel dizzy from time to time.
It seemed like you were moping around the house.
Is it because you're curious?
Or are you trying to find something?
I'm not really interested in other people's business.
Is that so?
Okay, then.
Shall we choose your outfit now?
Choose my outfit?
Yes, I'm taking you somewhere.
Come with me.
How's this?
Wear this tie. The shirts are right under there.
Wear this.
Why?
Because you're going to have to live in the same time zone as me.
What are you waiting for?
Do I have to dress you?
I can get dressed on my own.
What?
That's a first.
It healed up.
Is this for me too?
Yes, wear it.
You look surprisingly good.
Well, I'm still young.
Unlike someone.
- What? - Hey, old man.
Old man?
Elijah, did you have dinner?
I don't look like an old man.
You can drive, can't you?
Sure.
What are you doing? Get in.
Welcome, sir. Please come this way.
- Hello, Judge. - It's good to see you, Judge.
- Gosh, he's handsome. - Hello.
- He's really good-looking. - It's nice to see you.
Judge.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
I work for Mr. Seo, the board chairman,
at Social Responsibility Foundation.
My name is Jung Sun Ah.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Kim Ga On.
Nice to meet you too.
My goodness. There you are.
- You should become an actor, Judge. - Thank you.
Why don't you make your debut at our station?
You're going to scare him off.
The live court show is broadcast by our company.
I see.
She's the wife of Chairman Park of Saram Media.
And this is the wife of Chairman Min of Minbo Group.
- I'm Kim Sang Sook. - And I'm Pi Hyang Mi.
I'm Kim Ga On.
You've become a rising star.
Why don't you take a picture with me?
Good, good.
- I want to be in the picture too. - Okay. Come closer.
Give me a goddess pose and make a heart shape.
Okay.
Make a heart shape. Okay.
Don't you think it'd be more stylish if we can see his forehead?
No, this is fine since he has a handsome face.
But his outfit doesn't look good.
- You're right. It's too old. - Which brand is it?
It's a grandpa's suit. Can you take it off?
- No, wait. - Which brand is it?
Just take it off.
- Take it off for a second. - I'm okay.
- Come on. Take it off. - Excuse me, ladies.
I need to introduce him to many people today.
- Could I borrow him for a second? - Sure.
- Bye. - See you.
He's a child.
How long do you think he can last working under Kang Yo Han?
- He's so cute. - Yes, he is.
I like him.
So he's his chaperone.
I don't need a chaperone.
You looked like a fawn surrounded by a pride of lionesses.
- What, a fawn? - Hello, sir.
Your dazzle hurts my eyes. Look who's here.
- Hello. - Judge Kang.
Have a seat.
Thanks to these handsome judges,
our broadcasting agency is doing so well.
I'm Park Du Man.
You're making a lot of money from their advertising sales, right?
Yes, of course.
Now we can donate more money.
You're so vulgar.
The man who's being rude to me...
owns Minbo Group.
It's a really small store.
And he's the chairman, Min Yong Shik.
- I'm Kim Ga On. - So you're the popular Judge Kim.
Why don't you join our study session?
A study session?
We just gather together to worry about our country.
People from the financial, political, and academic world...
study about the world.
Sometimes we invite great scholars to speak at the session.
That's how we hang out.
Gosh, an ignorant merchant like me...
can't understand a thing they talk about.
You know that you are ignorant?
I guess you're smart after all.
Oh, gosh. Mr. President!
Goodness.
Let's go.
I should go too.
Thank you for taking part in our Dream Home business.
It's an honor to introduce our generous donors.
First, here are the donors who donated 100,000 dollars.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Now here are the donors who donated one million dollars.
Could you please stand up?
- Cheers. - This is so nice.
Cheers.
And there is someone who showed us exceptional love and support.
This person donated 10 million dollars.
Where are you?
Please give him a big round of applause.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let me introduce Board Chairman, Seo Jeong Hak.
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Benevolence.
(Benevolence)
The power to overcome rebellion...
ultimately comes from this word,
benevolence.
All men are born with human nature.
In Mencius' excerpts with Gong Sun Chou,
the foundations of the Four Sprouts,
- compassion. - Goodness.
If you do not take pity on people,
you are not human!
You must not forget that this mentality is the basis of...
our foundation!
You're so good at it.
That was funny. Here have a grape.
- Did Mr. Seo donate any money? - I don't know.
Oh, he's here!
That was a great speech.
It was incredible.
That was really good.
Sir, your speech today was so moving.
Compassion. You're right.
We must have compassion for the people...
for the nation to run well.
With that in mind, I will give my soul and body...
to support the Dream Home business...
fully and completely to the best of my ability.
- Thank you, Mr. President. - You're welcome.
Mr. President, you seem like a different person today.
Why?
Whether I'm awake or asleep...
Whether I'm sitting or I'm standing
I'm always worried about our country for the sake of...
my beloved and respectable fellow citizens.
Okay. Let's worry about the country after we finish eating.
Give us our food!
That was fast.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Please, enjoy your meal.
- Goodness. - I'm sorry, sir.
You can take your time. It's okay.
This is good.
Slowly.
Mr. Seo.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
You have an urgent call.
Is that so?
Well, then. Please excuse me.
Please continue.
Well the thing is...
Darn it.
I'm so sorry.
I still commit sins in my old age.
Old man.
Yes, ma'am.
Why can't you behave modestly for even an hour?
- What should I do about you? - I apologize.
I apologize.
Repent.
Repent!
Who are you?
I'm a dog.
What are you talking about?
You're an advocate for the slums who was nominated for a Nobel Prize.
No, ma'am. I'm just a dog.
Why is the great philosopher and national doyen acting so humble?
No, ma'am. I've fooled the world my entire life,
and only sought after dirty carnal desires.
I'm just a piece of trash.
Hey.
Aren't you Mr. Seo, a hidden power that not even the president...
can look down upon?
I hid behind my empty name...
and dirtied weak woman...
I...
I apologize.
I apologize. Please kill me.
- Old Man. - Yes, ma'am.
There's something you've been mistaken about.
Just because a dog bites a person,
does the person...
get dirty from it?
How dare a dog do that?
You're right.
That's true.
Let's repent.
Let's make it a month this time.
I'll just say that you're fasting in prayer for the nation again.
Yes, ma'am.
Did it hurt?
Judge Kang, your trials are quite refreshing.
We're all so deeply moved.
You grew up to be so successful...
despite the terrible events from 10 years ago.
You're too kind. It was all thanks to you.
Right. Whenever I see you, Judge Kang,
I feel bad for you.
We especially feel that way.
But after the most recent trial ended,
the people around me... Not me,
but the people around me were very worried.
Public sentiment is chaotic as is.
Did you have to make such a big fuss over something like that?
Young Min went to school with our kid, so I know him well.
He was very sweet and nice when he was young.
It's unfortunate.
I'm sorry, but we can't speak about an ongoing trial...
We're discussing the infringement of judicial independence.
The nation is falling apart, perhaps we must worry about that first.
The directors of the foundation have a lot of complaints.
They wonder if the live court show is going according to plan.
What if something happens because you continue to provoke commoners?
Will Judge Kang Yo Han take responsibility for it?
Listen here! What are you talking about?
That man doesn't know his place.
Does it have to be Cha Kyung Hee?
What do you mean?
As you may all know,
Cha Kyung Hee has a lot of enemies and a lot of flaws.
Does Cha Kyung Hee have to be the one...
to protect all of your fortunes?
Honey.
This is... Gosh. Hold on.
Judge Kang, you're a strong match.
I'm no match for you.
You're an imaginative lunatic!
You're a creative psycho!
You're right.
It doesn't have to be Cha Kyung Hee.
I'm talking about the next presidency, right?
Someone who is popular with commoners...
and has a strong background story.
People like that are more popular in this day and age.
That's how I ended up becoming president!
From the perspective of a businessman,
it's better to bet on the one who survives.
Although, it's hard to say who will.
The one who survives?
Chairman Park. If you put it that way,
you're upsetting the listener.
Doesn't that make you a jerk too?
I think I got it.
You, you, you.
- That's right. - You could rap.
You should be a rapper.
Look at this. There's a real lime here.
Shall I show you a killer verse?
It's killer.
[VIU Ver] tvN E04 'The Devil Judge'
"Yo Han Older's Brother"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
You must feel a little queasy.
Ms. Jung.
The Judge Kang you saw here.
Isn't it an unfamiliar scene?
What do you mean?
I just run errands for the chairman of the board,
but I unwittingly hear and see things.
It's utterly different from the image that...
the outside world knows.
Do you have something to tell me?
I will keep it a secret.
You know about the church fire from 10 years ago, right?
- Yes. - It wasn't reported,
but there was an event that day.
Judge Kang's older brother was to sign a contract stating...
he'd donate all his wealth to our foundation.
Kang Isaac?
A huge fire just happened to break out that day.
It was an old building,
so it caved in and people got buried.
Kang Isaac and his wife died that day.
But Judge Kang was found, purely by miracle.
The first thing he did when he left the hospital...
What was that?
He canceled the donation his brother made.
He even brought a doctor's note saying Isaac had a weak mind and...
was incapable of making sound decisions.
Is that something an average person can do?
Right after his brother and his wife died a gruesome death?
Whenever I see the live court show,
I think of that day.
It weighs on me.
Why the weird face?
Are you going deaf too?
What are you doing?
You should've answered.
What?
Are you disappointed by the sight of the real world?
It's the real side of the rich.
Do you think the poor are any different?
Human beings are equal.
In front of greed.
The prosecution still has not modified the indictment...
on Lee Young Min's assault case.
The live court show stressed it would be fair,
and criticism is gaining strength that...
the court is moving to let off the Minister of Justice's son.
Minister of Justice Cha Kyung Hee...
- has not made a statement. - Turn it off.
What she could say soon...
Punish Lee Young Min!
- Punish him! - Punish him!
Minister of Justice, resign!
- Resign! - Resign!
Punish Lee Young Min!
- Punish him! - Punish him!
Minister of Justice, resign!
- Resign! - Resign!
Punish Lee Young Min!
(Ministry of Justice)
- Resign! - Resign!
- Stop it. - Resign!
Minister of Justice, resign!
- Minister of Justice, resign! - Get them out of here!
Let go!
- Resign! - Minister of Justice, resign!
Hey, you! Resign, Minister of Justice!
- Resign! - Get lost!
Those crazy fools.
What?
Fine.
What did the foundation say?
The sly vipers.
They want me to deal with it.
It's really bad, ma'am.
This is my condition.
Tell the media the truth behind that case.
If you do that, I'll let your son go.
What did Kang Yo Han demand?
He met with you. That means he wants something.
You can sell my company and give it all to him.
Let's protect Young Min.
It's our fault that he's like that.
We left him alone as a kid...
and kept busy with our own careers.
We had no idea how much he was struggling.
Do you remember the day he overdosed?
He said he'd rather die.
Why did you bring that up?
I don't want to think about that.
Honey. Money and titles aren't important at all.
Let's protect our son.
Okay?
He won't last a day in prison.
The poor thing...
Nothing's more important than our son.
Honey.
I will get Young Min out.
Even if I must sacrifice myself.
The next trial is tomorrow.
Everything will be fine, right?
- Oh? - What? What is it?
Minister Cha Kyung Hee called an emergency press conference.
What?
Dear citizens.
I stand here today with a heart heavy with guilt.
My foolish son...
has caused the people much concern.
I apologize sincerely.
It is my failure as a mother for not teaching him better.
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
The prosecution...
submitted a request today...
to amend the arraignment of defendant Lee Young Min.
The charge was changed to habitual assault...
and the other incidents discovered were all included.
What?
- What is she saying? - In court tomorrow,
I expect the judges to hand out a severe sentence.
What... Mom.
- I will not ask for forgiveness. - Wow.
Did her political ambitions beat her maternal instinct?
Dad, this isn't right, is it?
This isn't what you told me.
It's not right.
What is that?
Young Min, calm down. Relax.
Why? What's wrong?
Do you have a migraine?
Where are your pills?
Here. Take a pill.
Anyone who has committed a crime...
Breathe.
must be punished accordingly. I stand strongly behind that.
That is the Korea I dream of.
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
After all I did to come here.
Nothing comes without a sacrifice.
Hi, Soo Hyun.
(The second live trial of Lee Young Min, VP of Joongwon FNB)
The defendant admits and deeply regrets what he did.
But I'd like you to understand that there were...
mitigating circumstances.
Please elaborate, Counsel.
The defendant was always a sensitive, lonely child.
All kids are supposed to be raised...
with their parents' love, right?
Of course.
How can it be otherwise?
Exactly.
But sadly,
the defendant had to give up his parents for society.
His mother as a public official and father as a pillar of the economy,
they both devoted their lives to this country...
and couldn't be there for him.
Oh, my. That must've been hard.
Judge Kang.
Your Honor.
All this happened because of his parents' incompetence.
I beg you to take the circumstances into consideration.
That's right.
As a result, the defendant grew up alone...
in that huge house with a housekeeper.
With 2 housekeepers, 1 cook, and 1 gardener, to be precise.
Not that it's important, though.
Oh, yes.
Growing up, the defendant witnessed...
the housekeepers steal things time and time again.
Naturally, he developed a fear of poor people.
That's what became the basis for...
his obsessive and aggressive behavior.
I submit renowned child psychology experts and psychiatrists'...
written opinions on this matter.
Please take it into account.
It must be hard.
Not really. It was much harder being a detective.
You should understand.
Right.
Anyway, why are you asking about something that happened so long ago?
- The court is just the same. - What?
They're desperate to find ways to raise our chief's popularity.
They want to strike while the iron is hot.
I guess the youngest ones must work hardest everywhere.
Then again, the story of a survivor of a horrible fire...
sure sounds intriguing.
The fire was at a church, right?
Yes. His father went there too.
But it seems like there was no service that day.
There was apparently a charity event of some sort,
but there's no record that shows who attended it.
Well, I don't see...
what this has to do with his popularity.
We're just looking for some nice stories.
We might have to do some interviews later.
Anyway, the cause of the fire is still unknown, right?
Yes.
The church was in an old school building,
which was made of wood.
The whole building burned down, and there's nothing left.
Maybe the curtains caught fire from a cigarette.
Maybe there was a short circuit.
Did you get a statement from Judge Kang?
Did he see anything?
I visited him once in the hospital.
But he didn't remember much,
which is understandable. The roof had come down on him,
and it was chaos.
That reminds me. He has another live court show today.
I have to watch it.
Excuse me.
I'm not saying the circumstances justify...
everything the defendant did.
But we all are parents.
Just because a child commits misdeeds...
doesn't mean he should be isolated from society.
That's right. My son is still young...
and inexperienced.
He couldn't tell right from wrong.
His parents couldn't care for him properly.
- They couldn't discipline him well. - Exactly.
They say it takes a village to raise a child.
The defendant wasn't loved and disciplined by his parents...
and committed misdeeds as a result.
Shouldn't we be generous and embrace him...
into society?
Young Min.
My poor son.
I'm so sorry.
If the defendant is put in prison for many years for this,
it's nothing more than emotional populism.
Then again, a prison sentence costs money.
That's right. It's paid for with tax dollars.
Wouldn't it be better if we let the defendant...
provide the victims with adequate financial compensations?
Let's face it, if we put this young man behind bars,
will it feed his victims?
Everyone is struggling to make ends meet.
That was very well said. Thank you, Counsel.
I apologize if I went overboard, Your Honor.
Don't worry.
It was logical. It made perfect sense.
And I agree with you totally.
Listening to your argument,
I've come up with the most appropriate punishment.
It doesn't cost any tax dollars,
the defendant won't be isolated from society for a long time,
and it'll only inflict temporary pain on him.
It's the most efficient and economical punishment there is.
- It's flagellation. - What?
Flagellation?
Hold on. My goodness.
Oh, dear. Unbelievable.
- Flagellation? - Just like Counsel argued,
the defendant wasn't loved and disciplined by his parents.
Society should give it to him on his parents' behave.
"It takes a village to raise a child," you said.
Flagellation?
Hey, search for some information on it and put it up on the screen.
Yes, sir.
This... This is absurd.
Tying up and beating a person in the 21st century?
That's too barbaric.
That sounds like an insult to many great nations...
that still carry out this punishment today.
Also, the verdict is based on...
the Special Act on Strengthening Law and Order, suggested by...
the Minister of Justice, who is the defendant's mother.
Am I wrong?
Crazy jerk!
Your Honor.
I apologize.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I'd like to apologize to all the victims as well.
What I did was wrong.
I apologize. Please let it slide this once.
I'm really sorry.
- I... - Let's see what the public thinks.
What do you think? Do you think this is...
an appropriate sentence for the defendant?
Your Honor.
Punish Lee Young Min!
- Punish him! - Punish him!
Minister of Justice, resign!
(Closing Down)
I'm done voting.
Me too. I hope it goes well.
(What's your choice?)
(Hourly Graph)
(National Vote Status)
Gosh.
What makes you all so special?
Young Min, calm down.
Get off me!
Young Min!
- Get off me. - Young Min.
What's so great about you?
What makes you all so special?
Are you any different from me?
Are you all so innocent?
Young Min.
Does this make sense to you?
Camera One, zoom in on Lee Young Min.
- Keep following him. - Yes, sir.
Camera Three, take a bust shot of Lee Young Min's father.
What makes me inferior to you all?
What did I do so wrong?
You're no different.
You, you, and you...
What makes you any different from me?
Is he serious?
(Hourly Graph)
Who gives you the right...
to judge me?
I apologized.
I said I was sorry. I did all of that.
Your... Your Honor.
I'll get down on my knees and apologize to you.
I'm really sorry, Your Honor.
Forgive me this once.
What I did was wrong. Please let it slide this once.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me this once.
Please let me go.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Your Honor.
Following the public opinion,
this Bench sentences the defendant...
30 floggings.
Your... Your Honor.
Compared to the misdeeds committed by the defendant,
this appears to be the minimum, most humanitarian sentence.
As the sentence was handed down by the public,
I believe it should be executed transparently...
in front of the entire nation.
I ask the Ministry of Justice to execute the sentence accordingly.
Yes!
(30 Flogging)
(30 Floggings, In Opposition To, In Favor Of)
Good!
He's quite refreshing!
Delinquents like him deserved to get beaten!
People like him deserve to become president!
He could get rid of all the trash!
Did you know that after Judge Kang was discharged,
he canceled the deed of convent...
his brother wrote?
What kind of nonsense are you talking about?
Oh, it's nonsense?
It could be the motive for a crime,
but you're saying it's nonsense?
Who are you? Are you crazy?
Are you slandering him right now?
If you do that, you'll get stoned to death!
Do you know how many people live to watch Judge Kang right now?
That's enough.
Let's go.
Oh, right. Detective Park. How did you open up this restaurant?
What are you talking about? I used my severance pay.
That's interesting.
From what I know, you had a lot of debt.
Gambling debt.
You closed a case on the basis that the cause was unknown,
and two months later, you suddenly quit.
Your gambling debt went away,
and you opened a restaurant in a good area.
You must've received quite a big severance pay check,
Detective Park.
(Cha Kyung Hee, Minister of Justice)
Minister Cha, I know this is hard,
but you must sign the sentencing order.
If you step back now...
(Sentencing Order)
(Cha Kyung Hee, Minister of Justice)
Hold on.
Wait.
- I guess it's today. - They're really going to do it?
I can't believe it.
(Live Broadcast of the Execution of Lee Young Min's Flagellation)
Serves him right.
Young Min!
- Stay still. - Dad.
Hold on. Wait a second.
We will execute his sentence.
Please start.
Sir. Hold on. Wait...
- No... - Wait...
(Live Broadcast of the Execution of Lee Young Min's Flagellation)
Young Min!
(Record of Execution of Sentence)
(Live Broadcast of the Execution of Lee Young Min's Flagellation)
Chairman Lee. Chairman Lee!
Chairman Lee!
(Live Broadcast of the Execution of Lee Young Min's Flagellation)
Should we proceed with it next week?
Yes. Let's treat him thoroughly before moving forward.
Darn it.
- Yes, that's right! - Until the East Sea dries
Are you satisfied?
Why wouldn't I be?
What kind of cruel behavior is this?
Cruel?
I just did what the majority of the nation wanted.
Isn't that what democracy is?
Don't be so hypocritical.
You're just doing this for fun.
You're nothing more than a cold-hearted monster.
You hunt for fun,
and you get rid of anyone who gets in your way.
That goes for your brother too.
Is that why you killed him?
Say that again.
Did you kill your brother?
Your brother, who treasured and loved you...
Say that again.
Say that again!
Cruel?
Do you know what being cruel really means?
The man who called himself our father died,
and my brother said that he'd donate all of our assets to the foundation.
That's incredible!
The foundation acted as though they were moved by his donation,
- Thank you! - and they held...
a grand party at the church.
It must've been hard to make such a decision.
No, sir.
I respect you. It couldn't have been easy.
Sharing and education. Practicing love.
This is incredibly difficult and hard, don't you agree?
Goodness. You must be Elijah. How cute.
Do you know how great of a man your father is?
He's like a saint.
You're being too kind.
You're incredible.
Gosh, is this a human or a fairy?
Why is she so pretty?
Do you want to sign a contract with my company?
Why are you doing this to a child?
- Goodness. - Hey, come here!
- Don't run! - Hey!
(Verena Church)
Why did you come outside?
Come in.
I'll come in very soon.
Go back inside and stay with Dad, okay?
- You have to come soon. - Okay.
Hey!
Are you back to sign the deal?
Let me see you. You're just adorable.
(Verena Church)
How much is that?
I don't know. Should be a huge amount.
He demanded so much. He's quite particular.
In two hours, the foundation will be tens of millions of dollars richer.
Hang in there.
This offering made by Kang Isaac and Yu Hee Jin, Cecilia.
So that the Almighty Lord will accept it,
let us pray.
- Amen. - Amen.
- The body of Christ. - Where's Elijah?
The body of Christ.
Mom!
Honey. Honey!
Move!
- Where is she? - Elijah!
- Elijah! - Move.
Get out of my way. Move.
Mom.
You lunatic!
Who are you?
Mom.
Mom!
- Elijah! - Mom.
- You're okay. - Elijah.
- Baby. - Mom.
Let's get out of here.
Get out of my way! Move!
Let go of me!
Yo Han.
Elijah...
Eli...
Yo Han.
Go.
I'll come right back.
Isaac.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Isaac.
Isaac...
Someone's coming out!
Say something!
How did you survive?
We have a survivor!
My gosh. You've been through so much.
Look at him.
(The Devil Judge)
I'm sorry.
I was out of line.
I knew it.
People love stories like this.
Hunters mask their scent completely...
until the time is right.
It's going to be so fun.
I knock people out of my way...
without hesitation.
We'll give Kang Yo Han a little homework.
I need to find out who's behind Cha Kyung Hee.
Let's aim for the body first.
Even if no one else in the world does,
I understand...
how it feels.
Anger.
Make up your mind. Will you stand in my way...
or next to me?