(Current Status of Donations)
This is fate, everyone!
A fate that I don't even want to think about.
While a plague never heard of before spreads throughout our country,
companies have fallen and people were made homeless.
The groundless instigation against the more fortunate...
led to arson and acts of terrorism.
Eventually...
Yes. It led to the Gwanghwamun Riot!
Bring them down!
The economic troubles are a problem of the past.
Forget all about it.
I will change it all.
The plague we're all sick of.
We have finally, at last, managed to overcome it.
Fight!
Deny allegations!
(Current Status of Donations)
(Seo Jeong Hak, Board Chairman of Social Responsibility Foundation)
(Cha Kyung Hee, Minister of Justice)
(Min Yong Shik, Minbo Group Chairman)
(Park Du Man, Saram Media Chairman)
(Looking for work)
Jobs?
I will create them.
I am Heo Joong Se, the man the loved and respected...
people of Korea chose.
I will turn Korea back into...
the grand country it was before.
I stake that on my life!
(Incoming donations)
He overreacts whenever a camera's rolling.
He just can't shake that habit.
The clown in him never goes away.
To get Korea back on its feet,
first, we must rectify law and order.
I passed a bill for a powerful judicial reform.
It begins now!
For the first time in history,
the whole nation can participate as jurors.
We have a judge...
who is known for being ruthless.
Judge Kang Yo Han...
will preside over trials...
and hand out sentences that you want to see.
I made it happen.
Heo Joong Se made it happen!
A total change of Korea!
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
Many are concerned.
Hello. I am Kang Yo Han.
Judge Kang, there's concern the live court show is unconstitutional.
What do you think about that?
What about the criticisms...
that it's anti-humanitarian and just for show?
There's also concern that...
you punish too severely and are inconsiderate for the weak.
- Who is weak? - Pardon?
Of the people I sentenced, who were socially disadvantaged?
There was a young offender.
Some were extremely poor and homeless, or mentally disabled.
The rapist of a classmate, a happy-slapper thief,
and the killer of a random victim.
Are they socially disadvantaged?
Still, the disadvantaged deserve some...
They are defendants.
I do not care if someone is powerful or not.
Can you hand down a hefty sentence on the defendant of the live show?
Chairman Joo Il Do is known for being very connected.
If his group or authorities put pressure on you...
I am power.
Me, me, me!
I am power!
I exercise the judicial power delegated to me...
by the sovereign Korean public.
Who is above the people?
The people are power.
I'll see you in court.
Yes.
He's good.
He is.
I congratulate our star judge.
Shall we do it too?
To sexy power.
(The Devil Judge)
(Episode 1)
I exercise the judicial power delegated to me...
by the sovereign Korean public.
Who is above the people?
The people are power.
(Tent Protest)
(The government must compensate the bankrupt companies!)
Hang on.
Excuse me.
What business do you have here?
I start here as of today.
Oh, you're a judge of the live court show.
Go on inside.
(Stop)
(Chief Justice Min Jung Ho)
Come in.
Professor.
My apologies, Mr. Chief Justice.
It'll be a while before I get used to your new title.
"Mr. Chief Justice", my foot.
Gosh, you look great.
You little brat.
This looks like some kind of temple.
It is.
It is the temple of justice.
This is a court?
The trials will be broadcast live.
Why does Judge Kang Yo Han want to raise the stakes like this?
"Judge"? He's no ordinary judge.
He is a revolutionist who will eradicate court corruption,
the devastated nation's only hope.
He sure seems extremely popular.
A monster emerges in turbulent times.
All those absurd bills he's passed so far...
He doesn't think like a jurist. He thinks like a politician.
You seem to despise him,
but you still want me on the bench?
Someone has to be there.
Someone who can keep his eyes wide open in this crazy wind.
No one else here wants to go against the wind.
You want me to be Judas?
Please.
Do you remember what I used to say in every lecture?
I do.
In the human world,
there's no such thing as easy justice.
Nice to meet you.
(Everyone has the power to judge.)
Is something wrong?
Nothing. I apologize. Judge Kim Ga On, right?
- Yes, I look forward to... - Welcome...
to the battlefield.
(We Just Wanted to Do a Good Deed)
(Conned Restaurant Owner Couple Kills Themselves)
(Personnel Information Form, Kim Ga On)
He looks just like him,
more than I expected.
(Oh Jin Joo, Kim Ga On)
(Associate Judge Oh Jin Joo)
Judge Kim Ga On?
Nice to meet you. I'm Oh Jin Joo.
Nice to meet you, Judge Oh.
It's a bit messy here, right? Sorry.
I came from far away, so I have a lot of stuff.
Don't worry.
Will you be sleeping here?
No, that's not it. Not every day, at least.
It's just a basic skill you need at work.
Work hard in the beginning to impress your boss.
I see.
Was your first position in Seoul?
Yes.
I've been in smaller cities all this time.
This is my first position in Seoul.
Let's face it, an opportunity like this...
doesn't come often.
What's with you? Are you the shy type?
Not really. I look forward to working with you.
You look like a different person when you smile.
Now I know the selection criteria for judges for this court.
The selection criteria?
If I have to say it,
their image?
Does that have anything to do with judges' work?
It does. Think about it.
We'll be presiding over trials in front of the entire nation.
The thing about people is, they believe...
the words of people they like, rather than the truth.
Charm is power.
- "Power"? - What?
Never mind. Forget I said that.
I'm overexcited right now.
I'm saying things without thinking.
To be honest, I'm...
a huge fan of Chief Kang Yo Han's.
The very fact that I'm here proves my success.
Oh Jin Joo, you've made it. Work hard.
Do you still want JU Chemical's case to be your first case?
It's the most appropriate case.
I'm sure there are simpler, easier cases out there.
There's nothing to worry about. We'll just go by the law.
He'll hire the nation's best law firms.
I'm sure he will.
Are you aware that barely 10 percent of people show trust in the court?
I am.
It's likely the legal decision will deviate from the people's emotions.
Why do you have to broadcast this difficult case...
Sir.
This isn't the people's court.
We just want to make trials transparent to the entire nation.
That's enough for me.
I'm leaving now.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Let's cross the street. Hold up your right hands.
Follow me. Stay on this side.
Jerks!
(Stop)
What's going on?
- Get ready to shoot. - Emergency. Stand by.
Situation room, a bus 200m ahead is speeding toward the main gate.
The driver is unidentified. Tell us what to do. Over.
What's going on?
Guys, hurry up and cross!
Are you okay?
What's the point of having a gun if you don't shoot?
I'm sorry, sir.
- The driver's still in the bus! - What if the bus explodes?
There's a man in the bus!
Sir, are you okay?
- Are you okay? - Call an ambulance!
(Punish Chairman Joo Il Do for driving people to death...)
(by discharging toxic wastewater.)
This morning, in front of the Supreme Court...
a kindergarten bus exploded.
An arrest warrant for the chairman of JU Chemical Joo Il Do...
was suspended and the kindergarten driver...
- who was discontented with this... - What is all this?
drove the bus to the Supreme...
He did it because they rejected to issue the warrant?
It's just a challenge to the authority.
With all due respect, I don't think it was a challenge.
It was more like an outcry.
What do you mean?
When you put a rat in a small space and make it starve,
it acts desperately and bangs its head against the wall.
Do you think people would be any different?
Sir, we need to make ends meet.
So the foundation should help us.
We managed to control the epidemic.
But so many are out of work that we can't collect taxes.
If the drought lasts for too long, a revolt breaks out.
You're right.
- Chairman Park. - Yes.
How's the preparation for the live court show going?
You don't have to worry about it. I'm sure it's going to be a big hit.
You have to work hard on it.
Our Minister of Justice is especially interested in the case.
I mean personally.
Korea has become a safe country.
Social responsibility...
(Social welfare for the poor)
(Lucky Loan Assure confidentiality)
Are you trying to build a jungle in there?
Hey.
I heard there was a terror attack in front of the Supreme Court.
You heard that already?
I guess it's because you're Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun of RIT.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
Did you jump in with both feet again?
Again? Don't worry.
I was so scared that I hid far behind the scene.
Like a real man.
Good. You finally became mature.
Let's go up.
You go ahead. I'll be there after I finish this.
Just finish it up and follow me.
Okay. But why do you sound angry?
Come on. Right now.
Cheers.
Aren't you going to buy me dinner?
- Why should I? - Because you're going to be on TV.
I won't be able to see you if you become a star like Kang Yo Han.
I can't wait.
What's with the sarcasm?
Cheers.
Drink up.
It won't hurt to be around a star like him.
And he has plenty of touching stories.
The heir to a great fortune.
A survivor of a tragic accident.
People just love those kinds of stories.
You're right.
His stories are totally different from mine.
What's wrong with yours?
Now that you became a judge after all those years,
you should move to a nicer neighborhood.
What's wrong with my neighborhood?
Well, things are not what they used to be.
- But it's the only place. - What do you mean?
It's the only place that reminds me of my parents.
Have dinner with me. I'll cook.
- Dinner? - You've lost weight.
You haven't been eating well, have you?
Hey.
If you keep on doing that, I'll ask you out again.
You've rejected me five times since kindergarten.
But it never ends until it really ends.
I don't want to lose my best friend.
Have dinner with me.
- You finished your beer, right? - Yes.
You heartless jerk.
I love you.
The point is that we should emphasize that the chairman...
didn't know wastewater was being discharged.
So the accident was beyond his control.
If we can't obtain public opinion during the trial,
what do you think we should do?
We should emphasize the purification facilities have improved.
So let them know everything was beyond his control.
- Sir. - Come in.
Don't you think public opinion is going against us?
Ungrateful people.
Tens of thousands of people are living off me.
It's hard to get clear evidence...
for cases related to environmental issues.
How can a company owner know what's in its industrial waste?
We're going to plead not guilty.
And even if things don't go well,
we'll be charged with professional negligence resulting in death.
Professional negligence resulting in death.
How many years will that give?
The maximum penalty is five years imprisonment.
Five years?
Well, a few special laws have been legislated.
But the court of law is very conservative.
So they won't toughen up prison sentences.
Don't you know I can only sleep well...
on a nice bed?
My goodness, Mr. Chairman.
Just read some books and work on your meditation for a year.
Then you'll be released on parole.
You'll be healthier than before when you're out.
Can I trust you?
If you can't trust me,
you know who to ask for help.
Of course, I do.
Sir.
Thank you for saving me yesterday.
Don't mention it.
You didn't even hesitate to shoot.
I didn't?
Were you going to kill that man?
- If I had to. - If you had to?
But the bus would've gone straight even if I had killed that man.
So you wanted him to get scared and steer the wheel.
Even if he smashes his bus and dies.
Yes, that's math.
2 is bigger than 1.
I guess so.
So you met Kang Yo Han.
What's he like?
- I don't know. - Well, I'm alive thanks to you.
You're welcome.
I guess I shouldn't be the smaller number in front of you.
Whatever.
Why do you think he chose Chairman Joo Il Do...
as his first defendant on his first mock trial?
Isn't it because it's the hottest case right now?
Yes, that's true.
But he is the biggest donator of Social Responsibility Foundation.
And Kang Yo Han's judiciary reform...
was possible because the Minister of Justice...
and the foundation supported the idea.
So he was in an awkward position to take the case...
but he insisted on taking it.
That's why I think he has an ulterior motive behind all this.
Chief Kang, about the bus driver from yesterday's incident.
Indict him without detention for now.
Then put him on trial later. How does that sound?
Why do you think that's a good idea?
The first live court show is right around the corner.
So we can't afford a scandal that'll draw public attention.
Besides, you pulled a stunt yesterday.
Giving a nice first impression is important, isn't it?
Are you saying I should be nice to a terrorist?
No, but you should consider what people would think.
I don't think I looked so bad.
It'll only draw more attention.
Haven't you heard of noise marketing?
It's only fair to have him incarcerated for a case like this.
Excuse me.
May I say something?
The three-year-old daughter of the bus driver...
is one of the deceased in the JU Chemical Case,
and her grandmother committed suicide over that case.
So what?
Despite that, you rejected the warrant for Chairman Joo Il Do,
yet you want to incarcerate the bus driver.
I'm worried that it isn't fair.
Judge Kim.
If we have a trial for Joo Il Do, he would just be a defendant.
Meanwhile, the bus driver was caught on the scene.
Do you not know this?
However, we must take into consideration his motive...
If you're a victim, do you have the right to hurt others?
No, but he's injured right now...
They have doctors at the detention center too.
Let's follow the rules.
Yu, the child that was receiving treatment due to...
the toxic wastewater leakage incident at JU Chemical, has died,
and her grandmother, Kim,
has tragically chosen to end her life.
As a result, there have been 11 deaths due to this incident.
The number of victims including those who are receiving treatment...
is a total of 47 people.
This particular case is currently being investigated,
and Chairman Joo Il Do will be facing trial...
I'm sorry. It's hard for me to watch.
It reminds me of where I grew up.
I'm from the countryside, although you can't tell from my looks.
I'm from Seoul, as you can see.
From a shanty town.
- Is it obvious? - Yes.
I guess those who grew up poor can recognize others who did too.
It's like a type of radar.
Then what do you see when you look at Chief Kang?
Our Chief Kang?
I'm not sure.
(You can do it, Oh Jin Joo. Let's go!)
(Associate Judge, Oh Jin Joo)
I don't see anything.
That's the basics of work life.
Useless curiosity about your bosses is forbidden.
- Let's get back to work. - Okay.
There's a trial statute, so read it.
A trial statute?
Yes, the trial statute from our mock trial.
You might get a bit annoyed from it.
Sir, you seem to really enjoy playing with numbers.
You want to come up with a verdict based on how viewers vote on an app?
Do you think that's playing with numbers?
I call it democracy.
If you want to hold a democratic trial, why do you need us?
I guess you read the trial statute.
Is that really a trial?
If you're going to neglect the opinions of the associate judges...
and make your final decision based on the number of votes,
then why do you actually need us?
In a state of emergency, we need emergency methods.
Also, it won't look good.
It won't look good?
It would look empty if there weren't people sitting at each side of me.
It's a TV show after all.
It's me. There's something you need to do for me.
Okay. What is it?
The spare key to the Supreme Court Record Storage Room.
Hey, do you think that's easy?
If you can't even do that, I suggest you quit being the chief justice.
Hello?
You're the one who brought me in here.
If the case records get damaged,
you'll be incarcerated.
I won't rat out my accomplice, sir.
I found it.
The tagger.
You're so tenacious. Did you look for the records from 20 years ago?
It's like how your first love is the dearest to you.
First love?
When Chairman Joo caused trouble when he first expanded his business,
the person who helped him was the elite prosecutor from Seoul,
Cha Kyung Hee.
She helped him three times whenever things became quiet,
so you couldn't tell.
Of course, it probably wasn't free.
When Cha Kyung Hee first ran to become an assemblywoman,
who was the head of her campaign club?
Joo Il Do?
So to clarify things,
Joo Il Do was Cha Kyung Hee's sponsor when she was a prosecutor.
Cha Kyung Hee is an influential person in this administration,
and she has been supporting Kang Yo Han.
But Kang Yo Han...
has declared that he will put Joo Il Do on trial?
And Cha Kyung Hee is not objecting and just watching it?
Do you think this is a trial to reveal his crimes...
or the opposite?
The problem is that all of this is just speculation.
We should try to do something no matter what.
I feel like I'm standing in the way of my own future,
but I think it's too late to turn back.
A first love that's dear to you.
Is Jae Hee doing well?
Hey, Ga On.
It's fine. Talk to me.
A listening device? Why do you need that?
Somebody help me!
Be quiet!
Ga On, I'll call you back later.
Somebody save me!
Stop!
I'm a police officer. Step back.
Please save me.
She's my little sister.
Go up against the wall.
I told you she was my sister.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Back off, lady.
Let go.
It's okay.
You're okay now.
(A safe Korea will be realized from now on.)
Ma'am, Director Jung Sun Ah...
from the Social Responsibility Foundation is here.
Tell her to come in.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm here to run an errand for Mr. Seo.
What brings you here?
I'm sorry, but may I have a seat?
Thank you.
Mr. Seo, as well as the sponsors of our foundation,
are all very worried about this upcoming trial.
What are they worried about?
I'm sorry, but let me be frank with you.
The reason why we are holding this mock trial...
is to catch petty criminals so that citizens can release their anger.
So?
So we're wondering if it's necessary to put a business person on trial.
If he receives a serious punishment,
it will become a negative precedent for other business people.
This is what they're worried about.
Have you ever seen Kang Yo Han make a mistake?
That's true,
but we thought it might be better if you went with an easier case...
for the first trial.
Why are you so adamant about this case?
Are you saying I'm being adamant?
I'm sorry. I'm just relaying what they have said.
Why are people who are in the business of social welfare...
No, to be more exact, why is an alliance of the wealthy...
so interested in how the country is being run?
I'm pretty sure I said that I would take care of it.
How arrogant.
I'm sorry, Minister Cha. I have overstepped.
May I dare say...
one more thing that is overstepping my boundaries?
The chair and desk where you sit behind.
The painting on the wall and the car you take to and from work.
Are you aware all of that was paid for by our foundation?
Because your ministry's budget came short this year.
There aren't enough prisons,
so we might have to build a private one ourselves.
I wonder, Ma'am.
Who is it...
that's serving the country?
What is it?
Why does a judge need a listening device?
Do you have a cheating girlfriend?
If that's easier to understand, let's go with that.
I understand, but I can't forgive.
Even if you can't, let's just go with that.
Quit joking around. What is it for?
You'll get hurt if you pry too much.
It's not the first time you've been so stubborn.
Let's test it. Go on the roof.
- The roof? - Yes.
You need to wear this.
What are you staring at?
You can't do anything on your own. Go outside.
A martial arts expert shouldn't assault civilians.
Do you hear me, Judge Kim?
Will you marry me?
No, I was kidding.
I love you.
She has a nice voice.
Did you hear that?
- Clearly. - And your answer is?
You're not supposed to show that you heard.
So you won't answer?
Fine. Catch your cheating girlfriend.
Hey, I just got called in.
- I'll call you. - Again?
Yes. See you.
Okay. Take care.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Will you marry me?
No, I was kidding.
I love you.
Will you marry me?
No, I was kidding.
I love you.
[VIU Ver] tvN E01 'The Devil Judge'
"A Monster Emerges in Turbulent Times"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Hey.
Thank you.
Judge Kim?
You're in early.
We have an upcoming trial.
What's the occasion?
The library is closed.
With the lights off?
I can see pretty well in the dark.
Goodbye, then.
What's wrong?
- You live alone, right? - Yes.
It's tough, isn't it?
Your shirt's all crumpled up.
I have no time to iron it.
I see.
Get back to work.
He's a funny kid.
(11 dead, 36 with lasting disabilities)
(Associate Judge Kim Ga On)
Yes, Minister.
Judge Kang, about the live court show.
I trust in you wholeheartedly.
Don't worry.
It'll go the way of the law.
The public won't be that foolish.
It's me.
Is everything ready?
Did you meet the doctor?
And what did he say?
Good. Well done.
I'll meet the lawyer when he's out.
That's Joo Il Do's lawyer.
What name is the reservation under?
Kang Yo Han.
The presiding judge met with the counsel before the trial...
and talked to the Minister, who is suspected to protect the defendant?
And who's Mr. Park?
It is suspicious.
But you do know this doesn't prove anything, don't you?
He could pretend he discussed the procedure with the counsel,
and all he said to the Minister is...
that he'd go by the law.
The trial's tomorrow.
We'll just have to...
watch him closely at the court.
To attract advanced facilities such as charging stations,
the building classification system needs to be improved,
and the floor plans should be made available to the public.
We should also establish a construction hub...
and develop and BIM roadmaps...
to make use of construction information...
Please continue.
There's something I must watch.
(The live court show begins shortly.)
Let's see what Judge Kang Yo Han's got.
Father, forgive them,
for they do not know what they are doing.
30 seconds to go.
- Prepare the insert. - Yes, sir.
Sound check.
I'm excited that the public gets to participate in the trial.
It'll help achieve public consensus.
Whoever commits a crime should be punished.
Regardless of the defendant's social status,
the public gets to decide by vote.
It feels like the court is finally working properly.
It's going to be so fun.
The first live court show will air today.
With the court having lost public trust,
will the live trial be able to change this reality?
Hoping for equality before the law,
the entire nation is waiting for the first live trial.
We'll have to wait and see whether Judge Kang Yo Han...
and the other judges will live up to expectations.
Hello, everyone.
This is a historical moment. Coming to you live from the court.
For the first time in history, the entire nation...
will get to participate in the trial.
The process is simple.
As you see here,
install the app, DIKE, the deity of justice.
If you tap the statue, you'll be able to watch...
- the ongoing trial live. - Mom!
- Hey, come here. - Below, you'll see...
two buttons.
(What's your choice?)
While watching the trial,
if you think the defendant should be severely punished,
tap the red button.
Otherwise, tap the other button.
Your votes will be collected, visualized in graphs,
and sent to the court.
The judges will be able to see...
the people's opinions in real time and make decisions accordingly.
Let me introduce today's presiding judge,
Judge Kang Yo Han!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to a court owned by you.
There will be no more trials...
that go against common sense.
The entire trial process will be made transparent,
and we will listen to the public.
We will take the people's opinions into account as well as the law.
This court belongs to...
you, the people.
(Counsel)
Stand by.
(Live Court Show)
First, let's hear about the case we'll be handling today.
Prosecution, please go ahead.
(Prosecution)
(Defendant)
There's a town abandoned by young people.
Population, 47.
Average age of residents, 72.
Eleven of them have passed away.
Twenty-three of them are still in the ICU.
Thirteen have been discharged, but they're suffering serious...
long-term effects including severe respiratory and nerve disorders.
One of the dead victims is only three years old.
Another victim is her grandmother.
After losing her beloved granddaughter...
who she looked after while her daughter was working in Seoul,
she took her own life.
Her granddaughter was the only child in this town.
The person responsible for this tragedy is sitting right there.
He is the owner of JU Chemical Factory Four,
which is only 5km away from this town.
The factory discharged toxic chemicals into rivers...
without treatment.
The residents used the water...
for drinking, washing, and farming.
Everyone.
This is murder.
Already? Hey, put it up.
Okay.
(National Vote Status)
(Innocent, Guilty)
(Guilty)
We've now heard the prosecution's defense.
To be more precise, it was incitement rather than defense.
Watch your language.
What we just witnessed is the danger of a media trial.
A trial isn't a movie, much less a show.
A trial should only be based on objective evidence.
The prosecution just accused the defendant of murder.
What kind of businessman would murder residents on purpose?
Knowing it might kill people,
he discharged toxic wastewater into rivers.
That's negligent homicide.
Well, please have a look at this.
The embankment on a hill l behind the factory collapsed,
damaging the wastewater treatment facilities.
Mr. Prosecutor, as far as I know,
embankment maintenance is the government's responsibility.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
It's true that the collapse caused a minor chemical discharge.
However,
the factory was closed down and repaired immediately.
The discharge didn't last longer than an hour.
Your Honor.
What more could my client have done?
This was beyond control.
What if chemicals were leaking from the old facilities before too?
Do you have evidence?
Using the emergency repair as an excuse,
you replaced and discarded all the faulty parts.
And now you ask me for evidence?
So you have no evidence. All right.
The only chemical discharge that's been proven so far...
was inevitable and lasted only for a short moment.
There's no evidence that this happened before too.
According to an authority's estimate, an hour's discharge...
- couldn't have caused... - Did you say, an "estimate"?
Did I hear it wrong?
Is an estimate objective evidence?
He's right.
(Defendant)
When you don't even have any evidence,
how could you accuse a patriotic businessman of murder?
In this economic crisis,
do you know how many people's lives rely on my company?
JU Chemical employs 17,400 people.
With their families and our subcontractors taken into account,
over 100,000 people's lives depend on my company.
- This media trial... - Please watch your language!
I have a right to speak.
Defendant!
(Innocent, Guilty)
Why isn't he saying anything? What is he doing?
This is a broadcasting accident.
Hey. Prepare the commercial.
Counsel, please return to your seat.
Yes, Your Honor.
Hold on.
(Innocent, Guilty)
(Counsel, Defendant)
- Defendant? - Yes.
Please have a seat.
Okay.
(Counsel, Defendant)
Counsel, have you made all your statements?
Yes, that is all.
Then we will take a break before we continue.
You should go use the restroom.
Your Honor, may I ask a question?
Go ahead.
The embankment collapse you mentioned...
happened at the beginning of this case...
on the evening of the day after the first person had passed away.
Is this true?
Yes, it is.
It seems like quite the coincidence.
How could such an accident occur...
as soon as someone passed away...
and get rid of all evidence?
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
but the cause of death for the first person to pass away is uncertain,
so we believe it is unrelated to this case.
Even though according to the medical report,
they suffered from vertigo, migraines,
convulsions, and loss of consciousness...
just like the other victims in this case?
It is nothing more than an assumption.
The deceased didn't even get an autopsy.
There is no evidence that they found traces of toxic chemicals.
Your Honor.
Please speak.
In order to hear an objective opinion,
I would like to call Dr. Yu Jong Baek,
the leading expert in heavy metal poisoning to the stand.
Okay.
Did you get everything ready?
Have you met the doctor?
Thank you so much for coming here...
despite your busy schedule.
Not at all.
The sample of stream water submitted for evidence...
There it is.
Have you analyzed it?
I would like to hear the opinion of an expert.
Among the victims, there are many who exhibit symptoms...
of heavy metal poisoning.
However, whether or not the wastewater was the cause...
is rather uncertain.
Many people believe that exposure to heavy metals...
come from special environments like factories.
But that's not the case.
It exists in every part of our daily lives.
It could come from food ingredients grown in contaminated soil...
or makeup.
Don't we encounter these things on a daily basis?
In particular, this area...
is the first to be affected by heavy metals in the fine dust.
As it is a farming village,
it's also severely affected by chemical fertilizers and herbicide.
In comparison to that,
with this amount of pollutants in the stream water...
I'm not sure.
Witness, I would like to ask you a question as well.
Yes, go ahead.
You just said that there were pollutants in the stream water.
Could you specify what kind of pollutants were in there?
There was a variety of chemicals mixed in...
Among them, which chemical was most prominently found?
Well... It's a chemical called potassium cyanide.
Please make it easy to understand.
Potassium cyanide.
What is the common name for this?
Dr. Yu?
It's cyanide.
- Cyanide? The poison? - What did he just say?
Camera number seven.
("JU Chemical's Chairman Joo Il Do Knew and Released Cyanide?")
(Prosecutor)
I am aware that the term can sound really serious,
but this particular chemical is quite common.
Yes. If you look into it, it's quite common.
It's in almonds,
apple seeds, apricot seeds, and cherry seeds.
It's even peach seeds.
It's not always dangerous.
The amount determines how dangerous it is.
Sir.
Near this factory is a village where most of the residents are elderly.
Could you really say that the amount found was insignificant?
I'm sorry, Your Honors...
Well... Your Honor.
You may know the law well,
but don't you think I know this area better than you?
Science is based on facts.
It's not based on the sentiment of the citizens.
- Witness. - Yes, Your Honor.
That's enough. You can stop.
Dr. Yu. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Please have a seat.
He must be exhausted after giving such a long statement.
Please give him a glass of water.
- Sir. - Please give him a glass of water.
(Witness)
Thank you.
Hold on. That water...
Are you sure you didn't mix it up with the stream water sample?
What are you doing?
Your Honor. It's not the same water.
The evidence is right here.
It looked similar,
so I was mistaken.
I'm sorry, sir.
He said it was okay to drink.
If it's okay, he should be fine drinking too!
Gosh, I'm embarrassed.
If you're done, you may leave.
Darn it. I shouldn't have done it.
What kind of embarrassment is this?
My gosh, this is all Chairman Joo's fault.
Gosh. What's wrong with me?
Darn it!
Your Honor, our next witness is Jang Ki Young, the caretaker...
of the factory in this case.
Witness.
You worked in this factory for 12 years.
Before the embankment collapse,
were there any issues with the wastewater purification facilities?
(Counsel)
Witness?
Didn't you already testify to that during the investigation?
Why aren't you answering?
Right, well... The thing is...
I am filled with a lot of thoughts.
- Witness. - Mr. Jang!
- Defendant? - Yes?
Please have a seat.
I apologize.
Please continue.
Yes, Your Honor.
To be honest, there is something I would like to say.
- What are you saying? - The waste water...
has been leaking since before then.
I still don't understand how an embankment that was fine...
suddenly collapsed that night,
but one thing is for sure. The waste water...
was leaking since before then.
Since it's an important issue,
I reported this to the chairman.
- Witness! - Counsel.
Please return to your seat.
Witness.
You can speak comfortably.
I told him that the facilities were severely worn out...
and that if they weren't taken care of immediately, it would be serious.
However, the chairman said...
the factory will move next year to Southeast Asia,
so why would waste money?
Why make a fuss over something so insignificant?
- Mr. Jang. - Okay.
What did you say upon hearing that?
I said to him what if something happened to the village elders...
- And? - The chairman...
said who cares about old people who already lived full lives.
Mr. Jang. When did I say that?
"Who cares about old people who already lived full lives"?
Do you mean to tell me he said that?
I thought to myself,
"Isn't this murder?"
How can a human do such a thing?
No. It's not true!
Your Honor. I really never said that!
Murder.
My nickname is Dr. Safety.
I worked my entire life following the safety manual.
I really want to die, Your Honor.
Did you get everything ready?
Have you met the doctor?
I would like to call Dr. Yu Jong Baek to the stand.
My nickname is Dr. Safety.
(National Vote Status)
(Guilty)
This jerk is a piece of trash. Don't you agree?
There's no need to keep watching. He should be executed.
- He's so shameless. - Press it.
Execute, execute, execute.
(Guilty)
Your Honor, I feel wronged. That is not true.
I never said that.
"Who cares about old people who already lived full lives"?
Why would I say such a thing?
You never said that?
- Then what did you say? - Pardon?
You don't deny meeting the witness.
What did you say to the man in charge of the factory site?
Well... I said...
Defendant.
Please answer. The nation is watching.
(Counsel)
I'm in charge of so many things that...
I do not remember the exact conversation, Your Honor.
No. Not at all.
Your Honor, I really never said that.
Do you take the public for a fool?
It's not that.
"Who cares about old people who have lived long enough?"
What did you mean by that?
No.
You don't care if people die as long as you make money.
Are you aware that is murder by gross negligence?
Sir.
(Professional negligence)
I'll say you're not guilty.
Even if things go sideways,
it'll be professional negligence resulting in death.
Are you aware of that, defendant?
(Innocent, Guilty)
(Murder X, Professional negligence O)
I'm sorry.
It is true that...
I got the report.
Do you admit to getting the report about the leak?
And you still didn't care if the locals died?
That is honestly not true.
Then what?
What is Kang Yo Han doing?
What is he up to?
Please calm down. I'm sure he has a plan.
What plan?
I just didn't think...
it would be so bad.
The leak wasn't that severe.
I didn't think it would get this bad.
Murder?
That is preposterous.
Then you deny it was murder by gross negligence,
but admit to professional negligence resulting in death?
Joo Il Do was Cha Kyung Hee's sponsor when she was a prosecutor.
Cha Kyung Hee is an influential person in this administration,
and she has been supporting Kang Yo Han.
Is everything ready?
Did you meet the doctor?
I'll meet the lawyer when he's out.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault. I was a fool.
I was foolish enough to not take it seriously.
You were planning to move the factory anyway, weren't you?
I deserve to die for what happened.
Yes, Minister. Don't worry. It'll go the way of the law.
The public won't be that foolish.
I trust in you wholeheartedly.
He made it professional negligence resulting in death?
Your Honor.
If we're to admit to murder based on a few lies told by the witness,
this court will be mocked.
Please hand down a sentence based solely on the constitution.
I'll keep counsel's advice in mind.
I shall give the verdict after a short break.
(Live Court Show)
(Counsel)
(Defendant)
Professional negligence is up to five years, right?
Don't worry.
Your parole isn't up to that judge. It's up to the Ministry of Justice.
Murder?
Why would he tell such a lie?
Judge! It's a hit.
Our average viewership is 11.4 percent,
and the highest per minute was 14.7 percent.
The rating of people in their 20s to 40s went over 6 percent.
- We're a hit, then, right? - Yes.
Is a trial a variety show?
No, but that's how interested the public is, sir.
He's gruff like that.
- Do your best. - Sure.
We spent a fortune just to get exclusive broadcasting rights.
Our chairman will grin from ear to ear.
You can't show your glee.
Okay, eat beef.
Bye.
Yes.
Treat us.
I'll treat you to all the food in the world.
You made a fortune.
(Live Court Show)
I will announce the verdict.
I heard the public's opinion and took it seriously.
(Live Court Show)
I thought carefully,
but based only on the submitted evidence,
I reached the conclusion that...
it's a reach to say there was intent to murder.
- What? - How is that?
However, as the defendant admitted,
I acknowledge the reserve charges...
that was professional negligence resulting in death and injury.
Five years is the maximum sentence...
of professional negligence resulting in death.
However,
the judicial reform bill that was passed last year...
says I can hand down an accumulated sentence...
to account for all the victims.
No way.
Kim Soon Ja.
Park Myung Soon.
Lee Jeong Ro.
Bae Myung Jae.
And little Yu So Young.
Lee Gab Boon.
Kim Dong Jae.
Park Yong Soon.
Hwang In Chan.
Kang Jeon Il.
Gu Jeong Ok.
(Gu Jeong Ok)
Kim Yoo Choon.
Jeong Kwon Ah.
Hwang Mal Ja.
Seonwoo Yoon Jeong.
Lee Myung Sook.
He's a true master.
Lee Seok Kyu.
(Lee Seok Kyu)
(Won Young Seon)
Won Young Seon.
(JU Chemical Sewage Leak, 11 dead, 36 with disabilities)
Because of your foolish greed,
you took innocent lives...
and those who survived will live the rest of their lives in pain.
I accumulated the sentence for all 47 victims and...
the verdict is...
a total of 235 years.
(Verdict: 235 years imprisonment)
(Guilty, Innocent)
Wait, stop the car.
(Verdict: 235 years imprisonment)
- That's crazy. - No way.
He really got it.
Look at that!
Is this even possible?
(Ratings)
Darn it.
(Live Court Show)
(Verdict: 235 years imprisonment)
I do wish you live a long life.
This is impossible.
No way.
(Live Court Show)
Your Honor.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Thank you so much, Your Honor.
- Please get up. - Thank you.
I can die with no regrets now.
Kim Soon Ja, the old lady who killed herself...
after losing her granddaughter, is my little sister.
I tried to kill myself many times too,
but dying isn't as easy as I thought.
I failed every time.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Then you deny it was murder by gross negligence,
but admit to professional negligence resulting in death?
If you put up the pictures on the screen,
I'll call their names one by one.
Yes, sir.
Bae Myung Jae. Lee Seok Kyu.
And little Yu So Young.
(The Devil Judge)
It was moving.
And you looked hot too.
The rule of law? Do you think the purpose of a trial is justice?
You just pretend to have a heart.
I sell hope and get paid fear.
What is it you want from me?
Prey?
A man who just enjoys himself isn't attractive...
or useful.
Why in the world do you do this?
You're just bait. Fresh bait.
Maybe he isn't tamed enough.
Crazy jerk!