[English subtitles are available]
Gao Liang.
Why do you turn away?
Jiang Nanzheng.
I'm sorry.
I didn't finish the task.
Turn around.
I won't.
Come on!
Does it hurt?
No.
Fine. You are a stone which can't feel the pain.
Take off your hat.
Why do I have to take off the hat?
I'll change fresh dressing for you.
If I had finished the task,
I would feel very good now.
What are you talking about?
Don't move.
Go to bed now.
Tomorrow, you can ask the medical officer
to change fresh dressing for you.
The soldiers over there, come here!
[Warehouse]
Go out!
Quick!
Don't push me!
Take a tool with you and open the door for me.
The door of the train car?
Cut the crap! Be quick!
All right. I'll open it.
New soldiers. Be quick! Be quick!
What is it? I'm working for you!
Be careful.
Be quick!
[Zhangmu Station]
Let's start working.
Come on! Let's start!
Gao Liang, Army B will use this train
to send weapons and ammunition to South Town.
They want Division 234 to be caught unawares.
In this way,
Division 234 will be defeated in this place.
We'd better not sleep.
What shall we do?
Shall we learn from the Railway Guerilla?
Let's bomb the train.
You can't do this when we are fighting them.
This place is filled with ammunition.
If you bomb the train,
all the captives will die.
I'll use a pickax to destroy the railway track.
They can fix it.
They can fix it?
I'll steal some hand grenades
and bomb the track. Can they fix it then?
They can do rush repairs.
I bomb it and they can do rush repairs?
After an airport is heavily bombed,
they can do rush repairs within 3 to 4 hours.
It's just a railway track.
That's the job of the army.
What do you think we can do?
I think
we should destroy the track
while the train is running.
If the train is derailed,
they can't do rush repairs.
Fine.
Let's do it then.
I think
we have to
destroy something
so that Army B won't be able to repair it.
But the consequence should not be too serious.
Do you understand?
You mean
to have a free meal in a restaurant.
[Zhangmu Station]
Commander of the First Company,
go there to take a look!
Yes!
Add more fuel.
We are about to leave.
Five minutes.
You've already fallen in battle, Veteran.
Don't cheat me!
Release the brake and the train will move.
What happened?
What's going on?
My brother, when I was living in a cave,
I loved lighting up the wick of a bomb.
After the explosion,
I saw the flame
and I thought of you.
[The First Commando]
Gao Shan!
Yes!
I think in this way,
I can get closer to you.
I really want to know
what you were thinking
when a bomb
exploded near you.
Now I'm wearing the same military uniform as you.
I've just bombed the railway track.
I've done something important for the first time.
Take him away!
Be quick!
Division Commander,
Directing Department has reported that
some new recruits had caused a disturbance
at Zhangmu Train Station.
The train hasn't departed at the right time.
The reinforcing artillery and armored forces
weren't able to leave.
Division Commander,
Zheng Yuan is calling.
Mr. Meng,
don't worry.
There are no heavy weapons in South Town.
You might not lose.
Let's talk about it later.
I feel I've lost face
because two new recruits
have ruined the drill.
Don't say so.
We were both
new recruits in the past.
Don't look down upon them.
My subordinate told me that
the two new recruits were really something.
Shall I ask some people
to send them to your place?
You can take a look at them.
I don't want to see them.
You can really keep cool!
Chess, drill, wine, and war.
I must keep cool.
Mr. Meng,
you don't have to worry about it.
Good new recruits
are like sharp needle tips.
I will see them sooner or later.
The more excellent they are,
the earlier I can see them.
You sound reasonable.
I'm not just a great talker.
Did you receive the gift
I had sent to you?
Stop!
Easy! Easy!
Qin Hanyong?
Commander,
the gift.
Who gave it to me?
Our Division Commander.
Commander,
you are standing so near.
You can't escape, can you?
Fellow soldiers,
the drill is over.
Release them.
Veterans,
please release them!
Veterans, please release them!
My brother,
It was the first time that I had been raised up.
They were cheering.
It feels so good to win victory.
I feel that
I really want to
tell it to someone.
I was surprised by such a thought.
I still firmly believe that
I saw her
among the cheering people
that night.
Division Commander,
I think these young men
are reliable.
Look,
they only bombed a big hole
beside the railway track.
They started the engine of the train,
but they didn't drive the train in motion.
What does this mean?
They wanted to tell us that
they were able to bomb the railway track
and start the train.
They could cause the train to be derailed.
Chen Dashan, you are shielding a fault.
The new recruits are so bold.
No one knows what problems they will cause
in the future training.
We must investigate this at the fastest speed.
Whose idea was it?
Who did it?
Such soldiers are like
time bombs in the army.
They must be punished.
Or they should leave the army.
New recruits can leave the army,
Regiment 720 can't leave.
We must find the cause from inside.
Division Commander,
our regiment has lagged far behind
in military training.
Especially after the reaffiliation,
we were always a drag on the Division.
If the general is incompetent,
the effort of the army will be wasted.
I have to criticize myself.
You first told me the reasons and then the difficulties.
After that, you criticized yourself.
Chen Dashan,
you are very good at
self-criticism.
I'll remember your self-criticism.
What's your condition?
Division Commander,
I want to start with the source of the problem.
I want five cadres.
How many?
Five.
That will be more than half of the cadres
who are in the "Four Modernizations" training this time.
Division Commander, you should use a heavy hammer
to sound the best drum.
Two.
I will ask two most professional Company cadres
in the Division to go to your regiment.
They will be a great help to Regiment 720.
Pay attention to the training, mindset,
style of work, and cultivation
of the new soldiers.
After two rounds of screening,
there must be highly qualified soldiers in your regiment.
Yes!
Regiment 720 will learn from Regiment 700.
Talking without practicing.
No.
Practicing without talking.
When an army is not fighting a war,
its problems will be simple and clear
like the fleas on a bald head.
However, when you
get ready to solve the problems,
you will find that
the problems
are like the enemies on the battlefield.
They are good at hiding and disguise.
You might hurt your allies.
Leading an army
is like fighting a war.
You can never relax.
Division Commander, we have won in this drill,
but it was a narrow victory.
We have won?
Is it a true victory if we
depended on two scouts to win?
Not knowing how we have won
will keep me awake at night.
Winning by chance is not something we can control.
It's more dangerous than failure.
Let me tell you,
this time, Division 234
could turn the tide
mainly because of two comrades.
One is called Qin Hanyong.
His great contribution was to get close to the enemies.
He is a cadre.
The other one is called Xia Lin.
I have the emphasize that
he is a soldier.
This time, he was not only rewarded,
he has also made an exception and
has become a cadre.
Make an exception and become a cadre,
my comrades-in-arms.
Think carefully
about how to learn from him.
What did he do?
Xia Lin
went to the enemy's rear area
and discovered their troops in ambush.
He fired off a red signal flare
and saved our Division.
What signal flare?
What red signal flare?
In the drill,
how many signal flares have we fired off?
What a question!
He fired off one signal flare
and became a platoon leader.
If you fire off several more signal flares,
you will become a cadre in the Regiment.
Only one signal flare?
Red?
Sergeant, I fired it off!
I fired it off!
Stop bragging!
You fired it off. You fired it off.
I did fire it off!
Believe me. I fired it off with the gun
of Mr. Li in Army B.
Gu Yiye saw it.
Hey, man!
I was not there.
[Station of Regiment 720]
We have arrived.
We have arrived at the regiment headquarters.
Yes!
[Army 53082 of PLA]
Shuanggang. We have really arrived at the regiment headquarters.
It's gorgeous!
One, two, three, four!
Who can you blame?
We can only blame ourselves for dropping the ball.
The chief of staff
will continue to pay attention to this issue.
You received the soldiers.
You know what was going on.
The training of these new recruits
is very important.
Give me some advice on
how to organize the company of new recruits.
Regimental Commander,
I'm just the Chief of Military Affairs Unit.
Don't abase yourself.
Your modesty is fake.
Tell me directly.
Yes!
Regimental Commander,
many new recruits of this year
are very
very lively.
Some were fighting each other on their way coming.
Well,
during the drill at Zhangmu Train Station,
in front of the cadres,
some of them just did what they want.
Of course,
the result was a good one.
But
when I recall this,
I'm covered with cold sweat.
You are also afraid?
How many new recruits
are like this?
Over eighty.
So many!
Therefore, Regimental Commander,
if our regiment wants to rise,
I suggest
we concentrate
the troublemakers.
In this way, the management will be easier.
Concentrate them
and solve difficult problems.
The achievement is not important.
The management will be easier.
If they are in different units,
you will be too busy to attend to all.
Too busy to attend to all.
You'll be put in a double squeeze in the future.
It's a good idea.
From a positive perspective,
we can choose new recruits
with higher qualities
-and put them in a company,
-Yes.
which can be considered as a modeling company.
Well,
in this way, will other people feel that
they have been given up?
Give up?
Give up on who?
The speed of a train depends on the engine.
Let the models take the lead.
We will bring about an upswing!
It's settled.
We will use this method.
Yes!
When organizing the companies for the new recruits,
put those with better performance
in the First Company.
Put the troublemakers
in the Third Company.
I think we can punish them later.
We can observe them for a period of time
and give them one more chance.
What do you think?
The chief of staff won't allow us to postpone the punishment.
In his words,
we need to investigate it as soon as possible
and give them severe punishment.
We can ask them to leave the army.
What can we do?
Follow the instructions of the chief of staff.
You can handle this.
Yes!
Excuse me!
Regimental Commander, I've come...
You've come. You've come.
You think I don't know your purpose?
You've come to request for punishment, right?
You've come to plead for the soldiers who had caused trouble, right?
I've been talking about it for a long time.
Regimental Commander,
I do know some new recruits
left the Division
and bombed the railway track at Zhangmu Train Station.
I should take responsibility.
Do you think
you can shoulder the responsibility for me?
Fine!
Come here!
Sit on this chair
and be the Regimental Commander!
Listen to me!
I'll repeat this again.
Listen carefully!
You didn't leave the Division.
Nor did you give them an order to bomb the railway track.
It had nothing to do
with you at all.
One is the Chief of Military Affairs of Regiment 720.
The other is a grassroots officer
from the Division.
If I punish you two,
who will
solve the problems of Regiment 720 in the future?
Am I not looking for trouble?
But, Regimental Commander,
it's unfair
for those new recruits.
That's right.
Unfair?
Lu Pingfan,
you are an officer as well as a student.
Have you become too bookish?
For a soldier,
there is only discipline and sacrifice!
Why are you still standing there?
Sir!
The Division wants our regiment
to organize the commending meeting.
It will be a ritual
where new recruits will receive collar badges and cap cockades.
Won't that be a farce?
How can new recruits receive collar badges and cap cockades?
Which fool has...
Division Commander gave this order.
He said the new recruits
had passed the test.
The order of the Division Commander.
The purpose of the Division Commander is very clear,
that is, to encourage them and to spur them on.
We should understand it.
We should organize the commending meeting well.
We must guarantee its complete success.
Yes!
[Headquarters of Regiment 720]
Hail to the Chief!
Salute to everyone!
The drill
was a test
for all members of Division 234.
A lot of problems have come to light.
We have also shown our fighting spirit.
We fear no hardship nor death.
In the end, we won victory in the drill.
Now I will announce
the units and individuals
that will be commended by the Division.
The following people will be awarded Merit Citation Class III.
You two, sit down.
The following are the people being awarded by the Division:
Regiment 700, the Third Battalion, the Sixth Company...
Sit down, please.
Sit down.
Soldiers in Reconnaissance Company:
Dong Guohui, Wang Guangwei.
Gao Liang!
Yes!
If you don't want to sit down,
you can stand up.
I can sit down.
Mr. Song,
Why do you want to talk to us now?
They are holding the commending meeting downstairs.
If I'm being commended
and they can't find me in the company,
how anxious they will be!
I don't want to affect
the procedure of the commending meeting.
You are in a good state of mind.
You are very optimistic.
It's a pity
that it's a wrong guess.
I've asked you to come
because I want to talk about
something very important with you.
Do you still remember what happened during the drill?
It's good that you still remember.
I have three points to make.
First,
did you
fight with other people
and start an affray
on the road?
Your attitude is good.
It will be easier to talk about it with you.
Second,
when the receiving regiment was held captive
at Zhangmu Train Station,
did you organize the mutiny of the new recruits
and
leave the Division?
We didn't.
We...
There was no mutiny. We were
organizing them to save our comrades-in-arms.
Did you do it or not?
No.
Yes.
It was our decision.
OK. Third,
did you steal some hand grenades
and tried to damage national facilities?
You've almost bombed the railway track,
right?
That's not right.
We wanted to help our division
win the battle.
That's why we wanted to bomb the railway track.
I didn't damage the railway.
I bombed a hole beside the railway track.
You have to understand that
Division 234 could win the battle
not because you did something to the train
or bombed the railway track.
Do you understand?
Sir,
what on earth do you want to say?
I have to tell you my attitude first.
You two are new recruits that I received.
You've passed the physical examination and political censor.
When the new recruits were on the road,
there was a drill.
We saw three problems
with you:
Fighting with other people;
Leaving the Division;
Stealing weapons
but failing to damage the railway.
Sir,
you are exaggerating it.
It was not at all...
Let me finish my words first.
Some cadres discovered
what you did at that time.
We knew part of the story after it happened.
Fortunately, we knew this early enough.
Everything was still in control.
Otherwise,
you might cause
immeasurable loss for the army.
Therefore,
The Military Affairs Unit have discussed about it.
We've reported it to the Regimental Party Committee and they have agreed.
We don't think you are suitable to stay in the army.
Now I inform you that
you should leave the army.
Leave the army?
Sir,
please don't scare us.
I can understand
how you feel.
The army will
contact the Military Department of your hometown
as soon as possible.
We will tell them clearly
why we ask you to leave the army.
As to your files,
I will think about how to write about it.
Go back and pack up your belongings.
You don't have to participate
in the activities of the Company tomorrow.
Go to the Military Affairs Unit
to report for duty directly.
No!
I refuse!
Why do you ask me to leave?
What did I do? You are asking me to leave.
I won't leave!
Gu Yiye,
This is a field force.
This is not the army compound!
You are from an army compound,
but you can't act unreasonably!
Song Jianshe,
were we wrong not to become captives?
The cadres knew it at that time.
We bombed the railway track
in order to protect the main force of Division 234.
Well,
the new recruits all knew it and they have all participated in it.
Now the drill is over.
There is a problem with that.
You want us to become the scapegoats.
Gao Liang,
don't mention other people.
Did I say anything wrong?
Didn't Lu Pingfan tell you that
it was risky to do so?
The investigation group contacted Lu Pingfan
and the new recruits who were present at that time.
After careful investigation,
they found
[Writing Paper for 53082 Army]
detailed evidence.
The decision can't be changed in principle.
I'll leave then.
Do you think I enjoy being a solider?
Let me tell you,
the cadres are all very annoying.
You are the most troublesome!
I'll leave.
I'll leave then.
I won't come back even if you beg me.
Gao Liang!
Mr. Song,
is there a way
to change this decision?
That's impossible.
It's the decision of the leaders of the regiment.
Unless
you go to see someone.
Who is it?
[Regiment 702 Warehouse
Huts for Female Soldier Platoon of New Soldier Company]
Did you see Jiang Nanzheng?
No, I didn't.
I didn't pay attention.
Nanzheng,
stop sewing. Something happened.
What is it?
Gao Liang and Gu Yiye have to leave the army.
Nanzheng, be careful!
What are you doing here?
Hello, Sir!
I want to see Gao Liang and Gu Yiye.
No, you can't.
It's an order from the higher authorities.
Female soldiers are not allowed to go into
the dormitories of the male soldiers.
I need to see them.
Well,
could you ask them to come out?
I'll say a few words to them, then I'll leave.
Could you just bend the rules a little?
I really need to see them.
-I told you couldn't.
-Ladies...
What are you doing?
Sergeant,
the ladies have difficulty.
Please help them.
Ladies,
What do you
want?
Hello, Sir!
I want to see Gao Liang and Gu Yiye.
Could you ask them to come out?
OK!
Gu Yiye is not here.
Gao Liang
is busy.
Miss,
could you tell me
your name so that I can...
If you have something to tell them,
I can help you.
Tong Bing, let's go.
My name is Jiang Weixing.
Scarlet airwave is transmitted in the sky.
The East Is Red sounded beyond the sky.
The satellite in the East Is Red!
Jiang Weixing.
Mr. Jiang, what happened just now?
A female soldier
insisted on asking my name.
I told her.
Is she beautiful?
Here you are.
Good morning, Squad Leader!
Where is Gu Yiye?
I don't know.
I didn't see him in the morning.
Go two hundred meters north
and you will see our sanitary area.
Please
try your best to clean that place.
Yes!
[New Recruit]
Gao,
I'm sorry.
Do you know?
That I became a soldier
was the biggest news in our village.
When I left my hometown,
all the villagers came out.
They came to see my off.
They were pounding on the gongs and drums.
Very noisy.
A wedding
is not so boisterous.
In front of all the villagers, my father said to me,
"Niu Mancang,
let me tell you.
If the army asks you to leave,
I'll break your leg!"
Then my father knelt down before me.
So did my mother.
Gao,
I'm sorry
but
the villagers have placed their hopes on me.
Zhang,
you can't become a cadre
because the two soldiers have to leave the army,
can you?
Lu Pingfan,
don't you know the Regimental Commander's attitude?
You weren't able to persuade him, were you?
We are all responsible for this.
Alright,
I'll take the responsibility alone. Is that OK?
Fine.
You are great. You have guts.
Your high morality reaches up to the clouds.
Don't I sympathize with them?
Don't I feel it's a pity?
Such strong desire of expression!
Excuse me!
Come in!
What’s the matter?
I want to ask
why Gao Liang and Gu Yiye
have to leave the army.
Zhang Fei,
you received the new recruits.
Now...
I know.
Now I should comfort them
and see them off.
Very good!
Did you see
the attitude of a good sergeant?
But...
But
during the drill
I agreed to
everything Gao Liang and Gu Yiye had done.
Well, tell me directly
what you want to do.
If
they really have to leave the army,
you should ask me to leave as well.
No.
Zhang Fei,
you are going too far.
While I'm here,
you shouldn't blame yourself.
Zhang Fei,
we joined the army in the same year.
Although you haven't become a cadre,
you've been assiduous
and bearing hardships without complaint for so many years.
You've cultivated so many new recruits.
You've never talked to the leaders for a personal reason.
What's the matter now?
What are you doing?
You want to give up your career
for the two new recruits?
Ask you to leave?
How can you leave?
Don't you know your family condition?
Chief. Song,
Commissar. Lu,
I'm serious about
every word I said just now.
I'm willing...
I'm willing to
answer for every sentence I said.
I've asked my comrade-in-arms.
During the drill,
Xia Lin fired off a blind shell.
The signal flare was fired off by Gao Liang.
Li Shaobing,
the Company Commander in Regiment 700,
can bear witness.
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
Reconnaissance company of Regiment 700, please.
-One, two, three, four!
-December 12 to 17,
[Headquarters of Division 234]
1983,
General Staff Department, General Political Department,
and General Logistics Department of PLA
[Enhance combat preparedness]
jointly held the First Working Conference of Military Representatives.
The conference summarized
the workflow and experience of representatives
of land military regions in the past over 30 years.
[Create a new situation in the revolutionary
modernization of the armed forces]
It was pointed out that
to speed up the facility modernization of the army
asked for building up a both socialist-minded and
professionally competent representative land force.
December 13, 1983, Xinhua News Agency reported.
According to the instructions of the State Council
and the Central Military Commission,
[Defend the motherland]
the PLA railway engineering corps
has been incorporated into the Ministry of Railways.
Please show your ID card.
I don't have an ID card.
I want to see the Division Commander.
What can I do for you?
Have you reported to the security post of the headquarters?
No.
Then you can't come in.
Please step back.
I'm a new soldier in Regiment 720.
I want to see the Division Commander.
Sir,
The sentry is inviolable.
Here is the division headquarters.
Please obey the disciplines.
I didn't offend the sentry.
Please tell me
what I should do according to the disciplines.
Why do you want to see the Division Commander?
I can only say it
when I see the Division Commander.
[Create a new situation in the revolutionary
modernization of the armed forces]
You really don't understand.
[Military Affairs Office]
You should not come to see the Division Commander.
Are you leaving?
I'm leaving.
Hello, Mr. Sun!
I regret it more and more.
Behind the Regimental Commander's back,
pull the rug from under his feet.
He went to the division headquarters to speak for two new recruits,
ending up being scolded to his face.
A government functionary should not do so.
It's all right if a student officer like you does so.
People all know that
you are not a clever man.
I should not get involved in this.
Tell me clearly,
what's wrong with a student officer?
Should student officers
be looked down upon
by sophisticated officers like you?
This is the last time.
I'm owing too many favors.
I heard
many of your peer student officers
had left.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I appreciate you very much!
A sophisticated officer like me
broke the rules once in a while.
That's quite interesting.
In such a weather,
a veteran can stand two to three hours
while a new recruit can stand at most 40 minutes.
I think
he can stand over an hour.
I can see that
you like this soldier very much.
To be honest,
Gao Liang is like a hedgehog.
It's fine if he leaves.
He won't bring any more trouble to the army.
Gu Yiye
is born to be a soldier.
It's reasonable to ask him to leave.
But if he stays in the army,
he will play an important role.
It's not for myself.
It's for the army.
If you want people
to think highly of this army,
it should not live in an old story.
There should be more soldiers with such quality.
I know student officers like you
always feel that indigenous officers like me
can't understand you.
I only want to tell you that
people don't know
they have their own pride and prejudice.
I don't disagree
with your judgment on Gu Yiye.
I feel
you might have underestimated Gao Liang.
Gao,
You are kind to Jiagui
and you are very kind to me.
I know it very clearly.
However, I really can't leave the army.
Gao,
you are different from Gu Yiye.
[Create a new situation in the revolutionary
modernization of the armed forces]
I'm different from you, too.
One, two, three, four!
[Create a new situation in the revolutionary
modernization of the armed forces]