(Previously...)
Say sorry, now.
Not that easy.
They are from Calderioz.
You've heard of them, right?
There are so many members.
And six of the top members
are in this school.
I'm really sorry.
What's the benefit for me?
I will do everything you wish.
Five wishes.
You have to fulfill my first wish today.
Come to the Calderioz's headquarters.
One wish is done.
I won't give up until we find proof.
And get our revenge on Ares.
I know you can do it.
Hurry up, the gate's closing.
It's all wet.
Why do you have to piss me off
this early?
You followed me into the toilet?
-I'm following you?
-What do you call this, then?
Isn't it the other way around?
Oh, my God!
-Res.
-Hey.
Look who's here.
I think I don't want to know.
-Zea?
-Fino?
What are you doing here?
It's none of your business.
Get out of here.
Now tell me, what were you doing?
Nothing.
Did you two...
Get your hands off me!
You're disgusting.
But, maybe we can do it next time.
Should we do it over there?
Or maybe we do it now?
-Continue what you're doing.
-What, are you jealous? Just say it.
-Let's do our business.
-What are you doing?
Ionized energy is required to release...
To release... What was it?
Ionized energy is an energy
from an atom...
in its gas phase
to release an electron.
So embarrassing!
A principal idea is the idea
behind a paragraph.
It's also contained in the beginning
or the last part of the paragraph.
Ares, can you tell me an example
of a storyline idea?
Hey!
What?
-Ares, you should go wash your face.
-Okay, Ma'am.
All right, class, let's continue.
You followed me into the toilet?
-I'm following you?
-What do you call this, then?
Isn't it the other way around?
Oh, my God!
Look who's here.
Ares!
Zea?
What were you thinking just now?
Focus on the subject!
Sorry, Ma'am.
Gosh...
♪I believe in second chances
For the broken-hearted♪
♪Now I can take it for granted
Each and every "disregarded"♪
♪I fall apart yet I am still right here♪
♪But broken heart is hard to heal♪
♪It kills me
Everytime I read between the lines♪
♪Love is divided went undecided♪
♪Fade and misguided
Just like another broken-hearted♪
♪Now since you've been gone♪
♪I should carry on♪
♪Cause I'm tired
Of writing songs about you♪
♪I have spent all night♪
♪Just to make this right♪
♪I can't be somewhere I don't belong♪
♪It's time to move along♪
♪Lonely♪
♪For sure♪
♪But I bet I'm not the only one♪
♪Just like a broken hearted♪
-Zea, is this the correct answer?
-Which one?
-That's correct.
-Thanks.
What are you doing, you pervert?
Are you crazy?
-No, I'm not doing anything.
-Just admit it.
We caught you red-handed!
-Admit it.
-I was just taking her pictures.
That means you're stalking,
and it's a crime, you stupid.
Give me your phone.
-This is my privacy.
-Give it to her.
-Or maybe...
-What?
-He has our pictures, too!
-Oh, my god!
-Do you have our pictures?
-You pervert!
-I swear, I don't!
-Grab his phone!
-I can't reach it!
-Grab his phone, quick!
Look, he ran away.
You should've taken it from him.
What do you want?
Huh?
There's quite a lot of pictures.
You know, taking pictures of people
without their permission...
means that you violated their privacy.
Are you going to delete them,
or should I do it for you?
Can't talk?
Don't you ever do that again.
That's a crime, you know?
All you do is dating.
Do your homework for once.
-That's my business.
-Get a girlfriend, then.
-I have one.
-Where is she?
Right here.
Res, I'll see you later.
I have to take my baby Carissa home.
Cut that out.
I'll catch up with you guys.
Don't you have anything better to do
than dating?
-Bye.
Serra.
Want me to take you home?
I will take you anywhere,
even to the wedding altar.
No, thanks.
Okay. Maybe next time?
Cleo. It's fine if you want
to go with them.
No, it's okay.
Aren't you going to look for Zea?
Maybe she's waiting for you
in the bathroom.
Peace be with you!
Hey, where did you get your muffler?
-At a shop near my house.
-Your muffler's nice.
Mor, close your mouth. You look ugly.
Shut up!
Res, I still remember her face...
when she saw me
come out of the bathroom.
She freaked out.
-Do you mean Zea?
-Yeah, her!
She looked so cute,
which makes me want to...
Give her a ride on my bike, Res.
-He's jealous!
-He is.
I think you like her.
Because I can see it from your gestures.
You always do this when she's around.
Mor.
But, you know what I mean, right?
That's why...
Why is it salty?
What are you doing?
Are you recording me?
Guys, look at this guy.
All the girls in Jabodetabek
are crazy about him.
He looks even better
when he's doing his magic trick.
Are you recording me?
-Delete the video.
-No way.
Dan, give me the phone!
What if the girls from school see that?
How am I supposed to save my face then?
Delete that!
It's live, how can I delete it?
-I have to go.
-Who's going to pay the bill?
-Thank you, son.
-You are welcome.
Sorry for troubling you.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Don't mind that.
I'm too old for this.
I don't think I have the strength.
You're walking on a slope, that's why.
Have you eaten your lunch?
Not yet.
-Let me buy you one.
-Sure, thank you.
Sir, can I have a bowl, please?
Again, sorry for troubling you.
-Thank you very much.
-It's okay.
-Here's your order.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Drink this.
-Thank you, son.
I got a pair of slippers for you.
You can use this.
Thank God.
Thank you so much.
-I have to go now.
-Okay.
Bara?
-How are you?
-I'm fine.
You never called me since you moved out.
Want to meet tonight?
I'll share my location,
so you can meet with The Wolves.
Of course! I miss you guys.
-All right, see you.
-See you, Zea.
Guys, Zea will be joining us
in a minute.
Seriously?
-It's been a while since I met her.
-Me, too.
Same as me.
Is she staying in Jakarta now?
-Just recently.
-Okay.
So listen up, Kar.
Find out information
on the activities that we can do...
when we go for our tour
to the villages.
I'm on it.
I think we should help the locals
with the problems in their village.
Like repairing a broken bridge,
or something like that.
What do you guys think?
-Sounds good to me.
-I agree.
We are now having our meeting.
And these two are playing games.
Look at these champions.
How are you guys doing?
We're good.
I died.
Hello, Bara?
I'm sorry, something just came up.
I can't meet you guys.
I see. All right, Zea. Take care.
She can't make it.
I'm here to collect on your promise.
You said you're going to give me
my money tonight.
If you don't have the money,
I can pay it off for you.
But your girlfriend Sandra
has to be with me tonight.
You should pay your debt.
And not just make empty promises.
I know, but...
Boy.
-What do you mean by this?
-It's nothing. I just...
Did you use me to pay off your debt?
Sandra. Speak of the devil.
We were just talking about you.
Should we go now?
Leave her alone.
Your business is with...
-Sandra.
-Wait.
I told you, leave her alone!
-Leave me alone!
-Sandra!
-Leave me alone! Help me!
-Relax.
-Help!
-Shut up!
Let her go.
We have a pretty girl right here.
Want to join us?
I think you're interested.
Are you okay?
I'm so scared.
It's alright now.
They can't harm you anymore.
Thanks.
I'm Sandra.
I'm Zea.
Let's get out of here first.
I think we're safe.
Can I ask what happened back there?
My boyfriend put me up for a bet.
I thought he was a nice guy,
but turns out he's not.
-Be careful next time, okay?
-Thank you.
Sandra, are you okay?
Thank God. I was so worried about you!
Where have you been?
Sorry I left you back there,
but I told Ares about this.
I think he's on his way.
Just relax, okay?
What? You called my brother?
What were you thinking?
If he knows I'm still outside
at this hour, I'm dead!
Sandra.
Are you okay?
Who's trying to mess with you?
Where are they?
You?
You know Zea?
What are you doing here?
She saved me from my useless boyfriend.
And she fought those guys.
Thanks for helping my sister.
You're welcome.
But, why are you here?
I was meeting a friend.
And I heard someone call for help.
Turns out it was your sister.
Are you really okay now?
-I'll go now.
-Thanks again.
Which one of you
was trying to mess with my sister?
Ares.
So she was your sister?
Yeah, she is.
What's up?
You should tell me if there is a fight.
I mean...
Sorry, I mean...
-What?
-I mean...
If only I knew she was your sister...
There's no way I would...
I was just kidding. There's no way
I'd do that to your sister.
Sorry.
Just kidding, huh? Huh?
I swear I didn't know
she was your sister.
I will spare you,...
but on one condition.
One condition?
What condition?
-Are you done?
-I'm done here.
-We're done.
-You think so?
There's still more.
-Do it.
-I'm going to lose a lot of weight.
Be my guest.
Let's make a vlog.
Hello, guys! We're from Calderioz!
Check out our vlog.
-We got someone to clean our bikes!
-Clean our bikes!
Hope you don't catch a cold.
If any of you want a free bike wash,
just come down here.
The usual place. Come on!
Enough. Turn it off.
Let's go.
Make it shiny.
Zea.
-Yes?
-This is for you.
I hope you like it.
Thanks, Fin.
Oh, so sweet! She has an admirer.
Okay, that's enough.
But I don't really like this.
You want this?
-I prefer strawberry juice.
-Give me. Thanks.
Love you.
Fino!
-I'm surprised Zea can fight.
-Me, too.
She's cute and can defend herself.
-The best match for Ares, am I right?
-I agree.
Or, the best match for me.
You should look in the mirror.
Who knows?
I haven't made my move on her.
I'll give her some ice tea.
You should sit with us.
We still have empty seats.
Of course! But, can you feed me?
Of course, babe.
Oh my gosh.
My stomach is suddenly hurting.
Serra!
Why is she leaving, too?
Have you heard the gossip
about that new kid at school?
Have you seen Zea?
No, we haven't.
(Dear, Zea.)
(Please know that you are
the most beautiful girl in the world.)
(I fell in love with you
the first time I saw you.)
I'm curious...
Who are you, really?
Let me introduce myself.
Zea.
I'm quite surprised...
that you know how to fight.
Do I need to explain that to you?
Be quiet.
Sorry, Ma'am.
I'm here...
to say thank you for saving my sister.
This is coming from my heart.
But, our agreement...
is still on.
It's not negotiable.
Ares!
Ares, pick up the books.
Zea. You, too.
Me?
Now!