Unforgettable Love
EP04
I've said it five or six times.
I'm almost a repeater.
Since you put on the big diamond ring,
you've changed.
You are beginning to take bubble bath and apply mask.
So elegant!
If the news that you're going to get married
gets around,
what would you do?
I'm just playing along with him.
He stirred up the trouble by himself,
so he should solve the problem by himself.
Now I just want Dr. Qin
to stop
rejecting my proposal.
Propose?
What's going on?
Why did he propose to Qin Yiyue?
It's impossible
Why is that?
What are you doing?
I'm now teaching you
how to make your ex eat a humble pie.
That's when your ex-boyfriend's
current girlfriend provokes you,
take a better new boyfriend
in front of him
If you agree,
I'd like to be your
better new boyfriend.
Then thank you, Mr. He,
for saving the day!
You make a wise choice.
By the way,
this new building,
no, Yiyue Guan,
just as
a gift
witnessing our love
is given to you.
What a rich man!
You go too far.
I hadn't thought of a name for the building.
This is the right moment.
I'll return this ring
to him tomorrow.
Then we don't owe each other anything.
It's bedtime.
Give the tablet computer to me.
You filmed it.
Have a sleep now.
I didn't expect this man
who looks like
he is the only one,
he is quite a gentleman at the critical moment.
Take your bath.
Let me try
the new toilet deodorant.
It works very well.
No, no, no, no.
By the way,
when you take a bath,
remember to take off
your big diamond ring.
You're so careless.
I'm afraid you'll lose it.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
How much do you think this big diamond ring is?
I estimate it to be at least ten carats.
I'll Baidu it.
That doesn't seem right.
You just said that
how many carats is that ring?
I estimate it to be at least ten carats.
Ten carats?
It must be worth more than hundred thousand yuan.
That is only enough to
buy a ring without diamond.
Even if you sell me,
I can't afford to pay.
What can we do about it?
Did you find the ring?
Nothing found.
Come on.
Take a look at your cell phone.
You're on the hot search again.
There are more than three million comments.
Not only Weibo,
all the major social media platforms
are discussing you.
Saying that in your past life,
you must have done a lot of good things.
We can make a new post
to talk about
the experience of
living with
an internet celebrity roommate.
I'm so upset.
You go back.
Qin Yiyue, how can you do this?
Marriage is such a big thing.
You didn't even tell me, your primary school classmate.
Congratulations.
As your aunt, I'm just calling
to congratulate you.
My daughter, Mengmeng, is not as capable as you.
Would you mind to
introduce her to a good boyfriend?
Dear,
I am now transformed
to be online beauty blogger.
Could you give me
some new products of your husband's company
for trial?
Do you want to buy a house?
Contact me.
Do you have insurance?
Contact my husband.
Who is it?
What's wrong with being so loud?
Hi.
Miss Qin, where's your ring?
Ring.
Can't you lose it?
I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
That's precious.
By bank transfer or by check?
Can I write you an IOU?
Where are you taking me?
Hello, I'm Qin Yiyue.
It's not Mrs. He.
I'm a doctor.
I'm not the stepmother.
I don't accept interviews.
I don't take ads.
I don't go on the red carpet.
I don't cut the ribbon.
I don't introduce connections.
I don't name children.
Hello, thank you.
Hello, goodbye.
This is Mr. He.
I don't care if you are or not Mr. He.
He.
He Qiaoyan?
I just let you know that
I've made an appointment for Xiaobao
and will go over for a follow-up consultation later.
In addition, Xiaobao's treatment
has shown remarkable results.
You did well last night.
There is a project award.
What kind of project award?
Project award?
The first indemnity fund for ring.
When did you and Doctor Qin
become like this?
It's not too late to know now.
Go too far.
Even bet on
your marriage.
For me,
getting married is just
adding an extra name to the spouse column.
No matter Qin Yiyue,
Zhang Yiyue, Sun Yiyue.
It will not affect the overall situation.
I don't care.
Or you have another picture in mind
All for Xiaobao.
What are you going to do next?
The engagement banquet and wedding ceremony
will be organized
by the most professional and efficient team.
If there's no accident,
within a month,
these processes will all be completed.
Wait.
Are you serious?
Besides,
I will give her a big present first.
Don't go away.
Take a look.
My God.
Mr. He is so exaggerating.
Luxury houses, sports cars
and other bride price are too low-level.
This is to show your love in public.
Not at all.
It's so embarrassing.
If showing love would kill me,
I'd like to die right now.
God forbid.
Don't curse yourself like that.
This is clearly
the building he donated to the hospital.
He merely
gave me a plaque.
This is not a reward at all.
He clearly wants to make a fool of me.
Look over there, sister.
What "If you're doing well, I'm doing well."
After breaking up,
it has nothing to do with each other.
Isn't it, sister?
Let's go.
Hi, President He.
Hello.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the only friend of He Qiaoyan.
I'm Wen Gu.
Do you like this award?
Xiaobao.
You first go with Sister Xiao'an
and Uncle Wen to play.
I'll talk to your dad,
okay?
Let's go.
Go.
Hurry up.
President He.
Now the Internet is circulating
the fake news of our marriage.
You still do this.
Who said it is fake news?
Eh.
No one else knows.
We know that
the proposal is false.
Kissing is fake, isn't it?
Kissing is fake.
But the proposal is true.
Are you out of your mind?
We've only known each other for a few days.
Why do you propose to me?
I mean it.
Or are you afraid?
You're afraid that after getting along with me day and night,
you will fall in love with me.
I fall in love with you?
I'm Qin Yiyue.
I'll never fall in love with you.
Then, Let's have a try.
You're crazy.
Qin Yiyue.
Now everyone in Qincheng
knows that
I am your fiance.
Can you stop
saying this?
It's a pity to lose
Mr. Right of Qincheng girls.
Be careful.
It's a pity that
you are not my Mr. Right.
You are not my Miss Right either.
I am a businessman.
Xiaobao is my only
and most important client.
What does he want
I'll do whatever it takes
to give him.
Dr. Qin.
I'll get you to agree.
What's wrong with you?
Hello, is my milk tea ready?
Right away.
Hello, lady.
Only you?
Can't you see that
I am alone?
Thank you.
Thank you for coming. Take care.
Here comes the drink.
Xiaobao is also here.
Dr. Qin is really ambitious.
For the patient,
she has become a stepmother.
This kind of doctor-patient relationship
is really worth learning.
Dr. Qin never has any additional ideas.
It's a pity that
you have such a good-looking face,
but you're ugly inside.
You're right.
She is the evil queen
of the cartoon.
She's the bad guy
who fed your mommy the poisoned apple.
How can you help your mother as a little kid?
Xiaobao.
If you need anything, just tell me.
I'll do it for you.
Xiaobao, you are so great.
You can even think of this.
Oh, what?
What?
How can I didn't understand anything?
You are not competent enough.
You and we
have a little generation gap.
What's this called?
It's called stream of consciousness.
Let's go.
Stop!
It's filthy.
How to wash this?
Can't you take water by yourself?
If you want to drink water.
Where's the ring?
The ring
is at home.
Drink it.
Such a valuable thing.
I'm afraid I'll lose it.
It's better.
The 15-carat diamond ring
is the only heirloom of our He family.
It is handmade by the designers
and craftsmen of the Swedish Royal Family.
It's quite expensive.
It's really not suitable for everyday wear.
Why haven't Xiaobao and Xiao'an
come yet?
I'll take a look.
Just make a phone call.
Hello, Xiao'an.
We're in the clinic.
Where are you?
We.
We're in the bathroom
Zhou Xiao'an, where are you?
Is there any trouble?
We are in the ward area on the sixth floor.
This is very ridiculous.
He's just a kid.
Where are our clothes?
Who took our clothes away?
If someone comes later,
what should we do?
Do something.
I dress like this
is not suitable to go out.
What if I go out and get seen by my colleagues?
Don't you hate
being called "Phoenix man"?
So you should protect me
like a man.
Ziyang.
Don't get me wrong.
We're just taking a bath.
So
you must not think too much.
I'll leave you two alone.
Qin Yiyue.
These are all designed by you,
right?
Don't jump to conclusions
until things are clear.
By the way, I'll tell you
don't target Dr. Qin everywhere.
Let's go.
What's the matter?
Did something interesting happen?
Let me see.
Where's Xiaobao?
Did you teach him that again?
How dare I.
It is Xiaobao who taught me to do it.
Sister,
Are you angry?
Anyway,
Zhou Ziyang and Ye Qing
won't let me go.
It's OK for me to take another misplaced blame.
Ruowei,
How are you doing?
Did you find the ring?
You hurry up and pack up
all your valuable things
and sell them all.
Why do I have
so little money?
I'm done.
There are people
taking pictures of Sister Qin wherever we go.
Because sister Qin took away
the girls' dream lover of the whole city?
Qin Yiyue, you are famous overnight.
Ladies, is this convenient for your photographing?
Your cell phone.
And yours.
Don't go, you guys.
Keep shooting.
The temperature is high recently.
You sweat too much.
The loss of water
will increase
the viscosity of your blood.
That's why
you've become so grumpy.
Drink this glass of water.
You think
you're helping Dr. Qin.
But have you
put yourself in her shoes
and position
to think about this thing?
How do you protect her?
You still have to rely on me
to clean up your mess.
I gave you a spare key
is not for you to just
go in and out of my house.
Go back to your room.
Think about it.
What's wrong with you again?
Your high-profile marriage
made my father very stimulated.
In addition to doing everything possible
to force me to go on a blind date,
he also interfered
with my work.
Pei Jin.
I've finished the contract for the planning department,
you can take it to the reception.
Make me a cup of tea by the way.
Why didn't you answer my phone last night?
Who are you?
Where's Pei Jin?
I'm Wang Beijing.
The chairman said
from now on
I'll be your secretary.
It is not only Wang Beijing
who replaced Pei Jin.
And Li Sha replaced Lisa.
Su Daqiang replaced Su Qiang.
Wang Miao replaced Wang Miaomiao.
All the female employees around me
have been replaced by men.
My dad also gave notice
that all future employees
can only be hired with his approval.
And he made it clear that
he would never
let me have any female employees again.
What does that mean?
This means that
the next woman I hold
can only be my wife.
Only you?
Another scum.
You're not supposed
to be here.
what are you laughing at?
Am I wrong?
I'll teach you a lesson tonight.
I think you are so cute.
Therefore,
I decide to make an exception
and give you a privilege.
Why is this bar
so tasteless?
Is it because of the song
or the wine
or the decoration?
Now I see.
It's because of the boss.
You.
How about
going to my booth
for a while?
Dear,
your booth are full.
Don't go away.
I haven't got your WeChat yet.
I'm blind to marry you.
Lady,
can I buy you a drink?
What a coincidence.
Yeah, it's a coincidence.
Get out of my way.
Let me teach you.
It's not that easy
for you to get a kiss from me.
I.
Can I buy you a drink?
A glass of wine is only a warm-up.
My special cocktail
is very strong.
You'll get drunk on one drink.
My God.
You drink
like a fish.
You can't do it.
Hello.
Come on.
Please send him
to the nearest hotel.
Aren't you coming along?
I can't do it alone.
I'm also responsible for the aftermath.
What does she take me for?
She's gone too far.
Should I call mom and dad and tell them?
After telling them,
they will be very angry.
I can buy lottery tickets.
How dare I buy a lottery ticket?
Since I was a kid,
I've only won a bottle of Coke.
How dare I buy a lottery ticket?
Why am I so unlucky?
My God.
How can you climb so high?
I still owe him a huge amount of money,
so I can't break his bracelet.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected for the moment,
please redial later.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed.
I have to go there.
Baby,
listen to me.
I'm sure
I won't let your mother get into trouble.
Only when you are safe at home
can I help your mother.
Good to listen.
Brother Ning Fang,
how come it's you?
I've helped you once again.
Didn't you go abroad?
Why are you suddenly back?
You didn't even tell me.
I just came back.
However,
are you a little fatter
than when you were in college?
I didn't
get fat.
I'm just kidding.
Is this yours?
How did it fall down?
Luckily it's not broken.
It just ran out of power.
Thank you.
Is this your cat?
It's not mine.
I saved it from the tree.
I don't know if it was hurt.
My studio is nearby.
Why don't we take it to check?
Great.
Let's go.
Qin Yiyue.
Validation failed.
Input error.
Locked.
Why did she change her password?
Here we are.
It's beautiful.
Hello, Doctor Ning.
Hello.
This is my new psychological clinic.
Let's go to my office.
Okay.
Come in, please.
Are these all your cats?
Yeah.
You still like cats so much
as before.
I still remember when we were in college
you specially placed a dozen huts
for the school's stray cats,
and then fed them water and food at regular intervals.
I am very happy as a cat person.
The money I earn from this clinic
is used to rescue stray animals.
I take care of
all the stray cats around here.
Come, let me see you.
Don't be afraid.
Let me check it for you.
It's okay.
it's just a little malnourished.
It seems that
you have rescued a lot of stray animals.
You are
so professional.
Do you want to raise it?
Of course I do.
But it's too small.
I'm afraid I can't take care of it.
Or
I just leave it with you.
It's enough for me
to look at it every day when I get off work.
Yes, of course.
Go inside.
You come to my place
without informing me.
You are too polite, right?
In fact,
the first thing I want to do after I return to China
is to see you.
I heard about you and Ziyang.
It's all over.
Qin Yiyue
is always out of touch.
The cost of communication is too high.
After joining the company,
this will definitely be a major hidden problem.
It can't be like this.
In the formal cooperation contract,
the relevant binding terms
must be added.
So you're being subjected
to cyber violence.
It's not really
cyber violence.
There are just some internet trolls
who have nothing better to do
but go to verbal attacks on others.
You know
when I see myself
on the hot search,
I'm really bummed out.
This is simply very irritating.
How unlucky
do you think I am.
First it was Zhou Ziyang,
and later it was He Qiaoyan.
You say
why I am surrounded by oddballs?
I think you should
talk to He Qiaoyan
about your situation.
I can't make it clear to him.
He is a conceited and
presumptuous eccentric.
I couldn't talk to him.
She even spoke ill of her fiance
to other men.
Or I'll help you make it clear to him.
President He.
What are you doing here?
Where is the bracelet?
It's here.
It needs to be worn all the time
for sample testing.
The wearer
must be serious, professional
and responsible.
Why do I must wear it when you tell me to?
Do you have anything else to do?
If nothing else, you can leave now.
Who is this?
This is my...
Why should I tell you?
You are Mr. He.
Hello, my name is Ning Fang.
I am Yiyue's senior brother.
Hello.
Thank you for bringing my fiancee back.
Pay attention to your image.
You're Xiaobao's mom.
You can't get too close
to other people.
I told you
I will not marry you.
Pay attention to your own image.
I won't say it again.
Oh, you.
You see.
He is such a conceited and
presumptuous eccentric.
You can't get too close
to other people.
Why is the heart suddenly tight?
It must be because
the change in adrenaline
caused a disruption of my cardiac sympathetic nerves
and cardiac vagus nerves.
That's why the heart suffers from
temporary hypoxic pain.
That's right.
It will be fine
after some rest.
You know
when I see myself
on the hot search,
I'm really bummed out.
This is simply very irritating.
President He.
You asked me to look up
articles about Dr. Qin on the Internet.
I've already found out.
What's the result?
On the whole,
all are
less friendly articles.
Some say Dr. Qin
went to great lengths to seduce you.
Some say Dr. Qin is ugly.
Even.
Continue.
It is even said that Dr. Qin
relied on you
to become a doctor at Yade Hospital.
Notify the public relations department,
so that they can report to the relevant departments
in the name of me, the person concerned.
Notify Legal Department
to prepare for litigation.
Yes, I'll do it right away.
She is not outstanding
but married to He Qiaoyan.
Why remove it
just after it was installed?
I don't know.
Good news.
Why is it removed?
It's better to removed it.
It's a lot easier for me.
What's the good news?
Those articles that spread rumors about you on the Internet
disappeared overnight.
You see.
Does that woman
really rely on the man to get the job?
Now the plaque is removed.
I guess
she is found to be what she really was.
My wife graduated from
the best medical school in the country.
While in university,
she earned a full scholarship
and a dual bachelor's degree.
She has won national awards
for her research on three topics.
Two of her papers published in international journals.
She is the youngest attending physician
in the hospital.
She ranks first for three years
in the number of patients she has treated.
She has achieved zero errors and zero absences.
In addition, my wife
is called that woman.
She has a name,
Qin Yiyue.
From this point of view,
it is not that she depends on me,
but that I am fortunate enough to be able to depend on her.
He is the best among all the CEOs in the novels.
So you also deal with
the articles on the Internet.
It was
my wrong way of dealing with it
that brought you such troubles.
I formally apologize to you.
You apologize to me?
You're
the first one
to make me apologize.
You should be proud.
Isn't it normal to apologize
for doing something wrong?
I see, Mr. He.
You finally realize that
it's impossible
to marry me.
You finally get it.
Well,
I'll give you a bow.
Thank you.
You're mistaken.
I don't give up
my determination to marry you.
Why don't you
make sense?
What is your reason
for refusing to
marry me?
Nonsense.
We have to be cautious
for marriage.
At least have a dating before getting married.
So you want to
have a date with me first.
Of course not.
I mean
We don't know each other very well.
We are
supposed to keep distance.
But you have been
in a serious relationship with Zhou Ziyang for several years,
Have you got any result?
You are still not married.
It's none of your business.
While in university,
she earned a full scholarship
and a dual bachelor's degree.
She has won national awards
for her research on three topics.
Two of her papers published in international journals.
In addition, she is the youngest attending physician
in the hospital.
She ranks first for three years
in the number of patients she has treated.
She has achieved zero errors and zero absences.
In addition,
my wife
is not called that woman.
She has a name,
Qin Yiyue.
From this point of view,
it is not that she depends on me,
but that I am fortunate enough to be able to depend on her.
blah, blah, blah.
He's a good talker.
Why do I think of him?
Look for the ring.
I'm coming.
Mom, dad.
Why are you here?
Pretty good.
Look at these
messy socks.
You leave things everywhere.
Do you have a lot of money?
You can't put plants in the bedroom.
It can absorb oxygen.
It's a succulent.
Succulent?
Why don't you wear socks?
How many times have I told you
that girls' feet can't be cold.
It can't be cold.
Why let me say it again?
Look at the hair all over the floor.
You stayed up late again, right?
Are you playing games on your phone?
You deserve your hairline.
Look how high your hairline is.
Your hairline is here.
You're like the people of the Qing Dynasty.
I inherited you.
You inherited me?
Why don't you inherit something good?
By the way, what's on the bed?
Eating snacks in bed again, right?
You haven't changed since you were a kid.
All right.
We're here to see our daughter.
You've become
an inspector.
Exactly.
It's still my dad.
daddy,
You've come
a long way.
Are you hungry?
How about I
make noodles for you?
Come on.
Don't go anywhere.
If we don't come,
even when your baby is born,
we still know nothing.
Yes.
Call that man for me.
which man?
Zhou Ziyang.
Why do you mention Zhou Ziyang now?
It should be He Qiao...
He Qiaofu.
It's not He Qiaofu.
He Qiaochen.
It's not He Qiaochen.
It's
Yan.
It's Yan from Yanhui.
Yes, He Qiaohui.
He Qiaoyan.
Aren't you talking about Yanhui?
All right.
It doesn't matter
whether it's He Qiaohui or He Qiaoyan.
We got the news
of my daughter's engagement
from the WeChat Subscription.
Do you know how we feel?
Even the ladies
who danced on the square with us
all congratulated me
on my promotion to the top class.
Don't you want
to be congratulated?
By the way,
Speaking of WeChat.
I haven't blacklisted
Zhou Ziyang yet.
I'm going to blacklist him now.
Yes, blacklist him now.
I blacklist him.
Dear daughter,
are you
pregnant?
I'm not pregnant.
Really not.
I'm crazy.
Dear daughter,
this man
must be an
idle dandy.
He thinks our daughter is inexperienced.
He tried every means
to attract her.
He proposed
and gave a building as a gift.
We are simple people.
Let's not compare with others.
I always force you to get married.
But,
If you marry for the sake of marriage,
you won't be happy.
You'll lose out later.
Are you clear about that?
Your mother is right.
Even though
others know some of the wrong things
we do.
But don't worry,
Your mon and I are going to give you...
Stop.
Listen to me.
I and He Qiaohui.
He Qiaoyan.
I and He Qiaoyan.
Our marriage is fake.
One day.
All in all,
He Qiaoyan
is just to help me out
and make Zhou Ziyang angry.
See?
False?
False.
But.
There is no but.
If.
There is no if.
Tonight,
I'll sleep on the sofa
and you two will sleep in my bedroom.
The meeting is over.
Wait.
Don't break up the meeting.
I just saw
a storage room over there.
You clean it up.
I can live there with your father.
Lao Qin,
let's
stay more days
with our daughter.
No problem.
I...
That's it.
Yes.
You...
Stop talking. That's it.
Help clean up.
Yeah.
Oh, my god!
I'll clean up the room.
All right.