Unforgettable Love
EP01
Scientific experiments,
search engines,
business growth,
and population migration
all depend on
the scientific analysis of data.
Heshi Group
has adopted the most advanced
artificial intelligence data analysis system.
It can not only protect the
privacy that customers are most worried about,
but also ensure the
scientificalness of the statistics.
So that it can better serve the society.
The data service of Heshi Group
will open the intelligent world that
analyzes every detail of your life.
OK, here's the free questioning time.
Mr. He,
there's a rumor on the internet that
you have been secretly married
and
had a son.
How do you explain that
to the reporters?
Please pay attention to your wording.
My son has his name, registered permanent residence
and legal guardian.
Please remove the word "secretly".
Bullshit,
it's not only about RMB 300,000 yuan.
I know.
You must be mad at me for
taking Ziyang away.
RMB 500,000 yuan.
I paid his rent,
the down payment for the car,
and the agency fee for studying abroad.
I wrote most of the
winning papers.
I even gave him the place to
study abroad.
Furthermore,
This person is not the one you take away,
but the garbage and waste
I don't want.
Qin Yiyue.
Thank you
for solving the problem for me.
Sister,
your recycling habits
really impressed me.
The rest RMB 200,000 yuan
is my red envelope
for you.
My pleasure.
By the way,
wish the two of you get old together.
That's good for the people.
Mr. He,
your father is in a meeting
so he can't return now.
Mr. He, be careful.
This, this,
this is your father's computer!
Mr. He,
Could you please come down?
It's too dangerous for you to stand on it.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Mr. He, I'll call up right away,
Right away, right away.
He Weifei, get down.
Mr. He, here you are at last.
Dad told you before
that I was working.
Of course I know
your three principles.
If Xiaobao gets angry, I have to apologize.
If Xiaobao needs me, I have to show up.
If Xiaobao wants something, he can have it.
But not now.
Call the doctor.
Mr. He, I was in such a hurry that
I forgot to tell you that
Dr. Kozak
had resigned
10 minutes ago.
He said Xiaobao
could let him have a heart attack at any time.
So he said
life is more important than money.
Call another doctor.
We've been looking for a doctor.
On average, one resigns every 3 days.
Dr. Kozak
is the longest serving doctor.
At least he persisted for ten days.
That's not what I want to hear.
Figure it out.
Mr. He,
Mr. Xu of R&D department
is still waiting for you for a meeting.
In addition,
there is a live broadcast
before the awards ceremony in the evening.
We have to go.
He Weifei, listen to me.
I never bluff.
If you want to make a scene,
you can tear down the office.
My time is for work,
not for you.
Mr. He, what about Xiaobao?
I can't hold him.
If I take care of him,
maybe the next one to jump
is me.
Prepare a car for Xiaobao.
That's great!
Eat something and don't drink all the time.
Apart from appearance,
there is no difference in function
from the previous generation.
What's really special about it
is that we've created
Catch Love application.
It can record
the heartbeat of every date.
It is more in line with young people's
intuitive feelings for love.
What about the market survey data?
Our main customers of the second generation
are young people
under the age of 35.
As for female consumers,
84 percent from
14 to 40 years old
are particularly interested.
84 percent
Where is the sample?
Put it on for me.
Members of R & D department,
please continue to advance your work.
In addition,
I'll get involved in the testing phase.
Are you tired?
The protest is of no avail.
I should never
have made these cards for you.
Continue.
You gotta be kidding me!
Others lovelorn people
would rather cry and lose weight.
But you are different.
You eat, drink and dance.
The appearance of love is just
a physical phenomenon
because the brain receives chemical stimulations
that occur in order to reproduce.
After two months,
the oxytocin,
dopamine,
and norepinephrine
have completely clear out of your body
and you will be fine.
Zhou Ziyang
won the Heshi Group's
Outstanding Youth Award.
The prize will be presented at
Qincheng Hotel at 20:30 tonight.
Why did he win the prize?
Is it because he's a first-class cheating artist?
The news says
it is the Tesn's academic research achievements.
The 90 percent of that paper
was my work.
The first author is not you.
Wow, that's going too far.
Grabbing your credit and fame.
He is so shameless.
Ruowei, you go back first.
I have one more thing to do.
Where are you going?
Get even with him.
He is so handsome.
The most handsome man in Qincheng
and won't take a rebuttal.
My husband! Please look at me!
Mr. He, I want to be your girlfriend.
Is this the live interface?
Yes.
This is
our pre-event
live stream.
You have come to the studio.
I had learned about live streaming before,
but I haven't studied it carefully.
Actually, it's easy.
This is
the number of people live online.
And then you see these flowers
and airplanes
are the gifts.
That's the money they spend for you.
Mr. He,
if you don't want to accept it.
It's kind of interesting.
It turns real-time interaction
into data and flow.
Again...
Let's get started.
You guys get out.
This is
an interactive live broadcast,
and for a while
there will be a lucky draw
and interactive Q & A.
I'm going to start looking at
the data
and flow on this platform.
Let's get out of here,
there seems to be some technical problems.
The reception is very unstable,
so we may have to change a room.
Xiaobao,
Kiddy,
Why are you here alone?
Where are you going?
What a lovely child!
Where are your parents?
Kiddy, you can't touch that.
Don't run away, kiddy.
Kiddy,
you've trampled this display card.
Could you give me the sticky notes?
I can take you to eat delicious food.
Kiddy,
Look at the display card you've trampled on.
Could you give me the sticky notes?
Call security. There's something wrong in the lobby.
I didn't notice that.
We've been focusing on the live broadcast.
This is the eighth floor.
There are three suites on this floor.
Only mine has staff.
It won't be more than
five minutes,
so he is not far away.
Are you OK, kiddy?
Didn't hurt you, did you?
It is OK.
It's OK, kiddy.
Don't worry, I am here.
You go to the first floor
and I'll go to the third floor.
Miss Zhong, go back to the room.
By the way, inform the medical staff.
Will Xiaobao suffer something?
Be prepared against danger.
It's too strange for him here.
His situation is very special.
I'll go back and wait.
Kiddy, please look at me.
It's all right.
Let me guess.
Your name is Xiaobao,
right?
OK, don't talk if you don't want to.
Well, let me ask you questions.
You can nod,
or shake your head,
OK?
"Stay away from me"
Is that what you want to say to everyone?
"I'm sorry"
Let me guess again.
means that you're trying to tell us
you didn't mean to
cause this mess,
right?
Xiaobao is really a
polite child.
Ok, let me look at it.
"thank you"
Can I have this card?
So now
can you tell me in whisper
why you
want it?
"dad"
Are you angry with your dad?
Don't be afraid.
They're not here to arrest you.
They're just
the guardian of the poster.
So,
is your father in this hotel?
I give you a small gift
in exchange.
Shall we return this poster
to these
two staff members?
The handkerchief and the little pumpkin
are all my favorite
presents.
Now I give them to you.
Xiaobao, you are so good.
It's good that Xiaobao is fine.
Who are you?
I'm his father's secretary.
You should tell his father
to take good care of his child.
Miss, who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
Kiddy,
I have something important to do.
I'm going to go.
Bye-bye.
I just had a fall,
why is my head dizzy?
Xiaobao,
Zhou Ziyang, you jerk!
Zhou Ziyang,
jerk!
You big jerk!
Jerk!
I've been waiting for you for three years.
Is that what you've been doing to me
for the three years?
The Tesn's paper is that
I worked around the clock,
with jet lag,
and spent most of the year writing for you.
From data analysis to topic selection,
how much did you
contribute to this paper,
and how much have you done to me?
Miss, you have mistaken me for the wrong person.
I am like
a piece of rag to you.
Use me when you need me
and leave me
alone when you don't.
And,
I tell you
that the study of medicine is sacred,
and I have enough evidence
to prove that
the first signature of that paper does not belong to you.
I'm going to
make it all public.
If only the boss Mr. He
had any sense,
he would withdraw the award.
He will
The boss Mr. He is very wise.
Who are you?
I should have
asked you that question.
Help me untie it.
Why me?
I...
Do it yourself.
Hurry up.
Please be gentle.
It's so hot.
There's a reason Mr. He
let us leave.
Host,
can we turn this off now?
Wait a minute!
What do you want to do?
Can't you see that?
I'm going to bring this tie
to the stage
later.
Isn't that solved?
So much nonsense.
And... I'm sorry
If you get hurt,
I'll take the blame.
I don't need it.
That's the best.
It's baffling.
Thank you
for coming to my celebration party.
Congratulations!
Thank you,
we are here to learn.
Thank you.
Ziyang, the party is about to begin.
We...
Now let's welcome
Mr. He Qiaoyan,
CEO of Heshi Group,
to announce
the next winner.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner of outstanding young people
in medicine 2020 is...
Tesn's paper is that
I worked around the clock,
with jet lag,
and spent most of the year writing for you.
And,
I tell you
that the study of medicine is sacred,
and I have enough evidence
to prove that
the first signature of that paper does not belong to you.
No one.
What's going on?
What happened?
Doesn't it belong to Ziyang?
Mr. He
This is the new doctors to be chosen
for Xiaobao.
Please have a look.
I don't know who's left to choose.
I'm going to bring this tie
to the stage
later.
Isn't that solved?
So much nonsense.
And... I'm sorry
If you get hurt,
I will take the blame.
This woman
turns out to be a
child psychologist.
He Weifei!
You should have been down
43 minutes ago.
You should have fallen asleep
28 minutes ago.
Go to sleep.
Your IQ
is far beyond the children of your age.
I'm not going to say
the same thing twice.
Good night.
Come back.
Come back
Don't go.
What are you doing here?
Dude, you're awesome.
Put your feet down.
Who is that girl?
How come I haven't seen her before?
You two are so close to each other,
and I didn't see
any discomfort with you.
Tell me the truth,
where's the girl from?
Is she from your company,
or a hospital,
or someone's daughter?
A mysterious woman.
It's all happened,
and you are still protecting her.
What nonsense are you talking about this morning?
Didn't anyone tell you?
See it.
Please be gentle.
Over there.
Congratulations, Mr. He,
happy to get hot search again.
It is the sixth time this year.
Twice more than me.
As Qingcheng’s famous
handsome boy,
the position of the top stream is not guaranteed.
I'm losing some exposure here.
Has she been exposed?
No one knows who she is.
Are you worried about her?
I'm afraid that this woman
would get me into trouble.
No,
I will ask the data department to
sort out public opinion report in time.
The disturbance may affect our group,
so we need to control it in time.
Who is that woman?
Trash.
How can you
describe a girl like that?
I mean
her files are in the trash can.
You like this type.
You've been in my room
for four minutes and 35 seconds.
You are seriously affecting
my schedule for today.
In addition,
That means
I couldn’t stagger the morning rush hour,
There will be
two more unnecessary traffic lights
and a congested section.
The arrival time
will also be seven minutes and 35 seconds
later than the expectation.
Company...
Okay, okay,
I got it.
I'm leaving now.
Qin Yiyue.
Gee, the dancing queen is awake.
I drank too much yesterday.
Could you please
throw trash away on the spot
after you finish picking it up?
Trash left for a long time will affect your mood.
Got it.
Look at your state.
Take the day off.
No!
I have a very important patient today.
You're dizzy right now.
Which patient doesn't matter to you?
Let another doctor
take your place.
You just take a day off.
Otherwise,
if your
these two big black circles
let the children see,
all have to call you auntie.
Auntie?
I am little sister.
The people in the hospital call me little sister.
Auntie Qin,
you had a great time
last night.
Look at it.
A mysterious woman
dating with Mr. He in the private space.
The prospective mother of Mr. He's son appeared.
What the hell!
Isn't that me?
He was
an hour and a half behind his
normal bedtime.
It's abnormal.
36 degrees.
It's normal.
Room temperature is normal at 26 degrees.
Three meals a day
is okay
and normal.
What's the matter, Xiaobao?
What's the matter, Mrs. Liu?
What wrong with you, Xiaobao?
Is this one?
Mr. He,
when I was doing the laundry this morning,
I saw it in the dirty clothes basket,
so I just washed it.
Mrs. Liu,
Where did this handkerchief come from?
I don't know.
I just saw it yesterday.
It's not ours.
You can go about your business.
Miss Zhong,
please go to Yade hospital and register
at the hospital for Xiaobao.
And chose child psychology department.
Mr. He,
don't worry,
Dr. Hu will take care of Xiaobao.
The building you donated to the hospital
has been completed.
We're planning to
hold a completion ceremony these days.
You are usually busy with your work.
You're just coming here today.
Why don't you have a look
and give me some advice.
Ok.
After a while,
please bring me the
re-inspection result of
Guoguo and Xiaobing.
And,
it's time for Niuniu to come for a follow-up visit today.
Don't forget to contact her.
Sister,
you really love children.
I'll give the case to Director Huang
and then show you the results later.
Xiaobao, Xiaobao.
Take it easy!
Xiaobao, Xiaobao,
Xiaobao,
Take it easy!
How beautiful the color of the car is!
Isn't it?
Look,
Three, two, one.
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid.
Xiaobao,
I'll call Mr. He right now.
I'll call your dad now,
OK?
Xiaobao, don't be afraid.
Take it easy.
Excuse me.
Xiaobao, don't be afraid.
Dr. Hu, what's the matter with this child?
He was fine just now.
Why is he...
Xiaobao, don't be afraid.
Kiddy,
If I guess right,
your name is
Xiaobao,
right?
It seems
Xiaobao
doesn't like these cars,
does it?
All right, no more for you,
I will take you
to a more fun place.
OK?
Come
"I want to be friends with you"
Seven words, right?
OK, I'll take it.
My name is Guoguo.
What's your name?
You are so cold.
Boys shouldn't be shy.
If you
want more toys,
I'll tell you,
no problem.
Considering you
are new here.
Let's play together, little boy!
As long as you like,
you can play with
all the toys here.
Be my good friend!
You're talking nonsense.
Did you
watch a romance with grandma again?
Dr. Qin, here you are at last!
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
Come and sit here.
Here.
Xiaobao,
I bought you water.
Here.
Stop!
If you want to play with him,
you have to let me agree.
Sit down.
Well,
let's discuss,
you go to that room first
and hide for me.
I'll find you later.
OK?
Three, two, one, run!
I declare
that you are mine
from now on.
This is a token
of our agreement.
You have one.
I have one.
Let's hook the pinkie finger
and make a promise.