[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 34]
How's it going with finding the expert?
This person is famous
in the field of neurosurgery in the United States.
She is a visiting professor at Lingnan University and
currently returning home for vacation.
We are trying to get in touch with her.
OK, you go first.
[International Reporting Hall]
Hu Yang.
Thank you for not forgetting me.
[International Reporting Hall]
We are always friends.
Friends are not worth your trip.
I'm here to beg you.
Professor Emir.
It looks like I'm really old.
I thought you would think of me
as Emil's student or assistant
to misunderstand!
Come on, let's talk at my place.
I am back, Gao Liangmi.
You woke up?
I feel
I have not seen you for a long time.
Not like that.
Look,
Look what I brought you.
[Report for marriage application]
It's too late to take a photo of us
so I used our photo
at ZhangMu Railway Station
and retouched it.
If you cut off mule Gu,
this picture would lose its essence.
In fact, I felt bad about it.
But it's our marriage,
he must disappear.
It's not good of you to do that.
So stubborn. In fact, you are very delighted, aren't you?
Come on.
Sign here.
Here.
You made a mistake.
It's what I want to write.
Gao Liang.
Gao Liang, what's wrong with you？Gao Liang.
[Love you, Jiang Nanzheng]
I always remember Gu Yiye in those days.
He is proud, firm,
confident and decisive.
For career and dream,
he can cut love without hesitation.
But what about you today?
You are flustered and helpless.
Gu Yiye,
You made me disappointed.
It doesn't matter.
Hu Yang.
It matters.
Do you still care about
the past thing?
Gu Yiye,
do you know how can I be
a good doctor?
Hu Yang,
in fact, the reason why I come here today...
Listen to me first.
Being a good doctor
is like being a good soldier.
There are two ways.
One is reading papers.
Another is operating.
Guess which kind I am?
Operating.
Do you really don't know me
or lose your analytic ability?
Of course I am the one who reads papers,
just same as you.
The reason why I can stand here today
is that in the past over ten years,
I don't have a day off
and I have never been lazy.
I have turned myself into a robot.
Everyday,
I'm fighting the weakness of my human nature
and I have never defeated.
But do you know
how hard am I by doing this?
Thousands of days and nights.
If your battle field is a training ground,
my battle field is the laboratory
and operating table.
Going to the Middle East and West Africa is nothing.
That's what I must do
to make up for my shortcomings,
just like people eat lunch when they are hungry.
Compared with
the long and boring road itself,
hardship and danger are not worth mentioning.
Instead, they are an interesting mediation.
Sit down.
Since we parted,
Gu Yiye, who was saluting in military uniform,
has always been on my mind.
That proud, firm
confident and decisive Gu Yiye
supported me in my most difficult time.
Before coming,
there was a question
confusing me specially.
When I knew that Professor Emir
was a young ethnic Chinese woman,
I've been hesitating about
shall I salute her?
After all, this is
my greatest sincerity.
But I thought she was a foreigner
and afraid that she would be overwhelmed.
But now I think
you deserve it.
This is not only because of my own debt,
it also has nothing to do with my plea today.
It's because of you, Hu Yang,
as a Chinese descendant,
who struggles and persists overseas who
deserves it.
How can you...
You know I can't stand this the most.
You are still handsome
after over ten years.
I think I can understand now
why did you refuse to operate for Gao Liang.
I have requirements for my career,
just like you.
I just said that,
in the past over ten years
I haven't
treated any surgery hastily.
And Gao Liang's situation today
is like a gamble for me.
I am a scientist
and I don't gamble.
In fact, there are times when I'm not pure.
When I saw you just now
I couldn't help asking myself
if the wounded person is you,
would I do it?
What's the answer?
I will not hesitate.
But that's it.
Except Gu Yiye,
no one in the world
can make me break my principles.
It shows that you are sincere to catch up here.
Come on, comrade officer.
Excuse me, professor.
The speech will begin soon.
Everyone is waiting.
Sure. Wait a minute.
I've met Gu Yiye.
I know your concerns.
I understand
how much do you value your career.
As far as I know,
you are the expert in the field of information.
You should understand that this reputation
contains our enthusiasm and ratification
of our own life.
Of course,
it also contains values.
You are right.
Top experts in any industry
are constantly making self breakthroughs.
Adventure is inevitable.
I am a scientist.
I don't gamble.
You have five minutes left.
We are soldiers.
Sometimes in front of reason,
another occupation is very similar to us.
It's Doctor.
It makes sense.
But you still haven't convinced me.
Just a hint.
A female scientist
can convince better
than a female soldier.
You can just regard me as an
unqualified scientist, Professor.
More than 20 years ago,
my PE teacher once told me
an old Greek Olympic motto.
I want to use it as the last word of today.
Don't pursue victory.
Just pursue courage to move forward.
Because from an indomitable struggle,
you will welcome honor for yourself.
But more importantly,
you will welcome glory
for all mankind.
Time is up.
Wish your academic speech
can win real applause.
[Serving the people by Mao Zedong]
[Professional Report]
I know
Gao Liang is in the hospital now.
Are you in a hurry, like Jiang Nanzheng,
aren't you?
Your brain is stimulated.
I forgive you.
Go back.
I know you would tear it.
I also prepared another copy.
Beause of Huang Tianwei event,
the division commander ordered you to be suspended.
But the group's latest survey report on you
has been filed.
Just wait.
Yiye,
letting soldiers like you go
is tantamount to letting soldiers like me go.
For the army,
It's the square of the crime.
You know I won't agree.
Colonel.
I know what do you mean,
and the meaning of the division commander is also very clear.
I, Gu Yiye,
as Deputy Secretary of the Party committee of the first battalion of red,
also as the military commander,
should take
the main responsibility for this event.
It must be taken by me.
Xiu,
I only want to ask you
who wronged you?
How can they do this to you?
Don't they know
you are the brightest star
in the army?
How can they treat you like this?
Xiu, listen to me.
If I'm really the one you said,
the brightest star.
Where am I going,
I am the brightest.
I promise.
What should we do?
Didn't you say
I am the brightest star?
You are right.
There is a military magazine
who checked my information
and looked for me.
They want to hire me.
Won't you
try again
and talk to the chief?
Xiu,
I have made up my mind.
Besides that, magazine presented a house to me
in order to keep me.
More than 80 square meters.
It's much bigger than here
and better than here.
Look,
our family
don't have to be squeezed in this small house anymore.
I like to be squeezed here.
I'd rather be squeezed here
than letting you take off this military uniform.
Works in the division,
I have made it.
With one month left, we can go through the formalities.
No hesitation.
Well, Xiu.
Tomorrow,
you pack up
and see what can we leave to others
in this house.
This table,
leave it to the deputy battalion commander.
That wardrobe,
leave it to the instructor.
We will buy a new one.
Buy a new one.
I don't want to.
No.
I can't leave it.
This is our home.
Give me a reason.
What?
Give me one reason to accept this operation.
Your reason.
He is my comrade.
You have hundreds of comrades.
He is not an ordinary comrade.
He is my blood brother.
He is my brother
who escaped from the
the blood line of war with me.
I have a last request.
I will do it if you promise me.
As long as I can do it,
just say.
Save yourself.
You know what I mean.
Whether you go or not,
save yourself.
This time I see you,
you look terrible.
This shouldn't be that
Gu Yiye who I haven't seen
in over ten years.
You can't go on like this.
I didn't want to
betray the Gu Yiye in my heart in the first place.
So I become who I am today.
I also don't want the Gu Yiye today
disappoint him before.
I promise you.
Go home after the operation.
Uncle Gu's research major has been revoked.
He has been studying for more than 30 years.
It is like another son to him.
He's as sad as you are now.
Thank you.
Come on.
♫ When you were gone ♫
♫ The sunshine was gone ♫
[Silence]
♫ The wind from mountain has blew ♫
♫ the heat of my heart away ♫
[Operating Room]
♫ When you fell ♫
♫the whole world was gone ♫
♫ It scattered on the ground ♫
♫ my persistence ♫
♫ I remember the things you left ♫
[Examination Room]
♫ my oath and legend ♫
♫ also the red flames in my eyes ♫
♫ Do you still remember ♫
♫ timidity fell just like a shooting star ♫
♫ tremble was lonely just like sea wave ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
Nanzheng.
Happy birthday.
♫ the river we crossed carrying each other♫
I love you.
Silly, I love you, too.
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ and the song we shouted in tears ♫
I love you more.
I love you most. I love Gao Liang most.
[Operating Room]
Salute.
♫ Do you still remember ♫
♫ timidity fell just like a shooting star ♫
♫ tremble was lonely just like sea wave ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫♫ the river we crossed carrying each other♫
♫ and the song we shouted in tears ♫
♫We are together ♫
♫ We are never apart ♫
[Operating Room]
The operation was successful.
I have never seen such a magical knife.
Broken bones have corrected.
Nervous system is intact.
[Silence Operation Room]
[Intensive Care Unit, Inpatient Area]
[Great internationalist fighter, Bethune]
Do you know that
who is Emir?
Who?
The girl in the era of Zhazi Company.
Now she is a returnee.
Professor Hu Yang,
you two are bounded by fate.
These years passed,
you two
are there again after diamonds and rust.
Game over.
What's wrong?
Hu Yang
hates Gu Yiye that much.
She definitely want to
put a bomb in my body.
Yes. She did.
And she said
she would bomb you
in front of you.
All right.
I have nothing to fear.
Give me a quick death.
Are you really not afraid?
Professor.
Hu Yang.
Thanks to your skills.
Otherwise, how can Gao Liang
be like this?
Now it seems that
the effect of broken bone correction is good.
Compression of nerves and blood vessels
have also be relieved.
That's great.
Is she
bringing a patient back to life
and beautiful with kindness?
Beautiful Professor Emir,
Thank you so much.
After I recover totally,
I will worship you, the best doctor.
Thanks. Don't do that.
I just want to see
the person who don't leave nor give up on you.
This is Jiang Nanzheng,
my girlfriend.
I know.
Can I
talk to you alone?
Hu Yang,
is it about Gao Liang's illness?
I want to talk to the patient's family alone.
She is not yet.
Yiye,
you have no right to know.
She is the immediate family member.
Things about Gao Liang,
Nan Zheng and I can decide for him.
Just say it.
One of you pretend to attack, another strongly attack to
persuade me jointly.
Is it premeditated?
No.
What we have is just sincerity,
Simple and direct.
Next, I'm telling the truth.
Please be prepared.
Especially you.
There was nothing wrong during the operation,
but it doesn't mean everything is fine.
For such patients,
the most difficult stage has just begun.
The most difficult stage?
Rehabilitation training.
His nervous system is damaged.
The degree of damage needs time to be verified.
It doesn't matter.
As long as he is recovering,
just getting better is good.
Legally,
are you his wife?
She always wanted to be his wife.
Do you must marry him?
Yes.
If he can never stand,
will you insist on it?
What do you mean?
Two weeks have passed.
The motor nerves of his lower limbs
has rarely no reaction on
external stimulation.
It can be concluded that
the injury this time has caused a
damage to his spinal nerve
which is beyond our judgment.
But doesn't rehabilitation treatment
just start?
Is it too early to make a final decision?
Rehabilitation treatment will have a certain effect.
But for organic damage,
the effect is extremely limited after all.
As long as it works,
even a little,
I will try.
But if efforts
are in vain after many years?
for example, ten years,
twenty years
or a lifetime.
So I advise you
onsider it carefully.
Nanzheng,
don't listen to her.
She is scaring you.
In the past, Gao Liang
teased her.
She is taking a revenge.
Don't take it to heart.
I forgive you, Gu Yiye.
Such a lie
just touched me a little.
It is very kind.
Hu Yang,
do you have to do this?
I am a doctor.
I am responsible for everything I say.
I like the sentence you gave me.
Don't pursue victory.
Just pursue the courage to move forward.
if you really believe this sentence,
I shouldn't worry about you.
But as a woman,
I still can't help reminding you that
looking for hope in despair
can be very hard
and very difficult.
Thank you.
I will insist.
Cheer up as soon as possible.
As a doctor, I treat the body rather than the heart.
I can only do this for you.
Go and see uncle Gu.
I'll see her off.
You're back.
Come on.
Eat some noodles with soup.
It's hot, be careful.
I have told the deputy battalion commander.
The table will be sent later.
All that should be boxed are boxed.
Xiu,
where are my uniforms?
They have been boxed.
Others
have been managed
or been
given away.
Where are my uniforms?
Here.
These are more than 100 pairs of insoles which made
by Jiagui's mom,
especially for our team.
Our mom
is not in good condition
so she can't see you in person.
She asked me to bring you two pairs.
Don't you know
soldiers in the team
are scrambling for these insoles,do you?
I told them
this
is made by hero's mom.
If you want it,
exchange with your grades.
Well,
these guys are very competitive.
Their performances are better and better.
They also got the
red flag of training pacesetter
again.
That's great.
Thank our mom for me.
But please take these back.
Deliver them to other comrades.
I can't use them here either.
Niu,
I don't know how long I've been lying down.
I almost forget
what is our army like.
There isn't a wake-up song
nor queue song.
Singing is not required before meal.
I just need to lie down.
Nobody governs me.
I used to run a 10 kilometers cross-country
without breathing heavily.
Now,
I can hardly hear myself panting.
But I have something new
to tell you.
Do you know
Glycerine Enema?
After using it,
you can't control yourself.
Look at me now,
look,
my pants,
look here,
a pile of
adult diapers.
That's not enough.
A layer of diaper must be put under it.
Lower,
a layer of plastic cloth must be padded.
Because I'm afraid of wetting the bed.
When you're here,
I can't even pour your water.
Do you know that time
Nanzheng came,
changed my clothes
and wiped my body..
Do you know how I felt in my heart?
Niu,
I am a soldier.
I have been a soldier all my life.
Now I can only lie on this damn bed.
I can do nothing.
How long do I need to lie down?
When,
Until when?
A lifetime?
Can I ask her to serve me all my life?
Niu,
I am telling you,
if you are free
later,
go back and pay attention to training,
especially new soldiers.
Don't come to see me
to waste time.
Gao,
I know
you hate to part with,
hate to part with military uniform.
Niu,
I'm fine.
I just feel wronged staying here.
I want to go back to the army.
I don't want to stay in this bed.
I know.
I want to hear those queue slogans.
OK.
Fine.
I also heard that
mule Gu
was cashiered.
Come on,
open your mouth.
You can't be dehydrated, come on.
Bro.
I am broken.
This is not what I want.
I can't walk,
I can't run.
I can't feel about my legs.
I have lost the most basic ability to live.
I feel death is better than living like this.
What makes me worse
is witnessing my favorite girl
giving up her life
and living with me in such a terrible condition.
[Ward]
Go out.
What's wrong?
He should do hyperbaric oxygen
but he just doesn't cooperate.
Do for what?
It's been more than a month.
I still don't know where my legs are.
Gao Liang,
hyperbaric oxygen is helpful
for your nervous system's recovery.
Help? What help?
I have done so many times.
It's like punishment every time.
disability is still a disability.
I won't do it.
Go out.
Go out!
Comrade,
so sorry.
He is in a bad mood today.
Or I will call you later.
Thanks.
Gao Liang, why don't you cooperate with the treatment?
I am telling you,
I've had enough this month.
I have to say it today.
Gu Yiye,
get her out of here.
I don't want to see your face
in front of me every day.
It makes me annoyed
and angry.
I can't breathe.
You make me unable to concentrate on recovery,
do you understand?
Why are you looking at me?
Don't you think you're redundant here?
Don't you think you are embarrassing me?
Go out!
Go!
Gao Liang,
are you crazy?
I'll be crazy if she is still here.
Get her out.
Nanzheng.
Gao Liang,
why do you speak like that to Nanzheng?
What?
Do you think you are paralyzed
so the whole world owes you, don't you?
Do you know that
in order to make you wake up, Nanzheng sit
with you and talked to you everyday,
and ran out to find a place to cry
every night?
Then she cleaned herself,
came back and cared you with smile.
For you,
she begged everywhere
to find an
expert who can do surgery for you.
For you,
she quarreled with others
to acquire marriage procedures.
For you,
she gave up
the opportunity to get a PhD.
She gave up herself
just for...
For one day,
you can stand up.
That's why
I hate myself.
She shouldn't bear these.
Right?
Why should she bear these?
The more she does,
the more I hate myself.
It is all because of my useless legs,
useless legs.
She did everything because she loves you.
I don't need it.
Both of you know I can't stand up.
You guys lied to me together.
Gao Liang, I apologize to you.
I shouldn't have kept it from you.
From today,
I promise you
I won't hide anything again.
I will tell you the truth about your illness.
Let's face this difficulty together.
I believe you can do it.
I don't believe.
I know what you just said
is to drive me away.
You don't want to drag me down.
You want me to give up.
You know it will annoy me.
You want me to hate you.
But I am telling you, Gao Liang.
Whatever you say,
I won't give up.
You are not allowed to give up either.
You just ran into this difficulty suddenly
and were panic.
You don't know what to do.
Nanzheng,
I am telling you,
before I can stand up,
I won't marry you.
That means
you should leave me now.
You should find someone
who loves you,
find someone you want to marry.
You should enjoy a happy life.
Don't waste time here.
OK?
I bless you.
I can promise you.
But I have conditions.
Say it.
One year later,
I will leave.
But now,
let's start.
If you don't speak, I'll take it as a promise.
OK.
Let's get back to the main topic.
I have checked the data.
There are many cases like you.
The proportion of complete recovery is less than 3%.
But
there is always a possibility of 3%.
In the proportion of 3%,
90% of them
are all athletes.
That means
your previous training as special forces
is helpful for your recovery.
Even if there is only a little possibility,
we work together.
Or
change to this one?
You will go away on vacation
so wearing cloth shoes will be more comfortable.
Forget it.
Just wear this.
It's up to you.
Wear this.
It's comfortable.
Fei,
let me ask you,
do you want to be a soldier?
I ask you one more time.
Do you want to be a soldier,
like your father,
like me?
[ZhangMu Station]
Go back.
Cadres' children are beating people.
What kind of man are you to hit one person with three people?
Do you have the ability to fight one-on-one?
OK. One-on-one.
Come on.
Let me show you
what is relentlessly beating the dog in the water?