♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 23=
Get married?
Really?
Yes.
We just discussed it today.
Such good news.
I didn't expect my baby girl
to figure it out so quickly.
Mr. Jiang,
I have another good news for you.
You will be a grandfather.
Fanlv, is that true?
Great!
By the way, Xiangyuan,
you should get your mother here
as soon as possible.
Fanlv is pregnant.
We should discuss
the wedding and arrange it soon.
OK. I'll inform them right away.
I have determined the hotel,
the best hotel in Shanghai,
Binjiang Hotel.
In addition to friends,
I will invite business partners.
Yes, invite all of them.
It is a great occasion for the Jiang's
to marry our girl.
We have to organize a large wedding.
Mr. Jiang,
that's what I'm thinking too.
Don't worry.
I will hold a grand wedding for Fanlv.
So, your father is not in good health.
I understand your feelings now.
If your father is not present,
who will be in charge of Yutian?
The rival.
The one who set you up here, right?
Maybe.
It seems that you want to
give up a rook to save the king.
Just like the pieces in your hand.
When you hold them in your hand,
they seem useless.
But when you put them on the chessboard,
they will play their roles.
No matter you
give up a rook to save the king,
or the opposite,
there will be sacrifice.
Playing chess is the same as
being a human being.
There are losses and wins.
The cumulative number of losses
may lead to the final win.
Miss Jiang, these wedding rings
are selected by Mr. Lin.
Please have a look.
You can select a ring you like.
Miss Jiang, please take a look.
These three wedding dresses are
the most popular ones we have this year.
Is there any one you like?
Do you need a reservation?
Mom,
I have good news for you.
I'm going to get married.
Of course, it's true.
Get ready to
come to Shanghai in the next few days.
Mr. Wei,
hello, this is Lin.
What? You already knew?
This is Xiangyuan,
and I'm going to get married.
I will definitely share his work
in the future,
and our business will be smoother.
Miss Jiang,
this is our most popular bouquet
of the year.
Are you satisfied with that?
Mr. Lin thought...
Enough! Get out.
I want to be alone for a while.
(Lin Xiangyuan)
Lin Xiangyuan, go to my father's office.
I want to talk to you.
Cancel the wedding?
It seems that
Miss Jiang is disrespectful to you.
Even if she is disrespectful to you,
she should not be disrespectful to
your mother.
She is your mother!
Take it slow.
Be careful.
Mr. Lin,
you can have a nap in the car.
I will wake you up
when we arrive at your place.
Mr. Jiang,
there may be a problem with the car.
The car cannot be started.
What should I do?
I have to meet Mr. Xu.
How about taking Mr. Lin's car?
I just saw that
he went out with Miss Jiang.
Zhang, is your mobile phone ringing?
No.
Mr. Lin,
is it convenient to talk?
Mr. Yu let me tell you that
he earned a lot this time,
and he wants to thank you.
(Shanghai Qingpu District
Marriage Registration Center)
I'm not complimenting you,
but you achieved
unintentional positive outcomes.
Mr. Yu did this
without leaving any trace.
(Household Register)
(Lin Xiangyuan)
Although Lei Yuzheng
has responsibility,
he was indeed wronged.
Hello, Mr. Lin?
(Conduct Administration by Law,
Provide Enthusiastic Service)
(Lin Xiangyuan, Jiang Fanlv)
(Marriage Certificate of
the People's Republic of China)
Congratulations to you.
Mr. Jiang, are you OK?
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
I'm OK.
(Fanlv)
-Hello.
-Dad.
Fanlv, where are you now?
Lin Xiangyuan and I just
got our marriage license.
What? You've got the marriage license?
You are back.
Where is my dad?
Didn't he ask me to
come back for dinner?
I don't know.
Mr. Jiang has not come back yet.
Mr. Lin, let me hold this for you.
Mr. Lin, please have a seat.
Today is your wedding day with Fanlv,
I don't dare to bother you.
Fanlv,
don't blame me for talking too much.
The wedding is too simple!
There is only one table
and several guests.
You should have a grander wedding.
My wedding is up to me.
Anyway, we are a family.
Fanlv.
Dad, why are you back so late?
Mr. Jiang.
Fanlv,
go out to buy a bottle of wine for me.
There is wine in the house.
Just go.
Don't nag.
Come with me.
Mr. Jiang,
are you looking for me?
Mr. Jiang?
Don't flatter me.
Mr. Jiang, what do you mean?
Lin Xiangyuan,
don't play the fool with me.
You're really good at business.
You killed three hawks with one arrow.
You ruined Lei Yuzheng,
built yourself up,
and made me a fool.
I married my daughter to you.
Mr. Jiang, calm down.
There must be misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Tell me, who is Mr. Yu
that Xie Li was talking about?
Mr. Jiang.
You disappointed me too much.
I didn't expect that
the person I promoted
would do such a thing.
Mr. Jiang,
Lei Yuzheng's imprisonment really
has nothing to do with me.
I would never
dare to do that.
I'm wholehearted to you and Fanlv.
I saw Lei Yuzheng looked down on you
because he is the major shareholder
of Yutian Group.
I was very angry.
I just don't like him,
but I never set him up on purpose
to such a serious extent.
Mr. Jiang, I swear
I didn't do it.
Shut up!
Lin Xiangyuan, still treating me
like a fool?
I've been in the business field
for decades.
I know one is always trying to
cheat the other in the business field.
But I have a bottom line.
Mr. Jiang.
Tell me,
how would I dare
to keep someone like you
with no moral bottom line around me?
How would I dare to let Fanlv
live with you for the rest of her life?
Mr. Jiang, I'm sorry.
I know that you don't trust me,
but I'm wholehearted to
you and Fanlv.
Shut up!
Mr. Jiang,
I have no complaints
no matter how you punish me,
but Fanlv and I are married,
and she is carrying my baby now.
If you put me in jail,
your grandson will be born
without a father.
Mr. Jiang,
I will make up for my mistakes.
After Lei Yuzheng gets out of jail,
I will return Yutian to him.
OK?
What's the use of making up for
what's already happened?
You know that
Fanlv and I
just registered our marriage.
Now, do you want her…
I swear that
I will love Fanlv and treat her well.
After Lei Yuzheng gets out of jail,
I will definitely return Yutian to him.
Fanlv, you're married today,
and I'm very happy for you.
You're my baby girl,
and I always hope that
you can marry a good man who loves you.
But I also would like to warn you,
there is a gap
between the ideal and reality.
You need to learn to protect yourself.
Keep an eye on everything.
Remember?
Don't worry, dad.
I won't leave you anyway.
If you have any grievance, just tell me.
Dad will always support you.
Mr. Jiang, a toast to you.
Since what is done cannot be undone,
I have nothing to say.
Xiangyuan, you should call me dad now.
Thank you, dad.
I have a word for you.
The moon waxes only to wane,
and water brims only to overflow.
Cherish what you've got now.
Leave some leeway for everything,
or you will lose more than
you've gained sooner or later.
Dad, I will keep that in mind.
Dad,
why are you being so weird today?
Nothing.
I just want to give some advice
about business to Xiangyuan.
Come on.
I wish you all the happiness.
May we have family harmony.
Here.
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Lei Yuzheng.
Yes.
A woman called Shao Kaixuan
is here to see you,
and she is waiting in the audience room.
Hello, Aunt Shao.
Yuzheng, how are you doing there?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Yuzheng, take care of yourself.
Zhenrong is gone,
and you're all that I have.
Remember,
where there is life, there is hope.
Be sure to take care of yourself.
Understand?
Aunt Shao, don't worry.
I've long since adapted to this place.
How is my father doing?
I forgot to tell you that
your father is doing well.
He is on vacation abroad.
Look,
your farther is getting old,
and he is worried about you
because he cannot see you.
But Assistant He told him that
you were busy
doing your own thing abroad.
And your father asked no more questions.
Aunt Shao,
you don't have to say any more.
I trust you.
When I see my father in this situation,
I feel bad.
He is quite old now,
but I still have him worried.
I'm not filial.
Yuzheng, I know that
what you've done is
to make Yutian
and the project survive.
Aunt Shao, don't worry.
I'm fine.
You and my father
should take care of yourselves.
When I get out,
I will show filial piety to you.
I'm leaving.
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Yes.
I understand.
OK, OK.
Mr. Jin, you can rest assured that
I will definitely show the simple,
modern, fashionable, high-end,
and magnificent style you like
at the lowest cost.
Do you think this is OK?
OK. Goodbye.
Du Xiaosu,
you're such a moneygrubber.
Only half a month left
before the Spring Festival,
and you receive so many orders.
Can you finish them in time?
Life is about making money.
Isn't that your motto?
No.
My motto is,
even if you don't earn money...
Who is that?
My mom.
Hello, mom.
Hello, daughter. When will you be home
for the Spring Festival break?
It's not easy to buy a ticket
if it's too late.
You need to book your flight
for the festival break earlier.
Don't be muddleheaded,
or you will be in a rush and muddle.
Xiaosu,
your mom started making
your favorite smoked fish yesterday.
We'll wait for you to eat that
when you return for the Spring Festival.
Dad and mom,
I was just about to
speak to you about this.
I may not go back home this year.
The studio is too busy,
and I cannot go back.
Fanlv.
Dad.
You're pregnant.
Why do you still
drive to work by yourself?
Where is Xiangyuan?
He drives you every day, doesn't he?
I sent him on an errand,
and he went out early in the morning.
Really?
He didn't bully you, right?
Him?
No. He treats me like a bodhisattva.
Don't worry.
Do you know who is
the model husband in our company?
Mr. Lin, right?
Of course.
Mr. Lin is so nice to Miss Jiang
to be nominated for "Touching China".
After Miss Jiang gets pregnant,
Mr. Lin even doesn't
dare to speak loudly.
-Hello, Mr. and Miss Jiang.
Dad, don't listen to their nonsense.
Xiangyuan treats you well,
and everyone sees that.
But you should have
a sense of propriety,
or they will think that
the Jiangs did not educate you well.
Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Lin is here.
Fanlv,
here are the yellow crab
and chicken porridge
I bought these especially for you.
I walked several blocks to get these.
Eat while they are still warm.
Xiangyuan,
come to my office later.
OK.
Let's go.
Xiangyuan,
I can see that
you have been treating Fanlv well
in the last few months,
and I'm delighted.
Mr. Jiang, I promised you that
I'd be nice to her.
And I will treat you as my own father.
That's all I should do.
As a parent,
my biggest wish is for my daughter
to marry a good man.
If you and Fanlv can
live a peaceful life,
it's the greatest filial piety to me.
About the mistake you made,
learn lessons from it
and never do that again.
I understand.
Tomorrow, I will go abroad
on a business trip,
and may not be back
until Spring Festival's Eve.
During my absence,
you take charge of the company.
Mr. Jiang, don't worry.
I will not disappoint you.
Bro,
what are you thinking about?
It seems that my father is really sick.
I didn't know my father might be sick,
until the day
Aunt Shao gave me this photo.
To say the least,
if my father is good,
why doesn't he come to see me?
Bro,
I know you are painful.
But all people living in this world
are painful more or less.
You should hide such pains
in your heart.
The more painful it is now,
the more you will want to live well
when you get out
in the future.
And in this way,
you can endure the life here.
Mr. Lin, you have obvious dark circles.
Are you OK?
Were you too tired last night?
Take care of yourself.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What are you doing
in the midnight?
Can you just sleep silently?
How can I fall asleep
when you keep snoring like that?
Don't be angry.
I will sleep on the sofa.
Annoying.
Can you just sleep silently?
How can I fall asleep
when you keep snoring like that?
Yes, it's me.
OK, I will notify Mr. Lin.
What?
Ning Weicheng said
Miss Jiang just threw up again
in the office,
so she asked for a month's leave.
He asked me to tell you this.
OK. Tell Ning Weicheng
to find someone to send her home.
Don't let her go alone.
OK.
He Qunfei was assigned
to the data and file room
as a clerk
to do odds and ends.
You thought about firing him before,
didn't you?
But Miss Jiang stopped it.
How do you know that?
I know a lot of things.
You don't have to fire him.
You can transfer him to
the logistics department
to manage the cleaning
of the entire building, instead.
Make him inspect the hygiene every day.
You're so mean.
Mr. Lin, you complimented me again。
Let's walk and talk.
Supervisor He, you mean I have to leave?
I'm surprised too.
You were here just a few days ago,
and did nothing wrong.
But look,
the executive office
suddenly issued an order
to transfer you to the logistics
department to manage the hygiene.
Maybe I shouldn't say that.
It's right for you to be loyal
to Mr. Lei,
but now it is not like the old days.
You have to accommodate
yourself to the circumstance.
Mr. Lin, Mr. Xie, what brought you here?
I'll get you two cups of tea.
Lin Xiangyuan, you're so mean
to get me in trouble on purpose.
Listen, a small-minded person like you
will never achieve great things.
Achieving great things or not
seems to have nothing to do with you.
But at least for now,
you have to do whatever
Mr. Lin wants you to do.
(Employee Job Adjustment Notice)
(Right position for you)
(Job Description)
(Recruitment. Interviewees wait here)
Who is No. 10, He Qunfei?
Nice to meet you.
(Resume of He Qunfei)
Mr. He, I'm curious that
why do you leave Yutian
where so many people want
to work.
Because...
As far as I know,
you and the current CEO of Yutian,
Mr. Lin Xiangyuan, have disputes.
(Applicant)
That's not the case.
Then,
why are you applying for a job here?
(Interviewer. Assistant)
Sorry, Mr. He.
You'd better go to another company
to take a chance,
or change the industry.
Thank you.
Such a beautiful girl.
Me?
Of course, it's you.
What will we eat later?
As you want.
Eat…
Shangguan.
What a coincidence!
Who is this beautiful girl?
Hello, I'm his girlfriend.
She is my cousin.
Shopping with your cousin?
OK. See you.
-Bye.
What?
What do you mean?
I'm your cousin?
Am I embarrassing you?
You misunderstood me.
This friend of mine
is gossipy.
If he knows that you're my girlfriend,
everyone will know that.
So what? Is it embarrassing
to have a girlfriend?
You just have fun with me?
What are you talking about?
I am true to you.
Even the sun and moon can see.
But...
I'm actually a very low-key person.
I really don't want to be
the subject of gossip
among those friends.
I swear,
if I'm not true to you,
I will...
All right.
I trust you.
Show me your smile.
No.
Smile.
I'm fine.
I'm a little uncomfortable.
Can you send me back?
Hello, sir.
Look, highly paid recruitment.
(High Salary Recruitment)
OK.
Here?
Yes, here.
I've checked on the phone.
Right.
You didn't even tell our daughter,
and you directly came to Shanghai.
You're not afraid of delaying her work?
-304.
301.
-301.
-Right, here.
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
Hello. We are looking for Du Xiaosu.
We... We're her parents.
We just came from our hometown.
Is she there?
Uncle and aunt,
please have a rest.
Where is Xiaosu?
She's not at work?
Is she sick?
No, no.
Xiaosu is fine.
But she is not here now.
She went to Lei's house
to look after an elderly person.
Lei's house?
To look after an elderly person?
Mr. Lei, look.
This is your favorite
red bean and glutinous rice porridge.
There are so many red beans.
Come on, take a sip.
Are you OK?
Let me wipe you off.
Go away.
I don't know you.
Don't you remember?
I'm the Marshmallow.
We're good friends.
I'm not your good friend.
You're all bad people.
You imprison me here.
You want me to die.
Yuzheng, Yuzheng.
Get out.
Mr. Lei,
it's night time
over there now.
Your son is sleeping.
You'd better not to disturb him.
Let's go to bed too.
Have a rest, OK?
I'm not sick. I don't take medicine.
It's OK. It's OK.
Let me clean here.
Marshmallow.
I'm OK. I'm fine.
Xiaosu, are you OK?
Are you injured?
Dad, mom,
why are you here?
If we're not here,
how long are you going
to hide this from us?
So much has happened.
Why didn't you tell us?
It's OK.
Marshmallow,
who are they?
Mr. Lei, don't worry or panic.
They're my parents, not bad people.
-Come here.
-Good people, good people.
You said you are busy and cannot
go back home during Spring Festival,
so this is what you are busy for?
I cannot believe you were lying to us.
If your father and I didn't see this,
we will never believe that
you're an accompanying nurse now.
Yes, Xiaosu,
how could you lie to us?
A girl in your company told us
that you are here.
I wanted to tell you this before,
but...
I'm afraid I cannot explain it clearly.
Tell us,
what's the relationship
between you and Lei?
If there is nothing between you,
why are you taking care of his father?
We're friends.
If the family of my friend have trouble,
I should help take care of them.
Help take care?
You think I don't know?
I have inquired before I came.
You make friends
with a person in the jail...
Mom, keep your voice down.
Mr. Lei doesn't know yet.
Go back with me right now.
No, I cannot go.
Mr. Lei is here alone,
and the butler went out.
I have to stay here.
Marshmallow, I want to watch TV.
OK, I'm coming.
I really cannot go.
How about this?
You two go back first.
When the butler comes back,
I will go back. OK?
Fine.
Listen to Xiaosu. We go back first.
What's done is done.
No hurry at this moment.
You...
I don't know what to say about you.
Let's go.
Go.
The Big Head Son and Little Head Father
is going to start.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
She is so...
Don't be angry.
Your daughter is playing the fool,
and you didn't stop her
but helped her instead.
I didn't help her.
No matter how serious the matter is,
we cannot make a noise
in other people's home.
Isn't it right?
She is spoiled by you.
You both...
It's weird.
Does Xiaosu like Mr. Lei?
Don't think so much.
Let's talk to her
after she comes back home.
She must give us a good explanation.
Maokai, move.
I'm coming.
Mr. Lei,
let me pour you a cup of tea.
No, I want yogurt.
OK, yogurt.
But you have to take the medicine
after yogurt, OK?
Then I will take it away.
OK, OK, OK.
Ok. Have only one.
Drink.
Aunt Shao, you're here.
What's wrong with you?
You don't look very well.
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
It's him.
You often come here?
I came here sometimes for work.
Come and sit.
Waiter, open a bottle
of champagne.
Sit over here.
Don't be so far away from me.
Come on.
It's OK.
Sir, here is your champagne.
Thank you.
He Qunfei?
Why are you here?
He Qunfei.
You're Du Xiaosu's friend, right?
He is Du Xiaosu's friend.
We met before.
Why are you here?
Part-time job?
I'm on probation.
I don't know if they want me or not.
What a coincidence today!
So many acquaintances have met here.
Is this Assistant He?
Why are you here?
Part-time job, right?
That's reasonable. I'm afraid
the low salary of a cleaning supervisor
cannot even be enough to pay the rent.
Look at what you're wearing.
Is the small red bellyband
comfortable?
Mr. Lin,
if Lei Yuzheng sees that
Assistant He is serving us,
what will he think?
Qunfei,
this bar is just so so.
Anyone can come here.
What do you mean?
There is someone here
who has done bad things behind.
Well, Mr. Lin,
does that sound bad?
Shangguan,
if you really want to help Lei Yuzheng,
don't waste time here with me.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the
tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪