[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[The show is an adapted fiction based on
stories of National Park Rangers.]
[All characters, events, regions,]
[organizations depicted in the show
are fictitious.]
[Year 1991]
Mayor.
Can we please talk?
Let's talk.
Stop being stubborn and sign the form.
Forget it all
and start a new life with Sol.
[Cable Car Construction Agreement Form]
[Jirisan Development Committee
President, Yang Geun-tak]
How many times do I need to tell you?
I'm not leaving!
This is where I was born and grew up.
I'll stay here until the end,
so don't ever come back.
Let's just go.
Dad.
Why can't we live down the mountain?
What?
Someone told you to say that?
No, but if we do,
my school will be closer,
and you won't have to fight with others.
They're wrong, and I'm right.
You got that?
What?
I don't hear the bees.
No way.
Mr. Kim.
Let's clean this up first.
Go away!
Leave! Get out!
[Kim Jae-gyeong]
No, no...
No, no, no...
You hear that?
What?
You hear that, right?
The sound of bees flying.
Look.
The bees came back to life.
Dad...
They came back to life.
They came back to life!
The bees came back to life!
I need more beehives.
Dad, what are you doing?
-What's wrong?
-Let go!
[Signee, Representative]
[Signature]
[Jin-ok keeps saying]
[that spraying pesticide
on the hives was a little too much.]
[She's the one who put
the dead raccoon in the well.]
[She's not any better.]
[Eung-soon's dad's been drinking
the whole time.]
I hope he doesn't turn himself in
for the hit-and-run.
No way.
Keep their mouths shut.
If they find out about Sol's mom...
You look like you saw a ghost.
Did you hear us?
[Cable Car Construction Agreement Form]
Good job, kid.
Now leave.
Go!
Go away!
My ears are falling off.
The bees are too loud.
Help!
[Mount Jirisan
Cable Car Business Promotion]
[Cable Car Construction Agreement Form]
What do you mean?
The project is canceled?
Yes.
We got the proper site
and permission from the local government,
but the Ministry of Environment
won't pass it.
What?
Don't worry.
I won't give up so easily.
Next time,
this cable car business
on Mount Jirisan...
I'll make it happen for sure.
-Wait, Il-man.
-Whatever.
-Just give us our compensation.
-Okay.
Give us our money!
-Il-man. Let go of this.
-Our compensation!
-Give us our money!
-Calm down.
Give us our money!
You lied to us. My money!
-My money...
-Calm down.
Hold on.
There, there.
-Calm down.
-Give us our money.
Give us our money.
Hey.
My compensation.
Give us our money!
[Mount Jirisan
Cable Car Business Promotion]
My money...
-Push it!
-Oh, gosh.
Wait. Now lift it.
Be careful.
How did our village come to this?
But...
It's still wise to leave now
when the national park offers to pay us.
[The murderer who's been killing people]
on the mountain disguised as an accident
is you.
Me? Killing people?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
It is you.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go tell the police everything I know.
Do you have any proof?
Why are you here?
If I really am the murderer,
I won't let you go alive.
So why did you come to
such a dangerous place alone?
You wish I'd kill you now, right?
This isn't the mountain.
There are security cameras everywhere,
and your phone can be tracked.
If I kill you here now,
there will be evidence
that I'm the murderer.
Because you don't have any proof.
Are you here to make evidence?
Yi-gang.
Would I do that
if I'm really the murderer?
Hello? Gu-yeong, it's me. Sol.
Yi-gang's at my place right now.
Could you come pick her up?
Okay, thanks.
Go tell the police tomorrow.
I don't know
if they'll believe you, though.
[What if Eung-soon's not the murderer?]
[What if it's Sol?]
[Gaeam hideout]
[A place where not many people visit
but the murderer knows well.]
[The secret hideout Sol knew well.]
[Old shelters from the past.]
[The evidence that the murderer took
from the Black Bridge Valley Shelter.]
[I must find them.]
-Are you okay? Nothing happened?
-No.
The GPS chip?
I put it in his rucksack.
I told him
I'm going to the police tomorrow.
He looked confident,
but I'm sure he'll go dispose of
the evidence just in case.
We must seize that chance.
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
How did it go?
[National Park Service]
You were right.
He's near Deokseoryeong.
-It must be around here.
-Right.
Right there.
-Is that him?
-Yes.
[Be careful. You must not get caught.]
[This is our last chance.
We need to find the evidence.]
All right.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're not completely cleared
of your charges yet.
Please refrain from long-distance trips
for a while,
and keep your phone on at all times.
Okay.
[Damsung Detention Center]
Dad!
Hey.
Sae-nyeok...
Do I really have to come
to a place like this?
I'm so sick and tired of Mount Jirisan.
You devoted your entire life here,
but this is how they treat you?
Let's end it here, Dad.
You've done enough.
Come home with me.
Sae-nyeok.
I'm sorry.
But I have to
go up one last time.
Thanks.
Shoot.
Wait.
That's towards Beori Forest.
The foggy area.
He's nearby.
[Jeong Gu-yeong]
-What happened?
[-We lost him.]
What do you mean?
[This jerk knew the chip was in his bag.]
[He led us here on purpose.]
He couldn't have gone far.
[We must find him!]
What's going on?
[I don't see him. He's gone.]
It's Sol. He's the murderer.
Gu-yeong and Il-hae followed him,
but they lost him on the mountain.
We must find him quick
before Sol gets rid of the evidence.
Commander.
We must find Sol.
[Gu-yeong, Il-hae. Switch the frequency
to the shared channel.]
Where was his last location?
Byeori Forest in Deokseoryeong.
Haedong Ranger Station, to all rangers.
[An SOS reported in Deokseoryeong.]
It's a national park ranger,
Kim Sol.
[He was last witnessed
in Byeori Forest of Deokseoryeong.]
[He can't be far.]
Search 3km within Byeori Forest.
It must be a bedrock area.
Like Black Bridge Valley Shelter,
with a cave.
It's most likely the bedrock
northwest or south of Byeori Forest.
We're the closest. We'd get there first.
Let's think of this as
finding a stranded hiker.
He's here somewhere.
This way!
There's a trace of someone
going northwest.
We'll search that area.
So you found it.
After all that's happened,
you still stayed on the mountain
to capture me?
See?
I told you ghosts exist.
People don't believe me, though.
You're the murderer.
That's right.
I killed all those people.
All these victims... Why?
Because they didn't remember.
They didn't remember
what happened back then.
[I didn't mean to kill them at first.]
[Year 2017]
[In fact, I was going to kill myself.]
[The sound of ghosts...]
[They never left me alone.]
[I've tried many times to kill myself,]
[but I was saved by others every time.]
[So if I'm on the mountain,]
[I thought they wouldn't be able
to find me.]
[So I brought a poisoned yogurt there.]
Oh, hello.
Please help me. I'm lost.
[I didn't recognize him at first.]
[I thought maybe I could have
some mercy on him before I'd die.]
You're from Black Bridge Valley?
That's right.
Why?
[Kim Hyeon-su]
Kim Hyeon-su...
Are you Hyeon-su?
Do you know me?
It's me. Kim Sol.
Kim Sol?
-Beekeeper's Sol?
-Yes.
It's been so long! So good to see you.
How have you been?
What a coincidence.
Baektogol pagoda ground is that way.
Thank you so much.
Oh, right.
Can you give me your number?
I'll call you when I finish my time
in the military.
How's your father?
I miss him.
I liked him a lot when I was little.
Sol?
What's wrong?
-Here.
-Thanks.
Here, have this on your way.
Thanks.
[No one thought it was murder]
[but an accident.]
[The mountain was on my side.]
[Kim Sol]
[And I came back to the mountain
as a ranger.]
[It wasn't hard convincing Se-wook.]
[He was also]
[living a hellish life.]
Since then, we've killed them
one by one.
All of a sudden,
I stopped hearing bees.
Same with Eung-soon.
He wasn't aware
of what his father had done.
But he came to investigate
the flooding accident.
When I threatened him
that I'd reveal the truth
about the death of Se-wook's father,
he couldn't do anything.
Thanks to that, I could fool you.
The mountain
is not on your side.
wanted to punish you.
That's why it showed me.
[The visions of you and Se-wook]
[killing people.]
[When I discovered the mark
at Sangsuri Rock,]
no one died.
How did you find this?
I'm Kim Sol,
a cultural resources researcher.
That's why the mountain showed it to me.
Thanks to that mark,
I was able to meet you.
The mountain was telling me
that you were the criminal.
I should have known then.
I have no idea what you're saying.
But the truth is that you couldn't get me.
That means the mountain's on my side.
No.
It's on our side.
You'll get your punishment.
Everyone who's seen me
died.
Cut the crap.
If you think
the mountain's really on your side,
try and stop me then.
I've kept them as a token of their sins.
But... Oh, well.
No...
Stop!
[Medical Report for a Patient
in the Process of Passing]
[Patient: Kang Hyun-jo]
[Summary: Intraventricular hemorrhage
due to external wounds...]
[Consent Form for Authorization
of Removing Patient's Life Support]
[Patient: Kang Hyun-jo,
Guardian: Yang Hyun-il]
What?
What's that?
[Commander, smoke spotted at 2km
northwest of Byeori Forest!]
It's all over.
All the objects in the cave are burnt.
[We can barely find traces.]
No.
No way.
It can't end like this.
Yi-gang. Yi-gang!
Too many people have died.
Da-won died,
and Hyun-jo risked his life for this.
We can't end it here.
There has to be something,
near the cave
where he burned the evidence.
Hyun-jo...
It's Hyun-jo.
That's the way to Bidam Cliff.
Where's he going?
[And about Sangsuri Rock.]
He said that's where he first
saved someone.
On top of Bidam Cliff... Sangsuri Rock.
That's where we first discovered the mark.
He's going to leave a mark.
Because Sol knows all the places
we decided on,
he's going to a different place
to leave a mark.
I'll tell other rangers to go there.
All the rangers went to Deokseoryeong,
which is two hours away
from the top of Bidam Cliff.
We don't have time.
Yi-gang.
Let's go up the mountain.
Watch your head.
Be careful.
Commander, right there.
Hyun-jo...
Are you all right?
Seo Yi-gang.
Did Hyun-jo leave this?
Yi-gang, wake up!
Only you can tell where this leads to.
It's not the mountain.
It's Haedong Police Substation.
-It's Haedong Police Substation.
-You mean, Eung-soon?
Hyun-jo suspected him,
but he already told me.
He wouldn't have left that here again.
It's going to be the last mark
that Hyun-jo leaves.
It must be a crucial clue.
Haedong Police Substation...
I came to ask something.
-Is this it?
-I don't know.
-There's a car accident outside.
-What?
[Kim Eung-soon]
The cell phone?
Se-wook?
Constable Park.
Gosh.
Not this again? You rangers really...
-This is something important.
-I don't care.
You shouldn't be doing this.
Just for a second.
I swear, just for a second.
Request a forensic examination
of this cell phone.
-Why?
-Please. It's urgent.
This could be critical evidence
to a murder case.
[Damsung Police]
[National Forensic Service]
-Call a nearby division for support!
-Yes, sir!
-Hurry up!
How did it go? Was there anything?
[Digital Forensic Result]
[Kill Granny Geum-rye...]
[I killed Kim Jin-deok
on the mountain today.]
[Great job. Next is Lee Jong-gu...
Just put the yogurt behind Bullet Rock.]
[I'll find out who he is. Don't worry.]
[Just finish what you need to do.]
Police. Are you in there, Mr. Kim Sol?
Hello? Mr. Kim Sol?
Mr. Kim Sol! Come on out!
Police!
[National Park Service]
-Sir.
-You're from the national park, right?
What do you mean the suspect
ran to the mountain?
His car was found here.
We think he ran off to the mountain.
We need your cooperation.
Okay.
You've ruined it all.
You don't even know what's important,
yet you put on airs
about protecting the mountain.
Do you know what the mountain wants?
For all of you to disappear!
Hikers, herb collectors, rangers...
All of them!
Why do you think floods
and wildfires happen every year?
It's to wipe you out, all of you.
Just wait.
I'll kill you up on the mountain
like others.
I'm sending you to your granny.
You did that to my grandma, too?
You didn't know?
How could you?
She did nothing.
I did everything
on behalf of the mountain.
I was going to kill you on the mountain
since you like there so much.
But this is also good.
Let's end this here.
Right here.
You said the mountain
told you to kill everyone?
Nonsense!
A mountain's just a mountain.
It's your delusional head
telling you nonsense.
You're just crazy!
No.
This is what the mountain wants.
[A year later]
On three.
It looks good.
Oh, no.
I'm okay.
Hold on.
Make your face sad.
All right.
Do you...
Do you trust me?
Yes.
I feel like I keep disappointing you.
Like when I met your mother.
But if you wait a little more for me,
I'll pass the promotion test
and promise you I'll make you happy.
You're so silly.
[I heard if you kiss here,
your love will last.]
[Congratulations to National Park Ranger
Jeong Gu-yeong]
[for passing the promotion test.]
How have you been?
[Team Leader, Jeong Gu-yeong]
I'm sorry I brought this so late.
A surprise for you.
I'll see you later.
[Team Leader, Jeong Gu-yeong]
Oh, hello.
Here, have some.
Why?
This is good for you.
No, thank you.
What was that?
But this is so good.
[Team Leader, Jeong Gu-yeong]
Hey!
You said you were just patrolling.
Why are you so late?
You've been slacking off
since you became a team leader.
As a commander, I'll say one thing.
Stay vigilant.
Gosh.
Not this again.
But I'm a team leader now...
It's a mystery, though,
how you passed the promotion exam.
Whatever.
I heard there's an interview today.
How's that going?
Well, I don't know.
That's not the commander's job.
I'm going to the bathroom, Commander.
-Let's hustle.
-Got that, sir.
[National Park Service]
Why did you apply for this job?
I'm not sure
if I'm qualified for this job.
But
if I can, I would like to become a ranger
and return the favor I received.
Are you still afraid of mountains?
I was also afraid of mountains once.
But...
[Interviewer]
A mountain's just a mountain.
It's just...
Everyone has a mountain
in their own heart.
Some go up mountains to live,
and some go up to die.
[The mindset that hikers have when they
climb the mountain isn't important.]
Because all we do is
to keep them safe.
If you have a burden in
your heart, put it down.
A mountain's just a mountain.
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
Jeong Gu-yeong.
Jeong Gu-yeong!
Wake up!
Get up. Mujin Station kids
are all ready to go.
Let's hurry.
I'm tired.
Hurry up.
I'm so tired.
Get up.
Gosh, I'm so tired of this.
Oh, and Happy New Year.
Gosh, this is killing me.
My neck...
-Where's Yi-gang?
-She should be here soon.
Hey.
Thank you, sir.
Wait for me!
You're lucky.
Can you carry me up this time?
-Hurry up.
-When did you leave?
Step back!
It's dangerous! Please step back.
Today's sun is exactly
the same as tomorrow's sun!
It's nothing special.
Be careful!
-It's dangerous.
-Ma'am.
-This way.
-Step back.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Please step back.
Be careful, please step back.
Wait.
You should know better.
Why?
I've never seen the sunrise with ease.
Can't I enjoy it with my daughter?
Please step back!
Please!
It's dangerous here.
You can see fine from back there.
Step back.
Step back, please.
Watch your step, you'll fall.
-Where?
-Where is it?
Please step back.
Sorry, let's move back.
-Oh, really?
-It's from that way.
Yi-gang!
I was just about to call you.
Hyun-jo.
Hyun-jo's breathing again.
He's getting treated in a different unit,
but all his signs are returning to normal.
The sunrise!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, everyone!
-Happy New Year!
-You, as well!
One, two, three.
Thank you.
-Could you...
-Of course.
Thank you.
Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
-Here you go.
-Thanks a lot.
[You don't see things anymore, right?]
[Yes.]
I don't see them anymore.