Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My Dear Guardian
Episode 28
He's the drug dealer's son.
I saw him when I was compiling
the materials.
He resembles you.
You told me
you had no siblings.
But as you know,
we journalists
have wide open minds.
For the whole afternoon,
I asked myself,
who was the man?
How is he related to you?
Perhaps
he was the reason you left
without a word.
Or perhaps
it was merely a coincidence.
So it is you.
Zhuo Ran.
Uncle Rao.
You're awake.
Where's Xiao Xue?
She went to grab some breakfast.
Is Li Lei alright?
He's fine.
You may see him once you recover.
And the suspect?
Dead.
Take it easy.
You need rest.
Just lie down.
Dr Xia.
When can I get discharged?
You've suffered a serious concussion.
You need time to recuperate.
When you're ready to be discharged,
we'll let you know.
Be patient.
I have to go now.
I'll see you again.
Xiao Xue.
Rao's team has suffered
no serious injuries.
But you should remind him
to get more rest.
Got it.
One more thing.
What is it?
Ke Wei's family
would like to visit the injured policemen.
That's not necessary.
I know it's a lot to ask
at a time like this.
But I have a feeling
the explosion
wasn't simply the act of a youngster.
Perhaps
there's a deeper reason behind it.
What reason?
Ke Wei's screensaver
is a picture of a suicide victim
with the words, "The City of Desire."
The City of Desire?
Are you sure?
I've seen that picture.
Does "The City of Desire"
bear any significance?
Do you remember the assassin
who went after us last time?
His smartphone
had a picture of a dead body, too.
And the words, "The City of Desire."
The City of Desire is
a dark and unfathomable world.
How did you know?
Does your wound
have something to do with him?
Maybe.
Is it done?
Does it happen very often?
Not too often.
About as often as violence
against doctors.
Given our predicaments,
it'd be difficult
for us to be together.
We'll only know if we try.
Have you said that
to your language instructor?
No.
What about the nurses at Isaia?
I'm going to see Rao Zhi.
It's not just the two of them, is it?
I only say that to you, Da Miao.
Dr Xia...
Dad?
What brings you here?
Hi, Mr Xia.
What's the matter?
Can't I visit you?
No.
I'd like to speak with my daughter.
Go right ahead. I was
just about to leave.
Are you going to just stand there?
I'm worried you might not
want to see me.
Come here.
What did you get?
Sweet soy milk,
vegetarian noodles,
chicken potstickers,
and cold shredded potato.
That's a lot of food.
They're all your favourites.
You remembered.
I didn't.
I asked my mum.
She knows I'm injured?
Good.
What do you mean "good?"
It's not good at all.
I told my mum
I was getting all these goodies
to fatten you up
like a pig.
So you can't be a cop anymore.
That's so mean.
But
after I told that lie,
I realised something.
What did you realise?
I realised
why you wouldn't let me be with you.
Why you always tried to get rid of me
and told people I wasn't your daughter.
But it seems
you don't hate me all that much.
So are you going to listen
to me this time?
Never.
Xiao Xue.
By the way,
I finished the portrait
and gave it to your colleague.
That night,
I walked along the highway
by the coast.
When I entered the tunnel,
I saw a man driving past.
Did he see you?
No.
The tunnel was pitch black.
What happened next?
Then I fell asleep.
When I woke up, I was already
in the ER.
A man named Zhuo Ran
brought me there.
He's Xia Chu's first boyfriend.
You know that, don't you?
As for what happened between
the tunnel and the ER,
I haven't the slightest impression.
Around what time was it?
I mean
when you saw the man in the tunnel.
Nine.
I was listening to a music station.
There was a time announcement.
Nine o'clock.
A man.
Zhuo Ran.
The suspect
has a history of substance abuse
in the public.
During his rehabilitation,
he would often
log in to the City of Desire,
exposing himself to the temptation
of drugs.
He received
a list of instructions for a game.
The instructions
are linked to the explosion.
The man who gave the instructions
is none other than the elusive
Scary Pirate.
The only person
who may have had dealings
with the Scary Pirate
is the drug dealer
who transacted with him
in Yunshan Tunnel.
According to the sketch
provided by witnesses,
we've ascertained
the suspect's identity.
Well?
I am
of some use to you, aren't I?
To me,
you're more than just a useful companion.
Xiao Xue,
go back to the US.
I don't want to.
I want to stay by your side
at least until you've fully recovered.
What are you writing?
How's your dad?
He's fine.
Good.
Are you
writing a love letter for me?
No.
Liang Mu Ze.
Where did you get this?
I met a woman,
an ex-accountant
who is now a transplant coordinator.
She was talking about
the importance of organ donation.
So I got a copy from her.
Are you going to donate your organs?
Ever since my near-fatal experience
with the gunshot wound,
I've been thinking about it.
You were shot before?
Here.
Xiao Xue.
Xiao Xue, don't...
Let me hear
what your heart
has to say.
People are looking.
This is embarrassing.
I get it now.
Your heart told me everything.
It knows you're accustomed to being alone
and watching "Aberdeen"
and it's all for it.
Send me to the subway station.
The Captain isn't around.
I can't leave my post.
Sorry.
You may go.
Captain.
Don't go home.
Come to the guest house
and have a good night's sleep.
Send her to the subway.
Okay.
Go on.
Thanks, Captain.
You came here just for this?
Do you think it's a small matter?
It's no big deal, really.
See?
I'm still alive and well.
Rest assured.
I can't.
The explosion incident aside,
you should count your lucky stars
that you're still alive.
When I heard you were
fooling around with that military guy,
a hundred fears came to my mind.
Dad,
how can you say that?
What do you mean "fooling around?"
Liang Mu Ze is
an upright soldier.
During my stay at his house,
he treated me with the utmost respect.
And we're getting along happily.
Honey,
that's just a man's trick.
If he doesn't throw you a bone,
how can he trick you
into becoming his girlfriend?
We've been over this.
I only pretended to be his girlfriend
to appease his mother.
Wait...
That's even more absurd.
Why is he using my daughter
to appease his mother?
You call that respect?
Happily, you say?
I think,
just like me,
you've let all the studying
mess you up.
I can't speak for you,
but I'm sure I'm not messed up.
I know better than anyone
what kind of person Liang Mu Ze is.
I admit I've mishandled
the whole girlfriend charade.
But
now,
I'm seriously considering
becoming his girlfriend for real.
Do you dare?
We're both single adults.
What's there to be afraid of?
You...
Change careers.
What?
I want you to change careers
and come back to Dong'an with me.
Is this a joke?
I'm not joking.
You encouraged me to study medicine.
You encouraged me to come
to Ningjiang.
You encouraged me
to see the world.
Now look what happened.
The daughter I worked so hard to raise
is going to become a wife
of a soldier
and a slave to his lifestyle.
I won't.
If you choose Liang Mu Ze,
that will be your future.
You'll be wasting your life!
Then
why can't I be selfish
and keep you by my side?
At least I can
give you a peaceful life
and you won't have to live in fear
with him.
I have work to do.
Dad,
let's talk
later.
I'm off.
Goodbye.
Can't you send me to the camp?
The Captain only let me send you
to the subway station.
It's not like he'll know.
But I do.
Can't you pretend you don't know?
I can't.
Bullheaded fool.
What did you say?
I said you're bullheaded.
What are you doing here?
The Captain said I could send
you to the subway station.
But he didn't say whether
it's the starting station
or the destination station.
What are you, my chauffeur?
♫ Your expression popped up on my mind ♫
♫ I learn to face the music
instead of evading it ♫
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
Hold tight.
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
By the way, I have something for you.
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫
You gave me an hourglass,
so I'm giving you a watch.
This way, we'll
live in each other's pockets.
Do you like it?
♫ Remembering your interests,
getting closer to you ♫
♫ If I can't predict the future,
I'll leave it up to fate ♫
Was it expensive?
♫ I can't remember when
I fell in love with you ♫
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
Not as valuable as the love
you gave me.
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
Thank you.
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
Let's take a photo.
Right here?
Yes.
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫
Or do you want to go to
the City Affairs Bureau?
That's not I mean. I...
I mean, isn't it
a little crowded here?
You're too self-conscious.
Everyone's looking at their phones.
No one cares about you.
♫ I am afraid that
I might lose you one day ♫
♫ Every minute, every second,
how do I resist? ♫
♫ I can't help but look forward
to your return ♫
♫ Replaying the moment I fell in love ♫
Do a blood test first.
Come back to me
once you have the results.
Thanks, doctor.
You're welcome.
Next.
What seems to be the problem?
I have a heart ache.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I got a number.
I can't see my daughter
and I can't see a doctor?
After such a dire experience,
if he really loves you,
he should
try to get recalled.
Instead of making you
endure danger here.
I'm not staying here
because of him
but for my job.
Think,
what has he ever done for you
while you were together?
What about you?
You've been married to mum
for so many years.
What have you done for her?
If women were rational,
all men would be single forever.
I treat your mum just fine.
This is the EICU. No entry.
Emergency Intensive Care Unit
Honey.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I'll send you the photo
once I've cleaned it up.
No need to.
All I did was kiss you.
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
Then I'll kiss you again and see.
Xiao Xue.
Knock it off.
I'm just pulling your leg. Come on.
Do you remember the way home?
Sure.
Get off at the third bus stop,
take a rickshaw,
walk for around ten minutes,
and I should be there by sundown.
Why don't I give you a ride?
Lieutenant, you're the best!
Let's go.
You walk in front.
I'll follow behind you.
Okay.
♫ All I need ♫
♫ Is a plain old hug ♫
♫ But I am too shy ♫
♫ I hide behind formalities ♫
♫ Politely greeting you in my soft voice ♫
♫ I wave goodbye, trying to run away ♫
♫ I can't avoid it, it wraps around me
like the wind ♫
I have a gift for you.
A gift? What kind of gift?
But I'm afraid you might
scoff at it.
Fret not, I'll definitely scoff at it.
So just let me see it.
What's this?
Last time, you said the heart protector
was too ugly.
I got some Dyneema
from an old army friend
who works at a defence manufacturer
and made a bulletproof vest for you.
Is the look
acceptable for you?
No.
Xiao Xue.
This is made from the most advanced
bulletproof material in the world.
It's incredibly light
and soft.
Of course, on such short notice,
the workmanship may be a little sloppy.
But I hope you'll accept it.
Stop laughing.
You must wear it when you go out.
Promise me
you'll wear it when you go out, okay?
That way,
Officer Rao can have peace of mind.
Is that the only reason?
Don't move!
What's that sound?
Stay here.
Tian Yong!
Don't move!
Stand right there!
Tian Yong!
What happened to you?
Wake up, Tian Yong.
Wake up, wake up.
I'm okay.
You gave me such a fright.
I wasn't lying.
It is handy.
But it's so ugly.
It's alright.
Just relax.
Relax, take a deep breath.
Come on, breathe in.
Relax. Everything's alright.
What's the situation?
The pregnant lady is having a severe
haemorrhage due to trauma.
She had five years of substance abuse,
one ectopic pregnancy,
two successful labours.
This is her third pregnancy,
but we've lost the baby's heartbeat.
Ask the anaesthesiologist and the
Neonatology Department
to prepare for surgery.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Dr Xia.
Coming through! Please move aside.
Can you hear me?
If you can,
grab my hand.
Set up the blood transfusion.
Ask Orthopaedics, General Surgery,
and ICU for a treatment plan.
And call Dr Song.
Okay.
Ye Feng's family?
That's us.
Foot the bill.
Doctor,
how's his condition?
Don't worry,
we'll do our best to save him.
Captain.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Xiao Xue is back at the camp.
I know.
She phoned me.
What about Boss?
He's inside.
What are they discussing?
I don't know.
Liang Mu Ze
comes from a long line
of soldiers.
He certainly has the discipline
of a military man.
Not only was he trained
in the Hunter Military School in Isaia,
he was
one of the top scorers among the fourteen
who graduated.
As Commandos Team Thunder's captain,
he has extensive experience
on the battlefield.
To be honest,
I'd like to have
someone who's as capable
as him
but less conspicuous.
This officer named Tian Yong,
why are his place of birth
and family details
unspecified?
He's an orphan.
He'll be discharged this year.
The paperwork is underway.
What happened to the pregnant woman?
She's in the ER.
She's well into her term.
Tian Yong.
I...
I feel I could've stopped her...
She was bleeding badly.
What if
she gives birth prematurely?
She's a drug dealer.
She shot at you.
You did nothing wrong.
If it weren't for you,
it'd be Xiao Xue
who's in the operating room
right now.
I understand.
I'm just worried about her baby.
Whether it'll
see its mother
when it comes out.
I can't take it.
Lieutenant Tian.
Here.
Please come in.
Yes.
General Conference Room
Chief.
That was a good showing today.
Sir,
I was merely helping
a fellow law enforcer
on the arrest.
Do you know who you arrested?
His name is Li Zhi Peng.
In name,
he's the owner of a youth hostel.
But behind the curtain,
he's a drug dealer.
Do you still remember
the mission at the bar?
I do.
Both parties did not show up
for the deal
and the mission was called off.
Wrong.
They completed their transaction
in Yunshan Tunnel instead.
One of the parties was Li Zhi Peng.
The other party, whom he had
contacted online,
goes by the online ID
of Scary Pirate.
Ever heard of the City of Desire?
It's the biggest
online drug trading platform.
Director,
Tian Yong seldom uses the internet,
let alone the dark web.
So are you familiar with
the Old Master?
Who is that?
Remember the villagers
you captured at the border
with the Border Armed Police?
According to them,
they were coerced into
drug trafficking
by someone
called Old Master.
I don't know him.
Nobody knows who he is.
The man
is highly elusive.
His power spreads across
Southeast Asia.
He's now
the true leader of the
international mercenary group, T4.
Explosives.
Drugs.
Human
and organ trafficking.
If there's money in it,
they'd do it.
They've become a cancer
upon the border.
Three months ago,
we arrested a drug dealer.
His name was Liu Zheng Min.
And it's all
related to the Scary Pirate?
That's right.
We've been
having trouble figuring out
the Scary Pirate's real identity.
But recently,
one of the Old Master's henchmen
approached the police
and offered to become an informant.
Is Old Master the Scary Pirate?
We're still verifying it.
We're going to use
Li Zhi Peng, whom we've captured today,
to contact the Scary Pirate
through the City of Desire,
and tell him
we have a huge amount of cash
that we need moving.
Then?
Then once the target takes the bait,
you'll be their point of contact.
Me?
Yes.
They need someone
with the single combat skills
and field experience
of a special forces soldier
yet do not belong
to the police force.
And my mission is?
Your mission is
to find evidence
that can prove the Scary Pirate's
real identity.
At the same time,
find out the Old Master's whereabouts.
Tian Yong,
any questions?
Feel free to ask.
Chief,
are they the culprits
behind today's incident?
In a certain way,
yes.
I have no other questions.
You must not fail!
Captain,
has Rao Feng come to?
He has.
Take me to him.
What about Tian Yong?
Tian Yong stays here.
He has a new mission.
Alright.
Why did they release me?
They don't have
solid evidence of your crime.
Besides, you're a foreign citizen.
Did you think they were
going to keep you for the New Year?
Even though I'm free,
it doesn't mean I'm safe.
I'm guessing
they'll be watching me 24-7.
We've received the order
to form
a joint task force with
your police department.
The idea
is to cast a wide net,
so we can catch him and the mastermind
in one go.
I'll ask my informants
to give their full support.
Good.
Relax.
We've been under their surveillance
for a couple of days now
and we're perfectly fine.
Any news from Old Master?
Do you know
what happened while you were in
the Public Security Bureau?
Somebody blew up
Liang Mu Ze's neighbourhood.
The Old Master ordered it
despite knowing you were there.
What are you getting at?
Of course, he did it
to get back at the police
for taking his goods.
He doesn't need to care
about the consequences
of ruffling the police's feathers.
After all,
he's abroad.
And to him,
your life
isn't worth a penny.
Guess
what the police
are going to do next?
I'm not going to guess.
And you can stop
trying to turn me against Old Master.
Do you think I'm stupid?
When I joined Old Master,
you were just a little baby.
Let me tell you,
if Old Master finds out
what you're doing behind his back,
you're dead meat.
Rescue Room
Why don't I book a flight
back to Dong'an for you?
No.
Are you okay with
leaving Miss Lan alone at home?
Your grandma and grandpa
are there.
They'll keep her company.
Listen here,
you can't come to Ningjiang
and ruin my day
just to avoid Grandpa, can you?
Why would I avoid him?
It's my house.
Sure, it's your house.
What about your department?
And your project?
You're always here with me.
Don't you have work?
Who do you think I'm doing this for?
Look,
this is about you.
Don't talk about me.
Let me tell you,
ever since you were little,
I've fulfilled every promise
I've made to you, haven't I?
So today, you must promise
to quit right now and move back
to Dong'an.
I will not allow you to see
Liang Mu Ze.
Hey,
what's gotten into you?
Are you having difficulties?
Why are you so stubborn?
Because we're old
and we can't have anything happen to you!
I'll go back to the hotel.
We'll talk when you're off work.
Dad...
Dr Zhang.
Xia Chu.
What happened to the pregnant woman
who lost her baby's pulse yesterday?
The caesarean caused too much bleeding.
The mother passed away,
leaving behind a pair of twins.
Twins?
Yes.
And they're adorable.
But they're showing signs
of neonatal withdrawal syndrome.
We're keeping them in an incubator
and giving them intensive care
and withdrawal treatment.
You may visit them when you're free.
Alright.
I know.
Don't worry.
I've taken the immunoglobulin shot.
Once the results are out,
I'll let you know.
I have work to do.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Xia Chu?
What happened?
The other day
we were operating on Ke Wei.
Turned out
that he had Hepatitis B.
He was writhing about during the surgery,
so we went up and held him down.
His blood was everywhere
and we were close to his body.
Did you get tested?
I had my blood taken.
But the doctor at the
Pathology Department said
even if it turns out negative,
we can't be 100 percent sure.
I have to get tested a few more times.
I was on the phone with my parents.
I couldn't hold it anymore
and told them everything.
But after I did,
I really wish I hadn't.
Ever since I went to university,
I haven't done a thing for my family.
If I'm infected,
what will become of them?
Actually, it could be worse.
After all, during the surgery,
I didn't contact the wound directly.
It's mainly psychological damage.
But poor Dr Zhang,
he was the one who conducted
the surgery.
And
I think he pricked his fingers
with the haemostatic forceps.
What happened to him?
Nothing serious.
But he's always in the operating room
or by the patient's bed.
He's been seeing more patients
than usual.
We're really worried
that he might break down.
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔