Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My Dear Guardian
Episode 26
Are you here looking
for someone of your same kind?
Are you?
What do you think?
Zhuo Ran.
Do you love me?
I understand
your restlessness and loneliness,
as much as I understand myself.
To me, love
isn't that difficult.
It's just like...
Like what?
Dad.
Mum.
Meng Zhen.
Let's eat.
I want to drink it.
Xiao Jun, eat up.
It's okay, he can have it.
It helps in digestion.
Here.
Take it.
Try it to see if it's delicious.
I don't like eggplant.
Xiao Jun, don't be rude.
Zhang Yi Chi loves eggplant.
When I was hospitalised,
I saw him ordering
braised eggplant with rice.
Xiao Jun
has good memories.
It's not good to be a picky eater.
Here, let's dig in.
Here.
Okay.
Well...
Meng Zhen.
What do you do for a living?
I own a bookstore.
I also sell clothes
that I design on my own
and some stationary.
You're self-employed.
Back in the university,
which course did you major in?
I majored in Dramatic Literature.
After graduating from the university,
I went back to my hometown and
joined an opera troupe as a screenwriter.
I think it's fate.
I decided to stay in Ningjiang.
In the end, I set up the bookstore
and met my late husband.
Your late husband?
He's a military officer.
He sacrificed in a battle eight years ago.
It's not easy to be you.
It's all right.
Dad.
Meng Zhen
is the most talented
among my female friends.
Furthermore,
she knows how to live a good life.
I bet you live under stress.
Everyone lives under stress these days.
For example, in the hospital,
those residents who work under me
usually resign within three years.
Do you know why?
Their job is tiring and worse,
they don't make much from it.
Their income
is not as much as self-employed.
If the job is so terrible,
why don't you change jobs
and become a bookseller too?
You don't say.
It's crossed my mind before.
Meng Zhen.
Are you hiring?
Stop joking.
You're a cardiac surgeon.
Don't put yourself on a job
unworthy of your talents.
What are you talking about?
To be frank,
everyone can be a master
in their own special field.
There is
neither lowliness nor nobleness
in careers.
Be it a doctor
or a self-employed bookstore owner,
I think
it's just a job anyway.
Am I right, dad?
Here.
Try the braised eggplant.
Try it.
Here.
It's your son's favourite.
Here, try it.
Mum, I need to use the washroom.
Sure, let me show you the way.
I can show him the way.
It's okay. I know the way.
Sit down.
Even if you don't want
to date someone of the same profession,
you can find someone
from another profession.
She could be a banker,
a teacher,
or a government servant.
We have introduced so many ladies to you.
Any of them is a good catch.
How aren't you fond of them?
Look at you.
You're after a lady
who got married before.
She has a son too.
What's wrong with
a lady who got married before?
What's wrong with that?
Mum, what's wrong with you?
Are you here to mess things up?
Mum.
Have you washed your hands?
Yes.
Let's go.
Mum.
I shouldn't have come with you, right?
No.
Why do you think so?
I can feel that
the old lady doesn't like me.
What makes you feel so?
She said that I'm not good.
You've misunderstood.
She doesn't mean that.
She thinks that it's not good
to be a picky eater.
Look, you're still young, right?
You're growing.
How do you grow up
if you are fussy about food?
She said that out of concern.
I criticise you at times too, right?
However, I'll always love you.
Am I right?
Stop thinking too much. Let's go.
If only I was not born.
Xiao Jun.
Listen carefully.
To me,
you're the most important.
I don't mind losing everything
but I can't afford to lose you.
Do you get it?
Yes.
That's great.
Be happy.
Let's go.
Listen.
For example, in the hospital,
the best surgeon
is not necessarily the most popular.
The person who suits me the best
is not necessarily a catch.
You're paranoid
because I don't have a girlfriend.
When I finally date someone,
you're being fussy.
I'm already 38 years old.
Of course.
I'm not compromising
because I'm getting old.
That's because Meng Zhen is outstanding.
She's really outstanding.
You haven't discovered that side of her.
It's destiny.
I accept my fate.
In that case,
you're ready to be a stepfather.
Xiao Jun is a good boy.
That's irrelevant.
Moving forward,
if you marry his mum,
you'll have a son all of a sudden.
It's not about living together
for a short period of time.
You'll have to live together
day in and day out.
It could be a few years
or a few decades.
Both of you are not blood related.
Are you sure
you can be responsible to him
as a stepfather?
Also,
moving forward,
you will have your own child.
You will have two children in total.
Are you sure when the time comes,
you can
be fair to both of them?
Xiao Jun.
You're back.
Xiao Jun has to go to school tomorrow.
He can't stay up.
I'm bringing him home.
Enjoy the food.
Let me send you.
It's okay. We can go back on our own.
Let's go.
Xiao Chi!
I'm full.
You!
Meng Zhen.
Let me send you.
It's okay.
We can go back on our own.
By the way,
I've transferred the money
for the present to you.
Thank you
for preparing the present
on behalf of me.
What is going on?
Let's go.
Let me send you.
It's okay.
It'll be difficult to drop the habit
once it becomes one.
Then, I'll just keep the habit.
When your dad asked you the question,
you hesitated,
didn't you?
I'm a mother with a son.
Hence, I can understand
your parent's feelings.
They just want to protect their son
and give what's best to their son.
It's understandable.
Therefore,
please understand my feelings too.
As for our relationship,
please give it some thought.
Both of us should give it some thought.
What do you think?
Xiao Jun, say goodbye to Yi Chi.
Goodbye.
We're leaving.
Are you hungry?
Here.
It's time to eat.
Eat up.
What's wrong?
Give me a shave.
Didn't you complain that it's prickly?
Give you a shave?
Can't you do it on your own?
I can't do it.
Why?
I'm injured.
Where did you hurt yourself?
It's over here.
Let me see.
Is it painful?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Give me a shave.
Okay.
I'll do it for you.
You're quite good at shaving.
Have you done it before?
For who?
Zhuo Ran?
I did it for patients.
When I worked at
the general surgery department,
I was in charge of skin preparation
before surgery was conducted.
It lasted for a month.
Making you shave
is a waste of your talents.
Thank you, Liang Mu Ze.
What for?
Thank you for carrying me back home.
I didn't know that
you've injured yourself.
I chose to carry you on my back.
I hit you too.
Is it painful?
Yes.
What should I do?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You've hit me anyway.
What's the point of telling you?
Well...
How should I make up to you?
You are already making up to me.
It would be better
if you could take it more seriously.
No matter what,
I still want to thank you.
If you didn't appear today,
I would be put through
a more awkward situation.
Are you sure you're only awkward today?
You can say whatever you want.
It's done, Captain Liang.
Are you happy with it?
Not bad, at least you didn't injure me.
Perhaps you're right.
There is nevertheless
a gap of eight years.
Many things have changed.
Example?
Zhuo Ran admitted that
he installed the tapping device.
I knew it from the beginning.
You knew it?
My understanding of Zhuo Ran
is beyond your imagination.
You won, Liang Mu Ze.
Like I said, I don't care about winning.
I care about the people.
It's for you.
What a cute keychain.
Where did you get it?
I made it.
You?
You know how to make this?
Do you like it?
I like anything that comes from you.
If that's the case, keep it properly.
Don't lose it.
Got it?
Sure.
Xia Chu.
The person who attempted to kidnap you
has been arrested by the police.
However, you have to be careful.
Stay vigilant.
Especially...
What?
Don't meet up with Zhuo Ran alone.
It's for your own good.
Got it.
I instructed my secretary
to get you a set of lingerie
based on your size.
She will send it here later.
Do you mind?
She's your secretary.
It's okay so long as you don't mind.
What are you doing?
I've set up a public account
and it's ready to be published.
I didn't know that
you have a public account.
It's done.
I'm going to blow dry my hair.
The hair dryer...
I want to read your article.
I'm giving you access.
From now on,
you're the co-admin of my public account.
If I don't have the time,
you may publish posts on my behalf.
Aren't you worried that
I may mess things up?
No.
To you,
I've never been on my guard.
How about you?
Zhuo Ran.
Rao Zhi.
Long Yi's lawyer is here
demanding him to be released right away.
Rao Zhi!
Call the ambulance!
I'm here. Don't be scared.
I'm here.
Rao Zhi.
The test result is out.
Long Yi is the suspect,
Xiao Yang.
He underwent plastic surgeries.
Rao Zhi!
Please calm down.
Stop Rao Zhi!
Don't let him go into
the interrogation chamber!
Rao Zhi!
Lock up the investigation chamber!
-Rao Zhi!
-Calm down, Rao Zhi!
Stay aside!
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Rao Feng.
You're a veteran police officer.
I don't have to tell you everything
because you should have known it.
You are not allowed to touch him.
Why?
Now, the only evidence in our hands
is the testimony
given by Zhuo Ran against him.
However,
the credibility of the testimony
is uncertain.
He's the legal representative
of the 3D Printing Company.
We found a 3D printed mask
near the black maple forest.
Soon after,
he followed Xia Chu
in an attempt to kidnap her.
He also appeared
in the jungle along the border
where drug dealers meet.
The 3D printed mask was broken.
We were unable
to retrieve his fingerprints
from the mask.
As such,
everything that you said
is only our assumptions.
It can't be considered as evidence.
Furthermore,
the real culprit
has not fallen into the trap.
How about my daughter?
That scum has destroyed my family!
Ever since Xiao Xue met with that
mishap at the age of 13,
every day,
I woke up in fear
from the nightmare. Do you know that?
I've stopped drinking beer.
I don't have the guts to drink anymore.
Do you know why?
That's because when I see the bottles,
I would be reminded
of how the bottles
were stuck in my daughter's body!
She was only 13 years old.
The doctor said that
the injury would never recover.
It would never recover
for the rest of her life.
My wife...
No, I mean my ex-wife.
She divorced me because of that.
She said she wished she'd never met me.
My daughter...
I could have taken good care of them.
But I couldn't do that!
I could only send them far away from me.
They have to stay away from me.
My daughter called me cold-blooded.
She said that I'm an irresponsible father.
Do you think I'm irresponsible?
Am I?
I know.
I'm a police officer.
As I'm wearing the uniform,
I have to be a role model.
I deserve to be punished
when I violate the rules and regulations.
I acknowledge that. I accept that.
However, Xiao Xue is my daughter!
I would risk my life to protect her!
Do you know that, Director?
Ever since Xiao Xue and her mum left,
I've officially died inside.
The only motivation that keeps me living
is to arrest that scum!
No matter how far I have to go,
I have to ensure that
I rope him up and wheel him to justice!
I'm not going to forgive him.
I'm not going to be generous!
Only by doing so
can I continue living. Do you know that?
Now, the person
who harmed my daughter is back.
He's just right in front of me.
His hands are full of my daughter's blood.
Yet, you told me not to touch him?
You even want me to let go of him?
I can't do it!
Officer 052326.
The detention period of Rao Feng,
Captain of the Criminal Investigation
Division of the Public Security Bureau
is up.
Let him go.
Yes.
I don't want to leave! I want
to see Tian Yong undergoing training!
I want to see Tian Yong
undergoing training!
Stop it!
Listen.
You have two choices.
It's either you stay at home
or you will be sent back
with the army truck.
Why can't I watch the training?
It's not confidential.
I just want
to see how iron men are trained.
No way.
Why?
You're affecting Tian Yong's performance.
I...
Are you still in a cold war with your dad?
It's none of your business.
Stop calling me, will you?
Delivery?
I'm not at home at the moment.
I gave you the address?
Will you please place it in the cabinet?
I'll get the parcel when I'm back.
All right, thank you.
Sorry for the trouble.
Well...
Can I go home now?
Have you thought it through?
I need to get my parcel.
When did she leave?
I think it's almost time.
I think I could run into her
if I go there now.
Sure.
Thanks, Mu Ze.
Are we heading to Cambridge Bay?
When is your wife's baby due?
When is the expected date?
It's been a few days late.
My mother-in-law told me
when she's pregnant with my wife,
she got into labour a few days late too.
When my wife gave birth to Xiao Xue,
she got into labour late too.
I think it's normal
when the baby is a girl.
Does that mean those
who are pregnant with a baby boy
will deliver earlier than expected?
I mean, my ex wife.
Listen,
when you have become a dad,
you must prioritise your wife and child.
Keep them company whenever you have time.
I know that.
Knowing it isn't sufficient.
You need to do it.
Listen.
Children grow up in a blink of an eye.
When you're ready to keep them company,
they've already grown up.
It's too late by then.
Especially when you have a daughter...
Rao Zhi.
When you reach there,
spend time with your daughter.
Don't think about other things.
I'll be waiting for you at the entrance.
Just give me a call if anything.
I'll be there anytime.
Is it nice?
Liang Shao Xue.
You have such a great taste.
Hello.
Hello, I have a parcel for Xia Chu.
Please pick up the parcel
at the pick up point now.
Are you going out?
I'm going to collect a parcel.
Are you going to
the pick up point at the entrance?
Li Lei is there.
I'll get him
to collect the parcel for you.
Hold on, Xiao Xue.
Li Lei.
Please collect a parcel for me...
Did I say I wanted someone
to collect it for me?
Did you ask me first?
No.
Xiao Xue, I thought...
You thought...
You always do everything on your own will.
You've never cared about my opinion.
Xiao Xue, let's go together.
Stop following me!
You're so irritating!
It must be Liang Mu Ze again.
It's nothing to do with him.
Even if he didn't tell me,
I could trace you too.
Stop looking for me!
It's pointless.
I won't tell you
what happened in the tunnel the other day.
It's okay.
However, you must protect yourself.
In the future, avoid going to
places like Yunshan Tunnel.
Don't tell anyone
you went there on that night.
Don't tell others that I'm your dad.
Leave this place
when you have had your fun.
Go back to your mum.
Okay?
No!
You refuse to acknowledge me.
Why should I listen to you?
Why should I?
Xiao Xue!
Will you stop following me?
I really hate you.
Hello, I'm here
to collect Xia Chu's parcel.
Are you Xia Chu?
No.
I'm her housemate.
You called me earlier.
Is this seafood?
Yes.
Please show me the inside.
Hurry up.
Fine.
I'll examine it when I reach home.
What are you doing?
Wake up.
Please don't just lie on the ground.
Wake up!
Help!
Village Chief.
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Rescue Room
Why are you rescuing him?
Please calm down.
Let him die!
Why did you do that to my dad?
-You're such a scum!
-Please calm down.
Scum!
Why did you do that to my dad?
Return my dad to me!
Xiao Xue, calm down please.
Why are you rescuing a murderer?
He is now a witness!
Teng.
Give it to me, Teng.
When can we meet again?
Way to go, Xiang Yang.
You're engaged in online dating.
Take it.
Let me do it on my own.
We're bringing you breaking news.
A serious explosion took place
at Cambridge Bay in the morning.
The casualties are pending confirmation.
According to the residents,
the explosion gave forth
a tremendous sound.
At the moment, police officers,
firemen and medical officers
have rushed to the scene.
The number of casualties
will be ascertained later.
Attention!
I saw the news.
The Public Security Bureau
just gave me a call.
Liang Mu Ze.
Yes!
Go to the hospital
to check on the situation.
Yes!
Tian Yong.
You should tag along.
Yes!
Ms Gu!
Village Chief.
Director Mi.
Have you found Ke Wei?
Not yet.
We tried to reach him through phone.
A few days ago, there were still signals.
Now, we couldn't reach him at all.
Before he left,
did he say anything
or mention any place?
My grandson is a good boy.
He seldom talks.
Did he behave abnormally?
No.
He did.
He refused to sleep.
It's like this.
Lately,
he's obsessed with computer games.
Qian Rong,
who is his mum,
paid him a visit a few days ago.
She gave him a laptop.
He's so excited.
He couldn't stop playing on the laptop.
Where is the laptop?
Please show it to me.
Well...
This lady...
Who is she?
Report to the police.
I've pasted
the documents for you.
Thank you.
This is another set of documents.
I need Professor Tang's help
to improvise it.
Your main goal
in asking me to do all these
is not to build a factory in Dong'an.
Your main goal
is to obtain project information
for the other companies, right?
Is there any difference?
I just want to focus on research.
I don't want to be a commercial spy.
Your salary for the month
has been transferred to your bank account.
Where did you get the particulars?
I have a way to obtain it.
Professor Xia, good day.
I'm Zhuo Ran.
I saw on the news that
an explosion took place
in Xia Chu's neighbourhood.
Did she contact you?
Is she okay?
Lan Zi Yu!
What's wrong?
Is Xia Chu living at Cambridge Bay?
You mean Ningjiang?
Yes, her house in Ningjiang.
Yes, what's wrong?
Is she staying together
with Liang Mu Ze?
She rented a room at his place.
Furthermore, Liang Mu Ze
usually stays in the military camp.
Why are you shouting?
Just how many things
are you hiding from me?
Will he die?
I can't give you any confirmation on that
but please trust us.
Xiao Xue!
Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔