[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 17]
Mr. Zhou, thank you for arranging meals and accommodation for us.
You all came from afar
to help me solve this problem of repairing the bridge.
Of course the county government should arrange for you.
Mr. Zhou, then I'll be frank with you.
This was the Xu's stockade's fault.
They are supposed to pay
half of the money.
Didn't Mr. Zhou
talk to Chief Xu in private?
Of course I know who's right and who's wrong.
But
I have paid my visit to the Xu's stockade for not less than ten times.
I just couldn't communicate with them.
But you are the county magistrate.
How could a chief dare not listen to you?
Miss, what does that mean?
Although I'm the county magistrate,
I also have to think for the people.
I can't take the officials
to force the people to pay the money, right?
If so, I'll become a so-called robber.
It's quite a tough job for you, Mr. Zhou.
I've been an official for more than ten years.
I've never met
such a difficult matter.
How about this?
I think Mr. Zhou
was quite annoyed by them today.
Since we came here from Lin'an,
we will get this problem solved.
Just leave it to us.
As soon as we figure out a way,
we will inform you right away.
If you think it's OK,
we’ll discuss it with the people in two stockades.
[The Xu's Stockade]
Boss Luo,
What do you think... You!
Me?
Follow me.
She must think Boss Luo is here to ask for the money.
That is the reason why we came.
Let's go and have a look.
Here.
Whether it's the distance from the bridge downstream
or the width of the river,
it's the most suitable of all.
Look.
What is that?
I think someone had set up a Sand Filtration Floodgate here.
Come here.
Come.
It seems like someone had pulled it out of the water.
So weird. Who would do such a thing?
If we don't pull it out,
are we just going to let the fish die?
Sir, what do you mean?
The Sand Filtration Floodgate...
I don't care about what a Sand Filtration Floodgate is.
The people of the Zhang's stockade
are always gonna pull it out every time we see it.
Wait a minute.
Are you also going to make
such things that could do harm to people's life?
We...
It's fine.
Sir, we want to see Chief Zhang
to get some information about the situation.
Could you please you show us a way?
We want to see him.
All of you, get up!
So it’s a trap.
Wang Sheng,
you must protect everyone later.
Miss Han.
You need to run first if we start a fight.
I won't be a burden.
Come, have a seat.
OK. Come.
I know why you are here.
It’s just that if you want to see Chief Xu,
it’s not that easy.
You should have a drink with our fellows first.
Come on. Drink up.
Niaoniao, don't force yourself to drink.
If I can't drink any more,
Boss Luo, you can drink it for me then.
If we can't get the fish out,
they will stink in the pond.
You have to think of a way.
Yes, you should.
The fish really are going to stink.
Enough.
Didn't the new craftsmen team say
they would come up with a solution in three days?
I don't trust any craftsmen team.
You know how many fish were killed
by the last craftsmen team.
You go find the chief yourself.
I'm going home to be with my wife.
Look, here she is.
Let's go.
Chief Zhang.
Guys.
What's going on?
Don't mention it. Tell me.
How are you going to repair the bridge?
Of course we will repair the bridge.
But we came to Chief Zhang today
only to ask
if we can build a Sand Filtration Floodgate
in the river outside the village.
What?
Another Sand Filtration Floodgate?
No! Absolutely no!
No way!
You can't build the Sand Filtration Floodgate.
Five years ago, when the bridge was built,
we also set one up then.
But the silt was too thick.
The fish could not live in the water then at all.
For a whole year,
the Zhang's stockade made a bare living by borrowing money.
We suffered a great loss.
So you mean
you removed the original Sand Filtration Floodgate?
That’s not a Sand Filtration Floodgate.
It's a Man Killing Floodgate.
It was ruining the lives of the people in the Zhang's stockade.
But just because
you removed the Sand Filtration Floodgate,
the wooden bridge collapsed, right?
You can't blame it on us.
Frankly speaking,
we'll pay for the bridge construction,
only if the Xu's stockade pays half of it.
Otherwise, you can leave as soon as possible.
Let's go.
Leave Jinnan as soon as possible.
OK.
We’ll leave now.
Let's go.
Come on.
Brothers, come on.
Drink up.
Fill it up.
Drink.
Drink up!
Mine's empty.
Here, fill it up.
Cheers.
Alright, stop drinking.
Boss Luo,
you have a high tolerance.
It seems like your wife also has a high tolerance.
How could you tell?
Besides,
inside the stockade besides Chief Xu,
I’m afraid only I know her best.
Boss Luo.
That’s it for today.
If you have any questions,
just ask me.
Oh no.
I really can’t remember the way.
Li Qingfeng, you need to think of a way!
We are really lost.
Didn't you say you would take me to look for the way?
What did you take me here for?
What are you planning to do?
You're being sarcastic to me.
It seems that the two of us
are going to spend the night in the forest.
I don't want to.
It's so dark that I can see nothing.
What are you looking at?
Wait for me. I’ll get some light for you.
Boss Luo. Come here.
What are you doing? Carry her.
[Avoidance Silence]
Slowly.
Go back and have a good rest.
Let's go, Niaoniao.
You can't drink as much as I do. You can't beat me.
That's all he's got.
Go back and rest.
Go.
Go...
Niaoniao, you should get some sleep.
Slowly.
[Silence Avoidance]
Boss Luo, how about I helping you go back as well?
Be careful.
You don't have to.
Where's Architect Chen?
Miss...
We went to the upper reaches together.
Then we met a fisherman
saying he would take them to the Zhang's stockade.
Then they let me come back by myself.
I really shouldn't have
left her and come back myself.
Don't worry. I'll go find them.
[Silence Avoidance]
So pretty!
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
♫The moon hidden in the boundless night sky♫
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
♫You are the starry night sky♫
What's wrong?
♫Every single word♫
Nothing.
Are you cold?
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
Now I'm not cold any more.
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
♫Not knowing why♫
♫Just let it pass by♫
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
What kind of bird is chirping?
♫From dark night to dawn♫
It must be...
♫Stars have sunk into the sea♫
It must be the kind that only Jinnan has.
♫And I only want to belong to you♫
I knew it.
Architects. Let’s go back to the official hotel.
Our chief executive really is resourceful.
By the way,
how did it go with the Xu's stockade today?
It's a long story.
Let's go back first.
Qingfeng.
[Impartiality And Integrity]
Here.
I’ve asked Luo and Wang Sheng
to buy medicine for you.
One pack is to dispel their hangover.
and one is for you to dispel coldness.
Here.
This is the ginger soup for you.
Drink it.
By the way,
where are the files Luo organized?
I want to look at them.
You've taken the medicine.
You should rest early today.
But I still want to find a solution as soon as possible.
Stinky wood.
Why don't you listen to me still
like always?
OK, I’ll listen to you.
I'll rest early.
OK. Sleep early.
I’ll go back to my room.
My light.
Can you warm me up?
They depend on the river to change the water in the fish pond.
And the best part to set up the Sand Filtration Floodgate
is just near the fish pond of the Zhang's stockade.
If we set up a Sand Filtration Floodgate,
there must be a lot of mud and sand silting in the river.
In that case,
the fish pond of the Zhang's stockade will be ruined.
I see.
So the Zhang's stockade should be responsible
for the collapse of the bridge?
But the law works for human relations.
Besides, the fish pond is the bloodline of the Zhang's stockade.
They had no other ways.
How can we blame them?
Is there any other way?
There's only one way.
Make the bridge more stable.
In this way, even if there isn't a Sand Filtration Floodgate,
the bridge can stand still.
But if we do so,
the project will become much more difficult
and we'll be needing more money.
It’s a lot of trouble.
It is always a lot of trouble when it comes to money.
The Xu's stockade still refuses to pay?
Actually, Chief Xu
is not unreasonable.
It's just that these years
they have earned little money from the harvests.
It's gonna cost thousands of taels to repair the bridge.
They really can't afford it.
I also inquired about it.
They could only afford 500 taels at most.
That's why they insisted
to pay half the money the Zhang's stockade pays.
What should we do?
In this case,
the Xu's stockade should offer 500 taels
and the Zhang's stockade should offer 1,000 taels.
It's 1,500 taels in total.
Miss, is it enough?
It is enough for a wooden bridge.
But if the Xu's stockade offers 500 taels,
why would the Zhang's stockade be willing to offer 1,000 taels?
You're right.
I remember yesterday Chief Xu said that
no matter how much money was needed,
they would only pay 33 percent of it
and the Zhang's stockade should pay the rest 66 percent.
It seems to be an impasse.
Qingfeng.
if we want to build a firm stone bridge,
how much would it cost?
At least
5,000 taels.
That...That is too much.
Even if I'm so merciful,
I don't have that much money.
So that's the problem of the Ministry of Works.
In my opinion,
let’s go back to Lin’an.
Luo, do you have the files?
I gave them to Her Lady.
Do you have an idea?
Not yet.
I'll go back to sleep.
If you need me to start work,
Luo, come wake me up then.
Well,
I’ll go back and have some sleep.
Enjoy your meal.
[County Government of Jinnan]
Come in.
Architect Li, your medicine is ready.
Drink it soon. It can dispel coldness and remove the body moisture.
Okay, leave it here.
Why just leave it here?
Here.
Drink the medicine first.
Finish it yourself.
Here.
Luo, it’s late.
Go back to your room and rest.
OK.
In this situation,
it's useless to go through these.
In fact, every project has its own problems.
But until the last moment,
as architects,
we can't stop doing what we are supposed to do.
If we can find a way to save money to build the bridge,
everything will be solved.
That's right.
So we can't let
other factors that are not included in the project
affect our judgment.
We should calm down and pay more attention.
That's how we can find inspiration.
I was right about you.
Do you know that
I didn't come to the Wood Feather House
to be an architect?
Can you guess my original intention?
I don't know.
I came to learn from you.
You must be so happy to hear that, right?
Actually, I don't want to be your master.
Don't be ungrateful!
You misunderstood me. That's not what I mean.
Then what...
You are so annoying.
Sir, are you asleep?
Not yet.
Come in.
Are you still not feeling well?
I want to die.
Don’t take it seriously.
What’s the matter?
Your clothes are dirty.
Since Mr. Wang took them off for you last night,
they've been placed here.
I'll go have them washed.
I don't want you to do this.
You can just throw away the dirty clothes. You don't have to be so busy.
Why throw them away if you can still wear them?
You are not a maid when you're with me.
Put them down.
In this case,
won't we be needing a lot of stones for the construction?
Even so,
I'm still worried that the bridge is not strong enough.
Are we really doing a losing business?
Five thousand taels is too much.
And construction isn't doing charity.
Let alone Luo,
I’m afraid Miss Zhao would lose too much for this.
Maybe can you make it 1000 taels?
I'm also thinking
if there is a way to save costs.
What's wrong?
This medicine works like sleeping drugs.
You have caught a cold.
You ought to have a good rest.
Maybe this is the sleeping drug
for you to get some sleep.
It’s late.
You should go back to your room and rest.
Otherwise are you going to make a bunch of stones out of thin air?
Fine.
Why are you staring at me?
Maybe we can really make a bunch of stones.
Did the fever really make you dizzy?
Think about
what the place where we're staying has.
You mean...
Yes, let's go.
Look.
Li Qingfeng,
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
I want to confess something to you.
Actually,
♫I feel so safe♫
I'm the Princess Zhaohe of the the Xiao Dynasty.
♫My dreams are all about you♫
Don't blame me for hiding it from you.
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
His Majesty wants to marry me to the Northern Zhou.
♫Just want to meet you again♫
I don't know how to tell you this.
♫I am so lucky♫
♫You did not give up♫
But I promise you.
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
I will stay.
♫You'll show me the world♫
I will stay in Xiao,
in Lin'an,
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
in the Wood Feather House
and stay with you.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
♫Ask your heart♫
I will be your deputy architect.
I will be
♫Even if only a drop♫
your wife.
♫A drop, a drop♫
♫A drop of love is left♫
♫I would love to♫
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
♫I feel so safe♫
♫My dreams are all about you♫
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
♫Just want to meet you again♫
♫I am so lucky♫
♫You did not give up♫
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
♫You'll show me the world♫
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
♫Ask your heart♫
Li Qingfeng, stop right there!
Aren't you gonna say something?
I don't know why I slept in her room last night.
But nothing happened between us.
You forgot how you got out?
How can I believe you?
I passed out after taking the medicine last night
and remembered nothing.
It's not like what you imagined.
What medicine could make you take off your clothes?
I'm afraid it was aphrodisiac you took!
You are slandering Langyue.
So you mean I woke up and ate a bun
just to slander master?
And you slept in her room for a whole night
but you're innocent?
If you don't believe me, go ask her.
If there's nothing else, I'll go back.
I'm not done yet.
Li Qingfeng,
since the first day I came to the Wood Feather House,
I have disliked you.
But I said nothing for master's sake.
Later, she got blind.
That's a bit inappropriate.
Anyway, she then started to have feelings for you.
My...My heart hurts.
But for the sake of master's happiness, I endured it.
Now,
how dare you do that to master?
You're so dead.
Official Meng, let me say it again.
Nothing really happened between us.
Even if anything did happen,
I will take my responsibility for it.
Take your responsibility? How?
Can you afford to take the responsibility?
In my mind, I've decided to marry Langyue.
Why can't I afford to take the responsibility?
You idiot.
Do you know who she is?
Good luck to you!
Who is it?
Master, it's me.
Come in.
Master, how dare Li Qingfeng did that to you?
What are you thinking?
It's just that he caught a cold last night
and slept in my room after taking the medicine.
Last night,
I slept in Luo’s room.
I came back this morning.
You can ask Luo if you don’t believe me.
You're just worrying for nothing.
Did you misunderstand Li Qingfeng again
and say something bad to him?
I didn't say anything I think.
Just two men talked to each other.
It's nothing.
You just can't get rid of that precipitance of yours.
Master, it really is not because of my precipitance.
I saw him come out of your room myself.
He doesn't know who you really are.
I'm just afraid he'll get beheaded.
Who dares to do so?
Master, you can't keep pretending to be ignorant.
He harassed the princess before he became the princess consort.
Can...Can you call that a trivial matter?
Since you said so,
I'll just let him be the princess consort.
I'm not stupid.
It's not up to you
whether he can be the princess consort or not.
You... You don't need to worry about that.
By the way,
since you're here,
I have something to talk to you.
Talk?
About what?
About you and Luo.
Luo and I?
I heard you were drunk yesterday.
Luo took care of you all day, right?
But nothing happened between us.
I believe you.
I just think that
Luo likes you.
Are you looking down on her
because she's just my maid?
How is that possible?
Luo is so cute and well-behaved,
even my mom likes her.
Why would I ever look down on her?
If so,
tell me, do you like Luo?
Master, stop making fun of me.
You're just making a casual match.
You're the one I like.
For so many years...
Then why haven't you
done anything to get in the way of us?
I thought
you have realized
that the person you love is not me any more.
Of course not.
Then what is it?
I know he can't be the princess consort.
Let me tell you the real reason.
I’m not the one you love any more.
But Luo is.
Master, are you...
Are you infected by Li Qingfeng?
Why are you talking nonsense?
Think about it.
Are you happy with me
or are you happy with Luo?
After all, you are the...
It has nothing to do with my identity.
I know you are good to me.
But
I always think
it is just an obsessiveness in your heart.
We grew up together.
In your heart, I'm just your playmate.
The happiness we share together
exists in memories more than in the present, doesn't it?
I often think of
the days we used to play together in the Ministry of Works.
So,
in your heart,
I'm just a playmate when we were young.
And now,
you need to find the one who will accompany you all your life.
That person is Luo.
Luo?
I've always seen Luo as my sister.
Think about it.
During the time in the Wood Feather House,
who is the one you feel happiest,
most relaxed and most carefree with?
Of course it's...
[A Bright Mirror Hung High]
But Chief Xu said
they could afford at most 500 taels.
I asked a lot of craftsmen teams in private.
Without six thousand taels,
I'm afraid the project can't be done.
Of course we know that.
So we came here today
to ask Mr. Zhou
if the government has the money to deal with the fund shortage.
I'm a noble official.
I...I don't...
Sir, don't get all worked up.
Qingfeng, you talk to Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou.
Yesterday Architect Chen and I
figured out a solution together,
which will only cost 1000 taels.
Maybe we could give it a try.
[A Bright Mirror Hung High]
I'm all ears.
There are two aspects that's gonna cost us the most money on the construction.
One is work force and the other is material.
Therefore, I need the two stockades
to offer me some work force for me to dispatch.
Besides,
there is also a solution to the problem of material.
Don't worry. As long as it is for repairing the bridge,
I can get people to come and help.
But how are you going to save the materials?
I want to bomb the mountain to get the stones.
No, you can't do that.
Why?
To be honest,
Jinnan County
has relied on the mountains and waters since ancient times.
We respect and admire the God of Mountain
and the God of River greatly.
If you really bomb the mountain,
I'm afraid before the bridge is built,
[A Bright Mirror Hung High]
Jinnan County will be in chaos.
It's just inappropriate.
But this is the only way
to save money.
Guys, I still find it inappropriate.
Tomorrow is the deadline.
How about
giving it a second thought?
Please.
Let's eat first.
Actually, it's nothing.
We can just take it as a three-day tour in Jinnan County.
Jinnan County has the best natural resources.
There must be a lot of beautiful scenery and delicious food.
Don't be in such low spirits, you all.
Why don't we take a break
and go out for a walk?
I'll discuss it with the chiefs tomorrow.
Maybe they are not as stubborn as the county magistrate said.
Things will work out themselves.
There are always good ideas.
I think Boss Luo is right.
The day before yesterday
when we visited the Xu's stockade, they were not that rude.
You were so drunk that day.
How could you have remembered even if they were rude?
Meng Yuanxu. How are you not embarrassed to say that about Niaoniao?
Luo, thank you anyway.
Alright.
Let's eat first.
Let's talk after dinner.
Right.
Let's eat first.
Is there anything more important than eating?
Anyway,
I have to get the project done.
I can see that. I also want to.
Some time ago, Langyue was full of worries.
She was not happy until we came to Jinnan.
She promised me
she would come home with me after finishing the work in Jinnan.
So I want to do it well.
What about her true identity...
I don't care about that any more.
I will find out about it sooner or later.
Right.
When two people are together,
happiness is the most important.
I'll take Langyue to see Master Yu today
and ask him if there is a good way to save costs.
We might not come back tonight.
Don't worry about us.
OK. You can just go.
As long as you can come back
before the meeting with the two chiefs
tomorrow.
[Master]
[Luo]
Sir, this is what you taught me.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, what wish did you make?
[Luo]
Master Yu.
Qingfeng.
You are here too.
Master Yu, long time no see.
Yes.
You two are here
to send me the wedding invitation, right?
Master Yu.
I really have a difficulty this time.
You brat.
I don't care about your problem.
I only care about when you two
are going to send me the invitation.
After this problem is solved.
You...
You are so cunning.
Don't beat around the bush with me.
OK. Go ahead.
What's the problem?
We are going to build a bridge in Jinnan County.
Why are you the one to deal with such a difficult problem?
Master Yu, you know about it?
Yes.
OK. Let's sit down and talk.
What do you think, Master Yu?
Can this work?
Wait.
No, it can't work.
Why not?
I know.
Bombing the mountain to get the stones
is a very clever way to save costs.
But you just said you couldn't set up the Sand Filtration Floodgate.
Then you must make the bridge
bigger and firmer,
which means more stone materials will be needed.
There's one thing you might not take into consideration.
The stones you get from the explosion
must be polished before using.
If you want to polish them,
you'll need stonemasons
to do the job.
Even if you call on all the stonemasons in Jinnan County,
they are still not enough for you.
And then you'll have to call on more stonemasons to come from Lin'an.
In this way, the cost will be increased.
Not to mention 1,000 taels,
it's still impossible to add 1,000 more.
But
traveling around these years,
I've seen a lot of
uncanny but fine water conservancy projects.
Let me try to recollect
if there's anything I can take example by.
Thank you so much.
In Ningbo, Zhejiang,
there is a Tashan Weir.
It was built by a county magistrate in the Tang Dynasty.
Nope.
It's a project that resists the intrusion of sea tides
and diverts fresh water from inland rivers for irrigation,
which is very different from your bridge.
What else?
Shanxi!
There's a Zhengguo Canal in Jingyang, Shanxi.
Still nope.
It's also used for diversion irrigation.
And Guangxi!
there's a Qinzao Canal in Xing'an County, Guangxi.
Can we take example by it?
Still no.
Sichuan! Sichuan has a Dujiangyan Irrigation System.
Let me tell you.
The scenery there is so beautiful.
It's everywhere.
Very beautiful.
I... Master Yu.
Stop showing off
your experiences of traveling around the world.
Tell us
if there is anything we can learn from.
Don't get all worked up.
Calm down. Give me a moment.
I got it.
There is a Lancang River in Yunnan.
I once saw
a unique way to cross the river there.
I called it the River Crossing Cable Bridge.
What is that?
It's actually very simple.
Look.
This is a river.
All you need to do on either side of the river,
which is here,
here, here and here,
is to set up four giant stelae that are at least three feet tall.
And then
use a lot of stones
to fix the bottoms of the stelae.
And then
connect the two stelae with a chain.
A chain.
And put an iron ring on this chain.
These iron rings are used for fixing ships.
In this case,
no matter how fast the river runs,
people can cross the river safely.
But if the rain is too heavy
and the water level exceeds the water line,
then don't take the chance to cross the river.
Nice. It can definitely work.
Now 1,000 taels is gonna be enough.
As long as it can solve the problem,
this River Crossing Cable Bridge is also a bridge.
This is the only solution for now.
If not,
that 1000 taels
is never going to be enough to repair the bridge.
But I have to remind you.
Jinnan County is different from Lin'an City.
Everyone in Jinnan County
believes in the God of Mountain.
If you want to explode the mountain and take the stones,
you should be mentally prepared
that they might not agree with this.
Don't worry.
We have Boss Luo
who is very eloquent.
By then,
he will convince those two chiefs.
Really?
That’s awesome.
You young people are all talented.
Here.
Today I'm gonna make a toast with tea instead of wine
to wish you success.
Cheers.
Boy, you should know that
that bridge in Jinnan
has been a pain in the ass for many years?
Unexpectedly,
you are going to be the one to solve the problem.
One day,
you will be like Liu Tong from the previous dynasty
to leave a good reputation in the history of construction of the Xiao Dynasty.
I don't care about reputation.
I just want to leave behind a few architectures.
Great.
As long as you have the heart,
you're worthy of being a good architect.
Your father is not as good as you in this aspect.
There's no need to mention him.
How long have you not visited him?
When you go back next time,
take her with you.
I'll take Langyue back with me next time.
You two are in love and a good match for each other.
You should take marriage into consideration.
Right?
By the way,
I haven't asked you yet. Are you from Lin'an?
What does your father do?
Master Yu, thank you so much for today.
When I'm here next time,
I'll bring you a large pot of plum blossom wine.
It's late.
Langyue and I should go back to Jinnan.
There's no need for you to go back in such a hurry.
I happen to have an empty room here.
I'll clean it up for you.
You can stay here.
Mr. Yu.
In the same room?
Yes.
Girl, you are thinking too much.
I won't tell others
and tarnish your reputation.
This is a remote mountain and few people are around here.
You two are clearly in complete harmony.
Don't care too much about these etiquettes.
Last time in Jinnan,
I slept in your room once.
One more time is really nothing.
I think you did it on purpose.
Maybe.