Unforgettable Love
EP17
Are you sad to leave?
I just can't bear to part with Xiaobao.
Don't be too sad.
You like He Qiaoyan.
This is a wonderful thing.
Even though you don't end up being with each other
you will also gain happiness in the process.
That's enough.
You're right.
The process is more important than the result.
Let's go.
Why did you make this recording?
Qin Yiyue, are you an idiot?
Good night.
Be calm.
After all, in such case
I don't have much experience.
Don't be too sad.
You like He Qiaoyan.
This is a wonderful thing.
What a trick.
Hi.
Something happened.
Something big happened.
What's the matter?
What's up?
Is Xiaobao lost?
Is Lin Wei pregnant with your child?
Do Qin Yiyue and Lin Wei
have a fight in the street and grab each other's hair?
To call the police or to find the lawyer?
I'll arrange it right away.
What can I do for you?
Just tell me
and I would do anything I can to help you.
Hi, bro.
What's wrong with you?
Do you have something wrong with your brain?
Let's go. I'll take you to...
Sit down.
What happened?
Dr. Qin likes me.
This is a great development in your relationship.
Hey, my buddy.
Grab the chance.
What happened?
I said love to He Qiaoyan.
Did you drink too much and vomit?
I said it word by word.
I said it clearly.
What did He Qiaoyan say?
He said nothing.
Nothing?
That's...
He is such an asshole.
That's fine.
Previously,
I had
some expectation on him.
But now I can completely give it up.
No, no, no, no.
You can't think like that.
Men and women
have different mindset.
So when a man is in love
his thinking is different from woman's.
There is no such difference.
I don't want to think about it.
He Qiaoyan
didn't agree to terminate the contract.
But now, to
keep distance from me
he definitely wants to
terminate the contract with me as soon as possible.
That's fine.
This is what I put forward.
That's what I want.
Now the situation is that she likes me
but she thinks that I don't like her.
It's too painful for her.
Thus
she wants to break up with me.
You
have said it 73 times.
It's really out of my expectation.
Qin Yiyue
is trying to figure out
whether I like her
or not.
Come on. Stop showing off.
I know you
have been confessed by someone you like.
You two like each other.
But now the key is that
she insists on leaving.
Really?
So I'd ask you
what are you thinking now?
How do you think about it?
For Qin Yiyue
the fact that you don't respond to her now
as well as your irresponsible attitude
is refusing her love.
If you can't
be serious to her love
the damage to her would be doubled.
Once a girl is vulnerable
she would be more likely to accept those boys
who try to get close to her.
Anyone's care for her
is likely to
be taken as a life-saving straw by her.
So the boy could take this chance.
You don't know.
I have a good knowledge of
those men around her.
Up to now
there is no man
who can threaten me
and be better than me.
Did you remember the man, Ning Fang?
What I can give Qin Yiyue
can never be provided by Ning Fang.
That's not necessarily true.
I'm telling you, once the love comes
who cares about weighing
the pros and cons.
Besides, you shouldn't forget that
they share
much more memories.
Now, for them
it's the best time to nurturing their relationship.
Forget it.
Coming.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
Come on, give it to me.
One sec, please.
Hello, Xiaobao.
Mommy.
Mommy's going to the mountain villa.
See you later, ok?
Good boy.
Give me a kiss.
Ok, bye.
Let's go
Xiaobao, what's up?
Mom is at the mountain villa.
Wait for me.
Xiaobao.
Pack up and get ready to go.
Brilliant.
It's all packed up.
Come here.
Let's go.
Go.
Hold on tight.
Everything must be efficient.
Why do you come so early?
In order to ensure Xiaobao's safety
and let him
integrate into the collective life better
I decide to
control the layout of venues by myself.
Make sure everything is all right.
It's unscientific to classify the toys this way.
First of all, the building blocks should be put together.
And then, the car toys
should be put together.
Don't underestimate
children's ability to learn
and to discriminate differences.
Let me do it.
You're hanging it backwards.
And you are hanging it so high
that even Yao Ming can't reach it.
Play by yourself.
I have something to say.
What do you want to say?
I think I should explain something
between us.
If you feel guilty
because
you refused me
that's not necessary.
What are you talking about?
Forced love does not last.
You can take a horse to the water
but you cannot make him drink.
This is our last cooperation
before the end of our contract.
Just stay with Xiaobao
and finish this parent-child activity.
Do I
cause you some misunderstanding?
The word I said before
is just a kidding.
Do you think that I, Qin Yiyue
is that kind of girl
who would only like one person
forever?
I'm going to
date with different kind of men.
Different kind of men?
Look at that man.
The math teacher with glasses.
Cold and elegant. I like him.
And that one
with strong muscle.
A PE teacher.
He's so cool.
I like him.
That kind of man?
It seems that you
know nothing about my charm.
Look.
Hey.
Your muscle is excellent.
I am a PE teacher.
I come here with Xiaobao.
He is in class three, grade one.
You can also think that
I'm Xiaobao's sister.
I wonder
whether it's possible
that such a young girl is a mom.
Let me help you.
It's so heavy.
It's OK. Put it here. I'll do it.
You are so man.
Do you have a girlfriend?
He has no girlfriend
but he has a wife.
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
Well, I mean that
if he doesn't have a girlfriend
I'll introduce one to him.
Honey.
You are lighter than the box
and you even dare to help carry it.
Excuse me.
My wife
doesn't
do such manual work at home.
She is such a person
who thinks herself strong enough
and seizes those rare opportunities to
help others.
Sorry to trouble you.
No problem.
And,
this is our first time to participate in
such collective activities.
Thank you very much
for taking care of Xiaobao for us.
No worries.
Hi, everybody
today
let me invite you
to eat barbecue on the grass for lunch.
In addition
I'll in charge of your accommodations.
I'll order rooms for you
at nearby five-star hotels.
If you have any problem
please contact me.
Terrific.
What did you mean just now?
As long as the contract is not terminated
you're still Mrs. He
You are Xiaobao's Mommy.
You should always pay attention to
your public image.
You should keep certain distance from the other men.
You should self-respect
and self-love.
Sorry but I disagree with you.
We are both independent from each other.
I'm not your accessory.
Also
I'm going to the bathroom now.
Should I also pay attention to my public image now?
Excuse me.
Self-respect and self-love.
Can we talk for a while?
Ruowei
I tell you that
He Qiaoyan is really bothering me.
What's up?
He just popped up
and had to be around me and made trouble for me.
He had such a big reaction.
In my opinion
his behavior
is to
tell others that you are his wife.
Men
are born with hunting attributes.
And they have a strong sense of territory.
You've successfully
aroused his sense of crisis.
So you don't have to
care about him.
The less you care about him, the more upset he would be.
Thank him.
Why?
Thanks for his demonstration.
It gives me a good idea.
Where are you going?
What do you want to say?
Can't we talk about it in front of Yiyue?
Sit down.
Two men are sitting here.
Don't you think it's weird?
Do you like Qin Yiyue?
She's my wife.
I'll say it directly.
From the beginning
I know you
are in a fake marriage without love.
And I know that
she's going to break up with you now.
So I
just want to remind you that
after termination
Yiyue wants to return to
her own life.
Please respect her freedom.
Don't disturb her.
It's none of
your business.
And in addition
I'm not going to break up with her.
I can guess
your reasons for refusing to terminate the contract.
If you like her
just tell her.
If you don't like her
just let her go.
Don't
torment her with procrastination and indecision.
Why do you
say this to me?
I like her.
Then why don't you just tell her?
I will.
Sometimes if you get close to the girl too quickly
you may lose her.
Then you are too slow.
You haven't told her your love until now.
It can only indicate that time
has given you the answer.
I'm not like you.
I think that man should insist his principles.
I will never hurt her.
Do you know her?
Yiyue is pure.
She seems always to be happy
and doesn't complain anything.
And she has tried her best
to be good to everyone around her.
When she falls down
she still smiles and asks for candy
just like a little girl.
She would pat the dust
just say it's OK and leave it behind.
I can see
her inner heart now.
She is painful because of you.
You think
you know her.
In fact, you
don't understand her feelings.
Our relationship
is none of your business.
But I'll remind you that
stop loss in time.
You should know who you are.
I am off.
I'm ready to go now.
Yang Ruowei.
We'll...
If you want to date with me, just tell me.
You don't need to
give such a clear hint.
Who says I’ll ask you out?
Then why are you dressed up?
I have an appointment with Mr. Wang of Diti Group.
That guy.
Why are you asking him out?
How did know him?
What are you talking about?
I'm such a brilliant single woman.
I don't need to ask a man out.
No, he's an asshole.
You'll get hurt.
Really?
I don't think so.
But what you have said
brings up
my desire to win.
Do you know how many girls
he has cheated on?
Many of my female friends
have been cheated by him.
They even can't complain about it.
What you said is to
criticize him
or show off that you have so many female friends?
I'll go. The taxi's here.
Hi
do you get here?
Yes.
My destination
is CL restaurant.
The restaurant with the English name CL.
The new one.
OK, I'll go down now.
Then I'll go now, Mr. Wen.
Bye-bye.
It's not true.
She is so deliberate.
She showed off in front of me
and got dressed up.
She said
the address of the restaurant.
It's obvious that
she wants to misguide me.
Whoever she wants to
date with.
I don't care.
Come on.
Wang Cheng
is such an asshole.
He is still using such a corny way.
Isn't this a set of valuables?
Trying to attract the girl I like.
It's impossible.
Calm down. It's not true.
No, no, no.
As he used to do
after the set of valuables
something bad would happen.
Yang Ruowei, Yang Ruowei.
You've missed the shot.
Hi, my sister.
What are you doing here?
I want to ask you something.
You are so manipulative now.
Several days ago
you were dating with
Mr. Wen.
Do you change your boyfriend?
Mr. Wang, just here.
Thanks. Bye.
See you.
Mr. Wang, Mr. Wang
don't go in a hurry.
Right?
I didn't come at the right time.
You go on, you go on.
Weiwei
why don't you invite Mr. Wang
to have a cup of tea.
Shut up.
Weiwei, why are you so harsh to me?
I'm observing the man for you.
This man
is definitely willing to spend money for you.
It's much more reliable than that Wen Gu.
If you can be his girlfriend
I can also have a backing.
Well, I have things to do.
so I'm off.
So...
What happened?
What are you doing here?
What's the matter?
Yes.
I want to borrow some money from my sister.
If I have a brother-in-law
who can give me some money generously
it would be better.
How much do you want?
50,000 yuan.
That's enough?
Enough. That's enough.
Don't even think about it.
I'm telling you, not even five yuan.
Take it back.
Then you give this to me.
Empty.
Do you think I'm such a woman who
eats out with other men, receives such gifts
and then takes the man home?
This dinner is on me.
After all, I asked you out.
And I want to thank you
for your affection for me.
The girl paying the bill
is not a good thing for me.
So you mean that
I don't have a chance.
Thank you for your kindness
but I can't afford
this gift.
Can I borrow
this paper bag?
Are you jealous?
Hey, bro, your watch...
Don't even think about it.
Don't bother your sister again.
Leave here.
It's strange.
It's so late.
Why my aunt is here?
This is 5000,000 yuan.
This is the last time I give you money.
The amount of money needs to be larger.
He Qiaoyan
has found my hometown.
I can't get home now.
What do you mean?
Get me an apartment in the city.
You
get someone monitor me?
Why is he here?
Drive away, right now.
Xiaobao, look at mom.
Is mom beautiful now?
Mom's skin is white and tender.
Mama loves masks.
When Xiaobao grows up
Xiaobao still accompanies mom to apply the masks.
OK?
That's my boy.
Xiaobao
daddy wants to ask you a question.
Do you think that dad
is a cold and elegant man
or a cool and handsome man?
I'm sorry
but I think you are
neither elegant nor cool.
Okay.
Then I'll tie up your hair.
Mr. He
what kind of hairstyle would you like today?
Ox horn?
OK, mom will tie up two horns.
Then, the left.
Xiaobao
now looks like a girl.
Shake it.
Do you feel itchy?
Tickle.
Xiaobao.
Xiaobao is asleep.
Not only Xiaobao
can accompany you to apply the masks.
I also can.
Do you know what that means?
I know it now.
Xiaobao is asleep.
Then I'll go back to my room.
Mom, don't go.
Mommy, don't go.
Xiaobao, mom won't leave you.
Mom' s here.
After Xiaobao falls asleep
I'll go back to my room.
That's not going to work.
Xiaobao will wake up as soon as you leave.
But there's only one bed.
That's all right.
Xiaobao sleeps in the middle
you sleep there and I sleep here.
It's impossible.
I'll go back to my room.
Mom, sing a song.
Xiaobao
Mom will sing a song for you.
Why is Wen Gu here?
Does He Qiaoyan know everything?
Wen Gu saw it.
♪ The moon is beautiful when the wind blows. ♪
♪ Where is the boat going? ♪
♪ Long time. ♪
♪ With me. ♪
Hello, aunt.
Hi
Where are you?
Xiaobao, Yiyue and I are
at the mountain villa.
What's up?
Nothing.
♪ Where is the boat going? ♪
♪ Long time. ♪
Who is singing?
♪ With me. ♪
It's Yiyue.
She is teaching Xiaobao to sing a child's song.
We are going to take part in an
activity of a parent-child program.
Aunt.
Qiaonian,
If you're out
and it's still early
come to my house.
I prepare
a birthday cake for Xiaobao.
A cake is prepared for Xiaobao.
There is a cake.
Aunt
I don't think we can come.
It's raining heavily.
What's wrong with the brake?
The brake is out of order.
The rain is too heavy, isn't it?
Sir, stop the car please.
There's an accident ahead.
It's dangerous to stop here, Miss.
Save lives! Hurry up.
I'm a doctor, sir.
Go ahead and find some people to help.
It's urgent to save lives.
Hurry.
Be safe!
Honey
Don't cry.
Don 't be panic.
It's OK. I am here.
♪ The moon is beautiful when the wind blows. ♪
♪ Where is the boat going? ♪
♪ Long time. ♪
That girl
is Qin Yiyue.
Now, let's invite
the performer of our No.2 family
to give us his performances.
Let's welcome the performer of No.4 family
Great, Xiaobao.
Let's go, Xiaobao.
Well.
All families
have given their performances.
What a beautiful song.
Qiaoyan
I happened to
talk to the investor
at the nearby golf course.
It doesn't matter. You go first.
Let's go.
Come by the way?
I think you do it on purpose.
Let's go.
OK, I admit it.
You said last time that
you were not interested in our alliance through marriage.
I think
it's not true.
You are just worried about Xiaobao.
To reassure you
and for our cooperation
I'll prove it to you that
I can
get along well with Xiaobao too.
I advise you not to waste your time.
Marriage is impossible.
Xiaobao is sweating so much.
I am sure that you have a good time.
Xiaobao,
it's too difficult to catch a fish for me.
Mom can do anything
except swimming.
I'm good at catching fishes.
I can help Xiaobao to complete the task.
Xiaobao, you trust me for once.
Ok?
Auntie.
Call her sister.
Catch fishes, auntie.
Ok, then.
I'll take you to catch fishes.
We can catch the whole pond of fishes.
Let's go.
Here.
Xiaobao, do you like Qin Yiyue,
auntie Qin Yiyue?
Mom.
But she's not your real mother.
All right, I'm going to catch a fish.
Don't use it.
What should I use?
Your hands.
You don't let me use tools but
ask me to use my hands.
Alright.
I didn't wear a watch.
How long have they gone?
About twenty minutes.
I didn't catch a fish.
Why don't they come back yet?
I'm still a little worried.
Xiaobao always
refuse to get along with those unfamiliar
alone.
Why this time
he agrees so quickly
to catch fishes with Lin Wei.
To be honest, I'm a little worried, too.
Let's go and find them.
Ok.
They are there.
Go and have a look.
Are you injured?
Are you ok?
My feet seem to be hurting.
Maybe it's a sprain.
Don't you have tools?
Why do you go into the water?
Xiaobao, he...
Come on, put it on.
I thought it was easy.
He Weifei
how can you do such a thing.
As a man
you shouldn't do this to girls.
Don't criticize him.
Come up.
It's urgent to go to the camp and find the medical staff.
I'll talk to you later.
Wrap it tight.
It's not serious.
The doctor said it was just a sprain just now.
No big deal.
I didn't expect that
Xiaobao should
try to embarrass you.
I apologize for him.
It doesn't matter.
It's just a kid's prank.
I won't take it to heart.
And I won't
give up so easily.
But I do hope that
you stop deliberately
getting close to Xiaobao.
I don't want him to be unhappy.
Besides, leave Heshi Group.
I don't think we should
go on working together.
He Qiaoyan.
It's too much.
He Weifei.
No one asks you to face the wall and reflect your behavior.
No need to play pathetic.
Xiaobao, where's your mommy?
Catching fishes.
Catching fishes?
I tell you
don't come here.
I've learned to kill snakes.
I know where your tender spot is.
I'll hit you even harder.
Don't come here.
Hey, buddy.
Buddy.
I'm just kidding.
You are the king of the mountains.
How dare I hit you, don't I?
Listen to me.
Life is like a play.
It's hard for us to meet.
Don't lose your temper over trifles.
It doesn't worth.
Two snakes.
Is she alone?
No trick, right?
Xiaobao, go back to your room and wait for me.
I'm going to find your mommy.
Qin Yiyue.
Qin Yiyue. Qin Yiyue.