Do not worry
Mother won't blame you
Even if the Queen is merciful
don't blame me
Don't let gossip
Damaged His Highness' name
after all
free at kisskh.me
Your Majesty's Injury
if recovered
Your Majesty will surely urge His Majesty
Departure for Nanjing
I know a lot
I am wholehearted
Worry for His Highness
Your Highness is angry
okay then
Akin
spread the word
Your Highness is staying tonight
Yes
stop
Prince Concubine
take a good bath
I'll go back first
queen concubine
Guo Guifei outside the Qianqing Palace
for three days
His Majesty
free at kisskh.me
finally relented
As expected
This year's Qianqiu Banquet
Because His Majesty is ill
Niangniang ordered to be spared
Concubine Guo's speech
To prepare a feast for the concubine
What do you mean by her?
what happened these two days
Which house is empty
Are they going to Qiongyuan to enjoy the flowers together?
Why can't I even see a ghost?
master
The slaves had previously sent people to watch them
Discover
here
Wu Cairen
Although the palace of the princess is big
Removable medical book tea case
really simple
Or you are exquisite and rich here
It can be seen that His Royal Highness is waiting for you
so much love
Greetings to the prince's concubine
all in the temple
Arranged according to everyone's preferences
what about the princess
like quiet
i love fun
What is the difference between likes and dislikes?
how to be at ease
I don't see it right
Prince Concubine
you come help me see
No need to be polite, just sit
Zhao Cairen
Let me see
this line
Try this
at this location
This place could be less
Wu Cairen
What's up
The prince and concubine do not know
everyone says
Wu Cairen is a fragrant doll
Love incense is crazy
come here
come a little closer
citrus scent
I also make it everyday
It's just too sweet
not so fresh
you smell
like freshly plucked from a branch
fresh citrus
Wu Cairen
you said it yourself
I will never deal with the prince's concubine.
The words are still in my ears
you won't forget
Your lord, am I like that?
a citrus-flavored skewer
also buy me
The fox spirit lives in the fox hole
Still smiling so sweetly at me
She saw that I liked the scent
Next time you will come to win me over
I won't be fooled easily
let's go
you mean
Concubine Guo will do it herself
Mother's Birthday Banquet
Yes
It's strange that you said it
Guo Guifei has always
Relying on His Majesty's favor
Don't look down on the queen
Now he's more diligent
late
Frozen three feet is not a day's cold
When things come to an end, I want to restore the old relationship
How can it be
Besides, Yongning Palace and Kunning Palace
There's never anything old to talk about
some people are doomed
not be friends
princess
Although the queen ordered to be exempted from the birthday celebration
but you can't
Go to the banquet empty-handed
What kind of birthday gift should I give?
you say
what will she give
Slave, go and ask
without you
Someone will go
The prince's concubine Wu Cairen has arrived
let her in
Prince Concubine
be careful
clumsy
Prince Concubine
what are you doing
She likes the citrus scent of yesterday
I teach her to perfume
Don't blame the prince and concubine
I kindly remind you
His Highness does not like
too strong aroma
girls on weekdays
The powder smell is a little more fragrant
He will also be unhappy
but i like it
As a concubine of the East Palace
Your Highness's preference should come first
this is my place
I naturally want to burn my favorite incense
Your Highness
he does not like
Let's go to his study then
Akin
try it yourself
I'll go over
why are you here
I
what is this
in a while
It is the Qianqiu of the Queen's Empress
Although the concubine is exempted from the birthday wishes
We also try our best
It was for hospitality
Are you going to offer this peony picture?
grinding ink
Prince Concubine
The doctor ordered
free at kisskh.me
your hand is not healed
Do not use too much force
it'll be fine in a while
do not forget
You are in front of the princess
how to say
In the blink of an eye, everything changed
so inflammatory
I'm so ashamed for you
What piano and chess
Poetry and painting
When Your Highness is in a good mood
You can also take it out for fun.
most of the time
Just bored in my own palace
no matter how good the painting
more beautiful tunes
elder sister
No bosom friend appreciates
what's the use
As for me
go wherever it's lively
Sitting in the Xinuang Pavilion
listen to them talk and play the piano
how fun
Might be lucky
Do you have a chance to meet His Highness?
look at your break
correct
Prince Concubine is proficient in spices
you can ask her
all traitors
His Royal Highness likes flowers, birds and landscapes
who's house
not hang two
does she have
I want to make His Highness happy
Also set up a pitcher?
Your Highness does not like noise
Do not like too strong fragrance
He said that women always bow their heads and become female celebrities
bad manners
especially misogynists
party noisy
Always live for no reason
what your majesty does not like
she's done
just to be happy
wait and see
when she regrets
Wu Cairen
just ignored
Want to call me back now
no need
Wu Cairen
Don't you like citrus scent?
Isn't it citrus scented?
Don't I have it in my house?
Prince He Lao's concubine
Who is it that sees you like it
From the citrus fragrance sent by the prince's concubine
even out
I asked the slaves to send it over
you
The slaves retire
master
where are you going
They want to be in Queen Qianqiu
send peony
How can I make them happy
go to see the princess
His Highness's injury is slow to heal
i'm really worried
Think of a foreign ancestral dress
hemostatic muscle drug
It's ready for you to try
Eunuch Chen
This medicine is the princess
stayed up three nights
just matched
Due to special formula
I have to hold it with ice for a long time
Once the medicine has melted
The medicine will wear off
bother
Use in the morning and evening for seven consecutive days
I'll send a new one
no need
The medicine that Sheng Yin gave me is fine.
Although Imperial Physician Sheng is a master of Xinglin
But doctors have their own expertise
my grandfather
It's for trauma
like an ordinary sword wound
Heal in less than a month
How can it be like now
recurring
I heard that His Highness had a fever again yesterday.
I can't sit still
love to go out
wind blows cold
it's better now
Yes
is there anything else
Next month will be the mother and the queen
But she was worried about her father's illness
unwilling to act
Strictly forbid concubines in the palace
Gifts with court wives
I was thinking
Ask everyone to prepare embroidery
or copy Buddhist scriptures
This is in line with the mother's will
not to stretch
But
I know what happened in the past
Your Highness has misunderstood me
But now sister Sun's name has been decided
those unpleasant things
It's gone.
But now she's making a big splash
The birthday gift of Zhang Luo's mother
I am afraid that she will enter into filial piety
Going against the mother's will
Why don't you go down and persuade
how does she love
Just leave her
Look at the look of your majesty
Could it be that Sister Sun is still blaming you
Too
Who has such an opportunity
It's hard to get rid of the resentment
Your Highness, don't worry
The human heart is always fleshy
slowly
How can you not be hot?
you have to be considerate
give her more time
Your Highness
If you want to meet the prince's concubine
It's just a servant girl
Why go for a trip
She never told me the truth
Your Highness
That's Cao Cairen
She probably didn't see His Highness
if you see
Baba came to say goodbye long ago
let's go
Luoyang red is so pretty
Do not
Still the prince concubine draws well
Refined and elegant
It is also a wonderful product
The leaves are so colorful
The whole painting seems too sweet and vulgar.
It's all your fault
don't stick to this color
Ruined a good painting
what's the matter today
Your Highness is clearly standing here
They pretend not to see
have a look
Wu Cairen
do not
i told you not to
did you see
Since the prince's concubine entered the East Palace
They go to her temple all day
Silk Bamboo Playing and Singing Female Red Painting
noisy
Where's the rule
you see
Are you secretly fighting?
Don't you revolve around her too?
I
I just want to see them
Can you do something unruly?
Your Highness, you take care of them
Your Highness
master
Your Highness seems annoyed
What should I do
It's good to be annoyed
What does His Highness hate, she must bear it
Waiting for His Highness to go back and reprimand her well
Inkstone
how did you come here
Come in
Your Highness
your injury
it doesn't matter
close your eyes
quick
free at kisskh.me
close your eyes
I hand it to you
Don't give it back to me in this life
I
I don't know how true you are to me
But my heart for you is never false
I don't expect you to reciprocate with the same heart
But I hope one day
can you be honest with me
adult
where did you go
I can't find you anywhere
There is an urgent report in Nanjing
Why don't you report such an important matter to the East Palace?
Now
right
Your Highness
existing matter
you need to know
you need my help
I'm helping you
Your Highness
Come in
Just received an emergency report that there is another earthquake in Nanjing
His Majesty urgently summons ministers to discuss
Go to Qianqing Palace
your injury
it doesn't matter
Your Highness
go quickly
Zijin
I will tell you what you say
don't worry
go
Your Highness is here
I can't come back tonight
You also set up early
master
This must have fallen from His Highness
Akin
you go to rest
Yes
April of the first year of Hongxi
Repeated earthquakes in Nanjing
Crown Prince Zhu Zhanji pays homage to Xiaoling Mausoleum
and stay in Nanjing
I don't know if His Royal Highness has come to Nanjing.
Sister Fang
You are concerned about the safety of His Royal Highness
Still worried about Mr. Chen's safety?
no nonsense
Guanglu Temple is in charge of rewarding the buluojia given to Baiguan
Among them are the ministers whom His Majesty loves very much.
I specially ordered our Shang Food Bureau to prepare for it.
are you all ready
Already checked
all sent away
Come
You two go and cook the new ears of wheat
another one
Birthday banquet for the queen
are you ready
Yes
Finally finished
Don't waste my hard work
Repeated scrutiny and revision
My eyes are so tired
can you get it
Just the manuscript you handed in
choose carefully
There are not two available
Sister Wu, you are here
The strange Taoist said that the source of the heart comes from the creation of foreign teachers
The same garden with beautiful peony
by different painters
What a difference
This is someone's skill in flattering
It's so windy
ok ok i was wrong
don't make trouble, you see
Three pearls are melted in this white peony
glossy color
bright and prominent
It's my fault
careful
This is my birthday gift to the queen
how can you
go
follow me to see the princess
let her judge
let go
What is the style of pulling and pulling
Obviously you are only talking about yourself
That's the disaster
is responsible
It's also you and I can't get out of the relationship
Why am I the only one to blame now?
Prince Concubine
you see
This is the pipa song you want
I finished the sheet music last night
How can you care about these now?
The peony figure is destroyed
Tomorrow Empress Chiaki
What to do with Shouli
Prince Concubine
Today's business is that I'm too reckless
you are generous
Will not care about me, right?
Curiosities in my house
whatever you like
will pay you
you
Lol lol lol
You won't be able to laugh in a while
queen concubine
Concubines and concubines, may the queen rise like the sun and be as eternal as the moon
Come
sit
mother
This is the picture of Ma Gu's birthday embroidered by the concubine
Congrats to the Queen Mother Songhe Evergreen
Okay
The concubine wishes the queen a good mood
Chunhui is forever
Okay
The concubine congratulates the queen on the sun and the moon
The maid and concubine wish the queen good health
Blessings are boundless
mother
former prince concubine
We also prepared a picture of peony as a birthday gift for you
It's all my fault, Miaoxian, this girl is clamoring to see
accidentally damaged
Miao Xian
Still not making amends to the queen and the concubine
queen concubine
The picture of peony is the effort of the prince's concubine
everything is mine isn't it
If you want to punish me
queen concubine
I can't spare this dead girl
Make sure she punishes herself three cups
But well
Something went wrong on Shouli
Can't come empty-handed
I heard that the prince's concubine is good at music
May wish to dedicate a song to show filial piety
go
Yes
is peony
Peace and prosperity
Fang You Phoenix Laiyi
Today's Empress Qianqiu
Special Phoenix Tire from Shang Food Bureau
Congratulations to the lady
queen concubine
This meal comes from the Tang Roast End Banquet
Tuanyu nourishes yin, clears heat and nourishes vitality
Cooked with Duck Yellow Winter Bamboo Shoots
No smell of stinky smell
Chang'an is rich and precious
Reward Street West Purple Peony
Do not have jade plate Chenglu cold
No one starts watching in the middle of the month
In the past, there was a peony meeting organized by Zhang Yuezhai
Above the hall today
Purple-clothed jade plate competes to vomit fragrance
Not much more
what is this
back to the princess
It's lettuce and peony petals deep fried
The slaves also specially added licorice juice
to preserve the fragrance of peonies
It's fitting
free at kisskh.me
Meng Shang food
You two chefs are no different.
Sure enough, he is a master chef
Yashiki Zen
The Empress is asking you to be the chef
Don't thank your mother for her grace
Thanks for the help of the Queen
Slaves will never forget
That's Hua Erqiao
It's clearly silver powder and Jin Ling.
How can there be silver powder Jinling in Qiongyuan this year?
It must be Hua Erqiao
Imitation of Zhang Yuezhai as a peony festival
All are peony nouns
Why don't we look in poetry
Mother's favorite peony
It's a pity that the peony will thank you
I bothered to stay until my birthday
But these few pots
Just as it should be
But the prince concubine is smart
This is her real birthday present
Prince Concubine is so stingy
The birthday gift is hidden to this day
I knew you were so carefully prepared
Why do I feel guilty to this day?
I have previously ordered
Don't move the crowd for the birthday
Not to mention the use of the dancers of the Jiaofang Division
queen concubine
How dare a maid and concubine make up her own mind
It was His Royal Highness that went to Nanjing
Can't celebrate birthday in person
I just told me to wait for the congratulations
queen concubine
It is indeed the prince who instructed the Jiaofang Secretary to prepare for the Peony Festival
Congratulations to the Empress and the Empress
Fukuzawa long
The prince is thinking about the queen's birthday
Do filial piety even far away
This kind of sincerity is really rare
I also hope that the Empress will not blame them by mistake.
reward
thank you queen
queen concubine
I learned that His Royal Highness is preparing for the Peony Festival
East Palace people
They all took the initiative to go to Qiongyuan to choose the manuscript of the flower book
The original intention was to present peony pictures at the peony fair
Congratulations to the Empress
Although the peony picture can't be seen
But the peony and silk flowers that the dancer just wore
All are based on the peony pictures drawn by everyone.
queen concubine
This prince concubine is an honest man
Don't take credit for yourself
so
That peony picture is everyone's hard work
Congratulations to the Queen
sit
queen concubine
Those people are also the daughters of sinners.
Has not been released due to outstanding qualifications
The emperor has pardoned them
The Ministry of Rites is so perfunctory
you go check it yourself
There is such a thing as yang and yin
must be severely punished
Yes
what you said
I will tell you to go down and do it with confidence
Concubine invite me
why?
you go down
Please forgive the queen
what do you mean
Young and ignorant maid
impolite
offended my mother many times
please forgive me
Guo Guifei
please get up
empress
The maid and concubine feel remorse day and night
As long as you can get your mother's forgiveness
The concubine is willing to close the palace gate from now on
Pray for the goddess all day long
why this
empress
I know
I am guilty
I dare not hope to get the forgiveness of the mother-in-law
Yesterday, His Majesty gave thousands of instructions
Let me be sure for the arrogance of the past
beg you
empress
please forgive me
Why don't you help your master up?
queen concubine
you have a big heart
not punished for past sins
today is your birthday
The concubine is willing to drink a glass of sake
Congratulations to the Empress
empress
Maid and concubine drink first
Congratulations to the Empress
annoying
His Majesty
Why is your majesty so angry?
That damn Li Shimian
How dare you insult me ​​in public
I'm so pissed
It's just a glass of wine
She is also kind
you think too much
Your Majesty Your Majesty
What happened to the prince
That's Jin Yiwei
quick
Kuaisheng Imperial Physician
Grass grows between your fingers
what to panic
Doctor Sheng please
Liu Gonggong
Your Majesty wakes up in good spirits
Also dealt with political affairs
How to get to Yongning Palace
I came back and fell ill
Your Majesty, this chronic illness must rest in peace
Where can it stand the toss?
Noon by Li Yushi
chest pain shortness of breath
don't look good
don't mention it
I have to hurry in and wait.
father-in-law
adult