Unforgettable Love
EP19
I
am
into
you.
Boy
You're finally willing to talk to Dad.
Do you get it?
I...
Why not choose
written expression, which is more rigorous?
For example, e-mail.
It not only can communicate in a timely and efficient manner,
but also can leave evidence
as a legal basis.
What are you doing?
I have watched lots of
Hollywood romantic films
and Western movies.
I find that,
after the perfect date,
they will choose to lie in bed together
and have a heart-to-heart talk.
Perfect date?
That's foreigner's date.
You watch some
pure love dramas that Asians watch. OK?
I have watched them.
After my analysis,
I draw a conclusion.
Asians are too reserved
in expressing their emotion.
But European and American people are more direct.
You want me to
express my emotion clearly.
If the fishing this afternoon
is not enough,
so come on now.
Xiaowei, Xiaowei
Mom
Are you all right?
I'm okay. I had a nightmare.
OK, just fine.
All right, it's time for dinner.
Your father won't come back for dinner.
For the wedding of you and Qiaoyan,
how's it going?
Your father is old.
From now on, our Lin family
will all depend on you.
You have to work hard.
And
as to the Bracelet project
that you're in charge of in Heshi Group,
I have already told your dad.
He'll help you.
He Qiaoyan let me leave Heshi Group.
What?
He...
He and the doctor
are dating.
It's said that
they have terminated the contract.
Why are they dating now?
I go upstairs.
No, I have to ask He Jiaqin.
What does she mean?
As long as you marry Lin Wei,
what you call hidden danger
won't exist.
And it's good for Bracelet.
Aunt.
As for this question,
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
I have a meeting later.
I'll hang up now.
A normal child
is lovely.
But if you
face a child-like Xiaobao every day,
who is more or less
abnormal,
I'm afraid that many people
will find him unlovable.
Aunt. Well.
It's just because I know
how cute they are by nature,
so I want to
help them get better.
The kids that you saved before
are very lucky.
But I hope
you can leave Xiaobao and Qiaoyan.
I know that
you think I'm not good enough for Qiaoyan.
But aunt,
do you really
want him
to marry a woman
he doesn't love for company
and then live unhappily
for the rest of his life?
Since Qiaoyan decided to
take over his brother's career,
it's not just
his own career.
He should be worthy of his dead relatives.
He can't escape.
Yeah
Aunt, I think you are right,
but also selfish.
For lovers who don't the similar family background,
it's hard for them to get married.
Even if they get married,
they will not be happy.
I've seen lots of such things.
You and Qiaoyan
will both be hurt.
And Xiaobao
will be hurt again.
Am I right?
Aunt
Please don't embarrass Yiyue.
I don't handle it well.
You come here so fast.
It seems that you really care about her.
Of course I care about her.
I know that
Heshi Group is the place
where I need to pay all my effort.
Since the day
my brother and sister-in-law died,
I've accepted
the fact.
Over the years,
except Heshi Group and Xiaobao,
I don't have my own life.
I'm very clear about the condition of our family.
I am more aware of
my situation and responsibility.
But at the same time
I long to have
what a normal adult
could have.
I want to be with the person I like
to form a family together.
Aunt
What you want,
I'll help you achieve it.
But as for the relationship between me and Yiyue,
I hope you don't interfere any more.
Let's go.
Aunt, we're leaving.
What are you doing here?
I heard that my aunt is going to invite you to dinner.
I know that
she would say that.
You're not angry, are you?
There is no reason to be angry.
I think you are fantastically handsome just now.
Be relaxed.
About aunt,
I can handle her.
You can rest assured that
I'm not so vulnerable.
Neither would I
be scared away so easily.
I will hold on to you
tightly.
I also come here today
to tell you
I am into you.
I am into you
From birth to now,
these words,
I never say them.
All the time
I adhere to
reason and data.
It's kind of embarrassed
to say I am into you suddenly.
But I finally say it.
It's a relief.
You're right.
Emotion
really needs to be expressed.
So I have lots of things
to change
and to learn.
Yiyue
Would you like to accompany me
to continue to change
and learn?
I do.
Thank you.
Idiot.
What's wrong?
Have I
said
thank you too many times?
It's not good, right?
I see the girl in TV plays
who falls in love with the hero
is spoiled
and coaxed by the hero.
As for me,
I meet a babe in the wood.
I have to teach you how to date.
You teach me.
But you are the person who enjoys the achievement.
What you said seems to be very reasonable.
All right.
I just stand on my own feet.
I plant the tree by myself.
And then pick fruits by myself.
Let's go, the babe in the wood.
Who?
Give me some medicine.
Lin Wei.
How much? I give you.
If you really want to transfer money,
you have to add my WeChat first.
When can I have my medicine?
What happened to you recently?
Nothing
Your anxiety disorder
needs a long-term consultation with a psychologist.
If you don't believe me,
you can find a
strange psychologist.
Or I can recommend you
a reliable one.
In a word,
I will never
reveal your identity.
No, I'll get the medicine from you tomorrow.
Mom
Miss Lin
They are all
core members of Bracelet project
in Heshi Group.
If you need something in the future,
you can just tell them.
Mom. Must you do that?
You should keep your word.
Otherwise you will disgrace Lin family in the end.
I get it, mom.
Sit down.
Don't worry. There is no camera in this room.
I have given you the money for the medicine.
Why don't you give me the medicine?
I'm a psychologist,
not a drug dealer.
Hey, Ning Fang.
I can give you the medicine.
But you should fill in this form first.
No
I have said that I don't need a doctor.
You just give me the medicine.
Are you
always so nosy?
I'm a psychologist.
I can't just sit back.
Okay.
Fill in carefully.
Miss Lin
Your current psychological state
is pessimistic.
I suggest you get treatment right away.
Otherwise, the condition will be uncontrollable.
I have filled out the form.
Please keep your word.
Give me the medicine.
The reason I let you fill in the form
is to make you more aware of
your own illness.
I have read your diagnosis abroad.
Give me the medicine.
This is the last time
I give you the medicine.
If you want more in the future,
you have to see a doctor for a prescription.
How are you feeling?
Is the strength comfortable?
Give me your cell phone.
Cell phone?
From now on,
the profile photo of your WeChat must be my picture.
The cover of you Moments
must be a picture of the two of us.
Let me see. What else.
By the way,
the lock screen password of your phone
must be my birthday.
Good idea.
Give me your cell phone.
I want to change, too.
Okay.
Cheer up, Yiyue.
I'll introduce you to some
cute young boys.
Don't always focus on
the old He Qiaoyan.
You give it back to me.
Your friends
still don't know
that we are dating.
Don't be angry.
I haven't
had time for the official announcement yet.
And she won't do that.
Really.
What are you doing?
I've just sent the message
to 637 friends
in your contacts
to update
your emotional state.
Mr. He
You are too naive.
Dear all,
at 9:30
this morning,
I have officially reached the love cooperation
with He Qiaoyan
and the cooperation project will be steadily advanced.
Please be informed and forward the message.
What's wrong with you?
It seems that my account is hacked.
You don't understand.
All right, get ready to go out.
Where are we going?
Everybody
Today I call all of you here.
Because there is one thing
that is very important
to tell everyone.
Yiyue and me are in serious relationship.
So I'd like to announce it to you.
Er
Mr. He
Actually
you can just post it on your Moment.
Don't need to show affection in such way.
Yeah
Just one piece of paper.
We can't rest assured
that Dr. Qin dates with you.
Come on, come on.
Let's play Truth or Dare.
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Come on. Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Dare.
Okay.
Mr. He
Please show Dr. Qin
this part of the line.
Impossible.
Why? Let me see.
Are you sure?
I'm ready.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
It's all your fault. And you don't coax me.
I really want to cry.
Beat your chest.
Bad guy.
Aha
You are so annoying.
Ah ah ah
Bad guy. Beat you.
Break up.
It's just "Dare".
Dare.
Don't stop.
There's a second round.
Come on, come on.
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Truth.
If I and Ning Fang fall into the water,
who will you save?
Naive.
I won't save anyone.
Because I can't swim.
When do you start to like me?
After you like me.
So
when do you
start to like me?
You can't ask me.
I'm going to ask.
Before you like me, of course.
There's a third round.
Come on.
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Dare.
Okay.
Come on.
Mr. He. Yiyue.
You two
eat the chips together
within 15 seconds.
I have finished.
You're cheating.
Yiyue, are you ok?
I shouldn't have fined her for drinking when she lost the game.
She always loses at games.
Hug.
It doesn't matter. You could go back first.
I'll take care of her.
Go, go.
Let's go. Let's go.
I know you are the same as me.
What?
We both drink.
Stop.
No drunk driving.
You will get a ticket.
How much shall I be fined?
Five million yuan.
Then I want Miss Qin
to help me with this business.
Okay.
Please give evaluation
for the service of Miss Qin.
Five star praise.
Millions of praise.
Is that enough?
No.
That's enough. That's enough.
No more.
Will Aunt come?
I call her and ask her.
Never mind.
I know
aunt doesn't like me.
But it's normal that she dislikes me.
Anyway, I grew up
not being
liked by teachers and elders.
Isn't that good?
You go on
being yourself happily.
As to other things,
let me handle them.
But this time is different.
I want to be recognized by aunt.
Not for me,
but for us.
Yiyue
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
What does aunt usually like?
I'm very good at learning.
Aunt
loves her career
and also likes profits.
She is a typical member of He family.
And
apart from work,
she would like playing golf.
Golf.
It sounds like
an easy one to learn.
Are you going to
open a golf shop.
It's called being prepared
before taking action.
Golf is a sport
of using clubs
to hit balls into a series of holes.
What's wrong?
Do I add too much pepper?
No, I don't add pepper.
Delicate.
Strength.
No.
The important factor of distance.
Distance.
Flexibility of the body.
Press three or four times.
Move away and bend to the right.
Only in this way can it be effective.
Stand with feet shoulder-width apart.
Choose the right angle to hit the ball.
Pick up the ball.
The distance between the feet
should be slightly wider than the shoulder width.
Toe forward.
The knee is slightly bent.
At the same time, keep your waist and back straight.
But when I straighten my back,
my club is far from the ground.
It means your movement is wrong.
Come on.
Let me help you.
Press your shoulders down.
Keep your arms straight.
Raise your hip a little.
Keep your back straight.
Move forward a little.
Is that so?
So
what Dr. Qin wants to learn is not golf.
I can also teach you this.
I'm going to learn the swing.
No hurry. Learn this first.
So many people are watching.
Never mind.
Let's continue.
Not bad.
What's wrong?
Is there something wrong in the company?
Yeah.
There is something urgent in company.
They let me go back.
Could you do it yourself?
Take it easy.
I'm a girl
who can beat off several hooligans.
There is no need to mention that matter.
All right. I'll pick you up when I finish.
Come back quickly.
I'll miss you.
Okay.
I have to go.
Pay attention to safety.
What happened?
I also
received their resignation out of the blue.
I haven't noticed any signs of that before.
Who's left now?
The
three old subordinates of Mr. He are still here.
Others
are brought in by Miss Lin before
or
employed after she arrives.
They're all gone.
Mr. He, don't worry.
We can
recruit new staff now.
The previous work framework and direction
are in accordance with
the original talent structure
and their respective resources
to build.
Recruit again.
Set a direction.
It's too late.
Well, you go back.
I'll find a way.
Let's go.
I have said that
I'll get in touch with you.
I'm afraid you'll forget.
Say it. Give me money or not.
I've given you a lot.
You leave Qincheng City first.
Otherwise, any talk is spared.
Now it seems that
you don't have the initiative.
You want to reveal the secret.
But you have to rely on me
to pay off your debt.
Just say it. Give me the money or not.
Is that my Aunt?
I will leave.
How can I go without money?
Give me money first.
Who dares to bully my aunt?
Money. I just want money.
The money, I will...
Aunt, I'm here to protect you.
You have arms and feet. Why do you rob money?
Let's go, aunt.
Dr. Qin, what are you doing?
You must be Mrs. He.
Does Mrs. He know that her husband
is the culprit?
Shut up.
Are you crazy?
What are you talking？
Mr. Zhang?
Aunt
Is he the driver
that He Qiaoyan has been looking for?
Stop running.
Stop.
Yiyue
Over the years,
he asks me for money
several times a year.
Aunt
What the man just said
isn't true, is it?
Five years ago,
the person who caused the accident
was not Mr. Zhang
but Qiaoyan.
And Qiaoyan...
Because of the hit of Qiaoyan's brain
in the car accident
and the stress reaction,
he has lost his memory
about the accident.
In order to protect him,
I decide to hide the truth.
Aunt
These are all things
that Mr. Zhang told you.
Right?
Don't be fooled by him.
It's true.
Yiyue, have you finished?
I haven't finished my work.
So I can't pick you up tonight.
Yiyue
You are a kind person.
I beg you
to leave Qiaoyan.
Aunt
I don't know what you're talking about.
Five years ago,
did you
see a car accident?
At that time,
you also saved a little boy.
And your hand was hurt for that.
It was the same accident.
So
do you know why
I don't approve of
you two being together?
You'll bring him up to
his subconscious memories of the car accident.
Your existence
is like a time bomb
that will destroy him at any time.
Something
need to be chosen rationally.
Thank you
for saving Xiaobao at that time.
I beg you
to save Xiaobao and Qiaoyan again.
Xiaobao misses you.
When are you going home, mommy?
Xiaobao
Mommy is waiting for the car.
I'll be home soon.
Little grizzly falls.
But it dries the tears,
gets up again
and picks up its little jar.
So you're the frightened baby
several years ago.
Look how you've grown up.
Mommy is really happy.
But you've been suffered a lot.
Why should you
suffer more?
Brother
Don't go.
Brother, please don't go.
Brother, brother.
You're back.
Come here.
Why don't you answer my phone all the time?
I...
I didn't pay attention to my cell phone.
It's all right.
Qiaoyan
Are you tired?
What did you just dream about?
I dream about my brother.
Recently,
I dream about him a lot.
Can you tell me something
about your brother?
My brother
He is warm, careful
and also very enthusiastic.
When I was 12 years old,
our mom died
and dad was always busy with his work.
So it was always my brother
who spent that time with me together.
The future of us
has been arranged by my father
since I was a kid.
But my brother knew that
I was not interested in business.
What?
Go abroad.
Choose a major you like.
Don't stay here and grab Heshi Group from me.
But you know that
dad wants me to study Business.
I'll persuade dad.
You can rest assured.
Really?
Study hard.
I can handle everything.
What happened later?
My dad
was persuaded by my brother.
But I didn't expect that
I've only been abroad for two years
when my father died.
Later,
without the permission of my brother,
I changed my major to Business.
Because I knew he needed me.
He needed me to come back to help him.
But I didn't expect that,
in the fourth year after I came back,
my brother and sister-in-law
had an accident.
If your brother
knows that you are well now,
he will be happy for you.
By the way.
I want to confess one thing.
Wait a minute.
Over the years,
I always dream of
the girl's back.
Over the years,
She warms me all the time
and gives me hope.
But I'm not going to search her now.
No matter whether the back
is real or not,
no matter
what she really means to me,
I don't want to know.
All I need is you.
That's enough.
You...
Are you sure
you have only seen her in your dream?
According to
the appearance of the girl in my dream,
I drew it.
I've been looking for her all these years.
I'm sure now
I haven't seen her in my life.
What's wrong, Yiyue?
I'm fine.
I'm tired and going to bed.