♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 19=
Halt!
That's the woman.
After luring me away,
she found the
blood night-blooming cereus,
and kept it for herself.
It's you...
Quit your nonsense.
Nonsense?
There's only going to be one side
that walks out with the cereus today.
Brothers,
charge!
You are all respected
people with known names and reputations.
You all claim to be decent men,
but yet act like thugs.
Just because you can't find it,
you feel entitled to rob it?
Let's stop wasting our time.
Charge!
Mengmeng.
What did you say to her?
Well, what did you do to her?
You said you wanted to
bring Mengmeng happiness.
Is this the happiness you meant by?
I just told her the truth.
Ask yourself whether
you told her the whole truth.
What's that sound out there?
What's going on?
It sounds like a fight.
Where's Her Highness?
Zhe Xiang is also missing.
His Highness...
Crap.
You guys stay here,
and protect His Highness.
You two take care.
Mengmeng, are you OK?
It seems like...
I really am the medical supplement.
The blood night-blooming cereus...
It's glowing.
It's mine!
Protect His Highness and
seize the blood night-blooming cereus.
Your Highness, be careful!
Mengmeng, hurry!
Go.
Mengmeng, give me the flower.
Give me the flower.
Give me the flower. Give it to me.
In front of greed,
lives can be destroyed,
families can be ruined,
justice can be trampled,
and love can be used.
I can't alter
where the story is heading,
but at least
I have the ability to end it
So long,
this stupid game.
Mengmeng.
Your Highness, stay back.
The blood night-blooming cereus
is recognizing the master.
has been collecting Reiki for centuries.
The power it contains
is far beyond what
a human body can bear.
9th princess is just a normal person.
She doesn't know Kung Fu,
let alone any inner power.
The cereus will eat her alive,
and burn her organs.
She will die from
bursting carotid blood vessels.
She's asking for her own demise.
How did things end up like this?
I can't believe I bring this to her.
No.
I'm the one to blame.
If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't have had the chance.
What are you talking about?
What's going on with Mengmeng?
Mengmeng,
if you die here today,
I'll keep you company,
even if that means going through hell.
She controlled the
blood night-blooming cereus.
The cereus has chosen the master.
They've now become one.
So that means princess won't die?
Great, now I have the plot armor.
I can't even die when I want to.
She won't die.
But it might be more
frightening than dying.
Mengmeng,
come here.
you're in great danger now.
Come with me.
I can protect you.
What do you want this time?
I'm protecting her.
- Meng...
- Enough!
Murong Chen,
you said I can have the right to choose,
right?
Annoying trash.
9th princess
has been controlled by the cereus.
What have I done?
- Mengmeng.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, are you OK?
I've fine now.
It's my fault.
If it wasn't for me,
she wouldn't have misunderstood you,
wouldn't have eaten
the blood night-blooming cereus,
and then forced to leave.
Brother...
What does the
blood night-blooming cereus
have to do with the crown prince?
Murong Chen,
what's going on?
Oh, and
when did your Kung Fu skills
get so good?
It's almost like
you were possessed by Yun Ya.
Was it something I said?
Song Che,
the truth is
I am Yun Ya.
What?
5th prince,
so you have been lying to our
princess this whole time.
No wonder...
No wonder our princess wanted to
break up with you that day.
A Chen.
Song Che,
have you lost your mind?
His Highness is still wounded.
Wounded?
I would rather beat him to death.
If it wasn't for him,
could Mengmeng end up like this?
Chang Kong,
let him go.
But...
I said let him go.
You're right.
I used and lied to you from the start.
Since we were in Ruo Shui Kingdom,
I've decided to travel with you guys.
Also for Jiang Mengmeng,
I've been using her this whole time,
so she could help me get the cereus.
And today,
I wanted to use her blood
as the medical supplement
to activate the
blood night-blooming cereus.
But I didn't expect
there to be such a scene.
And now,
both the cereus and Mengmeng are gone.
All previous efforts are wasted.
It's not true.
What?
Why didn't you just do it?
You only said those things
to invoke me,
so that I would beat you up.
And that would make you feel better,
right?
When did you get so smart?
I don't care if you're
Murong Chen or Yun Ya.
Mengmeng ended up like this.
You are also the one to blame.
When I bring Mengmeng back,
I'm going to make you kowtow
and apologize to her.
But before that,
the priority is to find Mengmeng.
That's exactly right, Song Che.
The more pressing the situation is,
the more we need to stay calm.
And also, what's with Zhe Xiang?
She rescued Mengmeng,
but didn't say a word.
Where did she bring Mengmeng?
I know!
Zhe Xiang is from Nan Cang.
She must have brought Mengmeng there.
I'll go find her right away.
She didn't go to Nan Cang.
How do you know that?
Song Che,
I'm going to be honest with you.
Zhe Xiang is just like me.
She has two identities.
Her real identity
is the first disciple of 	Jing Yue Sect.
You...
You mean...
She's...
from Jing Yue Sect.
Correct.
She pretended to be an oiran to join us,
and her real goal was
to get close to Jiang Mengmeng
and the blood night-blooming cereus.
No way...
Giving others shoes indicates
that you want them to leave.
With the IQ you have,
you're going to be tricked by others.
So at that time she already...
All of you
are just a bunch of lairs.
All efforts are wasted.
The blood night-blooming cereus is gone,
and there will be no hope for
me to practice Blood Moon Power.
What's the point of keeping her?
Master,
could you please leave her be.
Zhe Xiang,
I've kept you for years.
You've been with them
only for a few months.
How could you be silly enough
to give away your true heart?
It's my fault for not
trying hard enough.
If master must punish someone,
let it be me.
I'll willingly accept it.
I only beg you to let Jiang Mengmeng go.
You will definitely be punished,
but Jiang Mengmeng...
Master.
- What's wrong?
- Master.
Senior.
Jiang Mengmeng is
tearing the house apart.
You should check on it.
You did all this?
Mengmeng,
are you OK?
I didn't mean to...
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I can't control myself.
It must be the
blood night-blooming cereus.
(This is so mystical.)
(The cereus is fully absorbed.)
(She is the chosen one.)
(The chosen one!)
Master.
Rest assured.
I won't hurt her.
On the contrary,
I'll treat her well.
(Jing Yue Sect's Secret Chamber)
Let's begin.
Feel the power inside you.
Try to control the way it flows.
Your body has absorbed the
blood night-blooming cereus.
But for you,
it's way too powerful.
It's trapped in this mortal body,
and all it wants to do is escape,
which may cause destruction.
After you can fully control it,
I will teach you the
first level of Blood Moon Power.
The Secret Chamber is forbidden.
Only master and
our senior Zhe Xiang is allowed in.
But now,
master allows that Jiang Mengmeng
to enter as well.
I don't know what she's thinking.
(Chen Yan, Luo Xue)
Does master want her to be a disciple?
Oh, god!
I don't want this monster
to be my junior.
Senior,
did you bring home a Trojan horse?
When did 	Jing Yue Sect's affairs
become something you can moan about?
Listen clearly.
Jiang Mengmeng is
the saintess of Jing Yue Sect
and also my only heir.
Disrespecting her
is disrespecting me.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to rescue Mengmeng right now.
Do you even know what kind of place
Jing Yue Sect is?
Like Bai Hua Village,
just a bunch of women.
I can rescue Mengmeng
from Bai Hua Village,
and Jing Yue Sect will be the same.
You know nothing about 	Jing Yue Sect.
You breaking in like that
is asking for your own demise.
Of course,
Mr. "Master of Tian Ji Pavilion",
and Mr. Know-it-all.
You knew that Mengmeng's blood
is the key to activate the cereus.
You also knew Zhe Xiang
is a spy from Jing Yue Sect.
But you still let all of this happen,
just watching Zhe Xiang take Mengmeng.
Now I want to rescue her,
and you're trying to stop me.
Murong Chen,
what on earth is going on in your head?
Song Che,
- His Highness...
- Chang Kong.
Jiang Mengmeng has eaten the cereus,
and almost started a slaughter.
This has spread all over the world.
So what?
If Jiang Mengmeng
shows herself in public now,
people will want to kill her.
Why?
Her Highness didn't do anything wrong.
Well, others don't think like that.
You men of the world,
are ridiculous.
Initially, you fought against each other
for the blood night-blooming cereus.
Now that the power of the cereus
shifted to Jiang Mengmeng,
you regard her as a common enemy.
Being frustrated won't solve anything.
Jiang Mengmeng is now
staying in 	Jing Yue Sect,
and that's much safer than
being out in the world.
On the topic of rescuing her,
we need time and
discussion on strategies.
Are you hearing yourself?
Mengmeng is with Yu Qingzhu.
She's probably suffering right now.
When you're done with your discussing,
Mengmeng could be dead by then.
Zhe Xiang is there,
and she'll find ways
to protect Mengmeng.
Everything we're going through
is caused by Zhe Xiang.
How can you still trust her?
Anyway,
I trust her.
I get it now.
Your goal was the
blood night-blooming cereus.
Now that the cereus is gone,
Mengmeng no longer has value to you,
so you never thought of saving her,
right?
No response.
Fine.
Since you don't care about her,
I will.
I will rescue her,
even if that means losing this life.
Xiao Ai,
Song Che can't even find where
Jing Yue Sect is.
You sure you want to follow him?
I...
Chang Kong,
return to Tian Ji Pavilion.
Yes.
Why...
Why did everybody leave?
I...
Your Highness...
I did that?
You've learned it,
and all it took was once.
I didn't expect that
this good memory skill
can have added buff.
What?
What's buff?
Buff is like...
an enhancing skill.
Like when I ate the
blood night-blooming cereus,
that's also like a buff.
What's this?
It smells nice.
This is...
something called Xuefuxiang,
and it improves your power.
They all call you a demon.
Is that so?
But I think you're a nice person.
Why so?
Because like,
I ate your blood night-blooming cereus,
and tore apart your house.
But you didn't punish me.
Instead, you teach me Kung Fu,
and also how to control my power.
So I think
you're a nice person.
Are you trying to flatter me?
Oops, you can tell.
To be honest,
when I first heard you ate the cereus,
I was very upset.
I wanted to kill you right away.
But then I realized,
the cereus has seen you as its master.
Then I thought,
this might not be a coincidence.
Everything has a reason.
I've worked hard for so many years.
But I never could master
Blood Moon Power.
And I definitely
couldn't single-handedly
accomplish 	Jing Yue Sect's great cause.
But you
might be my god-given buff.
You learn pretty quick.
So rest assured.
I won't wake up one day
and decide to kill you.
Thank you then.
But I have another question.
Just ask.
That Blood Moon Power thing...
Could I maybe not learn it?
What did you just say?
You said...
you were not going to kill me.
The pre-condition for that
is that you must be
Jing Yue Sect's saintess,
and be my only heir.
As long as you behave,
in the future,
Jing Yue Sect will own the world.
And it will all belong to you.
Why would a nobody like me
want to own the world?
Try me and say that again.
I mean I'll learn it.
I'll learn it, OK?
I will.
We shall continue.
The Blood Moon Power have five levels.
No feelings,
no thoughts,
no form,
no ego,
and no end.
The first level, no feelings.
This means you must
cut all ties and all relationships.
Mortals have feelings.
Therefore, they have strings attached.
If you can overcome feelings,
you can overcome mortals,
and become fearless.
Everything will then seem like nothing,
and even iron walls
will seem like paper.
I mean... The first level
is already quite awesome.
Just follow me and learn.
(Jing Yue Sect's Medicine Storage)
(Ecstasy Incense)
Qing He.
What's the matter, senior?
Why is there one missing?
The incense can control people's minds.
Losing it can cause big trouble.
Master took one this morning.
I forgot to register it.
Master?
Where is she now?
She's teaching the Saintess
in the Secret Chamber.
(Jiang Mengmeng)
(Was I helping you)
(or bringing harm to you?)
Chang Kong,
send out the Tian Ji Token.
Rally all members from other branches,
and destroy every 	Jing Yue Sect branch.
Yes.
Have you seen a girl that's
very tall,
very fierce,
and very badass when she fights?
Have you seen a...
Jing Yue Sect.
Where's Jing Yue Sect?
I don't know.
Jing Yue...
(Jing Yue)
- Zhe Xiang. Zhe Xiang.
- What are you doing?
Where are you, Zhe Xiang?
Zhe Xiang, come out to see me?
Zhe Xiang.
- Zhe Xiang.
- Get out.
(Jing Yue Restaurant)
♪Sand dances as the wind blows,
armored horses charge in the field♪
♪Who is killing in this troubled time♪
♪The sunset glow shines the cliff,
where the blood battle takes place♪
♪Always thinking about her♪
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪