♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts
and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[Written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Captain Haider.
This is the sea map that I drew.
Happy to provide service for you.
Please follow me.
You can rest assured.
Captains who are brave enough to sail far
all have a map in their minds.
I don't want any of these things.
I just want to be with you forever.
But
the more fantastic feelings
are yet to come.
No!
[Episode 164]
No.
Those who kill people at sea
will eventually receive trails
conducted by the sea.
No!
Please spare my life.
The Purple Pearl Pirates asked us to do this!
Purple Pearl Pirates?
We need a good talk.
The sea is calm
but...
I feel strange somehow.
Xiang.
Go back for a rest.
I'll do the job.
No, thanks.
This is my job.
I can do this.
Don't say this.
In the sould arena last time,
if you hadn't caught me in time,
I would have fallen into pieces.
That's nothing.
We won because of you.
You have so much fighting experience.
I was surprised
that you suppressed water with fire.
That's certain.
We Shrek Seven Devils
were once famous for
our achievements on soul arenas.
Ever-victorious, you know?
All you know is brag.
But
I envy you a lot
for having been through
so many adventures with your friends.
I wanted to travel around before
but Grandpa was always worried
and kept me home.
Now you are one of us.
So
we'll go through
the adventures to come.
It'd be even better
if you're mine!
San.
Is it a good idea to let Haider take the wheel?
We aren't familiar with sailing on the sea.
Having him take us to Haishen Island
is the only way.
Pirates like him who only care about money
will surely obey
to be alive.
We take turns for night watch
just in case.
I'll take the first night.
OK.
I'm going back to my room first.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
So many accidents have happened
before we reach Haishen Island.
San said he'd take the shift for tonight.
But we must stay alert.
San has his reason to keep Haider
yet we can't let down our guard
for the safety concerns.
Papa.
I'm the King of Pirates material.
Son.
Rest assured.
I'll drag them to the grave with you.
What's wrong?
Let's hurry back!
What have you done?
You said "get there as soon as possible"
so I sail straight in full speed.
Now we are in the Magic Whales' territory.
Magic Whales' territory?
Deep down this sea area
is a submarine trench of a thousand meter deep.
In the trench
lives a Century Millennium Sea Soul Beast,
Deep Sea Magic Whale.
Why didn't you take a detour?
Speak!
Calm down.
Although Magic Whales dominate the sea,
they were born lazy
and only lurk in the bottom of the sea
to gulp down sea creatures.
Moreover, its left eye is blind.
We won't offend it
as long as we sail to his left eye direction.
It's too late.
Sea Devil is now in the right-eye direction.
[Soul Land]
The bomb just cast into the sea
has already irritated the Magic Whale.
It's said
that this thing is too powerful
so the God of the Sea poked its left eye.
Are you mad?
You'll also lose your life here.
Life?
You guys got my son killed.
I want your lives for his life.
Come on!
Kill me!
So I can see my son again.
Something's wrong.
Watch out!
I can understand you, a father.
But
how many people's sons have you killed
in your days as a pirate?
I won't kill you today.
Run
if you can.
The Magic Whale
is almost here.
What's happening?
Ao!
Flight Mushroom Sausage.
Now!
Ao.
Let's go.
This is the King of Deep Sea Magic Whales.
Such strong pressure is way beyond
which brought by a Century Millennium Soul Beast
such as the Titan Giant Ape
and thr Azure Bull Python.
It's a domain.
Straight line.
Soft Bone Rabbit Soul Bone Skill.
Invincible Golden Shield.
We can't avoid it.
Seven in One Fusion Skill
Invincible Golden Shield.
Brother San, let's fight to our last breath.
God Killer Attack.
[Since the commencement of animating
Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 164 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1529 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2479]
[Total scene: 60741]
[Total CGI: 28121]
[Total plan of action scene: 12624]
[Total scene model: nearly 569]
[Total character model: nearly 1035]
[Total props model: 13395]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest, illuminating
in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise, I have much
that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolors ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
If you want your friends to live,
move aside.
Even the strongest ocean soul beast
can't heal as fast as he does.
What if I can improve your soul power?
You...
What did you say?
Xiao Wu,
it's meaningless.
The rest is on you now.
Can't believe that guy
actually finished
the process of turning into a dragon.