Tine Teepakorn, a freshman from Faculty of Law,
I like you!
What?
You guys have to help me find a way to get rid of Green.
Date a guy then.
Sarawat from Faculty of Political Science, IR major
How hot does he think he is?
This is the type of guy that can make Green back off.
Seems like it’s not just me who wants to see Sarawat
Can you help…?
What are you doing?
Helping you.
Sorry.
A presentation is about to start.
Why don’t you come tomorrow?
We are late because we were talking to those girls about you.
They wanted to have my Facebook or Line ID, right?
They wanted to know about your ‘wanting to eat Sarawat’ status
How hungry were you, really?
I told you a thousand times that I didn’t post that.
Sarawat did it.
I have no idea how he knew my password.
The first group, are you guys ready to present?
We are.
But may we have a second? We’re having a problem connecting to a projector.
Ohm, can you go borrow the cable from next door?
Me again?
Yes.
[Was Sarawat delicious?]
Sarawat, how did you know my lock screen password?
[You set a dumb password, 1 2 3 4 5 6.]
[Even a little kid can find out.]
Saraleo! Stop messing with my Facebook account
Do you even get what I mean?!?
[Sexy Uni Girl in Classroom]
Saraleo!
I am sorry for being loud, professor.
Shit!
Damn it!
Shit! Since when?
Since your dumb password.
I wanted to tell you but it was so pleasing to watch
Guys, I got a new cable.
Tine, can I ask you a question?
Do you like Sarawat?
Of course not.
I like girls.
What a relief!
I saw you joined Team Sarawat’s Wives Group and you posted you wanted to eat him.
I was in shock
My friends were just messing around.
Why?
Are you afraid I will be taken?
I am afraid Sarawat will be taken.
It’s all good now. See you later.
You better hurry and get his phone fixed
before your image is completely ruined.
You don’t usually have any to keep anyway.
Hey!
I do, all right?
Does he think he will get away with this so easily?
Are you getting revenge on him?
No.
I’m going to get his phone fixed.
Sir, do you think you can fix this one?
Let me see.
Not hard,
Yo! Yo! I can fix it!
You can?
It can’t be turned on.
I think the battery dies.
Battery dies?
What is that smoke?
An electric shock, I guess.
Yo! Yo!
It’s nothing.
I can fix it
You sure?
Not hard, Yo! Yo!
It’s not hard to fix?
It’s not hard to give up and throw away
Yo! Yo!
May I recommend a new one? Yo! Yo!
I’ll give you a special price.
This one?
Yes.
I’m sure you’ll love it.
Yo! Yo!
It’s a triple-sim phone.
3 SIM?
Who would I call?
Girls.
Is there any other shop around?
Hey!
This one is smaller and its battery lasts longer than your previous one
Plus a charger here.
The battery will be fully charged in no time.
I am sorry
I will ask my mom for money and buy you a new one.
Okay?
Don’t need to.
I already bought a new one
You did?
Why did you want me to fix your old one then?
Because you needed to take responsibility for the damage.
Here is your phone.
Wait!
I need to talk to you about something.
But I don’t.
Please. I will take less than 10 seconds. I promise.
I give you 5…
4 3 2…
Be my boyfriend.
What on earth did you just say?
Not a real boyfriend
Just pretend that you like me.
I’ve been followed around by someone.
So I need you to be my shield.
Why?
Is she not pretty?
It’s a guy but I like girls.
What’s wrong with that?
It’s good that someone admires you.
It’s not good.
I don’t like people to get too involved with my personal life
You will never know.
Someday you might want someone to be a nuisance in your life.
That’s funny.
I know you don’t like people to invade your private life either.
There is one anyway.
One?
Where?
It’s you!
You’re such a nuisance in my life.
Me?
You let him go just like that?
How stupid!
He said that to my face. What would you do?
Right, Fong?
Right.
Phuak is right.
You don’t have his number. How will you contact him now?
You’re silly!
Ohm, go ahead and yell at me like these two just did.
Shit!
That’s it?
I wasn’t talking to you
Someone posted a video of Sarawat in a closed group
I’m sure we will get something out of this.
Sarawat, what club will you be joining tomorrow?
I don’t know.
What kind of activity do you like?
We might be in the same club.
Football, archery, planting, meditation, boxing, fencing…
Why doesn’t he mention scuba diving and coral planting too?
Scuba diving and coral planting too.
See?
Let’s not watch it.
It gets me frustrated
I think I just found you the way
If you can get in the same club he’s in, you’ll get to see him more often
That’s right
There’s one problem though.
We don’t know which club he’s going to join
Right.
That is easy.
A senior called him this morning and told him to go rehearse in the music club.
Music club?
You know and you just sit here making a dumb face?
What a dumb ass!
I don’t know what to call you, really
You give me a headache.
My head hurts!
But I can’t play any musical instrument.
Get into the club first and think about it later.
We will apply too and help you talk to Sarawat.
Hot freshmen over there, do you want to join Swimming Club?
We do.
Hold on!
What about our Music Club?
Music Club.
Swimming Club?
What?
We all do.
Where do we apply?
Right here.
Tine!
OH YOU'RE HERE-
Come with me.
Let me apply first.
Come here!
Fill out your application.
Are you tired swimming?
Don’t look!
I found a club for you, Tine
Green, why are you here?
Don’t look at them.
Ta-da! Welcome to Cooking Club
I used to think I would cook for my boyfriend every day if I had one.
I made you some cookies.
Let’s try it
Wait a minute.
Why not? Don’t you want it?
It’s not that.
It looks yummy
It looks so yummy that I want to call my friends to taste it too
Really?
Really.
Good.
I have so many dishes I want you to try
Wait for me here just one moment.
Hurry back.
I’ll be back soon.
See you soon.
Okay.
[Music Club]
Guys, please get in line.
I got it!
Tine my beloved friend, how are you?
But you guys are bad friends.
You saw girls and you left me instantly.
How will you snatch your spot from those girls?
Hi guys.
My name is Air. I am a club secretary.
This is P’Dim. He is our club president.
Our Music Club was founded more than 30 years ago
It has brought fame and admiration to our University.
But this year…
I heard that many of you join our club because of some guy.
If you are only here just to chase a guy,
get up and find yourself out
Do it fiercely when we sing ‘bounces up and down
You just asked me to be your boyfriend yesterday
I guess a kiss from me won’t hurt
If you are only here just to chase a guy, get up and find yourself out.
Wait!
As long as you love music, we don’t mind how it all starts.
P’Dim, we can't take them all anyway. We have a limitation.
Don’t let that trivial thing ruin our standard.
I will deal with the University board about that.
Welcome everyone to our Music Club.
Before you become our club members,
you have to go through our special welcoming ceremony.
You all need to sing these famous songs so loud that every being in this place can hear
And that would be ‘Roasted Chicken’ and many activity songs.
Now everyone, get up!
♪ Roasted Chicken ♫
♪ It will be on stick ♫
♪ Stick it in its left ass ♫
♪ Stick it in its right ass ♫
♪ Ooh! It’s so hot! So hot! So hot! ♫
For the next song, come out here Sarawat.
Come on out.
The reason to dance is that…
when we are on stage, we are all stiff.
This will break the ice and make you relax.
Kill it, man.
Come to the center.
The song ‘Apple Papaya Banana Orange’
♪ Apple Apple Apple ♫
♪ Papaya Papaya Papaya ♫
♪ Banana Banana Banana ♫
♪ Orange Orange Orange ♫
♪ Apple Papaya Banana Orange ♫
I need one more
A cheerleader, come out here.
Tine!
♪ Stick it in its left ass ♫
♪ Stick it in its right ass ♫
♪ Ooh! It’s so hot! So hot! So hot! ♫
Let’s pretend that I’m you.
Why do I have to do things like this in life?
Sarawat, get out of my face.
♪ Spider wanders out at night ♫
♪ When the clock hits 2 am, it bounces up and down ♫
Have you not been through any recreation activity?
What about me?
You…bounce on top.
Who will be at the bottom?
No one.
♪ Spider wanders out at night ♫
♪ When the clock hits 2 am, it bounces up and down ♫
One more time and we’ll be done.
One more spider and we will move on.
Do it fiercely when we sing ‘bounces up and down.’
♪ Spider wanders out at night ♫
♪ When the clock hit 2 am, it bounces up and down ♫
We have come to our last activity.
This game is called ‘Snack For Friendship.’
It’s so easy.
You will feed a snack to your friend using…
…your mouth.
Air, hand them their snack.
How many?
One for each pair.
If you drop it, everyone in your row will be punished
It will be a bit harder for girls.
Start now!
You need to eat it too.
Eat bit by bit, Wat!
Make it as short as possible
They totally pass.
Everyone in this place has gone through our welcoming ceremony!
You will have a 15-minute break.
After that, we will talk about our club rules.
See you guys in a bit.
What are you thinking about?
Everyone has gone on their break.
Thinking about what you did.
You think you can mess with me all you want?
You mean the kiss?
It wasn’t a kiss!
It was just a game. Why did you have to be serious about it?
Why are you being hot-headed now?
You just asked me to be your boyfriend yesterday.
A little kiss from me won’t hurt.
Tine, you are mischievous.
Only two seconds in that club and you got to kiss Sarawat
Our lips just touched, not a kiss.
Shit! Who recorded this?
Let’s take a break from this topic.
What I want to know is whether Sarawat agrees to help you or not.
You’re right. I didn’t ask him
I didn’t think about it.
I need to hurry before Green gets you kicked out of that club
Don’t worry. It’s easier to see him now
I will ask him to help me this evening.
That’s my boy.
See you then, Sarawat.
What? He’s not here?
Yes.
Those who can actually play will rehearse in a different room so you guys can focus.
These are the beginners from the first year?
For guitar, yes.
The rest are playing something else.
What do I need to do if I want to practice with those who can play?
You need to know the basic chords first.
You will get used to them in no time.
This guitar is a legend
It was used to win competitions?
Nope.
Its owner died of a heart attack.
It is now a club’s possession
Its strings are big and hard but you will get used to it one day
Come here. I’ll teach you.
This is chord C. It is the most basic one.
Look at my fingers.
Use your point, middle, and ring finger
Try it.
P’Air, you’re actually cute
Yeah?
Chord C now.
Like this?
It sounds wired. What did you do wrong?
Try it again.
What kind of strings are they? This is painful
Cooking Club always welcomes you, Tine
I heard that Music Club was cruel to you. They gave you an old guitar to practice.
I was so shocked.
I am more shocked that you know about this
I know everything about you
Move to my club and you will get to eat delicious food every day.
I made this especially for you
Thank you for your concern but I am okay
I need to get back to the club.
Tine, don’t go!
Tine, you seem really determined.
I will do whatever it takes to be in this club
What?
I mean I will keep practicing hard.
I will play a song eventually.
That’s good.
But what you played earlier were all wrong.
No worries. You still have time. You will get better
We have no time.
Why is that?
The University board doesn’t allow more club members than we agreed on.
This Friday, newbies have to go through a test
Those who fail will be out of this club.
What chord are you playing exactly?
What chord is it?
I don’t know either.
P’Dim, are you being serious?
Do we have any other way?
No.
And don’t be too nice to freshmen.
My guitar. Try it.
Where is the guy who comes to practice every day?
He might be finding himself a new club.
I don’t think he will pass the test
The test will be on Friday. Don’t forget to practice
Tine, you’re still here.
Yeah. I don’t have a guitar of my own.
So I think I will play on a bit more.
You guys can go.
I like your determination.
But what you play is still wrong
Thank you for your advice
Enjoy your snacks. From Team Sarawat’s Wives.
I am not stealing.
I am just protecting your snacks from anyone who wants to steal them
Wrong!
Can your fingers work properly?
Press harder
Wrong!
I can’t press any harder
Here.
What?
My guitar.
Its strings are better
Try it.
It’s okay.
Just take it.
Now play it.
It’s right this time.
Does it hurt your fingers?
No.
That’s good.
Keep practicing.
Now try chord E.
How do you do chord E?
Move over.
Your middle finger on the second fret, fifth string
Your ring finger on the second fret, fourth string.
Your point finger on the first fret, third string.
Now play it.
Memorize it so I don’t have to teach you again.
Play on.
What are you looking at?
I'm just wondering why you aren't in the Faculty of Music since you're so good.
I play because I enjoy it
I’m afraid that if I actually learn it,
it won’t give me pleasure anymore.
I do what I like by heart, not by duty
What are you still looking at?
I’m begging you.
Please help me.
Just pretend that you like me.
So you’re in this club because of this?
It’s not like that.
It’s…
Yes! I admit it.
Now that you know it, please help to be my fake boyfriend
Are you saying yes or no?
[Faculty Building]
Sarawat is here.
Record a video.
Let’s take a selfie.
Sarawat…
Have you seen a guy who comes to practice here every day?
I haven’t seen him
He might be finding himself a new club.
I don’t think he will pass the test.
P’Dim wants to see you in the storage room but I have no idea why.
Is that you, nuisance?!?
Do you think I will give up that easily?
If you want to get out, you have to be my fake boyfriend.
Deal with your own problem.
Let me out.
Up to you then.
Sleep tight in there tonight.
Are you threatening me?
Do you want to get hurt?
Do you think I’m afraid?
Tine!!
Are you in here? I think I just saw you.
You won’t get out of Music Club because you’re afraid of your seniors. Am I right?
Don’t be. I have friends from Bodybuilder Club just to help you.
Let me deal with the seniors for you
Open, please
Tine.
You don’t want to be in that club.
Just resign and join Cooking Club with me.
I know that someone is in there
If you don’t open the door, I will.
What are you doing here so loud?
I was sleeping in there?
Who are you here for?
In there?
Yeah, why?
I’m looking for Tine. Have you seen him?
Tine?
No.
Really?
I’m going to continue my sleep.
Anything else?
Nope.
Sleeping in a cupboard?
Sorry for bothering.
Bye bye.
Tine!
Come out, nuisance
That was close.
Thank you so much.
I didn’t want to help you.
I just didn’t want to get involved in your business.
It’s a good idea to change the club.
You won’t pass a test for Music Club.
What if I pass?
If I pass, you have to be my fake boyfriend.
Deal?
If you do, I’ll help you.
But if you fail, you have to leave me alone
Deal.
The result is out.
We don’t pass.
You told him you would stop bothering him if you failed?
Yes.
I didn’t have time to think
Who would think he’d challenge me back like that?
Can I call him and cancel the deal?
It’s too late now.
The test is tomorrow.
You don’t have a guitar, don’t you?
I don’t.
Are you buying me a guitar?
I am.
A guitar practicing app.
I just downloaded it for you
You are so stingy when it comes to friends.
You can buy this but can’t buy me a guitar
Come on.
We don’t have a guitar for you but we promise to stay with you all night
We won’t yawn
Won’t lie down.
Won’t sleep.
You guys can go back to your rooms actually
You all are distracting me
I’m cold.
That’s enough.
Get out.
Next.
The bottom
Down there.
You need some help?
Shit!
30 years since this club was founded,
you’re the only one who dares to do this
I…
Get out!
Next!
Wait!
I am sorry
I really want to be in this club
Can I have one more chance? Let me play again.
Please.
P’Dim…
Tine practiced very hard.
He kept playing with that old guitar with hard strings
That’s right.
I think we should give him one more shot
Wat, bring out your guitar for him to play.
He did it within a week.
Do you know anything else apart from the basic chords?
I don’t.
Do you like acoustic, classical, or electric guitar?
How are they different?
Do you know any other musical instruments?
I don’t
Do you anything at all?
It’s fine.
If we fail, we will go find some other club together.
I am so excited.
When will the result come out?
The result is out, guys
It’s here!
We don’t pass!
Move!
I pass the test.
Don’t forget your word
They let you pass because they felt pity for you.
Are you breaking the promise?
By the way, these snacks are from your fans.
Hey! I got one too.
From Prim?
Who is Prim?
Is she that cute little girl?
You have a lot there. Why are you taking mine?
What?
What are you doing?
Okay.
Okay what?
OKAY!
What the heck are you saying ok to?
Okay. I will be your fake boyfriend.
He is taken
Hey! So you will help me?
Do you know any other musical instruments?
I don’t
Damn!
Do you know anything at all?
I know Sarawat
He is the reason I want to play guitar.
Directed by Weerachit Thongjila
You came to see Sarawat again.
Why are guys always together these days?
I heard the rumor saying Sarawat likes Tine. Is it true?
True.
You can compete for anything with anyone
but you can’t beat Sarawat when it comes to love
You agreed to help me because you wanted some experience to write a song?
I have a guitar with very soft strings in my room
Can I borrow yours to record a video?
You can with on condition.
Go get it at my place.