[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 38]
[Operational Command Post On Duty]
All buddies of Special Force Two.
a new round of battle is beginning.
Listen up.
In this round of battle,
there will be no supply
or reinforcement for us.
The whole Blue Army, attention.
I am commander.
I only have
one order.
Any enemies landing on this island
should be eliminated
at all costs.
[Chief Director, Red Army Director]
At 6: 25 P.M.,
the Red Army completed a sudden attack
and landed on the island forcibly.
The two parties
have been fighting for more than 4 hours on the island.
There are casualties in both parties.
At 10: 50 P.M.,
the Blue Army organized a counterattack and succeeded.
[Chief Director]
Now, the Red Army is withdrawing orderly.
Didn't the Red Army get reinforcement?
How come it takes them 4 hours to land on the island?
Chief, report.
The Blue Army
blew up two scrapped supply ships
which sank in the water in front of the wharf.
The assault boats of the Red Army
could not approach effective landing point.
Their soldiers could only swim from distant intertidal zone
which is 100 meters away from the land.
Their commandos were totally exposed
to snipers.
They suffered heavy loss and moved very slowly.
The number of soldiers of the Blue Army has reduced to less than three companies.
The Red Army has absolute advantages on military strength.
Why they refused to hang in on the island
and withdrew?
What kind of strategy they are using?
Chief,
the Blue Army mainly consists of special troops.
Offshore,
they formed groups of frogmen
and attacked the naval vessels of the Red Army on the sneak.
In the intertidal zone, they organized firepower
to eliminate the Red Army's effectives.
On the island,
they set up barriers
to prevent the Red Army from moving forward.
[Communication]
Once the Red Army lands on the isalnd,
the Blue Army will withdraw to the underground fortifications.
They wait until the night
and act as special force groups
to raid the Red Army.
It's disadvantageous for the Red Army to fight at night.
So they have no way but to withdraw
and launch attacks again after daybreak.
The fight between the cheetah and the hyena
turns out to be the current deadlock.
[Map of A Army's Operational Area]
Didn't the aerial firepower of the Red Army
launch two rounds of bombing?
Three rounds.
And the bombing was very effective.
The Blue Army failed to reconstruct firepower on the island.
[Integrated Coordination]
And their radars
were taken down yesterday.
The artillery on the island were bombed for three times.
[Integrated Coordination]
Blow up all of them.
Now, they
can only fight with small arms.
And they may have a few
shoulder-fired anti-aircraft missiles for infantry
and anti-tank rockets.
They are tough.
[Signal breaks up]
What's going on?
Qin Hanyong,
[Signal breaks up]
your TV on the island is of poor quality.
It broke down at the beginning of the battle.
Does it
fail to handle
the violent battle?
Qin Hanyong.
Get somebody to fix it right now.
Don't delay observation team's work.
Yes.
In terms of the situation,
the Special Force Team is withdrawing quickly.
But the Regiment 700's way of
eliminating the Blue Army's effectives
costs too much.
No bargains when it comes to the sovereignty issue.
Moreover, Regiment 700 has enough sources of soldiers.
We could defeat them by consuming soldiers.
That's enough.
Who is on duty today?
Negotiate with them and get some water.
I used seawater to take a shower yesterday.
But I felt like being bit
and failed to sleep the whole night.
Chief.
Don't blame me for making suggestions.
You
are being well taken care of by Qin Hanyong,
right?
But when they meet us, people from Division 234,
they are harsh.
Yes.
Chief.
In my opinion,
you should do the negotiation.
You are of high status.
I am a hostage now.
My status is not working.
It doesn't matter.
Even though you are a hostage, you are the head of us.
Think about terrorists.
After being captured,
the head will read the statement according to the draft.
You are the head.
We are your minions.
Get away.
OK. I'll go.
Chief,
water is here.
They delivered the water?
I get it on my own.
Natural mineral water.
They haven't delivered water today, have they?
Did you seek personal privileges again?
Stupid.
It is raining.
We collect the water at the air outlet.
If so, I want to get some too.
Hurry up.
Collect more.
Who's there?
Wait.
I told you not to push me.
Get back.
Captain Qin is collecting water, too.
Why can't I do so while he can?
Because he is Captain Qin and you are not.
Behave yourself.
Comrade.
I am not your comrade.
And you.
They all pee at toilet.
But you have to pee at the marine outfall.
They all pee twice a day.
But you have to pee eight times.
And it does not include crapping.
Why you are troublesome?
Young man,
why you are so angry?
When you are at my age,
you will know the feeling of urgency, frequency, and difficulty of urination.
I am warning you.
Don't approach the pipes,
or I will get you some troubles.
Get back.
Division commander,
forget him.
Drink some water.
I can't.
I am not welcomed.
Song, calm down.
Chief,
did you hear that?
I am in uniform and wear the marks.
How come a senior colonel in the PLA
is being treated in that way?
Calm down.
Song.
Juat take it as
experiencing the feeling of being a hostage.
Take it as a kind of experience.
It may be useful some day.
Just forget it.
I am not angry.
It doesn't matter.
Right.
Who won't be angry?
It's hurting my self-esteem.
What's wrong with peeing frequently?
That's because of the wounds
on the battlefield.
You've brought a diaper with you?
Sticking-plaster.
Who asks you to pee eight times a day?
Hold it.
Yes.
Song, stick with it.
It's just a day.
That's right.
If Gu Yiye fails to take down the Qiaotou Island today,
I swear I will
hang him up and hit him after I go back.
Chief.
So here are the night snacks?
Yes.
OK. Bring them in.
-Yes. -Hurry up.
Be quiet.
Nanzheng.
Engineer Jiang, we are going back first.
I am looking for you.
The data you broadcast this morning
was read by chiefs.
They are all satisfied.
The commander also asked
whether they could sponsor the Mountain Net Number Two.
He said that troops were enjoying benefits
while the Command Military was paying.
Did the Red Army withdraw again today?
Yes. Soon after it got dark.
And they chose to withdraw.
Why did they do it again?
It was mainly because Gu Yiye
lost ten tanks
and more than 200 soldiers on the island.
He learned his lesson
so he withdrew soon after it got dark.
He launched all attacks
in daytime.
ow about him?
How is he doing?
You mean Gao Liang?
Wait, didn't you have the real-time data?
You didn't see him?
He only showed up once today.
And left quickly.
No wonder.
He seldom stays at the Operational Command Post.
Jiang Weixing is in that position.
The signal is poor
and smoke and fire is heavy outside.
And the director department
asks for the whole scene.
They emphasized not to shoot the details.
So you can't see him.
What?
You miss him?
Just now,
did you notice
why I drank the rainwater
instead of negotiating with hem?
Since the attack from yesterday's afternoon,
the Special Force Team has not put flour on
the face of the Regiment 700's soldiers they captured.
Also,
it is almost the noon.
The three bottles of fresh water they promised
haven't been sent yet.
He did not forget.
Gao Liang
is doing one thing.
He wants to delay the battle
until the time that no one could predict.
It is true that they are soldiers from Regiment 700.
I know my soldiers.
They are all hung in the water.
I didn't dare to stay longer.
I think
they are the 25 soldiers
that were captured at the first attack.
Any guards?
There's one.
We have to figure out ways to release them.
Release them?
Wait.
For what?
Calculate the number and hang them up again?
After being locked up for several days,
you get crazy?
For these 25 soldiers,
who are they?
Captured personnel.
They are captured but not dead.
After they are released,
they are sill powerful enough to fight.
Division commander.
You get crazy.
Has Qin Hanyong driven you mad?
Regiment 700 cannot lose to the Special Force Team.
If we are just waiting here,
even though we are thirsty or starving to death
Gu Yiye can't get in.
Then what do you want to do?
I know the ammunition depot of the Blue Army.
As long as we release our soldiers,
take the weapons,
bomb the ammunition depot
and make the headquarter a mess,
the Special Force Troop will lose.
But
we are not combat troops
but hostages.
That's the point.
Don't you know the duties of hostages?
Never give up to the hijackers
and seize chances to revolt.
Go.
Release them.
I am from the official troop.
I cannot do that.
This is emergency.
Let me think about it.
Think about what?
If you are not in,
I will do it on my own.
What happened?
Hush.
Keep silent.
I am the division commander of Division 234.
Song Jianshe.
Everyone, keep silent.
Watch out.
Are you ok?
You are out.
You cannot violate the disciplines.
Is that clear?
Yes.
Chief.
They are so bad.
Cut off food and drinks
and eavesdrop our conversation.
Save your complaints.
Say them later.
Now,
I am leading you to
take revenge.
Who are combatants?
Report.
leader of Platoon 1, Company 2 under the Battalion 1 of Regiment 700
Zhao Xiaoyong is ready for your order.
OK.
Now, I will recover your identities as combatants.
We will work in three groups.
Two groups are going to take their weapons and their channels away.
The other group
follow me and bomb their ammunition depot.
Clear?
Clear.
Wu Bo, Chen Tong.
Yes.
Both of you pick seven soldiers.
The rest follow me.
Yes.
Don't move.
Go.
Chief,
this is the situation.
Got it.
What?
What happened?
Where is Song?
Song went to rescue the captured personnel of the Red Army.
To rescue the captured personnel of the Red Army？
Yes.
And then
he will take them to blow up the ammunition depot of the Blue Army.
This is bullshit.
The director department stated clearly that
superiors cannot intervene
and let commanders fight themselves.
If the Division 234 is doing so,
I will take part in the battle, too.
Qin, calm down.
Theoretically,
you can actually do so.
According to the director department,
we are hostages now, right?
As criterion for hijackers to blackmail,
which are commonly called hostages,
among us
there will be hostages who are willing to cooperate,
hostages who
get Stockholm syndrome,
and hostages who would fight back.
I think Song belongs to the last type.
It not only fits the real identity of hostages
but also the content of the practice.
In other words,
when you two
are planning secretly,
I have already figured out your plan.
That's also why
I did not stop them.
Chief,
you gave birth to the Special Force Team
and you cultivated them.
It is your own son in certain degree.
If you are rebelling, just do it together.
Stop there.
Since the beginning of the drill,
you have been in opposing camps,
causing conflicts.
I didn't criticized you.
And you think that i am indulging you?
What's your current identities?
You are hostages.
Can you be hostages of your own troop?
The people who lock you up
are your enemy.
Not being aware of your identities,
how can you rebel?
The ammunition depot is here.
Open the door.
In the past a few days,
I haven't said a word.
But at this critical moment,
I think I have to say something.
Considering from the aspect of actual combat,
Song's starting point
is fine
and courageous.
But technically,
there are some problems.
If the purpose of
releasing the captured personnel
can be altered,
not aiming at bombing the Blue Army's ammunition depot
but aiming at
the information.
What does that mean?
It means
they should work separately
and send out information.
Such an action
will be perfect, right?
As an Information Minister, you did learn something.
You are seriously studying the actual combat.
Thank you, Chief.
Chief,
we cannot open the door.
Who's there?
Chief!
Being busy?
What are you still waiting for?
For the Spring Festival?
For the chief setting off firecrackers for you?
Hands behind your head. Crouch.
Crouch. Hands behind your head.
Chief,
take a rest.
You are captured.
After the drill of Camphorwood Station,
I have sworn that
in the rest of my life,
I will not be a captive again.
But you did again.
Hand over your guns.
Chief, you are violating the rules.
So what?
Come on.
Chief is old. Be more careful.
Come on!
Fall in battle?
Failed to escape?
Song Jianshe...
Politically,
we call it sacrifice.
But
in terms of information work,
we won't announce it to the public.
He can only be the hero on the intelligence front.
If so, I...
I actually admire Song.
He is a real soldier.
It seems that we've reached an agreement.
This kind of situation
has never happened before.
It is the first time.
However,
throughout out the world,
it hard to tell whether it will happen again.
If that's the case, I have a suggestion.
Report Song's performance
to the Military Command,
and ask for an award for him.
If you agree,
raise your hands.
Water?
Good boy.
Your mom didn't give birth to you for nothing.
I didn't cultivate you for nothing.
Where did you get it?
I fill it with the freshwater  from the pool in north.
It's not an easy task, but I met a nice guy.
Ma Jianfei.
Did you lose your mind?
Company commander...
The freshwater in the pool
is poisoned.
Even though you taste a drip of it,
you will be regarded as fall in battle.
Do you want to trap our company?
But if you don't drink it,
you will bleed to death.
But I'll die righteously.
Company commander, I heard that
the water was not poisoned.
If you die, we will lose our company commander.
He's right.
The water
is clean.
They just dropped a bottle of vitamin.
But according to the rules of drilling,
we take
the water as being toxic.
Yes.
Commander.
Private from the Ninth Company, the Second Platoon, the Fifth Squad,
Ma Jianfei,
broke the roles
and stole forbidden items.
I...
The company commander of the Ninth Company,
Li Guoqiang,
ask for punishment for him.
I didn't do it for myself.
I did it for our company.
I don't want the Red Army to defeat us
and lose the island.
We are the Live and Die Together Company.
I don't want buddies in my company to die.
I...
I want to do something for them.
Are you still reluctant to admit mistakes?
Do you know how serious your mistake is?
That's enough.
You drank the water?
Just two sips. I didn't dare to drink more.
Ok.
You should go
and find Director General Sun.
Tell him that you fell in battle.
Go.
Yes.
The company commander of the Ninth Company.
Go with him.
I can't leave the Ninth Company.
We only got these people.
We should respect the rules.
Yes.
Platoon leader.
The paltoon leader of the Second Platoon, Ding Youyuan,
is reporting.
From now on,
you act as the company commander of the Ninth Company
and command battle.
Bring your company commander
to the treatment room.
Yes.
[Chief Director]
[Red Army Director]
Yes.
Report. The Red Army reported that
they organized a night attack one hour ago.
Now, they've landed on the intertidal zone.
The Red Army changed their strategy.
Contact their Command Post
and ask them about
the reason why they changed the time to attack.
Unnecessary.
It is stated that there will not be plans
and let them battle on their own.
Leave him alone.
Deputy commander,
Gu Yiye
is taking risks again.
That's right.
Win with fancy strategies.
Win with high risks.
Attack the enemy
at the most unexpected timing and place.
Maybe the war will end.
You woke up?
How come I fell asleep?
You have stayed up for several nights.
You only slept for three hours.
And
the second batch of equipment has arrived.
Department of Communication wants the leader to sign.
But the team leader is having an intravenous drip in the clinic.
I will go.
They fought on the island for half a night.
The Red Army attacked in a point-to-point way.
And they eliminate
every fire bases of the Blue Army.
The Blue Army suffered a lot.
Their soldiers are less than half a company.
And the Red Army
doesn't seem like they will withdraw.
They have built support position in the intertidal zone.
If so,
the Red Army is getting ready for the final shot.
Observers of the director department have reported that
the commander of the Red Army
is not on the island.
Then where is he?
Arraign Niu Manang.
I wonder that
whether everyone in the Blue Army
is a tough guy.
Wake up.
Don't be shy.
Sit here.
What?
The supply of Regiment 700
is not so good.
Just eat.
I will release you after you finish.
I will attack the island.
Attack the island.
Just say it.
You want to wait for the Special Force Team
or surrender beforehand?
I am warning you.
Show me your respect.
Or I can let the Special Force Team
bring a dead body back.
Cool. A dead body.
You made it?
The drill hasn't finished.
We are stilling fighting.
Cool. Go on.
That's cool.
Stop mumbling.
Just eat.
I will send you away sooner or later.
Gu Yiye.
I am curious about something.
Why Gao didn't catch you
and let you hide in the corner?
Do you feel good?
If you feel bad, I am right here.
OK?
After I finish the can, you can shoot me.
Just kill me quickly.
I want to die as a martyr.
Among the monuments of the Special Force Team,
I have to occupy
a brisk.
To
Mancang.
Gu Yiye, Gu Yiye.
How come you turn out to be like this?
[Sword of the South]
Honestly.
You are fantastic. Very fantastic.
[Sword of the South]
Among the field grade officers of the A Army,
you are definitely the top one.
Top one.
But the Romance of the Three Kingdoms tells the truth.
Now that we got Zhou Yu,
why bother to bring Zhuge Liang?
We don't have Zhuge Liang.
We have
Gao Liang.
Don't mention him in front of me.
Yiye
Do you think that
you lock me up and make me stupid?
The drill isn't over.
48 hours.
You think I won't tell right?
You lock me in the ship's bottom
so that I can't see the sun.
You are right.
But you forget one thing.
Look at my soldiers.
They relieve guard every eight hours.
How many times in total?
You think I can't figure that out?
The drill isn't over?
You are attacking the island?
Who are deceiving?
Who are you attacking?
That's fun.
I care about too many things.
I bombed the reefs
for fear of
injuring the observation team.
Gu.
Let me tell you.
Gao
knows you so well.
He knew you were so cautious that
without preparation,
you won't take action.
So when we
were making plans for the battle,
we decided to avoid competing head-to-head with you.
You got it?
When you were working hard on the ocean,
two thirds of us
were sleeping in the underground facilities.
Do you know what we called it?
Turtles.
Ninja Tuetles.
Oh, and the observation team.
As soon as they landed on the island,
Gao sent them
to rest in the safest fortifications
and took good care of them.
Yiye,
why you didn't predict that?
Yiye.
You little fool.
What?
You cannot hold it?
That's right.
I know.
Failure of taking down the island
is not good for writing a report,
right?
Can we make a deal?
When you are writing your report,
can you neglect me?
I had been fighting for two days.
You are the only captive left.
If I neglect that,
the reputation of Regiment 700 will be awful.
You can mention me.
Cool. Talking about me. Anything you want, OK?
But that's worthless.
I didn't tell you anything, right?
You did.
You said that when I was attacking,
two thirds of you
were sleeping in the underground fortification.
What did you call it?
Ninjia Turtles.
You forget the words you've just said?
How about writing my report in this way?
The captured soldier of the Blue Army, Major Niu Mancang, said that
the entrance of the
central bunker of the underground fortifications on Qiaotou Island
was on the mountainside of the main peak.
I didn't say anything.
Get somebody and record the oral confession.
What are you doing?
It's useless.
The entrance is not on the mountainside.
It is at the bottom of the cliff in the south-east corner.
It is in the bush.
You're such a fool.
You...
I'm such a fool.
Didn't expect that.
Niu.
[Sword of the South]
To Gao Liang.
You are a loyal traitor.
Isn't the drill over?
Your words
will promote the end of the drill.
But after the drill,
you
will be nailed to the pillory
[Sword of the South]
[Map of A Army's Operational Area]
Got it.
Report.
Go on.
The commander of the Red Army reported that
they have got
the entrance of the central underground fortifications on Qiaotou Island.
The Red Army
applies for the last round of attack.
In an hour,
the attack will begin.
The commander
will take all military strength to the land.
[Blue Army Director, Chief Director, Red Army Director]
Why?
It seems that you are
unwilling to see this result.
It seems that
the Operation Azure is really coming to the end.
Reply the command post of the Red Army
the director department got it.
Yes.
The recording system of the Red Army's Mountain Net Number Two
goes wrong.
They want us to check it out.
Their commander asked for you.
Engineer Jiang of the Mountain Net Number Two is arriving.
I didn't expect that
you will treat me to come over in this way.
I admit it.
To ask for you from the director department,
I need some reasons.
I've asked you to come this time
not because I want to see you
but because chief and others are on the island.
This drill
lasts for too long.
I am worrying about his body.
I hope you can check it out.
The First Platoon are all back.
Only seven observation posts are left on the ground.
Only 59 soldiers
can continue to fight.
All heavy weapons were blown up.
I've just counted the ammunition.
Only 2865 shots are left.
Less than 50 shots for each person.
How are you doing?
I am OK.
As long as I get something to eat,
I can hang on for three more days.
Staff officer Jian.
Yes.
We can make it through like this.
Try to
find some herbs
for anti-inflammatory on the island.
Change the medicines for the wounded.
Yes.
Isn't the drill coming to the end?
You think so, too?
Don't forget that I come from the scientific research team.
I heard it on the way.
You
put all your military strength on this attack.
You are not going to
keep the drill going.
I really forgot that.
I didn't forget about your profession or
your identity.
I've forgot how smart you are.
OK.
I confess.
I've asked you to come this time
not for seeing the chief.
They are on the island.
In several hours,
they can get back to normal life.
And they're hostages,
so it's hard to approach them.
He's on the island.
Go see him.
Psychological warfare.
In your psychological warfare,
I am a functional gadget.
Food and drinks have been cut off for several days.
Apart from that,
soldiers
have to be vigilant about the Red Army's attack.
They haven't slept for a few days.
Gao.
We are fighting alone,
without any backup.
Don't you think that
the director department
works with the Red Army
to destroy us?
That's it.
The battle is over.
Jiang.
It is not over yet.
He has two ways to go.
The first one is
giving up
and saving the rest lives.
But you know that
he won't choose this way.
I don't care about
delaying the drill for two more hours.
What I really care
is reducing the casualties of my troops.
During these four days,
he has consumed half of my military strength.
I don't want the number
to increase.
Otherwise, even though I take down the island,
I could not
ask my superiors to record my meritorious deed after I go back.
And?
My soldiers are tolerating.
I cannot make sure that
they won't do something that exceeds what is proper.
That may be a slaughter.
And you are
his only soft spot.
I hope after he sees you,
he will be restless
and break down.
At least from the outlook,
he could be a little bit more feeble.
In that case,
less of my soldiers may die.
That's contemptible.
I admit it.
What if I refuse?
You will not.
You are an expert in information.
And it is a rare chance
to collect commanders'
comprehensive data.
And
you cannot avoid your emotions.
In terms of the drill,
you are not a combatant
but a citizen employed by us.
After landing on the island,
you have no right to
give them military assistance
or real
our military secrets to them.
Wait.
I want you help me
to take 50 boxed meals there.
This is an actual combat.
I will tell you
they are dying,
and all I can do
is to prevent them from starving to death.
At least in the public's opinion,
my reputation could be better.
But actually?
But actually,
I don't know
how many people they still have.
But I hope
there won't be too many.
Because
I poisoned the boxed meals.
Gu Yiye.
It is lucky that
I didn't go further with you.
I am flattered.
The battle is still on.
According to the rules,
I can't call you chief now.
Please forgive me.
You are coming to handle the aftermath?
Yes.
How will you
deal with us hostages?
I need to confirm a detail.
You have to be here.
I am the commander of the Blue Army.
[Map of A Army's Operational Area]
Director Xia,
the commander of the Blue Army is calling.
Transfer it here.
Yes.
Director department of the Operation Azure.
Four days ago,
the observation group became the hostages.
But I haven't received
the detailed identities
of the hostages form the superiors.
Now I need to know
the detailed identities of each one.
Does this question
have actual impact on the battle?
Yes.
I need to know
whether they are civilians
or the enemy's personnel.
If they are the latter,
I need to know their correct identities
and the detention task
the superiors have given to me.
They are important figures of the Red Army
so your task is
keeping the hostages with you.
Got it.
From now on,
I won't talk to the director department any more.
I will report my plan first.
After the Red Army launches the attack,
detention time for the hostages will start counting down.
As long as
any one of my army is still fighting on the island,
hostages will be alive.
No one could enter
the detaining site,
or the tripwire bomb will explode.
If the resistance on the island comes to the end,
according to the plan,
hostages will be executed.
None of them can survive.
Over.
Wait.
Hello?
Director Xia, he turned off the intercom.