♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 15=
Whoops.
Your facial mask is so horrible.
Don’t mind the pattern.
Just as long as it works.
What’s up? Hurry up.
Don’t waste my time.
Where is Ning Zeyu?
Upstairs.
Well.
Lower down your voice.
Don’t let him know.
You know what?
Things are getting worse.
Ning Zeyu’s mother is planning
to transfer him to another school.
Lower down your voice!
Don’t let him know.
Aunt is so abrasive.
She transfers him to another school now?
And in such a critical moment
in Grade 3.
Yes.
What should we do?
She asked me to tell him.
How can I do it?
In my opinion,
Ning Zeyu is capable to
prepare the competition
and final exam at the same time.
But his mother doesn’t think so.
So,
we have to let her know.
Monitor,
we share the idea.
As his friends,
we should help him.
How?
Two heads are better than one.
Well…
What?
It sounds unreliable.
Well, this is the only way.
OK. Get it.
What are you doing?
Me?
Well,
I’m sharing ideas
about skin care with Yuan Caixi.
Tomorrow is the exam, have a good rest.
OK.
Skin care?
You’re so stupid, Ye Jingxi.
What’s your idea? Can you make it?
You tell him the transferring.
OK. Let’s stop here.
I’ll hang up.
This is not bad.
Hello.
How to get to
the teaching affair office?
This way, please.
Thank you.
Check your answers.
And write your name properly.
I hope Ning Zeyu’s mother won’t come
so that this issue can be settled.
It sounds impossible.
Is that her?
Oh!
She is coming.
So quickly.
-What should we do?
-Where is Ning Zeyu?
No idea. Probably in the classroom.
It’s bad.
You hold up his mother,
and I’m coming to look for Ning Zeyu.
OK.
I saw Ning Zeyu’s mother come to school.
For this issue?
What?
Where has she headed for?
You didn’t act so quickly.
-Aunt!
You’re Ning Zeyu’s mother, right?
I’m Ye Jingxi.
I think you’ve known me.
No.
Aunt! Aunt!
I heard from Ning Zeyu
that you’re a professional lawyer.
Well.
I’m an actor.
So…
An actor?
The entertainment circle?
Yes.
Why are his classmates
PE students or actors?
How can he study hard?
It’s none of my business.
Let’s just find him.
Ning Zeyu.
Get on.
Why are you here?
Hurry up!
Mrs. Ning!
Listen to me.
I don’t think it’s a good idea
to transfer Zeyu to another school now.
It will not only affect his study,
but also impose pressure on him.
Miss Luo.
Of course you don’t want Ning Zeyu
to leave.
If he’s gone,
the graduation rates will be
greatly affected.
Mrs. Ning.
My classes
are always the top 3 of school.
The rate of first-tier university
is over 70%.
My suggestions are totally
out of profession and experience.
You should trust me.
I should trust you.
But what’s the result?
Ning Zeyu is wasting time
in programming.
And he started to lie,
forged a signature,
and ran away from home.
This is how you taught him.
Right.
These are big mistakes.
I’m to be blame.
But,
Ning Zeyu is now at a rebellious stage.
If he has been restricted all the time,
he’ll be overwhelmed.
He will break out sooner or later.
Transferring to another school
at this time
doesn’t help, right?
How can you be sure
that it doesn’t help?
Miss Luo.
I don’t want to talk
to subjective person.
Please make way for me.
Aunt.
Transferring school is a big issue.
Don’t you gonna tell Ning Zeyu?
Aunt.
May I have the last words?
I think you should listen to
and know
your son’s opinions.
He loves programming so much.
And now there’s a competition.
Are you not going to watch it?
Who are you?
I’m the monitor of Class 2.
Yuan Caixi.
Have Ye Jingxi and monitor known this?
They’re trying to hold up
your mom at school.
Unexpectedly,
you saved me at the critical moment.
Never mind.
But, is this competition so important?
Must you come?
The judges are professors from Tiangong
University of Science and Technology.
I’ve been concerning
about this competition for a long time.
Once I’m admitted,
I can join the winter holiday training
and meet the professors.
I have to come anyway.
OK.
Get it.
Be careful.
Hello, audiences at present
and on the internet.
Welcome to the preliminary contest of
programming competition in Haiwen.
In recent year,
internet has been developed
(Haiwen Preliminary of the 6th Programming Match)
into one of the most important technologies in China.
We set up the programming competition
in Haiwen
to encourage more young people
to join in this area.
The winners will be awarded
with rich bonus,
and will have the chance to communicate
with the top experts.
-Now it’s the preliminary for high school.
-Li He.
-There’re all together five items.
-Aunt.
-They are all questionable codes.
-Have a seat.
The competitors should
address the problems in limited time.
Faster and cleaner, the better.
The fastest at present is No.3,
Ning Zeyu.
He is also the youngest competitor.
The heroes are usually young.
Let’s expect
the results of the competition.
Aunt.
See, Ning Zeyu is so cool
when he’s programming.
What programming?
It’s a waste of time.
Your father and I have already
decided your future.
You’ll be a lawyer.
You’re so naive.
Do you think it’s possible
to just do what you want
in today’s society?
The leading No.3 Ning Zeyu
made a mistake.
Time is limited.
Can he debug
and turn the situation?
What does it mean?
No idea.
What’s wrong?
Why does it turn red?
It’s a mistake.
You’re Grade 3 after all.
Of course that your parents are strict.
It will be alright when you pass it.
Just stick to it
if you really like programming.
I just want to do what I like,
or I’ll regret.
♪Young and joyful♪
♪As gentle as the scattering stars♪
♪Luckily I’ve seen you♪
Come on! Ning Zeyu!
♪Leaving the bright light and fade away♪
Ning Zeyu recovered.
Let’s expect his better performance.
-Aunt.
♪The stars change♪
♪I don’t want to sleep
in a starry night♪
♪The night is precious when I miss you♪
Great.
Congratulations! You passed
the preliminary contest.
It’s just a preliminary contest.
It’s not hard.
I’ve watched the competition.
You’re amazing.
Your winter holiday training
will be achieved.
You can learn from the professors later.
It’s uncertain. I have to wait for
the notification to the training.
Oh. By the way,
did my mom…?
As your mother,
you need to talk to her
after coming back.
Yes.
I’ve planned to talk to her.
Don’t think too much. Just go.
Let’s go.
Let me see you out.
Mom.
You don’t have to say anything.
I know you like programming.
But you’re in Grade 3.
You can’t waste your time.
The competition is over.
I won’t blame you for this time.
If you don’t change your mind
and do this again,
I’ll transfer you to another school.
The scores of final exam have come out.
You can check it online.
This winter holiday is the last holiday
before the college entrance examination.
I have to remind you,
don’t spend all you time on having fun
during the Spring Festival,
make use of your time to study.
OK.
Pack up your stuffs and go home.
Ning Zeyu.
Come to my office.
The class is over. Miss Luo.
Miss Luo.
Have a seat.
Ning Zeyu.
I ask you here
to have a talk.
See.
Here.
The score has come out.
(Notification of Final Exam Score)
Your score has dropped nearly 30 points.
And your grade rank
has dropped to No.2.
I don’t know the exact cause of
your severe retrogress
in such a short time.
But I believe
there’s a reason.
I have talked to your mother.
She agreed not to transfer you
to another school presently.
But there’re less than 180 days
to the college entrance examination.
I hope you can focus on
the important issue.
Of course.
I know the dream is important.
So,
if your reach the final contest,
you can take the holiday
to prepare for it.
But after that you have
to focus on study.
After all the college
entrance examination
is the most important thing
for you presently.
I hope you
can prepare for it
with a perfect state.
Understand?
Understood. Miss Luo.
OK.
Well, study hard
and have a good rest.
OK.
Thank you, Miss Luo.
(Ning Zeyu. Total Score: 689.
Grade Ranking: 2)
What’s wrong with Ning Zeyu?
Is his mother here?
No idea.
It may be the matter about score.
No way.
How can he have problems with score?
Yes.
Why are you still here?
We’re waiting for you.
I’m waiting for Yuan Caixi.
Are you alright?
Nothing.
It’s just that I got No.2.
But on the other hand,
congratulations, you’re No.1.
What?
You’re No.2?
Monitor ranks before Ning Zeyu?
Amazing.
You deserve it.
-You won over Ning Zeyu.
-Yes.
Ning Zeyu.
You must be distracted
by the programming competition.
I hope you are not deliberate
to lose to me.
I wasn’t deliberate.
Monitor.
Are you questioning your ability?
Besides,
this is not
the college entrance examination.
Do you think
you can win over me next time?
OK. All right.
Stop talking about the exam.
I don’t want to hear about it.
The winter holiday is coming,
let’s hang out and have fun.
I agree with you.
You three go.
I failed my exam. I don’t want to go.
Ning Zeyu.
Appropriate relaxation
can help ease the stress.
It can release dopamine
that makes you happy.
-So…
-Monitor.
Do you have any other new words?
Ning Zeyu.
Stop mourning.
Think about it.
If I and Li He always
worry about our scores,
we can’t
continue our life at all.
Don’t include me in
when you talk about yourself. Thanks.
OK.
Let’s move.
How about tomorrow?
OK.
It’s decided.
I’ll call Jiang Yuan and Yun Xiang.
OK.
♪I want to see you again♪
♪See you again♪
♪Hey girl♪
So cute.
♪Like a sheep♪
♪coming across the destined monster♪
♪I never see through♪
♪Heart is rusty♪
♪I didn’t think too much♪
♪just to be with you♪
Sakuta.
Do you want it?
♪Keep deceiving myself♪
♪The love words to you♪
♪has been practiced for several times♪
♪No matter how dangerous it is♪
♪I’ll protect you♪
♪I really want to see you again♪
♪Where can you be♪
♪I want to see you again♪
♪See you again♪
♪I really want to see you again♪
♪Let me see you♪
♪The previous playground♪
♪The talk between you and me♪
♪Though I’m casual♪
♪I’m not an armchair general♪
♪I take you to watch a sweet movie♪
♪We make a promise on the Ferris wheel♪
♪The pink sunset glow is like your face♪
♪When you look at me♪
That’s it.
Is this the one you saw last time?
Yuan.
You like this?
Last time I saw it but when I came
to find it, it was gone.
I see it here today.
Yes. You have received the bonus.
It’s destined
that you should buy it for Aunt.
Hello.
Excuse me. What are the sizes for this?
Where are they?
Here they are.
Here.
Monitor.
Why are you here?
We’ve been looking for you.
Where’re the others?
They are in the stores.
Yes.
I think I have been recognized.
Let’s go to somewhere less crowded.
Don’t overreact.
No one recognized you.
I mean it.
Let go to somewhere less crowded.
Let’s go to eat.
Oh! There’s a dessert shop in front.
Let’s come here.
-Let’s go.
-Go.
Chief. Spoon. Spoon.
Give me one.
That. That.
This is mine. This is mine.
How about adding something.
OK.
How about this?
Today is the first time
we hang out to eat.
So,
it’s my treat. Order anything you want.
-Just order.
-Your treat.
Let’s have something delicious.
-I want two milk custards.
-It’s OK. Just order what you want.
OK.
-I want an ormosia milk custard.
-OK.
An ormosia milk custard, please.
Monitor.
-Yes?
-I have something to say to you.
Go on.
I got the notification of final contest.
I can go to the winter holiday training
very soon.
Congratulations!
I’m waiting for the schedule.
I’ll go soon.
Then you can meet
a group of interesting people, right?
Can I ask for a present for
reaching the final contest from you?
Come on. It should be
after you win champion anyway.
You know I’ll win.
OK.
Well.
It’s my honor to prepare a present
for the champion.
What do you want?
It’s a secret now.
I’ll tell you in proper timing.
So mysterious.
OK.
But it should be within my ability.
Are you saying yes?
Right.
Hello.
A durian cake
for each of us, please.
OK.
Thanks.
Let’s go.
I want sweeten red bean paste
and lotus seeds. Have you ordered it?
Yes. And I add two mild custards,
and a durian cake for each one.
She just come to order.
And you still follow her.
I come to order for you
in case you’re hungry.
No need.
I like everything monitor orders for me.
You don’t eat what I order, right?
It must be monitor who ordered it.
Alright. Alright.
Well, let’s take a photo.
OK. OK.
Three.
Two.
One.
(Old Dreams)
Daily check. Look at the libeler.
(Secrets in Mind)
You must be an ugly and unpopular
miserable guy in school.
(A Lonely Shadow)
You slander him because you envy him.
(Flashing Time)
I’m warning to delete photos.
Don’t start rumors,
or I’ll sue you.
You’re such a nut. Don’t slander others.
(Message, ENT Xiaoba)
Hello.
Do you have any personal photos
of Ye Jingxi?
We’d like to buy them.
We want to reveal his true personality
to the public
and disclose his guise.
You don’t have to worry
about the curses,
right?
Can I stay here today, monitor?
He is so handsome in the camera.
And he’s so nice in life.
I like him so much.
Han Yayi.
When I saw him,
I feel like in a dream.
-Han Yayi.
-What?
I haven’t noticed
that you’re so sentimental.
How am I sentimental?
Never mind.
Yuan.
When do you plan to give
the cheongsam to Aunt?
Before she leaves.
She must be beautiful in this cheongsam.
A cheongsam requires
a good temperament.
The most important is
that she will like it.
You know what?
The cheongsam is similar to the one
my dad gave to her before.
Yuan.
Let’s play a game.
What game?
I say someone’s name,
and you speak out your first impression
on this person immediately.
It’s not fun.
You haven’t played it.
Have a try. Just once.
OK. OK. Let’s try.
-I’ll start.
-OK.
Huang Yuan.
A fair lady.
Lin Chuan.
A good-for-nothing adviser.
This is great.
Well. Yun Xiang.
Little angel.
Ye Jingxi.
Brother Bear.
Ning Zeyu.
A rebellious guy.
Rebellious.
-Ning Zeyu?
-Yes.
Think about it.
Though he looks quiet and docile,
he learnt programming secretly,
and ran away from home.
What a rebellious guy.
Well,
Li He.
A lovely huskie.
By lovely I mean
the diligent and clumsy sports students
look so cute and inspiring.
Inspiring.
Especially when they come
across difficult questions.
Right?
And that time when he put on
turtle costume, he was so cute.
Cute.
Yuan, you’re right.
But I think your perspective
is different from mine.
-And the details…
-Do I?
Yuan, you’re…
Han Yayi.
It’s your turn now.
I have only one question.
-Yuan. I was wrong.
-I have only one question.
-What do you think of Lin Chuan?
-Let me go. I was wrong.
What do you think of Lin Chuan?
Little hamster.
I want my mom.
Get up, superstar!
-Get up, superstar!
-I’m late.
Get up, superstar!
It’s winter holiday.
(Bawan)
A phone call, superstar!
Hello.
What’s up?
Well, Ms. Hua asked me to tell you,
pay attention to the admission information
of Haixing Conservatory of Music.
It’s so early. You…!
And,
Ms. Hua asked me to tell you…
He hung off?
Let me go check it.
OK.
Coming.
Bear. Why are you here?
I come to have a free meal.
You come at the right time.
Han Yayi.
Jingxi.
Sit here.
-Hello.
-Jingxi.
OK.
Hello.
The breakfast in your house is always
so sumptuous.
I’ll start.
OK.
Jingxi.
You don’t take carbohydrate, do you?
It’s breakfast.
It can be sumptuous.
This is delicious.
Well, Bear.
Are you coming for extra tutoring?
Yes.
The deadline of Haixing Conservatory
of Music is November.
I still have a period of time.
So,
I can prepare for the college
entrance examination and pro exam.
Yuan Caixi.
I’m wondering,
could you please…?
OK. OK.
My sister is
almost like
a professional tutor.
When can you tutor
your blood younger brother?
No problem.
You deserve it.
Caixi.
Well, don’t be
so cruel to your blood brother.
I know it’s not easy for Yuan Caixi.
But I just
want to study here.
Or I’ll idle the days away
at home by myself.
I’ll just study here.
No problem. Yuan.
I’m OK with it.
But how to deal with Ms. Hua.
Have you told her?
No problem.
She will agree with it.
Yuan Haoxi.
Why did you kick me?
Hurry up.
Last ten meters.
OK.
For pairs and stretch up.
You’ll have to run 400 meters.
400 meters!
Hurry up!
Put your phone away.
Tell Han Yayi,
the class will be over in half an hour.
Don’t worry.
Han Yayi said she won’t come.
What’s up?
Are you sad?
I’m fine.
I’m worrying about you.
(Send to Han Yayi)
Ye Jingxi is studying in Yuan’s house.
I won’t come to meet you.
It’s OK.
It will be over in half an hour.
Don’t worry.
Mr. Bai. I’ll go first.
Where are you going, Li He?
An emergency.
You guys,
50 leapfrogs for each one.
Leap high!
I’m going.
Bear.
Hello, Aunt.
You’re here.
Yes. Hello, Aunt. Hello, Aunt.
Have the breakfast.
I’m having it.
You packed up so quickly.
-Yes.
-Hold on for a second.
OK.
I’m going to attend the homecoming,
and have to take the train.
Be good at home.
OK.
Mom.
What’s this?
Just check it.
Is it for me?
Yes.
Do you remember
I talked about the bonus before?
I wanted to buy this cheongsam
with it.
See.
Is it similar to the one Dad gave you?
It’s almost the same.
Am I look beautiful?
Yes. Mom.
If you go to homecoming in it,
you classmates will believe
that you’ve travelled through time.
You haven’t changed in over a decade.
Mrs. Liu Yanan,
did you eat corrosion remover?
You’re so sweet.
Caixi.
Yes?
I do like it.
Thanks, my sweetheart.
Thanks.
I’ll go to the homecoming
in my new dress.
I fold it for you.
OK.
I’m going.
-Mom, let me see you out.
-Be good at home.
Yuan, let me see Aunt out.
Let’s go.
You’re also going?
Yes. Let me take it for you.
OK.
-We’re going. Bye-bye.
-Be good at home.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye-bye, Aunt.
See, how funny he is.
It’s so amusing.
He’s like our son.
He’s like me.
What’s wrong with you?
Sorry.
Come back.
Change your shoes.
He. Have you finished training?
Dad, Mom, don’t wait for me
for dinner.
I’m going to study
in my classmate’s home.
What?
Where are you going?
Have you finished training?
I go out to eat something.
-Oh.
-And you?
The training?
Yes.
Well,
Aunt…
Winter camp.
This is the only way.
Besides,
it’s not exactly a lie.
Training is one type of winter camp.
Don’t worry. It won’t affect my study.
But in my opinion,
Aunt will know it
sooner or later.
Think about it.
According to my experience,
Your dad and mom know it.
They’re just waiting
for you to tell them.
You’re not going out to eat, right?
How do you know?
It’s winter holiday.
Who would go to eat with a schoolbag?
I’ll go to monitor’s home.
I know it.
You’re easy to be seen through.
Come on.
Hope you can win the champion
after the training.
Don’t be so perky.
Though I’m not here,
I’ll chat with her every day.
If chatting works,
I’ll leave my running champion to you.
Anyway,
mind that guy.
Of course I know it.
What do you think I’m rushing for?
OK. Don’t worry too much.
Focus on your training.
We’re waiting for you to come back.
OK.
Happy holiday, everyone.
How’s it going? Do you miss me?
Why do you come here?
This is my question.
Why did you come here?
I came here to study.
I’m preparing for the examination
to Haixing Conservatory of Music.
I asked Yuan Caixi
to tutor me in holiday.
What a coincident.
I come here to study, too.
I’m preparing for the examination
for high-level athlete.
I also need tutoring.
You can just come to a tutoring class.
Why didn’t you come to a tutoring class?
You’re so annoying.
You’re annoying.
Both of you are annoying.
Have you asked me before?
You just come here for tutoring.
I have.
OK. Never.
I have, too.
When did you ask me?
Early before that.
When I treated you the drumsticks,
you promised to tutor me.
What?
Is your tutoring time-limited?
You don’t have to come to my house.
You’re so cheeky.
Cheeky or not doesn’t matter.
Monitor and exam matter.
Sorry. My phone is out of power.
Are you taking videos?
I’m telling you.
I have the portraiture right.
Give me your phone.
Taking photos secretly is immoral.
Give it to me.
Yuan Caixi. Yuan Caixi.
I’m your blood brother.
-Yuan Caixi.
-Give it to me.
What’s the password?
I forget it.
I give in.
My brain doesn’t work at all.
Those literary masters,
why didn’t they just go out
and enjoy lives?
Why did they write so many poems
and travel notes?
Wasn’t it tiring?
Don’t give up.
Just open up your test paper,
and do it.
Bear.
Are you mad?
What’s this?
Never mind. Have a sleep
and you’ll remember it.
I’m hungry.
So am I.
Are you serious?
Writing test papers are
the easiest work in the world.
Why are you so exhausted?
Monitor.
Writing test papers is OK.
But don’t starve us.
Yes.
Look at the refrigerator,
it’s so empty.
Well. Are you using hands or mouth
to write test papers?
Brain activity requires physical power.
We have to eat something anyway.
Yuan Haoxi. Where’re you going?
Go to see a movie with my classmates.
You watch movies every day.
Don’t come. Stay at home and study.
Why?
Cuz I’m your elder sister.
And Mom asked me
to supervise your study.
Tell your classmates you won’t come
or you’ll lose your allowance.
For how much?
50.
100.
Caixi.
What’s your order?
OK. OK.
I have a proposal.
Let’s cook something to eat.
I agree.
The refrigerator is empty.
What do we eat?
It’s easy.
Go buy something in the supermarket.
OK.
How about steaming a fish?
Why do we steam a fish?
The adults are absent
and we should eat junk food.
You don’t do exercises, right?
Don’t you know junk food is not good?
I don’t know.
What are you doing?
There’re my fans in front.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪