♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 22=
Caixi,
have you taken enough rest?
Mom told you that
you should sleep before 11PM
every night from now on.
I’m still very worried about mom.
She’s fine.
She said she’s fine.
He knows it too?
It was an accident.
Good morning.
-Good morning, Zeyu.
-Good morning.
So, aunt’s reaction was different from
what you’ve expected when you told her.
She was so calm that
she wasn’t even like my mom.
It’s great.
If you both cried,
I don’t know what I could do.
Now, only Li He and
the others don’t know.
Caixi,
I have a suggestion.
Don’t tell them anything.
Look. You’re so healthy and energized.
What are you doing?
Chief, are you taking off the gauze?
The wound isn’t that severe.
Wrapping it cuts off ventilation.
So I thought...
Chief, are you worried that
others might find out
so you tried to take it off?
No.
How’s that possible?
Come on, Chief.
You just don’t want Yuan Caixi to know
that you’re injured.
The doctor said so.
The wound needs to breathe.
What does it have to do with her?
It’s fine that you always
think about Yuan Caixi.
But the race will come soon.
You’re giving up on your sportsmanship.
Mr. Ma, good morning.
Hello, Mr. Ma.
Keep your spirits.
-Mr. Ma, good morning.
Ning Zeyu. Yuan Caixi.
When you study hard,
you should also take enough rest.
You should balance study and rest.
Mr. Ma, good morning.
Why was he so rude?
-Are you all right?
-I’m fine.
We’ll go now, Mr. Ma.
-Mr. Ma, good morning.
What happened to your legs?
I was injured during the training.
Be careful.
Good morning, monitor.
Good morning.
Chief.
Take a mouthful.
Eat more. Eat more.
Yes.
Mom said she’d watch you eat.
Is it enough?
It’s for your own good.
Caixi, I have other matters.
I’ll go now.
See you at the next meal.
Since when did Yuan Haoxi become
so concerned about you?
Don’t mind him. It’s fine.
Yuan,
have you heard about
what happened to Li He?
What is it?
He was injured.
Injured?
Chief.
His knee?
Lin Chuan told me that
he accidentally fell down
yesterday during training.
His knee was injured and it bled a lot.
What?
Sit down.
Let me tell you the details. Sit down.
Actually Li He doesn’t want you to know.
It’s Lin Chuan who told me that.
Yuan,
what happened to you recently?
If there’s something on your mind,
you can just tell me.
Nothing.
Yuan,
Lin Chuan told me that
he wishes you can
go to watch Li He’s race.
After all, it’s very important to him.
Besides, he is injured
and his morale is down.
He’ll feel better if you watch the race.
I can’t go.
Ah! Why?
I can’t go because I have to study.
I’ll go now.
Oh!
Please do me a favor. Tell Li He
to be more careful during running.
I was off guard for one second,
and you already did this to yourself.
If you want to practice,
you can tell me.
If I were there,
you would’ve got injured.
It’s no big deal, I can still run.
Nonsense.
Go home and rest.
Go.
You bought so many medicines?
Go home and rest.
Li He.
Slow down. Where are you going?
Yuan Caixi.
Why are you leaving?
You left the medicines there?
Why do you leave
when you’re already here?
Wait for me. I’ll walk you home.
Li He,
College Entrance Exam is coming close.
I have to put my heart into study.
You should do the same.
You need to focus on training.
Stop thinking about unimportant matters.
I’m not lagging behind on
College Entrance Exam nor training.
But why are you hiding from me?
Fine.
I won’t force you if
you don’t want to tell me.
But, Yuan Caixi...
Li He.
It’s too late. I need to go home.
Let me walk you home.
No need.
Be careful with training
from now on.
Goodbye.
Come to watch my race.
Does it hurt?
A little bit.
It hurts?
A little.
There’s one more here.
Don’t worry for now.
Maybe it’s just anemia.
Do a blood test first.
I’ll look into the result then.
Go.
Thank you, doctor.
Monitor asked for a leave today.
Yuan seldom asks for leaves.
What happened to Yuan recently?
I saw Yuan Haoxi
came to school this morning.
Yuan asked for a leave, not her brother.
Of course,
Yuan Haoxi will come to school.
We can take this opportunity
and ask her brother.
You’re one smart hamster.
Han Yayi.
My sister treats you well,
so does my mom.
I...
Yuan Haoxi,
just tell us.
Lin Chuan won’t hurt you.
Okay.
Let’s be serious.
What happened to your sister?
Tell us.
My sister? She...
Think before you speak.
I want nothing but the truth.
Mr. Luo. That’s really Mr. Luo.
Yuan Haoxi,
you really won’t talk
unless we get rough, right?
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Will you say it or not?
-Say it.
-Will you?
But, I...
My sister forbids me
from telling others.
Yuan Haoxi,
we’re really worried about Yuan.
She has been acting
really strange recently.
She used to be a lone wolf,
but she’s different recently.
Just tell us what happened to her.
Ah! Okay. Okay.
My sister.
She...
is in the hospital right now.
Hospital?
(Qi Bangwei, Hematology Department,
Wanhe Hospital, Haiwen)
She has low red blood cell counts.
And her white cell counts and
hemoglobin level were also abnormal.
Of course,
there might be various causes.
But to be sure,
I suggest a bone marrow biopsy.
The hospital happens to
have less patients today.
You can do it today.
Mom.
Ay.
It’s fine.
It’s just a checkup.
-Don’t worry.
-Come on.
Dr. Qi,
you know about my family’s situation.
Because you know about
Caixi’s dad.
So I’m a bit concerned.
First,
her current symptoms
might be caused by leukemia.
These kids are young and
have strong immune systems.
Even if she has
the same illness as her father did,
if she receives treatments early…
The leukemia’s fatality
has dropped a lot nowadays.
Do you hear the doctor?
Mmm.
Let’s do the test first.
Don’t worry.
Leukemia?
Yes.
Yuan has such a severe illness.
How can you come to school
like nothing happened?
Are you heartless?
Nonsense. It’s not
a confirmed diagnosis yet.
Besides, why am I heartless?
What else can I do?
My dad’s dead. My sister might be ill.
My mom is having a hard time already.
If I pull a sad face like you do,
I’ll only increase their burden.
Wait. Yuan is fighting with
this severe illness on her own.
I’m just sitting next to her
as if everything is normal.
No wonder she often faints.
I just can’t help her.
Yuan is so poor.
Hey.
My sister’s not diagnosed yet.
Okay.
Any news from Yuan?
Talk to me.
Doctor asked my sister
to do a bone marrow biopsy to verify it.
(Class 2, Grade 3)
Let’s not tell Chief for now.
He’s got race tomorrow.
Chuan.
Hum?
Take a leak with me.
Come on.
Zeyu.
Chuan.
Yes?
Why do I feel even Han Yayi
is suddenly so close to Ning Zeyu?
Ah!
What else can it be?
She’s asking him about study.
Really?
Of course.
Monitor isn’t here.
Who else can she ask besides Ning Zeyu?
That’s right.
Chief, worry about yourself first.
How can you run tomorrow
with your legs like this?
Your overall score has to
be in top three in this competition.
Otherwise,
you can’t make into the final.
If you can’t make into the final,
you won’t be qualified as
national second-level athlete.
If you can’t get qualified,
you can’t apply for
the test of high level athlete.
Even you’re pessimistic about me?
Just because of the wound on my leg,
I can’t even make into the top three
with my capability?
No, that’s not what I mean.
Come on.
It’s not a big deal.
Thank you for taking care of Yuan.
You know it?
Lin Chuan and I just went to Yuan Haoxi.
She should be doing the checkup today.
Has the result come out?
Doctor said that
she needs a bone marrow biopsy.
It’s not confirmed yet.
We need to be optimistic.
Optimistic.
Just stop there. Thank you, Sir.
Slow down.
Caixi, be careful.
Thank you, Sir.
Are you okay?
Your waist wasn’t hurt just now?
No.
Mom.
Caixi.
Are you all right?
Let me perform a biopsy on you.
You still have the energy for jokes.
Mom, I’ll go upstairs now.
I want to take some rest.
Be careful. Do you hear me?
Ah. Okay.
Mom.
What did the doctor say?
The blood test result wasn’t ideal.
She has low red blood cell counts.
And her white cell counts and
hemoglobin level were also abnormal.
Your sister
did bone marrow biopsy today.
We’ll know when the result comes out.
Mom. It’ll be fine. Don’t worry.
The result will be all right.
Haoxi.
Yes?
You have to promise mom one thing now.
Mom, what is it?
No matter what happens in the future,
you have to tell me immediately.
Don’t hide things from me
like your sister did.
Ah! Mom, don’t worry.
I’m not as strong as my sister is.
I can’t keep secrets even if I want to.
It’s fine. Don’t worry.
My battery has died.
(Han Yayi)
Yuan, are you all right?
Lin Chuan and I went to
see Yuan Haoxi today.
He told us everything.
He just can’t keep secrets.
I’ll tell you everything
tomorrow at school.
Don’t tell Li He!
(Ning Zeyu)
You did bone marrow biopsy today?
It must hurt a lot.
I’ve organized today’s notes for you.
(Li He
Track and Field Event)
Hello, monitor?
You’re home? Are you all right?
I’m fine. The spot where I did
bone marrow biopsy hurts a little.
Lie down and rest.
Oh! Zeyu,
Han Yayi just told me
that Lin Chuan knew it.
Yes, but they won’t tell Li He soon.
After all, tomorrow is his race.
Great.
You...
Will you tell him
after tomorrow’s race?
No.
I’ll wait for the test result.
If it’s good, then it’s fine.
If the result is bad,
maybe my being mean to him now
is a good thing after all.
Will you go to watch his race tomorrow?
I’ll think about that later.
Tomorrow, will you come
to see me... ?
Zeyu.
I need to talk to you.
I’ll go now.
Go to bed early.
Wait. Hello? Zeyu?
-Zeyu.
-Mom.
Tomorrow is Saturday.
I will go to
your aunt’s place for dinner.
Come with me.
You can have a good conversation
with your cousin.
He was admitted with
a high score that year.
You can chat about things
other than study as well.
Relax yourself.
You’ve been really tired recently.
I was being too strict with you
a while ago.
Oh, mom, it’s fine.
I’m doing great. Don’t overthink.
I’ve arranged to go to school tomorrow
to do some research and tests.
I won’t go to aunt’s place
with you then.
Say hi to them for me.
Fine. Make your own plans for tomorrow.
Don’t exhaust yourself.
Okay.
Go to bed early.
(Sent to Yuan Caixi)
Tomorrow is the final of
my programming contest.
Come if you’re free.
Come in.
Caixi, you haven’t slept.
Not yet, mom.
Come and sit down.
Does it still hurt?
Caixi,
I didn’t take good care of you.
I have to apologize to you.
No, mom.
You don’t have to be sorry.
You really don’t.
I paid no heed to the changes on you.
I might not be...
a good mom.
No, mom.
It’s my fault. I should have
told you earlier.
Your dad will scold me if he knows.
No. No, he won’t. Mom.
Dad loves you so much.
He won’t scold you.
Caixi.
I saw you take so many tests
at the hospital today.
My heart breaks for you.
Baby,
but mom is so proud of you.
My daughter is just 18.
But she’s so brave.
And she has been through so much.
Do you understand?
I feel distressed and proud for you.
Seeing you suffer,
I wish to trade you and suffer for you.
My daughter.
You will be fine.
I’ll never let anything happen to you.
Your dad will bless you
from heaven as well.
You’ll be fine.
-Trust me.
-Yes.
Mom.
Caixi.
Ah!
My two precious kids are all here.
You are my lovely babies.
Dad. Mom. Good morning.
Sit down and have breakfast.
Okay.
You’ll go out?
I’ll go to the library.
You’re not going to your aunt’s place?
I’m not going to aunt’s place.
I’ll go to the library with friends.
Studying at the library is a good thing.
But don’t waste your time
tutoring them.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Li He from the next door.
I suggest you keep
your distance with him
at this vital stage.
You know what you should be doing
right now.
Okay.
Let the kid eat.
It’s rare that I’m home.
You know that too?
So I want to take the chance
to talk with him.
Son, take this with you.
-Ah! He’s going to the race.
-No need, mom.
I’m not going on a spring outing.
-Why do you give him so much food?
-What if he gets hungry?
Uncle, hello.
Ah. Zeyu.
Zeyu, where are you going?
I’m going to study.
Mom, dad, I’ll go now.
-Go for it.
-Stretch first.
Stretch your body first.
Okay. Do you hear me?
Come on.
-Come on.
Go all out in the race.
Although I’m still mad at you,
but we’re somehow brothers after all.
I guess you still
haven’t told your parents
about today’s programming contest?
After all,
we’re classmates.
You represent Sen Yong
in the competition.
Go all out in the contest
and honor Sen Yong.
Li He.
Yes?
Be careful with your legs.
(The fifteenth Haiwen
Junior Championships)
Chief.
Has she come?
No.
Yuan is not here herself,
but she’s rooting for you in her heart.
Don’t think too much.
Focus on the race.
Fine. Don’t just stand there.
Go inside.
Just go if you want to.
I know.
You’re scared that
you might drag him down.
But, Caixi,
instead of worrying about the future,
don’t you find cherishing the present
more important?
How about it?
Don’t you find me wise?
(Final of
Haiwen Network Programming Contest)
Is this Ning Zeyu?
Professor He.
We haven’t contacted each other
since the winter vacation training camp.
How are you doing? Are you prepared?
Yes, I am.
I have high expectations for you
since last training.
Tiangong University of
Science and Technology
really need science talents like you.
Hope you can do well. Go for it.
Yes, I will. Thank you, professor.
(Sent to Yuan Caixi)
How are you feeling today?
(Haiwen No.3 High School)
(Sen Yong High School)
Slow down.
What are you filming?
I’m taking videos for Yuan.
Will she come or not?
Aren’t you her best friend?
I should be asking you.
Athletes.
On your positions.
Come on. Li He, go for it.
♪Looking at you through the space
between my fingers♪
♪How lucky I’m occupied by you♪
♪My whole world My whole sight♪
♪Hold the joy of youth in my palms♪
♪The gentleness of scattering stars♪
♪Luckily I once met you♪
♪Blinked at a light year away♪
Li He, come on.
-Faster. Faster. Faster.
-Li He, hurry up.
♪Not every wish needs to come true♪
♪Stars shine and fade away♪
♪I don’t want to go to bed
Tonight’s sky is full of drifting clouds♪
♪The nights I spent missing you
are so precious♪
♪Luckily I once met you♪
♪Blinked at a light year away♪
♪The vacant nights The secret world♪
♪Is there a star by your side♪
♪Not everything goes as you wish♪
♪Stars shine and fade away♪
♪I don’t want to go to bed
Tonight’s sky is full of drifting clouds♪
(4. Li He: 4’22”)
♪The nights are so precious♪
♪Not everything goes as you wish♪
♪Luckily you left
the mesmerizing fantasies behind♪
♪When you finally find the quick fix♪
♪I can settle with a good dream♪
Dear guests, hello.
Welcome to the final of the annual
Haiwen Network Programming Contest.
After a winter vacation’s
intense training,
the contestants today...
Hello, is this Zeyu?
Hello, who is this?
I’m the doctor
at No.2 Experimental School.
A female student fainted here.
Hello. The girl you talked about
wears a ponytail?
Yes. I saw that you’re
her most recent contact.
So I called.
I wish to ask if you can
reach her parents.
You said she fainted?
Is she all right now?
She hasn’t woken up.
She’s still at our infirmary.
The infirmary of
No.2 Experimental School, right?
Yes.
I’m on my way now.
-Okay.
-Hello.
The contest will start soon.
Hello, what do you want?
I was told that my friend fainted
when I called here.
You’re Zeyu?
I don’t know the girl’s situation
for sure now.
Further inspection is needed
when she wakes up.
Okay.
This is her phone.
Take it for her.
Wait inside for a while.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
♪The distance between us♪
♪Changes all the time♪
♪Just like the last dessert♪
♪Making me want more♪
♪I don’t dare to breathe anymore♪
♪In case you feel my heart♪
♪Turn my back to you with courage♪
-Yuan.
-Yuan Caixi. Yuan Caixi.
♪The attraction of sight proves♪
♪45.7 is the distance of chemistry♪
♪The melody of the song♪
♪Fills our memories♪
♪The note of the class♪
♪Is filled with secrets♪
♪The shadow in the corridor♪
♪I mistake it for you♪
♪Oh my dear you♪
♪This is my love letter♪
I’m scared.
♪Can I express my feelings♪
♪I wish to have more♪
♪Closer to your heart♪
♪Why can’t we be together♪
♪Just you and me♪
Monitor, you’re awake?
Zeyu.
-Slow down.
-Why are you here?
How’s the result of Li He’s race?
How are you feeling now?
Are you feeling unwell?
I’m fine. Where’s Li He?
I don’t know that.
If I didn’t happen to call you,
you might have fainted
at No.2 Experimental School
without anyone knowing it. You know?
I didn’t mean to do it.
Of course, you didn’t.
Who would faint on purpose?
So,
you didn’t tell Li He
that you would come?
So you came here on your own?
And you didn’t tell him?
You were being so impulsive.
Why didn’t you just tell him?
Why are you being a coward now?
Hello?
Hello, Caixi, have you
finished watching the race?
It’s time to come home.
Do you need me to pick you up?
Yuan Haoxi.
Haoxi, I’ll take her home.
Don’t worry.
My sister went to watch Li He’s race,
and Ning Zeyu would send her home?
What’s going on?
Come on. Let me take you home.
The race ended earlier.
He must have left already.
Okay.
I’d better not see him
before the test result comes out.
Okay.
Let’s go.
No need. I can do it myself.
Hello.
Is this Ning Zeyu’s mother?
Yes, I am.
Who is this?
I’m a professor from
the department of network programming
at Tiangong University
of Science and Technology.
My name is He Yanjing.
Sorry to disturb you.
Professor from Tiangong University
of Science and Technology.
Why are you looking for my son?
Ning Zeyu
left the contest early.
According to the rules,
that constitutes a waiver.
I think he might
have a reason for doing it.
So I’m a bit concerned.
What?
Contest?
Mmm.
Have some water.
Stop it. Have some water.
You’re in my way.
Have some water.
Stay out of my way. I’m watching it.
-You practiced for an afternoon.
-You’re so annoying.
Here’s our champion. Applaud.
Come on.
Show me your trophy cup.
Or your medal.
At least a certificate of honor.
The host can’t be more miserly.
I’m so tired today.
Mom, dad, I’ll take some rest.
Wait. Li He.
Tell me.
Li He didn’t do well this time?
Yes.
Don’t be nervous.
Chief is training really hard
at school.
And his performance is really good too.
He’s just in a bad state this time.
So,
if he can adjust his state,
I believe he can do better next time.
Yes. It’s fine.
It’s just the way competitions are.
He’ll win and he will lose.
He can’t always win, right?
He’s young. He’s not afraid of defeats.
Besides, I think Chief can
demonstrate his best capability
next time.
And he’ll be the champion again.
Yes.
I’m just concerned and scared
that he can’t take this.
There’s nothing he can’t take.
Chuan, stay for dinner.
Have a try of your uncle’s cooking.
Thank you, aunt and uncle.
But I need to go home earlier and
help my mom organize merchandises.
I’ll go now.
I’ll come by another day.
Aunt, uncle, bye.
Chief, I’ll go now. Bye.
Don’t say he’s adopted recently.
Otherwise, he’ll be upset again.
It’s nothing.
Be a man!
Be tough!
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪