♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 12=
(Jiang Yuan)
What’s the fuss about?
(Rift Prodigals Academic Exchange Group)
We are going tutor that brat tomorrow.
I need to figure out a way
to stop monitor
paying too much attention on him.
(Yun Xiang)
She won’t.
Monitor has been rational and fair.
She will. Think about it.
We won’t wear school uniforms tomorrow.
That brat must have prepared a lot.
Ning Zeyu, the duplicitous jerk
might also plot something.
Why do you think so much?
Just train him hard.
When monitor knows your ability,
she will forget that wussy.
This is not what a real man would do.
Where is Chuan?
Chuan.
Chuan, stop what you are doing.
It’s very urgent.
Easy.
Don’t dress like a torn sack.
Tomorrow,
you can dress differently.
How differently can I dress?
My clothes are all sports style.
The couple dresses.
Not the same clothes,
but the same color.
Just to declare your sovereignty.
(Playboy)
(Unknown number)
Hello.
I have no money for any loan, house
or membership.
It’s me, Li He.
How do you know my number?
Zeyu told you, right?
Just forget about that.
Do me a favor. It’s urgent.
What’s the benefit for me?
Zeyu gave me
a book of Grade 10
Comprehensive Science.
Are you tired of living?
Ask me for benefits?
Do you forget who I am?
I’m the boss of Sen Yong.
Don’t you want to see
the sun coming up on next Monday?
Yuan Caixi is my sister.
Fine.
I’ll buy you drumstick for one week.
No problem.
Go ahead. What’s the matter?
Take a look for me
what color your sister’s
dress is tomorrow.
That’s it?
No problem. I’ll tell you
the first time, okay?
I’ll hung up.
My sister is wearing a green jacket
and a pair of blue jeans.
Remember the drumsticks next week.
What are you doing here again?
I just tidied your cabinet yesterday.
And you messed it up like a dump.
Listen.
Tidy it up well after you finish it.
Got it, Dad.
Your mom will kick my ass
when she sees the mess.
Remember it,
if your mom kicks my ass,
I’ll kick your ass.
Just leave me alone.
This one is not bad.
Ye Jingxi.
You are too well-shaped.
Handsome boy looks good in everything.
Right?
Coming.
Bear.
Look, not only me...
Monitor.
Don’t you realize
our clothes are in the same color today?
This is called a connection
and a special chemistry.
Why are you here?
Monitor asked us to help you.
Yeah.
Yuan.
What’s the situation?
Why are they here?
Didn’t you tell me
that you have a problem with
the schoolwork
and the movie lines?
I think that you also need training
for your physical fitness
and it’s too much for me
to do it on my own.
So I asked them to help.
Is that okay?
But I’m a celebrity.
What if they leak my address
and take photos of me secretly?
Who will take photos of you?
-Why would we want your photos?
Yeah.
Don’t waste time. Let’s get started.
I’m hungry.
Chang your shoes.
Chang your shoes, Li He.
It’s quite big here.
Chang your shoes.
There is also a yard here.
-Your house is not bad.
-Don’t go out.
Don’t come in then.
What are you doing?
Just stay outside.
Open the door.
I’ll count three.
Three, two, one.
Come on, Yuan.
Have some apples. It’s very sweet.
I’ll eat it later.
It’s not for you.
It’s not that sweet,
but pretty dry.
The water is quite sweet.
Really?
Yeah.
I don’t need you two to be my coaches.
You don’t need coaches like us?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You want to be an actor?
Look how
skinny you are.
How does that look good in the camera?
You will look thin and weak when you
stand beside other people.
All right.
By the way, have you
remembered
the movie lines?
The lines...
Oh.
I find it unbelievable
that someone would refuse to swim.
Getting in water, being closed to
the heart of the ocean
is the most amazing feeling
I’ve ever felt.
Well?
It’s on the first page
of your movie lines.
Oh, right.
I remember it.
Look at this.
We still have one month
before your audition.
So I made this, Ye Jingxi’s
Short-term Improvement Plan.
That’s right.
We will come here
to tutor you every weekend.
When we are not here,
you can review by yourself
according to the Plan.
Let’s try to get this audition.
-Yeah.
If you can make it.
Yeah.
I will try.
-Yeah.
It’s a good thing
that you are aware of it.
Come on.
It’s very hard to be trained by us.
It requires both your physical strength
and your brain power.
Ye Jingxi, come on.
Keep smiling.
Come on, let’s get started.
(Monday)
(Tuesday)
(Wednesday)
(Thursday)
(Friday)
Why are you here again?
Do you dress like this at home?
Never judge a book by its cover.
This is who he is.
This is my house.
I can wear whatever I want.
What’s more,
can’t you see
that you are not welcomed at all?
Fine, let’s go, monitor.
-Let’s go.
-Ah?
Don’t go.
Why? We should leave.
Didn’t you ask us to leave?
Yeah.
I was kidding.
Ah?
-Really?
-Please come in, come in.
-Yeah.
-Can we come in?
You can.
I haven’t changed my shoes.
No need.
Yeah, you should take off
your shoes, Li He.
Don’t bother. Feel free to come in.
-I’ll come in with my shoes.
-Go ahead.
Come in. Come in.
It feels good.
Have a try.
This carpet is quite soft.
Get us some dry apples like last time.
-We don’t want to tire him out.
-Yeah, we don’t want to tire him out.
-Go ahead. Hurry up.
-Hurry up.
He really takes himself as a celebrity?
Do some exercise.
-I can’t.
-Can you do it or not?
It’s easy for you to talk.
You do it.
Pull-up
is a multi-joint exercise
that is great for upper body
and waist strength.
That’s why I asked you to do it.
Look at me.
How is it going?
Do you need some rest?
Yuan, go back.
Don’t go, look at me, monitor.
-We are okay. You can go back.
-Don’t you want some water?
-Monitor.
-It’s okay.
One.
Come on, keep your waist straight. Two.
Come on.
I find it unbelievable
that someone would refuse to...
To swim.
In water... of the ocean...
Go on.
You guys work well together.
Don’t know what you are
talking about. English, please.
Fine.
I find it...
That someone would...
In water...
Close to the heart...
(Monday)
(Tuesday)
(Wednesday)
(Thursday)
(Friday)
(Monday)
(Tuesday)
(Wednesday)
(Thursday)
(Friday)
(Jingxi’s Short-term Improvement Plan)
After three weeks of training,
I think his physical fitness
is up to standard.
The next step is...
Next, his English pronunciation
needs to be corrected.
There are some problems with
his grammar and pronunciation.
Yuan, come here.
What?
-What’s the matter, Bear?
-What do you want to do?
I need Yuan to help me with the lines.
What do you mean?
No, wait!
-What’s the matter?
-Why do you close the door?
-Open it.
-Open the door.
-Ye Jingxi, what are you doing?
-Hold on. I need to rehearse my lines.
It won’t take long.
-Three, two, one.
-Just ten minutes.
-Stop it!
-You guys have some food first.
-Don’t throw yourself against the door.
-It won’t work even you do that.
-Open the door!
-For the last time.
Open the door!
Hurry up.
Li He!
A pair of four.
Bomb.
Do you know how to play?
Don’t play if you can’t.
How do you know that I can’t play?
I love to use bomb.
I have a lot of them.
Do you have a problem with it?
Counter bomb.
Counter again.
Bro, we are both farmers.
Why do you use bomb against me?
Is there any problem?
No problem.
We will keep blowing you up
if you keep rehearsing lines
with monitor.
Can you please relax?
We were only rehearsing my lines.
Do you need to lock the door
to rehearse your lines?
Yeah, you can ask me
to rehearse your lines.
I can act as an animal.
You only wore a turtle suit.
You little bastard, who told you that
I wore turtle suit?
Don’t you lay a hand on me?
I just did. So what?
What do you want to do?
That’s what I want to ask you.
You are such a smug at school.
Do you really take yourself
as a big star?
Am I not a big star? I am.
You...
But there is a huge difference between
your image in public and private.
None of your business.
Listen,
just go home if you can take a hint.
You’ve got some nerve.
Are you driving us away?
Yeah.
Look,
I’ll kick your ass
even with monitor being here!
Mm-hmm.
Come on!
-I’ll teach you a lesson.
-No, come on.
-What do you two want to do?
-I’ll see if you can keep being a smug.
What do you two want to do?
You three, stop it!
Get off me!
What are you wearing on your head?
You’ve played long enough.
I’ll answer the phone.
We’ll fight after I come back.
Wait for me.
Don’t leave.
Hello, Bawan. What’s the matter?
Ye, when are you coming to class?
Didn’t I tell you I won’t
take classes these days?
What’s wrong
with you two?
Sit properly.
I mean, you are here to be teachers.
We should tutor Bear.
Can you watch your attitude?
What’s wrong with our attitude?
Have we not behaved well?
That’s how Bai treats us.
How does he treat you?
With a pair of 4 and a bomb?
He would blow me up
even I play a pair of 3.
Are you…
If you want us
to have the right attitude,
you shouldn’t rehearse lines
with him behind the locked door.
The basic risk awareness is necessary.
Yeah.
I didn’t lock the door.
Can he lock the door as he wants?
Can’t you open the door and come out?
Monitor, you used to
hold Li He by his collar.
Yeah.
Now you’ve become a lamb.
No.
Well, I’m different from Ye Jingxi.
What? Are you on my side?
I’m on your side, but Ye Jingxi...
Fine. All right.
I’ll censor myself first.
I’ll try to be a good teacher for Bear
and correct my attitude.
I won’t be led by the nose.
That’s also what you two
should do, okay?
Okay.
Ye, this teacher is really good.
Are you not attending any class?
No.
Keep asking for leave for me.
Still?
Ye, Ms. Hua keeps asking me.
I can’t take it anymore.
Ye, don’t...
Hello, Ye?
How’s it going? Whose turn now?
Go on.
It’s your turn to recite your lines.
The three of us will
supervise you together.
Yeah.
Right now?
Do you hear that?
Take that thing off your nose.
And the one on your head.
The one on your head.
Don’t copy me.
What a repeater.
Aren’t we on the same side?
Yuan, haven’t I just recited the lines?
We can...
Get started now.
What’s wrong?
Can’t Ye Jingxi come?
Sorry, Ms. Rou.
Jingxi still has a cold.
Is he still having a fever?
Yeah.
His fever has been lasting
for days.
All right, tell him to have more rest.
Thank you, Ms. Rou.
I owe you a lot.
It has been a hard day.
It’s pretty tiring.
It’s all right. It’s just like
a normal school day.
I’m going to
use a different way tomorrow
and let him familiarize himself with
his partner’s lines.
That is good.
Teach me. I also want to learn it.
No problem. It’s rare
that you want to learn.
Why are you sighing, monitor?
Ye Jingxi is getting better very fast.
-Yes.
-He is the best actor for this role
in terms of strength,
popularity and price-performance.
Well...
-Won’t you two go home?
-I think he is right.
I’m about to get home.
Why don’t you go home?
Ah.
I’ve been enjoying
the conversation too much
and haven’t noticed
that we have already gone so far.
Not noticed? I’ve told you many times.
Okay, let’s go. Let us walk you home.
Come back.
I don’t need you two to walk me home.
I can go home by myself, okay? Bye-bye.
Why are you laughing?
Just go home.
Are you not going home?
None of your business.
It’s hard to keep on studying.
You don’t need to
send monitor home tomorrow.
Thank you for your concern.
I think you should go home
and have some walnuts
for your brain’s sake.
I don’t even bother to argue with you.
You go back first.
Why should I listen to you?
Can’t you see who the third wheel is?
You mean I’m the third wheel?
Yeah.
I know what you are up to.
Old fox.
Well.
You can’t recognize
the way home without having walnuts?
Where are you going?
None of your business.
I’ll make a detour.
Why does it take you so long?
Did you climb your way back?
You are fast.
But you still have to wait for me
to open the door for you.
Ning Zeyu.
I team up with you
to deal with Ye Jingxi,
but it doesn’t mean
our problem is resolved.
Open the door for me.
Oh.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I don’t know if you are reminding me
or reminding yourself.
Or you misunderstood something.
Listen,
I’m good.
But the gap in our IQ
decides that we can never be friends.
Speak louder!
See you later, poor guy.
Speak louder, what?
Don’t go! Open the door!
Open the door!
Ning Zeyu!
Little brat.
Well...
Open the door, Zeyu!
Zeyu.
Ms. Rou. I’m so sorry.
Jingxi still has a cold.
Is he having a fever?
Yeah, his condition is really bad.
That’s why he can’t
come to take your class.
He doesn’t come to class.
Why did you even hire me?
It’s not like that. Ms. Rou, Ms. Rou!
Ms. Hua.
That’s nonsense.
You even run wild with him.
Did I hire you
to play with Ye Jingxi?
Don’t you know how important
the movie audition is?
Ms. Hua.
Actually,
his classmates are pretty nice.
They can help him a bit.
Help him?
Do they know how to act?
Do they know that Jingxi’s right cheek
looks better than his left cheek,
and he should face his right cheek
to the camera?
Do they know Jingxi is easy to
get nervous before shooting
and he needs hot milk to fall asleep?
They know nothing.
A bunch of little kids.
They don’t know anything.
They thought they could help Jingxi.
Bawan.
Do you have a problem with your brain?
You really pissed me off!
Jingxi, open the door.
I know you are at home!
Open the door!
Yuan!
Don’t open the door.
I think Jingxi is not at home.
Why doesn’t he open the door?
Let’s go, Ms. Hua. He’s not at home.
What’s happening here?
What’s wrong?
He turned his phone off.
A woman?
She is my agent.
Then why don’t you open the door?
-I don’t open the door for your good.
-Let me ask you,
what has Jingxi been doing recently?
Why?
Nothing.
It’s for your good anyway.
Jingxi has been studying hard recently.
He better be.
Jingxi.
Listen,
you should know
when to stop horsing around.
You can try to skip
Ms. Rou’s class tomorrow.
She is threatening me again.
Jingxi.
Do you believe
I’ll take your phone away?
Open the door.
If you don’t open the door,
do you believe
I’ll take your phone away?
Ms. Hua, Jingxi is just getting cranky.
He’ll turn the phone on in a while.
And you...
Jingxi, open the door!
Ms. Hua.
You’ve been knocking the door
for a while and no one answers.
Jingxi is definitely not at home.
Ms. Hua, let’s leave.
It’s not good to make a big deal of it.
Let’s go, Ms. Hua.
Don’t worry, you got me.
She seems to have left.
She left.
She almost got us.
Why didn’t you open the door?
I didn’t open the door...
It’s for your good.
Just keep it in mind.
Why hasn’t she left yet?
Don’t open the door!
Why are you here so late?
Why do you turn your phone off?
It’s you guys.
You are like this
to hide from your agent?
You really scared me.
Why didn’t you answer the phone?
My phone is in my bag. I didn’t hear it.
I thought you were rehearsing your lines
with monitor
behind the locked door again.
If you are really aboveboard,
just explain it to her.
Why couldn’t you do that?
What do you know?
I did it for Yuan’s sake.
You should make it clear
for her sake.
All right, let’s start to study.
Hurry up.
She asked you to study.
Recite your lines.
The special training is finally over.
Wait.
It’s not over yet.
Body management
won’t end until
the last day of your life.
You still can’t eat
whatever you want.
I’ll keep an eye on you.
-Yuan.
-Yeah.
Let’s go to the concert. I have tickets.
It’s a really popular boy group.
What’s good about the boy group?
It’s better to see me running.
I’m much hotter
than them when I’m running.
Don’t forget that our exam result
will come out tomorrow.
Zeyu is right.
We should wait
until the exam result
comes out tomorrow.
I’ll leave now.
Yuan, let me take you home.
-No need.
Don’t bother, Bear.
Someone will take me home today.
-What?
Yeah.
Surprise!
Do you miss me, guys?
Hey.
That’s too much.
Li He.
Lin Chuan.
Chuan. Chuan.
What’s wrong?
Did I read this right?
You read it right.
I...
Passed the exam!
-I passed the English exam!
-You passed the English exam!
Wow.
One moment I thought I got 9 points.
But I got 90 points.
Monitor.
I passed my English exam.
Good.
How did you do that?
Oh my.
Monitor, Yuan, wait a minute.
Tell me,
when will I get more points
in my English exam?
What’s Ning Zeyu’s score?
He still gets the first place anyway.
What’s the difference?
Look at this question, this...
Our three-year friendship is not
as important as Zeyu’s English paper.
Zeyu.
Did you throw the exam on purpose?
You are still number one,
but your score drops significantly.
Looks like I can surpass you soon.
I’m still number one
even my score drops.
Monitor, shouldn’t you reflect on it?
This is who you are.
Well, are you trying to motivate me
in a different way?
No.
I’m just mocking you.
Yuan.
Look at my score.
Well done, Bear. You’ve gotten
40 more points.
Thanks to your help.
To express my gratitude,
come to my house this weekend.
I’ll treat you to a fancy meal.
How is it?
Just do me the favor.
This weekend...
Yeah.
Okay.
I’ll do you the favor.
Hurry up.
Don’t hit me. I’m the one
with the green hat.
Go ahead.
It’s a waste of time.
E-sports games can relax the brain,
make the cerebral cortex more active,
stimulate the secretion
of the pituitary gland
so as to increase happiness.
You can play for a while
without affecting your study.
-Yuan Caixi.
-Yes?
Keep making up.
Playing games can increase happiness.
You can even make that up
to encourage me.
I’m really moved.
I just want you to recover soon.
The competition will be fun in this way.
Otherwise, I won’t feel accomplishment
even I win.
Fine.
I’ll take my monitor’s order.
I’ll go to recover myself.
Okay.
I think we can win this time.
You are number two.
I’m number two. Don’t touch me.
I’m number two.
I’m number two now. Don’t touch me.
I didn’t touch you.
I fell into the volcano.
Use the props, don’t...
Don’t save them.
If I don’t save the props,
how I can hit him for you
when someone tries to surpass you?
It’s right time to use it now.
Which one is the brake?
Are you serious?
You’ve been playing for so many days
and you still can’t remember the keys?
I forgot it.
You are about to be surpassed.
I have no props left.
I’ll use my ass to hit him.
You are really weak.
I’m weak?
Are you not weak? Number two.
Look who is weak.
I would have been number one
if it weren’t for you.
Didn’t I guard your back?
Fine, play by yourself.
You play with him. I’m not playing.
I’m pissed off.
Why do you...
Maybe it’s called talent.
I’m gonna have a piece of pizza.
Well done, Zeyu.
Li He!
Don’t eat it!
-Monitor, what’s wrong?
-What’s wrong?
-I feel uncomfortable.
-How?
What’s wrong?
Pizza...
Pizza?
-What’s wrong with you?
-Does your stomach hurt?
Are you feeling uncomfortable, too?
There is a something wrong with
the pizza. Call 120.
It’s too late to call 120 now.
Let’s get a taxi.
Are you okay?
You go ahead first.
I’ll ask Bawan to pick me up later.
Are you going to wait for
Bawan at this point?
Go ahead.
The media will follow me if I go.
I don’t want Yuan to be exposed.
Go now.
I’ve called a taxi for you.
It’ll be here in three minutes.
Take care of him.
Li He.
Take good care of monitor.
Rest assured.
Are you okay?
(The A&E Center)
(EM Observation Room)
Doctor!
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
(Emergency)
(In-patient)
Is she okay, doctor?
No big deal.
Fortunately, she didn’t eat a lot.
She spit it all out.
Just go home and rest for a few days.
-Thank you, doctor.
-You’re welcome.
What’s wrong? You look serious.
I’m worried about you.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
I’ll try the food first
next time.
Then nothing will happen to you.
Are you a Silver Needle?
All right, go to check Bear.
I want to know how he is doing.
Okay.
I’ll go first.
Have some rest.
Yeah.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
Why don’t you go inside?
They won’t let me in.
How is monitor doing?
She will be fine after some rest.
I mean,
you brought him here.
Why don’t they let you in?
I don’t know.
That’s strange.
We are not fans.
We are his classmates.
Why don’t they let us in?
You really can’t go inside.
Ms. Hua said no one is allowed in.
Please help me.
I’ll let you know as soon as
Jingxi wakes up.
I think his condition
is not that simple.
I want to check monitor first.
Doctor, how’s he doing?
Well, he is stable.
Look, his body temperature is normal.
Take medicine on time
and stay for observation for a few days.
He can be released
if nothing else is wrong.
Thank you.
Doctor.
Please pay more attention
to his privacy.
Of course, we know that.
When I was young,
my parents were busy with work
and they had no time to take care of me.
I had to order takeaway
when I was a kid.
For safety,
I always ordered a meal for three people
so as to let others know
that I was not home alone.
But one day,
I suddenly realized
that I didn’t need to
order a meal for three people
because I have three good friends
who are staying with me.
Ning Zeyu helps me with my study.
Li He helps me with my exercise.
Yuan’s mother makes soup for me.
Yuan
is my good friend.
Sister.
I find
that I am not alone anymore.
You ungrateful brat.
Bawan and I have been
staying by your side all the time.
Do we mean nothing to you?
Sister.
Can’t you show some sympathy?
I’ve been rehearsing it many times.
This is the most touching words
I can think of.
Why do you have no reaction at all?
What sympathy?
Wait for me.
Over there.
Are you okay?
How’s Bear doing?
Forget about him.
Take care of yourself first.
He should be fine, right?
He should be fine.
I guess it’s for his image’s sake,
they won’t let us visit him.
What?
Ms. Hua won’t let us in.
We can’t blame her.
Several girls out there
have recognize him.
They want to take pictures.
Bawan can’t stop them at all.
Just for a while,
there are all kinds of
photos of him online.
The most important thing
is that someone frames him
for having alcoholism.
I remember Bear said
that the happiest thing for him
is to come to Sen Yong and meet me.
Because he thinks
he finally has friends.
But at this point,
we can’t stay by his side or visit him.
What should we do?
-Hello, monitor.
-Hello, Bawan.
How’s Bear doing now?
He is awake now.
Well, Ms. Hua wants you to come.
Has the big star woken up?
First of all,
thank you for taking care of Jingxi.
It’s nothing.
You helped him a lot,
but I hope you can understand
that
he is not an ordinary person.
As a celebrity,
the company has plans for him.
He also has his responsibility
to the society.
We hired a teacher for him.
He can’t skip class as he wants.
And you
can’t decide on your own
that you are qualified
to teach a celebrity
how to act professionally.
You think you are helping him.
But what’s the result?
Help him get in the hospital?
Ms. Hua.
Yuan Caixi also got sick.
Would anyone get sick
if Jingxi took the classes
as I told him?
Jingxi is a celebrity.
He has responsibilities.
But
it’s only his profession
to be a celebrity.
No matter what,
he is still a nineteen-year-old
high school student.
I’ve been his agent for years.
Do you think I don’t know it?
You are still young.
You have many ideas
and a lot of things that you want to do.
But everyone
needs to bear the responsibilities
and consequences for their choices.
They need to figure out what they want
and pay the price for it.
Jingxi
chose to be a celebrity by himself.
Then he should
pay the corresponding price.
So do you.
We got it, Ms. Hua.
We will pay more attention to it.
All right, go inside.
Okay.
Be careful.
He just vomited.
Okay, Aunt.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Yuan!
Are you feeling better?
Thanks to you, she kept vomiting.
What do you mean by that?
How would I know
that the pizza has expired?
Besides,
I also suffered a lot, okay?
Remember to clear
your refrigerator next time
and don’t eat any expired food.
Do you hear that, Bawan?
We are telling to you.
Ye Jingxi.
Yeah.
In fact,
Ms. Hua asked us to come.
Ye Jingxi.
Bear.
Yeah.
Maybe the things
aren’t as simple as we think they are.
We didn’t consider the consequences.
So,
you should listen to
Ms. Hua from now on.
Do whatever she asks you to do.
Don’t be rebellious, got it?
Oh.
You are also on the side of my company?
We are not on your company’s side.
We mean it.
At first,
I thought you took yourself
as a big star
and you looked like a smug.
Right now,
I realize it’s not easy for you, either.
Come on, I think you can make it.
Duh.
What?
Time to get an injection.
Oh.
Time for an injection.
An injection, right. I should leave now.
You two should give me some privacy.
We are all men. What are you afraid of?
We are not your fans.
We won’t take pictures of you in secret.
Hurry up, take your pants off.
Turn around.
Give him an injection.
Thanks.
He’s pretty white.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪