♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 16=
How about steaming a fish?
Why do we steam a fish?
The adults are absent
and we should eat junk food.
You don’t do exercises, right?
Don’t you know junk food is not good?
I don’t know.
What are you doing?
There’re my fans in front.
Fans? How’s that possible?
Quiet down. They’d hear you.
Ye Jingxi.
You’re not a big star here.
Nobody knows you.
Just accept the reality, okay?
Let’s go.
Stop. Bear.
You mustn’t eat this.
You’ll regret it.
Why?
Because the spicy flavor is better.
I think so.
Hurry.
-Hey.
-What?
Who’s that naughty kid?
I don’t know him.
And who’s the fool that
seems to have never visited
a supermarket?
Just a passerby.
Good one.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m buying meat.
This meat is too expensive.
Just pay for freshness.
Don’t waste money.
This... This isn’t expensive, is it?
This is not expensive?
Check out the price.
Hurry up! My sister’s in trouble.
My sister will be driven mad soon.
Have a try.
This is imported.
Mine is delicious.
Have a taste of mine.
Try my product.
Yuan Caixi.
What are you doing?
Ah! Thanks, Aunt. No more, please.
Thanks, aunt. Bye.
Bye.
Thanks, Aunt. Please, no more.
Thanks. Please don’t give me more.
Thank you, Aunt. Thanks.
-Have a try.
-Have one.
Try this. It’s imported from Australia.
Wow. This is tasty.
Yuan Haoxi, close the gate.
I can get hungry as well.
It’s fine. I’ll cook for you.
I’ll definitely fill you up.
Why it’s you who’ll cook for Yuan?
I can too.
Wow. That’s great.
You can cook together.
We didn’t say we’d cook for you.
If my sister gets to eat,
then I should either.
Great. Then the two of us
can sit and wait for dinner?
Rest assured.
Take some rest.
-Okay.
-Let me.
Then, we’ll leave now.
Go. Yuan.
Trust me.
Caixi,
will they set the kitchen on fire?
Don’t burn the house down.
-No problem. Don’t worry.
-Don’t worry.
Two steaks.
Ye Jingxi,
since I have sportsmanship,
to ensure the fairness in competition,
I’m obligated to tell you that
my cooking skill
is inherited from my family.
I also have the obligation to warn you
that I used to live abroad.
Those who have lived abroad have
cooking skills
that are rigorously tested
Besides,
though you may have cooking skills
inherited from the family,
I’m the one who knows Yuan
most thoroughly.
Do you know which food Yuan likes
and which she hates?
You don’t, right?
Is this a challenge?
Will you accept it?
Sure.
I think they’re in a competition now.
Let’s make a bet!
Tell me the conditions first.
Throwing trash for a week.
Plus doing dishes.
Throwing trash and doing dishes?
Are you scared?
I’m fearless.
That’s the deal, then.
Throwing trash plus doing dishes.
For a week.
Okay. Who will you bet on?
Definitely, Ye Jingxi.
He lived abroad for so long.
How can he still not cook?
That’s a convincing reason.
But,
my bet is on Li He.
Yuan Caixi.
What is your favorite hand-cream flavor?
I guess
your hands will get coarse
in the next week.
Save the hand-cream to yourself.
You’re destined to lose, Yuan Caixi.
He’s so naive.
Where’s sugar?
It runs out.
Why don’t you tell me before
you use up all the sugar?
How could I know you need it?
Don’t you know that sugar
is a must-have ingredient in cooking?
I don’t.
Why are you so angry?
It’s just sugar.
You can find a replacement.
Why don’t you use a replacement?
I’m making dessert.
I’m making braised chicken wings.
We just run out of sugar. So what?
Ye Jingxi, you’re so despicable.
You suggested the competition.
I competed fairly.
But you used all the sugar.
How can I compete with you?
We can both use sugar.
I didn’t know you need it.
Besides,
you can make another dish.
You really think you’re a star, right?
You really think you’re a star?
What do you mean?
You don’t have privileges here.
-No privileges.
-I’ll teach you a lesson today.
Teach me?
Yes. I’ll teach you a lesson!
Come! Teach me then!
-Come!
-Come on!
-Come on.
-I’ll get you.
-Don’t move.
(Zeyu)
Zeyu, how’s your training?
I’m doing great. How about you?
We?
Come here.
Are you a man or not?
We’ll soon find out
if we can live to see tomorrow
without getting food poisoning
or having the house burnt down.
Dare you hit me again?
So what?
Ye Jingxi, you really
see yourself as a star, right?
Let’s fight till death!
Caixi. Caixi. Caixi.
They’re going to fight!
What?
Caixi.
Zeyu, I’ll have to go now.
Monitor.
-Caixi.
-Let go.
Caixi.
What are you doing?
Li He, let go.
What’s going on?
Ask him. He used up all the sugar.
How many times I’ve told you?
I didn’t know you need sugar.
You didn’t know?
Wait a second.
So you mean
you used up
the sugar he needs.
Yes.
So you can’t cook?
Caixi.
What’s the flavor of
the hand-cream you like?
Can’t you grow up?
If you want to cook,
just behave and cook.
Why are you tearing my house apart?
Well...
Well.
What will you do without sugar?
I’ll figure it out myself.
Are you sure?
What else can I do?
Before we eat,
my sister and I made a bet
to decide which of you cooks better.
Monitor.
Who’s your bet on?
That doesn’t matter.
What’s important is to see
who cooks better now.
Wait a second.
Why is Yuan the judge
of your bet?
That’s fine.
After all,
Yuan definitely favors me.
Cut out the nonsense.
Aren’t you stupid?
If we both are the judges,
we can’t get a result
until tomorrow morning.
So,
I chose the best way.
Yes.
A blind taste test.
Okay.
Okay, Caixi.
Have we finished?
How’s it?
It’s finished?
Yes.
Then I’ll announce
my favorite dish first.
Chicken wings.
And...?
The second favorite is
the steak.
The third one is
stir-fried eggs with tomato.
The fourth is the cupcake.
Because the cupcakes are too sweet.
Oh.
Who made the steak?
I find it so familiar.
Bear.
You made it?
Yes.
Because you used to like the steakhouse
when you were a kid.
So, I made one
according to its taste.
Oh.
We haven’t been to
the restaurant for a while.
It’s fine.
From now on,
I can make it for you every day.
Ah!
I shouldn’t have said
that cupcakes are too sweet.
Are they?
But these were your favorites
when you were a kid.
When she was a kid?
Things are different now.
We like junk food when we were kids.
But junk food is bad.
But,
you cooked
these two dishes?
Yes.
Really?
Of course.
It’s the inherited cooking skills
of Li Family.
Wow.
How do you know that
my sister likes chicken wings
and stir-fried eggs with tomato?
Well.
Your sister has a small appetite.
Whenever the canteen
serves chicken wings,
she can eat more rice.
It’s the same with
stir-fried eggs with tomato.
She prefers home-style dishes.
She likes vegetables.
She likes baby cabbages.
She doesn’t eat eggplants,
green onions or peppers.
Right?
This is so scary.
Are you hiding in our house?
I hide under your bed.
Yuan.
Your food preference has changed a lot.
Well.
You...
How did you make this without sugar?
How dare you even bring that up?
I made it with this.
I planned on making
braised chicken wings.
But there was no sugar.
Luckily, there was a coke in the fridge.
So I made cola chicken wings with it.
Somehow, my cola chicken wings
are even better than
braised chicken wings.
Thank you.
It’s over. It’s over.
It’s over now.
This time,
Li He wins by huge margins.
It’s so good to have you, bro.
With you in my life,
everything’s so bright.
I’m winner in the race,
in the bicycle race,
and even in the cooking competition.
I’m about to fall in love with myself.
Go away.
Bear.
I’m so disappointed in you.
Wait a second.
You mean you bet on me?
Yuan bet on him?
Of course.
For the first time in life,
I felt I was smarter than my sister.
No. Let’s compete again.
Forget it.
This one doesn’t count.
Forget it!
Don’t waste our time.
Because of you,
I need to wash the dishes.
You have to do it with me later.
It’s really so delicious?
I don’t believe it.
Well.
Hum.
I didn’t expect you to be a good cook.
In my family,
my mom is the most important person.
To please my mom,
my dad, who previously couldn’t
tell onion, garlic, and ginger apart,
put a lot of effort in learning to cook.
He cooked a variety of dishes for my mom
and he forced me to learn from him.
He said that
when he’s not home,
I can cook for mom.
It’s great to
have a dad.
I’m sorry.
Did I say something I shouldn’t say?
No. You don’t have to apologize to me.
You know it as well.
When I was a child,
my dad passed away.
My mom raised Yuan Haoxi and me
on her own.
She’s still single.
Though she never says so,
I know
she feels bitter inside.
She’s jealous about those kids
who have a father.
It’s fine, Yuan Caixi.
From now on, I’m your...
What?
I’m your personal cook.
I’ll cook whatever you want for you,
from Western styles to Chinese cuisines,
from sweet to salty.
I can cook for you
whatever you order.
Thanks.
Are you feeling cold?
I...
Yuan Caixi.
Yes.
Actually, I...
I li...
Caixi, come on.
The star will perform now.
Yes.
I’m coming.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Come on. Hurry.
-Bye, Yuan.
-Bye-bye.
Hum. You made me wash the dishes.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Bye, Yuan.
I didn’t expect that
you play the piano so well.
It seems that Yuan was fascinated by
the cola chicken wings you made.
How can I not show off a bit?
So, you did it on purpose.
So cunning.
I’ve never seen Yuan
so close to a guy.
But I can tell that
she’s really happy.
Maybe, that’s the reason
I was in a hurry to impress her.
Don’t worry, man.
There are many beauties in the world.
You
just focus on
study,
playing the piano.
Just let me care for
monitor.
Get over yourself!
I said this
not because I’d give up on Yuan.
Don’t you find it weird that
we can still be friends
when we like the same girl?
No, I don’t.
Why?
Because you don’t have any friend.
I...
I’m just kidding.
When it comes to friends,
quality overcomes quantity.
You’ve got me.
You only need me.
You would be great as an actor.
Why?
You’re so shameless.
Ye Jingxi, listen.
If I have the opportunities you have,
I’ll be a more famous star than you’re.
Yep.
Did you hear me?
You? Just look at yourself.
-Well.
-Take a look at yourself.
Who are you? You can’t even act.
Can you run faster than me?
Is that you?
It’s so early in the morning.
Jingxi.
What’s going on?
Bad news.
What?
Bad news!
Does Ye Jingxi live here?
Is Ye Jingxi living with a girl?
Can you explain it?
Please explain it.
Caixi.
Stop it for now.
What’s your problem, Yuan Haoxi?
-Hurry. Come on.
-You.
What’s the problem, Yuan Haoxi?
What’s going on?
Caixi, can’t you see them?
What?
They scared me when I opened the door.
What did you do?
What’s the problem?
Caixi.
See it for yourself.
Well.
Where did they get these photos?
I live with Ye Jingxi?
What nonsense!
Caixi, I saw another one today.
Let me read it to you.
Since famous idol, Ye Jingxi,
returned to Sen Yong High School
for study,
he temporarily left the big screen.
ENT Xiaoba thought
he returned school for study,
but recently he was found
going in and out of a house
with a girl several times.
Caixi. This...
It’s talking about you.
I’ll talk to them.
No. Caixi, don’t go.
You mustn’t talk to them now.
Explanations only make things worse now.
Just stay here.
They will forget this thing soon.
How can I just stay here and do nothing?
They say Ye Jingxi and I
live together now.
That’s so exaggerated.
Ye Jingxi. Ye Jingxi. Ye Jingxi.
Sorry, we don’t take any interview.
We don’t do interview nor
answer questions.
Caixi.
Just listen to me. Don’t go.
Hello, Bear.
Don’t go online. Don’t go outside.
Do you hear me?
Let’s explain it immediately.
Just don’t go online or leave the house.
Wait for my words.
Hello?
Thankfully, Mom isn’t home.
We don’t do any interview. Thanks.
Make room. Excuse me. Thanks.
-Ye Jingxi.
-Don’t go, Ye Jingxi.
No way.
Reporters break in through the window?
-Li He.
Get down.
What are you doing there?
We won’t.
-Hurry up.
-There’s no one at the back.
There’s no one at the back.
Wait for me.
Slow down. Shut the door.
Let’s go.
Slow down.
-This way.
That’s them. Hurry.
That’s them. That’s the girl.
Stop!
Don’t chase me.
Don’t take photos of me.
No! Don’t!
No!
-Can we interview you?
-Don’t leave.
Ah! Caixi, wait for me.
News broke out this morning.
The whole internet is saying that
Ye Jingxi and my sister...
Live together.
Don’t mind me.
I’ve read the news hundreds of times.
Something new came up.
What is this?
(ENT Xiaoba)
Live together? Nonsense.
(Zeyu)
They’re cooking up rumors.
Hello, Zeyu.
Hello.
Where are you? Are you all right?
I just saw the news.
I’m fine. I’m at Li He’s place.
That’s great then.
I did some digging.
I found some evidence.
I’ll send it to you right now.
Take a look.
This photo is the culprit.
These rumors were started by it.
Isn’t this our house?
Yes.
I remember.
I posted this photo to my Qzone.
I saw it in your Qzone too.
(Yuan Haoxi)
But you and Aunt were also in it.
Yes.
My mom and I were also in the photo.
The photo was edited.
They did it to create misunderstandings.
They edited you and Aunt out of
the photo on purpose.
Who would do such a thing?
I don’t know who it is.
But it must be someone
who has access to your Qzone.
(Yu Xiaoba)
Since famous idol, Ye Jingxi,
returned to Sen Yong High School
for study,
he temporarily left the big screen.
What happened?
But a photo was found today
which led to heated discussions.
In the photo, Ye Jingxi stayed in
the same room with the girl
and had dinner with her.
-He was suspected for living with her.
-Ye Jingxi and his classmates.
Currently, Ye Jingxi and his agency
haven’t responded to the incident.
WeSee will continue to
bring you more updates.
Why isn’t it me?
Pan Hao, you’re here too.
Have you heard the news?
Pan Hao.
Hello?
So many people can read my Qzone.
-How can I know who it is?
-Let’s find him.
It doesn’t matter who he is now.
Maybe others appropriated the photo
and posted it to other social medias.
Even if we know who it is,
we can’t solve the problem.
So what?
Let’s post the original photo first.
Then everything will come to light.
I’ve already sent the photo
to Ye Jingxi.
His team will soon issue a statement
to explain it.
Ah! Jingxi.
This is the original photo.
Hurry and send it to Ms. Hua.
I know.
Ning Zeyu sent this to me.
Yuan said they’ll repost it
after I send it.
Okay.
Then send it to Ms. Hua.
Of course.
Ms. Hua is already working on a plan
with the publicity team.
But I have to participate the activity.
This is my work.
Okay.
How can one gossip have so much power?
Why don’t we just cancel it?
Why would I?
There are people here.
As long as there’s one supporter left,
I have to continue working hard.
Jingxi.
Keep the distance. Excuse me.
-Jingxi, we trust you.
-Excuse us.
(Jingxi, our beloved idol)
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Jingxi, we trust you.
Thanks.
Jingxi, go for it!
Jingxi, I trust you.
Thank you.
-Hello.
Thanks.
We’ll always support you.
(Jingxi, I like you.)
Jingxi,
have something sweet.
It can cheer you up.
Thanks.
Come on!
Cheer up!
Jingxi, we trust you.
Thank you for coming.
Jingxi, thank you for your work!
Go for it.
Thanks.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
-Come on.
Thanks.
Bye.
Drink more warm water, Jingxi.
-Take care of yourself.
-Thanks.
Such ridiculous articles!
Can you find out who posted those?
Bawan, the publicity division
is looking for you.
Okay. Jingxi, I’ll go now.
We must take those articles down.
It’s mere nonsense.
How can Jingxi do such a thing?
Mr. Lin, don’t worry.
We’ve found the original photo.
We can fix this problem soon.
Yes. Mr. Lin, don’t worry.
Jingxi’s sponsorship won’t be affected.
We’ll take care of this problem.
Sit.
Before you returned to Sen Yong,
I’ve warmed you that
you get a different level of attention
because of your identity.
You’re a student on the campus.
You must be careful.
You thought things are simple.
That’s just your delusion.
You skipped Miss Rou’s class.
And you insisted on
letting your classmates tutor you.
I scolded you. But you ignored me.
When you had food poisoning,
I said this not only to you,
but also to your classmates.
You’d better keep your distance.
That’s the way to protect you both.
Have I said this to you or not?
Yes.
But what’s the outcome?
Look what has happened!
Ms. Hua.
Those were fabricated.
I just had a dinner
at Yuan Caixi’s place.
You saw that too.
Besides, I always tell you where I go,
whom I visit, and when I’ll come back
except that time I asked Yuan Caixi
to help me practice audition.
I’ve reported all the other events
to you.
Things have gone so far.
I also feel wronged.
But when we were together,
we always have at least
three people in a room.
We’ve never stayed in a room alone.
I’ve never expected this to happen.
Now, we’ve found the original photo.
Ms. Hua, tell me what to do.
I’ll do my best to cooperate.
Ms. Hua, publicity company’s statement
has got more and more reposts.
There are 80,000 reposts in total now.
Ask the publicity team to press ahead.
Okay.
(Ye Jingxi Studio’s statement)
Ye Jingxi’s team has issued
a publicity statement.
Well.
Log in your accounts,
repost it and comment below it
to give it better exposure.
Ah. Okay.
Just as what I told you,
you don’t need to explain, right?
Thankfully, you said nothing.
If you show up,
the whole world will know your presence.
Don’t be mad.
Have some water.
I just don’t get it.
Why would someone cook up
such rumors so maliciously?
Why do you have so many questions?
We’re not taking a test or anything.
We athletes know that
sportsmanship means
being just, fair, and open.
But people still take dopes,
do match fixing.
People even harm others on purpose
in the field.
Sometimes, people are willing to
break every rule
to obtain what they want.
So,
that’s just the reality.
It’s no use trying to figure out why.
If you’re right,
we really can’t hold that person
accountable?
That’s not entirely true.
Think about it.
That person did this
because he wants to make Ye Jingxi sad
and make you unhappy.
If you’re really affected
by this incident,
then you’re giving him what he wants.
We can’t control others.
But we can adjust ourselves.
This is not our fault.
Why should we punish ourselves?
So, monitor,
cheer up.
Be happy.
Let’s catch this person together
and hold him accountable
for what he did.
Okay?
Yes.
Caixi.
Come over here.
Something new has come up.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪