♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 17=
Caixi, come here.
Something new came up again.
Look.
(Updates on the popular idol, Ye Jingxi)
(Ye Jingxi and a female classmate...)
So many photos.
Monitor, I just comforted you.
You hung out with him
so many times alone.
You didn’t even tell me?
Is this the right time for that?
The focus of the problem is this.
Monitor, have you really
spent time alone with Ye Jingxi?
Definitely not.
Look at this one.
The one taken in the canteen.
There are many people around us.
Moreover, Han Yayi
stood right next to me.
Oh. Right.
I was there too that day.
Yes.
Who on earth took these photos?
Look.
Some were taken in the canteen.
Some were taken on the campus.
Someone is stalking you?
No way.
An overly obsessed fan?
No.
Bear said that his fans
are well-mannered.
He doesn’t have obsessive fans.
Then who is it?
Where do these photos come from?
Jingxi is so careless.
Hurry. Find out
where these photos came from.
Okay. I know.
Find Ms. Bo from publicity department.
Okay.
Ms. Hua.
Mr. Wan. Bad news!
What?
Fans went to confront the girl.
How do you know?
A rational fan told me that
she couldn’t stop them.
Explain it to the fans.
It’s not like what they believe in.
Hurry.
Jingxi.
(Idol Ye Jingxi’s hidden history)
This is too much.
They’re digging deeper.
They went through all the news
since Bear’s debut
and his family background.
How can they not
respect a person’s privacy?
Monitor, don’t be mad.
That’s just the way haters are.
Zeyu, I’ll hang up now. I’ll call Bear.
Okay. Keep the contact.
Sir, please head to Chunxi Road
at maximum speed.
Hurry. Now!
The number you just dialed is busy now.
Sorry.
Call him later.
Ms. Hua might have
confiscated his phone.
Call him later.
Caixi,
someone seems to exposed the incident of
Ye Jingxi moving house
when he was a kid.
According to insider information,
the girl in the photo is
Ye Jingxi’s childhood sweetheart.
They knew each other
since primary school.
It’s unknown whether she was involved in
the accident that caused
Ye Jingxi to move house at Grade 3.
Who said this?
Okay.
Don’t be mad.
There are many stories on the internet.
Everyone has their own opinions.
It can’t be Ye Jingxi
who told the story.
There were many people
present at that time.
Maybe someone accidentally leaked it.
Hello, Bawan, what’s going on?
Monitor, is Jingxi with you?
No.
Monitor, when Jingxi contacts you,
you must tell me immediately.
I’m afraid he...
He...
Wait. What? Just tell me.
His fans went to your house
to confront you.
He might have rushed there to stop them.
Okay, I see.
Let’s go.
What?
Let’s go home.
It’s too dangerous to go home now.
Bear knew that
my home address has been leaked.
He’s heading towards my home.
It’ll be disastrous
if he meets his fans.
Then...
Then what should we do?
Come. Let’s go.
Ah! These two.
Your clothes.
It’s her.
She’s using Jingxi to gain attention.
That’s her.
I’m here.
Jingxi.
-Are you all right?
-I’m fine.
Hurry. Let’s go.
Have some water first.
Thanks.
I found it.
Disinfect it first.
Li He.
Do you know how to do it?
I get injuries everyday
because of running.
Of course, I know.
Hurry.
It’ll hurt a bit. Tell me if it does.
Hum.
Does it hurt?
I’ll be gentler.
Okay.
Fine.
Try to bear it.
Okay.
What?
Thank you.
You don’t need to thank me.
It’s what I should do.
I really don’t understand the fans
we met today.
Why don’t they join the track team?
They’re strong and fast.
They pushed me today.
I felt that I was bleeding inside.
Ah!
How’s Bear doing?
Don’t worry.
Those fans
can’t catch him.
Even if they do,
they won’t do anything to him.
I hope so.
Anyway,
those fans are too destructive.
They’re so strong.
You sleeve...!
Today, I really...
Gush.
But I’m not worried about his fans.
I’m worried about what will happen
when he returns to his agency.
It’s from Bear.
Yuan.
I’m sorry for causing
all this trouble to you.
But please trust me.
I’ll take care of it.
The number you just dialed is busy now.
Please redial later.
Call him later.
He will contact us
when he’s handled it.
He asked you to trust him, didn’t he?
Okay.
I hope this incident can be over soon.
(Zeyu)
Ning Zeyu.
Zeyu.
Hello, Zeyu.
How’s everything going on?
Are you all right?
Yes.
We’re home now.
Okay.
As long as you’re safe.
Don’t think too much.
Go to bed early.
Yes.
Okay.
Jingxi.
I’ll be back in ten minutes.
Ms. Hua fainted.
She’s in the hospital now.
What?
Come here and take a look.
I’ll come right away.
Sir, please head to the hospital.
Right now.
How’s it?
Listen to the doctor.
Ms. Yan fainted because of fatigue,
low blood sugar, and low blood pressure.
They all hit so suddenly.
That’s why she fainted.
She’ll be fine in a few days.
Does she need
some nutrition supplements, or...?
Don’t worry.
Just let the patient take more rest.
-Thank you, doctor.
-Thanks, doctor.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take a look inside.
Let her rest.
I...
I’ll just take a look.
I won’t bother her.
Let her rest.
Are you mad?
Let me pass.
I can explain.
Jingxi,
it’s too late now.
Let me drive you home.
It’s not that serious, right?
I can explain.
Jingxi,
have you seen the trending topics?
You went to find her
amid this huge scandal.
You want the affair to get more severe?
The agency can handle it.
I know your classmates
are important to you.
Yuan Caixi is even more important.
But you can’t always be so capricious.
Go back, Jingxi.
I’ll take you home.
Ms. Hua.
It’s my fault.
I’m sorry.
Take some rest.
I’ll go to bed.
Me too.
Let’s go to bed.
You...
You’re not leaving?
Let’s go.
Come on.
-Caixi. Caixi. Caixi.
-You...
This... this is my room.
I’ve thought about it.
When disaster struck,
help came from all sides
Besides, we’re classmates.
He and I are
excellent new-generation men.
It’s our responsibility
to keep you safe.
So, tonight,
we’ll sleep here.
Fine.
I can also protect her if I sleep there.
Yuan.
Don’t be angry if I tell you this.
So many girls are willing to
be put in your position.
Do you know that?
You were besieged by fans.
Jingxi used himself as the bait
to distract them.
And Li He escorted you home.
Is there anything that’s more romantic?
Is there?
Answer me!
Han Yayi,
you won’t even comfort me
when I’m injured?
Yuan.
I’m injured as well.
Can’t you see?
My heart is aching.
Yuan.
Fine.
-I’m injured too.
-Keep aching. Bye.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I’m sorry, Yuan.
I’m sorry.
Yuan. Yuan.
Seriously,
this news came out of nowhere.
The photos don’t
show the girl’s face.
But...
But classmates all know it’s me.
Yes.
Which heartless person
took those photos?
Who is this heartless person
that’s still unaware of what she did?
I...
I just don’t get it.
Why are there suddenly so much gossip?
Where do these photos come from?
Stop wasting your energy.
If even you
can figure it out,
then, it’s weird.
Let’s talk tomorrow.
Me...?
Yep.
What did I do?
Come on, Han Yayi.
Why aren’t you a bit smarter
after being with me for three years?
If you have time,
go through those photos again.
One of them was taken by you.
Me?
How’s that possible?
Well. Some of them
were taken by others.
Look.
Your sister also said that
they’ve never spent time alone.
So those photos were edited.
The key question is...
Where do they come from, right?
Take a look at your classmates’ Qzones.
These photos were all taken from
our classmates’ Qzones.
The other classmates were edited out.
But my sister’s face was also blurred.
It seems that my sister is protected.
The paparazzi
isn’t completely heartless.
He tried to protect high school students
Paparazzi want to protect you?
I know it.
In this case,
the one who stole these photos
didn’t intend to put monitor in trouble.
This person might be someone
who’s close to us.
Yes!
I guess
this person just wants to
collect your photos, edit them,
and post them on the internet
for attention.
But it’s hard to guess
how they end up
in the hands of paparazzi.
Good job, Yuan.
You have my utmost respect.
But,
at this point,
do you know who the culprit is?
Who is he?
Well done, Li He.
You’re not completely brainless.
Go to sleep first.
Ouch. My hand.
To be honest,
I did guess it.
But I don’t want to say it now.
Is he...
Someone we know...?
Our classmate...?
I’ll confirm it when I find the chance.
I’ll tell you
once I’m certain.
Okay.
Then, you must tell me.
Oh! Yuan, are you safe
in your house now?
Why not sleep at my place?
It’s fine. Don’t worry about me.
Fans have left already.
Besides, I’ve got Yuan Haoxi.
Moreover, Li He
is here today.
What?
He’s still there?
He hasn’t left?
Where is he sleeping at?
Han Yayi.
This is all you care about?
Don’t you feel touched by
what he did for you?
I’m indeed touched.
If it weren’t for him today,
I really wouldn’t know what to do.
Well.
Besides feeling touched?
Wow. It’s so late. It’s time to sleep.
Hello? Yuan.
Why are you sleepy when we talk about
the most important question?
Okay. Fine.
Why aren’t you so interested in study?
Bye.
(In-Patient)
Notice the media.
Hold a press conference.
Ye Jingxi will
explain everything.
And he will also...
Is that still necessary?
Ye Jingxi is livestreaming.
Livestream.
To my friends who care about me,
thank you for your concern.
My personal life took up
public media resources,
I’m really sorry.
From the beginning,
I’ve been really grateful to
those who like me.
It’s all my fault that
such things happened.
I’m sorry for
not being discreet enough.
It’s my fault.
I also let down
my agency’s trust and support.
My dear fans.
My colleagues.
I’m sorry.
Besides apologizing,
I beg you not to disturb my classmates,
my friends.
They’re my good friends
who genuinely care about me.
The photos that are spreading
on the internet
have all been photoshopped.
My agency and I
will definitely find the source
of those edited photos
and defend our rights
by taking legal measures.
In the end.
My fellows.
My friends.
Monitor.
The straight-A student.
The world champion.
I’m so sorry.
Ms. Hua.
I’m so sorry for
letting you down.
I’ll learn to grow up.
I’ll be a wise person
who knows how to care for others.
Please, trust me.
I’ll handle this incident the right way.
From now on,
I’ll learn how to make music.
I hope you can like the me
who’s focused on producing music.
Thanks.
I asked him to go abroad and act.
But he insisted on learning music.
Jingxi has a tough life as a star.
He’s the person I remember him to be.
I’m almost his fan now.
Let me peal the egg shell for you.
What are you doing? Go head.
My neck is hurting.
Really?
I stayed in the same position
for a night.
A message from Bear.
(Bear)
We found out who leaked the photos.
I’ll send you the evidence.
It’s really him.
I suspected him too.
But then I thought we are classmates.
How could he?
Zeyu.
We know who posted the photos.
Yes. I guessed it too.
But now we have
another matter to take care of.
What?
Haven’t we already found the guy?
But the point is he’s not the one
who posted those photos.
We need the poster to delete photos
or explain everything
so as to fix this problem
once and for all.
That’s right.
After all, Bear did so much.
We need to do something as well.
What should we do now?
I’ve found his personal email address
through his IP address.
But, I just don’t know
how to ask him out.
That’s simple.
I guess
you’re waiting for us.
You asked the wrong person.
-I’m here to meet...
-That’s right.
That’s us.
I’m the one
who claimed to have more photos
of Ye Jingxi,
sent you an email, and asked you out.
Don’t go, sir.
Let’s talk.
Do you know the consequences
of your behavior?
You used edited photos to
cook up rumors and
slander a person on the internet.
If Ye Jingxi’s agency wants to
hold you accountable,
you not only have to delete photos,
apologize publicly,
but also have to compensate the damages.
So, we suggest that
you immediately delete the posts,
issue an apology letter,
and restore the truth.
Otherwise, we’ll hand over
all your information
to Ye Jingxi’s agency.
They’ll teach you what to do.
Pan Hao.
What?
You came here by the request of monitor.
But you’re gonna flee when you see me?
Why?
What?
I don’t understand what you’re saying.
Stop pretending, bro.
I know you’re not that bad.
Otherwise,
you wouldn’t edit Yuan’s face.
Tell me.
What on earth happened?
You didn’t intend to
spread the rumors, right?
I told you. I don’t understand
what you’re saying.
Fine.
I’ll report it to the school.
No.
Please, no.
You’re allowed to post my photos?
I won’t be lying if I tell others
that you posted those photos.
Why can’t I?
I didn’t do it on purpose.
Once,
I posted a photo of you surrounded
by classmates in the store.
They were all buying water for you.
I said you were putting on airs.
Then your fans started to curse me.
I just said that in the moment of anger.
Then you sent my photos
to paparazzi?
No, I didn’t.
They did ask me for your photos.
I declined.
But he threatened me.
He said he’d tell my classmates
that I hated on you.
I’m afraid that
my classmates might find out.
I had no other options.
He asked me to
give him that account.
So many people were cursing me.
I don’t want that account anyway.
So I agreed.
Then, how did the paparazzi
have so many more photos?
At that time, he gave me a website
and asked me to fill in
my account and password.
I didn’t think too much.
Once I did it,
my phone...
My phone was hacked.
And the photos in it
as well as my QQ account
were all hacked.
I panicked.
I threatened him.
I said I would expose him.
He said if I dare to make it public,
he would tell others that
I sent him the photos.
I didn’t mean it.
I didn’t expect things to
take such a drastic turn.
Actually, I’m here to apologize.
It’s not too late to apologize.
(Bear)
Monitor always knew it’s you.
But she didn’t say it.
Pan Hao.
We only know each other for a semester.
I’m not close to you.
You played pranks on me in Grade 2.
Did I?
I don’t remember.
You’re the chief at South Campus.
How can you remember anyone?
Of course.
No one notices me
ever since I was a kid,
not even my parents.
They like to compare me to others
ever since I was a child.
They say I’m worthless.
So I studied so hard
and made it into Sen Yong.
I think that’s
the only thing I’m proud of.
But when I’m in high school,
there are Zeyu and monitor
in the class.
The others can only see them.
Then, later,
you athletic students came to the class.
I just don’t get it.
You’re not good at study.
You’re troublesome.
But more and more people like you.
Later,
you came here.
You’re the only people
others care about.
-Who can notice you, right?
-Who can notice...?
Right?
I think Yuan can take care of
the paparazzi.
As for you,
I think you’ve learned your lesson.
So...
You forgave me?
When I chose to be an artist,
I wished to be noticed by more people.
I understand how you feel.
But I wish, you can fight for the things
you want with your own strength,
as opposed to
taking advantage of others.
Monitor.
I’m sorry.
How about me?
Ye Jingxi,
I’m sorry.
Yes. Don’t breach the contract.
Let him contact our lawyers.
Why me?
Pan Hao, how many times I’ve told you.
You must behave at school.
How about you?
You caused so much trouble.
Your dad and I were supposed to
go on a business trip last night.
We had to change our flight for you.
Don’t you know how it affected our work?
What? He needs to be transferred
to another school?
Well.
This incident indeed has
a bad influence.
It’s not a big deal.
If this isn’t the right school for Hao,
let’s just transfer him.
Are there any due procedures?
I’m in a hurry.
Today...
Even if you’re in a hurry...
Hello?
This is your son.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
His father is really...
I know he didn’t do it
on purpose.
However,
considering that
Hao’s study will be affected
if the other students find out,
so, we invite you here for a talk
to decide if you can agree
to transfer him.
Mr. Ma.
Principal.
Let me be transferred to another school.
Miss, you have a good taste.
This is the bestseller in our store.
This bracelet means a sweet secret.
It might bring good luck.
Really? I’ll take this then.
Okay. Here’s the checkout counter.
Do you need me to wrap it for you?
No, I can just wear it.
Maybe I’ll have good luck
the moment I leave the store.
Sir, are you buying present
for your friend?
Yes.
This little crown is good.
It’s cute.
Girls all want to be princesses.
She might not want to be a princess.
She just want to be the No.1.
Wow.
Your friend is good at study.
She’s forever the first place
in my heart.
Wrap it for me.
Okay.
(Yuan Caixi)
Zeyu, when will you come back?
This afternoon.
Okay.
Come to Bear’s house. Let’s celebrate.
He said he wants to thank us.
Okay. See you later.
Well.
Why isn’t me who’s in the kitchen now?
Because the person who’s in the kitchen
believes that she cooks better than us.
So, we’re so obedient?
Yes.
Don’t try to disobey her.
Dare we disobey Yuan?
No.
Well.
Monitor.
Huh.
Do you need my help?
No. I can do it myself.
I always cook for Yuan Haoxi at home.
Look.
What I just told you?
Aren’t you afraid that
she’d bomb your kitchen?
It’s not that bad?
Right?
Are you all right, monitor?
-I’m fine. Fine.
-Let me help you.
No. Sit down.
Listen. The outcome is what’s important.
Don’t mind the process.
Ah. Ning Zeyu has arrived.
For all these years, you’ve never had
the chance to laugh at monitor.
Here comes the chance.
She’s cooking.
What? She’s not good at it.
It’s more than that.
Yuan Haoxi told me that
her cooking is horrid.
Horrid?
Ah! That’s not right.
Resident Evil style.
It’s done.
My mom is looking for me.
I’ll go home now.
Yes. I need to do work out.
Bawan wants me for work.
Freeze.
What’s wrong with you?
You’re leaving when
I’ve just finished cooking?
Don’t you know that this curry beef stew
is the feast I cooked specially for you.
-If you won’t eat it, tell me earlier.
-Curry beef stew?
I thought this is black sesame paste.
Fine. Just go if you don’t want it.
We’ll eat it.
Let’s eat it.
Of course, we will.
Well.
How about...?
-Ye Jingxi eats first.
-Come on.
-Have a try first.
-Bear.
Have a taste first.
Me... ?
Let me help you.
Have a taste.
Wait. Yuan.
A cook must taste the dish first, right?
Have a try first.
Fine.
This... this...
This is not right.
I followed the recipe!
Why does it taste like this?
Monitor.
Cooking needs talent.
You might just not be talented in it.
Yes.
Let’s eat something else.
I’m hungry.
You must all be hungry. Are you?
Are you hungry?
Are you?
Yes.
Great.
Have you finished?
Almost.
Let’s go play a round.
Let’s go.
Come on.
These two...
Oh. Zeyu.
How’s your training?
You must have learned a lot?
Yes.
Indeed. This time, I’ve learned that
there are people who’re more talented.
That’s true.
But this time, I...
Especially from this incident.
I used to care about nothing
in the past.
My biggest worry is how to beat you
and become No.1.
But Pan Hao’s incident
made me understand that
every one of us
has our own worries.
This has indeed taught me something.
That’s true.
-But...
-Well.
For the three years
we spent in the same class,
I’ve never found out that
Pan Hao wants attention so badly.
As a monitor,
I paid no heed to it.
If we care for him more,
he might not do those things.
Right?
Yes.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪