♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 18=
(Ye Jingxi’s idol love scandal)
Coming.
Ah! Why are you here, Ms. Hua?
I’ve brought you fans’ letters.
Let me get you some water.
Look. So many letters.
So many letters?
The semester begins tomorrow.
Are you prepared?
Yes, I am.
Ms. Hua. Take a look at this letter.
This fan wrote,
dear Jingxi,
since fans call themselves watermelons,
whenever I eat watermelon,
I feel I’m eating another one
of your fans.
So to live up to their sacrifice,
I invented various ways to
eat watermelons.
Watermelon sashimi. Watermelon broth.
Watermelon salad.
These show my fans’ love for me.
I need to reply to all of them.
Why don’t we host an event
to express your gratitude?
Don’t rush to disagree.
Look.
This incident changed
so many people’s views about you.
At this point,
your attitude is important.
Let’s host a return banquet to
show the fans that you care about them.
But isn’t it better if
I reply to their letters personally?
Besides,
throwing a return banquet now
may make people feel that
I’m taking advantage of the event
to gain attention and advertise myself.
I don’t like it.
Well.
You have good intentions,
while my eyes are on money.
All I want is to help you gain more fans
and get more popular.
Ms. Hua.
I know you only want what’s good for me.
But after this incident,
I start to realize that
I’m not worthy of their affection.
My fans support me unreservedly.
I should work harder too.
Yuan.
Ning Zeyu.
Li He.
They are all pursuing their dreams.
So, I think...
Me.
The popular idol, Ye Jingxi
will study from today on.
I’ll prepare for College Entrance Exam.
And I’ll prepare for
the music major’s test.
I’ll get into
Haixing Conservatory of Music
and become a professional music producer
to repay their affection.
Actually,
you can consider
studying abroad.
Haixing Conservatory of Music
is a good school.
But its courses are more about
classic music theories.
I don’t think
that’s the right school for you.
Look.
This is the school I asked them
to investigate.
Austria Lakeside Music School.
I think this is the right school for you
considering all the factors.
Ms. Hua.
I know.
You don’t want to part
with your friends.
But, Jingxi.
Like what you’ve just said,
your friends are all
fighting for their dreams.
They should be your source of power.
I wish you can make the decision
after you’ve thought about it carefully.
In this case, you won’t have regrets.
Fine.
Think about it first.
-Okay.
-I’ll go for now.
Let me walk you out.
Ms. Hua, bye.
Take care.
You wish to be a better self
for your friends and fans.
Then, you must aspire higher.
Find the career that’s suitable for you.
Real friendships
won’t be defeated by time and distance.
Yuan.
You’ve already made the decision, right?
Caixi.
Soy milk and deep-fried dough,
or milk and bread?
This.
You always choose milk and bread, right?
I’ve had too much of it.
I want a change of flavor.
Women.
You’re so capricious.
You need new spirits
in the new semester.
Boys, straighten up!
Lin Qiang.
You didn’t do well in chemistry
last semester.
You’re also responsibly for
my chemistry performance?
I’m in charge of all your subjects
before your graduation.
Okay, Mr. Ma.
Hello.
Okay. Great.
Come on.
Yuan Haoxi.
Have you finished your homework?
I made one copy for you.
Really?
Thanks.
You’re such a nice girl.
Don’t you have hands yourself?
Miss.
Please let him do his own tests.
Go back to class.
What’s going on?
What are you doing?
Yuan Haoxi.
Are you free this weekend?
Let’s go for a movie.
-Of course.
-No. He’s not available.
It’s Grade 2 now.
Go back to class.
Okay.
What’s your problem?
Yuan Haoxi, what’s your problem?
You’re in Grade 2.
You’ll be in Grade 3 next year.
You don’t know it yourself?
No food in class.
Don’t play with your phones.
Listen to classes attentively!
Do you get it?
I’m not in Grade 3 yet.
That’s the same.
So odd.
Hello, Jingxi.
Hello.
It’s been a winter vocation.
But you’re still so handsome.
You still have so many fans.
No wonder he’s my idol.
Do you know that
I wrote an anonymous fan letter?
Anonymous?
Yes, I get to see Jingxi every day.
If he knows it’s me, it’ll be awkward.
Wow, Han Yayi,
does Lin Chuan know what you did?
-He can only know from you.
-Caixi.
-Good morning.
-Yuan.
Caixi, now’s the new semester.
I’ll be No.1 again.
I won’t let that happen.
Can we have a better chat
at the beginning of the semester?
Caixi, in this new semester,
I’ll protect you.
Yuan.
Yes.
Nothing. It’s just great
to see you again.
We see each other every day.
Can you let me copy
your math homework?
I have English homework.
Do you want that?
Ah. Give me your English homework.
I can lend it to you.
But you have to promise me.
You’ll never copy my homework again.
Chuan, you’re so mean.
I’ll tell Han Yayi that you like her.
Dare you threaten me!
Here. Take it.
Just my homework.
How dare you
tell Han Yayi!
You had a better one than me.
My mom hired a tutor for me.
I had five hours’ classes every day.
Where have you been
in the winter vocation?
My mom and dad took me to Heihujiang.
That’s the first time I saw snow.
Zeyu.
Have you done your English homework?
I want to check my answer with you.
I don’t have to do that.
Good morning.
Stand up.
-Good morning, teacher.
Sit down please.
Today is the first day of this semester.
I have something to tell you.
Pan Hao has transferred
to another school.
I won’t elaborate on the reasons.
But I have to warn you.
There is less than half of a year left
before the college entrance exam.
Your future is a new start
that’s full of hope.
It’s also a start of hard work.
The next few months are very important.
So I wish you can put
aside the things that
aren’t related
to the college entrance exam.
These few months pass by so quickly.
Let’s all bite the bullet and work hard.
Okay?
Yes.
Let’s open the book.
Page 49.
Read the poem with me.
(Class 2, Grade 3)
You’re looking for me?
Another gossip?
Someone tipped you off again?
They’re investigating my identity again?
No.
This incident is over now.
Stop thinking about all day.
It’s fine.
Why are you being so mysterious then?
Yuan.
I have a question for you.
Answer it truthfully.
Listen.
If you have the chance to go abroad now,
will you go?
Go abroad?
I’ve never thought about it.
Besides, I’ll have college entrance exam
next semester.
I don’t want to go.
If you can study abroad?
Study abroad?
That’s even less possible.
You know that my family situation
won’t allow that.
Besides, I’d be worried if I leave
my mom and brother behind.
If you can set those aside?
If you don’t have to think about others?
Just ask yourself.
Do you want to go?
I’ve never thought about that.
Then think carefully.
Tell me when you’ve made the decision.
Wow.
Wait a second.
Why are you being so weird today?
If you don’t know where to go,
you can check on the European schools.
There are many good
finance colleges in Europe.
You can do some research.
Think about it.
Europe?
The fifteenth Haiwen
Junior Championships.
I don’t have to reiterate
the importance of this match, right?
This is city level competitions.
The preliminaries will be hosted
next week.
If you have good performance,
get into the final, and get into top 3,
you can apply for
national second level athlete.
Yes.
If you become
national second level athlete,
you can apply for the test
of high level athletes.
Are you prepared?
Chief is surely ready!
He’s been in so many competitions.
This is just a piece of cake.
This will decide whether
Chief can be qualified as
national second level athlete.
This isn’t just an average test.
I’m asking you, Li He.
Are you confident?
I...
Who am I?
I’m Li He.
I’m the race champion of
the city-level competition.
I can do it.
This kid.
He’s even boasting himself
before we start to.
Don’t worry about him.
I’ll work hard.
If you have the chance to go abroad now,
will you go?
Go abroad?
Where?
Come down, Yuan Caixi.
Wait a second.
Slow down.
Li He, where are you taking me to?
Hurry!
I’m warning you.
If you keep on doing this,
you’ll smash my windows one day.
No, I won’t.
Stand still.
Wait.
What are you doing?
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
How’s it?
This is for you.
Eat it before it gets cold.
What’s this?
The sticky rice balls my dad made.
I guess you’d like it too.
You came here just to give me this.
No.
I’m also here to see you.
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
You just saw me.
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
Today’s
weather is so good.
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know♪
Oh. Li He, I have a question for you.
Listen.
Where do you want to go to the most
if you have the chance to go abroad?
Jinling.
First, my question
is about going abroad.
Second, why the city of Jinling?
Our country’s Olympic champion
Wan Yunxia is from Jinling.
If you ask about going abroad,
I want to visit Ethiopia.
Why?
Which race champion is from Africa?
Kenmerick.
You’re indeed crazy about running.
Yes.
When I’m running,
I feel I’m free.
I just want to know how far
my legs can take me to.
Oh.
Yuan Caixi.
Can you run with me?
But I can’t run fast.
I can carry you on my back
as long as you’re willing
to run with me,
as long as I can still run.
I’ll never leave you behind.
♪Achoo I sneezed twice♪
♪I might have an allergy
because of the change of season♪
What are you doing?
♪Please listen♪
Where are you going?
Don’t mind me.
Let me open it myself.
Aren’t you going to try it?
Let me try it myself.
Let me open it for you, then.
No need.
Hurry up.
My dad is really good at cooking.
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
I’m not that strict.
Do you really think
I’m so strict with you?
I’m not that strict.
Caixi.
Mom.
You’re willing to come back?
Am I talking to you?
What are you looking at?
Mrs. Yuan is talking about
her sweet honeymoon story with Mr. Yuan.
Oh my god.
This photo must be over 20 years old.
This is from 18 years ago.
This is my favorite one.
We just got married at that time.
Now I look back on that time.
We were so poor back then.
I originally told him that
we could just have a trip in China.
But you dad just didn’t agree.
He insisted on taking me
to another country.
I was really so worried.
We really racked our brains.
Finally,
we decided to go to Thailand.
Why?
Well.
It was so cheap.
We spent five days in Thailand.
We spent too much time
in the swimming pool.
But we still didn’t wanna leave.
We just enjoyed food every day.
We had fun.
We wandered around.
It was such an amazing experience.
I was so happy.
Why didn’t we get married earlier?
Mom.
Do you want to visit Thailand again?
No.
Why?
Because I’ve already seen
the best views.
Jingxi.
Why are you here?
Are you working overtime?
Yes.
Thank you.
Jingxi,
you’re here just to give me
the midnight snacks?
Ms. Hua told me about
the return banquet for fans.
I know you refused it.
I’ve decided to host it.
Why do you suddenly change your opinion?
You’ll know when you see it.
I’ve made the decision.
I’ll take my chance.
Ah?
I’ll go now.
You’ll leave now?
Jingxi.
I don’t understand any of it.
(File)
(Jingxi, our beloved idol)
(Jingxi, our beloved idol
Concert The Crazy Night)
Ms. Hua found me
the best school in Europe.
I’ll study abroad soon.
Before I go,
I want to take the leap of faith
for myself.
I’ll host the return banquet.
And I’ll take this chance to tell Yuan
the words from the depth of my heart.
(Bawan)
Jingxi, I get it. But honestly,
I’m 99 percent sure that you’ll fail.
(Ye Jingxi)
There’s one percent chance then.
Jingxi,
why do you become a fool
when it’s about Yuan Caixi?
I was just comforting you when
I said you have one percent chance.
Jingxi, think it through.
Don’t cry by then.
Maybe,
I just want to give myself
a reason to give up.
Did you do the second question
of the test?
Han Yayi.
You’re playing on your phone already?
Take it. Finish it soon.
What’s it?
My idol, Jingxi will host
a return banquet soon.
I told you not to call him your idol.
Jingxi, our beloved idol.
Ye Jingxi 2020 concert.
Well done.
It looks so well-designed.
(Jingxi, our beloved idol
Concert 2020 The Crazy Night)
How’s it?
You’ve all received it?
Yes.
How could we miss it
when you’ve reminded us all?
But, Bear,
the first mock test will come soon.
Can we...?
No.
It must be now.
Why now?
Why can it be a week later?
Why in such a hurry?
Why?
Because my fans miss me.
If I keep them waiting any longer,
they’d go mad.
Your fans can’t wait?
Do your fans know that
you’re so conceited?
Yuan.
You must come.
But, Bear,
the time I spent before
the first mock test...
Yuan Caixi.
Promise me.
You must come.
Okay.
Since you’re calling me by my full name,
I must come then.
Yuan Caixi?
This isn’t right.
That’s not good enough.
Your performance is above average now.
But this can’t ensure your championship.
Don’t be upset.
If you outperform yourself,
you can be qualified as
second level athlete.
Then, I shall work harder.
Bai.
Should I...?
I must be qualified as
second level athlete.
From next week on,
no matter how tough the training is,
I can take it.
Good kid.
You didn’t let me down.
Let me do another lapse.
Go.
Mom, you didn’t go out?
Ah.
The meeting was canceled.
I’ll go out.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I promise to go to a performance
with friends.
A performance?
Yes.
Who will go with you?
There are only three months left
before college entrance exam.
You’re still thinking about a concert?
Isn’t it about the star in your class?
I’ll come back in no time.
I’ll be home in less than three hours.
No.
Mom.
Everyone in the class will go.
And he’s my good friend.
You mustn’t go.
Go back to your room and study.
After your college entrance exam,
you can do whatever you want.
I won’t stop you.
(Sent to Class 2 Grade 3’s Group Chat)
Sorry. Something came up in my family.
I can’t go to the return banquet.
Have fun.
Caixi, come on.
Hurry.
Hurry up!
Take a photo for me.
-Why? You get to see him every day.
-Hurry up.
Come on. One. Two. Three.
Take a look.
Yes. Here.
Take it vertically.
-Vertical.
-Yes.
Cool.
He’s indeed a star.
Where’s Li He?
He said he can’t come today.
Stop the chitchat. Hurry.
The performance is about to start.
Can you be less obsessed with him?
(Ye Jingxi)
My watermelons, do you miss me?
Yes.
First, I have to thank
my friends at Sen Yong,
Class 2, Grade 3.
Your accompany
gave me a joyful year in Grade 3.
And I spent the year
of my 19 years old happily.
Moreover,
I have some words
for a particular person.
When we were kids,
you thought I always protected you.
But actually,
when everyone thought
I was fat and silly and despised me,
you were the only one who was
there for me and encouraged me.
You made me confident.
You made me realize what I want.
You gave me courage
and confidence to pursue my dreams.
So,
please allow me to be willful
for the last time.
Let me fight for myself.
(The secret we know)
♪Listen the childhood whistle♪
♪Only I can decipher♪
♪Your secret code♪
♪I’m there in time to support you♪
♪Never a second late♪
♪Looking into the mirror♪
♪We’re all growing taller♪
♪Devour all the inevitable worries♪
♪And put on a smile♪
♪Fill memories with happiness♪
♪I know that you know♪
♪No matter how proud I am♪
♪As long as you give me a smile♪
♪You’ll get♪
I’m about to faint.
I will faint.
If I do, it must be because
Jingxi is too handsome.
He’s so handsome.
♪Let’s go to the island♪
♪Let’s laugh at whoever gets lost♪
♪We hurry to the cake
following its scent♪
♪Put the wishes in the flames♪
♪The burning candle witnesses our vows♪
♪Another second closer to farewell♪
♪The backpacks packed with candies♪
♪Mark the taste we had♪
♪The edge of calendar was
ripped off by hour hand♪
♪I’ll store everything secretly♪
♪I know that you know♪
♪No matter how proud I am♪
♪As long as you give me a smile♪
♪You will get a silly smile from me♪
♪You know that I know♪
♪Our hands are held tightly♪
♪Even if we go to our different islands♪
♪The tsunami yearn ties us together♪
Surprise.
Hello.
Yuan Caixi.
I’ll go all out.
♪We both know these words♪
♪But please listen carefully♪
♪You fly far and high with your eyes♪
♪I’ll be your wings to bear the storm♪
I’m here.
♪We both know these words♪
♪But I have to make a promise with you♪
♪Even if the distant future
changes its appearance♪
♪My chest is still pounding
with heart beat♪
-Jingxi.
Okay. Li He.
That’s it for today.
Fine.
Have some water.
Bai, after you.
(Chuan)
Chief! Bad news!
Ye Jingxi did something great this time.
Come to the return banquet now!
Where are you going?
I have to win her over.
(The secret we know)
You’re right.
I failed.
Let’s go, Jingxi.
She won’t come back.
Since I’ll say farewell,
I’ll definitely say it to her
face to face.
I listened to the song. It’s great.
But you’re not the Yuan
I used to know.
Yes.
I’ve grown up.
You’ve also become a super star, right?
Can we go back to the old time?
Go back?
Why should we?
We’re all heading
to the right direction.
Why should we go back?
But I miss
-I...
-Hear me out.
Ms. Hua
found me the best music school abroad.
I’m going abroad.
So, Yuan,
have you made up your mind?
Do you want to study abroad with me?
I know you’ll say no.
But I think
it’s worth trying.
There are many schools in Europe.
We can study together.
You don’t have to worry about tuition.
I can take care of that.
Besides, we can...
Bear.
Though I want to go
to a good university,
I want to earn more money,
I don’t want to leave my family.
Bear.
Let me tell you a story.
When my mom and dad got married,
they spent the honeymoon in Thailand.
So, a few days ago, I asked her
whether she wants to
visit Thailand again.
She said no.
I asked her why.
She said it’s because
she’s already seen the best views.
So what’s important isn’t where.
Rather, it’s whom I’m with.
So,
I’m not the one
that you want to be with.
Bear, you have a bright future.
Don’t forget. There are 1.4 billion
people who like you.
Of course.
But you’re forever my Brother Bear.
♪Dare not to breath♪
♪Afraid you might find out
about my heart♪
♪Fight the courage to
turn my back on you♪
♪Class notes♪
♪Filled with secrets♪
♪The figure in the corridor♪
♪I mistake them for you♪
♪Oh my dear you♪
♪This is my love letter♪
♪No words♪
♪Can express my love♪
This...
Someone is its better owner.
♪Why can’t we be together♪
♪Just you and me♪
I can’t take back
what I give away as a gift.
Bear.
If you don’t want it,
I won’t give it to others.
Why not just throw it away?
♪How can I be sure♪
Fine.
I...
I’ll go now.
Goodbye.
Bear.
♪Our sight shows the affection♪
♪45.7 is the distance of romance♪
♪The melody♪
♪Filled our memories♪
♪Oh Please let me know♪
♪Sent the text Allow me to say it♪
♪The future has you and me♪
♪I just want to say it out loud♪
♪Oh my dear you♪
♪It’s my confess letter♪
♪No words♪
♪Can express my feelings♪
♪I wish more♪
♪Closer to your heart♪
♪Why can’t we be together♪
♪Just you and me♪
Why hasn’t Yuan come out?
Where’s your chief? Did you text him?
Where’s Yuan Caixi?
Chief, you’re so late.
She’s still inside.
Chief.
Why are you all looking at me like this?
Ye Jingxi confessed. I know.
Then? How about Yuan Caixi?
Just talk to me.
Chief.
You might be late.
Jingxi just played a song for Yuan
before everyone.
It’s a song specially written for her.
She can’t resist such romance.
He just played the piano.
How can she not resist it?
-Chief.
-Li He.
-Move.
Why are you so late?
Are you all right?
How can anything happen to me?
Is the song Ye Jingxi played
for you good?
It’s great.
I can play the piano as well.
No. I just had a conversation with Bear.
He’ll go abroad soon.
He’ll study music at Austria.
What? Jingxi will go abroad?
When?
He’ll leave soon.
So that’s what happened?
I was so scared.
Chief.
Look how nervous you were.
I didn’t even see you panic like this
in your first competition.
I’ll soon see my son married.
Do you want to get beaten?
-Do you?
-No. No.
Right!
When will I eat it?
Let’s go.
I just slipped on my way here.
You messed up my hair-do.
Stop being sad. Han Yayi.
I can’t take it.
Yuan Caixi.
Yes?
Promise me one thing.
What is it?
Promise me first.
You have to tell me first.
From now on,
you mustn’t leave
without saying goodbye.
Even if you’ll leave,
you have to get my approval.
Okay. World Champion.
I won’t go anywhere.
I just want to go home and sleep.
Come on.
Yuan Caixi.
Yes?
You have to trust me.
Trust you?
What?
Trust me with everything.
You’re so bossy.
Yes, I am.
Fine. Go to bed.
I’ll leave now.
What is he thinking about?
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪