♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 8=
We won’t be called truant, will we?
We were training at night before.
We can let Mr. Bai help us.
Anyway,
we have to go back
before the second class.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
Let’s go.
I knew Zhang Ye was bragging.
How can their school hire a retired coach
of a national team?
Be quiet.
Ready.
Awesome!
Top muscle controls like this,
even Mr. Bai can’t do it, right?
Brats. What are you guys doing here?
You startled me.
Why are you here, Mr. Bai?
I come to watch their training.
-Hey. Hey.
-Come. Come.
It’s time for class.
Why haven’t they come back?
PE students have extra training.
They’ll be back soon. Just wait.
Right.
Ready.
Why are some students still absent?
Where are Li He and Lin Chuan?
Perhaps,
they skipped classes and went out.
Boys said there’d be a match today.
Did they go for the match?
How bold they are.
They dare skip evening classes.
Monitor.
Keep an eye on the class.
I’m going to deal with this.
OK. Sure.
(Bai Fei)
Mr. Bai.
The national team coach
is really something.
It gets better
once the moves are adjusted.
He’s indeed awesome.
I’ll apply to the headmaster.
See if we can invite this coach
to give us special training
for some days.
Is it OK?
We can have a try.
At worst,
I’ll give up my bonus this month.
Wow, Mr. Bai. it’s so kind of you!
(Study for mentality,
sports for physical quality)
(Li He: Go back early at evening class.
I need to talk to you.)
(See you at evening class)
Hey, hold on.
What time is it now?
The first evening class is almost over.
Go back now.
Hey.
Are you skipping classes?
Well...
It’s not skipping classes with you here.
Yes.
Go back now. Go back.
Chief, why are you running so fast?
Hurry up.
I’m back.
Hey, I’m back.
So be it. Why bother telling me?
Didn’t you say you’d tell me something
at the evening class?
Yes, but now it’s over.
It doesn’t matter.
What’s wrong with you?
Nothing. Don’t disturb me.
If you have any question on your study,
feel free to ask me.
Can you explain this question again?
I didn’t get it just now.
Oh. OK.
This is a subjunctive.
Pay attention to the personal pronouns.
It’s hard, because you need to use
correct personal pronouns.
You’ll lose points
if you make a mistake.
So, You’d better not use it.
-I choose C.
-You choose C for this?
It should be B.
You should look...
Baby. Baby.
Hey, baby!
Miss! Miss! Miss!
Miss Luo!
Can you hear me out?
What else do you want to say?
Can you not go to Mr. Ma?
I...
They skipped the whole evening class.
Won’t Mr. Ma know it
if I don’t tell him?
How will he know if you don’t tell him?
Alright.
You take me as blind.
Are all the classmates blind?
Didn’t they see it?
If you tell Mr. Ma,
what should they do?
Think about it!
If I don’t report it to Mr. Ma
and he hears a word about this,
what should I do then?
Baby.
It... It’s all my fault. My bad.
I know you’re defending them.
But you shouldn’t indulge them
and let them have their way.
But look, baby.
They didn’t go to play games.
They intended to improve their skills.
This is a good thing.
Alright.
Let me ask you something.
For sportsmen,
apart from physical fitness,
what is more important?
Discipline.
I’m going to Mr. Ma then.
Let’s go.
I’ll stay for a moment.
You go first.
Keep my paper. I won’t use it today.
OK. I’ll return it tomorrow.
What’s this?
No need to return this.
See you tomorrow.
Monitor.
What’s wrong?
Hey, you...! Hey!
What’s wrong with you today?
Where did you go at the evening class?
I went for the match.
I know our appointment,
so I came back early.
Should I say thanks to you?
No.
Just tell me what happened to you today.
Stop keeping me guessing. OK?
Yuan.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Yuan, are you angry with Li He?
Don’t ask, or my answer is no.
Why?
You prepared study materials for him,
yet he went to watch the match.
I’ve said I’m not angry.
He can go wherever he wants.
Alright. Alright. You are not angry.
Let’s go home.
Ning Zeyu.
Hey.
I was greeting to you.
Why didn’t you answer?
I’ll answer if it’s anyone else.
But I don’t want to meet you.
Right.
You don’t want to meet me.
It will be different if it’s Monitor.
Right?
You two chatted happily
at the evening class.
Yes.
We have a lot in common,
and she’s intelligent.
Of course we were happy.
I have a question.
Is Yuan Caixi angry with me?
Yes.
Why is she angry with me?
Why?
Why should I tell you?
Better use your brain.
If you still can’t figure out,
it means the monitor and you
are not the same kind.
I’m off.
Bye.
Can’t you be straightforward?
(Han Yayi)
I don’t know. I dare not say even if I do.
Please help me out of this.
I don’t want her unhappy all the time.
Caixi.
I’m coming in.
Hey.
Aren’t you doing homework?
I won’t eat.
Take it out.
Life is so amazing,
yet you’re so cranky.
You must need some vitamin.
Mom made these
specially for you.
Have some.
Let me guess.
Is it
because of Li He?
You’re idle.
Have you finished your homework?
You’re more important than homework, OK?
I seldom see you so angry.
Caixi.
What
did Li He do to you?
He made a deal with me that
he wanted to pass the monthly exam once
to show his parents
and make them happy.
I said that’d be great.
Tonight I prepared him
all the review materials.
I told him to come back early
for evening class.
Turned out that bastard
didn’t come back.
He went to watch a match.
It’s so ungrateful of him.
This is called
“the more you love,
the more you hate”.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
-What love and hatred?
-Caixi! Caixi!
-Your butt!
-Sorry! A slip of tongue!
A slip of tongue! A slip of tongue!
Caixi.
One last question for you.
Well.
Are you angry
for he didn’t study hard
or
he didn’t take
your appointment seriously?
What’s wrong with you today?
Where did you go at the evening class?
Watch the match.
I knew our appointment,
so I come back early.
Should I say thanks to you?
No.
Hello, sir.
Hey, Monitor.
Monitor.
I can’t do this question.
Can you help me?
It’s my bad that I didn’t show up
on time yesterday.
I promise it will never happen again.
Don’t make any promise.
If you really want to pass the exam,
you wouldn’t have gone for the match.
The match?
What match?
Didn’t you skip class
for the match yesterday?
No.
I went to see the training in
No. 2 Experimental Middle School.
Now you know it. Right?
I didn’t skip class to have fun.
Why did you explain it to me?
I don’t care about where you went.
So, you were angry because you thought
I forgot our appointment
and went out for fun. Right?
Do you need my help or not?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
This one. This question. Here.
Which question?
This one.
As for this question,
you should find the stem first.
The stem is...
Li He.
What?
Focus on your study.
Monitor.
I will never ever forget
our appointment again,
not even a second.
Are you pushing it?
Look at the question.
I’ll explain it only once.
As for this question,
you should solve the second one first.
Um.
Only when the second one is solved,
can you do the first one.
(Self-criticism)
What are you looking at?
I don’t know how to write.
Your pocket money will be deducted then.
Anyway, not much pocket money left
this month.
Hey.
Even Mr. Ma didn’t say anything.
Why are you punishing me?
Moreover,
I’m a grownup.
Writing a self-criticism
will be a shame to me.
Right?
Mr. Ma didn’t punish you,
because I told him
you had extra training.
That’s why PE students
have half-day classes less.
Um.
Be mature afterwards.
Don’t be like a kid, OK?
Yes.
I’m immature.
I’m not as mature as the date
your mother introduced to you,
a well-educated civil servant,
who has a car and a house. And,
he’s a local.
At the same age.
What a perfect match.
I’m a peasant.
How can I match a returnee like you?
Are you stepping on me?
Of course.
Why are you speaking ill of my mom?
Just wait. Huh?
Let’s see if that civil servant
can put up with your temper.
Bai Fei.
What?
All what you just said
was right,
but not this.
I, a returnee,
really like stepping on you,
a peasant.
What are you looking at? Keep writing.
Mr. Ma didn’t punish you.
You just need to write a self-criticism.
Are you even perfunctory on this?
We are teachers.
We should be models for students.
Yes, right.
Bai.
What are you doing?
Are you bullying Luo again?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I... I’m writing a self-criticism.
A school punishment?
What’s going on?
Nothing.
Do you need my help?
No. Go for your business.
These are the essence of the essence.
Hey, Yuan.
When you graduate,
you can sell all these
to juniors.
You will make a fortune.
OK. Let’s split it 50/50.
No. 40/60 will do.
Or 30/70.
After all, I’m just an assistant.
I can’t take too much.
Isn’t that too much?
Um.
But listen. You not only take too much,
but also talk too much.
What?
Don’t you know it?
Li He has been letting Lin Chuan ask you
about my recent things,
right?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Alright. Alright.
I’m not blaming you.
So, help Lin Chuan with his homework
in a while.
Um.
I’m off.
Yuan is indeed awesome.
Devil.
As for Chinese,
read the full text first.
Recite the paragraphs
based on the keywords.
Monitor.
It’s fine to recite.
But what about math?
These are the most basic questions
I summarized from weekly tests.
Get the easy points first.
Alright?
Hey. Wait. Wait. Wait.
We didn’t invite you here.
I know
what you are thinking very well.
We have Monitor here.
That’s enough.
Your foundation is so bad.
Do you want to tire her to death?
No way.
Monitor.
Li He seems unsatisfied
with the tutoring arrangement.
Hey.
No. No. No.
We didn’t mean that.
No.
Don’t listen to his nonsense.
Monitor.
I’ve got it.
Study is like running.
We should start with the basics.
Come on.
Easy ones first.
Put the math back.
Take Chinese out.
Shall we?
♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
I’ll do a spot check.
-Stop reciting.
-Hey.
♪Never disappointed at the failures♪
You... You... Recite this first.
♪Wind is no longer that fierce♪
Breath of the Wild is incredible.
I think of it every morning
when I wake up.
We can play together on weekends.
That’s a must.
Hey. Look. Aren’t they
Li He and his classmates?
Gosh.
Are these students
helping them with their study?
They are a bunch of bookworms.
They got Li He like this.
Exactly.
Monitor.
What’s the matter?
How was our performance today?
Quite good.
If it goes like this,
at least you’ll pass Chinese.
That’s great.
Thanks for your help.
Or else,
Chuan and I would fail again.
Listen to me.
Don’t be cocky for what you achieved.
Understand?
Rest assured.
I won’t.
I just
want to thank you for your help.
Can I treat you to dinner?
Dinner?
Yes.
I’ve had a plan.
How about barbecue?
OK.
Let’s go.
But not tonight.
Why?
I can’t solve a question.
I’ll meet Zeyu at the bookstore.
Sorry. I just made an appointment
with him.
Because I don’t know.
It’s fine.
Study is the most important thing.
We can have dinner next time.
Can we take a rain check?
Sure. Anytime.
OK.
I’m off then.
-Bye.
Who will come later?
You ask too much.
Chief, we’ll take that table.
OK. Come and have a seat.
I’ll order food.
OK. Take your time.
Feel free to order if you need more.
Hello.
Have you bought it?
Come here quickly.
I’m waiting for the goods.
I’m on my way.
Um. Um. Um.
Sorry, Zeyu.
The class is over,
but I take up your time now.
It’s fine.
I don’t want to go home anyway.
I’m kidding. You’re so gullible.
Why don’t you
spend the time on these questions?
I’m in a hurry to go home.
Oh, right.
Take this.
(Strawberry milk)
Drink it when you are thirsty.
Ah?
Thanks.
This question.
How is it?
Is he coming?
He won’t come.
He won’t?
What’s going on?
He can’t come.
Where is Xiang?
I’m coming.
Strawberry milk.
Am I late?
Hey.
Don’t we have a guest?
She and I are not the same kind.
You’re right.
Don’t you contradict me?
It should be correct.
Take a look. Is it correct?
Let me see.
It’s correct.
Wow. Your method works so well.
Crap. Now that you’ve learnt my method,
what if you surpass me?
I’ll soon surpass you.
Don’t worry.
Hey.
Even your attitude changed
after you learnt it.
You bet.
But seriously,
I’ll definitely surpass you,
fair and square.
Fair and square
Um.
That said,
since you want to surpass me,
why do you help Li He with his review?
Actually, I can quite understand him.
For a PE student,
the study result isn’t that important.
But I can understand him that
he wants to do well once
to make his parents happy.
Because I was alike before.
So, I want to help him.
Is that the only reason?
Yes.
No, not exactly.
Actually,
it’s because they helped us once
at the relay race.
Now I returned his favor.
We are even now.
Well.
Are you free after the exam?
I suppose so.
There’ll be a lecture after the exam.
Would you join me?
We can decide by then.
If I don’t do well in the exam,
I won’t want to go to the lecture
with my rival.
Alright.
It’s your call. Let’s decide by then.
OK.
Just because you are not the same kind,
she has something you don’t,
while you have something she doesn’t.
So,
you should find out what you have
but she doesn’t.
This way,
you can get closer to her quickly.
You can complement each other.
More importantly,
don’t be too active.
You should play hard-to-get.
That makes sense.
I can’t believe it.
You’re an expert, huh?
Being smart
is too lonesome.
You just deserve some punches.
Just take my advice
and play hard-to-get.
Hey. Morning.
You come early today.
Um.
Do you have any questions
in your homework?
You can ask me.
Not bad. I don’t have many questions.
I didn’t mean it yesterday.
It’s fine.
By the way...
Yes?
What’s wrong?
What’s the matter?
Oh, forget it.
Nothing.
Jiang Yuan.
This question...
Are you still playing your phone
even now?
I’m not. I’m waiting for a message.
What message?
Some good news anyway
which can help Chief’s urgency.
Don’t make any trouble.
I’m not making any trouble.
Didn’t you see Chief was so worried
yesterday
for the exam?
I can help him out.
Wait and see.
Mr. Bai will be late for something.
I’ll lead you
to warm up first.
Attention, everyone.
Separate for a distance.
Align the lines and rows.
OK. Hands down.
Listen to my command.
Ready.
Go.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two. Two. Three.
Yuan Caixi.
Yes?
What are you doing?
I didn’t catch up just now.
You know you didn’t?
Come on.
Do the chest expansion exercise.
-Aren’t you a genius?
-What’s wrong with you today?
What do you mean by that?
Why are you picking on Monitor?
What did I do to her?
I have high requirements
on every classmate.
Come on.
Do the chest expansion exercise.
You can give a demonstration.
Why me?
Ning Zeyu. Step forward.
Show us the chest expansion exercise.
Stop clapping!
Ready.
Go.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
Listen.
Had I learnt seriously,
I’d be a top student.
Lin Chuan.
Come here.
Excuse me.
Go. Go. Go.
What’s the matter?
What’s the problem with Li He today?
He’s always been with a problem.
Li He was cold to Yuan today.
He even picked on her.
What on earth happened to him?
Are you asking this for Yuan?
How does she feel now?
How does she feel?
She feels great.
It’s very quiet.
No one is jabbering
around her.
Why do I feel she is kind of
absent-minded and anxious?
And she cares a lot about
Li He’s attitude to her.
You know little about Yuan.
There’s no one yet
who can make her dramatically emotional.
Is there anyone
who makes you feel affectionate?
I...
I mean emotional, not affectionate.
Don’t distort it.
I’m off.
Miss Han.
Please help me with my schoolwork.
I haven’t finished it yet.
Please help me with... With...
Please help me with English.
I can’t do English very well.
Miss Han.
Did Han Yayi really say that?
What she said doesn’t matter.
What matters is that she came to me.
It means Yuan Caixi has lost her poise.
She’s found out your attitude changes.
I keep ignoring her.
What if she’s really angry?
You got to the point.
Think about it.
If you keep ignoring her,
she’ll keep thinking why.
Then you can find a proper time
and appear suddenly,
showing your care to her.
Then
she’ll feel
upset but also sweet.
Oh, I see.
It’s called,
“play hard-to-get”.
“Play hard-to-get”?
According to my analysis,
this is their trick.
With the excuse
of your refusal to dinner,
they are playing hard-to-get
in order to gain your attention.
Once Li He gets enthusiastic about you,
you’ll fall for him immediately.
Fall for him?
Are they playing tricks?
What should we do then?
Play along.
Monitor.
I finished my homework.
Please help me check it.
Have you finished?
That’s good.
You haven’t checked it.
No need.
Well...
Well, what should I do next?
Do whatever you should.
What’s wrong, Li He?
Anything else?
No... Nothing.
Go back then.
Wait.
I’ll help the teacher
sort out materials.
Perhaps I can’t tutor you.
I’m off.
But... Monitor.
What should I do, Monitor?
-Monitor!
-You’ve got me
and these.
Is it necessary?
Yes, of course it is.
Chuan. Chuan.
I’m like you.
I also have high requirements
on classmates.
The same to you.
I’ll be strict with you as well.
(You received an email)
(Chemical Exam Answers
Biological Exam Answers)
(Grade 12
Class (2))
You did quite well, huh?
Through your hard work today,
you’ll surely do great
in the exam tomorrow.
You’ll be reborn.
Thank you, sir.
Not at all.
Chief.
Chief. I got it.
-What did you get?
-I got it!
-What?
-What did you get?
The monthly exam answers.
Yesterday, I asked for help
in the web forum.
Someone said
he had monthly exam answers.
Look, guys.
(Monthly Exam Answers)
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪