♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 13=
Be careful. Be careful.
Yuan?
Are you feeling better?
Thanks to you, she kept throwing up.
What do you mean thanks to me?
I didn’t know my pizza was spoiled.
Besides,
I suffered as much, all right?
Be careful next time.
Clean out your fridge
and don’t eat expired food anymore.
Do you hear him, Bawan?
I’m telling you.
Ye Jingxi.
Yes?
In fact,
Ms. Hua sent us.
Ye Jingxi.
Call me Bear.
Bear.
Mm.
Perhaps,
we were thinking too simply,
without considering the consequence.
So,
you must listen to Ms. Hua.
Do whatever she asks you to,
and don’t try to resist. Got it?
I see.
You’re now working for my company, too?
What are you talking about?
We’re serious.
At first,
I thought
you loved to snub,
simply because you were a star.
But now,
I know life isn’t easy for you, either.
Work hard. I think highly of you.
Humph.
Humph?
What?
Bed No.1, time for injection.
Oh.
I’ll get the injection.
Injection? Oh, yes. I’ll leave.
Why don’t you leave?
We’re all men. Why are you embarrassed?
We’re not your fans.
We won’t take photos of you.
Be quick. Take off your pants.
Turn around.
Nurse, give him the injection carefully.
Thank you.
He has fair skin.
Press it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well,
you have a good shape.
See? I trained him.
I don’t think he looks stronger than me.
What?
You’ve got a good shape, too?
Why not take off your clothes
and compete with him?
How do you feel now?
Any better?
Though you two
have seen
my hips,
it doesn’t mean
you can threaten me.
How do you know
we didn’t take photos of you?
How dare you!
Why don’t we dare?
Be careful.
This time...
Mm?
I’m grateful to you.
But,
as for Yuan...
I know what you mean.
All right.
I’ll get to the point, then.
I know you always stop me
from staying with Yuan alone.
Yes.
I admit that.
You’re straightforward.
I also know that
you help me with study
so that you can keep an eye on me.
Time’s limited. Get to the point.
The point is
I like Yuan Caixi.
So do I.
I’m sorry,
but I love her most.
I grew up with her.
She and I have a lot in common.
No offense,
but I carried her on my back, hugged her,
and carried her on my shoulder.
What are you doing?
When I count from three to one,
-let go of me! Do you hear me?
-You’re not convinced?
Three, two, one.
It hurts! It hurts!
What? You get cocky, huh?
I’m a patient.
I’m still lying in bed.
You’re a patient, so what?
I just got an inspection. Let go of me.
You weak men,
what do you want to do?
Fight against me?
You know what?
Even if you fight me together,
you can’t hurt me.
If you’re not convinced, hold it in!
Li He,
you must understand.
Even you hugged her,
carried her on your back and shoulder,
that was because she was poisoned, hurt
and got stuck in fire.
Don’t take that seriously.
Even if you and she
have a lot in common,
she and I have common memories, too.
Get your hands off me!
You’re both unconvinced, right?
How can you two
make her feel safe?
Ah?
If you’re unconvinced,
compete with me like a man does.
Okay.
Come on.
Come on. I must compete with you today.
Get off the bed.
Show me what you can do.
Childish boys.
Stand there.
What shall we compete?
Arm wrestling.
-Come on.
Wait.
Finished?
We’re worried about you.
Jingxi, have a good rest
and get well soon.
We can’t do without you.
Yes, yes.
It’s okay. It’s okay.
-Are you alright now?
-Yes.
Drink more hot water.
Why is he standing already?
I’m going back tomorrow.
-So early? Don’t be in a hurry.
-Not early.
All right, you two.
Let him have some rest.
We should leave now.
-You’re right.
-Yes.
Be quick. Have some rest.
Lie down in bed.
Have some rest.
Be gentle. Be gentle.
Don’t catch a cold again.
-You finally get better.
-Tuck the quilt.
Remember to drink more hot water.
Get your face in, too.
-We’ll wait for you.
-Bye-bye.
-Have some good rest.
-He knows. Don’t worry.
I haven’t finished yet.
Bye-bye, Yuan.
Looks like Ms. Hua worries
for a right reason.
We should consider the consequence.
Yeah.
Let’s get back home first.
Li He,
what’s bothering your little mind?
I’m thinking that
Ms. Hua made a sense today.
Ye Jingxi is nearly of our age,
but he has to bear so much.
Come on.
Whose little mind do you mean?
Ye Jingxi is nearly of our age,
but he’s decided his future long ago.
When he does what he wants,
he has to bear a lot.
You’re right.
What about you?
Do your parents know
you like programming?
Even if they do, they won’t support me.
What’re you going to do, then?
No idea.
If only I could do what I want
like you and Ye Jingxi do!
If someone were as smart as you,
he could do everything.
But I’m confused.
Why do your parents force you
to be a lawyer?
Thanks for the compliment, Li He.
My parents always want me
to live my life as they have planned.
No deviation is allowed.
Don’t bother about me.
Let’s talk about you.
Running is good.
What’s your plan for the future?
I made a deal
with Lin Chuan and other teammates that
we’ll keep running
in Haiwen Sport University.
Haiwen Sport University?
Yep.
You’re doing better in study now.
You can have better choices, can’t you?
I don’t care
which university I’ll study in
as long as I can keep running.
You should at least
have a plan for running.
Don’t you want to study
in a better university?
Come on.
Do all good students like you
talk like that?
Monitor said something similar.
Maybe she and I think alike.
No way.
She cares about me.
It’s none of your business.
Then you should think
more carefully about it.
Don’t let her down.
Don’t worry.
I’ll think carefully about it.
You’d better care more about yourself.
Why are you coming back so late?
Oh.
I’m back late for some reason.
Mom, what’re you doing in my room?
I’m folding your clothes.
Were you going through my stuff?
I wasn’t.
I had planned to clean your desk.
What are you talking about?
By the way,
today is Sunday.
Where have you been,
instead of studying at home?
I...
I was with friends.
Friends?
Why are you wasting your time with friends
at such a critical moment?
Are you getting close to Li He lately?
He’s a PE student.
It’s okay
if he doesn’t do well in study.
But you’re different.
It’s not true.
He’s studying very hard, too.
How dare you talk back!
This is a very critical moment for you.
You can’t even waste one single second.
But you keep playing around every day.
Can you bear with the consequence?
I can.
I take responsibility for myself.
You!
How can you take responsibility?
How can you do that as a student?
Do you know what you’re talking about?
I do.
Zeyu, don’t always
get close to PE students
in case they mislead you.
Do you hear me?
What a boy!
(English paper)
(English paper, Ning Zeyu)
(Introduction to C Programming)
(Collection of Physics
for the College Entrance Examination)
(Simple Demonstration of C Programming)
(Class 2, Grade 3)
You’re looking at the notice
for parents’ meeting
and the application form.
Discuss with your families
about how to fill the form,
though it’s only for reference.
You can take the chance
to talk with your parents
about your development
after graduation.
Class’s over.
(Application Form for Universities)
Yuan,
how I envy you!
You’re good enough to be admitted
to Beikai University, right?
Don’t make fun of me.
What about you?
Which university do you want to go?
In fact,
I want to go to Zhongzhen.
Zhongzhen?
Zhongzhen University?
Yes.
Its Chinese Department is newly founded,
with new teachers
and teaching philosophies.
Mostly importantly,
it has the Creative Writing Course.
I really want to go.
It suits you.
You’re going to Zhongzhen?
That’s too far.
I’m not even going to leave Haiwen.
Chief,
what about you?
We made a deal
to go to Haiwen Sport University, right?
I’ve filled my form.
Chief?
What?
Haiwen Sport University.
Oh, Haiwen Sport University.
Chief,
don’t tell me you changed your mind?
We made a deal three years ago.
We planned to go there
as early as we were in Grade 10.
You’ll be disloyal
if you change your mind now.
No. You’re thinking too much.
I was just lost in thought. Be seated.
I’ll fill the form.
Something’s just on my mind.
(Application Form for Universities)
The air is so fresh.
What?
Want to be taken photos of
without makeup?
Get in the car, Jingxi.
Get in the car, Ms. Hua.
Surprise!
Isn’t it a surprise, super star?
This isn’t a surprise, but a shock.
We knew you left hospital today.
Then we asked Bawan for the key.
We came earlier
to prepare a surprise for you.
You haven’t seen us these days.
We’ve been worrying about you.
You have?
Yes.
You worried about me?
I... I certainly did.
How do you feel now? Any better?
Are you alright now?
-Li He.
-Don’t. Don’t.
I’m very well.
But you’ll hurt me again.
You were away lately.
In case you fall behind in study,
I’ve sorted out the papers,
homework and note for you.
Aren’t you moved?
I’m so moved.
It’s really my honor
to have good friends like you.
You’re welcome.
And this.
Miss Luo asked me to bring this to you.
You must hand it in next week.
Application form?
Yep.
Well,
you’ll go to Beijing Academy of Drama
or The Central Film Academy, right?
I want to study music, in fact.
Music?
Which university?
I haven’t decided yet.
Yuan, which university
do you want to go?
The Finance Department
of Beikai University.
There’ll be no problem.
You have such good marks.
You’ll easily be admitted.
There’s no problem
with Beikai University.
But it’ll be hard
if I want to go to Huatsing University
or Yanbei University.
But Zeyu is different.
Zeyu, which one do you want to go?
I haven’t decided yet.
But either will do.
It depends on my feeling.
Your feeling?
You think you can pick a university
like picking vegetables?
It’s not very different to me.
You know, I have quite high scores.
All right.
Don’t bother about others.
You make people worry most.
Which university do you want to go?
Why do you worry about me?
I’m special in PE.
I’ve made stable progress in study.
I can go to many universities.
Which one do you like best?
I’ll think carefully about it.
Don’t worry, monitor.
It’s the afternoon.
The audition should have been finished.
Why hasn’t Ye Jingxi texted us yet?
Bear?
How was the audition going?
Smoothly.
The director said
I looked like a swimmer.
Casting directors
were also satisfied with me.
You mean you passed the audition?
No.
Don’t pull a long face.
That’s normal.
Many actors compete for one role.
But we worked hard for a long time.
Others worked hard, too.
Besides,
if I feel sad
every time I fail an audition,
how can I live my life?
It doesn’t matter.
That’s fine.
The final exam is coming.
Review your lessons carefully.
Yes.
I think so, too.
So,
Yuan.
Mm?
Keep helping me with my study, okay?
Me?
Yes.
I’ll help you, too.
So will I.
Yes.
We’ve made a deal.
Stand up. Let me talk to him.
We’ve set up a study group,
simply to study hard.
Mm.
Is that so?
-Yes.
Good.
Now you have a high awareness.
Jingxi, Ms. Hua is coming.
She’s very angry, I think.
Ms. Hua, coming to visit me so late?
I really appreciate that.
Ms. Hua,
shall I wait for you in the car?
Stay here.
You should also listen to
what I’m going to say.
Artist
is an occupation.
There’re rules for every occupation.
In the film audition,
you deliberately behaved bad
so that you disappointed
the casting directors.
Have you thought of
what consequences
may be?
Don’t stare at him.
You think I know no one
in the film company?
You don’t care if the audition video
will be exposed
or if your future will be influenced.
You neglected your duty
as an artist.
Do you know how senior actors
became successful?
They’re devoted to work,
and responsible.
What about you?
Ask yourself.
Have you fulfilled your duty?
I can’t fulfill that.
You always ask me to act in films.
I know you want to study
in a conservatory of music!
But have you studied hard?
Do you think you’re different
from ordinary students,
you have privilege
and you can pick any university,
because you’re a little famous in China
and everyone in the company
flatters you?
You’re young,
but impetuous!
A little reputation makes you arrogant!
You want to study music?
Okay.
But you should study hard first
and pass the entrance examination
with your own strength.
Now that you don’t want to be an actor,
you should make clear
what else you want to be
and how you can be it!
(Minimum Score for all majors
of Haixing Conservatory of Music)
(Ms. Hua)
Ms. Hua,
I understand what you said.
I was too childish.
Please get me
a professional music teacher.
I’ll study hard.
Monitor,
collect the application forms
and send them to my office.
-All right.
-Class’s over.
Yuan,
I have something to tell you.
What?
Let’s talk out of the classroom.
All right.
You two.
Why do you always follow us around?
Don’t talk nonsense.
Why are you taking her out so seriously?
From tomorrow on,
I’ll ask for a two-week leave.
Two weeks?
So long? What are you going to do?
Yeah.
My company has arranged
professional music training for me.
I must go.
What did I say?
You’re not talented in acting!
You’d better work hard on music.
Just... just kidding.
Last night, Ms. Hua said a lot to me.
I have to admit that she’s right.
So,
I can no longer idle away my time.
I must chase my music dream carefully.
What about school work?
Have you asked for a leave?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Don’t worry about school work.
We’ll leave notes to you.
Thanks.
All right.
That’s all?
Let’s go for lunch.
Come on.
Study hard.
Bai.
What?
Come on.
Let me show you a photo of a girl.
What photo?
My family introduced her to me
last month.
Beautiful, isn’t she?
Looks good.
She has fair skin,
and big eyes.
And she’s tall.
She’s my cup of tea.
We make a perfect couple.
Shall I introduce you a girl, too?
-Me?
-Yes.
Don’t bother. I’m doing alright.
No.
You’re no longer young.
You need a girlfriend.
You should consider about that.
No. No, I don’t.
You know that.
It’s been long
since you last had a girlfriend.
If I didn’t know you,
I would think
you have problems with love.
Who has problems? Who?
-Kidding. Just kidding.
-I don’t need a girlfriend.
Come on.
This is my girlfriend’s best friend.
Beautiful, isn’t she?
Looks good.
How come?
Ridiculous!
-Ridiculous?
-Oops.
I said no, no, no!
Bai Fei!
Come over.
I said no, didn’t I?
Ridiculous, isn’t he?
What happened?
Li He,
do you really know how to fill the form?
I do. I’m not illiterate.
Be serious. Don’t try to fool me.
Ning Zeyu,
do you know how important
the application form is?
I do.
It’s a starting point.
After filling it,
we’ll work towards it
and study hard
so as to achieve our application.
All right.
Let me ask you again.
(Information Engineering,
Tiangong University of Science and Technology)
You filled this form
by yourself?
Yes.
I’m serious. I filled it carefully.
-So, you really want to...
Tiangong.
Huatsing.
Zeyu,
I know
you’ve been an obedient boy.
But you have a mind of your own.
At your age,
you have the mind to rebel.
I can understand.
But you shouldn’t give vent on
by ruining your future.
I don’t want to rebel.
I really want to go to Tiangong University
of Science and Technology.
You chose that,
instead of Huatsing and Yanbei.
Do you families know?
Not yet.
But I will communicate with them.
-Zeyu.
-Miss Luo,
I really want to learn programming.
Tiangong University is
China’s best university
for programming.
In term of programming,
I think it’s as good
as Huatsing and Yanbei.
I also don’t think
following my parents’ decision
can be the only right choice.
You also said,
do what you have to do,
till you can do what you want to do.
This is my application form.
I hope I can apply personally.
Huatsing!
Li He,
I know you’re always confident
for no reason.
There is a fine line
between confidence
and excessive confidence.
Bai, that sounds absurd.
Others look down on me.
You also do?
I don’t mean that.
I...
I just want to tell you that
it’s good to be ambitious.
But there’s a gap
between ambition and reality.
There’s only one term
before the college entrance examination.
How can you be admitted to Huatsing
with existing scores?
Why can’t I? I checked it.
I can be a high-level athlete
for Huatsing.
It’s hard to be admitted to Huatsing.
But a high-level athlete
doesn’t need a score
as high as academic students.
I can have a try.
It’s not that problem.
Yes.
Huatsing has preferential policies
for outstanding PE students.
But your score isn’t good enough.
Do you know
if you fill the application improperly,
you might be admitted to no university?
Bai,
don’t worry.
I’ll study hard
and I will succeed.
Why do you think so?
Monitor.
Enjoy the drumsticks.
I won’t. They’re poisonous.
Why are they?
I just bought them.
Ah.
What trick are you trying to use?
No trick.
Yuan,
could you be my private tutor again?
For what subjects?
Chinese, Math, English,
Physics and Chemistry.
Help me with whatever
I don’t do well in.
Anytime and anywhere.
Are you trying to make trouble again?
Listen. Let go of Mr. Ma.
It’s really hard for him.
I’m not trying to make trouble.
I’m serious.
I want to study hard.
Study hard?
That’s what you said last time.
What?
I want to go to Huatsing University.
Li He,
stop joking, all right?
It doesn’t sound funny at all.
I’m not joking.
I want to be a high-level athlete
and go to Huatsing University.
High-level athlete?
What’s that?
A high-level athlete is the best
among PE students.
He has to do well in sports,
but his score
for the college entrance examination
must also be above 65%
of the second batch.
A high-level athlete can be admitted
to a comprehensive university,
more than a sport university.
So,
to go to Huatsing University,
I must become a high-level athlete.
Do you understand?
Good, Li He.
World champion.
The future...
All right. The future world champion,
I’m waiting to get your autograph.
No problem.
How many seconds?
Good job.
You’ve made so much progress.
It’s no big deal.
Have some water.
Thank you, Chief.
Yun Xiang.
Well done.
Oh, Lin Chuan,
I don’t think
I’ll go to Haiwen Sport University.
What?
I want to apply for Huatsing University.
Are you serious?
I didn’t care
which university I would go
as long as we could run together.
But this time,
I want to see how far I can go.
All right.
It doesn’t matter.
It’s your own decision, anyway.
Don’t say that, Chuan.
I never forget what we promised.
We can apply for it together.
Let’s work hard
towards the biggest ambition.
Stop explaining.
If you can be admitted
to Huatsing University,
you’ll be the pride
of Sen Yong Sport Team.
I’ll be proud of you, too.
Chuan,
you can also apply for Huatsing.
You study the best
-among us four.
-I’m not going.
Why don’t you go?
You also do the best in sports.
I think you know
why I must go to Haiwen Sport University.
Wish you success!
Chief,
it’s a good thing
when you want to apply for Huatsing.
We all support you.
But,
you know what we can do.
We may not even pass the sports exam,
not to mention
the college entrance examination.
Chief, we’re not going to the tutorial.
See you at the training, Chief.
You’re back?
Mm.
I’ve got the material ready.
You come back alone?
Yeah.
It doesn’t matter, monitor.
Let’s get started.
Can I not do math problems today?
All right.
Let’s start from Chinese first.
♪The distance between us
Changes all the time♪
♪Just like the last dessert
Making me want more♪
♪I don’t dare to breathe anymore
In case you feel my heart♪
♪Turn my back to you with courage♪
♪The attraction of sight proves♪
Lin Chuan, shall we...
♪The melody of the song
Fills our memories♪
♪The note of the class
Is filled with secrets♪
Boys also bicker?
We’re not bickering.
No?
Then why are you here alone?
I thought PE students like you
are more open-minded.
Turns out you’re not different from us.
♪The problem between us
Can be solved by no formula♪
Why don’t you buy me dinner?
After helping you for a long time,
I’m starving.
♪How I wish time would stop right here♪
♪Get stuck in sweet silence♪
There you are.
How many of you?
Three.
How about that table?
But we always take this table.
It’s a table of six, you know.
But only three of you...
AC is over there.
Come on.
Make your order and then tell me.
Here.
Be seated, please. I’ll be quick.
Sir.
Come on.
All right. Be right there.
When the dishes come, eat more.
What do you mean?
Just get to the point.
Don’t beat about the bush.
You don’t say it, huh?
Yun Xiang, you say it.
We just want you
to communicate with Chief.
Why must you bicker?
Who bickers with him?
What can I communicate?
If you don’t communicate,
Jiang Yuan and I
will be too embarrassed.
Yeah.
We can’t even have the big table
for barbecue.
Yeah. He’s right.
Go get a table.
I’ll go wash my hands first.
All right.
Go ahead.
Chief?
Chuan.
I’m full.
Are you not going to talk to me anymore?
I’m fully full.
I know changing my application
has upset you.
But it doesn’t mean
I don’t care about you.
I want us to be better.
All right.
I feel happy for you
when you have a higher goal.
I support you.
Isn’t that enough?
If you really supported me,
you wouldn’t behave like this.
I never mean to leave you alone.
We can go there together.
Why must I go with you?
Let alone whether I can be admitted
to Huatsing.
Even if I could,
it’s too far away from my home.
Can I really go?
Li He,
can you be better
simply because you want?
Sir, the bill, please!
Chief, I’ll go persuade him.
Lin Chuan?
Jiang Yuan.
See you later.
Take your seat.
Sir,
take the order, please.
What would you like to eat?
So, what did you quarrel for?
Nothing.
It’s boys’ problem.
Girls won’t understand.
You have serious sexual discrimination.
I don’t.
I mean...
I can’t understand before you explain.
I don’t understand the feelings
between you and your teammates, either.
I just want to listen to your worries.
We fell out because of the application.
I want to go to Huatsing.
I wonder if I’ve made a wrong decision.
Huatsing is one of the best universities
throughout China.
When you told me about your application,
I felt surprised and incredible.
But when you want to go
to China’s best university,
you’ve done nothing wrong.
No.
I’m not worried because I may fail.
It’s not the problem
with Huatsing, either.
I just broke my promise.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪