♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 1=
Sen Yong High School has been
ranked among the top three
(North Campus South Campus)
key high schools in Haiwen.
It has two campuses.
The South Campus focuses on sports
and the North Campus focuses on
academic subjects.
Each campus has its own strengths.
(North Campus South Campus)
But...
Where are you sweeping it to?
There is too much rubbish
in the South Campus.
There is more rubbish
in the North Campus.
You are quite uneducated.
-How dare you say that about me!
-I just did!
Say it again.
The students in the North Campus
have good grades
and the admission rate is much higher.
The PE students
are physically strong
and they fight hard on the sports field.
One of the lions has to leave the den.
Therefore,
students in the North Campus
have always looked down on
those simple-minded PE students.
The PE students also regard
academic students as learning machines
and teacher’s puppets.
The two parties are at loggerheads.
It won’t be that serious, Han Yayi.
Caixi just went to get the handbooks
at the South Campus.
What can they do?
Huang Yuan, there is
something you don’t know.
She’d better pray not to meet
the monster and his sidekicks.
-It’s said that a student in the South Campus,
-No.
Li He, is arrogant and domineering.
-Those who stood against him
-Really.
-never ended well.
-I really can’t.
But why is Li He so wild?
Although Li He
has been mischievous,
after he got enrolled,
the South Campus of Sen Yong
got rid of its shameful record.
He also brought glory to
the school many times.
The teachers can do nothing about him.
In the past few years,
Li He has won numerous awards.
He is having the time of his life.
He broke the situation of
the strong North and
the weak South by himself.
Well, can Caixi
handle it?
Zeyu.
Where are you going?
The bell is about to ring.
Don’t worry about him.
Even he misses the class,
the teacher won’t say anything.
He can score the highest
with his eyes closed.
(South Campus of Sen Yong High School)
(Class 7 Grade 2)
Come on. Come on. Try harder.
Hi.
I’m here to collect
your Quality Handbooks.
Who is that?
I don’t know.
There are twenty handbooks.
Twenty handbooks?
Aren’t there twenty-four
people in your class?
You should know
who these four people are.
Zhang Ye, hurry up.
We are all waiting for you.
Come to train.
When?
(Han Yayi)
(Li He chief of South Campus)
Yuan.
(Lin Chuan Inept Adviser)
You must be careful of
(President of the Radio Club)
these PE students.
(Jiang Yuan Grumpy Guy)
(Yun Xiang Peacemaker)
They are the hardest ones to deal with.
Come on.
If you lose again...
Thank you.
I’ve collected
all the twenty-four handbooks.
Who is she talking to?
Please let me go.
I really can’t.
You promised us.
But you haven’t finished it.
How can you break your promise?
Bro. Bro.
Why are you crying? Bro.
We just want you to play
one more game with us.
We are about to reach the Diamond level.
Yeah, handsome boy.
We’ve agreed on that.
Do the job since you took the money.
We’ve bought the comics for you.
Just help us.
But you guys are too weak.
I can’t...
I can’t make it.
How are we weak? Here.
Here are the comic books.
Let’s play a few more times.
We will win anyway.
Come on, why are you crying again?
Don’t cry. Don’t cry.
All right. Forget it.
Stop crying. Stop crying.
Chief.
Chief!
Not good.
Someone from the North Campus
came to collect the handbooks.
Aren’t the handbooks
in the radio room?
Yes, I have the key.
What?
Hold on.
The point is that the girl
said she collected
twenty-four copies.
Ah?
If she takes the handbook back
and those guys from the North Campus
write something on it,
we will be screwed if Mr. Bai sees them.
Who came from the North Campus?
A girl. She looks quite familiar.
A girl?
Yes.
Don’t they have any man?
Why did they ask a girl to come?
It should be Class 2’s turn
to write comments this time.
If I guess right, it should be
the monitor of Class 2, Yuan Caixi.
I know Yuan Caixi.
The one who gave a speech every year
when the new term began.
I haven’t finished yet. Don’t interrupt.
From the first year of high school,
Yuan Caixi has been
elected as the monitor
by the teacher and classmates.
(Monitor)
She never comes late or leaves early.
(Yuan Caixi)
She got the attendance bonus every year.
I heard
that she never participates in
anything else except study.
It’s impossible that she comes late
or leaves early.
She starts to do exercise as soon as
she enters the classroom.
I heard that she even
finished the math exercise
for the whole year in one week.
She is beautiful and clever.
Many boys are deeply attracted to her.
She never stops receiving letters.
♪Embrace the heat
It’s hotter than flames♪
♪North or south Pro or con♪
♪Blend the chemistry♪
But it’s not working on her at all.
Countless boys’ hearts
are broken by her.
That’s why
they all call her
an emotionless studying machine.
It’s scary.
Wait.
Did you just say that she is in Class 2?
Yeah.
You really scared me.
The handbooks are still here.
What?
Xiang.
You got us the wrong information.
How should you be punished?
Well?
That girl said she took the handbooks.
Girl?
What girl?
All right.
I knew that no one
would find them in such a secret place.
Now I’ve found it.
(Sen Yong Radio)
You...!
How do you know we hid them here?
The bases of PE students
include the rostrum, the equipment room
and the radio room.
The equipment room is too crowded.
Many PE students have keys.
But the radio room is different.
You are the only one
who has the key to it.
Because you are the president
of the radio club.
My only way
is to make you believe
that I get the handbooks
and you would come here
to check it on your own.
(Handbook)
Thank you.
You are very nice.
Do you think you can come
and go as you please?
Do you think you are at your home?
I think I’m at school.
I’m going back to take my class.
Please step aside.
You can leave.
Just put down the handbooks.
What if I don’t?
Then tell me
why the North Campus guys
should write the handbooks
of PE students?
Yeah.
Do they remember who we are?
I think you guys
impressed them a lot.
What do you mean?
Do you know the person
standing in front of you
is the future champion of
World Championships in Athletics,
Li He?
Open your eyes wide.
Fine.
Let me tell you.
The person standing in front of you
is a student who is going to be late
for self-study.
I don’t have time to deal with you.
My agile skill
and vigorous pace.
Her eyes
are full of appreciation for me.
Oh, my troublesome charm.
Chief, why are you hugging together?
Shut up and don’t talk nonsense.
They are not hugging.
What are you so arrogant about?
That Ning Zeyu who ranks first
in your class means nothing to me.
Not to mention the eternal number two
who can never rank first.
What does my grade
have anything to do with you?
You are the future world champion?
Let me remind you.
If one day you win the prize,
remember to change your clothes.
Otherwise, others will think
you are the world idiot champion.
(Retarded)
Caixi.
Zeyu.
Why are you here?
I’m just walking around.
Are you all right?
I’m fine. What’s wrong?
Why did you go to the radio room?
Well, I...
How do you know
that I went to the radio room?
The broadcast was turned on
and everyone in the school heard it.
Everyone heard it?
Yeah, you struck back nicely.
Let’s go.
He called her the eternal number two.
I didn’t notice that before.
Caixi!
Yuan.
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
I’m good, very good.
That’s good.
Can you lend me a pencil...
between 1B and 3B?
Okay.
Thank you.
Why did you trip her?
Ah?
You start to bully girls now?
Chief.
I was just angry.
Look at the way
she doesn’t take us seriously.
Besides,
you saved her.
But she called you an idiot champion.
Aren’t you angry?
I am angry.
But we are men.
We should be generous.
Got it?
Got it.
How is it? Did you get it?
What does it mean?
It basically means
(Stupidity Retardation Fool)
mental retardation, which means an idiot.
Why did you send it to me?
Chuan.
What’s your intention?
I’m wronged.
I don’t know where my mother
got the clothes.
It looks nice without
this word.
I wanted to keep it to myself.
Take it back then.
I want to see you wear it every day.
Damn, Chief.
Your conversation with
Yuan Caixi just now
was broadcast throughout the school.
Now everyone is talking about it
at the school forum.
Look.
(Li He is useless.)
(He wants to challenge Ning Zeyu?
What a joke.)
(He can’t even handle Yuan Caixi.)
(Li He is useless.)
(He overestimates himself.)
That’s irritating.
The North Campus nerds
are mocking us.
They said
you can’t even handle a girl.
They also said
you are no match for
Ning Zeyu’s little finger.
Who is Ning Zeyu?
Does he run faster than our chief?
Chief.
It’s okay, don’t take it personally.
Ning Zeyu
is just a straight-A student.
He is not worth mentioning.
Straight-A student?
Ning Zeyu is not just
a straight-A student.
He is a prodigy.
The difference between
a straight-A student and a prodigy
is the difference between 99 points
and 100 points.
Isn’t it just one point less?
Just one point less?
The straight-A student scores 99 points
because that’s
the best they can do.
The prodigy scores 100 points
because that’s the full marks
of the examination.
All right.
What straight-A student and prodigy?
Ning Zeyu is just
a normal high school student.
So does the eternal number two.
They are only better at
studying than us.
But we run faster than them.
Don’t be afraid. No big deal.
Xiaowu.
Pipi.
Li Jiefei.
You come with me.
I also want to join your team.
Can you run fast?
Can you play well?
You’d better go back
and do your homework.
Let’s play football!
Li He! Li He! Li He!
(Award Ning Zeyu Number One)
Why are you so angry?
One is a prodigy.
The other is a straight-A student.
We are no match for them.
We’d better find a way
to make us look good.
What did I tell you?
They are just paper tigers.
They will show their true colors
when they are on the playground.
How to get them on the playground?
Are you stupid?
The physical exam is in the afternoon.
-Knock, knock.
-Yeah?
Yuan.
You’ve been staring at Ning Zeyu.
I’m just thinking
why he can always get the first place.
You two rank among the top two.
It looks the same to me.
How can it be the same?
Do you remember who was the second
person to land on the moon?
Buzz Aldrin.
Formerly Edwin Eugene Aldrin Jr.
Born in Greenwich, New Jersey, USA
on January 20, 1930.
You asked it.
Anyway,
I must get the first place once
in my third year of high school
so as to get a scholarship.
Yuan, did I hear you right?
You’re not such a money-grubber.
No.
I am.
Yuan.
You...
Wait for me.
Yuan.
Li He has been staring at you.
His eyes are fierce.
But he is retarded.
Yeah.
Chief, Yuan Caixi has been
staring at you.
Perhaps it’s because I’m handsome.
Chief.
Are we going to stick to our plan?
Yeah.
Be smart.
Today is the final physical exam
for sophomores.
I hope
academic students and PE students
can take this physical exam seriously.
Because your results
will be recorded in your handbooks
and directly affect
the physical education courses
for your next semester.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Sir.
We want to
help academic students pass the test.
How?
We can help them stretch
before they take the test.
It’s not violating any rules.
Okay.
Try it.
Right now,
dismiss. Relax yourselves.
Limber up.
Dismiss!
What do you want to do?
It’s for the physical test.
Wait. Wait.
Easy.
What do you want to do? Listen.
I don’t need your help.
Yuan Caixi.
Can you pass the test without my help?
I can’t pass the test if you help me.
Go away.
What are you doing?
You did it on purpose!
Your name is Pan Hao, right?
Let me help you.
Hello.
Being distracted during exercise
can hurt yourself.
Are you ready?
Let’s do it!
Can you take it?
Don’t hold it back. Your face turns red.
You will faint.
No.
I can do it. I can do it.
It doesn’t hurt.
You are pretty soft.
Mr. Bai.
Obviously, they are revenging themselves
on us. Won’t you do something about it?
Revenge themselves?
For what?
Yeah, for what? Tell us.
Besides, we are helping you.
Can you pass the test without us?
Help us?
A bunch of retards.
How can you help us?
What did you say? What retards?
Can you understand if I say it again?
-I dare you to say it again.
-Stop it.
Get back and line yourself up!
Those who finish the trunk flexion test
will take sit-up test next.
Academic students. 30 sit-ups is
the passing score. 40 is excellent.
Understand?
Yes.
Mr. Bai.
Well...
Go back.
Start!
Mr. Bai!
The leaders have arrived.
One.
Mr. Ma asked you to come over.
Got it.
Two.
Li He!
Yeah.
Collect the test results later.
Okay.
Come on, number two.
Don’t worry, I’m professional.
Hurry up.
All right, I’m not afraid.
One.
Two.
Non-standard. Two.
Three.
Two.
Do it again. Two.
Well, I found that number two
are meant for you.
You are doing it on purpose.
I think you have special preference
to number two.
-Fine.
-Hurry up.
Keep counting.
Two.
Cheer up.
One, two.
Non-standard. Two.
Smile.
Go down.
Non-standard, do it again.
Two.
One.
Two. Non-standard. Two.
Two. Still two,
Two.
Still two.
Non-standard.
Cheer up.
-Two.
-Do you have something on your mind?
Non-standard. Do it again.
Come on. Get down.
Can you do it or not?
Use your abdominal muscles.
Do you know how to do sit-ups?
Get down.
Non-standard. Do it again.
Two.
What a wussy.
Who did you just call that?
Who is a wussy?
I’m calling you a wussy! What’s wrong?
You are a wussy.
I said you are a wussy. What can you do?
It’s fun to watch us
make a fool of ourselves, right?
No one wants to make a fool of you.
We are helping you.
We will record your score.
Well,
did we record less score for you?
Yeah, what’s more,
can you pass the test without our help?
You should thank us.
I dare you to say it again.
I can say it a hundred times.
You should thank us.
You are a wussy if you don’t say it.
Who are you calling that?
Let’s play a game if you dare.
You are a girl.
I’m not playing any game with you.
They will blame me for bullying a girl.
I’ll play with you.
Okay.
Play what?
Whatever you want.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to Sen Yong High School Cup’s
Academic and PE Dodge Ball.
Right now, academic students
and PE students
are lining up in two teams.
The game is about to start.
Players from both teams,
(Referee)
get ready!
Come on!
You are a girl. Don’t play it.
Ask a boy to play the game.
What’s wrong with being a girl?
Can’t a girl do it?
You can.
Don’t accuse us of bullying you later.
Are you okay?
Okay, I can do it.
First of all.
Each team needs to send a player
to snatch the ball
in the center of the court.
The player who gets the ball
needs to pass it to the teammate behind.
The teammate who receives the ball
can attack the opponent immediately.
During the game,
anyone who is hit by the ball
will be eliminated immediately.
When all the members of one team
are eliminated,
the game is over.
The game starts now!
Li He got the ball first.
Ning Zeyu is one step behind.
♪We chase each other in light laughter♪
The PE student
Jiang Yuan attacked first.
Yuan Caixi dodged a ball
and counterattacked.
Ning Zeyu aimed at Li He
and made a quick move.
Li He took the ball from Lin Chuan
and threw it hard at Ning Zeyu.
Pan Hao rushed out from behind
and attacked Li He.
-Li He leaned back and dodged it.
-Come on!
♪North or south Pro or con♪
♪Blend the chemistry♪
Li He and Ning Zeyu
are standing in front of each other
with a ball in hand.
They are feeling each other out.
No one takes it rashly.
Yuan Caixi came to help Ning Zeyu.
Li He is at a disadvantage.
Seeing this, Lin Chuan also
joined the battle.
♪Let’s capture
the innocent relationship♪
They are in confrontation now.
The two teams are alert.
They started moving
and slowly changing the formation.
♪Boom The collision curve♪
♪Is full of sweetness♪
Suddenly, Li He made an attack.
Ning Zeyu responded quickly.
Their balls collided in the air.
Lin Chuan and Yuan Caixi
made an attack in succession.
Li He and Ning Zeyu
dodged the ball respectively.
The PE students attacked again.
♪We’re simple♪
Come on!
The competition is heating up.
Back and forth attack
between the two teams.
Pan Hao was hit in the head.
Hitting the head doesn’t count
according to the rules.
Ning Zeyu took the chance
and attacked from the side.
Li He made a quick turn.
He caught the ball
and threw it at Pan Hao.
Pan Hao was hit in the leg
-and fell to the ground.
-Come on!
He was eliminated
before he had time to fight back.
The academic team lost a player.
Yuan Caixi and Ning Zeyu
looked at each other.
Unexpectedly,
-Yuan Caixi changed her direction.
-Come on!
Yun Xiang was eliminated.
The academic team made a comeback.
Come on!
Suddenly, Li He jumped up from behind.
He threw a fastball.
Yuan Caixi is about to be hit.
Ning Zeyu jumped up from the side
and pushed her away.
They dodged the ball,
but their teammate behind
was knocked out.
Are you okay, Zeyu?
As long as you are fine.
Be careful.
Okay.
Don’t try to look cool.
Just give up if you can’t make it.
I can’t bear to see you lose too badly.
Well, do you want to give up?
The game is not over yet.
We don’t know who will win.
There are only Yuan Caixi and Ning Zeyu
in the academic team.
The situation is not optimistic.
Unexpectedly, these chicken
are quite persistent.
We will win no matter
how persistent they are.
It won’t take long.
Yuan Caixi is looking for a chance
with a ball in hand.
Jiang Yuan fell down.
Yuan Caixi took the chance
and made an attack.
Jiang Yuan was hit.
Well?
-Who spilled the water?
-Come on. Come on!
You were hit and eliminated.
Don’t try to find any excuse.
Don’t you see the water here?
He accidentally slipped.
It doesn’t count.
It doesn’t count?
Shouldn’t he be eliminated
after being hit?
You play dirty because you know
you can’t win us.
You spilled the water when he wasn’t
paying attention, right?
Do you have any evidence?
How can you say that?
Evidence?
You dare not admit what you did.
You guys wanted to play a game first.
And you played dirty
when you couldn’t win.
I finally realize
that those who study well
like you are all shameless.
I dare you to say it again.
Who did you call shameless?
Yeah.
What’s wrong with that?
Who?
Did you get hit?
The admission rate of
Sen Yong High School is high.
The school life here is also
harmonious and peaceful.
I did learn something today.
You guys are really treacherous.
The PE students
and academic students
are like a family.
You are quite good at
generalizing about people.
They work in unity and help each other.
Play what?
Why should we play with
treacherous people like you?
If you dare...
Well, are you bullying girls now?
I’m not bullying girls.
Don’t you need to go to class?
What are you doing?
Where’s your head teacher?
Take them to the office!
You are such a troublemaker.
You don’t focus on running,
but make troubles for me.
You really picked a good day.
(Director’s Office)
You had to drop the ball
at this critical moment.
What day is today?
Today is...
No matter what it is,
you shouldn’t make trouble.
Mr. Bai.
It’s not our fault.
The academic students provoked us first.
How did they provoke you?
I’m the head teacher of Class 2,
Luo Xiyan.
Li He, please tell me
how my students provoked you.
They made fun of us in English.
We were too angry.
So we posed a difficult question.
Then somehow we started fighting.
Is that so?
You started it?
No.
It was a fair competition.
Yeah.
I know my students the best.
Yuan Caixi and Ning Zeyu
are not provocative students.
Therefore, Li He.
You must have inadvertently
or deliberately
omitted something.
Anyway,
students make mistakes
because they are young and ignorant.
But it’s the negligence of the teacher
if he doesn’t teach his students well.
The negligent teacher,
don’t you have anything to say?
Instructor Bai.
Negligence?
Mr. Ma, I think
it’s not totally because of
my negligence.
After all, every student
can be naughty some time.
They are just...
All right.
Are you finished?
The three of you.
Go back and write
a review of 1,500 words.
Put it on my desk tomorrow morning.
-Review?
-Okay, Mr. Ma.
An apology should be enough.
Is it too little for you?
2000 words!
What are you still waiting for?
Go back and write it.
It’s too much.
All right, go back.
Goodbye, Mr. Ma.
Bai Fei.
Can you look out for what you say?
Think a little bit
before you say anything.
Okay?
I said it in too much of a hurry.
What did he say?
He almost told them about the merging.
However, Mr. Ma,
are we really going to
merge into one campus?
Yeah, Mr. Ma.
I don’t think it’s a good idea.
Academic students and PE students
are essentially different.
How can they take classes together?
If they study in the same classroom,
they will fight every day
just like today.
Whether they fight or not,
we are going to merge into one campus.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪