♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 20=
Mom, we’re back.
Mom.
It flies up!
We made it!
Isn’t it great?
Caixi.
I’m a little tired.
Come on.
Come sit with me for a while.
Why do you get tired so quickly?
I’m older than you.
I’m not as energetic as you are.
I’m better than Dad!
Since you are better than me,
will you take care of
your mom and brother?
Of course. I want to be
the head of our family.
The head should take care of everyone.
That’s great.
In this case,
I can rest assured.
When I get old,
you will be the one to
take care of your mom and brother.
I don’t want you to get old.
Then I don’t want to be better than you.
You will grow up slowly.
And I will get old day by day.
This is normal.
If I don’t want to grow up,
will you not get old?
Silly girl.
Caixi.
You must grow up
and become strong enough.
Then when I get sick,
you can take care of me,
your mother and your brother.
I don’t need to be any better than you
to take good care of you.
Actually, the important thing
for your mom and brother
is companionship.
Come on.
Actually,
it’s fun to grow up.
You will have more friends,
see the wider world,
and see a more beautiful
scenery than this.
More beautiful than now?
Yeah, much more beautiful.
I want to see it.
Then you should grow up quickly
and enjoy the beautiful scenery for me.
But I want to see it with you,
Mom and Haoxi.
Don’t worry.
I will always be there for you.
Mom!
(Dad, Happy Birthday)
Mom.
Try it and see if it’s tasty.
Okay.
Mom, what’s this red one?
Yummy.
It’s so delicious.
Today is Yuan Caixi’s father’s birthday?
Yes.
Her parents were deeply in love.
They only celebrate his birthday.
They don’t celebrate
his death anniversary
to not make Aunt sad.
Every year on this day,
monitor and Haoxi will go home.
They don’t want Aunt to feel lonely.
Don’t think too much about it.
Monitor is down today
not because of you.
Caixi.
Come in.
What’s the matter?
Caixi.
How much do you remember about our dad?
When Dad was gone,
I was only four years old.
I can’t remember anything.
Caixi.
Tell me about him.
Come with me.
Caixi, why are we here?
Come on, help me move this.
Caixi.
What’s this?
The password is
our parents’ wedding anniversary.
This is...
This is me?
Who else could it be?
See if there is anything else.
This is the diary
Dad wrote when he was sick.
Don’t read it.
It will only make us sad.
I want to read it.
Yuan Haoxi, Dad has been
gone for so long.
What’s the use to read it now?
It’s of no use.
But he is my dad.
I want to know what happened to him.
March 1, 2008.
The doctor said it might be leukemia.
Yanan doesn’t believe it.
But I know the chances are high.
I have a poor appetite recently.
I feel dizzy and tired.
And the bruises won’t heal
for a long time.
I guess it’s leukemia.
She kept telling me
we can make it.
But I know
she is comforting herself.
All right.
Stop reading it.
Caixi.
It’s enough.
All right.
It’s okay.
Let him read it.
Mom, we just can’t sleep tonight.
So we come up...
Yeah, Mom. Don’t get angry.
Why would I be angry?
You did nothing wrong.
I know
Haoxi was too young when your dad left.
You want to know what your dad was like.
Haoxi.
Before you read it,
I want you to remember
that your father was the kindest,
the most responsible,
and the best dad.
He has also been the most handsome man
in my heart.
Yeah.
I haven’t used
this computer for a long time.
You are back.
Yeah, Mom.
Well.
You scared me.
Get off me. Don’t bother me.
Listen,
I have no money for you.
Dad.
What?
It’s nice to have you
and my mom by my side.
Are you going crazy again?
Go away!
It’s too gross!
It doesn’t work on your dad. Come to me.
Let me give you a hug. Come on.
Come on.
Tell me what happened today.
-Mom.
-Well?
When Grandpa died,
how did my dad comfort you?
What?
Why do you ask this suddenly?
My good friend’s father passed away.
I don’t know how to comfort her.
Her family passed away,
she must be very sad.
Actually, it’s no use
no matter how you comfort her.
You’d better
just stay by her side.
Don’t ask too many questions.
It would be the best
if there is something
that can distract her.
Or you can cook something she likes.
That’s how your dad
comforted me at that time.
Yeah.
Tell me what your monitor likes to eat.
She loves chicken wings.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
-Cabbage.
-Yeah.
Anything else?
How do you know that, Mom?
Silly boy, I’m your mother.
I know what you are going to do
when you raise your butt.
Mom, you are impressive.
It’s getting late.
You two go to bed earlier.
-Okay.
Good night.
I wish there is a time machine
that can let me see Dad again.
Dad will be pissed off
to see you like this.
Well?
Caixi, what’s this?
Nothing. I hit the desk today.
Don’t scare me.
I just saw the photos of Dad
when he was sick.
The bruises...
Caixi.
Won’t you have leukemia?
You are the one who is sick.
Let me warn you,
I won’t die before you die.
Go back to sleep.
Then I can rest assured.
Remember what you said.
You must stay alive to that time.
Okay.
-Not a minute less.
-I got it.
I will outlive you.
-Okay, good night.
-Good night.
-Yuan Caixi!
-Ugh...
Let’s go.
Wait, Yuan.
Are you okay?
-Yuan!
-Yuan Caixi!
Yuan, have you had
a bad appetite recently?
Why are you eating less?
The school doctor said that you are
too tired and undernourished recently.
Yuan Caixi, are you okay?
Do you feel dizzy again?
I have a poor appetite recently
and feel dizzy and tired.
And the bruises won’t heal
for a long time.
I guess it’s leukemia.
Leukemia is too scary.
(Yuan Caixi)
Tell me, is the traitor Ning Zeyu
or Han Yayi?
(Li He)
Well, why can’t I be telepathic?
Can you use your telepathy
to know today is my dad’s birthday
and come to comfort me
because you don’t want me to feel sad?
Don’t underestimate the IQ
of the world champion.
World champion, you should go to sleep.
Good night.
Monitor, I’ve always been there.
Okay, I know.
Well, monitor.
Are you also going to the clinic?
No, I’m going to the toilet.
Oh, I’m gonna go.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Come in.
Hello, what can I help you?
I have something to ask you.
Okay.
-I have a friend...
-Oh.
You have a friend.
I have a friend
who has a poor appetite.
She always feels dizzy and falls easily.
The most important thing is
that she got a lot of bruises on her.
Where? Let me see.
It’s not me.
It’s a friend of mine.
Okay, then tell me about
the bruises on your friend.
She gets bruises
when her body hit somewhere.
And the bruises won’t heal
for a long time.
Are there any other symptoms?
Her father
died of leukemia.
Leukemia is not a genetic disease,
but if she has
a family history of leukemia,
she is at high risk for leukemia.
If she often feels tired
and has a poor appetite,
and the bruises won’t heal,
I suggest she go to
a big hospital for a checkup.
Yuan.
Where did you go?
I’ve been looking for you.
What’s wrong?
Yuan, let me see your math paper.
I slept last night and didn’t write it.
Write it yourself first.
Just let me see it for once.
The last time. Just for once.
You either sleep
or read comics every day.
Do you know you are
a student of Grade 3?
The college entrance examination
is six months later.
Are you going to see
my math paper at the time, Han Yayi?
What’s wrong?
It’s just a paper.
Don’t you always let her see it?
Why are you so angry today?
Yuan Caixi.
-Stop chasing me.
-Yuan Caixi.
What’s happening?
You run so fast
and you don’t let me chase you?
Fine.
I won’t chase you.
But you need to tell me
what’s wrong with you.
Nothing.
By the way,
do you have a match two days later?
Yeah, it’s the day after tomorrow.
Are you really okay?
I’m fine. I don’t know
what’s wrong with me recently.
I think there is too much on my mind.
Don’t be sad.
Go back to class.
Yeah.
Which question? I’ll teach you.
Are you not angry with me anymore?
You are not angry anymore.
How can I be angry?
That’s great.
Sorry that I lost my temper.
I guess I’m too stressed recently.
It’s okay.
Yuan, considering how sad I’m,
write the paper for me
to redeem yourself.
I won’t beat you if you
get your hands off me.
No problem.
Here.
Does your family run a mini mart?
You give her strawberry milk every day.
I heard that sweet food
can relieve stress.
It’s okay, Monitor.
I’ll bring you a box of milk
from my house.
Thank you.
It’s nice to have you.
You’re welcome.
Am I the most handsome man?
Yuan.
Kinship is a paddle
and friendship is a sail.
Let’s travel on the ocean of
the college entrance examination!
-Well-said!
-Bravo!
Write the homework. Hurry up.
Zeyu?
Shouldn’t you be
in the classroom right now?
I just want to be
in a different environment.
Your book.
Thank you.
(Secrets of Blood)
You can take it. I’ll find another book.
Did your father die of leukemia?
Han Yayi said you have
lost your appetite recently.
You even fainted
more than once.
Don’t take a wild guess.
I never take a wild guess.
I said it’s just a friend of mine.
If my judgment is right...
Where else?
Ning Zeyu!
What’s wrong?
I don’t know.
Aren’t they the two
straight A students in Class 2?
Oh, Zeyu and monitor are having a fight.
Come with me.
Ning Zeyu!
Get off me!
Did you go to the hospital?
Why should I go to the hospital?
I said it’s a friend of mine.
Even Li He won’t believe it.
-It’s really a friend of mine.
-Which friend?
As far as I know, you only have
one friend, Han Yayi.
Is it Han Yayi?
Does Han Yayi have leukemia?
Don’t curse her.
Who is that then?
Did you go to the hospital?
No.
Why?
I’m scared.
Does Aunt know it?
My mother, Yuan Haoxi, Li He
and Han Yayi, they all have no idea.
If I hadn’t met you today,
no one would know it.
Yuan Caixi, what are you thinking about?
It’s such an important thing.
Don’t you think you should
talk to your family first?
How should I tell them?
My dad died of leukemia.
How should I tell this to my mom?
Tell her that I got
the same disease as my dad?
How will my mom take it?
She will go crazy!
But keeping it from her
can’t solve the problem.
It’s leukemia.
It’s not a cold or any minor illness.
You can’t get treatment
if you don’t say it.
What should I do with you?
I don’t know what to do.
Zeyu.
Can you promise me one thing?
Fine. Go ahead.
Keep it a secret for me.
You must keep it a secret for me.
You can’t tell anyone, especially Li He.
He is going to have a match.
I can’t affect him.
I’m not important. His match
is the most important thing.
Can you do it?
Please.
I’m begging you.
Fine.
To the end of the month.
I’ll keep it secret for you
only to the end of the month.
If you don’t go to
the hospital next month,
-I will tell them for you.
-Okay.
Let’s go. Let me take you back.
I put the key at the door of
the broadcasting room.
It’s under the mat.
Remember to take it tomorrow.
Are you all right?
I’m fine. Let’s go.
What’s happening?
You can’t keep a secret forever.
It’s better to say it earlier.
Li He.
I’ve been waiting for you for a while.
Didn’t you go to the library?
I didn’t find you.
Where have you been?
There are a few questions
I don’t know how to solve.
So I went back to ask Zeyu.
Have you finished?
-Yeah.
-Can I take you home?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Bye.
-Let’s go.
-Yeah.
What questions did you ask Ning Zeyu?
Different values of X should be solved
by different analytic functions.
Piecewise function?
That’s all you asked?
Yeah.
I left after I asked him.
It sounds right.
Ning Zeyu spends all his time
doing homework or writing programs.
There should be nothing else he can say.
Let’s go.
Rest early tonight.
I’ll pick you up tomorrow morning.
Well, you don’t need to.
Why not?
Aren’t you going to have a match?
Just stay focused on
preparing for the match.
You don’t need to pick me up.
Picking you up won’t affect the match.
But...
There is no but.
Yuan Caixi.
You are you. The game is the game.
There is no conflict between you two.
Whether there is a game or not,
I will pick you up and take you home.
Do you hear me?
What are you looking at?
You don’t want to go home
or you don’t want to leave me?
Let’s go.
The weather is great.
The moon is really round.
Tell Chief. Don’t tell Chief.
Tell Chief.
Don’t tell Chief.
Tell Chief. Don’t tell Chief.
(Chuan)
What if I think too much about it?
I must be thinking too much about it.
(Chief)
Hello, Chief.
Hello, Chuan.
Why did you call me?
Nothing, actually.
What is nothing?
Well... it’s...
Just say it.
I need to get up early tomorrow.
I will buy breakfast for monitor
and then send her to school.
Chief.
I saw monitor and Zeyu together again.
And then?
Then?
I said that I saw them together again.
Chuan, are you stupid?
We are at the same school.
What’s so strange to see them together?
When you were running
during the night classes,
I saw them talking very intimately.
Were they near the library?
Yes, near the library.
She told me about it.
She was going to study near the library.
Later, there was a math problem
she couldn’t solve.
So she went to ask Zeyu.
What’s wrong?
No way.
Ask him a math problem in that place?
You don’t understand
the world of straight A students.
Stop guessing.
Chief.
Do you believe whatever
Yuan Caixi told you?
Yeah, she won’t lie to me.
All right, there is nothing else.
Chief, good night.
Silly boy.
Well, well, Li He.
You are silly indeed.
(Renke Buns)
Aunt, I want a meat bun
and a vegetable bun.
And some black rice porridge.
-One more red bean bun.
-Okay.
I’ve paid the money, Aunt.
Zeyu.
Why are you here?
I can’t rest assured to let you
go to school alone.
But I left home
half an hour earlier today.
I know with my knees
that you will leave early
to avoid Li He.
Well?
Didn’t you leave early to avoid him?
Now you want him to show up?
Let’s go.
Okay.
Monitor!
Let me carry the bag for you.
It’s okay, I can carry it myself.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪