♪The further we look up at the sun♪
♪The harder the wind howls♪
♪Struggle with shoulders and hands♪
♪To change where the dream goes♪
♪How shall we long for♪
♪Where we’re going♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
=Please Classmate=
=Episode 14=
Sit please.
Sir.
Can we order?
Here.
What do you want?
So what really happened between you?
It’s fine.
It’s just a boys’ problem.
You girls don’t get it.
You’re being extremely sexist.
No, I’m not.
I...
How can I understand
if you don’t tell me?
I don’t understand the brotherhood
between you and Lin Chuan.
I just want to listen
to my friend’s concerns.
We had a fall-out because
of university application.
I want to go to Huatsing University.
I don’t know if I’ve made a mistake.
Huatsing University is one
of the best universities in China.
Though I felt a bit surprised
when you told me that.
But how could
aspiring to go to a top university
be a mistake?
No.
I’m not worried about failing to get in.
Nor do I think Huatsing University
isn’t good enough.
It’s because I broke a promise.
We made a promise of going to
Haiwen Sport University together.
But I broke that promise.
On your positions.
Ready.
Go.
Have you finished the race?
Not yet.
Then what are you waiting for?
Get in the line.
Coach, I...
I can lend you my shoes.
You can’t run barefoot.
Come.
See if we have the same size.
Can I?
Why not?
How are they?
Just right.
Thank you for your shoes.
Go.
On your positions.
Ready.
Go.
On your positions.
Ready.
Go.
-Jiang Yuan.
-Yes.
-Mo Xiaoding.
-Lin Chuan.
-Yes.
-Gao Jie.
-Yun Xiang.
-Yes.
-Li He.
The students whose names were called
should come to the field
at 7AM tomorrow for training.
Dismissed.
Thank you for the shoes.
Congratulations.
You’re welcome.
I just saw you run.
You did so well.
You too.
Let’s compete
when we get the chance.
Sure.
I’ll wait for you.
It’s fine, Chuan.
You were so handsome just now.
There were a bunch of girls
secretly taking photos of you.
So what?
I just lost.
There are only two outcomes
of a competition.
Winning or losing.
Being defeated is fine.
You can try next time.
Yes.
It’s fine.
Okay.
It’s your turn.
Chief.
Don’t worry.
With this pair of shoes you gave me,
I’ll definitely be the champion.
-Come on.
Bye.
Don’t come back unless you’re No.1.
Come on.
-Go for it, Li He.
-Come on, Li He.
Ready.
-Go for it, Li He.
-Come on, Li He.
-Come on! Go for it!
-Hurry! Hurry!
Come on.
-Come on.
-Go for it.
-Li He. Li He.
I told you he’s got talent.
-Awesome.
-Li He.
Thank you, mister.
Take some photos with this medal too.
No. No.
I won’t wear a medal that’s not mine.
Fine.
When you get a medal in the future,
we can take photos together.
That’s a deal.
Of course.
Let’s toast.
This is mineral water, not wine.
It’s our sponsor.
Chief.
Yes.
Which university do you want to
go to after high school?
I’ve never thought about it.
How about you?
I want to go to
Haiwen Sport University.
Fine.
Let’s go there together.
Really?
Yes.
But why do you choose
Haiwen Sport University?
Because it’s close to my home,
and I can receive scholarship.
In that case, my mom
will have less financial strains.
Okay.
After all, we’re brothers
who have shared
the same pair of sneakers.
Anywhere is all right
as long as we’re together.
You’re a true brother, Li He.
From then on,
they called me Chief
because I won that year’s first
championship of Sen Yong High School.
Every time we talk about universities,
we see Haiwen Sport University
as the goal.
No wonder.
I’ve never seen you so depressed.
I can’t get used to that.
I feel sorry for what I did to them.
And I wish we can do better.
Because choosing a university
is such an important decision.
It’s very helpful
to our future life path.
So I want them to do it with me.
So, you think Lin Chuan is mad
because you broke the promise?
Isn’t he?
Is Huatsing University what you want?
But have you thought about
what he wants?
Every person’s choices and
aspirations are different.
Take me as an example,
I want to go to Beikai University’s
department of finance.
But they think my studying every day
must be extremely boring.
But I’m willing to do that.
I want to provide my family
with a better life.
You? You have a higher aspiration now.
But Lin Chuan might be different.
You’ve been close buddies for years.
He definitely won’t be mad at you
for wanting bigger dreams.
But have you thought about
what he wants exactly?
(Chuan)
(Sent to Chuan)
Lin Chuan.
Can’t you act like a man?
Stop making me guess!
Just say it. What do you want?
(Li He)
Lin Chuan.
Can’t you act like a man?
Stop making me guess!
Just say it.
Why are you speaking like a girl?
Mom, I said I’d do this.
Ah. It’s fine.
-Okay, Son.
-Go get some rest.
Okay.
(ASP Program Design Basics)
Mom.
Answer me.
What are these?
You searched my room?
I did this for you.
I’m glad I did.
If I hadn’t searched your room,
I wouldn’t have known that
you’re still reading these books.
How many times have I told you?
I don’t mind you reading these books
in the 10th or 11th grade.
But now you’re in the 12th grade.
You’re still reading these books.
Game programming?
This is such a waste of time.
This isn’t a waste of time.
I’m always the No.1 in class.
This hasn’t affected my scores.
No.1? So what?
You have to understand.
Your competitors are people
who’re as smart as you
from across the country.
Being No.1 in Sen Yong High School
can’t secure your success.
Zeyu.
If you can get into law school,
your dad and I have planned out
your future.
You’ll have brighter futures
Than your mom and dad.
I don’t like to study law.
I like writing codes.
I like designing programs.
I want to do things
that are challenging.
Kid,
you’re so naive.
Do you think you can do
whatever you what
in a society like this?
(Li He)
Bring me two meat buns tomorrow.
Mom.
You and Li He are so close.
You’ll even waste your time
to buy buns for him.
I’ll say this one more time.
He’s an athletic student.
He has tons of time to waste.
But you’re different.
You’ll be a lawyer one day.
Mom, I get it.
I’ll get back to study.
You might hate me now.
In the future,
you’ll be grateful to me.
Ning Zeyu.
Ah.
What are you doing?
Look. Are these your books?
(Internet Program Design)
I knew something was wrong
when you didn’t text me back yesterday.
When I went to throw trash later,
I saw these books.
Did your mom throw these away?
It’s fine.
I can keep these for you for now.
Tell me when you want to read these.
You can come to my house.
Or I can take these to school for you.
Okay.
Don’t be sad anymore.
After all, we’re in Grade 12.
Parents tend to be stricter.
It’s fine.
Have you changed your
major choice to programming secretly?
Yes.
I applied for Tiangong University
of Science and Technology.
Not bad. You’re so ambitious.
Well.
Which university did you apply?
Huatsing University.
Good for you.
You’re even more ambitious.
Well, bro.
It’s not too late to ask for
my autograph now.
Buy me one meal.
I can give you ten autographs.
When did I become your brother?
Fine. We are fake brothers.
Fine. Fake brother. Wish you
can pass all your exams soon.
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
Lin Chuan.
What?
If Chief asked you to come,
you can leave now.
Why do you think I’m here
because of another boy?
Come.
I’ll buy you a meal.
Hurry up. Eat.
Why barbecue again?
Because I don’t have enough fund.
My mom didn’t give me much allowance.
Tell me.
What did Li He want you to tell me?
No.
I didn’t come
because Li He asked me to this time.
But, he’s indeed
the reason
why I buy you this meal.
I’m not being unreasonable.
I want to be a high-level athlete.
I want to get to Huatsing University.
Well done. Li He.
The world champion.
That’s in the future.
Okay. Future world champion.
I’ll ask you for autographs then.
Sure.
Can I have
another request?
Can you...?
No.
You two.
Can you
also teach
Chuan,
Jiang Yuan, Yun Xiang,
particularly Chuan?
Sure.
Of course.
Yes.
I can take that into consideration.
But, Li He.
So we buy one, get three free.
We come in a bundle.
In Gintama,
Shimura always gives
Gintoki cold shoulders.
But at critical moments,
Shimura is always by his side.
Even though he’s weak,
he will fight with Gintoki without fear.
Shimura is so fearless
because he trusts Gintoki.
No matter what happens,
he believes that
Gintoki will never leave
a friend behind.
Li He never thought about
abandoning the dream you all share.
He just wishes to
pursue higher goals
and achieve higher scores with you.
Chuan.
I’ve made up my mind.
I want to apply for Huatsing University.
I can’t keep our promise to apply for
Haiwen Sport University.
I’m so sorry.
But,
can I invite you to apply for
Huatsing University with me?
How can I?
My mom runs that little shop
all on her own.
How can I go to such a faraway place?
Are you dumb?
What does your mom work so hard for?
So you can study at a nearby university?
So you can go back and
run that small shop?
She saves every penny
because she wants you to
go to a good university
and have a bright future.
Chuan,
if she knows that you give up
Huatsing University
because of her.
She’ll feel sorry for
the rest of her life.
Do you really want that?
Besides,
is it worthwhile to make such sacrifice?
You’re capable of going to
a better university.
You’re able to provide her
with a better life.
Why don’t you do that?
I think you’re out of your mind.
What?
Why do you smell like barbeque?
Well done. Kid.
I’ve been looking for you all day.
You sneaked out for barbeque.
With whom? Han Yayi?
I...
What?
What excuses do you have?
I knew it. Girls come before friends.
You’re so heartless.
No way.
Girls come before friends?
I can accept the other allegations.
But this one?
I’d better give it back to you.
Me?
When did I ever
put girls before friends?
Dare you say that Yuan Caixi
isn’t part of the reason
you apply for Huatsing University?
No.
She applies for Beikai University,
not Huatsing University.
-Bei...
-What are you looking at?
Go.
Go back to study.
She’s really applying
for Beikai University.
Yes.
I thought you’d apply for
the same university.
-Chief.
-You’re back.
Chuan.
Boss.
Sit.
Listen, if you don’t come soon,
I’ll have higher scores
than you do in exams.
Keep dreaming.
-Come.
-I want it too.
Yes.
Thank you, monitor.
Just write like this.
Oh.
I’m back.
Brother.
You’re back.
Bear?
Two weeks flew by so quickly.
I came back
so I can study with you.
What?
Do you miss me?
Do you?
Sure.
Why are you still so annoying?
You came back right on time.
You can study with us.
You and Li He, two problematic students,
can stay in the same group.
What?
How can you compare Li He to me?
Do you think I want to
be compared to you?
Go ahead.
Do this test first.
You can teach me
if I don’t know the answer.
I have to do it myself?
Don’t tell me you can’t do any of these.
I can. I just...
Han Yayi.
Yun Xiang. Focus.
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪Never disappointed at the failures♪
I know another one.
-This is called a union set.
-A union set.
What are you doing? Don’t touch me.
-Check out this one.
-Do you have a problem?
You do.
You have a big problem.
I know. Don’t mind me.
-Just let her help me.
-I’ll help him.
♪How to make a sore spot♪
♪Become the cutting edge♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
♪No matter how frustrating it can be♪
♪Let’s bear with our shoulders♪
♪No matter what may confront us♪
♪We only hear our pounding hearts♪
Then, I...
Why are you here?
Who knows. I told them that
Li He would take you home.
Then, they insisted on waiting here.
Yuan.
You must be really tired.
Go home with Haoxi first.
We have something
we want to talk to Li He.
What?
Nothing special.
We made a deal.
Yes.
It’s all right. Go home.
Okay.
Let’s go. Come.
-Bye.
What’s this face, Yuan Haoxi?
What?
We agreed to compete fairly.
But you accompanied monitor home
secretly without our notice.
Don’t you know that
your action violated our rules?
What?
Any problem?
If so, let’s have a match.
-Fine.
-Come on.
How about this?
I’ll give you a five-second head start.
On the count of three.
Whoever makes it
to that dessert shop first
is the winner.
What’s the prize for the winner?
We can decide later.
Anyway, the loser must
buy drinks.
The winner can accompany
monitor home tomorrow.
Okay.
Come on.
Let’s do it.
Three.
-Two.
-One.
Let’s go.
(Zeyu)
I’m coming.
Wow.
Mrs. Ning.
Hi. Why are you here?
Come inside.
No, thanks.
Is Zeyu at your place?
No.
Li He hasn’t come home either?
Do you want to confirm it inside?
No. I’m just asking.
Mrs. Ning.
I guess these kids
are studying together.
Don’t worry too much.
They’ve grown up now.
Mrs. Li.
I don’t think Zeyu’s scores
are good enough
to help others.
He’ll become a lawyer one day.
He’s different from Li He.
Mrs. Ning, listen to yourself.
You think our Li He is not good enough?
Listen up.
The other day, school had a conversation
about university applications.
Our Li He will take the test to be
a high-level college athlete.
Well, it’s uncertain
who’ll get to a better college
in the future,
right?
You had the conversation
about university applications?
Yes.
You don’t know?
Have I said something
I’m not supposed to?
(Parents’ letter of confirmation)
(Ning Zeyu English test paper)
(Physics tests for
College Entrance Exams)
(C primer Plus)
This bad kid.
Mom, I...
Who did you learn this from?
I’m asking you.
You lied to your teachers.
You cheated your parents.
And you forged my signature.
You even secretly filled in
college application.
Did you learn this from Li He?
What does this have to do
with Li He again?
Forging signature will give
you civil liabilities.
In worse cases,
this constitutes contract fraud.
This is very serious.
Mom.
I’m your son, not your client.
Then this is even more unforgivable.
Your test results came.
You’re still No.1.
But your scores dropped.
To keep me from knowing,
you even forged my signature.
If I hadn’t asked Li He’s mom,
I wouldn’t have known anything about
the interview with parents.
You even kept that a secret from me.
And you hide programming books.
What on earth do you want?
You went to Li He’s home?
You think this is embarrassing?
Now, you feel embarrassed?
Do I really want to?
You help others study every day.
Your own scores dropped because of that.
If I hadn’t searched your stuff,
I wouldn’t have known that you
kept so many things hidden from me.
Give me your phone.
What?
From now on,
all of your activities after class
are suspended.
Don’t even think about
helping others to study.
You can forget about school’s
self-study sessions as well.
Tomorrow, I’ll call your head teacher.
I’ll tell her.
From today till the day
of college entrance exam,
Ning Zeyu will come home
immediately after class.
Stay home.
Study at home.
I don’t want to.
You must even if you don’t want to.
Give me your phone.
I’ll repeat it again.
Give it to me.
Ning Zeyu.
What’s the situation?
He must have a rough time
because of his mom.
Oops.
I must have said too much.
It’s all my fault.
That’s not true.
If you didn’t told her,
she wouldn’t find out?
She will find out sooner or later.
He.
Call Zeyu. Ask him what’s going on.
I will.
How’s it?
No answer.
Well. It’s late in the night.
Where can he go?
Ning Zeyu.
Excuse me.
Can you take me in for a night?
Oh.
Come in. Hurry.
What’s going on?
So,
you ran away from home?
What a surprise!
The straight-A student is so rebellious.
I’m not being rebellious.
I really don’t know
how to explain to my mom.
I don’t want to go to law school at all.
My mom and dad just don’t get me.
This is the only thing I can do.
I didn’t expect this.
The straight-A student
has come to this dilemma.
This is unexpected to me too.
You take pleasure in my misery.
But don’t show it.
Let me show you something.
I found it
unbelievable
that someone would
refuse to...
Isn’t this... ?
Your audition?
I remember that you were well-prepared.
I found it unbelievable that
someone would refuse to swim.
Being in water,
we’re close to the heart of the ocean.
It’s the most amazing feeling
I’ve ever felt.
You memorized it pretty well.
-I did it on purpose.
-Why?
At that time, why did you... ?
I don’t want to go.
So I did this.
I just want to sing and produce music.
But my agency got
this opportunity for me.
It’s a good one.
I had to go.
Then, later,
I came up with this lame idea.
If you’re truly passionate
about programming,
then stick to it.
At start, my parents were against
me entering the music industry.
Because we have a family business.
But I told my mom that
I’m willing to inherit
the family business.
But if I do so,
I can never be happy in my life.
Then,
my mom agreed.
No matter what,
just tell your family you’re safe.
We got school tomorrow.
Take some rest.
(Missed call, from Mom)
Li He.
Aunt,
I’m just here to tell you this.
Zeyu is staying at
our classmate’s place.
Don’t worry about him.
Which classmate?
A boy or a girl?
I’m just here to tell you this.
I don’t know the rest.
It’s late. Go to rest early.
Isn’t this Zeyu who ran away from home?
How do you feel?
Tomorrow is the final.
Don’t let this affect your performance.
If I under-perform in the exam
and you get the first place,
will you be happy or sad?
What do you mean?
Nothing. It’s just a joke.
(Class 2, Grade 3)
I want everyone to take a look at
the names of these minority groups.
Can someone tell me the similarities
between these groups?
Ning Zeyu.
Answer this question.
Zeyu.
Ning Zeyu.
Oh.
Is there an answer outside the window?
Sorry.
They share the same Asian culture
full of kindness and bravery.
That’s about right.
Sit down.
So we all know that
China’s vast geography and population
is composed of a diverse variety
of minority groups.
But apart from the few listed
on this board behind me,
I want someone to come up
and write down some of
the other minority groups.
Yuan, eat more meat.
-Don’t eat his.
-I can’t have more.
This is used.
-Just eat your food.
-How can she eat yours?
-You have such a huge appetite.
-Well.
I’m different.
I think Zeyu’s problem
isn’t just his argument with his mom.
I’ll talk to him
when we get home tonight.
And he was absent-minded
throughout the class today.
Yes.
Look.
Look what I found in
the entry list.
(Entry List for Haiwen Internet
Programming Preliminary Competition)
So, he’s worried about the competition.
I don’t know when he became
interested in programming.
It’s beyond mere interest.
The time he spent studying programming
has already exceeded
the overall time I spent on study
at high school.
Moreover, he didn’t even want to
go to Beikai University
or Huatsing University.
Huh.
The school he chose
on his application is…
-Tiangong Uni of Science and Technology.
Tiangong University of
Science and Technology.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
Yes.
Why?
I’ll tell you the details later.
The competition is
scheduled on tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes.
Isn’t tomorrow the day of our final?
No wonder he’s so stressed out.
He has to prepare for the exam
and the competition at the same time.
But based on my knowledge
of Zeyu,
he shouldn’t act like this.
The final is just
a piece of cake for him.
Anyway,
having to choose between
his dream and his parents’ dream
must be difficult.
Mrs. Ning.
You’re looking for me?
I’m looking for your son.
Oh. Come inside.
Come in, please.
Please tell Zeyu.
I’ll transfer him to another school
after tomorrow’s final.
Ah!
-Wait.
-Mrs. Ning.
Zeyu is in the 12th grade now.
You’re transferring him
to another school?
Aren’t you afraid that
this will affect his study?
His study will be affected
if I don’t transfer him.
After all,
he’s surrounded by people
who affect his study.
Mrs. Ning, your words
have other meanings, right?
Li He and Zeyu are
classmates and best friends.
We live opposite to each other.
When you were too busy with work
and couldn’t take care of Zeyu,
we helped you out.
We are neighbors.
That’s what we should do.
Well.
Li He’s scores aren’t as good as Zeyu’s.
But he is working hard.
We all witnessed that.
Right, Li He?
Wow! Mrs. Ning.
You must be too worried recently.
You even got a pimple on your lips.
Was it because you were
too angry at Zeyu?
Listen up! My Li He has one merit.
He never makes me mad.
We’re like close friends.
We tell each other everything.
Right?
The boys are in their puberty.
They might throw little tantrums.
They might be a bit rebellious.
That’s normal.
If you transfer him to another school
because of such trivial matters,
it might influence his future.
Anyway, please tell him.
Goodbye.
Look at her.
-She was being so mean.
-Mom.
Thank you for speaking up for me.
My stupid son.
It’s true. My son is so good.
How can I let her say bad things
about you, right?
But Zeyu is about to be transferred.
Don’t worry.
Call him later.
Try to convince him
to apologize to his mom.
He’ll be in great trouble if his mom
really transfers him to another school.
Okay.
I’ll figure something out.
♪Achoo I sneezed♪
♪I’m not thinking of you secretly♪
♪Your insolence overwhelms my calmness♪
♪I don’t want to get close to you♪
♪With declined immunity
I’m getting sick♪
♪Achoo who’s missing me secretly♪
♪You look even more lovely♪
♪The world turns pink when I meet you♪
♪I don’t know what to say but nonsense♪
♪My heart beats together with yours♪
♪Please listen♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Or you may know my feelings for you♪
♪Wind blows of a strawberry scent♪
♪Your face is like a red apple♪
♪If you really like me♪
♪Could you say it out loud♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking♪
♪Could you stay right ten meters away♪
♪Could you circle around within it♪
♪Bend your head and count to three♪
♪You’ll find me behind you♪
♪Please stay ten meters away from me♪
♪Your presence even dims the rainbow♪
♪I’m used to avoiding eye contacts♪
♪Stop trying to be stiff♪
♪Be a law-breaking probationary judge♪