[English subtitles are available]
[Crush]
[Episode 6]
Ms Sang.
Xiao Wei.
What's wrong?
In the coming performance,
I'm going to perform on the stage too.
I'll sing a song.
Please help me with the practice.
Me?
Why didn't you approach Mr Su?
He's a pro in singing.
I don't want to trouble him.
I'm too shy to approach him.
I see.
Actually,
don't worry about troubling him.
If you approach him,
he'll help you for sure.
It's recess. Time to play.
Those boys are so annoying.
But
you like Mr Su, right?
Of course.
Mr Su is different from them.
Even a ten year old girl
can tell
men and boys apart.
Xiao Wei.
Do you want Mr Su
to help you with the practice?
Yes.
However, Mr Su has left.
Tomorrow's the weekend.
It's simple.
I'll give him a call.
I don't know what I should say.
What you just told me is good enough.
Don't be nervous.
Just tell Mr Su
what you just told me.
[Incoming call from Sang Wu Yan.]
Hello.
Xiao Wei.
Mr Su.
I'll be performing in the performance
mentioned by Mr Li.
I'll sing a song.
Please help me with the practice.
Sure,
I'll go to the welfare home tomorrow.
[Binhai Welfare Home, Xiamen]
Ms Sang.
It's me.
All right.
Let's start now.
Mr Su.
Should we arrange the formation?
I can help.
It's okay.
Let's start from singing practice.
Xiao Wei.
Start singing.
♫ Outside the long corridor ♫
♫ Along the ancient road ♫
♫ The green grass
seemed to connect with the sky ♫
No wonder Su Nian Qin dotes on her.
I'm so envious of those who can sing well.
Stop.
How about this?
Sing one by one.
Start from you.
♫ Outside the long corridor ♫
Not bad.
You have improved.
♫ Along the ancient road ♫
Not bad.
♫ The green grass... ♫
Seemed to connect with the sky
Xiao Jie.
You need to sing in tune.
Please practice more, okay?
Good boy.
♫ The setting sun illuminated
mountain by mountain ♫
Here.
You have improved.
All right, let's sing again.
Three, two, one.
♫ Outside the long corridor ♫
♫ Along the ancient road ♫
♫ The green grass
seemed to connect with the sky ♫
Xiao Lu is not here yet?
She will be here later.
You didn't bring an umbrella.
Let's wait together.
It's okay, I'm good.
Let's get an umbrella
from the convenience store.
I promise.
I'll leave after we get the umbrella.
Sorry to trouble you.
It's not troubling at all.
My umbrella is smaller.
You have to stand closer.
Don't wet yourself.
Come on.
It's time to turn left.
We're here. Watch your step.
Okay.
Wait for me.
It always rains lately.
For some odd reason,
it's been raining non-stop this year.
I got you a black umbrella.
Okay.
It's done.
That will be 35 yuan.
Hello, this is the change.
Do you need a towel
or napkins?
It's okay.
I'm good.
You must be too busy
to take care of your friend.
Look at you, you're drenched.
No.
We're not a couple.
Sang Wu Yan.
I'm sorry.
Where can I get towels?
It's just beside the umbrella.
Thank you.
Go get the towel.
I think you have to let go of my hand.
♫ Nothing much to say ♫
♫ I've been waiting for something ♫
♫ It's written in the stars ♫
My goodness.
♫ There's a voice in my ears ♫
I always do this.
♫ Which has been keeping me company ♫
♫ Because of that,
I'm no longer afraid of sunset ♫"
♫ The sun showers deliberately ♫
♫ Drop on my shoulders ♫
♫ I suddenly recall something ♫
♫ I think I heard it somewhere ♫
♫ Subconsciously ♫
[Incoming call from Yu Xiao Lu]
♫ I recognise you ♫
♫ By your astonishing voice ♫
♫ In the next second ♫
Hello?
♫ You look up and smile at me♫
Come out now.
Okay.
♫ You say the lyric is a tongue twist ♫
♫ I quench the galaxy ♫
♫ In dark, naturally ♫
I have to go.
♫ We hug and hold hands ♫
Sure.
♫ I've never spoken my mind ♫
Bye.
♫  But everything has changed ♫
♫ After I met you ♫
♫ Ever since I met you ♫
♫ The starry sky
has always been behind us ♫
♫ Ever since I met you ♫
♫ I learned how to love carefreely ♫
Go get the towel.
♫ I want you to know ♫
♫ You're the only thing I need ♫
♫ Even in exchange
for the entire universe ♫
I saw that lady again.
Is she fond of you?
No.
How do you not?
It's not like you can see...
Perhaps
she admires me just a little.
So, you're Yi Jin in front of her.
You...
♫ Outside the long corridor ♫
♫ Along the ancient road ♫
♫ The green grass
seemed to connect with the sky ♫
♫ The night breeze blew ♫
♫ An old flute resonated melancholically ♫
♫ The setting sun illuminated
mountain by mountain ♫
♫ At the edge of the sky ♫
♫ And the corner of the land ♫
♫ The soulmates parted ways ♫
She is Su Xiao Wei.
[A warm welcome to Caring Enterprise]
When she was six years old,
she lost her parents
in a road accident.
She injured
her eyes in the accident.
Later,
she was sent to the welfare home.
Though she's lost her parents,
the warmth from the society
has made her happy again.
Xiao Wei is currently in Year Three.
She's received lots of attention
and love from her teachers.
Look,
her class teachers are over there.
Well...
Why do they aim their cameras at us?
Just ignore them.
How do I ignore them?
Just look to the front.
Keep your eyes straight.
Think about the time you torture me.
When did I torture you?
[A warm welcome to Caring Enterprise]
Xiao Wei, you must be exhausted.
You did a great job.
You performed
sign language and singing at once.
Do you know?
Mr Su was clapping for you all the time.
Thank you.
Where is Mr Su?
Has he left?
Xiao Wei, we need to go now.
Wu Yan, you may leave now.
It's been a long day.
Go some rest.
Sure.
Xiao Wei, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Ms Sang.
Get some rest.
[It's Yi Jin's song.]
[However, I really have the urge]
[to hug the person in front of me.]
[However, when he left quietly,]
[he made me think that]
[he has an odd temperament.]
[He doesn't usually express his thoughts]
[but he's always the gentle guy,
Su Nian Qin.]
It's me.
I know.
You're right.
I'm too naive.
I...
I can't take on the responsibility  for
the consequences that Xiao Wei may face.
Just like today.
I thought
it would be a cheerful event.
However,
it turned out this way.
Yet, I had no idea
what to do about it.
When I was young,
I had to perform like this too.
Those people
sincerely think that
they're doing charity.
Of course,
I don't deny that.
But they
have no idea what the kids really need.
It's not that they have no idea.
It's more like
they didn't bother to find out.
In front of the kids,
they repeatedly mention
defects,
abandonment and orphans.
They keep reminding the kids
and make them think that
they're inferior to others.
However,
the disabled
are merely those with physical defects.
They're different from other people.
We don't want to be sympathised.
We ask for equality.
Then...
Then, you...
It's okay. It's over now.
[Are you back yet?]
[You said you'd let me clean up
the interview draft tonight.]
[I'll give to you when I'm back.]
[Huh? Where are you right now?]
[I'm still at the museum.]
[It's too remote. I can't get a ride.]
[Send me your location. I'll get
a ride for you.]
[Xu Qian: Contemporary Music Museum]
[Hurry.]
[Xu Qian is stuck in a remote place.]
[Go get her.]
[Wei Hao: Okay]
[Missed call]
Thank you.
It's okay.
It's Wu Yan.
Of course it's her. Isn't it obvious?
Well...
I won't force you
to come back to the band anymore.
But can we still be friends?
Don't feel pressured. I'm not...
Sure, let's be friends again.
[Mum]
Hello, what's wrong?
Stay still.
I'll come now.
Stop following me.
I can go back to the hostel on my own.
Qian Qian.
Why are you here?
I couldn't find you.
I had no choice but to come here.
Why do you come home so late?
I'm too busy.
What's wrong?
Aren't you in Guangzhou?
Were you dumped by that man?
Don't be mean.
We separated on good terms.
Qian Qian.
You...
Do you have money?
[Transferred to Mum]
500 yuan is all I have.
You should at least go home
and pay grandma a visit.
Thank you, love.
Nian Qin.
You told me to investigate that family
and I did.
It's just an ordinary family.
The husband is a doctor
while the wife is working
as an administrator in a company.
Nothing special.
However, due to the wife's health issue,
they don't have any children.
Did they commit any crime
or something bad before?
What do you mean?
They're about to adopt Xiao Wei.
Nian Qin, you're taking it too seriously.
You really care about that young girl.
Are you...
Enough.
Thank you for the help, Xiao Lu.
I should be the one who attends to it.
However, with your company,
I think she'll be more at ease.
Don't worry, Madam Zhang.
We'll keep her company.
When everything is over,
we'll send her back.
Okay, thanks for the help.
Have a safe journey.
Xiao Wei.
We have to go now.
Let's go.
Xiao Wei, were you cold on your way here?
How do you like warm milk?
She's afraid of strangers.
Let's order some food.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Xiao Wei.
Is there anything you want?
How do you like strawberry juice?
Or
do you want some bread?
How about cakes?
Do you want to listen to the radio?
Can you please switch on FM82.4 for me?
I think they're playing
"Xiao Man's After Work Music".
What's wrong?
I'm surprised that
you listen to the radio too.
Moreover, it's a mainstream channel.
Or what?
Is it better to listen to your show?
How do you...
You remember my voice?
That's the only time I hosted
a radio show.
I didn't know that my voice is so special.
♫ The warm sunlight idly crawls into
the window ♫
♫ A faint and tipsy scent of
coffee aroma ♫
Why do you enjoy listening to the radio?
♫ Suddenly you're by my side again ♫
I don't have to watch it.
♫ Smiling as bright as the stars ♫
♫ Turning to the next page
of the storybook ♫
Do you know
why I love listening to the radio?
It's because I hate the sunset.
♫ You said the wind
will dry the tears shed by the clouds ♫
I hate seeing the sun
go down bit by bit.
♫ I asked you
how to console the sighing wind then ♫
Then, one day is gone.
Worse, I haven't completed my tasks.
I choose to close my eyes, put on
headphones and listen to the radio.
♫ You smiled without replying ♫
When I open my eyes again,
the sky has turned dark.
♫ Telling me not to be silly  ♫
It's yet another endless night
for me to waste my time.
♫ Oh clear skies outside the window ♫
♫ Oh yeah ♫
What a fool.
♫ I want to hug you from the back
and never let go of you ♫
Did you just smile?
♫ Why do beautiful things
always make people sad? ♫
No, I didn't.
♫ I'm afraid of you leaving ♫
I swear I saw your smile.
My eyesight is perfect.
♫ Hai yeah ♫
♫ I thought I would see tomorrow's sun ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ The warm sunlight idly crawls into
the window ♫
Therefore,
do you want to ride on the Ferris wheel
with me and Xiao Wei two days later?
♫ A faint and tipsy scent of
coffee aroma ♫
No.
I bet you'll come.
♫ Suddenly you're by my side again ♫
♫ Smiling as bright as the stars ♫
-You...
-Be careful.
We're very close to each other now.
♫ Turning to the next page
of the storybook ♫
♫ You said the wind will dry
the tears shed by the clouds ♫
♫ I asked you
how to console the sighing wind then ♫
♫ You smiled without replying ♫
♫ Telling me not to be silly  ♫
♫ Oh clear skies outside the window ♫
♫ Oh yeah ♫
♫ Perhaps the wind will blow dry
the cloud's tear when she cries ♫
I'm back.
You're back.
It seems that you've thought it through
and decided
to get a master's degree with me.
How is that possible?
Didn't I tell you before?
I'm not getting a master's degree.
What are you doing then?
I'm using science to attract a guy.
I aspire to be
a technical heart stealing thief.
What are you doing?
You're smiling like an idiot.
Su Nian Qin said
"No".
What does that mean?
You've studied psychology
for so many years now
and you use the knowledge on this?
Yes, I've studied psychology
for so many years now.
After a careful analysis,
I obtained the mighty victory
as my bravery overcame my self-knowledge.
He has personality disorder
but I have the knowledge.
You're really something.
However, I have a question.
Why are you referring to
abnormal psychology?
Well...
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Are you not joining them tomorrow?
Aren't you fond of the young girl?
I'm not.
You told me to investigate
the background of the adoptive family.
I guess you like her.
That's why you're concerned about her.
Did I understand it wrongly?
No, I'm not going.
That place is surely crowded.
Moreover, it's not fun.
You've never ridden on a Ferris wheel.
How do you know that it's not fun?
Just join them.
You've never gone on a date.
It's quite rare.
I said, I don't want to go.
Fine.
[Ticket booth]
Xiao Wei.
When we're in the park,
you have to
hold on to me all the time.
If we get separated,
just stand still
and shout my name, okay?
Got it.
Good girl.
You're always careless.
You might not be able
to take care of her. That's why...
Sure.
I'm always careless.
Do you want to go inside?
If you go inside,
I can be your guide.
The park is crowded.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's get the pink one.
Show me.
You look super adorable.
Su Nian Qin.
Lower your head.
What did you call me?
What is this?
It's just Mickey's ears.
What is Mickey?
Su Nian Qin,
you really have no childhood.
You...
Xiao Wei.
Look, do you think
Mr Su looks extra handsome now?
What's so handsome about me?
Xiao Wei, aren't you...
Let's take a ride on the Ferris wheel.
We will have to queue up for a long time.
Let's go.
This is so foolish.
The rain falls on the eaves
and the swallows return.
Ms Sang, what are you saying?
Me?
I'm reciting
the lyrics written by my idol.
Idol?
Who is your idol?
My idol is...
He's a talented songwriter.
♫ I want to see ♫
♫ All the possibilities ♫
♫ Make me believe ♫
♫ You're the only one ♫
♫ Yes I believe ♫
♫ All the promises that you gave ♫
♫ No matter how long the journey is ♫
♫ We'll be together ♫
♫ You're the most reliable ♫
♫ Refuge ♫
♫ You're also my deepest ♫
♫ Secret ♫
♫ In fact, we're indeed very close ♫
♫ to each other ♫
♫ However, it still feel as if
we're separated by glass ♫
Isn't it
usually initiated by men?
What's wrong, Ms Sang?
Nothing.
I think it's gone too high.
How did you know?
Ms Sang.
Did I ever say that I'm blind?
I'm not completely blind.
I can detect movements within three feet.
Now I know that
you're a fan who goes overboard
when you see your idol.
I'm not.
I don't see you as Yi Jin.
To you...
Don't talk too much
in front of the young kid.
Did anything good happen?
Nothing.
Did you have fun with the girl?
What could be so fun about it?
How come you made a mistake?
Did I?
You made a mistake.
Didn't you notice that?
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
Music is meant to express one's feelings.
There is no right or wrong.
It's fine as long as one gets
to express his feelings, isn't it?
Hello, it's me.
Listen.
I think we need to get Nian Qin a doctor.
Go to hell!
Why are you so irritated?
You look as if
you have the early warning signs of mania.
Do you need a check up at the hospital?
Why should I go to the hospital?
He's the one who needs treatment.
I'm so angry!
He did it on purpose.
Otherwise,
why did he voice it out
only when I got so close to him?
It's to make you think that
you've succeeded
and to see you embarrassed yourself.
He's so cunning!
Cunning!
How cunning.
That's not right.
In that case...
Thank you. I can do it.
Is he really blind?
Excuse me, are you Yi Jin?
-You...
-Be careful.
We're so close to each other.
So, he could see all this while.
You've been
embarrassing yourself all this while.
It doesn't matter now.
Why did you say that?
What is so embarrassing about
flirting with him?
I have the courage to own up to it.
The main point is...
What happened?
As you didn't lose your first kiss...
-So...
-Says who?
When did that happen?
Why didn't I know?
She's odd.
Mr Su.
It's like this.
Next week,
Ms Zheng will be back to school.
For some reasons,
she decided to end
her maternity leave early.
Therefore...
Therefore, thank you for your hard work.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you so much
for replacing her.
All the students really like you.
Don't mention it.
Mr Li.
Ms Sang...
Is she here yet?
Wu Yan?
She's on leave today.
She said something happened
at the radio station.
What's wrong? Were you looking for her?
Nothing.
I'll get going then.
I'm curious.
[Engineering Office]
Both of you are in charge of the news.
Sang Wu Yan.
Why weren't you involved in it?
Xu Qian interviewed pedestrians,
-do you know that?
-I...
It's not something serious.
I think it's fine
without that paragraph.
Even though you put in a lot of effort
to prepare for it,
the audience will forget it
as soon as it's over.
-Can you hear yourself?
-How could you say that?
I...
Conduct the interview again.
Before Friday,
make sure you get the material ready.
This is the last chance.
-Thanks.
Let's go.
We'll conduct the interview again.
Don't you have something to do at 4 p.m.?
It's almost time.
That's right.
Go ahead.
I'll visit the site today.
We'll go there together
when the plan is ready.
In that case, I'll get going for real.
If you need my help,
don't hesitate to call me.
All of a sudden,
I have a feeling that
you're back to the old you.
You're crazy.
I'm leaving.
That's not right. Why am I panicking?
He's the one who fooled me.
Su, you're here.
Where is Ms Sang?
She's behind me.
Hello, Madam Zhang.
Hello.
Do you have eyes on your back?