=City of Streamer=
=Episode 22=
Most people think
Australia is desolate, barbarous,
and sparsely populated.
But in Australia,
the vast land
is suitable for livestock grazing.
A terrific amount of wool
is produced every year.
It's cheap, but of good quality.
In my opinion, we can import
a large order of wool from Australia,
find cheap factories in Nanyang
for rough processing
and then transport it back for sale.
The profits will be considerable.
Our company
has a route to the north.
If we form a partnership
and complement each other,
how nice it would be!
Good idea.
You want to develop Nanyang route
while we want
to develop the route to the north.
We quite coincide with each other
in doing business.
Like father, like son.
Your son is a brilliant successor.
I'm afraid you can retire early
and enjoy a happy life ever after.
Let's do it in the Chinese way.
Hope we'll have a good cooperation.
Jiashang, it's been a long time
since we last met.
I remember when you were in Chongqing,
you were quite bad-tempered.
But today, you sweet-talked my father.
Back in Shanghai,
I've got more experienced
and I've restrained myself more.
My sister has been thinking of you.
Why don't you get back together?
My relationship with Shiori is gone.
Everything is possible.
Look.
She has been waiting for you there
for quite a while.
All right.
Have a nice talk.
Jiashang,
you saw the Gold Kylin.
Is it the one you're looking for?
Your father treasures the Gold Kylin.
I offered a high price for it,
but he rejected me immediately.
That's for sure.
Father always thinks
the Gold Kylin is the talisman
for my eldest brother.
He won't sell it to you
unless my eldest brother is dead.
Do you really
want it so much?
Forget it.
After all,
a gentleman doesn't
snatch things from others.
Jiashang,
I promised
that I would help you.
Help me?
Your father treasures the Gold Kylin.
How are you going to help me?
You and I
were in a relationship.
Now, I'm the daughter
of the Hashimoto family.
As long as you call off
your engagement with Miss Du,
I'll persuade my father
to marry me to you
with the Gold Kylin as my dowry.
Your eldest brother can't live
without the Gold Kylin.
How can you persuade your father?
My brother
will not live much longer.
He was born with serious heart disease.
According to the doctor,
he can't be cured without a new heart.
But in this world,
there isn't such a miracle
of medical science.
Today, he struggled to meet the guests.
Usually, he can't even get off the bed.
Otherwise, my brother and I
wouldn't have been taken back,
after we were expelled.
Ma'am has found a new doctor
with excellent medical skills.
After taking the new medicine,
my brother managed to get off the bed.
But I don't think
he will live
much longer.
Shiori,
I used to think
you were a pure and kind girl.
But now,
I realize I'm wrong about you.
Are you saying
we'll wait
until Shiori's eldest brother dies?
According to her,
he won't live much longer.
After he dies,
his father no longer needs
to keep the Gold Kylin.
We can then offer a high price for it.
I don't think he'll reject us.
Why don't we wait a little bit longer?
Don't trust Shiori.
He was said to die before he turned 15.
But he's still alive.
Now, he's said to die
before the Spring Festival.
But maybe he'll survive
for another decade.
Waiting for someone's death
is like waiting for the rain.
If it rains whenever we want it,
what's the point of digging wells?
Are you saying
we'll get the Gold Kylin by ourselves?
Is Meng Xu'an urging us?
Did he set a deadline?
Now that we can't buy it
or wait for it,
we have to steal it
or grab it.
Hashimoto carefully protects
the Gold Kylin.
You witnessed that.
It's not only secretly kept,
but also guarded by private guards.
How can we steal or grab it?
Now that we know
it's in the hand of Hashimoto,
we'll manage to get it.
Why are you ba...?
Mr. Jiashang.
What are you doing here?
The weather is fine today.
Butler Zhang asked us
to clean the guest rooms.
What do you want, Mr. Jiashang?
Nothing.
Oh.
(McTyeire School for Girls)
Don't push, there.
Ladies.
- I saw it.
- I saw it. I saw it.
- Fanglin.
- Mother.
So crowded?
It's so crowded.
(McTyeire School for Girls)
Come on.
Excuse me. Make way, please.
- Make way, please.
- This is great.
- Be careful, Misses.
- I'll go get you something to eat.
All right.
(Admission list of McTyeire School for Girls)
How is it going?
- Are you admitted?
- Am I on the list?
(Rong Fanglin)
Be careful.
I'm not on the list, I guess.
Mother, I'm admitted!
Where's your name?
Look.
Sweetheart,
you're awesome.
I can finally feel relieved.
Mm.
What about you, Fanghua?
I...
Let's keep looking.
(Rong Fanghua)
I was freaked out.
Fanghua, here's your name.
Fanglin, I made it! I made it!
- This is great.
- I'm admitted.
Great. I feel so happy for you.
Mm.
Fanglin, let's go back home
and tell Miss Feng about it.
- Mm.
Go tell Master to come back.
This is great news.
Let's celebrate for the girls.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Go.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Mr. Jiashang.
What about your property at Wenchunli?
Did you sell it?
The ruins
are worthless
and the land is of little value.
You had quite a hard time.
I can't imagine
how you pulled through.
Shixun?
You're off the night shift?
Mm.
I'm going to make bamboo shoot soup.
It tastes best when it's hot.
Shizhen.
Mm?
Why did you quit your job in advance?
The admission list has been published.
Miss Fanglin and Fanghua are admitted.
They no longer need me.
What about the last time?
Why did you quit last time?
Last time?
It was because
Concubine Sun slandered me.
Then I quit my job.
Shixun,
why do you sound so weird?
I don't.
Yesterday, Concubine Sun
came to the hospital.
Her son was sick.
He was?
What's wrong with him?
His fever wasn't gone
before I was off the night shift.
He's detained for observation.
Shizhen,
I've found a job for you in my hospital.
Quite similar to your previous job.
Go to work with me tomorrow morning.
Shixun,
may I
think about it?
Hello.
Mr. Jiashang,
Miss Feng has left her home.
She's taking a rickshaw
to the church in Yang King Pang.
I get it.
Shizhen.
Shixun.
Why did you ask to see me here?
Why can't we talk at home?
Shixun,
I'm sorry.
You got me a job in the hospital.
But after I thought about it,
I decided not to take it.
Fine.
But why?
If I work in the hospital,
I'll only arrange files
or answer the phones.
It's way too boring.
It doesn't work for me.
What works for you, then?
A job in the Rong family,
as the governess for Rong Jiashang?
Shixun,
what makes you say that?
You think I don't know anything
only because you haven't told me?
When Concubine Sun took her son
to see the doctor the other day,
she told me what happened.
She told me
how Rong Jiashang harassed you
and how you were forced
to quit your job.
Shizhen,
you're good at keeping things from us.
Shixun...
Rong Jiashang
is a playboy.
He only flirted with you for fun.
You used to be sensible.
What's wrong with you now?
Are you insane?
Do you not want a good reputation?
Shixun,
you misunderstand
my relationship with him.
I've quit my job already, right?
Trust me.
Fine.
Do you refuse to work in the hospital
because you still want to go back
to the Rong family
and stay with Rong Jiashang?
Do you still
have illusions for him?
Shixun,
he and I are just friends.
He's a rich young man.
But you...
You're a poor governess.
What kind of friends can you be?
The Rongs are going too far.
After he flirted with you,
he just let it go with a rough excuse.
I have to talk to him.
What on earth does he take you for?
Shixun,
don't be mad.
Listen to me.
I'm your brother.
You should listen to me!
Shixun,
I feel
that I've fallen in love with him.
What did you say?
I can't lie to you.
I can't lie to myself, either.
But I indeed fell in love with him.
I tried to stop,
but I realized I couldn't.
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't have loved him.
I've been adjusting my emotions.
But I...
Do you really think
the Rong family is respectable?
It's probably them
who set fire to Wenchunli!
Surprised?
When I heard about it,
I was as surprised as you are now.
She really didn't know that.
Then she had no motive.
But she knows everything now.
How did you know that?
Concubine Sun told me personally.
You can refuse to believe that.
But I believe that.
The Rong family
is renovating Wenchunli.
Can't you figure out the reason?
Think carefully about it, Shizhen.
I don't dare to think too much.
So, you suspected them?
What's worse,
Rong Jiashang has been engaged.
What are you going to do?
To be his concubine?
Shixun,
I haven't thought about that.
Shizhen,
what's gotten into you?
What makes Rong Jiashang so attractive
that you keep sacrificing?
And his family...
They knew you were from Wenchunli
but they still hired you.
Rong Dingkun is quite crafty.
You're no match for him.
For your safety concern,
you must break with Rong Jiashang
and his family.
All right.
I get it.
I'm going back to work.
Think carefully about it.
Reverend,
I want to confess.
God bless you.
I didn't know you came personally.
I haven't seen you for days.
I missed you.
They have left.
If you want to say something,
feel free to say it.
Thank you, Boss.
I think
I must tell you something.
It's about the Gold Kylin.
Rong Dingkun
is quite cunning.
He cut the horsehair.
But in this way,
it can't be sold at a high price.
Actually,
it's not a priceless treasure.
It's just of great significance
to my family.
It's said to be a burial article
of an emperor.
Elders of my family told me about it.
The Gold Kylin
is an auspicious thing
that protects the family.
I heard my family lost it twice
in history.
Every time it was lost,
my family suffered a lot.
Things didn't get better
until it was taken back.
Rong Dingkun
swindled my sister
of the Gold Kylin.
In my family,
accidents happened unexpectedly.
My family members died or left.
Our business suffered
a disastrous decline, too.
But Boss,
you have prospered your family again
without the Gold Kylin.
It proves
that the prosperity of a family
counts on human efforts.
It also depends
on the talent of descendants
and the political situation.
My father and grandfather asked me
to get back the Gold Kylin
before they passed away.
Unexpectedly,
I didn't get any clues
until 17 years later.
It's filial of you, Boss.
By the way,
are you sure
Rong Jiashang will do
what you expect him to do?
He's against Rong Dingkun all the time.
I've just made myself
one of his trophies.
What kind of man
would fight his own father
for a woman only?
He will fight for nothing,
but his freedom and dream.
But your brother misunderstands you.
Have you figured out
how to explain to him?
Thank you for your concern.
As for my brother...
I'll try to explain to him.
You...
Do you really like him so much?
Boss, if you don't mind,
I'll take my leave.
You don't have an appetite?
What?
After you're used to big meals
in the Rong family,
you don't want the simple food?
Big meals
made my stomach churn.
A young lady like me
feels best
to have such simple food.
What happened
between you?
Nothing, Father.
I rejected the job in the hospital.
Shixun felt disgraced
and he's being upset.
The job in the hospital
is steady and decent.
But your sister's will matters most.
Now,
our family
is finally getting together
after all the trouble.
Don't make more trouble.
Mm.
- I won't, Father.
By the way,
now that you don't want
to work in the hospital,
what kind of job would you like?
It's not easy to find a job
before the Spring Festival.
But then I have time
to stay at home
and accompany you and Mother.
Mm.
When looking for a new job,
remove the scales from your eyes
in case you get stuck
and be bullied again.
Who bullied Shizhen?
- No one.
Don't keep anything from me.
We didn't.
Father, it was just a figure of speech.
I wouldn't let anyone bully me,
right?
Here, Father.
Enjoy the food.
Have some vegetables.
All right.
Father, Mother, I'm full.
Mother, I'm on the night shift.
Don't leave the door unlocked for me.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't be exhausted.
Mm.
Mother,
I'll walk him out.
Mm.
- I gotta go.
- Take good care of yourself.
Shixun, Shixun.
Let me take your bag.
(Renshouli)
Shixun.
Are you still angry with me?
Why should I be angry?
You quit your job, didn't you?
What? Are you
still going to be in a relationship
with him?
Shixun,
what are you talking about?
What are you going to do
with Wenchunli?
You want to ask Rong Dingkun
for an explanation?
How?
I don't even have any evidence.
To put it plainly,
Concubine Sun told me about it.
If Rong Dingkun knows
Concubine Sun sold him out,
how will he punish her?
Even if I want to take revenge,
I can't leave her in danger.
But I can't just let it go.
(Yong'anli)
Think about it.
Our house was burned down.
But we're still alive.
However...
Some of our neighbors
lost their family members.
They're still suffering in pain.
They don't even know
who brought such pain to them.
I must
get justice for them.
Shixun,
think carefully about it.
Rong Dingkun is rather powerful
in illegal and legal areas.
Due to the protection
of warlords and politicians,
he managed to keep such a big fire case
from everyone else.
If we fight him,
we'll be like kicking
against the pricks.
When you want to take revenge,
I fully support you.
But before you plan to do anything,
think of our parents
and don't act on impulse.
If you have an idea,
discuss it with me.
What do you say?
I'm in my twenties.
I'm no longer a teenager
who is impulsive and irritable.
I won't get you in bigger trouble
(Yong'anli)
just for quick revenge.
Don't worry.
Mm.
Shizhen,
you stayed in the Rong family
for three months.
What weaknesses does Rong Dingkun have?
As far as I know him,
he cares most
for his reputation.
He's mercenary and lecherous
and has done a lot of bad things.
But he pretends
that he's a decent gentleman.
Unfortunately, he's ill-behaved
and immoral.
So, he failed many things
because of his own problems.
When I was in the Rong family,
I always avoided him
and didn't interact with him too much.
Many people told me
that he likes young schoolgirls
who are submissive and well-educated.
I'm a young schoolgirl.
But my behaviors
never make me
submissive.
Once,
I talked with Miss Fanglin
about the new women stuff.
When he heard us,
he was upset.
So,
at heart,
he's a very conservative man.
What about Rong Jiashang?
What makes you like him?
I didn't like him when I first met him.
When I first taught him,
he didn't obey me at all.
It took me quite a long time
to convince him
so that he took classes regularly.
After I communicated more with him,
I realized
that he was different
from what others
thought of him.
How different?
He's just a spoilt playboy
who can do nothing, isn't he?
Shixun, think about it.
(Yong'anli)
He was brought up by his stepmother.
(Renshouli)
How could he be spoilt?
He's just young
and he's eager to distinguish himself
so that he'll no longer
be taunted by his stepmother
or be controlled by his father.
He goes to extremes
in some cases.
But he isn't a playboy.
What's more,
he's very clever and talented.
He's just keeping a low profile.
He doesn't want to take over
his family business, either.
He only wants to join the army.
You speak so highly of him.
Of course.
He has shortcomings, too.
No man is perfect.
He's in his early twenties, anyway.
I don't mean to praise him.
I just don't want you
to misunderstand him.
What about
his flirting with you?
He was quite innocent.
He was drunk that day
and talked to me when staggering.
Maids of his family saw us.
To stir up trouble,
they shouted out.
We were both embarrassed.
Without another option,
he took the blame forcibly.
His father scolded him,
but he didn't complain.
So, you fell in love with him?
It's not the exact reason.
After we communicate more,
I realize
that he's a lonely man.
What's rare,
he has a pure heart.
He's sincere to me, too.
At first,
I was attracted
by his intelligence and talent.
Later,
I had pity for his loneliness.
Besides,
he indeed looks handsome.
So,
it's because he's handsome?
Come on, girl.
You're quite...
Shixun, do you dare to say
that you don't like beautiful girls?
You've got girls since you were little
and when you were in college.
They're all beautiful, aren't they?
It's just history.
Now, I've grown up.
I'll no longer
be attracted by appearance.
Instead, I value more
over a girl's character, knowledge,
and manners.
But Shixun,
you and Rong Jiashang
haven't contacted too much.
You don't know him very well.
So,
how do you know
if I have judged him correctly?
You have a prejudice
against him, don't you?
He's Rong Dingkun's son, anyway.
How do you expect to end up with him?
You make sense.
(Yong'anli, Renshouli)
(Red House Hospital)
Shizhen.
Oh, superstar.
You look so fashionable.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take a few shots
in the movie set.
What about you?
Are you sick?
No.
I brought lunch to my brother.
I'm glad you're not sick.
These days,
I've been expecting to dine with you.
What do you think of my new car?
It's my birthday present from Boss.
It looks great.
Come on. Get in the car.
Let me drive you.
Mm.
Be careful.
Shizhen.
Get out of my way.
I miss you a lot.
Your father
had Wenchunli burned down,
right?
I didn't mean to keep it from you.
I just got to know that.
These days,
I've been thinking
about your family business.
I don't know how to explain it.
I'm afraid that you may hate me.
But I also want to push my luck
and I wish you didn't know it.
There's no absolute secret.
If I didn't know it,
would you keep it from me forever?
I don't know.
I'm selfish.
It's already hard to have you.
I don't want any other trouble.
Have you thought about the consequences?
If I really got to know that
after we were in a relationship,
what would I do?
I have.
But whether you know it or not,
we can't be in a relationship.
But when I keep it from you,
you won't hate me at least.
Are you going
to defend your father forever?
No.
He has done all kinds of evil.
And he'll get what he deserves.
I enjoy the wealth he gets from evil.
I'll be punished, too.
Everything is fair.
I never mean to speak in defense of him.
I just don't want him
to influence our relationship.
But looks like
it's too late to explain.
You have reasons to hate me.
I don't hate you.
I just don't know what to do.
You saw my father.
You saw the ruins of Wenchunli, too.
My father survived luckily.
But many neighbors
have lost their families
in the fire.
The fire is like a pain in the neck
between us.
How can we be in a relationship?
Your feelings for me
move me a lot.
Since I was born,
you're the first man
who has had such true love for me.
Everybody wants
a simple, peaceful, and sweet life.
But destiny makes fools of us.
Troubles come one after another.
So, Jiashang,
give up.
Why must you live a thorny life,
instead of having a bright future?
But in love,
we can't stop just as we wish.
I don't want it.
I love you,
as if I were going crazy
and as if you cast a spell on me.
I don't want to give up like this.
What do you want, then?
Let's try
if we can find out a way
to make you not hate me.
All right.
Ask your father
to apologize in the newspaper,
admit what he has done,
surrender himself to the police
and compensate the victims.
If he can do that,
I'll no longer
hate your family.
We can be in a relationship, too.
But the problem is...
Can he do that?
That day, you also told me
you wanted
to break off your engagement.
It was a beautiful plan.
But you failed to do it.
Because you're Rong Dingkun's son.
You share the benefits of your family.
You won't hurt yourself just for love.
Is this what you think of me?
I'm a weak and useless man
who keeps lying.
You're just too young and inexperienced.
And you said something
ten years earlier.
Jiashang,
we didn't meet at the right time.
♪The perplexity that binds me♪
♪Be activated by reality♪
You still have my word.
Give me more time.
I said I wouldn't let you down
and I'll keep my promise.
♪Like countless hidden hands♪
You have my word, too.
I never wait deliberately.
Besides, the case of Wenchunli
isn't that simple.
♪The deeper I get stuck♪
I'll take revenge by myself.
Shizhen,
don't do stupid things.
You don't know my father very well.
He's far more merciless
than he appears to be!
♪I want to pretend it never happened♪
I'm more merciless
than I appear to be, too.
♪Whenever I want to escape from you♪
♪I'll lock the memories♪
♪Somehow there are hands♪
♪Pulling my heart back♪
Bro,
I know you feel bad.
Cheers.
Let's drown the sorrow.
(Tianchan Ballroom)
She said I'm too young
and inexperienced,
and I'm not capable enough.
Actually, when I'm being cruel,
I can do anything.
♪Different emotional stresses♪
♪Drown us♪
Bro,
a father picks up the pieces
for his son.
But you have to do that for your father.
♪However dangerous the future can be♪
Yunchi.
♪I won't yield♪
Is there a way
to make her no longer hate me
without hurting my family?
I can't think of any.
♪No need to escape♪
♪In the next moment♪
You're right.
It's a deadly feud.
There's no way
to get the best of both worlds.
♪It's like thousands of arrows
penetrated my heart♪
I'm just too naive
and greedy.
♪I want to pretend it never happened♪
No wonder she never trusts me.
♪You are everything I want♪
♪Whenever I want to escape from you♪
♪I'll lock the memories♪
♪Somehow there are hands♪
♪Pulling my heart back♪
Shizhen.
Shizhen?
Shixun.
What's wrong?
Why are you staring blankly alone?
If I don't stare alone,
shall I stare with a lot of people?
Don't be glib-tongued.
What?
Shizhen,
have you read today's newspaper?
Not yet.
(Rong Dingkun burned down Wenchunli
after failing to acquire it.)
(It was then sold at the lowest price.)
It's the news
on all today's newspapers.
Read this.
And this.
All reports are about the fire.
The reports
are well-founded and logical.
Some certain insider
must have told the reporters about it.
Oh, Shizhen,
you've stayed in the Rong family
for several months.
Who do you think it can be?
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪