[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 22]
[Gu's Group]
Come in.
Mr. Gu,
They know it's Yu Jia who did it.
What are we gonna do?
Stupid!
I need you to destroy everything
about her.
Be quick!
Yes.
[Nanxi City Hospital Out-patient Building]
I have something very sweet to tell you.
Come here.
From now on,
except me,
don't worry about anything else.
It's finally over.
Yu Jia also promised to turn herself in.
Unfortunately,
from now on,
I lost another family member.
No everyone is worth cherishing.
Don't be so upset.
Yu Jia is a silly girl.
She knew Gu Yan didn't love her,
but she still insisted that
she did everything
and it had nothing to do with Gu Yan.
She's ended up like this.
And Auntie Lan was still in bed.
I...
Come here.
I know that
you're very much emotionally attached to Auntie Lan,
and you care about Yu Jia.
But that's the way life is.
Everyone's experience is different
and so are their choices.
No matter how good a friend is,
now matter how good a lover is,
they're just passing through.
If only
none of these had happened.
What are you afraid of?
Even when the sky falls,
I'll be the one who hold it up for you.
But I'm afraid
one day you will leave me too.
I lost you seven years ago.
Seven years later,
you came back to me.
I think
it's a gift from God
so I can spend the rest of my life
making it up to you.
So,
no matter what happens,
I'm
not gonna let go of your hands.
Chris.
Bei Bei.
Were you a good student today?
Did you get along with your friends?
Bei Bei.
Can you stop nagging me?
Women are always nagging,
and we guys are under a lot of pressure.
Kid,
you're really a big man!
It's my turn.
Childish!
Aren't you ashamed?
I'm still here!
Aren't you a big man?
How did you get hugged and kissed?
Did you do your homework?
You guys keep going.
I'll go first.
Hello, the number you dialed is busy.
Please try again later.
[Gu Yan The other party has turned on friend verification, and you're not his friend.]
[Police]
Jiajia.
Sister.
Take care of master.
Auntie Lan and I will wait for you.
Chris and I will always be with you.
I want to meet Gu Yan.
I...
I know what you‘re trying to say.
You can't say no
and you can't be jealous.
Fine.
Then I'll go with you.
I won't let you
out of my sight again.
I thought
you two got divorced
because of emotional discord.
I didn't expect it was a setup
to catch the mole.
I also didn't expect my most trusted friend,
a man who I thought of integrity,
would be so vile to use a woman to achieve his goal.
Maybe he was forced to do that.
Gu Yan.
I can't figure it out.
You framed Gu Chengze to be in charge of Gu's Group.
But why did you frame Lu Nan?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't know or you don't want to know?
Until now,
you still refuse to admit it.
Su Bei.
What exactly do you want me to admit?
Yu Jia pled guilty to everything for your sake.
And you are pretending
you know nothing here.
Don't you feel guilty?
Yu Jia?
Isn't Yu Jia the tailor in your team?
I've only met her a few times.
What does she have to do with me?
If anything,
it's just a friend of a friend.
I don't understand why you would suspect me.
Did you misunderstand me about something?
Before I came here today,
I thought
you might be forced to do it.
But now it looks like
I was wrong.
You better watch out.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
I didn't expect that as soon as the company went public,
our stocks were soaring.
The stocks on offer
were snapped up overnight.
Isn't that what we have been expecting?
What's so happy about it?
If you have time,
take a look at this.
What's wrong?
I'm OK.
Blood clots have been affecting me
more and more frequently recently.
Your illness can't be delayed any longer.
You have to listen to the doctor and have the operation as soon as possible.
No.
You didn't want to have the surgery before
because the company was going public.
Now that the company is listed,
what excuses do you have?
I'm gonna tell Su Bei
and let her persuade you.
Don't tell her.
Why can't I tell her?
Too many things have happened.
She's already very upset.
I don't want her to worry about me anymore.
But you are husband and wife.
You should face difficulties together.
I don't think Su Bei wants to be kept in the dark.
Wait.
You want to take everything on yourself
like you did seven years ago?
Yun Fan,
I want to be nice to her
while I can still see.
I want to give her a happy life
without burdens.
This is what I owe her.
I have to pay it back.
OK.
But you have to give me a time.
When I clear the way,
Su Bei
can take over Eminence.
Thank you,
Yu Fan.
When things are over,
you and Ye Ting will get together, right?
Come on.
I will wait until your condition is stable.
Yun Fan,
will you do me one more favor?
I forgot
what Su Bei looked like when she married me.
Before I do the surgery,
let me see it again.
No problem.
[LOVE]
[Seeing you exhausted, my heart aches.]
🎵 In the mist, your silhouette 🎵
🎵is far and near.🎵
[Seeing you exhausted, my heart aches.]
🎵 I'm right behind you,🎵
[I like your gentleness and manners.]
🎵 being so careful.🎵
[I love dearly your toughness.]
🎵 Like a faint light, 🎵
[I like the way when you're working.]
🎵 I hold you in my palm. 🎵
[I like your subtle gentleness.]
🎵 I'm afraid that🎵
🎵 I may lose you. 🎵
Do you like it?
🎵 The road home 🎵
I like it very much.
🎵 is cold and quiet. 🎵
🎵 The shadows under the street lamps 🎵
Ms. Su Bei,
🎵 fade away. 🎵
I know there are a lot of things
I don't do well.
🎵 Cold air is coming. 🎵
But I will try.
I'll try to do my best.
🎵 Leaves are falling. 🎵
🎵 When I turn around, 🎵
I can't promise to love you forever,
🎵 I wish I could see you. 🎵
because forever is too long.
But I can promise you that
as long as I live,
🎵 We're both glad, 🎵
I'll love you.
🎵 thinking it's better to have than to lose. 🎵
I know
it wasn't very pleasant
🎵 We naively let down our guard 🎵
when we met again.
🎵 and open our hearts. 🎵
So,
can you give me another chance
🎵 If we go back where we were, 🎵
to start over?
🎵 will we meet again? 🎵
Hello.
🎵 Will we still let waiting become an addiction? 🎵
My name is Lu Nan.
I am 29 years old.
Will you please marry me?
🎵 I can't figure out the ending yet. 🎵
🎵 I thought the story would continue. 🎵
🎵 Watching you leave, 🎵
Will you?
🎵 I lie to myself 🎵
🎵 that there's nothing I can do. 🎵
🎵 And I can't bear to hear from you anymore. 🎵
🎵 I'm rational, but missing has become an addiction. 🎵
[ONLY LOVE]
Stop it.
Let's go to work.
I‘m the boss.
Can I skip the work today?
Yes, you can.
But the employees will think,
the company just went public and the boss is not doing his work;
so will the stock I bought fall?
Will I lose my job?
Will the original shares I bought depreciate?
Yun Fan will think:
will my lazy boss
send me to Africa?
My wife is a workaholic.
Looks like I can retire
and enjoy the life.
No way.
I'm telling you.
As long as we don't catch the big boss,
we can't be at ease at all.
So,
get up and fight, Mr. Lu!
Come here.
Don't worry.
I've got a plan.
Gu Yan will be brought to justice.
Trust me.
Then...
You don't think about retirement anymore?
Last night was a little exhausting.
I'll go to sleep.
Then you go to bed.
I have to work.
You...
Hello.
Yun Fan,
are you there?
OK.
Wait a minute.
Hello.
It's Su Bei.
Ms. Su, there was an accident at the Environmental Clothing warehouse.
[Environmental Clothing Materials Warehouse]
Mr. Yun,
this is our biggest banquet hall.
Have a look first.
OK, thanks.
Take your time.
I think.
We can set up
a flower door there.
And,
here,
roll out the red carpet.
And,
do you want a round stage over there?
I saw other couples having round stages.
Couples can stand on it and worship each other,
with guests on both sides.
And we're gonna have a buffet reception.
Everyone is in their evening gowns,
chatting over red wine and champagne.
Can you be more tacky?
How's that tacky?
Ye Ting said she liked that
European
and exotic style.
It's me who get married,
not you and Ye Ting.
This is your second marriage.
Why do you care?
Or,
what about a group wedding?
It's very popular now.
Ye Ting and I can join too.
I'll pay for your wedding.
You'll find your own venue.
OK.
Let's go.
I'll take you back to the company now.
You go back to the company,
and I go to the factory to find Su Bei.
Didn't you just meet?
You want more?
Dirty.
I'm picking up my wife
and we're gonna have dinner with our son.
You have been married for seven years.
No more PDA please.
Fei.
What do you want?
Lu Nan and I will give you everything you ask for.
You and Lu Nan?
How dare you mention Lu Nan!
Fei.
This is warehouse.
Nothing can go wrong with these orders.
Calm down and put the lighter down.
Are you scared?
So you have things you're afraid of being destroyed, huh?
Fei.
Stay calm.
There's nothing
we can't talk about.
I have nothing to say to you.
You destroy my family.
How I wish I could have a family.
You destroyed my family
that I loved for more than ten years.
Don't you think you should pay for it?
Is there anybody?
Is anybody there?
Why can't I open this door?
Is there anybody in there?
Hello?
Anybody?
Is there anybody in there?
What are we gonna do?
What happened?
I don't know.
The door of the warehouse was suddenly locked,
and there is a smell of gasoline in it.
Is there anybody in there?
Su Bei, are you there?
Su Bei!
Is there anybody?
I can't open it!
Say something!
Is there anybody in there?
Why don't you say anything?
You are afraid to get Lu Nan into trouble?
I'm the one you hate.
There's no need to get him involved.
I do hate you,
but I also admire your courage.
The buck stops here.
Today you and I,
we two
will die here together.
Lu Fer'er!
Stop!
Put it down.
Get out!
It's none of your business.
Su Bei will die with me!
I gave you chance,
but you didn't get it.
You're hopeless!
Let Su Bei go.
You want to die?
I'll die with you.
I don't want you dead.
I only want you to love me.
Only love me.
As long as,
as long as you promise me now
that you'll leave Su Bei
and stay with me
forever,
I'll let her go.
And we'll leave here
like nothing ever happened.
We'll travel around the world
and never come back.
I have disowned you.
You're not my sister anymore.
And there's no way I'll be with you.
Lu Fei'er,
you end up like this.
It makes me feel terrible.
Lu Nan, stop talking.
I don't want to be your sister at all!
I just want to marry you!
What did I do
to make you hate me so much?
Fei,
calm down.
I'll convince your brother to let you go home.
You'll always
be a part of our family.
Shut up!
It's your fault!
If you die,
maybe everything will go back to the past.
No, Fei.
Lu Nan.
Su Bei!
Go to hell!
Come on!
Brother!
Lu Nan!
Be quick!
Brother!
Be careful.
Slow down.
He's my brother! Get off me!
I need to talk to him!
Brother!
Lu Nan!
Lu Nan, why did you save me? Lu Nan!
Lu Nan.
Lu Nan, hang in there, Lu Nan.
Lu Nan!
[Emergency]
[Nanxi City Hospital]
[Seven years ago]
Here.
Can any of you explain to me
[Su Bei Zhao Rui]
why these two drafts
are so similar?
I trust Su Bei.
Grandma,
if you trust me,
stop questioning her.
I didn't copy it.
My original sketches are all here.
[To my lover: Mr. Lu Costume Design Sketch Date: August 3, 2012]
Why did you send me away?
She's dead.
How can you prove your innocence?
If you stay here, all you can get will be criticism.
[Divorce Agreement]
Su Bei!
[Su Bei]
Don't go!
I'll find you!
Lu Nan.
Nan Nan.
Answer me if you wake up.
Don't scare grandma.
Bei Bei.
I...
I'm here.
Su Bei,
sorry.
I shouldn't have insisted on sending you away.
The charge of plagiarism hurt you a lot.
I should have let you stay,
protected you
and comforted you.
I shouldn't have been so greedy,
thinking that I could save Eminence's reputation
by sending you away.
I should have proved your innocence to everyone
in the first place.
I tried to stop you.
I went to the airport for you.
But I...
I forgot about you.
I shouldn't
have left you alone in Italy for seven years.
I shouldn't...
And I shouldn't have doubted you
after you came back.
I shouldn't...
Sorry.
Stop talking.
It's all over.
Aren't we
all fine now?
From now on,
Chris and I will be there for you.
You...
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I think I just woke up,
so I'm a little dizzy.
I...
I'm a little hungry.
Fine.
Grandma will go home and make you something to eat.
What do you want to eat?
I want some of grandma's soup.
OK.
Su Bei.
Why don't you go back and help grandma?
Chris is at home with grandma.
I'm worried.
Are you all right?
Hurry up.
How are you doing?
Are you really all right?
Yun Fan,
I...
can't see anything.
[Nanxi City Hospital]
[Diagnostic Analysis: The blood clots are affected by the external force,
and the disease is getting worse, accompanied with blindness. ]
Judging from the results of the scan,
the blow to the head
exacerbated the whole condition.
And the clots now are
pressing against the nerves in the brain.
The temporary loss of vision after you woke up
was mainly caused
by emotional fluctuations.
How do you feel now?
It's blurry,
but I can still see something.
Do the surgery as soon as possible.
You can't wait any longer.
I have to think about
the surgery.
Director Wu,
can you keep a secret for me?
There's nothing to think about.
Bro,
I won't listen to you this time.
Director Wu,
we can...
Thank you, Director Wu.
Let's go.
Actually,
we can find
an internationally renowned doctor to do the surgery.
With his/her competence,
we can minimize the risk.
I know you're worried about me.
But you know,
the Gu's Group
is eyeing Eminence now.
If anything happens to me,
there's gonna be chaos in Eminence.
How can you bear
to see me give away
what I've worked so hard for?
Don't worry.
Even if I risk my life,
I'll keep Eminence safe for you.
As a friend,
you've done enough.
Thank you.
Don't change the subject.
You didn't do the surgery
because of Su Bei?
Our relationship
is still unstable.
After everything we have been through,
I don't know how to tell her.
What if
something happens during the surgery and I can't wake up?
I don't want her to be restrained by our relationship.
When a married couple has difficulties ahead,
they should overcome them together.
You two were separated for seven years because of misunderstandings.
Do you want another seven years like that?
Su Bei
is a woman who can stand by you.
And she's not as fragile as you think.
Don't tell her yet.
Don't tell me what?
What's going on with him?
He's all right.
The latter stage
may need
a longer period of observation.
During this period of time,
don't
provoke him again.
Doctor.
Thank you. Thank you.
Before,
I‘ve heard that
President Guo's business skill
is first-class.
I didn't expect
your golf skill is also first-class.
Whoever plays with you in the future
will be under a lot of pressure.
Mr. Gu,
you're kidding.
I'm not even
close to you.
Mr. Guo is too modest.
Mr. Gu's is usually very busy.
So I'm sure that you've invited me here
not because
you just want to play golf, right?
Mr. Guo is really straightforward.
Well, I'll be straightforward, too.
I asked you out today
because, first, I'd like to make friends with you.
Second,
I'd like to help you get Eminence.
Mr. Gu, you've got to be kidding.
I‘m just a small stakeholder of Eminence.
I'm not that ambitious.
Mr. Guo,
It's only you and me here.
Don't be nervous.
I just want to know:
are you really willing to take a back seat?
Mr. Gu,
what do you want?
It's nice to talk to smart people.
My request is very simple.
Destroy the hero,
and win the beauty.
I'm sure you've heard a lot about
Su Bei and me.
Yes.
I have a crush on her.
And my brother
was framed by Lu Nan.
Our family
can't just take such an insult.
That's why I came to you.
I want to work with you
to take over Eminence.
In this way,
you'll not only receive more money.
Maybe,
there will be more surprises.
This
is not easy.
You see,
Eminence is on a roll now.
Taking it down won't be easy.
But you will help me with it, right?
Let's go.
[How to treat the sequela of a cerebral hemorrhage in a car accident?]
How's it going?
Is it serious?
But Lu Nan still won't tell me the truth.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Yes.
Then,
I need you to get Yun Fan out of there.
If he's there, I can't get any information from Lu Nan.
Don't worry.
Looks like
he's willing to do whatever you tell him.
Are you sure you want to be with him?
N...
Not yet.
I don't like him.
He's short, stupid and weak.
He's too easy to deal with.
Silly,
if he doesn't like you,
how could you do that to him?
He has dignity too!
Yezi,
it's not easy to meet someone you like.
When you have it, cherish it.
I regret that
there were so many misunderstandings between Lu Nan and I
that we wasted so many years.
Never mind.
I'll read it to you.
It says...
Come out.
I need to talk to you.
No.
Mr. Lu wants to see me,
right?
Yes.
Yun Fan has something to tell me.
What are you doing?
Ye Ting won't hurt him.
Besides,
it's their relationship,
and you can't meddle in it.
Mr. Lu.
Yes.
Come out.
Lu Nan, what kind of friend are you!
This is the follow-up cooperation contract
with Sia.
If there's no problem, just sign it.
Well,
I've been reading just now,
so my eyes don't feel good.
Can I take a break first?
This is urgent.
Just sign it,
if there's no problem.
Done.