♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 8=
Xiaosu,
I personally
admit your working ability,
but it's really inappropriate for me
to interfere with personnel transfer.
Mr. Ning, sorry for the inconvenience.
But I need money for urgent use.
These 30 days mean a lot to me.
I'm willing to work in any position
only if you can put me in one,
only if I can make money.
There's indeed one position open.
Then, please let me do it.
It is supervising the construction site
of the Entertainment Center.
Think it over.
Working on construction site means
working in all weathers
from dawn to dusk,
together with the workers.
Can you manage that as a girl?
Yes, I can. Don't worry.
And this job pays quickly,
which is exactly what I'm looking for.
Mr. Lei,
would you like to visit the sales office
where you can see the whole view
through sand table?
Yes.
Please.
OK.
Mr. Lei,
that girl just showed up a moment ago.
This time she didn't insist to come in
and just stood there
staring at the building.
So I didn't send her away.
Manager Li,
take Mr. Li and Mr. Wang
to take a look at the sand table.
I will be there later.
OK.
Mr. Li, Mr. Wang, this way please.
Excuse me.
See you later.
Miss Du,
what a nice mood you have.
You even have time to stand here
looking at the view.
I'm curious how things are going
with gathering money for the house.
Mr. Lei, it has been only 2 days.
Don't tell me that you are going to
go back on your word.
Why would I?
As long as you are not
giving up in the middle.
Miss Du, once the time limit is up,
and you have all the money,
I would for sure hand over the house.
Of course,
if you cannot last any longer,
I'd love to accept your defeat.
Watching me suffer
must be very relieved for you.
Actually, it feels good
to have one more person hating me.
Being hated means that
someone still cares
about your existence.
Then remember this hatred.
At least,
it can make you live more easily.
Don't worry.
It doesn't matter how hard it is,
for this gambling,
I will stay until the end
and never give up.
Please wait for my good news.
Recruitment.
Miss Du.
Don't force yourself.
Don't wear yourself out.
Siqi,
do you have any part-time job
that you can introduce me to?
It won't help
even if I introduce you to 10 jobs.
How could you gather millions of yuan
within such short time?
I'm telling you that
you can fight against Lei Yuzheng
as you wish.
But you cannot fight against god
or your life.
But I don't have any other choice.
One of my friends operates a bar
at the Bund.
I heard that it's doing really good
and the payment is good too.
I will ask for you.
Thanks.
Hi, I'm a friend of Zou Siqi.
She should have told you about me,
right?
Yes.
Here's my resume.
We don't look at resume here.
You only need to
answer one question.
Can you drink a lot?
You are such a direct person.
Although I cannot drink,
I can sell.
When I was in college,
I sold phones in a hypermarket
and used to rank 1st place every month.
I was just wondering
if one can earn a lot
by selling alcohol.
Yes, if you work really hard.
How about this?
You come here tonight and give it a try.
All right,
I will be here on time for sure.
Thank you.
Here, dad.
See, there's no place better than home.
The inpatient ward is big enough,
but the sanitizer smell makes me
lose all my appetite.
Here, dad. Try this fish.
The doctor said that
fish can help with recovering the brain.
Yuzheng,
after I got sick, I realized that
it's useless to pretend to be strong.
After working so hard for decades,
it's time when I should accept my fate.
It's good to see you
making progress so fast.
I feel relieved
trusting Yutian to you.
Dad,
Yutian is what you've built for life.
I'm only taking care of it for you.
Everyone is waiting for you to go back
after you feel better.
You don't have to comfort me.
I know that
Yutian is doing well
under your management.
And the Entertainment Center project
is going to have its
foundation-stone laying ceremony soon.
Those stakeholders don't say it aloud,
but I can tell that
they admire you sincerely.
Mr. Lei.
Same as always, two glasses of Brandy.
OK.
Bad guy, since when did you go to a bar?
A doctor
also needs relaxation sometimes.
Their Whiskey tastes really good.
Try it.
Just tell me what it is.
Why does there have to be something
for us to have a drink?
I know you too well.
That's why I take you as my brother.
Let's cheer first.
Let me take it.
Mr. Shangguan,
how about this?
I will take 3 more glasses
and you buy three more bottles.
Miss Du,
how about you finish this bottle and
I will buy all the alcohol.
All.
You drank too much.
Brother Lei.
Who are you?
I don't know you.
Move.
Shangguan,
you can't fool me.
You never planned to buy the alcohol.
Well, well.
What are you doing?
I haven't finished my drink.
Leaving now.
Put me down.
Lei Yuzheng, put me down.
Why would you bother with me?
Because you owe me.
I owe you?
I have nothing left now.
Put me down.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am crazy.
I have been crazy for a long time.
Did you just realize that I'm crazy?
I,
I don't have a lover
or a job,
not even the house anymore.
I'm a crazy person with nothing left.
Why would you bother?
You should've left me alone.
I'm just a lonely soul,
who can die anywhere.
No one should bother with me.
Let me go.
You think that I want to bother?
If it's not for Shao,
for him,
I would not care
whether you die or live.
Du Xiaosu,
who do you want to show it to
by acting like this?
Do you think that I would give you
the key to the house
if you drink to death today?
Of course not,
because you hate me,
and you are dying to see me
losing the deal.
Do you think that I don't feel any pain?
He's gone,
and my heart is gone too.
Have you ever seen a person
without heart?
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
I'm that kind of person,
like the zombie in the movies,
like those ghosts.
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
Stand up.
Come on.
Du Xiaosu,
do you think that people will pity you
if you treat yourself like this
every day?
I'm telling you
that it's not only you who's in pain.
Lei Yuzheng,
you are painful?
Do you have heart?
There's only a rock here,
a cold rock with no temperature at all.
Have you ever felt painful?
Lei Yuzheng, let me go.
Where are you taking me?
You said that you are ghost,
and I'm taking you
to release your soul from suffering.
Lei Yuzheng, I'm not going with you.
Lei Yuzheng, I can't go with you.
Let me out.
Lei Yuzheng, let me out of the car.
Where are you taking me,
Lei Yuzheng?
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you want to vomit.
Du Xiaosu, I'm warning you.
Swallow it if you want to vomit.
If you vomit in my car, I...
♪Frantic pursuit of the marks
on the chest♪
♪The one and only in destiny♪
Give me water.
Open it.
Here you are.
♪The pain on the back
and the marks on the chest♪
♪Continue to indulge in the dream♪
Lei Yuzheng,
I never imagined that one day
I can torture you like this.
It feels so good.
Psycho.
Lei Yuzheng, stop pretending.
Although you look like a person
in front of other people,
you are actually the same kind of person
as I am.
You think that
you are not a lonely ghost?
You are exactly like me,
half dead inside.
Have you cried at night?
Have you woken up
in the middle of night?
Have you ever thought about
what are you living for?
Lei Yuzheng, I think that
both of our lives suck.
The person we love the most is now gone.
The most important part of heart
became empty.
It's like carrying ruins in the heart
while living our lives every day.
Don't you think that we are funny?
Where do you live?
What?
Why?
Did I say it right?
I know I was right.
Don't worry, Mr. Lei.
I won't tell anyone.
When the sun rises tomorrow,
you are still Mr. Lei, the president
in exquisite suits.
No one would dig up into your surface
or discover what's hidden inside.
Again,
where do you live?
Or I can just throw you on the street?
Du Xiaosu.
Lei Yuzheng,
why are you taking your clothes off?
What?
Lei Yuzheng,
Lei Yuzheng, I'm telling you,
don't do anything stupid.
Lei Yuzheng, don't come here.
What are you doing?
Are you going to harass me?
Lei Yuzheng,
I will sue you for harassing me.
You... let me go.
What are you doing, Lei Yuzheng?
I
harass you?
Look at the mirror.
Who would do this to himself?
Harassing you
whose hair is
as messy as shredded squid?
You wish!
Lei Yuzheng, what are you doing?
Wake up.
Gu,
send some clean women clothes
to my apartment.
Size?
How do I know the size?
Mr. Lei,
here's the clothes you asked for.
Thanks.
So pretty.
The whole Huangpu river.
I can see the whole Huangpu river
from here.
It's so cool.
When can I
have such luck
to sleep here?
Miss Du,
are you planning to leave
without saying anything?
Mr. Lei,
I'm sorry.
I should go back now.
Oh,
I will return this clothes to you
another day.
Do you want to leave?
OK.
But you might not be able to get a taxi
now.
I'll take bus.
The earliest bus would arrive
in an hour.
If you still want to leave,
please go ahead.
Eat something first.
What?
You dare not?
Don't worry, no poison.
Last night, Miss Du
told me many things
from your heart.
Mr. Lei, it was an accident.
If I said anything weird,
I apologize.
Talking about weird stuff
is not a big deal,
but acting recklessly is.
You were lucky to meet me.
If it was someone else,
you might have been robbed or harassed.
Mr. Lei, I'm not a three-year-old girl.
Who are you trying to scare
by saying that?
I really appreciate that
you saved me in the bar,
but you shouldn't scold me
just because you did something right.
Besides,
I didn't ask you to do that.
You should've just left me alone.
You think that I wanted to bother?
I'm done.
Xiaosu,
here is your reward.
Take it.
This much?
Too much for you?
Then I will switch to
a smaller package for you.
Never too much.
Thank you, boss.
You're welcome.
You were such a topic last night.
The sales last night
was more than what we sold in a week.
Keep going and we will pay you well.
OK.
Thank you, boss.
Young lady, it is you.
You haven't been here for a while.
Why are you here so early today?
(Wishing wall)
(Du Xiaosu is piggy Du)
Why are you giving me this pig?
Because you are piggy Du.
But don't worry,
even if you really become a pig one day,
I will not leave you.
You are more like a pig.
Who did you say is pig?
Mr. Lei.
OK, thank you, Mr. Lei.
Anything else?
Mr. Lei,
I heard that
the Entertainment Center project
is going to kick off soon, right?
You are well informed.
Why?
It seems that Mr. Lin doesn't trust us.
No,
Mr. Lei, that's not what I mean.
The Entertainment Center
is just a small project for Yutian.
Mr. Jiang and I
feel very assured.
I was just wondering,
since it's quite a big news
to start construction,
why don't we make some noise?
You and Mr. Jiang?
Mr. Lin,
shouldn't the ranking be re-ordered?
It's none of my business,
but I would love to know,
Mr. Lin,
what kind of noise do you want to make.
Mr. Lei, you got me wrong.
It was a slip of the tongue.
I just want to know about the noise.
Tell me about it.
I'm thinking that
we can have an opening ceremony
where we invite all the social elites
as well as media.
As soon as the news release comes out,
everyone would know that,
you, Mr. Lei,
have made a great achievement
for Yutian,
so that the stock price of Yutian
may keep increasing.
Why didn't I figure that out earlier.
Mr. Lin, you are such a talent.
I'm flattered.
Then I want to ask,
Mr. Lin,
is this idea actually helping me
or ruining me?
Brother Xie,
Lei Yuzheng really doesn't buy it.
Why?
I said a lot to convince him,
but the opening ceremony wouldn't work.
He rejected it
and blamed me.
I've told you
that Lei Yuzheng is very low key.
I've found the people,
and you can just sit and wait.
Be careful, Xie.
Don't make troubles for me.
Right there.
Let's stop here, stop, stop.
Stop working,
unless you want to be a cripple.
Supervisor Du, something happened.
Engineer Wang,
a bunch of people coming from nowhere
wouldn't let us work
and said they would break the arms
of anyone who dares to work.
What shall we do?
Leave your work for now and follow me.
Quickly.
Let's get armed. Let's go.
Quickly, run!
But I would love to know,
what kind of noise do you want to make.
I think that we can
have an opening ceremony
where we invite all the social elites
as well as media.
When the news release comes out,
everyone will know that you, Mr. Lei,
have made great achievement for Yutian.
Qunfei, turn around
and head to the construction site.
What happened? Calm down.
Why would you ask me that?
What did you do?
Calm down.
I'm the supervisor here.
You can tell me
if anything happened.
Yutian has broken down our factory.
You think that by leaving us some money
this can all be settled?
This is ruining our way
to make a living.
How are we going to make money?
Right.
It has cut off our way to make money.
How are we going to make money?
Everyone, calm down.
The contract was signed with Xinsheng,
and the price was decided by Xinsheng.
It has nothing to do with Yutian.
You should go ask Xinsheng
instead of Yutian.
How is there nothing to do with Yutian?
Now we can't make money,
then there's something to do with you.
We don't care
who you signed the contract with.
Whoever takes apart the building
is who we are looking for.
We need to live, right?
Right, we need to live.
We want our money.
What's wrong with that?
We want the money that belongs to us.
That is nonsense.
Who's talking nonsense?
You or I?
There are many of them.
Don't irritate them.
Then we will go to Yutian
and ask their boss for money.
If you cannot take the responsibility,
there will be someone who can.
We need to live. We need money.
No, you can't go to the company.
How can you go to the company?
Calm down, calm down.
You can't go to the company,
please don't.
It won't change anything. Everyone,
calm down, calm down, calm down.
You, yes, it's you.
Why would you incite everyone
to make trouble?
How am I making trouble?
This is big deal for us.
Let me go.
Let me go, let me go.
No.
I can't let you go to the company.
Although you are a girl,
I may also hit you.
Let me go.
I can't let you go there.
You.
It hurts.
Who are you?
Let me go.
Trust me,
I can destroy you now.
It hurts.
How dare you
to be a gangster.
Who asked you here?
If you have the power,
don't bully a girl.
Try me.
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
It's none of your business.
President of Yutian,
Lei Yuzheng.
This guy is trying to fool us.
Who knows if he's actually the boss.
I have heard why
you came here to make trouble.
You think the relocation fee is too low.
I can understand how you feel,
but have ever you thought about
talking peacefully
about the relocation fee?
Gathering around against the law
and affecting the construction progresses
will cost you a lot.
Wait.
The construction progress
has nothing to do with us.
We can't even live now, can we?
We just want to live.
We want our money.
There's nothing wrong with it, right?
Yes.
We want our money.
What's wrong with it?
Give us money.
Why can't we?
You can't go.
We want our money.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Calm down. Let's calm down.
What are you doing?
No, no.
Let's talk about it.
What's there to talk about?
What are you doing?
Du Xiaosu.
Are you ok, Du Xiaosu?
You have made a big trouble.
No one shall leave. Surround them.
Surround them.
You cannot leave,
especially you.
She fell off by herself.
It has nothing to do with me.
Surround all of them. No one can leave.
You are all my witness.
You can't leave.
She fell off herself.
It has nothing to do with me.
Sir,
faster please.
The patient fell off
due to long term fatigue
and severe malnutrition
which caused hypoglycemia and dizziness.
I have injected
nutrient solution for her.
Remember to rest well.
It's going to be fine.
Thank you.
Zhenrong,
don't leave.
Zhenrong.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪