[English subtitles are available]
[Crush]
[Episode 3]
Good morning, guys.
Morning.
Wu Yan, what is this?
My dad asked someone
to bring me these glutinous rice balls
from our hometown.
I'm sharing these with all of you.
We can't keep them for too long.
It's better if you cook
and finish them tonight.
Thank you.
We're lucky.
My dad made these himself.
It's full of the flavour of happiness.
You'll feel even happier
after eating these.
Please distribute these for me.
Thanks.
Mr Su, this box is for you.
I'll put it here then.
I don't want it.
It was my fault for
thinking like that previously.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologise.
You didn't do me wrong.
Why is it so hard to cheer him up?
Teacher, sorry.
I'm late.
Xiao Ling?
Teacher?
Where is Xiao Wei?
Mr Li, I can't find Xiao Wei.
I'm afraid she has been left behind.
Wu Yan, go check the classroom now.
I told them before.
If they can't find
their classmates or teachers,
just go back to the classroom.
Okay, I'll go find her.
[Grade 3 Class 3
Department of Visual Impairment]
Xiao Wei?
Mr Su, Mr Su.
Mr Su, I thought you're all gone.
I thought you don't want me anymore.
I'm right here.
Have you forgotten?
We're doing health examination now.
Now you remember, don't you?
Good job, Xiao Wei.
You came to the classroom when you
couldn't find your teacher and classmates.
You listen to what the teacher said.
Great job.
Good girl.
Don't cry.
It's me.
I'll take Xiao Wei
to the health examination.
I know you won't listen
to my explanation,
but trust me,
I'll take good care of Xiao Wei.
You should at least
give yourself a chance
to trust people.
Xiao Wei,
let Ms Sang take you
to the health examination, okay?
Okay.
Then we'll leave now.
Let's go, Xiao Wei.
[Su Nian Qin]
Oh, his attitude.
What a waste of that beautiful face.
Wu Yan,
you're still here.
I'm just about to leave.
Mr Li,
I noticed that Mr Su
seems to favour Xiao Wei.
Xiao Wei's surname is also Su.
Are they relatives?
No.
How long has Mr Su been working here?
Over a month.
As a matter of fact,
he's not exactly our teacher.
The teacher who taught Braille,
Ms Zheng is delivering a baby.
She's on maternity leave.
There was another retired teacher,
Miss Xu.
The school wanted to hire her again.
However, she needs to take care
of her grandchildren out of town.
This is why we were in need of a teacher.
Principal Pei
happens to know Mr Su very well,
so he hired him as a substitute.
I guess he'll be here
for over half a year.
What was his previous job?
Did he teach somewhere else?
I've no idea.
He never joins our conversation.
Glutinous rice balls?
Where did you get these?
From a colleague.
This is the first time you received
a gift from a colleague.
I didn't expect your colleague to like you
with this attitude of yours.
Go home.
They're really good.
These are the best glutinous rice balls
I've ever had.
Are they really that good?
Try it and you'll know.
[My dad made these himself.]
[It's full of the flavour of happiness.]
[You'll feel even happier
after eating these.]
They're good, right?
They substituted sugar with osmanthus.
It's quite special.
Ask your colleague where she got this.
Her father made these.
I knew it.
People say that food always tastes better
if it's made with love.
Food made by a father is just different.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I don't mind.
Nian Qin,
there will be traffic jams on a rainy day.
You'll be late for school.
You only have one lesson today.
Why don't you make a call
and make adjustment with the school?
No.
The kids still go to school
on a rainy day.
Alright.
I'll pick you up after work.
Be careful.
Don't worry. The rain has just stopped.
Mr Su, you're here.
That was a heavy rain, wasn't it?
Come in.
Mr Su, I'll put it
in the umbrella stand for you.
[I'll give you three seconds.]
[Three.]
[Two.]
Appreciate it.
No problem.
[Appreciate it?]
[He looks well-mannered
but he actually has a thin skin.]
Mr Su, I'm sorry.
In your coming Braille lesson,
I need to use some of your time.
The school has just issued a notice.
We need to brief the students
about the Mid-Autumn Festival holiday.
I'm taking a day off tomorrow,
so I have to inform them in advance.
Do you have any issues with that?
No problem.
Okay, thanks a lot.
Wu Yan, there's nothing much to do today.
If you're busy,
you can leave first.
Alright.
Take care.
Beside Zhuque Bridge,
rank grasses overgrow.
Over Wuyi Alley, the sun is setting slow.
Swallows that gathered
on Wang and Xie's eaves in bygone days,
Are now dipping among
the humble home's doorways.
Rank grasses overgrow.
The sun is setting slow.
It's low.
What?
Over Wuyi Alley, the sun is setting low.
No. It's obviously setting slow.
Slow.
I know.
But in this poem, it is setting low.
It's low.
Is that so?
When I was a second year student,
I even went to Wuyi Alley.
If the tourist hadn't mentioned it,
I wouldn't even know.
Wang Xian Zhi and Wang Xi Zhi
are one of the Wang and Xie
in Wuyi Alley.
I heard that Wang Xian Zhi
was quite a romantic guy.
He was the allusion
of a ferry or something.
It's Taoye Ferry.
It's 12 o'clock.
I should get going.
See you.
Mr Su, I'm worried that you can't find it.
I'll leave your umbrella here.
Over here.
I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
You know what?
There are no logos or patterns
on Su Nian Qin's clothes.
They're always just simple jackets
or shirts.
However, they look exceptional and clean
when he wears them.
Besides, I noticed
that a woman has been picking him up.
She drives a white BMW.
I already saw her twice.
That woman
is pretty good-looking.
I wonder what her job is.
I guess
she's a rich woman.
Su Nian Qin is a kept man.
Do you hear yourself?
You're a highly educated
university student.
Why do you have
such old-fashioned thinking?
Then it's the opposite.
But Mr Li told me,
he's just a substitute.
The hourly wage of a substitute teacher
is very low.
How does he support himself?
♫ The rain falls on the eaves ♫
What do you think?
Are you asking me?
What's going on?
Why would you ask for my opinion?
Is it bad?
It's good.
The style is different
from your last work,
but this is very mature and complete.
The combination of Western music
and Chinese classical literature.
It's pretty elegant.
Where did you get the inspiration?
Give this song to Zheng Ye.
Do you mean
the singer-songwriter
who asked you for a song
via private message?
Arrange a recording.
I've done the arrangement.
Okay.
♫ In the dream ♫
♫ Old memories appeared ♫
♫ I'm sober and speechless ♫
[Starnest Music Center]
How did the recording go?
It's almost done.
The most complicated string section
has been completed.
Sorry.
Please tell the band to re-record it.
I want to switch to D minor
before entering the chorus.
Re... Re-record?
You want to switch it at this part,
but no one does this.
I do.
Nian Qin, you've worked all night.
Later...
Xiao Lu.
thirty-two notes and half notes
are the same in Braille music sheet.
But I've made a remark there.
This is not the first time.
When you copy it to the staff
in the future,
please pay attention, will you?
I will.
[Donghu Music Broadcast]
This morning,
Zheng Ye dropped his latest single,
Zhuque Bridge,
out of the blue.
Without further ado,
let's listen to this song.
♫ The rain falls on the eaves ♫
♫ Swallows return to the mansion ♫
♫ Beside Zhuque Bridge ♫
♫ The ship has sailed away ♫
♫ After this year ♫
♫ When will I see you again? ♫
♫ I murmured under the umbrella ♫
♫ Among Wuyi Alley ♫
♫ The sun is setting ♫
♫ Tea is boiling in the pavilion ♫
♫ The strings strum ♫
♫ As I look back ♫
What's the matter?
I heard this song before.
I did. I heard it before it was released.
♫ In the dream ♫
♫ Old memories appeared ♫
♫ I'm sober and speechless ♫
♫ The morning breeze
and lingering moon ♫
♫ The flower withers ♫
♫ Who is the face
that I see as I'm writing ♫
The lyrics is the story of Wang Xian Zhi.
Wuyi Alley and Taoye Ferry.
♫ The story is sad ♫
[Zhuque Bridge
Songwriter: Yi Jin]
♫ Summer cicada and winter snow ♫
It's Yi Jin?
Yi Jin wrote this.
This is unbelievable.
What's going on?
[First,]
[when Nie Xi interviewed Yi Jin,[
[I met Su Nian Qin]
[at the radio station.]
Second,
this song.
Heard Su Nian Qin played this before.
Third,
both Yi Jin and Su Nian Qin
live in Xiamen.
No way.
That's my dream guy, Yi Jin.
The songs he wrote are mellow.
Would he have such a bad attitude?
There is one more thing
which can tell
whether Su Nian Qin is Yi Jin.
Nie Xi's interview.
You talked to him for so many times,
you should be able
to recognise Su Nian Qin's voice.
You're right.
[Interview of Mysterious Songwriter,
Yi Jin]
[Hi, everyone. I'm Yi Jin.]
[Everyone is entitled
to their own opinion.]
[Whatever they're thinking,]
[I don't care.]
[To produce a good song...]
Do I know you?
No, thanks.
Nian Qin. Q-i-n, Qin.
You can leave now.
Over Wuyi Alley, the sun is setting low.
Oh, my God.
My God.
Calm down.
I need to go out for a while.
Where are you going?
I need to do some jogging
to calm myself down.
[FM27.1]
Hello, Mr Li.
[Wu Yan, I need you to do me a favour.]
What is it? Tell me.
Here's the story.
Today,
I'm supposed to send something
to the welfare home.
But something came up. I can't leave.
[Could you go there for me?]
Sure.
I'll go there after work.
[Great.]
The materials
are inside the file cabinet of the office.
[Just call me after you get there.]
[I'll tell you the exact location.]
Okay.
Sorry, Mr Li.
I need to hang up now. I have work to do.
Mr Jiang.
Next Wednesday,
there will be
an offline musicians meeting.
Go check it out.
Me?
Yes, you.
You should gain some experience.
Xu Qian has all the information.
If you don't understand, go find her.
I...
This...
[Wei Hao, listen carefully.]
[I don't want to play
love games with you.]
And I hate complicated relationships.
I'm very busy.
That's it.
Thank you for sending them over here.
Don't worry. It's understandable.
Su, you're here.
Are you here to see Xiao Wei?
Hi, Madam Zhang.
Why are you here all by yourself?
Where is Xiao Wei?
A girl came.
She asked Xiao Wei
to play stones with her.
Yes. The three of them
always hang out together.
It's been a while since I last met you.
How are you doing?
I'm good.
-Wait here. I need to go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
Su,
I got so caught up with work
that I forgot to ask about you.
It's fine.
Just do your work.
Don't mind me.
I've finished my work.
You must be boring sitting here alone.
Since we haven't met for a while,
we should catch up.
Su, are you seeing anyone recently?
You should let me meet her.
-You...
-Do you really want to know?
Ms Sang.
Sang, what's the matter?
Nothing, nothing.
By the way, have the children
been living here their whole lives?
No.
Some of them were lost.
The police couldn't find their parents,
so they were sent here.
Some of them were abandoned
by their parents.
Some were sent here
when they were a toddler.
Some were sent here after they were born.
Is that because they were sick?
They usually have birth defects.
How can there be such parents
in the world?
There are also parents
who gave birth to children
with birth defects,
but they still take care of them
for their entire lives.
Mr Su,
I didn't expect you
to visit Xiao Wei here.
You seem to really adore her.
Where are you going? I can send you there.
You don't have to.
[Are you done?]
I'm outside the welfare home.
Okay.
Mr Su,
I've been wanting to ask you something.
Are you
Yi Jin?
You should at least say something.
If you don't want to admit it,
you could've faked it.
Why are you acting like this?
You're acting like you'd catch a plague
if you talk to me.
Go wherever you want.
I'm not getting in your way sitting here.
But please don't stand in front of me,
and stop bothering me, will you?
Mr Su, what do you think
you're talking about?
Just now, you were walking in front of me.
I was behind you.
Now, you're sitting, I'm standing here.
You sat on this bench first,
but you didn't construct this road,
did you?
I can stand wherever I want.
You... I can do whatever I want.
Listen.
When Yi Jin did the interview,
I met you in the lift.
Yi Jin's new song is based on
Wang Xian Zhi’s allusion.
And we happened to discuss this before.
It's certainly not a coincidence.
Who is Yi Jin?
Forget it. That's fine.
Why don't you let me take you home?
You can't just
keep sitting here, can you?
It's getting dark now.
You need to eat.
Are you waiting for someone
to pick you up?
Waiting alone is quite boring, isn't it?
I can talk to you.
Do you think
that you're quite cool?
Okay. You're really cool.
Really cool.
How did you know that I work here?
Zhao Ying saw you and told me that.
I've asked them out for dinner.
You should at least have dinner with us
and make things clear.
I've nothing to say.
I shouldn't quit in such short notice,
but I really don't have time for the band.
Be honest with me.
Have you encountered any problem?
No.
What kind of problem would I have?
Stop following me.
This is my last warning.
Aren't you cold?
We've been sitting here for some time.
It's quite chilly.
You should go home first.
Aren't you hungry?
Wu Yan.
You...
He... He's my boyfriend.
We're on a date.
Mr Su, the almighty Mr Su,
please have some mercy
and finish this play with me.
Thanks.
Finish this play with me.
Ms Sang,
please behave yourself.
He's hungry.
He couldn't think straight.
Su Nian Qin.
Su Nian Qin!
Su Nian Qin, stop!
I told you to stop. Didn't you hear me?
I told you to...
♫ I'm willing to imagine ♫
♫ All the possibilities ♫
♫ Make me believe ♫
♫ You're the only one ♫
♫ I'm willing to believe ♫
Please let go.
I won't.
♫ No matter how long the journey is ♫
I can let go.
But you have to go there
and explain to her.
Was I not telling her the truth?
You...
How could you do this?
Do what?
How... How could you do this?
Listen.
I fell out with my family
and moved to Xiamen with you.
You said you'd be nice to me.
You also said you'd be a good father.
How could you leave me
and go on a date with that woman?
I haven't eaten anything yet.
Our child and I are starving.
How could you be so cruel
and fool around with other woman?
His wife is pregnant,
but he's cheating on her.
Exactly. Why would anyone do this?
When we were young, you only like me.
Why would you
be with another woman now?
I could've let it slide
if it were someone else.
But she's my best friend.
How can both of you deceive me?
A good-looking man
will never be loyal.
He's a beast.
He's worse than a beast.
What the heck is this?
Sang Wu Yan.
Get up first.
No.
You can do whatever you want.
Get up first.
I'm hungry.
I want KFC.
Put this on.
I'm not cold.
You still have to wear it.
Do you want me to keep crying?
Put it on.
You keep holding this blazer.
I thought it'd be hideous.
But it actually looks good on you.
Let's go.