HOSPITAL PLAYLIST
Buy me dinner, please.
Buy me dinner this weekend, Professor Ahn.
Sure. Let's have a get-together
with everyone.
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us, outside the hospital
and not in these scrubs,
but in our personal clothes.
I have plans.
I need to visit my mother in Yangpyeong.
I'm sorry.
HOSPITAL PLAYLIST
-That's awful.
-Hold on.
Let me get this straight.
The real estate agent told the owner
that he signed a contract
to pay monthly rent.
But Dr. Do signed
a deposit-based apartment.
The agent gave the owner 20 million won
and the first month's rent
and took the rest of Dr. Do's deposit.
Yes, that's what happened. Jeez.
What's he going to do now?
He spent his whole life
saving up that money.
He took out
a 100-million-won mortgage too.
He lost all of his money
and has to pay back the interest, too.
-Did the police catch the agent?
-The agent already bolted.
He reported it to the police,
but they told him
not to keep his hopes up.
Where are they going to live now?
They can live there and pay rent.
The contract is nullified anyway.
The house owner
just wants him to pay rent.
Can't they just stay there?
Seon-bin, I guess paying 900,000 won
every month must come easy to you.
No. I'm sorry.
Don't. You don't have to apologize.
There's nothing wrong
with having rich parents.
Paying 900,000 won every month
is too much. He has to move.
As a matter of fact, they'll stay there
by the end of this week.
His wife will go
to her parents' house in Paju.
And Dr. Do will be staying
at a cheap studio for the time being.
I'm not sure if he'll be able to focus
after all that has happened.
He's probably out of it right now.
I'm really not interested in it.
I won't do it.
Have you ever seen me take
a managerial position? I'll never do it.
Do you want to leave
the CS department without a chief?
I'm sure a few professors
would want the position.
Tell Professor Cheon to do it.
He'll have an easier time getting rebates.
The chairman said
he could never be the chief.
He won't let Professor Cheon take over
except for the CS Department.
He thinks he will cause trouble again.
If he is bound to cause trouble,
he should be investigated
and punished accordingly.
Why would he stop midway through?
-Exactly. You should take the position.
-Exactly.
I'm sorry.
Did you tell the perfusionist
that the patient has a left SVC?
Right. I'm sorry. I forgot to check on it.
You didn't confirm it
with the perfusionist?
I'm sorry.
Did you even look at the ultrasound?
What are you doing? Get a grip.
I'm sorry.
Do you want the kid to die?
Don't bring your personal life
into the OR.
If you can't do that, leave.
No, I'm sorry.
I'll insert the vent catheter
in the coronary sinus.
Were you able to reach Eun-won?
No. She was having a hard time
when she was on the night shift recently.
The death of the patient, Yun Mi-seong,
must have hit her hard.
She was already physically tired,
but she lost a patient.
I think that case triggered it.
Of course, it's hard. There is
so much work, but we're short-staffed.
-And she was sleep-deprived, too.
-What happened?
Dr. Myeong Eun-won has been
MIA since yesterday morning,
no word for two days.
What if she never comes back?
-Hello.
Hi.
-Dr. Chu.
-Yes?
If you hear from Eun-won,
please let me know right away.
Okay. I will.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Let's look at the CT scan.
This is the right side of your liver.
Can you see this mass,
about two centimeters,
deep on the right side?
You have cirrhosis of the liver, too.
From your blood results,
your CEA level is high.
I think...
I do think it's liver cancer.
Oh, no.
It's only two centimeters.
We caught it early.
But for liver cancer,
checking if it's operable or not
is the most important, not the size.
First, we should take an MRI
in order to confirm
my diagnosis
that it is indeed liver cancer.
We also need to check
if the cancer has spread to other parts.
Surgeries are the best treatment plan
for liver cancer.
If the cancer has metastasized,
we may have to change
our course of treatment.
Doctor,
will I be able to live?
Of course. You have to live.
I am not sure
if this will comfort you in any way.
If this is operable, it will mean
a huge chance of your survival.
Please don't think it's the end.
Let's be optimistic about it
and wait for the test result.
Doctor, when can he get the surgery?
We want it done as soon as possible.
Let's get you admitted today.
Let's get you admitted and run tests
that will confirm my diagnosis.
And if it is cancer,
let's check if it spread, too.
Okay.
And one of my surgeries
got canceled the following Tuesday.
If the tests confirm that it's operable,
let's get your surgery on that day, then.
However, if the tests show that the cancer
has spread or is abnormal,
the surgery date can be changed.
Once you go out, the nurse will explain
the steps of getting admitted
to the hospital.
You need to stay strong
for your father to stay strong, too.
Okay.
Thank you.
Professor Ahn,
do you have a headache again?
-Do you want some medicine?
-No, I'm good.
-Did you take her abdominal X-ray today?
-Yes.
How much drainage did she get
yesterday from the tube?
It was 50 two days ago. It's 20 today.
It went down a lot.
Is that so?
Let's see.
My gosh.
It was really green yesterday.
It's transparent today.
You should visit a doctor.
Do you want me to give you a referral?
I'll take care of it myself.
You should introduce Bidulgi to me.
She's very busy right now.
I'll introduce you to her later.
So she is your girlfriend, right?
I'll tell you everything another time.
What's taking Jeong-won so long?
He'll get nothing if he comes late.
There he is.
What's taking Jeong-won so long?
He'll get nothing if he comes late.
There he is.
Seeing how he's happy,
his patient must be doing well.
-Or his patient is about to be discharged.
-Hey.
Jae-i is pooping really well.
Is that so? Congrats.
The color is beautiful,
and the shape is great, too.
She poops right away
whenever she eats now.
Her poo is so beautiful!
What about my bread? Where's mine?
We finished all of it.
It's turning into poo now.
Yes.
I'm on my way now. Bye.
Hey, it's right there.
There are valves in everyone's heart.
The blood flows in one direction.
The valves make sure the blood
doesn't flow backward
once it passes through.
Usually, one or two valves may leak
or shrink when babies are born.
We often have to perform surgery for it.
But your baby is a very rare case.
All of the valves in his heart
are leaking.
We didn't find anything unusual
from the genetic testing.
I cannot diagnose your baby
with a known name of the disease.
For now,
Hun's heart can't pump blood out of his
heart. The blood keeps flowing backward.
The aortic valve regurgitation
is severe with his case,
so I cannot put him on ECMO, either.
And when he was transferred
to our hospital,
he had brain damage due to either CPR
or genetic defect.
We must induce him with a high dosage
of diuretic to produce a bit of urine
since cardiac output has
drastically decreased.
He has a severe case of pulmonary edema,
so we can't treat him
with more medication.
What about surgery?
Doctor, if he gets surgery,
wouldn't he be able to live?
The survival rate is about 50 percent.
We perform heart surgery
to improve patients' health.
As for your baby...
But then, again,
surgery is the only option we have.
It's hard for me to tell you
what will happen during surgery.
But we can't let him go
without fighting for him.
I can't guarantee that I can fix him,
but there's no other way.
We should give it a try.
Okay.
All right, then.
You should lean on your back
and tuck your chin in
to avoid herniated discs.
Okay.
Having a sedentary job must be tough.
It's all done.
You're the one with a hard job.
You always go home late.
How did you know that?
You always look so tired.
I see.
MOM'S 70TH BIRTHDAY TRIP ACCOUNT
Will you make another savings account?
You're a long-term customer at our bank,
so you'll get a good interest rate.
I wanted to start a new installment
savings account for 100,000 won.
But I have to get going today.
-Have a good day.
-Bye.
By the way, I heard
that your bank gives out dolls
when the installment savings matures.
Wait, please.
Mom, Song-hwa asked
if this is good enough.
That's perfect.
My gosh, that looks beautiful.
Song-hwa is beautiful and smart,
and has wits like this.
-Why--
-Why isn't she married?
No. Why
doesn't she like my son?
If you marry a girl like Song-hwa,
I could join the Lord even tomorrow
and have nothing to wish for.
Come on.
My son is sensitive and delicate.
You're beautiful like flowers.
And you also easily get hurt like flowers.
It'd be nice if you have
a reliable life partner like Song-hwa.
Mom, you're turning 70 soon.
I'll send you on a trip.
Tell me anywhere you want to go.
I must book it now to get tickets.
And we'll have a birthday party, too.
I'll make sure you're not lonely,
even without Dad here with us.
Your youngest son will throw you
the biggest birthday party ever.
Forget it. I don't want a party.
No more throwing parties, okay?
I'll go somewhere close like
Southeast Asia with Song-hwa.
Or should we go to Jeju Island?
The four of us can go together.
-Why are there four of us?
-I must take Jong-su with me.
He's a lonely man.
What's the point of having
successful and rich children?
He has colorful bruises all over his body,
from his forehead to knees,
because he slipped in the bathroom.
I haven't had it for a while. It's good.
Stop lying.
You always eat ramyeon at home.
I haven't had cup noodles for a while.
Your kids must've been scared.
What did Geon-tae say?
You called him, right?
No, I didn't.
He must be busy at his new hospital.
Why bother him?
What about Tae-ung?
You should at least tell Tae-ung.
He's working on a big lawsuit these days.
He's working all night.
They are both busy.
It's a hassle when the kids come, too.
I'm better off alone.
Hey, Rosa.
Me?
I'm in Mr. Kettle's office.
Okay. See you at the cafe in ten minutes.
Not the one in the lobby.
There's a new cafe
in front of the hospital.
They serve delicious drinks.
Yes. That's the one.
When have you been there?
Good for you.
You go on dates to the cafes
with your son.
Okay.
By the way,
did you appoint a new chief?
No. No one wants to take the job.
Golfing is more fun for old professors.
Young professors prefer
going home early even for a day
instead of getting 300,000 won
for the managerial position.
No one wants to be the chief
because they'll end up working more.
Besides, we don't have
that many professors for NS and CS.
So it's harder to fill in the position.
What about Professor Min Gi-jun of NS?
He's in charge of the Neuroscience Center.
He's in charge of the center,
appears on TV, and YouTube.
He's busy.
Make a young professor
take the position for CS.
Just order someone to do it.
Jong-su, why don't you retire?
Do you think they listen to the director?
They all know exactly what they want
for themselves.
As a matter of fact, I'm going to retire.
Really?
I'll retire after running the hospital
for three more years.
Jeez.
Mom, I have surgery. I've got to go.
-Get something delicious with Mr. Ju.
-Okay. Go on.
CHIEF PRIEST
Father, how have you been?
Jeong-won left his phone here.
I see.
Please relay this message to Andrea.
Go on.
They accepted their recommendation letter.
Congratulate him for me.
They accepted
-the recommendation letter?
-Yes.
I just received the email.
The parish in Naples received
the recommendation letter.
They are willing to accept him,
so they'd like to see him in person.
I told them I would talk to Andrea
when he could be available
for the interview
and call them right back.
I'm sorry, Father.
Jeong-won can't make it to the interview.
-Pardon?
-I'm sorry. I'm hanging up.
My apologies, Father.
Where did I put my phone?
Jeong-won.
Yes?
The chief priest just called.
They accepted your recommendation letter.
I don't need a fancy 70th birthday party.
I won't be sad
even if you don't throw me a party.
You don't have to do that.
Just stay by my side.
We don't have to live together
or call each other.
Just stay by my side.
Please.
Live a normal life.
That's my last wish.
This won't do it.
Stop talking back to me,
and give me some painkillers.
I notified the doctor,
but I didn't get the order yet.
Please wait.
Mr. Lee Jeong-bae,
I'll take your blood pressure.
The doctor will be here.
I'll dress your wound.
Okay.
Then, are you telling me
that I have to be in pain like this?
Does this hospital just let patients
suffer in pain? What is this place?
Excuse me.
-What's going on?
-I gave him his meds,
-but he keeps asking for painkillers.
-Which one?
An hour ago,
I gave him an ampoule of Tridol.
No, I don't want that one.
What was that called? Pethidine?
I want pethidine
or whatever that's called.
PETHIDINE: A NARCOTIC PAINKILLER
Sir, we cannot give you pethidine
unless a doctor prescribes it for you.
Why do you need a doctor
to give me a shot?
Just give me a shot of pethidine
and leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
Can you get me some betadine balls?
Okay.
Come on. Why are you
being so uptight about a shot?
Is giving me a shot that hard? Hey!
A patient is in pain!
I'm in serious pain right now.
You're fine.
The surgery went well.
And the wound is clean, too.
Keep an eye on him for a few hours
and get back to me.
Okay.
All you guys do is cut people open.
You know nothing.
I'm in pain. Okay?
Give me pethidine. Just give it to me!
Hurry!
Are you addicted to narcotic painkillers?
We already gave you a drip for the pain
and Tridol an hour ago.
If we give you pethidine on top of this,
you might lose consciousness.
So I can't prescribe it.
Do you still want it?
Forget it. Damn it.
I understand that you are upset.
But you can't just say--
She was fine
when she went to the hospital.
You guys messed up.
That's why she's still stuck in bed!
Listen, sir. The patient,
your wife, had pneumonia
even before the surgery,
so I explained to you she would need
the ventilator for a long time and she may
stay in the ICU for a long duration.
It's okay as long as you explain it?
You say you're her doctor,
but how much time did you spend on her?
Is this how you'll treat your own mother
if she's lying in that bed?
Okay, sir. I'm sorry. Bye.
Who was that? A guardian?
My gosh. That was
the husband of my patient.
She has pneumonia and is old, too.
She's been on a ventilator
for some time after surgery.
I've had a lot of patients lately.
Yesterday was the only day
I couldn't check on her.
I can't believe
he'd just attack me like this.
Why did you choose CS?
There are a lot of other easy departments.
They said I'd get ten million won more.
Not a lot of doctors applied to CS.
They said I'd get ten million won more
on my annual salary if I applied.
That's why I picked CS.
What about you, Dr. Ahn? Why NS?
You're not even well.
Why did you become a surgeon?
I saw a documentary.
Only neurosurgeons did surgery
while sitting down.
There are more surgeries
we do on our feet.
Professor Chae has
a cervical herniated disc.
Exactly. I didn't know any better, then.
What should I do? I'm doomed.
Hello, who is this?
I'm the daughter of the man
that just called you.
I was next to my father.
I'm sorry, doctor.
I see.
My father is having a tough time
because of my mom.
He can't control his emotions well.
I am very sorry.
I see.
Your father was very rude on the phone.
Well, I understand
that this is hard for him.
But treating me like that...
What's going on?
Are you going to a wedding?
You're wearing contact lens.
Yes, one of my school friends'.
But I'm not really close to her.
If you're not close, why go?
She came to my second
and third brothers' weddings.
I should go to hers.
You don't have to go
to everyone's wedding.
What a weary life.
Jeez.
She must be loaded seeing that she's
getting married on a weekday afternoon.
Jeong-won is buying dinner later.
You can't come?
I should go. Father Ahn is buying.
I'll join you guys
straight from the wedding.
Hey, the kettle is hot.
It burns.
How will you do surgery
with these fingers?
My goodness. You should be more careful.
-How old are you?
-Forty.
Hey, hold on.
My pinkie is fine.
Come on.
I don't have
surgery tomorrow.
I have two surgeries in two days.
I think I can do it.
How will you perform surgery with these?
The burns weren't that bad.
Wait, hold on a second.
Hey, did you just turn me
into Demetan Croaker?
You wrapped too much.
You're right.
I wrapped it too much.
I'll fix them later.
Stay like that for now.
I'm leaving now.
You'll leave me like this?
Yes.
You won't die from it.
Bye.
Hey. Wait. Do you want me
to fill the Rainbow Pond with my tears?
Croak, croak
-Didn't you go to the hospital?
-I did.
I went there yesterday and the day before.
-I've been there since 8 a.m. today.
-Hey!
I don't need to get this checked out.
I'm totally fine.
No, you're not.
Did you break your bone?
What did your kids say?
They don't know.
-Why not?
-I didn't call them.
It's not like I'm dying.
Why would I call them?
What do you want? Coffee?
It's decaf, right?
My goodness. This hurts a bit.
You don't know your son's number?
My oldest son
moved to a new hospital in LA this summer.
He moved to a new house
and changed his phone, too.
-You can ask your second son.
-He doesn't know, either.
Besides, Tae-ung is busier.
It's been over two months since I saw him.
-Why do you live like that?
-What do you mean?
I'm living a good life
without my children.
Did I tell you to rely on them?
Did I tell you to live with them
and eat together all the time?
They are your children,
and you're their father.
You call your family when you're sick
and celebrate together on happy occasions.
That's what family does.
Why are you all alone? This is pathetic.
-This is annoying.
-My goodness.
I'm happy that they are making
good money and living a good life.
I'm fine.
After my late wife got sick,
I got better at eating alone
and doing laundry. I'm doing well, Rosa.
When your wife was sick,
how many times did Geon-tae
and Tae-ung come to see her?
They came only once.
Their own mother was bedridden
for seven years,
unable to move, but they came only once.
How the hell did you raise your kids?
You're frustrating and annoying.
You're such a dimwit!
Song-hwa, here.
Give two servings to that table
and three servings to ours, ma'am.
Jeong-won is buying dinner tonight,
so we're at a tteokbokki restaurant, Mom.
Right? Rich people are such cheapskates.
Okay. Goodnight.
Andrea, can we get jjajang tteokbokki?
You two soldiers, go ahead.
Ma'am, two servings
of jjajang tteokbokki, please.
What's the occasion, Jeong-won?
Did your savings account mature?
He did. He put in 100,000 won every month
for three years. It matured today.
He'll send his mom on a trip
for her birthday.
Then, what do you spend your salary on?
What's wrong with your hands?
Are you copying Inside Men?
He recklessly burned his fingers.
The director gave him an earful.
Jeong-won, send your mom to Mojito
and have her drink a glass of Maldives.
Is that funny to you?
I love his jokes.
Jeong-won, you can just tell us now.
-Tell you what?
-I'm sure your father
left something modest in your name
before he passed. Right?
I mean, think about it. You're
the only son left in this secular world.
Thank you.
In fact,
he did pass something down to me.
-What is it?
-What?
He had secretly been
donating two million won
to an orphanage every month.
-It's far from ready.
-I know.
You're no fun at all.
-You're no fun.
-Is it cooked?
I think it was an automatic transfer.
I took that over, so I've been
donating every month since then.
Jeong-won, I'll pay for the meal.
That would make me feel at ease.
Guys, it's on me. Eat a lot.
Order as much as you want.
-Will you?
-Yes, that'd be better.
-Do that. That sounds better.
-I saw it coming.
-Can I order some dumplings?
-Go ahead.
Ma'am, two dumplings, please.
Ma'am, give us Sprite and some noodles.
-And some Coke, please.
-I want cheese, too.
Guys, no. I can totally pay for this.
My savings account matured today.
-I said I was buying.
-No, that's okay.
It's like taking money from a poor man.
Ma'am, two servings of tteokbokki
for to-go, please.
I want my takeout cooked, please.
Seok-hyeong, how's your mother?
What do you think?
It's back to square one.
My goodness,
have some mercy on us, merciful Buddha.
I bet she won't divorce him now.
Exactly. She won't divorce him
no matter what.
I don't know what to do now.
She won't divorce him
even if he gives her all of his properties
and the entire company.
Seok-hyeong. Then,
will all the buildings and properties
be yours when your mother passes away?
Probably.
Hey, can you list me and U-ju
under your family register?
You don't have any children anyway.
Adopt me and U-ju as your sons.
It's only a ten-story building.
And a lot of stores are vacant anyway.
And don't you know my mom?
She'd rather have them vacant
than renting them out.
Right. That's true.
Right. Dad.
Did the resident who went MIA come back?
Not yet. How did you know?
My gosh. My son is so nosy.
I heard people talk.
Everyone at the hospital knows.
I heard that, too.
It must've been hard on the resident.
Be nice to her when she comes back.
Of course.
-Dr. Chu.
-Yes?
I hope you have some time for a snack.
Totally. Yes.
It's non-alcoholic.
If I don't drink this today,
I might go crazy and cause a scene.
I'll be on night shifts forever.
I was on a night shift yesterday,
and today as well.
I'll be on call tomorrow, too.
My colleague isn't helpful at all.
She's such a pain in the ass.
Is she the only one having a hard time?
Does she think I enjoy working?
Would I come to work shouting,
"Yes! I get to work!"?
Ms. Han, had I known
it would be this hard,
I would have stayed in the lab.
I was sick of staying in the lab
every day.
I became a doctor
since all I ever did was study.
Look at me.
The only colleague I have
is the sliest colleague ever.
And my professor is
the most slow-witted slug ever.
I'm done.
As of today,
my career as a doctor will end.
I'll put an end to this.
I'll go tell the slug tomorrow morning.
Look at me. I'm an excellent doctor,
I didn't run away from my job,
and I'm good to my professors.
Why? Why does he only comfort her?
Eun-won ran away from her job.
I can't reach her.
And she's not even diligent.
Why is he only nice to her? Why?
Min-ha isn't here yet?
Professor Yang.
It's already getting chilly.
Have a cup of hot coffee.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll bring them in.
Okay.
How much drainage?
No, I'll check it myself. Okay.
Please. Please wash my face.
No. I hate touching other men's faces.
Hello.
So cute!
Goodness. I knew I'd find you here.
What?
-Help me wash my face.
-What?
I couldn't wash up last night
and this morning.
You know, it feels like
there are bugs all over my face.
Should I help you take a shower?
What?
But you know that
my showers last an hour, right?
I'll wash your face.
But I'll be really thorough with you.
My goodness. Seriously.
You're my last hope, Song-hwa.
I have faith in you.
Sorry. I'll come back another time.
That's fine. I'm done putting them on.
Really?
What happened to you?
It looks like you didn't wash up.
Jeez.
My gosh. Whenever patients see me,
they always ask
when they can wash up and wash their hair.
Now, I get why.
I can finally breathe again.
Should I wrap bandages again?
You can take them off now.
I need to go see the hospital director.
Gyeo-ul caused some trouble.
Let's have lunch together.
Can you wipe my neck a bit more?
My gosh, that feels so nice.
This side, too.
You're all Dr. Jang's supervisors?
Right. She's in GS.
Yes. It's about my patient.
She's with my department this month.
-Did it all work out?
-Luckily,
-yes.
-Gosh.
It turns out he was a real drug addict.
He got out only a month ago.
He probably doesn't want trouble,
so the chief of the CS Department
apologized this time
and we'll reduce his medical bills.
This all got resolved.
Getting calls from the CS Department
is the scariest. It really is.
Anyway, tell the residents
to be more careful.
I know their job is hard,
but what's the point
of treating patients day and night?
If they say a word wrong,
we get complaints right away.
Then, the hospital has to comply
with all of their demands.
And if that happens, we really
might end up with serious problems.
Thank you for your effort.
I'll talk to her.
By the way,
I don't think
Dr. Jang was completely wrong.
I'll talk to her.
I've got to go.
I need to go. A guardian wants to see me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. Have a good day.
You startled me.
-What are you doing here?
-How did things go?
It all worked out well.
He'll take down the post.
It's all resolved now. Don't worry.
Do you want some coffee?
I heard once I'm past 12 weeks,
my pregnancy is considered safe.
You said nuchal translucency
was fine as well.
Doctor, does it mean
I don't have to worry now?
Actually, there's something
that concerns me.
There's a lot of blood around the uterus
on your ultrasound.
Finding blood in the uterus at 12 weeks
isn't that common.
This may increase the chance
of a natural miscarriage.
She has to rest up and be careful.
If you see any bleeding,
you must come to the ER at any time.
First, I'll prescribe you
with progesterone,
so it can help your uterus stabilize.
Don't worry.
I'll keep checking.
Let's keep this baby safe no matter what.
I texted Jeong-won to come over.
Wouldn't you rather have him
comfort you than me?
No, it's all right.
I'm sorry.
Don't be disappointed
in the director or the hospital.
There are some good days
and bad days, you know.
And keep your chin up.
And something like this happens again,
make a decision based on your principles.
Just do that.
Thank you.
And I don't think
Professor Ahn will come.
He's been staying in PICU these days.
My goodness, Jeong-won.
What's wrong with that punk?
I hope he can be half as nice
to you as he is to my son, U-ju.
You know, he loves kids.
He came over to my house last weekend
and played with my son the whole day.
Did he go to your house last weekend?
-Yes.
-On Sunday, too?
He came on both days. Why?
He told me he had to go
to Yangpyeong last weekend.
He told me that he was busy.
I think I should forget him.
If he's lying to me,
I should stop pursuing him.
Thank you for keeping my secret
all this time.
Thank you for the coffee.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
Dr. Chu.
Ms. Park Seon-yeong,
the one who gave birth at dawn.
It was a deep laceration,
so I made lots of sutures.
-Is the episiotomy okay?
-Yes.
It was fine after the delivery
before going up to her room.
But I didn't check it afterward.
I'll check on it right away
and notify you. I'm sorry.
Check on patients
once they go up to the ward.
-Okay.
-I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Don't be at other department's services
for now. Stay on mine.
I'll straighten it out.
My gosh, look at you, Eun-won.
You lost a lot of weight.
Go home early tonight.
No, I'll go home after I finish my work.
Okay.
I'll take over your patients who are
getting admitted today and tomorrow.
Dr. Chu, I'm sorry.
Tonight will be the last time
I'll ask you to take my night shift.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Ms. Do Jae-yeong will be coming up soon
after the admission process.
Right. It's today.
Ms. Do Jae-yeong will get admitted
this afternoon.
She's sensitive because
she's coming in because of preterm labor.
Take good care of her.
If the contractions are regular
and her stomach hurts,
check her cervix for dilation.
The baby is only 30 weeks old,
so check the monitor frequently.
Okay.
I'm going to check on a patient
with contractions.
Ms. Han, this is for you.
-What's this?
-Ms. Do Jae-yeong wrote down
a list of things the medical staff
wants to follow before she gets admitted.
Someone delivered it to me.
You should take a look.
I WANT ONLY MY HUSBAND TO MASSAGE ME
DIM LIGHTING WITH CANDLES
ALL THE STAFF MUST BE FEMALE
EXCEPT FOR THE PROFESSOR
Who spoiled the mood?
He's very tired
from getting all the tests today.
Doctor, when will we have the results?
We'll have them in two days
at the earliest.
Sir, did you eat?
I don't have much of an appetite.
I just want to get the surgery
as soon as possible.
You must eat your meals and cheer up
especially at times like this.
Doctor.
If the cancer spread to other organs,
I can't get the surgery, right?
I heard when cancer spreads,
it spreads quickly,
so I won't be able to beat cancer.
Dad, we haven't gotten the results yet.
Why are you worried about such things?
Also, even if it did spread, you can get
chemotherapy and take medication.
We can fix it.
You seem to know better than me.
Doctor.
I can't seem to eat.
All of us couldn't eat at all.
Don't you need to go to work?
I took some days off from work.
It's her teacher certification exam soon.
I told her to go and study,
but she won't listen.
The whole family is on pause right now.
My gosh.
-How about this?
-Pardon?
Why don't we move the patient we just
saw, Choe Jung-won, to a six-person room?
Suggest that to them.
That's a great idea.
-Can you help me?
-Okay, I got it.
Yes, this is Kim Jun-wan. Yes.
My gosh. Come on.
Okay. I'll be right upstairs.
This has to be a déjà vu.
Something like this happened a while ago.
Oh, my head.
He said the guardian
was rude on the phone.
Unbelievable.
He should have just cursed at her.
I'd complain too
if I heard something like that.
Who'd stay quiet when someone says
your father is rude on the phone?
Why does his daughter
have to be a lawyer though?
And she's very well-connected.
I barely managed to stop her
from talking to the TV station.
So, what do they want?
An apology and a handwritten letter?
Forget that.
They don't even want money.
Then what are they asking for?
Proper punishment.
They want us to show them
that we're taking this seriously
and how much we want to mend the situation
by penalizing the resident.
So? What did you say?
A pay cut for three months.
A pay cut over something like this?
They're quiet now because I said that.
They said they'd think about it,
which means they're not unhappy with it.
Professor Kim.
Let's just go with this
and get the situation sorted out.
Okay. I have an emergency patient.
Please excuse me.
Hello?
Yes.
I think I'm not living my life well.
I studied for the bar exam
for six long years,
yet I made that ridiculous blunder
when signing my new lease.
And what kind of chief resident
spews such nonsense
to someone who is devastated
because of their ill mother?
Gosh, seriously. What is wrong with me?
I'm bad at my job because I'm dumb.
There's nothing I can do.
My existence is harming others.
Hey.
If you ever run into me
at a hospital somewhere,
don't pretend as if you don't know me.
We've been through thick and thin together
-for years, you know.
-Gosh, please.
What the heck are you talking about?
Have you gone mad?
Why are you quitting? Why would you quit?
I won't let you quit.
You're right.
I sure can't quit.
I'm working the night shift today.
Damn it. I have to go.
Patient Do Jae-yeong isn't here yet?
No, but she's coming up now.
Then I'll check her in before I leave.
Okay.
She's my patient,
but I have to go into the OR now.
Could you please have
the doctor on the night shift
take care of the patient for me?
Oh, sure.
What the...
Hello.
Oh, we're not even set up yet.
Why did you come so early?
The professor left just now.
The C-section ended
just a few minutes ago.
I wanted to help you with the preparation.
Dr. Myeong, you're scrubbing in?
I was expecting the chief resident.
I want to watch and learn.
I still have a lot to learn.
All right, sounds good.
I'll be in my office.
Page me when everything's ready.
Yes, Professor.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
Dr. Chu.
Yes.
Everything seems okay
with the patient, Do Jae-yeong,
but she doesn't feel any movement.
She wants you to check.
Again? This is the third time,
for God's sake.
Gosh.
The baby is moving.
It's probably just that
you can't really feel it.
Everything looks good,
so we'll just wait and see.
Doctor, did you wash your hands?
Yes, I did. Just before I came here.
Don't worry.
I don't want to be hooked up
to that monitor.
It's so uncomfortable.
Can you take it off?
I can't sleep.
Without it, we can't really see
how the baby is doing,
so we'll be worried.
I know it's uncomfortable,
but we have to keep it on.
Why don't you just get rid of it
and check in on me more often instead?
PEDIATRIC INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
CHIEF DO JAE-HAK
I'm not even the backup
for the night shift today.
Isn't that Professor Cheon's patient?
Yes, that's right.
And he's the backup
for the night shift today.
But when he was leaving,
he told me not to call him.
Jeez.
He told me to just go ahead
and make my own decisions,
but I'm not sure
whether I made the right decision.
How much epinephrine?
She got 0.2 micrograms.
But the BP keeps dropping,
and the test results aren't looking good.
We've been adjusting the setting,
but CO2 keeps filling up.
And her BP is hovering around 50 to 60
at the moment.
I'm wondering if we should open the chest
and do a shunt revision,
but I'm not sure.
What should we do, Professor?
All right. If the BP keeps dropping,
try using vasopressin.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
We don't need to open the chest for this.
You watched her well.
Professor Kim.
Professor Kim, I have to talk to you
about something.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
This is my ex-colleague.
He's been asking me to set him up
with a fellow doctor.
You should meet him.
No more one-sided crush.
It's all right.
It's not all right.
I've already set a time and date for it.
Tomorrow at 7 p.m. Look for a black SUV.
He'll be waiting for you
at the entrance by the ER.
Just go and have dinner with him.
I know you're busy,
but you still need to eat.
Okay.
Good. That's what I like to hear.
All right, then. Let's get some sleep now.
ELAPSED TIME
It keeps ripping.
Professor,
it is better than before the surgery.
But it keeps leaking.
There's nothing more we can do.
The annulus is small to begin with,
so we can't tighten it further.
And the leaflet itself
isn't fully developed,
so I keep cutting through it.
I'm just ruining the shape here.
BP is still low.
Professor, this will be difficult.
What did you give?
Epinephrine, 0.05
and five micrograms of dobutamine.
For epinephrine, move it up to 0.1.
JO MUN-JEONG'S BABY, MALE, 3 WEEKS OLD
Epinephrine can go up to 0.2.
Got it.
I'm leaving for the day.
You must have a date.
No, I'm having dinner with my mom.
Patient Lee Su-yeon lost a lot of blood
during delivery. Is she okay?
Well, the bleeding has stopped.
I checked her hemoglobin count.
It's around nine,
and her pulse is around 90.
She's pretty stable now.
Really? She'll be okay, then.
Take it easy.
I'm the only one who's stuck here.
Honey.
Can we talk for a moment?
COMMON TEMPLATE FORMS
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Doctor, Do Jae-yeong is experiencing
abdominal pain. Can you check on her?
Please?
Dr. Chu.
This is the second time, tonight alone.
Okay, I'll go check.
She might be my last patient,
so I should go check on her. Jeez.
DO JAE-YEONG
Hello, let me have a look.
Ms. Do, please stay with us.
This looks like placental abruption.
What do we do?
I'll let the professors know.
Professor, Do Jae-yeong needs surgery now.
She passed a lot of blood clots,
and the baby's pulse
is hovering around 80.
Hurry. We need you here
as soon as possible.
Get an OR first.
And call Pediatrics.
Okay, got it.
Professor, we have a pregnant patient
in critical condition. We need an OR now.
She might lose the baby. Please hurry.
It's a placental abruption.
She's bleeding a lot.
Yes, as soon as possible. Thank you.
Doctor, this is Chu Min-ha.
A pregnant patient in week 30
has placental abruption.
We'll begin the surgery right away,
so please come to the OR.
Yes, thank you.
Sir, I'm sorry to ask you this,
but my pregnant patient is
in critical condition, so I'm in a rush.
If you get a speeding ticket,
I'll take care of it.
I'm sorry.
Please drive as fast as you can.
Sure.
Min-ha, call whoever you can
get a hold of and get the baby out.
No one else is available.
The fellow is doing a C-section,
and the chief resident
is performing emergency surgery.
What do I do, Professor?
What if she dies?
I'll be there in five.
Seven minutes, including the time
it takes to go up there.
You may need to get the baby out
before I get there.
You can do it, right?
No, I can't.
I'm only a second-year resident.
Then what? Will you let
both the mom and the baby die?
Go! Get the baby out!
Put me on speaker.
I'll walk you through.
I'll tell you exactly what to do,
so don't worry and just get started.
You got this, Min-ha.
Stay focused.
PROFESSOR YANG SEOK-HYEONG
Hurry, her BP will drop.
Are her vitals okay?
The bleeding is ongoing.
We must get the baby out
as soon as we can.
Professor.
I'll take it from here.
Go to the other side.
The baby's coming out.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Doctor, the baby is alive.
First layer, please.
FIRST LAYER:
TOOLS FOR SUTURE
Well done.
You did well, Dr. Chu.
Thank you, Professor.
If everything else was good,
a transplant would be an option.
But unfortunately, that is not the case.
I'm suspecting a genetic disorder,
and the brain isn't looking good either.
The heart too. We can't keep depending
on the ECMO machine,
so I'm afraid
there's nothing more we can do.
Hun must be in a lot of pain now, right?
We should probably let him go.
Right, Doctor?
Honey.
We should
let Hun go now.
That poor little thing is suffering...
Don't give him more inotropes.
INOTROPICS:
ALTERS MUSCULAR CONTRACTIONS
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
It's me, Min-ha.
Come in.
Have a seat.
This isn't my mess.
It's all his.
Oh, I see.
Is that a bribe?
Yes.
This is perfect. It doesn't look like
I can go home today anyway.
I'm sorry, Professor.
For what?
To tell you the truth,
I've been thinking
that you're kind of obnoxious.
I always thought
you were emotionally sensitive
and detail-oriented
unlike how you come across.
But I realized you can be
pretty slow-witted at times,
so I've been bitching about you to myself.
I'm sorry.
I could tell what was going on,
but residents have their own rules,
you know.
I knew you were stressed out,
but I just didn't know
how I should get involved
and sort out the situation.
Sorry.
For not looking out for you.
I've been a little...
I mean, a lot.
My feelings were really hurt, Professor.
Right, I'm sure.
I have a lot to learn.
If something like this happens again,
I'll step in and get it all sorted out.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I said a lot of mean things about you
to myself,
so let's call it even.
Min-ha.
I prefer people who are responsible
over those who are brainy and smart.
On my way here,
the taxi had to stop at a few red lights.
But every time that happened,
I got so anxious thinking
that you might quit
if we lost the patient.
Do you know how worried I was?
I know
that you'll be a good doctor.
You dealt with it responsibly.
You didn't run away,
and you did your very best.
You know what?
You did an excellent job today.
Thank you, Professor.
Go get some sleep.
I'll answer all the calls
regarding Do Jae-yeong.
-Professor.
-Yes?
Thank you for the tteokbokki.
Ms. Han told me earlier.
Oh, I see. No problem.
The day when I totally lost it,
you went and picked up tteokbokki for me
and asked everyone
to take good care of me.
You were the only one who did that for me.
She told me not to hate
the sensitive slug too much.
All right. Go get some sleep now.
Why didn't you tell me any of that?
If you did,
I wouldn't have bitched about you as much.
I figured bitching about me
would help you de-stress.
Anyway, go get some sleep.
I'm going to wash up.
Thanks, Dad.
Gosh, I said I'd take care of the bill.
Thanks.
-I'd like to pay.
-Sure.
-I'll pay for the to-go as well.
Enjoy.
Thank you for this.
You came back because of this?
Yes, I was worried about Dr. Chu.
Please take good care of her.
She must be stressed out now.
Will do.
Oh, don't tell her that it's from me.
-Okay.
-I'm off.
-Bye.
-Take it easy.
Hi, honey.
Did you have dinner?
Yes, I still have some things
to finish off.
We'll lose
a beautiful baby soon.
I have to say goodbye to the baby.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll see you on the weekend, honey.
Yes, thanks.
I love you.
My gosh, it sounds like you two are still
in the honeymoon phase.
What's going on
with your resignation letter?
What did Professor Kim say?
What's going on
with your resignation letter?
What did Professor Kim say?
Professor Kim Jun-wan
has no interest
in other people's personal lives.
Even now,
he went to say something very cruel
to the couple
who just lost their baby.
You must be devastated.
I'm sorry to have to ask you this,
knowing that.
May I ask you
to donate Hun's heart?
It's such a rare condition.
If I get another patient like Hun...
I want to save them.
I know this is a lot to ask,
but if you donate Hun's heart to us,
we'll study it
and make sure no other baby dies
from the same condition.
It'll be a difficult decision,
but please
kindly consider it.
I'm sorry again.
FOR MEDICAL PROFESSIONALS ONLY
Jo Mun-jeong's baby
expired
at 11:05 p.m.
Hun...
Daddy is so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Daddy is...
Andrea, have you decided on the date yet?
Father, I have operations
booked back to back until December.
The earliest would be
sometime at the end of December.
Would that be okay?
Yes, I think so.
They know all about your situation,
so they'll be able to make it work.
I see. I know you're a busy man.
I'm sorry to bother you with this.
No, I'm still trying to persuade Mom.
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Dr. Do, what brings you to my office?
Oh, I already spoke
with Professor Kim Jun-wan.
But I guess he's busy.
He hasn't said anything since then.
Oh, that.
It's been sorted out. You didn't hear?
Oh, does that mean
my letter of resignation was accepted?
What are you talking about?
The three-month pay cut.
It's been all sorted out.
Pardon?
Really?
Yes.
The chief of CS turned it down.
By "CS," I mean Cardiothoracic Surgery.
Regarding residents, each division's
chief makes the final call.
And the chief of CS turned it down,
which means you don't need
to worry about it anymore.
You didn't know?
But the chief position for our division
is vacant at the moment.
It no longer is.
We filled the position recently.
Very recently.
Hello?
Who is this?
Hello, Professor. It's Jun-wan.
Why are you calling so late?
I'll do it. I'll take the chief position.
What the heck are you talking about?
Hey, you... You just said you will do it.
You can't take this back, okay?
All right. I'm sorry I woke you up.
Okay, see you at work.
And Jun-wan... I mean, Professor Jun-wan
spoke with the guardian on the phone.
They said they'd just let it go
if you apologized.
And he apologized on your behalf.
He told them you're one of the residents
he's mentoring
and that he will make sure
it won't happen again.
I think he was able
to build rapport with them.
Gosh, Kim Jun-wan...
He's so good to his students.
If only he were this good
to his professors.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
KIM JUN-WAN
AHN JEONG-WON
Who is it?
It's me, Jae-hak.
Do you have a black suit?
-Yes.
-Then go get changed.
I'll meet you in the lobby.
Well...
In conclusion,
it hasn't spread.
-Thank God!
-My gosh!
Gosh...
My gosh.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-Thank you.
Dad, you're good.
You're good now.
This means that you can eat now.
Yes, let's eat.
No metastasis found
in your chest, brain, and bones.
Everything looks good,
which is amazing news.
Now, we can just perform the surgery
as planned.
It's small,
and we found it at an early stage.
So keep up with the treatment
after the surgery, and you'll be fine.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-My gosh.
-Dad, let's eat something.
-Okay, sounds good.
Dad, this is such great news.
Am I the only one who's eating?
-That's right.
-Gosh, congratulations.
-Thank you.
-I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations.
My gosh, thank you.
Keep up with the treatment,
and you'll recover in no time.
Yes, thank you. Thank you so much.
Oh, have you called
your insurance company? I'll show you.
Thank you.
He's become much more cheerful
after he moved to this ward.
Thank you all for your help.
-Thank you.
-Gosh, we didn't even do anything.
All we did was chat with him.
That's not true.
You kept him company and cheered him up
when we were running around,
and you helped us stay strong.
Thanks to you, we were able
to get through the past few days.
Thank you so much, all of you.
-Thank you.
-Then let's have a party!
-Yes!
-Yes! A party sounds great!
-Let's do it.
-Let's party!
-Let's do it!
-Yes!
My gosh, it's such great news.
-Honey.
-Yes.
Give the doctors something to drink.
Oh, okay.
It's all right. No need.
We're not thirsty.
You must've been in a lot of pain
yesterday. How are you feeling now?
I feel fine.
Much better than yesterday, for sure.
Doctor, thank you.
For saving me and my baby.
Don't thank me.
You should thank Dr. Chu Min-ha here.
Dr. Chu.
Thank you.
I was such a handful, wasn't I?
I'm sorry. I'm usually not like that.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's okay.
I completely understand.
I would've been the same way.
I'm so glad that both you
and your baby are okay.
I'm very grateful.
Thank you.
Don't cry.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
You're going home early today.
Yes, I have plans this evening.
With Dr. Chu Min-ha?
No.
I'll be off, then.
-Hi, Andrea.
Did you see an angel or something?
Gosh, why are you all spaced out?
It's cold. Get in.
Okay.
"He has cancer."
As soon as I said that,
his whole family just froze.
His family must've felt like
their whole world was collapsing.
It's something you think
you'd only hear in dramas.
But it didn't spread,
so his family is having a party tonight.
My gosh, really?
Yes, with other patients in the ward
and their families.
Before his surgery?
Yes.
What a happy family. I envy them.
Yes, they're such a happy family.
He has two daughters.
But since he checked into the hospital,
they haven't been going to work
or to the library. My gosh.
His whole family stopped
doing everything else to look after him.
Gosh. I mean,
it's unfortunate that he's ill.
But it's so lovely to see.
That's how a family should be.
I rarely call my dad,
but they inspired me to call him.
I went to see a patient
who's recovering from her C-section,
and I could just see
how much her husband loves her.
From the way he was looking at her,
I could tell that he loves her very much.
Even I felt the warm fuzzies.
-Get remarried, then.
-Right back at you.
What about Jun-wan?
He has plans.
He said we should just do it without him.
Gosh, he's going crazy about this girl.
Who is he dating?
I'd love to meet her.
With Ik-jun's hand like that
and Jun-wan bailing on us,
why don't we just practice another time?
What are you talking about?
Hey, my fingers are fine.
Had you not tied them so tight,
it wouldn't have taken this long.
Doctors who go overboard
are always the problem.
What the hell?
I got to the wedding 30 minutes late
because of you.
Why go to a stranger's wedding
to begin with?
I was late because of you.
My hand is like this because of you.
I shouldn't have helped you.
You're banned from my office.
Jeez, then you're banned
from my office too.
-Oh, gosh!
-What? What is it?
-Nothing.
-You little...
Jeez.
Around the time
When the stars outside my window
Start to fade away one by one
I write a letter to the sky
You left me for another man
But I still can't forget you
So I gather my tears
And send them to the sky
Even if you don't love me
I will lie down by your side
Whenever you need me
Because I can't forget you
I will just keep on loving you
My darling, I will wait for you
When my tear-filled letter reaches the sky
You will come back to me someday
Back to me
I believe that you will, with all my tears
"WITH ALL MY TEARS"
Even if you don't love me
I will lie down by your side
Whenever you need me
Because I can't forget you
I will just keep on loving you
My darling, I will wait for you
When my tear-filled letter reaches the sky
You will come back to me someday
Back to me
Doctor...
My darling, I will wait for you
When my tear-filled letter reaches the sky
You will come back to me someday
Back to me
I believe that you will
With all my tears
What is your name?
Have you been experiencing
dizziness or vomiting?
How's your vision?
-Let's move the patient.
-Okay.
How are you feeling?
Stay with us.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
I practically begged her on my knees,
in tears.
I said we should be happy
even if we just had one day left to live.
The situation was critical,
so it's still too early to tell.
Let's wait and see.
I'm so worried.
Mr. Ju has been diagnosed
with early-stage depression.
What?
I think he collapsed
due to ICH in the cerebellum.
Hey, are you all right?
What's the matter?
-What?
-The situation isn't looking good at all.
What do we do? We don't have time.
It's my fault.
I'll take care of it, no matter what.
It's raining. Shall we go for a drive?
You said you have plans this evening.
I guess you have no interest
in getting married.
The guy kept asking her to marry him,
and Ik-sun liked him enough
to change her mind about it.
You know that talking about this
is pointless, right?
What will happen to us?
Oh, Gyeo-ul is here.
He lied to you,
and he's always so cold to you.
You still like him?
Just one month. In a month,
it'll be all over for good.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs