[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 16]
[Zhang's Mansion]
My lady, hurry up.
Miss Chen, you're here.
Why don't you take a rest?
It’s OK.
Let me help you, sister Niaoniao.
Master, you are drunk.
Did He do anything to you?
No way. Don’t talk nonsense.
Miss Chen.
Go in and have a look.
Architect Chen.
Li Qingfeng.
Well, do you need my help?
Does your head still hurt?
No.
You are the deputy architect.
Of course I need your help.
What should I do?
You wrote so much material for internal decoration.
Don't you remember?
No.
Here.
[The draft of tent in the Northern Zhou]
My Chinese characters are...
They are cute.
Why are you staring at me?
I like watching you.
OK. Let’s get back to work.
I heard that Miss Zhang is getting worse
and slowly losing weight.
We need to speed up.
OK. You're the boss.
Where are you taking me?
I want to go to the most beautiful house.
You'll know when you arrive.
Brother.
I'm so tired.
I want to go to the most beautiful house. I want to sleep.
We'll be there in a minute.
W...where am I?
Dad, I want to go to the most beautiful house.
Brother. Father.
Architect Li, take me with you.
I want to go to the most beautiful house. Please.
Fu, wait.
Wang Sheng.
Architect Li, what are you doing?
Architect Li, you’ve gone too far.
Fu, let’s go.
Go.
Fu,
I can’t give you a luxurious dress.
I can't give you a nice house like that in Lin'an.
What I have
is a heart that will love you forever.
You...
Will you marry me?
Yes.
In my opinion, this tent
is the most beautiful house in the world.
Fu, when I return to Lin'an,
I’ll go to your house to propose marriage.
If your father doesn't agree...
Xu Qian, no matter what,
I will be with you forever.
The most beautiful house.
This is the most beautiful house in the world.
Xu Qian, do you see it?
I'm back.
Father. Brother.
Fu, you remember everything?
Thank you.
Fu, I’m sorry.
I found the most beautiful house.
But the best person is gone.
Thank you all.
So,
Mr. Zhang still thinks that
[Win-ever Gambling House]
Miss Zhang's love with a man from the Northern Zhou
is a shame to his family.
It’s not easy
to erase the bias against family status.
In this world,
in my opinion, only Miss Zhao Yining
can ignore these things.
Only Mr. Zhao gives his daughter
the right to select on her own.
It’s really rare.
I...I just said that.
That's true.
I really admire
Miss Zhao for this.
Li Qingfeng,
you are so lucky.
You mean
you still regret that you are not lucky enough?
No, no.
Master, you misunderstood.
I didn’t mean that.
Luo, explain it for me.
Master, I…
What are you laughing at?
Master.
I was just kidding.
[Lehudu]
The tide and the sea
cannot compare to the love of thee and me.
Tide is more reliable than love when we're blaming each other.
My love for you is deeper than the sea when I'm missing you.
Don’t be hypocritical.
When did I become such a person?
But I just don’t understand.
Everyone likes me
and tries everything to pursue me.
But you, Li Qingfeng,
you ignore my feelings,
and have hurt me so many times.
But I still can't hate you.
Forget it. I should have known
I love you.
There's no reason for love.
Coming.
Architect Chen.
Come in.
Tell me. What is it?
Something happened at home.
Lord wants you to go back.
Why does he ask me to go back again?
I give you a farewell dinner in this private garden
because I hope no one will disturb us.
I hope you don't mind.
Your Majesty treats outsiders as brothers and friends.
Just like the Northern Zhou and the Southern Xiao are only separated by a narrow strip of water.
I know what you mean.
I will convey your words to my father.
Indeed, we're only separated by a narrow strip of water.
The foundation of peace between the two states
is among those words.
Exactly.
We are so close geographically.
If we can unite by marriage one day,
it would be a blessing for the people of both states.
Your Majesty, you're always concerned
about the state.
I sincerely respect you.
Here.
Thank you, Princess Zhaohe, for your company
during my stay in Lin'an.
I think when I return to Northern Zhou,
I'll always think of this time.
Don't say that.
You are my friend from afar.
Come on.
Come on, friends from afar.
Prince.
His Majesty was here just now.
I haven't thanked you properly.
Thank me?
For the tent.
You are too kind.
For me,
a bigger event is more worth
of your thanks.
A bigger event?
You can discuss it with His Majesty.
I like nothing else but eating, drinking,
and building houses.
It seems His Majesty
hasn’t mentioned that big event to you yet.
What is it?
His Majesty asked you to send me out
to give me a chance
to tell you in person.
In fact, I came to Southern Xiao this time
with a big event
other than political discussions.
Don't keep me guessing.
Tell me, what is it?
The marriage
with princess royal in Southern Xiao.
Brother.
You may leave.
Is what Yelv Zhigu said true?
Brother,
I don't want that Prince.
Please cancel the marriage as soon as possible.
The agreement between the two states is not a joke.
You haven't asked me if I want it.
Isn't this a joke?
Your marriage is a national affair.
Why can't I make the decision?
But I love
Li Qingfeng.
Li Qingfeng?
I told you that
you two can be friends, but you can only be friends.
Brother, why?
Langyue.
It's my fault to hide this from you.
But I have my own thoughts.
You are my favorite sister,
but you're also Princess Zhaohe of the Xiao.
Now,
your marriage has become a national affair.
Not only you have no choice,
even I
have no choice.
Why?
You can't understand the crisis of the state.
In the past two years,
the Northern Zhou has invaded the border of our state for many times.
-But we... -I don't care about that.
You don't care about that.
But I’m serious.
This matter has been settled.
I see.
It turns out that you have planned everything.
You made up your mind when you asked Madam to teach me
needlework and rites.
No wonder you asked me
to take Yelv Zhigu to hang around Lin'an.
No wonder you told Li Qingfeng
that I have an engagement.
It turns out that you did all this
on purpose.
It's useless to talk more.
Go back to the palace as soon as possible.
Don't leave the palace anymore.
Fatuous Emperor.
I am the emperor.
How dare you say that?
The princess has returned to the Wood Feather House.
She doesn't want to stay any longer.
Since the marriage has been put on the agenda,
should I take her back to the palace?
You keep protecting her.
You'll take her back
when I need her.
This is the last freedom
I can give to Langyue.
Yes.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Since you came back,
you have something on your mind.
That obvious?
It's written on your face.
I don't want to force you,
but I still hope you can tell me.
No matter what happens,
I'm willing to face it with you,
even if it takes my life.
Do you understand?
-I... -Qingfeng,
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
I officially inform both of you that
Wood Feather House has another big deal.
Everyone,
this is a great opportunity for the House
to earn great repute in Lin'an.
It’s raining heavily, but we still need to work.
Did the water destroy a bridge?
You are correct.
I was just kidding.
Exactly.
There is a wooden bridge outside Jin'nan County.
Over the years,
people in Zhang's village and Xu's village can use it.
The two villages communicated with the outside through this bridge,
and got along well.
But recently,
the bridge was destroyed by heavy rains.
So residents in the two villages decided to repair this bridge together.
Just to renovate a broken bridge for two remote villages?
Does it have anything to do with being famous in Lin'an?
There's something you don't know.
The two villages
were supposed to split the bill 50-50.
But Xu's villagers thought
they only have half of the people of Zhang's village.
They only want to pay 33% of the total cost.
In desperation,
this matter came to the government office in Jin'nan County,
then to the Ministry of Works.
The Ministry of Works can do nothing about it.
Because this bridge is a civil building,
so they can't use public funds.
Recently, the heavy rain
has destroyed the houses in many places.
The Ministry of Works doesn't even have enough people.
Under desperation,
they had to hire a folk team,
which means the Wood Feather House has undertaken this job.
Didn't you say the Ministry of Works has no money?
Yes.
So you mean
we will have to work for free
and clean up a mess.
This is why it is the best time for our House
to be famous in Lin'an.
We have to be famous before we can make profits.
We just need to make Xu's village
to pay the half of the money,
and then we repair the bridge.
It will be a great favor to the Ministry of Works.
If the Ministry of Works has any work in the future,
they will definitely choose the Wood Feather House.
With the support of the Ministry of Works,
our Wood Feather House will be famous in Lin'an.
In this case,
this is a good opportunity.
We can go and have a look.
Wait.
Am I the only one that found the problem?
Xu's village refused to pay.
They first came to the county government,
and then to the Ministry of Works.
It hasn't been solved yet.
It's easier said than done, Luo Ye.
Can that empty talk
you made
make them willing to pay for the other half?
Since Luo Yao said it,
it means he's confident.
You trust your brother a lot, huh?
Well, Mr. Luo,
may I ask, what is your plan?
Take measures according to the actual situation.
If you can really solve this,
I'll be convinced by you.
To be honest,
I have made a promise with the Ministry of Works.
Anyway,
we must do it well.
It will take some time
to go to Jin'nan County.
Well,
girls, pack your bags first.
I will report to Miss Zhao.
Qingfeng,
go pack the tools now.
OK.
Officer,
you and Wang Sheng go find a few carriages.
We’ll leave immediately
when the rain lets up.
Don't bring too thick clothes.
No way.
Even the rain lets up in Lin'an,
it may not stop raining in the county.
It's a long journey and it's cold in the carriage.
What if you get cold?
We won't sleep in the carriage.
No way.
In the middle of nowhere,
if you catch a cold,
I'll be guilty.
My lady, do you want to bring the moon?
Take it.
What if you can't sleep without the moon
after we arrive?
Stop joking.
I’m so worried now.
I hardly know
how to tell Li Qingfeng who I am.
Now His Majesty wants me to get married and move to the Northern Zhou.
I have no idea how to tell him.
What would Architect Li do
if you tell him the truth directly?
I can't imagine.
I think
you should beg His Majesty.
Don't say that to me again.
If I say one more word to His Majesty,
I'm afraid I'll be locked up
and tied up to send to the Northern Zhou.
How could His Majesty...
How could he bear to let you leave?
Unfortunately, His Majesty has made up his mind.
Luo,
I have no choice.
If that's the case,
why didn't His Majesty ask Lord Wang
to take you back to the palace?
I don't know.
I just have a hunch
that the situation will get worse.
Forget it.
Don’t think about these troubles.
Just
let it be.
That's what it is.
[Ledger]
This is a good time for us
to be famous again.
I'm afraid it's not as simple as I thought.
The harder it is,
the more it can show the outstanding points of our Wood Feather House.
Boss,
do you want to go with us?
I won't go.
Boss,
you haven't been to Wood Feather House for a long time.
Do you want me to gather everyone before you leave
to listen to your instructions?
Don't be so glib with me.
I'm fine.
I'm not going to the Wood Feather House
because I have other things to do.
It's good that you're fine.
If anything happens to me,
I won't withdraw the investment of Wood Feather House.
I've invested in a lot of businesses these years.
Only a glib businessman like you
does the job well.
Thank you for your compliment.
If there's nothing else, I'll go back.
Boss,
are you really not going to see everyone off?
Forget it.
It makes me look distant.
Let's go back to the Wood Feather House.
Miss Zhao, please.
Everyone,
as for these three carriages
except the first carriage Wang Sheng drove,
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
you can arrange the rest.
Li Qingfeng, wait.
I have something to tell you.
Miss Chen, please come with us.
Is she here to make trouble again?
No.
Just now in the meeting hall,
Miss Zhao wished us
to complete this job successfully.
Since Miss Zhao doesn't go to Jin'nan with us,
she must have let it go.
Architects.
First of all, I want to congratulate you.
After these days, I've figured it out.
You two are the best people
to match each other.
A few days ago, I had a fantasy.
But then I thought about it, I shouldn’t have.
I, Zhao Yining, am not a troublemaker.
So the second thing
is to ask you to forgive me for being restrained in the past.
Miss Zhao, you overstated.
Miss Chen, just say you forgive me.
Okay.
So the third thing
is to bring me something novel or delicious
in Jin'nan,
if you find any.
Is that too much to ask?
OK, I promise you.
You finally promised me one thing.
There's nothing left to say.
Take care.
I’ll wait for you.
Li Qingfeng,
can you give me a friendly hug?
Miss Zhao, thank you.
Take care.
I’m leaving. Take care.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Anyway,
I want to take a carriage with Master.
I don't want to take the same carriage with you.
Master.
Please don’t.
I have to serve her on the way.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Luo is right.
Luo, get in.
There are fruits
for you and Architect Chen.
Architect Chen will get in soon.
Luo Ye.
Didn't you hear what I said?
Officer,
we should
find our own home.
What do you mean?
Mr. Luo means
it would be tiring on the way.
You should take a carriage with Luo.
Luo.
What about you?
Don't worry.
Architect Chen has her own carriage.
OK.
Let's go.
Architect. Let's get in the car.
If I took a carriage with you,
would Mr. Luo hate me?
You overstated.
Can't you see that, Niaoniao?
If we separate Qingfeng and Architect Chen,
we will be the worst sinners in the world.
Let Mr. Luo arrange it.
We only have three carriages.
Get in.
Let's go. That one.
OK.
Get in the car.
Wang Sheng and I have something to talk.
I’ve been observing you for days, but you haven’t made any moves.
His Majesty really said nothing?
No.
Really?
His Majesty has no clear instruction.
I trust you for the time being.
I'll drive the second carriage.
No need. You can drive the first carriage.
Yes.
Let me do it.
OK.
Luo, sit here.
I don't know if my lady needs anything or not.
Li Qingfeng is there.
You don't need to worry about Master.
Since when did you trust Architect Li so much?
That’s because I can’t do anything.
What can I do now?
Wang Sheng, do you want an apple?
No.
Forget it.
No wonder Luo Ye has changed.
Three women can take one carriage.
Three men can take another carriage.
But now there is a third car.
Aren't you satisfied with the distribution?
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
Everyone is happy.
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
That's why Luo Ye is smart.
♫The moon hidden in the boundless night sky♫
I want to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
Miss Zhao loved you so much before,
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
have you ever liked her?
Never.
♫You are the starry night sky♫
Then how much do you like me?
♫Every single word♫
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
Can't you feel it?
I want you to say it yourself.
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
♫Not knowing why♫
It.
♫Just let it pass by♫
Did you hear that?
It.
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
Am I talking about saying "it"?
Li Qingfeng,
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
why are you so flippant now?
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
♫From dark night to dawn♫
♫Stars have sunk into the sea♫
♫And I only want to belong to you♫
Mr. Luo, what kind of calculations are you doing?
Niaoniao.
I really care about my money.
What’s wrong?
Qingfeng and I
can take one carriage together.
But now there are two more carriages.
It costs a lot of money!
They are right.
You are the reincarnation of the calculator.
I'm making money for marrying you.
If you want to wash my clothes,
you'll have plenty of chances after we arrive in Jin'nan.
You wish.
You look like you bite your tongue.
Do you have something to tell me?
Actually,
I should tell you.
But
I don't know how to say it.
Don't worry. We have plenty of time.
I can wait patiently.
Before,
you kept chasing me around and asking me.
Why? Are you not anxious now?
Do you want me to keep asking you?
Forget it. Forget it.
I won't ask if you don't want to tell me.
Isn't this the trust you want?
Yes.
But...
Don't say "but".
I can stop asking.
But after coming back from Jin'nan,
you must go home with me.
Go to your home?
My father has been waiting.
If
we can come back together,
I'll go.
Really?
Yes.
OK. Take a look.
Lay your cards. Lay your cards.
I...
I won.
Luo, you won many rounds.
Of course.
Sir,
you taught me this.
Triple  with single.
You learned so fast.
It's windy.
I'll go get some thick clothes for my lady.
Li Qingfeng.
I don't think it's necessary. Forget it.
I'm just calling your name.
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
Look.
The sky is clean after the rain.
♫I feel so safe♫
So many stars.
♫My dreams are all about you♫
Nothing in the human world
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
can compare to the stars in your eyes.
♫Just want to meet you again♫
♫I am so lucky♫
And the moon.
♫You did not give up♫
Two moons.
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
Cut it out.
♫You'll show me the world♫
There are stars in the eyes of the moon.
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
I can't see it.
Then I'll take them off.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
What are you doing?
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
It's for you.
♫Ask your heart♫
Star.
♫Even if only a drop♫
Moon.
♫A drop, a drop♫
Be careful. It's hot.
♫A drop of love is left♫
Is it good?
Yes.
Have a taste.
Let me have a taste.
♫I would love to♫
I remember.
Here, take it.
Everyone, it's cold at night.
I've prepared some good wine.
Would you like to have a drink
to warm up?
Great! Great!
To improve my luck in gambling,
of course I have to drink good wine.
OK.
The wine is in the carriage. I'll get it.
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
Good wine.
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
Come on. Cheers.
-Wait a minute. -Cheers.
♫I feel so safe♫
I have something to say.
♫My dreams are all about you♫
I wish our Wood Feather House
will be successful in the future.
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
I wish everyone here
to be happy
♫Just want to meet you again♫
Be happy.
I hope
everyone will stay in our House.
♫I am so lucky♫
Wood Feather House is the best team.
♫You did not give up♫
The best team.
Cheers!
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
♫You'll show me the world♫
♫Put on the wedding dress for you♫
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
[Honest and Justice]
[Silence]
[Keep away Silence]
Stop arguing.
My lord.
Are you from Lin'an?
Yes.
Are you the craftsman team hired by the Ministry of Works?
Great.
Oh my God!
You're finally here.
Now they can stop arguing.
This is the craftsman team
sent by the Ministry of Works to repair the bridge for us.
If you have anything to say, just tell them.
OK.
Please judge for me.
Zhang's village has over 300 households.
We only have 150 households.
Why should we pay half of the money?
The bridge is used together.
We need to repair it together.
So you pay half of the cost. What's wrong with that?
Who are you scolding?
I'm scolding you.
Say it again.
Enough.
[Keep away Silence]
-Stop. -I’m scolding you.
Enough. Stop arguing.
We're here to repair the bridge,
not to solve the case for you.
How about this?
Take us to the scene.
If this work is not complicated,
it won't cost much.
You don't have to fight like this.
Am I right?
No matter what,
they offer 66% of it.
I'll give 33%.
Listen.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who are you scolding?
You have no conscience.
We were so nice to you.
We gave you the rice every year.
You have any shame at all?
We exchanged the rice with fish.
It's natural to exchange things with things.
Don't talk like we owe you.
OK.
From this year on,
just eat fish every day.
You won't be able to
eat a single fish from Zhang's village.
I won't eat fish.
I won't.
Fine.
Alright.
Why are you quarreling again?
Can you take us to the scene?
Just go.
I'm not afraid.
Let's go.
Lord, please.
I'm going too?
You are the county magistrate.
Who else will go if you don't go?
Please.
[Impartiality and integrity]
Everyone,
I think
you'll have to stay in Jin'nan County for a while.
I've prepared the room.
Thank you, Lord Zhou.
Niaoniao, Luo.
You don’t need to go.
Set up the luggage and tools in the car.
OK.
My lady,
is it dangerous for you to go?
Don’t worry.
They are ordinary villagers,
not bandits.
Yes, Luo.
Li is here.
She won’t be in danger.
Let's go to the scene first.
My lady, be careful.
It's okay.
They are fighting.
Charge!
Xu's village must be making trouble.
We don’t cause trouble,
but we are not afraid of trouble.
I'm not afraid of you either.
Stop fighting!
It’s really lively.
This is not a good time to stand by.
If someone gets hurt,
the conflicts between the two villages can't be reconciled.
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
Master, don't come over.
Stop fighting!
Alright.
I'll protect you. Let's go.
Guys, stop fighting!
Stop fighting!
Stop!
That's what I'm saying.
Can it solve the problem?
What should we do?
Yes, what should we do?
Everyone, calm down.
Qingfeng, you and Architect Chen go to have a look
to check the amount of work.
Let's go.
Everyone, calm down. Don't fight.
Let's check the amount of work.
The bridge deck is completely broken.
Only the bridge abutment is left.
But the deck and the abutment are a whole.
Even if we build
a strong deck,
the standing pier,
will not be as persistent as before, I'm afraid.
It will collapse from heavy rain.
I think the underwater foundation of the bridge deck
is basically destroyed by the water.
I'm afraid we need to build a new bridge.
Build a new wooden bridge?
The work amount is huge.
Not a wooden bridge, but a stone bridge.
A stone bridge?
Yes, look at this river.
The upstream is the confluence of two tributaries.
The water flows are not small even in sunny days.
Even if we build
a strong bridge deck,
the part under the water will still be washed out by water.
It's still dangerous.
So for safety,
we need to build a stone bridge,
a stone arch bridge.
Let's go.
We can't make it clear.
We have to check the amount of work before we can solve the problem.
Qingfeng, how's the work?
I need to build a new stone arch bridge.
This is really a big project.
Sir,
you're here to build the bridge for us.
We all agree.
We all rely on the bridge to live by.
It's natural to spend money on repairing the bridge.
But if they want us to pay half of the money,
we will never agree.
Yes, never.
Look.
They are so unreasonable.
I don't want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to you either.
Sir,
if you have a solution,
the whole village will thank you.
If you can't work it out,
you can go back to where you come from.
We won't repair this bridge.
Yes, we won't repair it.
Yeah.
You just said you all relied on this bridge,
but you won't repair it now in a blink of an eye.
You change so fast.
What's wrong with that?
Stop arguing.
Stop arguing!
Everyone, listen to me.
Calm down.
Give us some time.
We will find a solution.
Sir,
since you promised that you have a solution,
I trust you.
Tell us, how many days do you need?
Three days.
Just three days. How about that?