[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 4]
Let's go.
Hurry up.
[Construction according to conditions]
Luckily, it's not serious.
But it'll still take some time to recover.
All right.
How did the fire start?
Someone must have set it.
Because before the fire started,
our door had been locked from inside.
Who the hell did it!
If I catch him,
I won't let him be off the hook easily.
This is not the most important thing right now.
Grandma's house is.
But Grandma's house is almost burnt down.
We told Grandma we could finish in three days.
But now...
It was an accident.
If we tell Grandma about the accident, she will understand.
No.
If Grandma finds out,
she will feel guiltier about it,
and it will scare Tongtong.
This is also
why Miss Chen asked Luo to stall grandma
so that she wouldn't know
the real reason Qingfeng got hurt, right?
Architect Li is right.
The most important thing right now
is Grandma's house.
What about the arsonist?
Wang Sheng.
Did you see anyone last night?
No.
I guess it must be Butcher Zhang.
No way.
We already took over his shop.
How dare he do so?
It's exactly because I took over his shop
that he sought revenge.
Let's put it aside for now.
Just take it as an accident
so that the culprit will lower his guard.
And we will be able to catch him.
Anyway, we need to build Grandma's house first.
But how are we gonna do it?
It's burned down completely.
Architect Li, what do we do now?
It's not as bad as we thought.
Grandma's house wasn't valuable in itself.
So it's easier to rebuild it according to the drafting,
especially the re-direction of the fire path.
As long as we change the fire path
according to the current drafting,
there will be no problem,
and the underfloor heating will also be solved.
It's just that time is limited.
Slow down.
We have no time to lose.
Be careful.
Let's continue the work.
How about you leave it to me?
You can't work while you're still injured.
I'm fine.
[Wood Feather Pavillion]
Here is 1.1 feet.
Here. 1.3 feet.
And this is 1.6 feet.
The bed will be placed here.
So the temperature of the bed shouldn't be too high.
Otherwise,
Tongtong and Grandma will get hot,
and they may fall ill.
Now Mr. Luo and Meng Yuanxu
have gone to clean the scene.
In the afternoon, we will be able to follow this drafting
to set the fire path.
OK.
Li Qingfeng.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I told you to be careful.
I'm fine.
Li Qingfeng.
Miss Zhao, don't get me wrong.
We... We...didn't do anything.
I heard you were burned.
Why don't you stay in bed and recuperate?
You're still working when you're injured?
Just a minor injury.
It doesn't matter.
This is
a gift to my father from one of his friends.
There are mint, thistle, purple Dahurian angelica,
Sanguisorba officinalis...
Anyway, there are many other ingredients as well.
Put it in your tub when taking a bath.
It helps reduce swelling and relieve pain.
Thank you, Miss Zhao.
You're welcome.
Architect Li.
How about I take everybody to the fire scene now?
I shall go with you.
Li Qingfeng, did you not hear me?
I don't want you to work while you're still injured.
Tongtong's house was burnt,
and we have limited time for renovation. I...
Miss Zhao is right.
It's not good for you to wok with your injury.
Why don't you just have a good rest?
Go back to work when you're recovered.
OK.
Go and check it out there.
Don't worry about the exterior walls for now.
Start from the inside first.
All right.
Got it. I'm off.
Vegetables! Fresh vegetables!
[Wood Feather House]
Chen Langyue, you idiot.
You forgot to bring the drafting.
[Wood Feather House]
Why is it so smoky here?
Is it on fire?
Miss Zhao.
Li Qingfeng.
Why aren't you dressed?
I'm taking a bath.
I forgot to take the drafting, so here I am.
I saw smoke in your room
and I thought it might be on fire.
No, it's not.
So are you gonna stay here?
No.
Miss Zhao is back!
So...
I don't want her to misunderstand me.
Won't what you're doing create a bigger misunderstanding?
Li Qingfeng.
Are you okay?
Why is the door open?
I'm fine.
Miss Zhao,
the wind blew the door open.
please wait for me in the meeting room.
I'll go as soon as I get dressed.
OK.
Both the window and the door are closed.
Where did the wind come from?
I see. It's breeze blowing.
I'm going to get dressed.
I haven't finished yet.
I'm ready.
Are you?
I don't know what you like to eat.
So I bought something of everything.
See? This is almond.
And plum cakes.
Steamed abalone.
There are more down there.
Miss Chen.
Miss Zhao, you're still here?
Take your time.
I just came back to get something.
See you.
[Wood Feather Pavillion]
Li Qingfeng.
You're back.
You scared me.
I was a little tired.
I just fell asleep.
Did everything go well today?
Thanks to you, Architect Li,
it went very well.
That's good.
I'll work tomorrow too.
You...
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
Wait for me.
What is this?
Your hairpin was burned in the fire.
Here's a new one.
You can insert it into the hair,
clip your hair with it
or comb your hair when you open it.
You're welcome.
I like hairpins.
I also like contraptions.
But a hairpin with contraptions...
You don't like it?
It's good.
I like it.
See you tomorrow morning then.
♫The smile at the corners of your mouth♫
♫Like a petal flying into the heart♫
♫Weaving the feathers of youthful dreams♫
♫Take me through the darkness of the night ♫
♫Watching for the next dawn♫
♫Counting in time♫
♫those old footprints♫
♫It's me who defies the odds♫
♫to embark on a long journey for you♫
♫You're the shining star♫
♫in our story♫
♫A glance is better than anything else♫
♫Life is as beautiful as my passion♫
♫Youth returns as♫
♫the clear sky yesterday♫
♫There's a time for everything♫
♫It's our journey together♫
Grandma, this house...
Is this our house?
It looks completely different.
I've never
lived in such a clean and nice place.
Grandma.
Everyone of us has worked hard
for the renovation.
I hope you'll live comfortably here.
Grandma, let's take a look at the inside.
Let's go.
Do you like it?
Yes.
So beautiful.
Grandma, the bed is really comfortable.
Is it?
Great.
Give the bowls to everyone.
OK.
Dinner is ready.
The dishes are ready. There you go.
Come on.
Kids,
thank you for giving me and Tongtong
a cosy and beautiful home.
Let's eat together.
OK.
Come on.
Great.
Miss, hurry up.
Don't touch me.
Don't go back. I can do it.
Look at them.
I want more.
You're drunk!
Slow down.
Take care.
Come on.
Master, I haven't had enough.
I'm so dizzy. I drank too much.
Master.
I feel terrible.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Have you noticed that someone is following us?
Yes.
Look at you. You have no clue.
I do.
You don't!
Alright, let's get down to business.
If you don't tell me,
everybody will be gone.
Let's check it out.
[Wood Feather House]
Who's that?
The one who set the fire.
I don't think he's the butcher.
Maybe he’s a spy sent by the butcher.
We haven't taken any action so far.
So he asked someone to keep an eye on us.
[Wood Feather House]
Now we have two options.
One is to follow that guy
and find out the truth.
The other is to do nothing.
When the butcher thinks he's safe,
he'll come out himself.
That butcher is so vicious.
I won't let him get away with it again.
Let's go.
Come on.
Who?
It's me.
No one is following you, right?
Of course not.
Come in.
How is it?
Everything looked normal.
They drank a lot after the construction
and went back to the Wood Feather House.
They didn't mention the fire at all.
They probably think it was just an accident.
Idiots.
In that case,
I don't have to hide here.
Two of them were in the house.
Weren't you afraid you would kill them when you set fire?
That's even better.
Now who knows I did it?
Who is it?
I know.
I won't admit it.
What can you do to me?
Do you recognize this?
This is...
Behave yourself.
I didn't set fire.
The butcher did it.
You're going to tell the government about that.
I followed you because I didn't want you to find him.
Because...
Because I'm here
to kill the butcher myself.
One should never take advantage of his friends' wife.
But that asshole Zhang Ganglie harassed my wife.
I saw you did it.
Dong Ergou!
You traitor!
As the saying goes,
you get what you deserve and reap what you sow.
Zhang Ganglie,
do you really think I'm here to help you?
Bastard.
I provided you with this shelter
so that no one else could find you
and I can get close to you.
Had Mr. Li and Miss Chen not come,
I would have killed you tonight.
Dong Ergou,
I'm gonna make you pay for it!
If you do too many evil deeds, you will get yourself killed eventually.
You deserve it!
[Zhen's Spices]
Miss Chen and Qingfeng sent the butcher to the court
and found a witness.
This matter is officially settled now.
Tongtong and Grandma don't have to worry anymore.
Considerable credit should be given to you two.
Actually, I didn't do anything.
It's all thanks to Miss Chen. She was very observant
and helped catch the butcher.
If you want to give credit,
give it to Miss Chen.
But
if it weren't for you,
on the night of the fire,
I would have already been burnt into ashes.
Besides, if it weren't for you last night,
I couldn't have caught the butcher by myself.
Both of you did a good job. Don't be modest.
Anyway,
we've had a perfect ending of this matter.
Well done, everyone.
By the way,
you need to deal with the trial today.
OK.
Now that the butcher's going to stand trial,
I'm supposed to deal with the case.
I will make sure that the guy never gets out of prison.
You can't handle his case.
If you do, people will criticize you.
Architect Li is right.
Mr. Luo should go instead.
Master.
Why are you always defending Li Qingfeng?
Am I?
When did I do that?
Since the night of the fire,
the way you treat Li Qingfeng has changed.
If you have nothing else to say, go back to your room.
Sir.
Miss.
Go.
Miss Chen, you just dismissed him...
No worries.
He will be fine soon.
Since Grandma's house is done,
I should leave now.
What?
Are you leaving?
Miss Han.
You said you have work
for us to do, didn't you?
I thought about it later.
feeling it too complicated.
Architect Li, you would be too good for the job.
So I don't think you should waste your precious time
to do it.
I'm not afraid of complicated work.
It will help prove the strength and improve the reputation
of our Wood Feather House, right?
Qingfeng is right.
Anyway, forget it.
No, you can't leave.
That's right, Miss Han.
Let's not talk about the job.
Would you please consider
working as a supervisor in the Wood Feather House?
I'm really sorry.
See you then.
Miss Han!
Why?
It seems that
there's something she couldn't tell us.
Since you really want her to work here,
I shall go to bring her back now.
Go!
Her lady didn't mean to upset you.
Please don't take it personally.
Luo.
I need to go home.
Come with me.
Me?
For what?
Robbery.
Robbery?
Go home for robbery?
Right.
Aren't you afraid that
Lord Meng will punish you?
I won't rob him.
Then who are you going to rob?
My mother.
Rob Madam Meng?
You know what.
My mother has prepared a gift to her future daughter-in-law.
It's a bracelet.
I'm going to take it
and give it to Master when the time is right.
Let's go.
Sir.
Why do you want to give her a token of love all of a sudden?
You silly girl.
Didn't you see how they talked to each other today?
If I don't take any action,
Master will be taken away
from me by that Li Qingfeng.
But Sir,
if you just
give her lady the bracelet so rashly,
she won't accept it.
I know.
That's why I said
I'll give it to her when the time is right.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
OK.
Check it out.
Miss Han!
Mr. Luo.
What are you doing here?
Miss Han, are you free now?
Let's go to the teahouse for a cup of tea
and have a chat.
Sir.
Do we really have to do this?
This is the make-or-break moment.
But we're gonna do it in broad daylight.
Isn't this too risky?
Don't worry.
I know my home very well.
There's a route that no one will take.
OK.
Come on.
I have a plan.
The bracelet is in my mother's jewelry box.
Her room is right in the front. It's not far from here.
After going through three scenic walls, four hallways,
and two gardens, we'll arrive at her room.
I'll go in and get the bracelet.
And you stay outside and be on the watch.
This way. This way.
Me?
You...
What?
Sir.
I think we've already taken this route just now.
Uh, yeah.
I did it on purpose
so that no one will follow us this way.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Are you here to steal something?
Luo, what day is it today?
May 15th.
What's wrong?
It's the day for the guards' training.
Answer me!
Run!
Go get them!
Come on! Stop!
This way! Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Go!
Hurry! Over there!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Hurry up!
Over there!
This way!
Sir.
Sir, how can we get out of here?
Luo, calm down.
Everything's going according to my plan.
This is my mother's room.
Guard at the door please.
I find it!
Thieves?
Yes.
They're one man and one woman.
Sir, your mother is back!
It's okay. Let's leave from the window.
Stop.
The footprints stop here.
Oh no! Someone came in here.
Madam.
Come in.
The footprints of the two thieves
stop at your back window here.
If they did enter your room,
then I'm afraid they're still here.
How dare you!
You're trying to steal at Lord Meng's mansion!
What are you waiting for? Come out!
I'll count to three.
One.
Two.
Yuanxu?!
Young master, what are you doing?
I... I was just trying to play a prank on mother.
Look at you. What's all the fuss about?
You're idiots!
Hurry up. Get lost.
Get out.
Young master, Madam.
We'll take our leaves then.
Alright.
- Let's go. - Yes.
Come on.
Come here.
What's going on?
Mother, don't tell father about this.
All right.
Really?
But I have some questions for you.
Go ahead.
You dress like this
with the bracelet in your hand.
What do you want to do?
I'm going to pawn it to gamble.
Not convinced.
I'm going to find a prostitute.
You never do that.
I'm going to...
You're having a crush on a girl?
Is she the one in the architect team?
Madam, you misunderstood it.
I'll be honest with you.
Yes.
We're in love.
I hope you'll agree.
Girl.
What's your name?
I...
An Xiaoluo.
Luo.
What a beautiful name.
Take care, young master.
You can leave now.
Sir.
Why did you say that?
If I didn't say so,
my mom would do whatever it takes
to find out the truth
and even investigate it behind my back.
Once she finds out that Master leaves the palace,
and then let my fathers know it,
Master will have to go back to the palace.
That'll be terrible.
But...
Luo, Don’t worry.
I just said we were in love for now.
I didn't say what's gonna happen next.
After a while,
I'll explain to mother.
I won’t hold you back.
That's not what I meant.
Don't worry.
Let's pretend that nothing happened today.
Master doesn't know about this.
So she won't ask anyway.
OK.
All right. Don't be upset.
I owe you a favor.
I will make it up to you in the future.
You promise?
I promise.
Get in. Let's go back.
[Wood Feather House]
Miss Han is from Yangzhou.
She came to Lin'an alone to make a living.
She didn't know anyone
and was almost sold to Yichun Brothel.
Thanks to Liu Yiyun, the most talented girl in Lin'an,
she didn't have to be a prostitute.
Miss Han thought she owed Liu Yiyun too much
and decided to stay with Miss Liu as her maid.
I'd like to say
I really admire you
for being so grateful.
I understand
you want to return the favor of Miss Liu.
But
Miss Han, to be honest,
you're not supposed to be a maid.
You're born to be an architecture supervisor.
And the Wood Feather House
exactly needs a supervisor.
It's destiny that brings us together. Please stay.
That's right, Miss Han.
Please stay and put down your burden.
We all have faith in your competence.
I appreciate that you trust me so much.
In fact,
I am very happy
to spend these days with you.
But please give me some time.
I'll go back and explain to Miss Liu.
If she agrees,
I will stay with you in Wood Feather House.
But if she doesn't...
I will make her agree to it anyway.
Great.
Miss Han.
Please tell us
about the complicated work.
Right.
How complicated could it be?
The work is actually
the construction of Miss Liu’s resort mansion.
I've asked several teams of architects.
But it was either that Miss Liu was not happy with their design,
or the architects didn't want to do it.
That's why I don't want you to take the job.
I'm afraid you will
work for nothing.
Is there anything special about the place?
It's Huan Cai House.
Huan Cai House?
This is Huan Cai House.
The garden needs renovation?
When will Miss Liu come?
I'll go and have a look.
Miss Liu.
I’m here.
Greetings, everyone.
We've heard so much
about Miss Liu Yiyun being the most talented lady in Lin'an.
But now that we meet you,
I think you're more of
the most beautiful lady in Lin'an.
Beauty will grow old.
And my talent is all but limited.
I'm flattered to hear that.
Let's not talk about it.
What do you mean?
Meng Yuanxu, just shut up.
Let me introduce ourselves.
I'm Luo Ye from Wood Feather House.
Li Qingfeng, our architect.
These people
are also architects of Wood Feather House.
I've heard of Mr. Li.
Mr. Meng, you're the local official, right?
Have you met me before?
No.
But Niaoniao once mentioned you.
In fact, my father and your father have been friends for years.
You're an official
but is in charge of the architect team in the Wood Feather House.
I'm sure you must be the best team of architects.
We're here
because we'd like to know
what Miss Liu thinks about the refurbishment of the garden.
Everyone,
please follow me to the pavilion for the details.
[Grand Virtues]
Lor Meng knows his father.
I know it!
His father is the assistant Minister of Ministry of Rites.
Liu often invites my dad to dinner.
He gets drunk easily.
[Waves Pavilion]
Miss Liu.
Go ahead.
I asked the painter to draw this.
The painting
is what I envision about the garden.
This is just a painting of landscape,
not Huan Cai House.
Yes.
We'll take this job.
You understand this?
I've seen a lot of architects,
but only you understand me.
We'll take our leaves.
We'll be here tomorrow to measure.
[Waves Pavilion]
Miss Liu.
I have another request.
Go ahead.
It's just a landscape painting.
Do you really understand what she wants?
Not completely.
And you took the job just like that?
I'm an architect.
Of course I can take the job I want.
I'm also an architect.
A deputy one, though.
You need to consult me before you take any job.
I'm gonna do it anyway.
You...
Why are you so bossy?
Why do you think I will listen to you?
Last time, the restoration of the house was your own decision.
And I did what you said.
This time, it's my turn
to call the shots, right?
I...
Fine.
I don't think I have anything to say about that.
Indeed.
That's the deal!
Come with me tomorrow at 7 o'clock to measure.
You...
My lady.
Wait,
I was in charge last time because they voted for me!
Right!
I don't think he did anything wrong.
What?
Wang Sheng! You traitor!
Don't forget you voted for me too.
That's what happened.
I hope you can understand us.
Of course
I will make it up to you.
You can choose another ten maids in my mansion.
They're well trained by our Meng family.
Every one of them is smart and helpful.
Thank you so much.
Niaoniao.
If you want to work somewhere else, you should have told me earlier.
I see you as my own sister.
I won't make it difficult for you.
I know you are kind to me, Miss.
You helped me out when I was in the darkest hours of my life.
How can I just leave you like this?
Silly girl.
I helped you because I liked you.
I didn't want to see you suffer.
Now you're able to live a good life,
and also have a chance to show your talent.
I'm happy for you.
Miss Liu, you're both talented
and understanding.
Now I see why you're the wisest lady in Lin'an.
I owe you a favor.
If you need me in the future,
just let me know.
In Lin'an City,
there's nothing I can't help.
So do you have any other questions?
Yes, yes, yes.
Since Architect Li has decided to take over this job,
well, about the pay...
Mr. Luo.
How much do you think I should pay you?
Miss Liu, this garden is quite different from other places.
It was built by Master Liu Tong from the previous dynasty.
So it will take lots of efforts for us to refurbish it.
You agree with that, right?
Since you agree,
let me elaborate on the expenditure, Miss Liu.
Let me see...
The cost of wood
plus stones and workers,
and...
What are you waiting for? Go!
[Music Pavilion]
I didn't get to have a close look at it yesterday.
This garden
is truly amazing.
It's really a masterpiece.
Mindblowing!
Measure the pavilions
ponds
and counterfeit mountains in the garden.
I’ll check it later.
What?
Just the two of us come to work here？
And you want me to measure everything by myself?
Then why do you think I bring you here?
What are you gonna do?
I’ll go to discuss with Miss Liu
in detail about the reconstruction.
Take this.
Me?
[Music Pavilion]
What's wrong with you?
Li Qingfeng.
[Huan Cai House]
I'm here today
to hear Miss Liu’s plan for the renovation.
Looking out from here,
I can see the mountains and the mist.
I feel like I'm not staying in Lin'an City
but a paradise.
It makes me feel very relaxed.
But once I look around,
I'm back to Huan Cai House
and Lin'an City.
It's a change of your state of mind.
Since I moved to Huan Cai House last year,
I've been in love with this house.
It's a better place than my home
and makes me happier.
I love every grass and tree,
and every brick and tile here.
Even when I close my eyes,
I can still feel them.
So every time when I think of
the possibility of me leaving here,
I feel sad.
Miss Liu, have you ever thought about leaving here?
I thought I had another place to go.
But it's just a wishful thinking.
Then I realized
this house is my final destination.
The world is so big.
You can go anywhere.
You know what.
The world is indeed very big.
But there's only one place I belong to.
If I can't go there,
I'll have nowhere else to go.
Turn left in the garden,
you'll see crystal jade lamps with a pearl curtain.
All of those
were set according to my ideas.
But the changes
are all but superficial.
They just appear to be different from before.
So this time
should be the last renovation of this garden.
I hope it will really make a difference.
Please tell us what you want, Miss Liu.
Take a closer look at this painting.
You see.
The materials of wood and stones are listed here.
The extra 20%.
is our profit.
OK.
Li Qingfeng
- When I see him, I will... - My lady.
Miss Chen.
Why are you back?
Where is Li Qingfeng?
He?
He asked me to go to Huan Cai House with him early in the morning
to measure the garden.
But he
gave the tool box to me
and let me measure everything all alone.
He left
to discuss the renovation plan with Miss Liu.
That's not what really pissed me off.
Just now,
I saw him drinking and talking with Miss Liu.
They looked so happy together!
Li Qingfeng.
Li...
Miss Liu said that
when she met with her friends,
nobody should disturb her.
I'm a colleague of the man inside.
I'm afraid you can't go in.
I hope you can understand.
Drinking and chatting can't mean anything.
I trust Li Qingfeng.
He took this job without consulting any one of us.
I'm sure
he has a crush on Miss Liu.
[Han Yuan Hall]