( woman screaming )
( whimpering )
Alex: We should've never
put up the signs.
What the hell did we think
was gonna happen?
We brought them here.
We were trying
to do something good.
- ( laughs )
- We were being human beings.
What are we now, Gareth?
( woman screaming )
( radio chatter )
Abraham: They seemed nice enough,
but I was ready to go.
We just got here,
but, damn,
it was time to go.
When I told them about DC,
a wink and a nod from
the head asshole in charge,
they pulled their guns
and it was right back
to our regularly scheduled
shitstorm.
Sasha: Before they put you in here,
you didn't see Tyreese?
- Michonne: No.
- Sasha: Good.
Daryl: Black car with a white cross
painted on it.
I tried to follow it.
I tried.
Maggie:
But she's alive?
Daryl:
She's alive.
( radio chatter continues )
( men chatting )
- Man: What are you doing?
- Man #2: Everybody shut up.
Shut up!
All right, got four of them pricks
coming our way.
Y'all know what to do.
Go for their eyes first.
Then their throats.
Man: Put your backs to the walls
on either end of the car now!
( clanging )
Move!
( all coughing )
( doors opening )
( gas mask hissing )
- Man: Move!
- Man #2: Get up!
( grunts )
( distorted voice, indistinct )
( saw buzzing )
Okay, hold up.
All right.
( whimpering )
( muffled screaming )
- ( knife slices )
- ( blood pouring )
( man, muffled )
Please, no! No!
Hey, guys.
What were your shot counts?
- 38.
- ( thuds )
Gareth:
Hey!
Your shot count?
Crap, man, I'm sorry.
It was my first roundup.
Gareth: After you're done here,
go back to your point
and count the shells.
Kaylee won't be gathering them
until tomorrow.
( Bob, muffled )
Hey.
Hey, let me talk to you.
Four from A, four from D?
Man:
Yeah.
Hey, let me talk
to you for a minute.
Let me talk to you
for a minute.
- Let me talk to you for a minute.
- What?
Don't do this.
We can fix this.
- No, you can't.
- You don't have to do this.
We told you there's a way
out of all of this.
You just have to take a chance.
We have a man
who knows how to stop it.
He has a cure.
We just have to get him
to Washington.
You don't have to do this, man.
We can put the world
back to how it was.
Can't go back, Bob.
We can!
You don't have to do--
We saw you go
into the woods with a bag
and come out without it.
Had to pull my spotters back
before we could go look for it.
What was in it?
You hid it, right?
In case things went bad?
Smart.
Still, we'll find it.
But it's too dangerous
to go out there right now.
What was in it?
I'm curious.
And it was a big bag.
You really gonna let me do this?
Well, let me take you out there.
I'll show you.
Not gonna happen,
but this might.
Rick:
There's guns in it.
AK-47.
.44 Magnum.
Automatic weapons.
Nightscope.
There's a compound bow
and a machete
with a red handle.
That's what I'm gonna use
to kill you.
( chuckles )
( sighs )
Thanks.
You have two hours
to get them on the driers.
Then we go back to public face.
Now's the time
we can get messy,
but we need to dial it all in
by sundown.
- Got it.
- Yes, sir.
( gunshots )
Hey, Chuck?
( gunshot )
( explosion )
( theme music playing )
We're close.
I'm gonna get you both there,
make sure you're safe.
( Judith coos )
But I'm not gonna stay.
( raspy breathing )
( snarling )
( crying )
I can't. Not yet.
You're going to have
to be able to.
( snarling )
( whispers )
More.
( snarling )
( gunshots )
( gunshots continue )
That gunfire,
it could have been
from Terminus.
Someone was attacking them.
Or they were attacking someone.
Do we even want to find out?
Yeah.
There's another track due east.
It'll get us there.
We'll be real careful.
We're gonna get answers.
Woman on radio:
10-minute count.
You screw up,
you're on your own, Martin.
You don't have to tell me.
I wipe my own ass.
Alex didn't get it.
See, I knew the chick
with the sword was bad news.
Bitch looked like a weapon
with a weapon.
He was always
a sloppy-ass mother.
Yeah, I told Albert I want the kid's hat
after they bleed him out.
Keep your finger
off the button and drop it.
( radio clatters )
They're only doing eight
before public face.
- Don't wait on 'em.
- Listen, y'all don't have to do this.
Whatever you want, we got a place
where everyone's welcome.
- Shut up, man.
- Okay.
We're friends
of the chick with the sword
and the kid in the hat.
They attacked us.
We're just holding them.
I don't believe you.
Who else do you have?
Do you know their names?
We just have the boy
and the samurai, that's it.
We were just protecting ourselves.
I don't believe you.
There's a bunch of us out there
in six different directions.
There was a lot of gunfire
back home.
We need to set off our charges
all at the same time
to confuse the dead ones away.
- That's good for you, too.
- No, it isn't.
There's a herd heading
toward Terminus right now.
We don't want
to confuse them away.
We're gonna need their help.
It's a compound.
They'll see you coming.
If you even make it that far
with all the cold bodies heading over.
Carol.
How are you gonna do this?
I'm gonna kill people.
( flies buzzing )
She got a name?
Hey, she got a name?
Judith.
She your daughter or something?
She's a friend.
Huh.
( sighs )
I don't have any friends.
I mean, I know people.
They're just assholes
I stay alive with.
The other one your friend?
The woman?
I used to have 'em.
Used to watch football
on Sundays.
Went to church.
( laughs )
I know I did.
But I can't picture it anymore.
It's funny how you don't even
notice the time go by.
Horrible shit just stacks up
day after day.
You get used to it.
I haven't gotten used to it.
Of course you haven't.
You're the kind of guy
who saves babies.
It's kind of like saving an anchor
when you're stuck without a boat
in the middle of the ocean.
Been behind
some kind of walls, right?
You're still around, but you haven't
had to get your hands dirty.
I can tell.
See, you're a good guy.
You have no idea
about the things I've done.
You're a good guy.
That's why you're gonna die today.
It's why the baby is gonna die.
Or...
you can get in that car,
get out of here,
keep on being lucky.
You think you're gonna kill me?
Why haven't you killed me?
How does having me alive
help you?
Why the hell are you
even talking to me?
Take her, take the car, and go.
I don't want to do this today.
( walkers snarling )
Man: Backs to the walls
on either end of the car, now!
( snarling )
Move! Move!
Help! Help! Help!
( gunshots )
( explosion )
- Is that Terminus?
- Yeah.
Probably.
Maybe you're gonna win this.
Maybe your friend--
I mean,
maybe that woman
just got capped.
Maybe I'm gonna be the one
who gets capped when she comes back.
Nobody's gotta die today.
( scoffs )
Man, if you believe that...
then it's definitely
gonna be you and the kid.
Even if that place
is burning to the ground.
( gunfire )
Man on radio:
Mary, what the hell was that?
Mary, do you copy?
- You stay here.
- These guys aren't going anywhere.
Stay here until I know
what's happening!
Man #2:
So we just sit here?
Got a job to do.
( grunting )
( gunfire continues )
( gasping )
( snarling )
Oh, Jesus.
Man:
Get them!
( snarling )
( screaming )
- You there, Gareth?
- He's busy.
You smell the smoke?
You hear the shots?
He could be dead.
The hell we doing here?
The whole place could be going up.
You went on one roundup
and you blew protocol.
We don't deal with security.
That ain't our job.
This is.
Hey, look at me.
What?
No, no, no, no!
Glenn:
Rick!
What the hell is going on?
- Michonne: Someone hit them.
- Maybe our people got free.
Excuse me.
What the hell are you doing?
I might be able to use this shell
to compromise the door.
From the sound of things, there may
not be anybody left to open it.
Eugene, I'm sorry,
but shut up.
- Okay.
- Hey.
My dad's gonna be back.
- They all are.
- They are.
And we need to get ready to fight
our way out with them when they do.
( snarling )
- Man: There's too many!
- ( woman screaming )
( gunfire continues )
( screaming )
( gunshot )
( snarling )
If they got problems,
we got a chance.
It sounded like a bomb.
- Sounds like a damn war.
- Right there.
What the hell are these people?
They ain't people.
Don't.
Let him turn.
Cross any of these people,
you kill them.
Don't hesitate.
They won't.
( gunfire continues )
( man screaming )
Rick:
If we run, we can get by them.
They're distracted.
We got to let those people out.
That's still who we are.
It's got to be.
Man:
Help me!
Left flank.
Man:
Help!
Please help me!
Please!
Come on, come on,
come on.
We're the same!
We're them!
- Back off!
- We're the same.
( snarling )
Come on.
( grunting )
( gunfire )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( people shouting )
- We got to double back.
- Rick: A is that way.
We go back,
we don't know where we are.
We don't really have
a choice, do we?
( gunshots )
- Wait here.
- Rick. Rick!
( snarling )
- Man: Reloading!
- ( people yelling )
( groans )
( walkers snarling )
( woman screaming )
( screaming )
We're gonna have to double back.
( gunfire continues )
- ( gun cocks )
- Drop your weapons and turn around.
I want to see your face.
( walkers snarling, pounding )
Now!
( grunting )
Ah!
( panting )
The signs...
they were real.
It was a sanctuary.
- People came and took this place.
- Just tell me where--
And they raped and they killed
and they laughed over weeks.
But we got out
and we fought
and we got it back.
And we heard the message.
You're the butcher...
or you're the cattle.
The men they pulled from that train car,
where are they?
- ( screams )
- Where are they?
( groaning )
Now...
point it at my head.
( laughing )
You could have been
one of us.
You could have listened
to what the world is telling you.
You lead people here and you take
what they have and you kill them?
Is that what this place is?
No, not at first.
It's what it had to be.
And we're still here.
You're not here.
Neither am I.
( snarling )
No! No! No!
God! No, God!
No! No!
( walkers snarling )
Back off!
( crying )
Put your weapons on the ground.
Kick them over right now.
Right now!
Tyreese:
Please.
Please, don't hurt her.
( crying )
Go outside.
Go outside!
Just one twist, man.
- Don't!
- Don't make me!
( crying )
Go outside.
- ( snarling )
- ( screaming )
- ( walkers snarling )
- ( Tyreese shouting )
Cynthia, do you copy?
( banging )
- ( pounding )
- ( Tyreese shouting )
( pounding stops )
( walker gurgling )
( fussing )
( grunts )
Yeah.
That's how it works.
I won't.
( grunts )
I won't!
- ( blows landing )
- Tyreese: I won't!
I won't!
( gunfire )
What's the cure, Eugene?
It's classified.
We don't know
what's gonna happen.
Abraham:
You leave him be.
- We need to keep working.
- Yeah, but it's time to hear it.
'Cause we don't know
what's coming next.
What's next is we get out of this.
Even if I told you all,
even if I provided
step-by-step instructions
complete with illustrations
and a well-composed FAQ
and I went red-ring...
the cure would still
die with me.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
The best-case scenario,
we step out into a hellstorm
of bullets, fire, and walkers.
I'm not fleet of foot.
I sure as hell can't take
a dead one down
with sharp buttons
and hella confidence.
Yeah, but we can and we will.
You don't owe us anything.
Not yet.
But we just want to hear it.
You don't have to.
I was part of a 10-person team
at the Human Genome Project
to weaponize diseases
to fight weaponized diseases.
Pathogenic microorganisms
with pathogenic microorganisms.
Fire with fire.
Interdepartmental drinks were had,
relationships made,
information shared.
I am keenly aware of all the details
behind fail-safe delivery systems
to kill every living person
on this planet.
I believe with a little tweaking
on the terminals in DC,
we can flip the script.
Take out every
last dead one of them.
Fire with fire.
All things being equal,
it does sound pretty badass.
So let's get back to work.
- ( banging )
- ( gasps )
Come on!
Fight to the fence!
Abraham:
We do not leave his side!
- Go, go, go!
- Carl!
Let's go!
( gunshot )
Up and over.
Abraham:
Let's go, let's go! Move!
Let's go! Move!
Rosita:
Come on!
Right here.
Abraham: The hell
are we still around here for?
Rick:
Guns, some supplies.
Go along the fences.
Use the rifles.
Take out the rest of 'em.
What?
They don't get to live.
Rick, we got out.
It's over.
It's not over till they're all dead.
The hell it isn't.
That place is on fire.
Full of walkers.
Abraham:
I'm not dicking around with this crap.
We just made it out.
The fences are down.
They'll run or die.
Did you do that?
( laughs )
Rick:
Thank you.
You have to come with me.
( crying )
Judith.
You're okay.
( sobbing )
( no audible dialogue )
( Judith crying )
What happened?
There were a bunch
of walkers out here
and he got his hands
around Judith's neck.
No, he's dead.
I-- I had to.
So I did.
I could.
I don't know if the fire
is still burning.
It is.
Yeah.
We need to go.
Daryl:
Yeah, but where?
Somewhere far away
from there.
We'll talk to him.
Not just yet.
( whimpering )
Alex:
Mom, Mom! Mom.
( Mary gasping )
No! No!
Man:
That one.
No, no, please.
Not again.
( sobbing )
No! No!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- ( shrieks )
No, it's not.
( chuckles )
( screams )
- ( door shuts )
- ( latch clangs )
We're gonna take it back.
How?
We will.
You're either the butcher
or the cattle.
Oh.
( theme music playing )