( snarling )
( rock music playing )
♪ So impressed
with all you do ♪
♪ Tried so hard
to be like you ♪
♪ Flew too high
and burnt the wing ♪
♪ Lost my faith
in everything... ♪
( knocks )
( breathing heavily )
♪ Lick around divine debris ♪
♪ Taste the wealth
of hate in me ♪
♪ Shedding skin
succumb defeat ♪
♪ This machine is obsolete... ♪
( whimpering )
( snarling )
♪ Made the choice
to go away... ♪
Turn it off.
♪ Drink the fountain
of decay ♪
♪ Tear a hole-- ♪
( knocks )
( snarling )
( gunshot )
( crossbow twangs )
There's more of them around here
than there used to be.
- Don't know if any people are--
- Shh.
Someone is.
( theme music playing )
( audio rewinding )
Aiden was trying to save us
from a roamer,
shooting at it.
Then Glenn distracted him.
I saw the grenades.
I tried to stop him.
They wanted to just go,
I didn't.
He was gonna run.
Nicholas:
I wasn't gonna leave him.
Deanna:
What about Tara?
I wasn't gonna leave her.
But we made him stay.
Couldn't get Aiden
out of there without help.
Then when we got
into the lobby...
All he had to do
was hold the door.
Nicholas:
...he was hitting on the glass,
pushing my door open.
They were gonna kill me.
But he panicked.
Or they were trying to.
Or they just didn't care.
Noah-- I had him.
I had his hand.
And if I didn't push back,
I'd be dead, too.
I tried.
I watched him die.
Nicholas:
They did this.
It was them.
Deanna: But you all
came back together.
How did that happen?
Spencer:
Mom, what are you doing?
Deanna: I need it for later.
We have to do this now.
No guns.
No going outside the walls.
Same goes for Glenn
until I finish looking into this.
Nicholas: What do you need
to look into?
I-- I'm telling you
how it went down.
These people have to go.
They are not like us.
I know you see it, too.
Deanna: You don't know
what I see, Nicholas.
And I see a great deal.
I almost left him out there.
Could have told a story.
What, you think I should have?
They don't know
what they're doing.
- Any of them.
- We'll show them.
I don't know
if they can see it.
How things really are.
I don't know if they can yet.
- They haven't caught up.
- We have to be here.
- We have to.
- Yeah, we do.
But their rules,
we don't answer to them.
We are them, Rick.
We are now.
Noah, he believed
in this place.
I'm telling you,
we gotta make this work.
I sent a casserole
to Deanna's family.
We want her to see that.
Thought about Pete?
About what I said?
Yeah.
Talked to Sam some more.
He said his mom put a bolt
on the inside of his closet.
Tells him to lock
himself in sometimes
and not come out
till morning.
He said he can hear
his dad yelling,
things breaking,
his mom crying.
Last month it got quiet
right in the middle of it
and he went out
and found her on the floor...
unconscious, bleeding.
Pete was just sitting
on the porch.
Why do you care
what happens to Jessie?
You know why.
And I know why you do.
Why?
I've seen you talk to her.
Carol:
If walkers hadn't gotten Ed,
I wouldn't be standing here
right now.
Yeah, you would.
Hey, Rick.
Rick.
You okay, man?
Keep walking.
What?
What are you--
( sighs )
( knocks )
Come in.
Hey.
- How is she?
- Stable.
Hanging on.
I'm gonna go back there later.
I think Sasha might have spent
the night in the tower.
Is she still up there?
Abraham's on watch now,
but she hasn't been back
and nobody's seen her.
Rosita:
It's up ahead.
Michonne:
She told you about it?
Rosita: I saw her going out
one day with her rifle.
I knew somebody
was already in the tower.
I asked.
( running footsteps )
It's the first time I've been out
since we've been here.
Me, too.
It already feels different.
That's good.
I don't know.
After Eugene,
after finding out he lied,
I was screwed up
because I lost something.
You seem screwed up
because we found something.
Noah's dead.
And I think--
I just feel like
I was asleep in there.
You were trying to forget
so you could try.
- I don't want to forget.
- So don't.
But that doesn't mean
you have to give up.
You didn't bring
your sword with you.
That's not nothing.
I'm sorry for what happened.
How are you holding up?
I'm not.
We have a problem with Pete.
I hoped it'd get better.
You knew?
It hasn't gotten better.
It won't.
Pete's a surgeon.
He's saved lives.
He might be saving Tara's life.
He's beating his wife.
- We have to stop it.
- How?
We separate them.
We tell him that's how it'll be
from now on.
What happens when he doesn't
want to do that?
It's not his choice.
So what happens?
I kill him.
We kill him.
We don't kill people.
This is civilization, Rick.
Warning someone to stop or die,
that is civilized nowadays.
- Oh.
- So what?
So we just let him hit her?
We let him kill her?
No, we exile him
if it comes to that.
We do that, we don't know
when he comes back
and what he does to them.
Letting him go
makes this place vulnerable.
You really want to wait till someone
in that tower has to take care of it?
- And that's if we're lucky.
- We are not... executing anyone.
Don't ever suggest it again.
That sort of thinking
doesn't belong in here.
People die now, Deanna.
They do.
There's times like this
you can decide who and when.
Or it can be decided for you.
It already was.
I wouldn't kill you.
I'd just send you away.
Michonne:
Got it in the back of the head.
Had to be her.
Back of the head.
She's hunting them.
( twigs snap )
Enid:
Carl.
I know you're following me.
Again.
And you're going
the wrong way.
You knew?
- Enid: You're very loud.
- ( twigs snap )
Can you go back?
To be honest,
you scare me.
You shouldn't sneak out
by yourself.
Two people just died.
Oh, come on.
People always die.
You know that.
We should go back.
Why?
What do you do
out here anyways?
Same thing as you.
( snarling )
( clicking, ticking )
( alarm ringing )
Nicholas, don't talk,
just listen.
Those four people
you lost on that run,
that's on you.
And Noah,
that's on you, too.
Those five lives,
you have to carry that.
People like you
are supposed to be dead,
but these walls went up
just in time, so you're not.
You don't go outside
those walls anymore.
Not by yourself,
not with anyone else.
And that's how
you're gonna survive.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
I'm someone who knows
who you are.
I know what you did.
And it's not gonna
happen again.
I've been protecting this place,
helping provide for it.
You just got here.
Don't forget what I said.
Are you threatening me?
( chuckles )
No.
I'm saving you.
( panting )
We're supposed
to be out here.
to feel like this.
I don't want to forget.
And running
makes me feel better.
I can't forget.
I dream about it.
Being in the forest with them.
I do, too.
Ron's a good guy.
He is.
Does he know
you come out here?
No, I--
he wouldn't understand.
Why do I scare you?
I don't know.
You just do.
Cool knife.
It was my mom's.
What happened to you
before you got there?
Does it matter?
It does.
I know.
Something bad
has happened to me, too.
( walkers snarling )
We need to go.
Sounds like a lot.
It's their world.
We're just living in it.
Cool.
You're afraid of me, too.
( silenced gunshots )
( snarling )
( silenced gunshot )
- Michonne: Sasha.
- ( sighs )
- ( walkers snarling )
- Go back.
What are you doing?
I'm sick of playing defense.
So you're just gonna
take on all of them?
Yeah.
Rosita:
We've got to get out of here.
Oh, you do, I don't.
- I don't need your help.
- This isn't for you.
( gun clicks )
( panting )
I had it.
Don't need your help.
I told you to go.
You...
you can't do anything.
It worked out for you.
Don't you see that?
You can't help me.
Nobody--
Noah.
I told him
he wouldn't make it.
Whoever did this
took what was left with them.
This just happened.
( flies buzzing )
She's tied up.
And they fed on her.
Tore her apart.
This just happened?
Yeah.
How the hell did this happen?
( snarling )
Jessie.
Hey.
I don't want Ron and Sam
to know about those.
Well, your secret's safe.
Noah was a sweet kid.
( sighs )
But Tara, she's--
she's in good hands with Pete.
He's hitting you.
He's hurting you.
It has to stop.
- It will.
- How?
There are things
in his life that happened.
I don't care.
Look, it was like this before
and he got help.
I helped him
and things were good.
I can fix it.
No, you can't.
But I can.
No, what--
what can you do?
What are you gonna do?
You gonna put him in jail?
You're only gonna
make things worse.
If it's gotten worse,
it means he's killed you.
That's what's next.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen.
Why do you care?
Why is this
so important to you?
Now?
You've made it.
You have a home
for your kids.
Rick, what are you doing?
I'm trying to help.
I don't know that.
I'm married.
Okay?
I can take care of myself.
We have to take care
of ourselves.
What are you doing?
You know Sam asked for a gun?
To protect you.
You shouldn't be here.
Jessie, in here, you can't see it,
but it's the same.
It's the same as out there.
We have food
and roofs over our heads,
but you don't get to just live.
You don't get to put it off
or wish it away, Jessie.
If you don't fight,
you die.
And...
and I don't want you to die.
I can-- I can help you.
I can keep you
and your boys safe.
I can.
All you have to do is say yes.
Would you do this
for someone else?
for anyone?
No. No.
Yes.
Rick.
What are you doing here?
Pete.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave, Rick.
No.
Excuse me?
You need to leave.
What are you talking about?
Just go, Pete.
What have you been
saying to each other?
Huh?
What have you been doing?!
Pete, you and me
are gonna leave now.
You come into my house...
Pete, you and me
are leaving.
Pete:
You're leaving right now.
You think you're the law?
You actually think you have a say
in anything here?
- Step back.
- Who the hell do you think you are?
Someone who's trying
not to kill you.
No!
- You wanna stop now!
- ( shouts )
Come into my house?!
- Pete, stop it!
- It's my house!
Pete, stop it!
( shouts )
( glass breaks )
- ( fight continues )
- Jessie: No! Stop it!
( shouting )
( snarling )
( distant glass breaks )
( screams )
( grunting )
Deanna!
Ah!
Dad, get off!
Deanna:
Stop it!
Stop it right now.
You touch them again
and I'll kill you.
Damn it, Rick!
I said stop.
Or what?
You gonna kick me out?
Put that gun down, Rick.
( panting )
You still don't get it.
None of you do!
( snarling )
Rick: We know what needs
to be done and we do it.
( silenced gunshot )
Rick:
We're the ones who live.
You, you just sit
and plan and hesitate.
You pretend like you know
when you don't.
- ( walkers snarling )
- ( silenced gunshots )
Rick: You wish things
weren't what they are.
Well, you want to live?
You want this place
to stay standing?
( silenced gunshot )
Your way of doing things is done.
Things don't get better
because you-- you want them to.
Starting right now,
we have to live in the real world.
We have to control
who lives here.
That's never been more clear to me
than it is right now.
Me? Me? You--
( laughs )
You mean-- you mean me?
Your way is gonna
destroy this place.
It's gonna get people killed.
It's already gotten
people killed.
And I'm not gonna stand by
and just let it happen.
If you don't fight, you die.
I'm not gonna stand by and--
( grunts )
( panting )
( theme music playing )