( birds chirping )
( chuckles )
Looks good.
Hi.
Hello.
( spoon clattering )
You can lower that.
What's the W for?
You know,
the first settlers here,
they put bounties
on wolves' heads.
Brought the natives into it.
Made them hunt them.
Didn't take them too long
to kill them all.
They're back now.
Thoughts?
Everything gets a return.
- Are you shitting me?
- No, I shit you not.
( both laughing )
I like this.
Just talking.
( laughs )
I don't get to meet
new people very often.
Maybe once
every two weeks.
- That's a lot.
- Oh, I work at it.
We do.
Sometimes we find camps.
We run through them.
But we have traps, too.
It's different.
It's not like meeting like this.
As equals.
Little chats in front of a fire
with a stranger.
That's the closest thing
to movies now.
I miss the movies.
I used to-- put that down.
Why?
'Cause I want it.
I want everything you have.
Every last drop.
Can I keep a little of it?
Just to get me through
a day or two?
You know,
just to keep me alive?
I'm taking you, too.
And you're not exactly
gonna be alive.
Okay.
Some of the tribes
around here,
they thought that the first people
were wolves transformed into men.
And now...
well, you know.
Everything gets
a return, right?
You can have my supplies.
You can have everything.
Doesn't need
to be any ugliness.
But I can't allow you
to take me away.
I will not allow that.
Don't move.
( sighs )
Just be still.
( grunts )
Morgan:
You should just go now.
No.
Just go.
Please.
Now!
( snarling )
( clicks )
( clicking )
( honks horn )
( theme music playing )
( groans )
( chuckles )
Michonne:
What's so funny?
You were here
the whole time?
All night.
What's so funny?
It's-- it's like the train car.
After the whole thing,
I'm still there.
Deanna wanted you in here,
calm things down.
Rosita patched you up.
Carl came by for a while.
I sent him home.
Rick.
What are you doing?
( sighs )
We put Pete
in another house.
You could have told me
what was happening.
It moved fast.
And then Noah.
I couldn't tell you
about the gun.
No, you couldn't.
Oh, you wanted this place.
We had to stop being out there.
Well, we're here.
( Michonne scoffs )
Well, you just said you weren't.
( door opens )
Michonne:
Where'd you get the gun?
Carol: You took it, right?
From the armory?
That was stupid.
Why did you do it?
Just in case.
Glenn: Deanna's planning
to have a meeting tonight.
For anyone who wants to.
- To kick Rick out?
- To try.
We don't know that.
Maggie's with Deanna right now.
She's gonna find out what it is.
At the meeting,
you say you were worried
about someone being abused
and no one was doing
anything about it.
You say you took a gun
just to be sure
that Jessie was safe from a man
who wound up attacking you.
You say you'll do
whatever you want them to.
Just tell them a story
that they want to hear.
It's what I've been doing
since I got here.
Why?
Because these people are children
and children like stories.
What happens
after all the nice words
and they still try
to kick him out?
They're guarding
the armory now.
We still have knives.
That's all we'll need
against them.
Well, tonight at the meeting...
if it looks like it's going bad,
I whistle.
Carol grabs Deanna,
I take Spencer, you grab Reg,
Glenn and Abraham cover us,
watch the crowd.
- We can talk to them.
- Yeah, we will.
If we can't get through,
we take the three of them
and say we'll slit their throats.
Like at Terminus?
No, we just tell 'em.
They give us the armory
and it's over.
Did you want this?
No.
I hit my limit.
I-- I screwed up.
And here we are.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm just gonna sleep some more.
Reg: Maggie, hey.
She's out on the porch.
What do you need
to talk about, Maggie?
The meeting tonight.
Maggie, if we could talk--
I want to talk to everyone
about what happened
and what we need
to do about it.
If it includes sending Rick away,
it's not gonna work.
Tell me what that means.
You let Rick in.
You let all of us in.
You talked to us.
You decided.
And now you want
to put that decision
on a group
of very frightened people
who might not have
the whole story.
That's not leadership.
Well, tonight is just a forum.
It's just for people
to say their piece.
And I'll make the decision
as I've done since the beginning.
He was frustrated.
The things he's seen.
The things he's lost.
The things we have all lost.
The things you've lost?
We've lost so much more.
Rick took a gun
and he pointed it at people.
He didn't pull the trigger.
That's a metric?
That he didn't pull the trigger?
- Yes.
- Michonne stopped him, Deanna.
Michonne did.
I'm gonna do
what I have to do, Maggie.
Maggie.
Look, Maggie.
The cavemen...
they were all nomads.
And they all died.
Then we evolved into this
and we lived.
Civilization starts
when we stop running.
When we live together.
When we stop
sending people away
from the world
and from each other.
That's what I'm going
to tell her.
to tell everyone.
Okay?
( sighs )
Somebody came through here
a while ago.
If we see them,
we hang back,
set up the mike,
watch and listen.
For how long?
Until we know.
We have to know.
You've sent people away?
Yeah.
What happened?
It was early on.
It was three people.
Two men and a woman.
Davidson was their leader.
Smart as hell, strong.
I thought they'd work out.
They didn't.
I brought them in
and I had to see them out.
So me, Aiden,
and Nicholas,
we drove them out far...
gave them a day's worth
of food and water and left them.
They just went?
We had their guns.
We had all the guns.
I can't make
that kind of mistake again.
Wake up.
It's good what happened
last night.
We have more cover now.
All of them think you've been
found out, that it's over.
Why didn't you want to tell them
we had more guns?
Michonne stopped you.
She knocked you out.
Well, I deserved it.
Well, it was stupid.
She's with us.
Glenn is.
I didn't tell them
about the guns just in case.
( sighs )
I don't want to lie anymore.
You said you don't want
to take this place.
And you don't want to lie?
Oh, sunshine,
you don't get both.
Aaron:
What's he doing?
Daryl:
Wild leeks.
Son of a bitch knows about
how to keep mosquitos off of him.
Come on.
Hey, Tobin.
Hey, Rick.
- You met with her?
- Yeah.
So what is it?
It's what we thought.
I'm gonna talk to people.
I'll talk to everyone I can
right up until.
I'm gonna try to solve this.
What?
I love you.
We're gonna work it out.
I know it.
- I'll see you there.
- Yeah.
( metal rattling )
Sure you don't want
a gun, Father?
I just want a quick walk.
The word of God
is the only protection I need.
Carl:
Dad.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry.
I heard about the meeting.
You're staying home.
That's what it is now, right?
Home?
Yeah.
They need us.
They'll die without us.
I might have to threaten
one of them.
I could have
to kill one of them.
- You won't.
- I might.
You have to tell them.
I told them last night.
You have to tell them
so they can hear you.
I don't know if they can.
Does that make you afraid?
Just for them.
You have to tell them.
( walkers snarling )
We checked the forest,
we checked the roads.
We can't find him.
Sometimes they slip away.
It happens.
But...
you don't come across
something like this every day.
We do this now,
it means we're giving up.
Home is 50 miles back.
It's time to go.
You saw it last night.
There's bad people out here.
That's why we ought to keep
looking for the good ones.
We need more people
and we'll find them.
But when we do,
we'll need to feed them.
All right.
( metal ringing )
( snarling )
( flesh squelching )
- ( cans clanging )
- ( wind whistling )
Huh.
Whoa.
( chuckles )
Wasn't sure I'd ever
see one of these.
Hey, listen, I don't
like giving up either,
but the guy is in a red poncho.
You can see him
from a mile away.
We've gone a lot of miles here.
No sign of him.
But...
if we come away
with a trailer full of cans,
I'd say that's a good trip.
Here we go.
( snarling )
Over here!
Daryl:
Come on!
- No!
- Come on.
Come on!
Go!
Glass will hold for a while, right?
Maybe.
Maybe we can make it
so they can't see us.
In a couple hours,
something will come by,
they'll follow it out.
There's got to be something in here
we can use to block the view.
We can cut up these seats.
( knocking at door )
( knocking )
( sighs )
What the hell are you doing?
You need to check on Tara.
You treated her.
You're a surgeon.
You need to do that.
Get out.
I could kill you right now.
I could.
I will.
And then who would believe I did it
because I didn't like you?
No one.
They'd believe
you tried to hurt me.
Definitely believe that.
( gasps )
Come at me.
No?
Yeah?
No.
The way this has played out,
you have a chance.
You're here.
Your wife's there.
You're a small, weak nothing.
And with the world how it is,
you're even weaker.
Play your cards right,
maybe you don't have to die.
And I want my dish back clean
when you're done.
Pete:
This isn't my house.
( furniture crashes )
This isn't my house!
( branch snaps )
( gunshot )
( sighs )
You should go.
I just wanted to check on you.
Your eye.
He did it right when
it was happening.
It wasn't you.
People shouldn't see us
talking right now.
I'm not sorry I did it.
No matter what happens
or what I have to do.
Don't turn around, Rick.
You were right.
( chuckles )
What?
I came out here to...
not feel all closed up back there.
Even now,
this still feels more like me...
than back in them houses.
That's pretty messed up, huh?
You were trying.
I had to.
No, you didn't.
Listen, I saw you with your group
out there on the road.
Then you went off
on your own by the barn.
Storm hit and you led
your people to safety.
That was it.
I knew I had to bring
you people back.
You were right.
We should have kept looking
for that guy in the poncho.
I shouldn't have given up.
You didn't.
I'll go.
I'll lead them out.
You make a break for the fence.
No, no, no.
This was my fault.
It wasn't a question.
And this ain't your decision.
It ain't nobody's fault.
Just let me finish
my smoke first.
No. You don't draw them away.
We fight.
We go for the fence.
We do it together.
All right,
whether we make it or not,
we do it together.
We have to.
All right.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
We'll go on three.
One, two--
Come on.
Come on, get in here.
That was--
that was-- thank you.
I'm Aaron, this is Daryl.
Morgan.
Why?
Because all life
is precious, Daryl.
Whoever set that trap,
they're coming.
But I have good news.
We do.
We have a community
not too far from here.
Walls, electricity, it's safe.
If you'd like to come join us--
I thank you.
But I'm on my way
somewhere.
Fact is, I'm lost, so...
if you could tell me
where we are.
( whistling tune )
( munching )
( whistling louder )
I'm ready.
( snarling )
( gurgling )
( whimpers )
( splats )
( gasping, gurgling )
( sobbing )
Oh.
I'll come by later.
He's asleep.
Sit.
( clatters )
Whoops.
Good afternoon.
Eugene:
She saved my life.
She also cracked
open my gourd
to considering
implications I hadn't.
I will remark about those
at this time.
You got us here.
All I did was craft
a top-shelf lie
to which a person with strength
and heroism could apply their talents.
My bet was you needed that.
I thank you.
I am sorry.
And I mean both emphatically
and in equal measure.
I'm...
sorry, too.
Utterly and completely
unnecessary.
I almost killed you.
Yes, there's that.
You're back.
Good, just wanted
to sneak off to the meeting.
You think we could find
some time to talk later?
About Aiden?
Just some things
I need to say
and I'm not sure
who I can say them to.
I don't really have
anyone here right now,
if you know what I mean.
I'll see.
Cool.
Can you get that?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
( snarling )
( gunshot )
( grunts )
( screams )
( groans )
( screaming )
- ( snarling )
- ( Glenn screaming )
Rick.
You ready?
Carol, Daryl,
and me...
we worked it out together.
Carol took three guns
from the armory.
I still have one,
she still has one.
We lied to you because I wasn't sure
how you'd take it,
what you'd do.
( jacket rustles )
You think I'd try to stop you?
Well, you did hit me
over the head.
That was for you, not them.
I was afraid
you'd talk me out of it.
You could've.
We don't need them here.
I don't need my sword.
I think you can find a way.
We can find a way.
And if we don't...
I'm still with you.
Something's gonna happen.
Just don't make
something happen.
Don't be too long.
Bob's voice: You're gonna find
yourself in a place
where it's like how it used to be.
And if you let too much go
along the way,
that's not gonna work.
'Cause you're gonna be back
in the real world.
Rick's voice:
This is the real world, Bob.
Bob's voice:
Nah, this is a nightmare.
And nightmares end.
( door closes )
I came here...
because I don't--
I don't know what to do.
I'm losing my head.
Can you help me?
No.
( people chatting quietly )
We're going to start.
Can we wait?
There's still people coming.
Glenn, Rick.
We're going to start.
It's already dark.
We're going to talk
about what happened.
Not the fight.
Not what precipitated it.
We're dealing with that.
We're going to talk about
one of our constables,
Rick Grimes.
We're going to talk about how he had
a pistol he stole from the armory,
about how he pointed it
at people.
And we're going to talk
about what he said.
I was hoping he'd be here.
She said he's coming.
I'm sure he'll be here.
And I'm sure we can
work this all out.
( distant dog barking )
I think I want to die.
Why wouldn't you want to die?
You don't deserve to be here.
What you did
can never be undone.
The dead don't choose,
but the choices you made,
how you sacrificed your own--
I know what you're doing.
Bob was mutilated.
Consumed.
Destroyed because of your sins.
Stop it.
Your brother felt
he was apart from it.
He was a part of it.
He didn't deserve to be here.
- You don't!
- Stop it!
Stop it!
( barking continues )
( panting )
( snarling )
And after being out there
and then not being
how you were out there...
it can drive you crazy.
Rick just wants his family to live.
He wants all of you to live.
Who he is
is who you're gonna be...
if you're lucky.
( grunting )
( silenced gunshot )
( grunts )
Rick Grimes saved my life
over and over.
There's terrifying people
out there.
And he rescued me from them.
People like me,
people like us
need people like him.
I know what happened
last night was scary.
And I'm sure
he's sorry for that.
But maybe we should listen
to what he was saying.
( snarling )
( crunching )
( groaning )
Simply put...
there is a vast ocean of shit
that you people
don't know shit about.
Rick knows every fine grain
of said shit...
and then some.
( snarling )
( gunshot )
- Please don't.
- Shh...
- No.
- They'll hear you.
It'll take longer to reset it.
Just be still.
( gurgling )
Welcome home.
My father respected
Rick Grimes.
Rick is a father, too.
He's a man with a good heart
who feels the things he does,
the things he has to do.
And all of us who were together
before this place,
no matter when we found
each other, we're family now.
Rick started that.
And you won't stop it.
You can't.
And you don't want to.
This community,
you people...
that family...
you want to be a part of it, too.
Before we hear
from anyone else, I--
I would like to share something
in the spirit of transparency.
Father Gabriel came to see me
the day before yesterday
and he said our new arrivals
can't be trusted,
that they were dangerous,
that they would put themselves
before this community.
And not one day later,
Rick seemed to demonstrate
all the things Father Gabriel said.
I had hoped Gabriel
would be here tonight.
I don't see him here,
Deanna.
So you're just saying
what someone said.
Did you tape him?
- He's not here.
- Neither is Rick.
Excuse me.
( grunts )
Noah died because of you.
And I tried to tell you how it is,
how it has to be
and you try to kill me?
( sobbing )
( gun hammer clicks )
( breathing heavily )
( snarling )
- ( beeps )
- ( loud music playing )
I just want to keep
my family safe, you know?
And I don't even know
what that means anymore,
but if it means that
we've got to get rid of--
( footsteps )
( women gasp )
( breathing heavily )
I was scared.
- I don't belong out here.
- Shut up.
( sobbing ) I was scared.
I was just scared.
- Shut up.
- I don't-- I don't belong--
- Shut up!
- ( sobbing )
I don't belong out here.
I don't.
Shut up.
( screams )
( Nicholas sobbing )
Gabriel:
Do it.
( breathing heavily )
( door opens )
Sasha.
( whimpering )
You should let her.
They died.
They all died because of me.
They did.
There wasn't a guard
on the gate.
It was open.
I asked Gabriel to close it.
Go.
I didn't bring it in.
It got inside on its own.
They always will--
the dead and the living,
because we're in here.
And the ones out there...
...they'll hunt us.
They'll find us.
They'll try to use us.
They'll try to kill us.
But we'll kill them.
We'll survive.
I'll show you how.
You know,
I was thinking--
I was thinking how many of you
do I have to kill
to save your lives?
But I'm not gonna do that.
You're gonna change.
I'm not sorry
for what I said last night.
I'm sorry for not
saying it sooner.
You're not ready...
but you have to be.
Right now,
you have to be.
Luck runs out.
( footsteps approaching )
You're not one of us.
You're not one of us!
Pete, you don't want
to do this.
- Get the hell away from me, Reg.
- Pete, just stop.
- Get away from me.
- Deanna: Reg. Reg.
( whispers )
Not now.
- Get away. Get away!
- Pete, stop. Pete--
( Deanna screams )
- No, no! Oh, my God! No!
- ( gurgling )
Deanna: Oh, my love.
My love, my love.
- This is him!
- Stop!
- ( Deanna sobbing ) Oh, God!
Oh! Oh, my love.
My love, my love.
( sobbing )
No, my love, no, no.
No, my love.
No, my love, my love.
Pete:
It's him!
This is him!
Rick...
do it.
- ( gunshot )
- ( women scream )
Morgan:
Rick?
( theme music playing )
( snarling )
( cans rattling )