[Girls Planet 999]
[The second mission is called
Combination Mission.]
[The second mission has begun.]
[Combination mission]
[The first cells will be disbanded,]
[As the existing cells broke up,
it became harder to survive.]
[and you will go into battles
of 3, 6, and 9.]
[New battles among 3-member, 6-member,
and 9-member teams begin!]
[Top 9... They're like the Avengers.]
[Team Avengers with
4 Planet Top 9 is created!]
[Still, I don't want to drop out.]
[They need the benefit to survive
more desperately!]
[I need the benefit no matter what.]
♫ Someone else, you must have
confused me, confused me with ♫
[The second mission performances begin!]
♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
♫ Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
[Including special Rap Master
Woo Won Jae,]
I want you to continue to be a rapper.
♫ The love we lost in this life ♫
[the touching performance
surprised everyone.]
It was nice.
This is hopeless.
You need to do better.
[You should do better.
The 1st place can't do it like this.]
Rank one is
supposed to do better than this.
[Pack your bags or survive.
It's one of these two.]
Or pack up. It's either of the two.
♫ I spend a year trying to erase you ♫
[Number 1 Kawaguchi Yurina's crisis]
[What's the result of the performance?]
[The third mission of Girls Planet 999.]
[The third mission is revealed!]
[New songs for Creation Mission
are revealed today!]
[And]
[the interim result of the 2nd global
voting will be revealed shortly!]
[A week has passed
after the first Survival Announcement.]
[The girls are here.]
There.
I get scared whenever I see this.
[Who made the girls scared?]
What's that?
What...
I'm nervous.
We might be given
the second mission today.
I can't wait.
Oh, gosh.
What could it be? I'm so curious.
I don't want to do
anything charismatic this time.
-Since I did "How You Like That."
-Same here.
-What could it be?
-I wonder what.
Will the masters be here?
I guess.
[They aggressively welcome Planet Master.]
I love his outfit today.
Me too.
[Colorful clothes]
-Hello.
[Group bowing]
I'm Planet Master Yeo Jin Goo.
It's good to see you.
So close.
The first survival announcement
took place last week.
Before we get started,
let me congratulate you 54 girls
for getting the chance to stay here
and keep pursuing your dreams
to debut as K-pop idol singers.
[Congratulations.]
Congrats.
Aside from the cell rankings
from last week's survival announcement,
the 54 girls have gotten
new individual ranks in each group
[C09 Li Yiman, P09 Kim Chae Hyun,
J09 Kuwahara Ayana]
along with the new Top 9.
The votes have been reset.
And from this voting on,
there won't be any cell votes.
-What?
-Is it all about individual votes?
[The new rule caused a stir
among the girls.]
No more cell votes?
Cell votes will be gone.
Just the cell votes?
-Or the cells?
-We're still in a cell, right?
-I don't know.
-Gosh.
-No.
-Are they getting rid of cells too?
-From now on,
-Do we compete individually?
the members of each group
will be ranked individually
through global votes
instead of cell votes.
-This is shocking.
-From the bottom rank...
[C23 Wu Tammy]
The same number of members
in each group will be eliminated
from the bottom rank.
I just got goosebumps.
I'm scared.
I'm in danger.
Oh, dear.
-The same number...
-This is crazy.
Just crazy.
If then, down to which rankings
will you get to survive?
Please.
-Mom...
-I hope it's not too many.
[The ones to be eliminated]
How many?
This coming voting result
will eliminate...
Please.
A few.
I'll let you know in a minute.
[I hate "later"!]
Now the second mission of Girls Planet 999
will be revealed.
[Screaming]
It's called Combination Mission.
[Combination Mission]
-What?
-"Combination."
What, combination?
Combination pizza?
[Kim Su Yeon, 19 years old,
Deep love for pizza.]
It means a mix.
-What?
-A mix.
A mix.
[Combination?]
During this mission, your cells
will be disbanded.
You'll be joining new teams.
Don't disband us as you want.
[We don't want to break up.]
I'm not okay.
[They're cell "It's Okay"
but now cell "It's Not Okay!"]
We're not okay.
-Why is it over for us?
-It's so sudden.
I knew the cells would be disbanded
at some point.
But I didn't know it'd be this soon.
This soon?
[Of course, I want to stick to my cell.]
[Jeong Ji Yoon, Ezaki Hikaru]
[My teammates gave me so much help.]
I wish I could keep it this way, but...
In front of you,
there are 3, 6, and 9 written here.
These numbers mean
the minimum and maximum number of members
of your new teams.
It's not cells, but teams.
[Translation of what Myah said: No way.]
-Teams?
-Yes.
And during this Combination Mission,
the groups with 3, 6, or 9,
the same number of members
will be competing.
So six teams will be competing.
-So 2 teams of 9 members.
-Not bad.
Now let's check
the songs for this mission.
[Let us know.]
-This, I can't wait.
-Me neither.
-I'm curious.
-Oh, gosh.
Let me reveal the songs for each group
and the position of each song.
[A magic that makes them
automatically stretch their body]
Oh, gosh.
Goodness.
I need to be prepared for this.
I'll start with the songs for the group
of three-member teams.
I can't stand watching this.
The first mission song.
[Focused]
["My House" by 2PM]
[3-member group 1,
"My House" by 2PM for vocalists]
For vocals, "My House" by 2PM.
["My House" by 2PM that recently gained
popularity again is a groovy song]
[that honestly expresses
feelings of a man attracted to a woman.]
[I love it.]
♫ To my house ♫
That's for vocals?
-For vocals?
-It is.
[What, that's for vocals?]
It was new because I thought
it'd be for dancers.
"My House" is a great song.
It might be cool.
That's for vocals? Not bad.
♫ It's all right ♫
[They're already into "My House".]
The second mission song.
-Dance.
-Rap?
["VVS" from "Show Me the Money 9"]
For rappers.
[3-member group 2, "VVS"
by SMTM 9 for rappers]
-Great.
-"VVS" from "Show Me the Money 9."
["VVS" by Show Me the Money 9
is about a life and a goal]
[that will shine like VVS diamonds.]
-♫ VVS ♫
-It's a great song.
[Everyone is obsessed with "VVS" rap.]
♫ VVS ♫
-"Show Me the Money"!
-"Show Me the Money."
[Excited]
[I was truly torn.]
[I wanted to do it so bad.]
"VVS."
[I wanted to do it.]
The third mission song.
Let it be a song for dancers.
-Please.
-Reveal it.
["We Are" by Woo Won Jae]
-Rap.
-For rappers.
[3-person Group 3, Rap,
"We Are" by Woo Won Jae]
"We Are" by Woo Won Jae.
[Won Jae described his past days
when he felt the difference of time.]
We can't do this!
This song is amazing.
How are we supposed to do that?
Wow.
[Kim Hye Rim, 23 years old, vocalist,
Wannabe MC]
♫ Before the spit on my monitor dries up ♫
I don't think I can rap.
The fourth mission song.
-The fourth.
-It's probably a dance song.
Dance?
["All About You" by Taeyeon]
[3-person Group 4, Vocalist,
"All About You" by Taeyeon]
For vocals, "All About You" by Taeyeon.
[This soundtrack of "Hotel Del Luna" is
about the affection toward one's lover.]
"Hotel Del Luna."
[The girls' reactions to seeing
Gu Chan Sung right before them]
-"Hotel Del Luna."
-It was the soundtrack.
[Pleased]
♫ A poem about you ♫
[All about you]
This song suits you well.
[They are both great songs]
and I hope I get to perform one of them.
The fifth mission song.
["MAFIA In the morning" by ITZY]
For vocals,
"MAFIA In the morning" by ITZY.
[3-person Group 5, Vocalist,
"MAFIA In the morning" by ITZY]
[A hip-hop song by ITZY
with their honest and confident charms]
That's a song for the vocal position?
[She's not mad.]
[The dance moves for the song
"MAFIA In the morning" is amazing]
[so I was confused why it was for vocals.]
The sixth mission song.
For dancers,
"No Excuses" by Megan Trainor.
[3-person Group 6, Dance,
"No Excuses" by Meghan Trainor]
[A pop song with a funky baseline,
guitar riffs, and rich electronic sounds.]
Oh!
♫ Talking crazy ♫
I wanted to do that song
the moment I saw it.
[Combination Mission]
Next, we'll move on to the battle songs
for six-member groups.
I think a lot will be for dance positions.
The first mission song
["Missing You" by BTOB]
[6-person Group 1, Vocalist and rap,
"Missing You" by BTOB]
is for vocal and rap.
"Missing You" by BTOB.
["Missing You" is a ballad song in which
BTOB's singing skills stand out.]
BTOB?
♫ Missing you ♫
I love this song!
The second song is
["My Sea" by IU]
[6-person Group 2, Vocalist,
"My Sea" by IU]
for vocals, "My Sea" by IU.
[IU sings her sorrowful lyrics
and shows off her high notes.]
Wow! I want to do that song.
Isn't that song really hard?
Totally.
It has a lot of high notes.
[It's known to be difficult
even among vocalists.]
That song is really hard.
Next is the third mission song.
["Missing You", "My Sea"]
Is it a rap?
[6-person Group 3, Dancer,
"Fate" by Lee Sun Hee]
-For dance,
-That's for dancers?
"Fate" by Lee Sun Hee.
[A song that represents the legendary
Lee Sun Hee with a lyrical melody.]
Dance?
[Dance?]
[Doubting their eyes]
What?
Dance? Wait...
Dancing to this song?
It was very new to me.
Lastly, I will announce the battle songs
for nine-member groups.
Dance?
The first song is
for dancers, "Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK.
[9-person Group 1, Dance,
"Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK]
[A cheerful and refreshing song
featuring Selena Gomez]
♫ Ice cream, chillin' ♫
I want to do that song.
The second mission song.
["Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK]
[9-person Group 2, Dancer,
"Salute" by Little Mix]
For dancers, "Salute" by Little Mix.
[A song that gives powerful energy
to the listeners]
I want that one!
-I want to do that song.
-Salute!
Salute!
There are a lot of good songs.
Now all the songs for Combination Mission
["My House", "VVS", "We Are",
"All About You", "MAFIA In the morning"]
have been revealed.
In this mission,
we'll test your individual strengths.
Choose the position you're confident in.
You'll write the rap, create choreography,
and do the arrangement.
Wait. Hold on...
Oh my gosh.
The arrangement too?
What's the most important for this mission
is the benefit.
As before,
when all 11 teams are done performing,
[the masters will chose]
[the best teams from each group.]
Everyone on that team will receive
benefit points.
-Points?
-The benefit
[Points?]
will be divided among
the teammates equally.
Three-member teams get a third.
Six-member teams get one sixth.
Nine-member teams get one ninth
per individual.
So the teams of three
have more competition,
["My House", "VVS", "We Are"]
but they can get higher individual scores.
["Ice Cream", "Salute"]
The teams of nine have less competition,
but they will receive
lower individual points.
Maybe I'll do Meghan's song then.
The Combination Mission's benefit points
-is...
-Is it 100,000?
-Is it 90,000?
-It's...
[The benefit of the Combination Mission
is 270,000 points!]
It's 270,000 points.
It's 270,000?
[I have to get it to survive.]
It's 270,000 points?
[I felt I had to win.]
This is what the winners will get.
Three-member teams
get 90,000 points per member.
[90,000 points per member
of a 3-person team]
Six-member teams
get 45,000 points per member.
[45,000 points per member
of a 6-person team]
Nine-member teams
get 30,000 points per member.
[30,000 points per member
of a 9-person team]
You may now start
picking your songs.
[I hope there's one vocal position
for me!]
[I'm going to dance no matter what.]
The order of selection is by cell,
starting with
the one in first place
[17th-place cell]
based on global votes.
[13th-place cell]
[The Planet Pass holders will choose
their songs last.]
We'll be last.
-Cell order? Then we go first.
-Right.
[Cai Bing, Choi Yu Jin, and May are
in the lead to choose the song.]
But there's a limit to each group.
Songs for three-member groups.
One from each K, C, and J.
Songs for six-member groups.
Two from K, C, and J.
Songs for nine-member groups.
Three from K, C, and J.
Now, first place.
Choi Yu Jin, Cai Bing, and May.
Please start.
What do I do?
Which song do you want?
"No Excuses" and "Salute".
I want to do so many of them.
This one, this one, and this one.
-What should I do?
-What will you do?
[I just have to pick the one I want.]
[The dignity of the 1st placer]
What should I do?
"No Excuses" isn't bad.
"Salute" would be good too.
"Fate" would be hard, but worth trying.
What should I do?
[The composure of the one
who has a choice]
[Yu Jin and May chose a 6-person group.]
[On the other hand,
Cai Bing chose a 9-person group.]
["Fate" by Lee Sun Hee]
["Salute"]
[They've all chosen the songs
they want to perform.]
Second place. Young Eun, Xiao Ting,
Yurina. Please start.
-Waiting is more nerve-racking.
-Right?
Dance position.
-Vocal position.
-Vocal.
-Vocal?
-Really?
Yes.
Dance is good,
but I wanted to try something new.
Here.
["My House"]
Who is it?
[Shen Xiao Ting and Kawaguchi Yurina chose
a 6-person group.]
What...
Oh my.
[She only smiles mysteriously.]
You came here?
Yes.
[The two walk toward them in peace.]
You should come here.
[It's here.]
[Shen Xiao Ting betrayed Yurina
and left her.]
[Which will Kawaguchi Yurina choose?]
That one?
[She chooses "Missing You" by BTOB.]
Really?
[They all chose the positions
they wanted.]
We met again.
-Did you decide?
-Yes.
-Me too.
-Did you? Oh my...
-I want this one.
-I want this one too.
No way!
I wonder who we'll get.
I'm so excited.
There's so many of you.
Oh my.
-Really?
-I'm with you.
Wow!
["Fate" Team consists of girls
with high rankings.]
I'm alone.
Gosh.
[Ezaki Hikaru chose "No Excuses"
of a 3-person group.]
I can do it.
People will be surprised to see our team.
Come on.
Bye.
Gosh.
[The three part ways.]
Which one?
[Kang Ye Seo is the only one
who chose a 6-person group.]
Us?
Is it us?
[Nodding]
[The first one I saw was Yu Jin.]
[Then May, Xiao Ting, and Rui Qi.]
I was like, what a lineup!
What's with this group?
I was flustered.
I got chills!
[Getting goosebumps]
That team's amazing.
["Fate" by Lee Sun Hee]
We're done for.
[They have many people from Top 9.]
[So many of them are skilled and popular.]
[I was a bit worried.]
What?
[Kim Chae Hyun and Li Yiman chose
a 6-person group.]
Oh my.
Here?
-Where?
-So this is how it's done.
[Please come to me.]
Come to me, please!
-Hi.
-Here?
[Chae Hyun chose the same team
as Jeong Ji Yoon wished.]
Wow.
I'm so glad you came.
[It feels so reliable.]
[Kim Chae Hyun and Li Yiman chose
"My Sea" Team,]
Yes!
[Kuwahara Ayana chose
"My House" team of three members.]
-Let's do our best.
-Yes.
[The door is opening. You come in.]
It's Xu Zi Yin.
Hello.
Xu Zi Yin.
[Come here, Xu Zi Yin.]
It's my favorite girl.
Yay.
[Kim Do Ah and Arai Risako
chose "Salute" Team.]
Come here.
[Songs were chosen rapidly.]
-It's over.
-Really?
I'm so happy to be in a reliable team.
Six-member "My Sea" Team
[Vocal position]
is closed.
-Don't say that.
-It's over.
-Okay.
[Vocal positions are filling up fast.]
[I don't have a choice.]
I kept counting what was left.
"Ice Cream".
[Higher ranking girls chose the songs
they want.]
[I keep praying.]
I hope there'd be one dance spot left
for me.
Everyone. I beg you.
-"My House" Team is closed.
-My goodness.
[Vocal position]
-No.
-Zhou Xin Yu.
-I'm jealous.
-It's okay, Wen Zhe.
-Wen Zhe.
-Don't cry.
We can do it.
I'm having a mental breakdown.
I don't have a choice.
[Which positions will these girls take?]
[Ikema Ruan automatically fills the
remaining spot of "Ice Cream" Team.]
[Wen Zhe fills the last rap position
of "We Are" Team.]
Good.
[I was smiling when I was standing there.]
But I kept thinking, "What do I do?"
["What do I do now?"]
All the teams are completed.
[3, 6, 9 Combination Team per position
are set.]
Do you like your new teams?
-Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Lastly, it is what you are curious of
the most.
The elimination?
-You're right.
-I will reveal the number of elimination.
Please.
-I wonder how many it is.
-Is it 22?
Out of 54 girls,
the number of girls who will be eliminated
in the second survival announcement...
My heart aches.
I'd rather not hear it.
It's 30.
What?
-What?
-Is this the last round?
Based on the result of global voting,
ten people with low ranks
from each group
which means ranks 1 to 8
in each group will survive.
From ranks 9 to 18 will be eliminated.
That's so many.
No one knows what will happen to me.
[Even being in K9 makes the same.]
However, the only hope
for the eliminated girls...
Planet Pass?
Is there another Planet Pass?
-Planet Pass is
-Another one?
available.
[Girls are relieved
that Planet Pass exists.]
So please show the Planet Guardians
you're doing your best to the end.
[Planet Masters as well]
Good luck, everyone.
-Let's go.
-I can do it.
Thank you.
-Good luck.
-We can do it.
[After the song selection...]
[Getting ready for the
Combination Mission.]
["Show Me The Money 9",
Rap position of "VVS" Team]
[Feeling awkward]
-Let's pick the leader first.
-The leader.
Who should be the leader?
[She's 18.]
[Lee Chae Yun, the youngest,
tries to read the room.]
I'm the oldest.
[I'm the oldest.]
[Leader sister?]
[Leader selection of "The Eve" Team
for Connect Mission]
I'm the oldest.
[Leader vibes]
Can I be the leader?
[Fu Ya Ning became the leader
by being the eldest.]
-You're the leader.
-Let's do this.
[I'm a big sister too.]
I'm the oldest.
You?
I can do it.
What about you? Are you okay with it?
-I want to be a leader too.
-I see.
[It didn't work out like Fu Ya Ning.]
[I want to be a leader too.]
I can't speak Korean.
[She happily gives up her leader role.]
You should do it.
-Really?
-Yes.
Are you sure?
This is my first time becoming a rapper.
-Your first time rapping?
-Yes.
-I see.
-We can do it.
[Honestly, I was a little worried.]
[I was worried.]
-We can do it.
[Is there a reason for choosing "VVS"?]
I don't know why,
but the moment I had to make a choice,
[I suddenly felt brave
and decided to give it a try.]
"VVS". I can do it.
-Shall we listen to it first?
-Okay.
Okay.
[They're listening to the music
seriously.]
[Serious]
Let's divide the parts first.
-Like this.
-Okay.
That's one bar.
[Let's me try to follow.]
-Okay?
-Okay.
We have to cut the lyrics.
We have to first pick the person
for the killing-part.
Let's listen to it again.
-Can we listen to it one more time?
-Yes.
[They're listening to the music
seriously again.]
We will have to divide the parts more.
It's here.
Let's listen to it again.
Okay.
[Listening for the third time already]
Okay. Good.
I was thinking...
Let's listen to it again.
[Sighing]
[It's so hard.]
After choosing the song,
I noticed the difficult parts in the song.
We have to choose the person
for the killing-part now.
[Liang Jiao feels "VVS" too difficult
as it's her first time to rap.]
[The team member is studying
Liang Jiao's reactions.]
[Will she listen to the song again?]
Let's listen to the whole song again.
[Did we hear it wrong?]
Don't you think it's better
to divide the parts first?
Don't you think it's better to divide
first and listen?
[Team members are fed up with
Liang Jiao's constant request.]
I had no idea where to start.
[It was very, very hard.]
I never expected it to be this hard.
[Now I'm getting afraid.]
["We Are" by Woo Won Jae]
["We Are" Team is depressed
as they also need to rap.]
[The team members don't look happy.]
[When Combination Mission song
is being selected]
Do you know this song?
I don't know.
I don't think I should rap.
[Kim Hye Rim of K-Group sings the song,
"We Are" to Wen Zhe.]
♫ Even before the spit
on the monitor dries up ♫
[I don't know this song!]
[Which part did you want to avoid
the most?]
I want to avoid rap.
"VVS" and "We Are".
"We Were"?
[I don't know the rap.
I thought I could never do it.]
"MAFIA In the morning" J-Group is closed.
[Vocal position of J-Group
filled up fast.]
["My House" Team. "All About You" Team.]
[The vocal songs kept disappearing.]
J-Group is closed.
[I kept thinking, "What do I do?"
I was worried the whole time.]
If you give me one vocal spot,
I will do my very best.
"My House" Team. "All About You" Team.
[Vocal position of K-Group is
filling up fast as well.]
"MAFIA In the morning". "Missing You".
"My Sea" Team.
[Oh, no.]
They are all closed.
[Sighing]
[This is terrible.]
It could be my last time.
So I'd like to sing.
♫ I keep shedding tears endlessly ♫
Seriously, I can't rap.
[Three people who got rap songs
are full of worry.]
[I can only sigh now.]
Let's write the lyrics in Korean.
In Korean.
[I'm in trouble.]
Since it's hard, let's try a little.
[Kim Bo Ra and Wen Zhe are writing
the lyrics in a calm and orderly way.]
[Nagai Manami looks at the two writing.]
[I have to compose in Korean,
but since I can't speak Korean at all,]
[I thought it was really hard.]
I wrote three bars.
Really? That's amazing.
♫ I am practicing alone at 3 a.m. ♫
[Wen Zhe raps with the lyrics she wrote.]
[Listening carefully]
Yeah.
♫ People are starting a new morning ♫
[Kim Bo Ra does it well too.]
-Amazing.
-Good job.
-You think so?
-You tried.
-I did.
[Nagai Manami envies the two.]
Do you want to try too?
[Sighing]
Right.
Let's go.
[Despite the team members' support,]
[she is not gaining courage...]
I'm afraid
this will be my last time.
[I don't want Bo Ra and Wen Zhe to
be eliminated.]
I wonder if I'm dragging them down.
[I feel so confused.]
[1 hour ago,
when they were choosing the song]
[She went to
"MAFIA In the morning" by ITZY]
"Mafia"?
[Sakamoto Mashiro choose
"MAFIA In the morning".]
[The song has a bit of a dark mood.]
[I thought I'd be able to show
some of my new sides.]
So I wanted to do it.
[Someone heads towards Sakamoto Mashiro.]
[It's Fu Ya Ning of C-Group!]
[Nervous]
♫ We go up, helicopter ♫
[During Planet Scout Battle,
her powerful voice intimidated everyone.]
[C-Group's Fu Ya Ning surprised everyone.]
♫ But you don't ♫
[Surprised]
[Nervous, anxious]
I want to do this song.
I never imagined I'd come to do it
with Fu Ya Ning.
["MAFIA In the morning" Team
gathered after choosing.]
[Awkward]
[Careful]
[Glancing]
[Whimpering]
Why don't we decide
-on our team's leader first?
-The leader.
[Fu Ya Ning should be the leader.]
I'd like Mashiro to be our leader.
-Me?
-Yes.
Right, I have my faith in you.
She led Team 1 of "Fiesta,"
[Fu Ya Ning, "MAFIA In the Morning" Team,
Connect Mission]
-and her team won.
-Team 1.
[So I believe she has
her own ways to lead a team.]
I thought you'd want to do it.
I thought you would.
[I told her that I expected her to do it,]
[but she said no.]
So I took the offer.
When you heard this song,
did you come to have any ideas?
-Me.
-You have an idea.
-A bit of rock.
-Rock?
[Sound of the electric guitar]
We can add the sound of heel clicking.
[Sound of heels]
Like, "It's me." How's that?
[Point motions]
[They actively suggest ideas.]
After we go, "I'm mafia..."
I listen to others' opinions.
Rock, good idea.
[Sakamoto Mashiro's Leadership Tips,
1. Listen to suggestions.]
Nice. It's very nice.
I organize ideas.
Let's take out the part that goes,
"Yesterday night."
[Sakamoto Mashiro's Leadership Tips,
2. Organize ideas.]
-Me too.
-Right away.
I work hard
[Sakamoto Mashiro's Leadership Tips,
3. Promote peace.]
to keep things in peace.
[Arrangement Meeting]
Who's the leader?
It's me.
-Our plan is
-Go on.
[What's the concept for
Team "MAFIA In the Morning"?]
-to give it a rock vibe.
-Rock?
-That's how we want it to be.
-I see.
And our concept is three girls
[All three of them date a bad boy]
determined to get back
at their bad ex-boyfriends.
[and seek revenge.]
-Revenge?
-Right.
[During their meeting, they came
together on the theme of revenge.]
-Taking revenge.
-Right.
Three betrayed girls
[Their concept is a girl seeking revenge
on a guy that betrayed her.]
-Right.
-taking revenge on bad guys.
Bad men.
[Bad boy, Bang]
"Bad men."
The concept is
[Nervous]
not bad.
I like this powerful, rock vibe too.
I see.
She's good at leading the team.
She has her own ideas,
and I know she will lead us well.
-I believe you.
-I believe...
I'll do my best so that my teammates
won't get in arguments and stay in peace.
[Meanwhile, the 3-member dance team
"No Excuses" looks serious.]
[J-Group's Ezaki Hikaru]
[A bright, hard-working genius]
♫ Burn Crush in your area ♫
[K-Group's Kim Su Yeon]
♫ In this moment ♫
[An all-round player
and performance genius]
[C-Group's Yang Zi Ge]
[A shocking and terrifying fashion queen?]
[It was shocking and frightening.]
Are you a dancer?
I...
I don't know.
[Bright]
Was Yang Zi Ge a dancer?
C... Who's coming from C-Group?
I hope it's someone similar to us.
[The door finally opens.]
Oh, my.
Is she with us?
[Her hand shows how flustered she is.]
[Everyone is focused on
C-Group's Yang Zi Ge's choice.]
No?
[C-Group's Yang Ze Ge joins
Team "No Excuses".]
[No way.]
-This is crazy.
-Gosh.
-Oh, my gosh.
[They're flustered at her
unexpected choice.]
Oh, my gosh.
[I didn't know she'd actually choose it.]
I was surprised for a short moment.
[Kim Su Yeon, "No Excuses" Team,
Connect Mission]
When she performed "Pretty U,"
she sang more than danced.
I thought she was in a vocal position.
Interestingly, I sang a lot here.
But I didn't get to show
my dancing skills.
So I wanted a chance to do that.
We have to work on the choreography.
Honestly, I've never created one before.
What do we do then?
She said she'd never made
any choreography before.
And that she was not very good.
[So I didn't know what to do.]
It's not like you can't
create dance moves at all, right?
Even if you're not very good at it,
give it a try,
and we'll work on it together
to make it better.
-Oh, okay.
-You know what I mean?
-Okay.
[Su Yeon really puts faith in me.]
Let's work on parts individually
and share the moves later.
[They begin dividing up the parts under
K-Group's Kim Su Yeon's lead.]
-What do you think?
-Good.
So I thought I'd do my part
[as best I could.]
Do you want to see what I made?
-Okay.
-Sure.
Together like this.
[C-Group's Yang Ze Ge shows her teammates
the choreography she came up with.]
[Flustered]
And then...
This side.
[She continues showing them
her choreography, but...]
I didn't show it.
But I felt completely lost.
I didn't want to hurt her feelings
because then that'd ruin the mood.
Like when we performed "The Eve."
[Glaring]
Right.
Well...
[Kim Su Yeon and Ezaki Hikaru were
uncomfortable]
Hold on.
[when there was trouble during "The Eve".]
-Da Yeon.
-What's wrong?
That wouldn't be good at all.
We know it.
That it's not good at all.
We tend to be careful with what we say.
-♫ Open up ♫
-♫ Up ♫
[They try out Yang Ze Ge's choreography.]
Is this how we're going to do it?
Or like this?
It's too easy.
We can change it up as we go.
[We can do it.]
[I feel more at ease.]
I do feel more at ease.
[But I've become worried]
that things might get harder.
["My House" by 2PM,
"VVS" by Show Me the Money 9]
["All About You" by Taeyeon, Vocal]
[The situation when they were
choosing their songs]
-Choi Ye Young.
-Hey!
[The 3-member vocal group desperately
want a girl from K-Group.]
Ye Young, please.
Please.
[It's K-Group's Choi Ye Young!]
Is this how it's going to be?
[Choi Ye Young, Connect Mission]
[During "Fiesta," I did the killing-part]
[and so I had to yield
on other vocal parts.]
So I wanted a chance
to show my vocal skills this time.
[What is Choi Ye Young's choice?]
It's crazy.
["All About You" by Taeyeon
vs. "MAFIA" In the morning by ITZY]
Ye Young.
[Choi Ye Young chose "All About You".]
[Disappointed]
Ye Young.
[I've heard Ye Young sing
many times before.]
So I know she's good at singing.
[Huang Xing Qiao, "All About You" Team,
Connect Mission]
I performed "Fiesta" with her.
So I know she is very good.
Should we listen to it first?
♫ A poem about you ♫
[Before dividing up the parts,
Team "All About You" sings the song.]
♫ Whenever I think of it ♫
♫ I want to memorize it ♫
[A soft melody that covers our ears.]
♫ Please don't forget ♫
That's what the song is like.
The song goes in a shy mood.
In the first verse,
let's express a shy emotion.
In the second verse,
we could approach that person.
-Like a story?
-Yes.
[Give it a story.]
I'd like our performance to progress
[Choi Ye Young suggests they change things
up in the 2nd verse to fit the story.]
to go along with this story
of approaching one's crush.
Okay.
We had to create a performance
that's 2 minutes and 30 seconds long.
So we threw different ideas
and thought of making it cute.
[Arrangement Meeting]
-Who's the leader?
-Me.
Could you tell us how you will perform?
We're wondering if the second verse
can be cute and bubbly.
Could you give us an example?
♫ In this fleeting season ♫
[Choi Ye Young demonstrates
according to her idea.]
♫ My heart stays unchanged ♫
-That's a shuffle rhythm.
-♫ A poem about you ♫
[The song sounds brighter
than the original.]
♫ Whenever I think of it ♫
Could it be changed this way?
[Satisfied]
[Satisfied 2]
So you want to change the song completely.
[It sounds like you want to make it
into a completely different song.]
Yes, just the second verse.
When I think of this song,
it's poignant and emotional,
not cute.
Discuss it a little more.
It's "All About You."
[Your song is "All About You".]
[Their Arrangement Meeting is over.]
-Why didn't I think of that?
-I know.
Why didn't we think of that?
-Why didn't we?
-We're fools.
What on earth... Let's think more.
[At first, we thought]
that we only needed to focus
on showing our vocal skills.
We took it too easily.
[We needed to understand the song first.]
[And the fact that we didn't]
made me feel ashamed.
["My House" by 2PM]
[The other 3-member vocal team]
"My House."
Why did you want to do "My House"?
Because I wanted to be cool.
Because it's cool like "Mic Drop."
[Like during "Mic Drop"]
[Embarrassed]
That's too...
[Wang Ya Le was in charge of rap
for "Mic Drop".]
[Discouraged]
[You can just go home, Wang Ya Le.]
I'm not confident and I'm afraid.
Last time, I had no choice but to rap.
[But I want to return to my element]
and return to singing.
-Leader.
[They decided to choose the leader first.]
Leader.
[Wang Ya Le volunteers to be the leader.]
First, I learned music for 7 or 6 years.
I want to produce our music.
I want to be the leader, too.
[I wanted to be the leader, too.]
But I thought Ya Le had better
musical knowledge.
But you can play the piano.
So I think you'll be a good leader.
Okay.
First time being a leader.
Two or three?
♫ Give me, give me ♫
♫ It's alright ♫
We need a chorus here.
[Leader Wang Ya Le suggests them
to add a harmony.]
A chorus.
It'd be so touching
if three people
sang chords in harmony.
[Mid-checkup D-1]
♫ I'll be waiting for you there
in ten minutes ♫
[Seo Young Eun and Wang Ya Le practice
the harmony.]
♫ It's alright ♫
We're off-chord.
♫ I'll be waiting for you ♫
[Leader Wang Ya Le's unstable tone]
♫ Let's go to my place ♫
[They keep practicing,
but they keep going off.]
She suggested we sing in chords
but none was working.
♫ I'll pick you up ♫
[They are in a serious situation
a day before Mid-checkup.]
[I felt I had to step up.]
You know this chord here...
Why?
I think it's a different style.
It's mid check-up tomorrow
but if we don't have the chords down,
we have nothing to show them.
Does anyone want extra practice?
[Practicing]
♫ Goodbye, baby, goodbye ♫
We have nothing.
I'm sorry.
[We have to practice. We have to.]
[I'm so desperate.]
Ya Le, can you do the chords well?
Of course.
Me. It's me.
-"Fate" Team. Let's do this!
[Meanwhile, "Fate" Team is peaceful.]
Wow, I love our team. It's perfect.
[I thought we were a purple team.]
I'm very confident about our team.
-"Fate."
[Checking the mission song video]
I sang this at a karaoke a lot.
Are we dancing to this?
It's hard to make moves to this.
[The members were worried
about the difficult choreography mission.]
[At that moment,
the remix part of "Fate" plays.]
-Whoever does this will win.
-I know.
-You'll win if you do that.
-You can't beat that.
The team will win this.
-We already have six winners set.
-Yes.
[I really wanted it.]
Everyone seemed to want it,
[Rank 1 cell]
[and we got to choose first.]
[That's why I was so happy.]
[Over 4 P9 gathered after 4 choices.]
Wow.
[Is this the hottest place for Top 9?]
-I got goosebumps.
-Oh my.
That team is so strong.
They are legendary.
Thank goodness we are not against them.
Thank goodness.
[The top ranks gathered for "Fate" Team.]
[I could hear girls say we are strong.]
[I am a member of "Fate" Team.]
I felt so proud. "Don't say that."
I was proud.
Who wants to do the killing-part?
-Hands up!
-Hands.
Me.
Killing-part?
I will just try it out.
Me too.
It's okay.
[Raising her hand]
If you want to try, raise your hand.
They are all older than me.
Nine years older than me.
[I was not sure if I could try.]
What are you doing?
I never got to try it.
I will just try it.
I tried a killing-part before.
Someone else should get the opportunity.
Yes.
Ye Seo, you first.
I think she goes well with this song.
Good luck.
My hands and feet are sweaty.
[The Killing-Part applicant begins
the free dance.]
How pretty.
She is so pretty.
[The applicants express the song
in their own way.]
How pretty.
It feels sentimental.
-How heartbreaking.
-Right.
[Who will take the Killing-Part?]
-Two, three.
Ye Seo.
[Kang Ye Seo got 4 votes.]
-Ye Seo.
-Okay.
Thank you.
[The youngest Kang Ye Seo won
the Killing-Part.]
-Good job.
-Ye Seo.
We don't have to worry now.
["Fate" Team has a smooth start.
How will their future turn out?]
Wow.
[There is awkwardness
in "Missing You" Team.]
[One person draws attention.]
[Exclaiming]
Wow.
[Number one was in our team.]
Kawaguchi Yurina.
[Yurina is in first place in the Top 9.]
That's why I feel reassured.
Yes!
We should see who gets the killing-part.
♫ Please come back ♫
This is the killing-part.
♫ I can't forget you ♫
♫ Please come back ♫
[The main vocal part slash the
Killing-Part has a charming high pitch.]
You have to be able to sing it to get it.
-♫ Please come back ♫
[Each member warms up their voices
to try the Killing-Part.]
♫ Please ♫
[Unusual warmup]
[On eggshells]
Until now, I was scared to try out
[for the main part or the killing-part.]
[But this time, I want to live up]
[to the people who are cheering for me.]
[I want to be more aggressive]
[when going for a part
or sharing opinions.]
♫ Please come back ♫
[Kubo Reina's loud voice
echoes in the rehearsal studio.]
[Nervous]
Let's go, Yurina!
[But until now, I have never been
the main vocalist.]
[I'm not confident,]
[but I want to try it.]
Start.
♫ Please come back ♫
[Kawaguchi Yurina plucks her courage
and tries the Killing-Part.]
[It is time to vote.]
Shall we vote?
Three, two,
[Who will get the Killing-Part?]
one.
[Kawaguchi Yurina gets the Killing-Part.]
-Yurina.
Really?
[There are many good singers]
[on the team,]
so I didn't think I'd get it.
I was so startled I forgot to be happy.
[Arrangement Meeting]
Who's the main vocalist
with the killing-part?
Yurina will do it.
Shall we hear you sing?
♫ I can't forget you ♫
♫ Please come back ♫
I think the key is too low.
Should we make it B major?
Try it.
♫ Please come back ♫
We have to change the key.
We have to change it
to fit the female voice.
Try practicing with this.
[The Arrangement Meeting ends.]
[They are flustered
by the unexpected situation.]
I think we should rethink
about the killing-part.
[I was given an important role,]
[but I didn't think
we should leave it as it was.]
[I was feeling confused]
[because I thought]
it would be hard to keep my ranking.
[Just like "Missing You", they are
struggling with the Killing-Part.]
♫ Eyes ♫
I can't do it.
That's high.
It's too high.
We have to test our limits.
It's hard to sing without falsetto.
[IU pulls off the high pitch easily.]
♫ Eyes ♫
It's too high.
[Giving up]
[Turning over a new leaf]
Does anyone want the killing-part?
♫ I will not let the darkness
that traps me ♫
♫ Close my eyes ♫
[Everyone is impressed
with Jeong Ji Yoon's high notes.]
Wow, Ji Yoon.
[Thumbs up]
Wow.
[Eyes widening]
[Ji Yoon's voice echoes even in
the space for 9-member groups.]
Is she the one from "The Eve"?
Yes, Ji Yoon.
The vocal power.
I want to do it,
but I cannot get the note.
Just yell it out and try it.
[She tries while everyone
is cheering for her.]
♫ I will not let the darkness ♫
I'm in trouble.
I don't think I can do it.
♫ Mi ♫
[But she can't sing the notes
that are usually easy for her.]
What do I do?
♫ Answer ♫
♫ Every day ♫
Did I have trouble with this note before?
From what I remember,
I could do that note.
I'm scared.
[Shana can't sing high notes
for some reason.]
Don't be scared. You can do it.
[She got even scared to sing.]
I'm scared.
[Sighing]
After starting Girls Planet...
["All rounder."]
[Nonaka Shana was confident as
an all-rounder when she first appeared.]
[But after "BOOMBAHYAH"
where she was shadowed by Ezaki Hikaru]
[There are a lot of people]
[and the "The Eve" performed by many
talented people with high ranks,]
[prettier than me and better than me.]
[she met Jeong Ji Yoon who was the main
vocalist of Team "The Eve" again.]
[So I lost confidence.]
[Ji Yoon is practicing and she's good.]
I feel embarrassed to practice around her.
♫ That traps me ♫
It made me so nervous.
I don't think I can do it.
Shall we pick the killing-part now?
-Now?
-Yes.
♫ Close my eyes ♫
[Killing-Part candidate Jeong Ji Yoon
successfully sang high notes.]
[The second Killing-Part candidate
Nonaka Shana]
Shana.
[She became nervous as it's her turn.]
Just sing it the way you want.
♫ I will ♫
♫ I will not ♫
I can't do it.
[Shana gave up on the Killing-Part
in the end.]
This isn't going to work.
[Will she be able to get her confidence
back on stage?]
[The 9-member groups will compete
against each other as dancers.]
Nine.
I'm worried.
About what?
["Salute"]
That team is really strong.
[Team "Salute" has Yoon Ji A and Cai Bing
who showed charisma in Connect Mission.]
Their eyes...
They are scary.
They're all charismatic girls.
"Salute" is going to look cool.
But as for us,
we're all cute and cheerful
like ice cream.
I think we'd look better visually.
That's why we have to go for the opposite.
[Kim Da Yeon suggested
going for a contrasting concept.]
They can't do something cute.
-We can look cool or cute.
-Yes, we can do both.
-I'm cool.
-What?
What?
[The age of 16
when they want to look cool]
Sure. Be cool.
[I love my team.]
I'm 100 percent happy about our team.
Shall we pick the leader?
[It's time to pick a leader of the team.]
-Yes.
Does anyone want to do it?
[Everyone's eyes are on someone.]
[Kim Da Yeon
raises her hand to become a candidate.]
Yes.
Okay.
I've been dancing for a long time.
I've been a leader many times before.
I'm confident, so I raised my hand.
Anyone else?
[You're so cool.]
How cool.
Da Yeon has experience making dance moves.
She's a good dancer too.
That's why we can rely on her.
Anyone else?
[The second leader candidate]
-The leader?
-Yes.
[The second leader candidate Chen Hsin Wei
surprised everyone.]
Do you want to try it?
She had an eccentric impression.
[Staring]
[Near-sighted]
I'm nearsighted.
[Cute dorky girl Chen Hsin Wei]
Let's say goodbye.
Honestly, I was surprised.
Raise your hand for Wei.
[Chen Hsin Wei received 2 votes.]
[Kim Da Yeon]
Who wants to vote for Da Yeon?
[received 5 votes.]
-Da Yeon.
-Da Yeon should be the leader.
[Kim Da Yeon became the leader
of"Ice Cream" Team by a majority vote.]
Thank you.
I think the better leader
should lead us.
Leader.
[I want to accommodate
everyone's opinions.]
I want to lead them
in terms of performance.
-Leader.
["Ice Cream" Team chose their leader
in a friendly atmosphere.]
-Leader.
-Okay.
-Good luck.
Who wants to be the leader?
I want to be the leader.
Okay.
[I want to be a leader as well.]
-Then...
-I used to be a backup dancer.
In the past.
Me too.
I want to plan out a bigger picture
and focus on the details.
I can divide up the parts well.
I have experience making choreographies
for singers and idols.
[Impressed]
I can be very fast
at organizing the positions.
I can do a good job.
[I think Bing really wanted to do it.]
[I have experience with choreographies.]
I think Bing would speed up the process,
so I want her to do it.
[Do Ah voted for Cai Bing
as she trusts her experience.]
[Many members vote for Cai Bing
with a lot of experience.]
Me too.
I agree since she has experience.
Thank you.
I'll now be able to show my leadership.
[I'll lead my members well
to help our team win.]
[It's time to decide who is going
to do the Killing-Part.]
Who wants to be the main dancer?
The one who can deliver this song well
should be in charge of the killing-part.
[That's why I decided to go for it.]
[Killing-Part candidate 1, Cai Bing]
[Killing-Part candidate 2, Yoon Ji A]
-She's good.
-It's expected.
I'm good at such dance moves.
This is hard.
If we want to look cool,
Ji A should do it.
If we want it to be sexy, Bing should.
I don't know.
[It was hard to choose.]
I like her sexy charm,
but having Ji A in the middle
allows us to go for a strong concept.
I think I suit this song really well.
Shall we vote?
[Killing-Part]
I think Ji A suits
the main dancer.
-Cai Bing.
I think Bing would be better.
-Okay.
-Then, Bing.
[Cai Bing became the leader
and got to sing the Killing-Part as well.]
-Congratulations.
[I think I won the battle
because my performance was better.]
[In my opinion, the ace is someone
who can deliver the mood the best.]
That's me.
[Leader: Kim Da Yeon,
Killing-Part: Kim Da Yeon]
-Kim Da Yeon.
I'll make sure all of you stand out.
-Thank you.
We'll do our best.
-We'll do our best.
Should we listen to the song?
-Is this it?
-Remix.
It's faster than I thought.
["Ice Cream" Team listens to the music
to come up with choreography.]
What? Are we already here?
I never tried making dance moves.
I've never made up moves before,
so I'm honestly worried.
If one person is looking pretty,
[Kim Da Yeon suggests so many ideas
on the spot.]
other people can surround her
and wave their hands.
Everyone else can stand in a line.
[She's full of ideas.]
One person can walk like this.
-Walk?
-Sounds good.
[With Da Yeon's lead, the choreography
is quickly getting close to completion.]
-Is it okay?
-Yes.
[Thumbs up for the leader]
I think Da Yeon already has it
in her head.
She was so cool. I want to learn from her.
[Automatic applause]
I couldn't help but do this.
It was expected of her.
I have some moves in my head for this.
That's amazing.
The other teams worked on moves together,
[but Da Yeon led us all in our team.]
I feel so bad.
-I'll do my best.
-Oh, yes.
Does your team have a special strength?
Looks, charms,
Da Yeon's talent.
We're all just following Da Yeon.
[The night of Planet Camp
before the second mission]
[Good job.]
Even if you make a mistake on stage,
don't do this and just move on.
Okay.
"Ice Cream" Team, let's do well.
-We have to win.
-I think we'll do well.
[K-Group]
I'm in ninth place. I'm in danger.
Everyone, stop talking. I'm in 23rd place.
[C-Group]
I'm leaving.
Let's work even harder tomorrow.
We can do it. I mean it.
The youngest and the oldest.
Good luck.
Combination Mission starts now.
[Combination Mission finally begins.]
[Diverse performances
as well as various charms of the girls]
♫ Better than that ♫
♫ Na na na na ♫
[The story of the girls' challenge
that touched everyone!]
♫ When everyone's asleep ♫
I want you to continue to be a rapper.
[The Mid-checkup result of the 2nd global
voting will be revealed shortly!]
[The day of Combination Mission]
[This was filmed in compliance
with the COVID-19 prevention guidelines.]
[The girls transform
before taking the stage.]
[A spoon of beauty]
-It's pretty.
-I know.
Smudge it.
[Ready to step on the stage]
[The second performance will decide
who gets the Benefit.]
[The Masters look as tense as the girls.]
Gosh.
-Let's do a good job.
-Let's do that.
-I look forward to working with you.
-Same here.
[Won Jae visited
as the special Rap Master.]
-She's so pretty.
-My gosh!
[Is that really him?]
I'm suddenly nervous.
-He's so cool!
-Totally.
I look forward to working with you.
-Your voice...
-You have such a nice voice.
Thank you.
[And...]
[the Planet Master with a sweet voice]
The man of autumn!
[Changing her mind]
How cool.
Where the girls' great stories start.
Girls Planet 999.
Today, we're finally
starting with the second mission,
Combination Mission.
[Combination Mission]
For this mission,
their first cells have gotten disbanded,
and the girls have been
divided into new teams.
In order to show off their strengths,
[they have chosen a position
that they feel most confident about,]
[among vocal, dance, and rap positions.]
[Thus, they will be
showing off their skills]
[on song-arranging, choreography-making,
rap-writing, and stage-producing.]
Today's performances are
to take place specially with a live band.
[Planet Band]
That's the way to go. We need live music.
[They're lit.]
[The best]
The winning teams will earn a benefit
of 270,000 points.
-They get 270,000 points.
-They need to win.
[I really want the benefit this time.]
[I need to get it this time for sure.]
There are 6 teams of 3 members,
[3 teams of 6 members,]
[and 2 teams of 9 members.]
[A total of 11 teams will perform.]
Since they must show their strengths
during this mission,
I'll look forward to seeing
their originality in their performances.
They're performing in new teams this time.
[So I'll focus on]
how they express their strengths
and how they pull off their performance.
For today's Combination Mission,
[we have invited a special master.]
It's Rap Master Woo Won Jae.
[Cheering]
Woo Won Jae.
[With his unique character,]
[the skilled rapper, Woo Won Jae,
draws people in.]
-Let's do a good job.
-Yeah.
[Happiness index at 999 percent]
I'm so happy to be here today.
Since I'm a Rap Master,
I'll do my best to evaluate everyone.
What a sexy voice.
Girls Planet 999's second mission.
[The second mission, Combination Mission]
Combination Mission begins now.
[It begins now!]
[Girls Planet 999]
[Episode 6. Combination.
Confidence Is My Style.]
[Which team will perform first
for the Combination Mission?]
The first ones to perform are
the group of three-member teams.
[The 3-person group]
[Expectations rise.]
Gosh.
[Which member will perform first?]
It won't be easy.
I'm not sure how to introduce this song
with the original singer here
in front of me.
[The original performer]
This song received a lot of love
with its sensual lyrics and beats
[It topped all the charts.]
and aced all music charts.
[Cheering]
[Yes, it's my song.]
"We Are" by Woo Won Jae.
["We Are" Team]
["We Are" by Woo Won Jae]
How do you feel
to have girls sing this song?
I don't know.
-I rather...
-Yes, nice walking.
-What on earth?
-My.
[Swaggering in]
[A hip entrance
with the beat flowing in her body]
["We Are" Team is definitely
absorbed in it.]
Yes, nice walking.
[The Master genuinely laughs.]
-What on earth?
-Yes.
That was totally...
Wen Zhe is so funny.
I was surprised.
Woo Wen Zhe.
-"Woo" Wen Zhe?
-I gave her a nickname.
Please introduce yourselves.
When I say "we," you say "are."
-We.
-Are.
-Hello.
-We're Nocturnal Sentiments.
Goodnight.
Nice.
[Confidence level at 999 percent]
-As expected.
-Nice.
They're very different
from the mid-checkup.
-Right.
-I'm surprised in a good way.
How did you gain
so much confidence, girls?
First off, we practiced really hard.
And we put our story
into this performance.
That gave us more confidence.
Good.
Please get ready for the performance.
-Go for it.
-You can do it.
[Good luck, "We Are" Team!]
[Will they be as confident on the stage?]
-How surprising.
-They're so different.
-Very different.
-I know.
[How was the Mid-checkup
of "We Are" Team?]
[Combination Mission Mid-checkup]
In order to coach you how to rap,
[Is it...]
we invited a special guest today.
[Excited looks]
A rapper from "Show Me the Money."
It's Woo Won Jae.
[Extremely thrilled]
No way!
-Don't do this.
-It's okay.
[Stop lying.]
[The special Rap Master,
Woo Won Jae, enters.]
[Screaming]
Nice to meet you.
[While everyone's exhilarated,]
It's okay.
[they lose their minds at the entrance
of the originator.]
[I couldn't believe it.]
[I was excited that he came,
but I became so nervous.]
I forgot all the lyrics I memorized.
[It was crazy.]
As such an outstanding artist came,
I got even more nervous.
[Mid-checkup in front of the originator]
My heart is racing so much.
["We Are" Team looks even tenser.]
Oh, dear. Are you nervous?
I would.
I'm nervous too.
[And...]
[the most nervous ones...]
[are us.]
You seem really nervous,
-but it's your first time doing it.
-Right.
[Making rap lyrics]
So relax.
[I became so nervous]
that my head went blank.
[I was truly worried.]
["We Are" Team begins with tension.]
♫ In this repeated routine ♫
[Wen Zhe starts rapping
with a stiff look.]
♫ My day begins ♫
-♫ I'm practicing ♫
-♫ We are ♫
[They meet eyes as they practiced]
[and find their confidence.]
-♫ Don't you know that, we are ♫
-♫ We are ♫
-♫ Yeah ♫
[I had to write lyrics in Korean,]
[but I was so lost.]
Manami, you want to try?
[Nagai Manami can't seem to muster her
courage to show them.]
I wonder if I'm dragging them down.
-♫ Don't you know that, we are ♫
-♫ We are ♫
[Nagai Manami shows her rapping skill.]
♫ This moment, when I shine ♫
♫ Don't think of me the same way ♫
♫ The time for those
who made me dream on ♫
♫ Dust never settled on
the practice room ♫
♫ Since the age of six,
Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
[How does the originator evaluate
"We Are" Team's Mid-checkup?]
Rather than the beginning,
I liked how
you saw each other and smiled
as you continued.
-♫ We are ♫
["We Are" Team found composure
by meeting eyes.]
-♫ We are ♫
[The part put a smile on his face.]
When you looked determined
to do a good job,
you looked too stiff and troubled.
But when you smiled and saw each other,
it got a lot better.
-Thank you.
And Manami...
I want you to have more confidence.
I've seen you perform so far,
so I know you have a good sense of rhythm.
And you're good at rapping.
You're good,
but the lack of confidence is
stopping you.
So have more confidence.
[I didn't write the lyrics myself.]
[Bo Ra helped me out a lot.]
Should we meet in a rap team?
-You have to write lyrics though.
-Right.
[Rap-making]
-I can help you out.
-Okay.
[Bo Ra helps Manami compose
what she wants to say.]
Like, "When I'm under the stage light."
[Bo Ra, you're the best!]
♫ Since the age of six,
Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
[They also repeated Manami's part
to practice.]
♫ Since the age of six,
Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
[Exclaiming]
You're a genius.
[A special compliment]
A genius.
She helped me out
even before she worked on hers.
[I was really grateful.
She's someone I can rely on.]
-You did a great job earlier.
-Good job.
[The Mid-checkup performance]
Be energetic
-when you do it.
-Okay.
Manami. Don't you know?
[Manami]
[Exchanging...]
-Don't you know?
-That's how you do it.
[cheers]
-In 2, 3.
-Don't you know, we are!
[Since I'm the youngest one,
the members adore me.]
[And I'm so grateful]
[that they've taught me stuff in detail.]
[After the Mid-checkup stage...]
You like Bo Ra?
-Do you like Bo Ra?
-I do.
Do you like Wen Zhe?
-Okay.
I like both of you so much.
-Both of you.
[I don't want to leave any regret.]
♫ We are ♫
[While having fun...
I want to do the performance]
♫ Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
[that the masters]
[would approve.]
[You'll see the different side of me
from what I showed earlier.]
I really hope they do well.
[Good night. Go to bed first.
I'm still practicing.]
♫ It's 3 a.m.
I'm practicing all alone ♫
♫ The same day repeats itself
I don't know what day it is ♫
♫ I always pull an all nighter ♫
♫ The sun sets, the sky turns dark ♫
♫ Do people think I'm weird? ♫
♫ Hey! I'm just extraordinary ♫
♫ I've been walking
this road for eight years ♫
♫ The one word
that'll put my family to ease ♫
♫ I gave up being normal,
I feel like being jet lagged ♫
♫ I'm fine ♫
♫ My story is just about to start ♫
♫ Will you listen to it? ♫
♫ I keep dreaming, I keep walking ♫
♫ My eyes are open wide ♫
♫ Ya ya ya ♫
♫ We're living in a different time zone ♫
♫ My day and night switched ♫
♫ Have a good night,
go ahead and sleep I'm still practicing ♫
♫ We are, we are, who we are ♫
♫ Ah ♫
♫ Hey, don't you know who we are, yeah ♫
♫ I'm shining right now ♫
♫ Don't think my performance
is the same as everyone else's ♫
♫ Is the same as everyone else's ♫
♫ Don't think ♫
♫ When people were sleeping and dreaming ♫
♫ I was thinking of
my dream and practicing ♫
♫ I have to do it, this time difference ♫
Manami is good.
♫ My time on stage
made me dream ♫
♫ Dust never settled on
the practice room ♫
♫ Since I was six years old
until now ♫
♫ Manami on the beat, yeah ♫
♫ Morning is dark, and night is bright ♫
♫ I'm still at yesterday
and today becomes tomorrow♫
♫ My day ends late at night♫
♫ My dreams fill me up ♫
♫ The end becomes a beginning ♫
♫ My dream becomes my time difference ♫
♫ At the end of this night
you will remember me ♫
♫ My voice will be
etched into your heart ♫
♫ Ya ya ya ♫
♫ We're living in a different time zone ♫
♫ My day and night switched ♫
♫ Have a good night,
go ahead and sleep I'm still practicing ♫
♫ We are, we are, who we are ♫
♫ Ah ♫
♫ Hey, don't you know who we are ♫
♫ We are much comfortable
when everyone's asleep ♫
♫ Don't you know who we are, yeah ♫
♫ I like pulling all nighters
to become the me I want ♫
♫ Don't you know who we are ♫
♫ I like practicing at night
which everyone hates ♫
♫ Don't you know who we are ♫
♫ We are ♫
♫ Don't you know who we are, yeah ♫
They're so good!
Oh, you're Woo Wen Zhe indeed!
Good night.
[Nagai Manami of J-Group]
[Kim Bo Ra of K-Group]
[Wen Zhe of C-Group]
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
Thank goodness.
-Thank goodness.
Manami...
She's good, right?
-She's cute and cool at the same time.
-Right?
[I totally agree with that.]
You don't have to put those away.
["We Are" Team is cleaning the lyrics
paper that they threw on stage.]
You don't have to put those away.
-Leave them.
-It's okay.
[Unexpected behind the scenes]
Tidying up their own stuff.
I couldn't take my eyes off until the end.
It's "We Are" Team.
Master Won Jae, this is your song.
How did you like it?
[What review will the original singer
give to "We Are" Team?]
-Manami.
-Yes.
Well...
I want you to continue to be a rapper.
Yeah!
[Oh, gosh!]
[Yes!]
[Very touched]
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I mean it.
If this was your first rap writing,
and improved this fast, you can do it.
I really want you to keep rapping.
What a compliment.
Same goes for all of you.
You all did a great job.
Good work!
"We Are" Team.
Nocturnal Sentimental Team, good work!
-You may leave the stage.
-Thank you.
-Good job!
-Well done.
Great work.
-It must've been really hard.
-It must've been.
Good job!
Good work.
["We Are" Team
got recognition from the original singer.]
You guys did so well.
Great work.
[I feel really happy.]
I'm so relieved now.
[It was so much fun.]
That was fun.
-It was really fun.
-Really.
I couldn't have enjoyed the stage
if it were not for my teammates.
[So I'm thankful.]
I'd love to
perform with them again.
Let's continue with Combination Mission.
[Combination Mission continues.]
The next group who will be performing
is a group of nine.
They're both great.
The first performance
of the group of nine.
["Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK
with Selena Gomez]
"Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK.
Don't get nervous.
Just do as we practiced.
You can do it.
[Ikema Ruan who survived by Planet
Pass looks very nervous.]
-Ruan.
-Ruan!
You can do it, you're good.
[Kim Da Yeon cheers Ikema Ruan
as the leader.]
Just do it.
[Connection Mission Mid-checkup]
["Ice Cream" Team, come forward.]
[-Yes.
-Yes.]
Da Yeon, you're the leader
and doing the killing-part.
Yes.
It's the same with team "Salute".
This team, too.
The leader and the killing-part.
-It's me.
-The same person.
[Cai Bing of "Salute" Team is
both leader and Killing-Part.]
Doesn't that make you feel nervous?
I think...
that may be the case,
but I want her to feel
nervous because of me as well.
I think...
it'd be a chance for both of us to grow.
[What will be the result of these girls
with the same position?]
-Ikema Ruan.
-Yes?
-You've survived with a Planet Pass.
-Yes.
Ikema Ruan from J-Group!
[Ikema Ruan survived by Planet Pass.]
Ikema Ruan!
After watching her performance,
I thought she was star material.
She was always practicing in the corner.
-How do you feel?
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Since you survived with the Planet Pass,
I think you should show us something.
Are you ready?
I'm not very confident now,
but I'll try harder so look forward
to what I'll show you.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-You can do it.
Let's see "Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK.
-Yes.
Let's go.
-Let's do this!
["Ice Cream" Team of nine members
has created a new choreography.]
[Kim Da Yeon of Killing-Part is showing
her solo performance.]
Gosh.
[Wu Tammy leads the next group
choreography.]
[The group choreography continues
with Ikema Ruan's lead.]
-Thank you.
-Wow.
Okay.
You know...
-I could really see each one of you well.
-Yes.
Hsu Nien Tzu, you have great energy
-Thank you.
-for a girl that tall.
Bahiyyih was so cute, too.
When Ririka showed up in the center,
it just felt so good.
Da Yeon gave the other members
chances to shine since she's doing
the killing-part.
-Thank you.
-Right.
[Kim Da Yeon created the choreography
so that all the members can stand out.]
And Ikema Ruan.
You're being passive.
Ruan's part...
[Ikema Ruan's group choreography
is linked with Wu Tammy's part.]
[There's Tammy's part]
[and Ruan's part comes up next.]
[Compared to Tammy's, you lack energy.]
[Ikema Ruan's part of group choreography
looks less powerful.]
You survived through a Planet Pass.
You've got to show something.
-That you deserved it.
-Right.
-Can you do it?
-Yes.
[I kind of saw that coming.]
I thought I was doing well,
but from the day I got the Planet Pass,
I wasn't sure if I truly deserved it.
[I was very insecure about myself,
and I think that just showed to others.]
[I don't feel confident,
and I'm not good enough.]
Since I got the Planet Pass,
I wanted to do my best
not to leave any regrets.
[Highest ranked of
the 9-member group, Kim Da Yeon]
[Lowest ranked of
the 9-member group, Ikema Ruan]
All the same...
[The highest and lowest ranked members
are from "Ice Cream" Team.]
[She wasn't so confident about dancing,]
but having survived with a Planet Pass
made her lose confidence even more.
[Ruan's teammates comfort her.]
It's okay.
-Don't cry.
-It's okay.
We have a lot of time left.
We can do it.
My goal is to bring Ruan up
from the bottom rank.
Ruan, you're doing this.
[Kim Da Yeon explains everything
step by step to Ruan.]
Ruan, you need to practice this.
[Their leader helps her teammates,
so they don't lose their confidence.]
The basics.
One, two.
Come here.
Ruan.
[So that every member can shine,]
This part shouldn't be like this.
[Team "Ice Cream" practices
one step at a time.]
Three, four.
[Ruan.]
[They practice hard day and night
for Ruan.]
[Ruan!]
Boom, boom.
[Ikema Ruan begins growing
thanks to her teammates' help.]
And this, this.
Nice, Ruan.
Good!
If I practice a lot, I'll gain confidence.
[I hope I can enjoy practicing.]
You're lost?
[I have a question.]
Come here.
Ruan... Yes. Jump.
[I felt sorry that we got criticized]
during the mid-checkup.
I hope I can be a motivation to everyone.
I want to win.
-They're cute.
-So cute.
How cute.
-How pretty.
-Let's go.
Is it harder to practice
the more people there are?
It's really hard.
With so many opinions and interests...
[They're incredible.]
I wonder if Da Yeon's hard work
will pay off on the stage.
How exciting.
["Salute" Team
watches their performance nervously.]
I'm nervous myself.
-I know.
-I'm nervous too.
It's driving me crazy.
[The girls recorded the song for
the Dance Position Performance.]
Gosh.
["Ice Cream" by BLACKPINK]
Look at their faces.
♫ Come a little closer
because you're looking thirsty ♫
♫ I'm going to make it better,
sip it like a Slurpee ♫
♫ Snow cone chilly,
get it free like Willy ♫
♫ In the jeans like Billie,
you be popping like a wheelie ♫
♫ Even in the sun,
you know I keep it icy ♫
♫ You could take a lick,
but it's too cold to bite me ♫
♫ To bite me ♫
♫ Frozen, you're the one been chosen ♫
♫ Play the part like Moses,
keep it fresh like roses ♫
♫ Look so good, look so sweet ♫
♫ Looking good enough to eat ♫
♫ Coldest with the kiss,
so he call me ice cream ♫
♫ Catch me in the fridge,
right where the ice be ♫
♫ Look so good, look so sweet ♫
♫ Baby, you deserve a treat ♫
♫ Diamonds on my wrist ♫
-♫ So he call me ice cream ♫
-How cute.
♫ You can double dip
because I know you like me ♫
-♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
-Chilling!
-They've gotten a lot better.
-♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
-Chen Hsin Wei is so much better.
♫ Ice cream, chilling, ice cream ♫
-♫ Chilling like a villain ♫
-Let's go, Da Yeon.
♫ Chilling like a villain ♫
♫ Crazy speed racing in my La Fera ♫
♫ It's so fast that you miss it,
I spend as much as I want ♫
♫ I earn millis, billis, every day ♫
♫ I spend as much as I want,
I earn millis, billis, every day ♫
Kim Da Yeon!
♫ Ice on my wrist ♫
♫ Keep it moving like my lease up ♫
♫ Think you fly, boy, where's your visa?
Mona Lisa kinda Lisa ♫
♫ Needs an ice cream man that treats her ♫
♫ Keep it moving like my lease up ♫
♫ Think you fly, boy, where's your visa?
Mona Lisa kinda Lisa ♫
♫ Ice cream ♫
♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
♫ Look so good, look so sweet ♫
♫ Looking good enough to eat ♫
♫ Mona Lisa kinda Lisa, ice cream ♫
♫ Na na na na na ♫
♫ Ice on my wrist, I like it like this ♫
♫ Get the bag with the cream ♫
-♫ If you know what I mean ♫
-They're so good.
♫ Ice cream ♫
♫ Get the bag with the cream
if you know what I mean ♫
♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
♫ Na na na na na ♫
-♫ Ice on my wrist, I like it like this ♫
-They're so cute.
♫ And I'm nice with the cream
if you know what I mean ♫
♫ Ice cream ♫
[Fujimoto Ayaka]
[Guinn Myah]
[Huening Bahiyyih]
[Wu Tammy]
Okay, I have to stand up.
[Ikema Ruan]
[Kishida Ririka]
Seriously.
[Chen Hsin Wei]
Oh, joy.
[Hsu Nien Tzu]
[Kim Da Yeon]
-They rocked it.
-Love!
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
["Ice Cream" received a lot of cheers.]
Bravo!
-Cheers.
-If then...
Okay, I have to stand up.
[Standing ovation]
Oh, joy.
They rocked it.
Their energy was no joke.
How come they're this good?
What do you think?
I'm just fascinated.
They're good.
They're all talented.
-They got such great energy.
-Yes.
Da Yeon's good at making choreography.
[Exclaiming]
[Tiffany Young can't stop cheering.]
It's crazy.
How did you like the performance?
I don't say this often,
but I wonder
how they could pull it off so perfectly.
I want to know
how you were trained.
I'm stunned. They did an amazing job.
-Thank you.
I'd like to give a big compliment
to Da Yeon.
She had the killing-part,
but she made the choreography
in a way that everyone would stand out.
♫ Looking good enough to eat ♫
[It was a performance where every part
stood out like it was the highlight.]
♫ To bite me ♫
♫ He calls me ice cream ♫
-♫ Ice cream, chilling ♫
-Chilling!
Everyone stood out.
And as a leader,
-she was very considerate.
-Right.
And the teammates followed her opinions.
Her leadership shined in this performance.
She did a wonderful job.
They looked like they already debuted.
They looked like an actual group.
-Thank you.
-I loved it.
And Ruan.
Yes.
Goodness. There, there.
-Please don't cry.
-Gosh.
It's okay, Ruan.
You did well.
Good job, Ruan.
-She must've been under a lot of pressure.
-Right.
She survived with a Planet Pass,
so she probably felt a lot more burdened.
Ruan, you did really well,
so it's all good now. Right?
Yes.
Great job, everyone.
[Team "Ice Cream"
finished their performance.]
-Thank you.
You worked so hard. Good job.
Good job.
Da Yeon! Yes!
-Thank you.
-How can they be this good?
They were more powerful towards the end.
The later parts had
all the powerful dance moves.
Da Yeon made
a narrative arc strategically.
This is needed.
I keep getting goosebumps
to see how they prepared
such a performance only in a short time.
-Plus, it's just so well done.
-I know.
I better score them
after watching the other teams.
Honestly, my choreography was difficult.
-Don't say that.
-But none of you showed it.
-It's all thanks to your dancing skills.
-Good job.
-Right.
-I know.
I love you guys. Good work.
-Good work.
-Good job.
-Ice cream, yes!
Good work.
When we listen to this song,
our shoulders start to groove right away.
It makes us want to dance.
It's "No Excuses" by Meghan Trainor.
Oh, Meghan Trainor.
I love this song.
We're the vocal trainers.
[She's Meghan Trainor.
We're vocal trainers.]
-Hi, guys.
-Hi.
[Hi.]
Look.
-We're Bling Cling Girls.
They're so cute.
Did you have any difficulties
with making the choreography?
[Combination Mission Mid-checkup]
You made the choreography
from start to end, right?
Yes.
[Exclaiming]
[That is how much
they look forward to it.]
What are you doing?
The hand...
Who's doing the killing-part?
Hikaru encouraged me
that I'd pull it off nicely,
so I decided to take the job.
I think Su Yeon is totally suitable
for the killing-part.
Really?
I want to do it,
but my lack of confidence says otherwise.
No, it goes well with you.
-It's got a happy mood.
-Happy.
[They are happy.]
And you can do
things like this.
Then I'll try my best.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[Kim Su Yeon takes the Killing-Part.]
How's your practice coming along?
Yes.
Why do you look so worried?
Well...
[Well...]
-You have a lot of concerns?
-Yes.
["No Excuses" Team's Mid-checkup begins
with worries.]
[Two masters watch them
more composedly than before.]
-It's not fun.
-No.
If this choreography already existed
and this is how you practiced it,
I would...
[You know?]
We all know you're good dancers.
I want you to focus more on acting.
You're smiling,
but I don't know why.
If you decide on acting and characters,
your gestures, eyes,
and dance highlights will change.
You need a vibe like, "I'm the best."
But now, you just danced like,
[It felt like a machine.]
"One, two, three, and four."
Hikaru, you always make this look
when you start dancing.
[Hikaru's unique expression
for "BOOMBAHYAH" and "The Eve".]
It doesn't go well with this song.
[That does not match this song.]
You just did your thing
and gave a strong vibe.
To advance to the next round,
you need to make the audience go,
"Oh, gosh. Yes, Su Yeon!"
You need such reactions from them.
I think they tried to make
their comments sound nice
so they wouldn't hurt our feelings.
But they looked so disappointed.
I was sad.
We were all too powerful.
It's not impressive. This is hard.
We were busy working on the choreography
that we couldn't
focus on our facial expressions.
Our efforts seem meaningless.
[I was disappointed in myself.]
["No Excuses" Team lost confidence
after the Mid-checkup.]
-My gosh.
-Ta-da.
[What is that?]
-Didn't you get it from the Dancing Queen?
-What...
That's right.
Congratulations.
[It is the prize Su Yeon received
for winning the Planet Dancing Queen.]
Thank you.
-My gosh.
-Yes.
[They refer to others' performances
for expressions that match the song.]
We have to work on facial expressions.
-Right.
-Until the end.
-Let's do it.
-We can do it.
[Let's get started. Stand by.]
[Combination Mission Rehearsal]
[They look better than before.]
They're good.
Oh, no.
[Su Yeon makes a mistake
on the difficult move.]
Maybe she's exhausted.
She took the wrong step.
[She finishes the rehearsal
with a mistake.]
You may now leave the stage.
[She bursts into tears due to worries.]
What do we do?
[I fell on the backflip]
that I couldn't do my part at all.
[We practiced so hard.]
[Until at dawn on the last day.]
[Back in the room]
I'm not safe
in the rankings either.
[So I'm more desperate to do well.]
I can't wait to watch Su Yeon perform.
-She's good.
-Right.
Why does she look nervous though?
-She seems all tensed up.
-Right.
I hope she doesn't make any mistakes.
I'm thrilled.
-Please come out!
-Come out.
[Like the MC]
["No Excuses"]
[The girls recorded the song for
the Dance Position Performance.]
[What are you doing?]
"What are you doing?"
[Where are you?]
"Where are you?"
[Answer your phone.]
-"Answer my call."
[Let's break up.]
♫ What you sipping on
that got you talking crazy?
♫ ♫ Looking at me sideways,
always coming at me ♫
♫ Why are you acting hard
when you are just a baby? ♫
♫ Boy, I keep it real with you,
but you trying to play me ♫
♫ Have you lost your mind? ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ Someone else, you must have
confused me, confused me with ♫
♫ Someone else, you must have ♫
-They're good.
-♫ Confused me, confused me with ♫
♫ Someone else, there ain't
no excuses, excuses, babe ♫
♫ Someone else, your mama
raised you better than that ♫
[Let's go.]
Yes!
♫ Because your mama
raised you better than that ♫
♫ Have you lost your mind? ♫
♫ Open up your eyes ♫
♫ Someone else, you must have
confused me, confused me with ♫
♫ Someone else, there ain't
no excuses, excuses, babe ♫
♫ Someone else, your mama
raised you better than that ♫
♫ How did she raise you? ♫
♫ Someone else, you must have
confused me, confused me with ♫
[She succeeds where she messed up
on the rehearsal.]
♫ Confused me, confused me with ♫
♫ Because your mama
raised you better than that ♫
♫ Better than that ♫
♫ Confused me, confused me with ♫
♫ Because your mama
raised you better than that ♫
[Are you asleep?]
[Ezaki Hikaru]
[Yang Zi Ge]
[Kim Su Yeon]
Yes!
Well done.
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
[That was cool.]
"Are you asleep?"
-They're so cute.
-They did a good job.
["No Excuses" Team finished
the performance without a mistake.]
They're good.
Love.
[She loves it.]
They're the pride of this show.
All of them were so good.
They've changed everything
that you pointed out.
Yes!
During the mid-checkup,
it was a little boring
that I told them to work on it.
But now, I had so much fun watching
because there was no time to be bored.
The most important thing
about a dance clip
is that it has to make you want
-to dance along to it.
-Exactly. I want to watch this
-again.
-I'd keep watching the video of this
and dance along to it.
If I didn't watch this performance
right here,
but on TV or online,
I'd consider them as professionals
who already debuted.
[Kim Su Yeon cries
after getting compliments.]
Why are you tearing up?
Su Yeon.
-You did the best job.
-I guess
-she was very nervous.
-It must've been hard for her.
Don't cry, not now.
-It's not the time to shed tears.
-Now isn't the time.
All my struggles and worries
[might work as a trigger
for me to improve more.]
Su Yeon must've been under pressure
to pull off the killing-part.
[I'm truly glad]
[-she aced it.]
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Next up is the group of six-member teams.
[Who is performing next?]
[6-member group]
I'm sure a lot of people become
emotional and nostalgic
to think about this song.
It's "Missing You" by BTOB.
["Missing You" Team by BTOB]
I wonder how the performance will be.
Please come up to the stage.
I'm even more nervous.
["Missing You" Team came on stage
with the scent of autumn.]
How pretty.
-They have this autumn vibe.
-They're girls of autumn.
-Hello.
-Like a palette.
-With our colorful voices.
-We deliver messages.
In 2, 3.
-We're
-Drawing Sounds.
Drawing Sounds.
I like the name.
[How did they prepare?]
Kawaguchi Yurina.
Yes.
You ranked one
[She became Top 9 number 1
as chosen by Planet Guardians.]
[at the survival announcement.]
However, you ranked the lowest
in the mid-checkup.
[Combination Mission Mid-checkup]
Planet Top 9...
[6-member group]
[Top 8, Top 4, Top 2, Top 6]
[Top 9]
Rank one.
[Honorable Top 1]
[Exclaiming]
Rank one.
Number one Yurina.
[Kawaguchi One-rina.]
-Here we go.
-Yes.
[6-member group]
[Nervous]
[The music starts playing
while everyone is nervous.]
♫ My life ♫
[It begins
with Leung Cheuk Ying's narration.]
♫ Is imcomplete♫
♫ I'm spending another day as usual ♫
♫ I still live like this ♫
[Zhou Xin Yu can't rap although she's
looking at the lyrics.]
♫ I guess I'm still there ♫
♫ My heart hasn't changed
I still want you ♫
[Glancing]
[She couldn't rap
a single bar properly in the end.]
♫ I can't forget you ♫
-♫ Come back to me ♫
-♫ Even if it is another same ending ♫
[Kubo Reina in charge of the Killing-Part
sings high notes amazingly!]
[There you go!]
♫ I spend a day trying to forget you ♫
[The song is reaching the end.]
♫ A day is gone ♫
♫ I spend a year trying to erase you ♫
[The masters look less and less happy.]
♫ To erase you ♫
♫ This is ♫
♫ This is how I live ♫
[Han Byul's serious look level 1.]
♫ I miss you ♫
["Missing You" Team made him
his serious look level 2.]
♫ I miss you ♫
[The mood became dark in an instant.]
-Thank you.
This is bad.
It's embarrassing to even ask,
but what did you think, Rap Master?
I have no comment
for Zhou Xin Yu
because I couldn't hear your rap.
Half the song is rap.
How can you compete with a song
that's missing its half?
This is terrible.
I'm really curious.
-Yurina.
-Yes?
Yurina.
Yes.
Why did you pick this song?
Rank one is
supposed to do better than this.
The others got it wrong because of you.
♫ This is how I live ♫
[Kawaguchi Yurina's mistake
caused others to be out of tune later.]
♫ I miss you ♫
You need to practice a lot.
You need to know.
You have nowhere to go up now.
[She's already Top 1.]
It's only a downfall from now.
[Kawaguchi Yurina tears up in the end.]
So what's it gonna be?
You just have to make it work.
Or else, you're going home.
[I hated myself for making a mistake]
[in such an important moment.]
[I couldn't hold back tears.]
It's okay.
[Something has to be done.]
[I should work harder.]
The way you're singing now is...
[Master Han Byul tells her how to practice
after the Mid-checkup.]
Like this.
[He teaches how to breathe with his
demonstration for better understanding.]
You should sing like this, instead.
You need more breath
and the chest voice.
The pitch is not that high.
It's in your range.
Good luck.
♫ I just ♫
[Yurina practices step by step,
following Han Byul's instructions.]
♫ I spend ♫
♫ This is how I live ♫
[Upset]
Why can't I do it?
It's okay. You're always better on stage.
You did a great job today.
Good job.
Don't cry, okay?
You're working harder than anyone.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[She's encouraged by the warm words
from her teammate Lee Hye Won.]
[Zhou Xin Yu in charge of rap
must've had a long day as well.]
Are you okay?
You're doing really well.
I want you to know that.
If we practice together,
I'm sure we can do it
without any mistakes.
I want to do well
for our team.
[I tried rapping for the first time]
[in this mission,]
[and I wasn't confident.]
[But I won't give up. I'll practice hard.]
[I will show]
[a good performance.]
[and try hard to survive.]
[What would their performance be like?]
["Missing You"]
♫ My life is incomplete ♫
♫ It's missing you ♫
[Cheering]
That was amazing.
It's like a movie.
["Missing You"]
♫ I'm spending another day as usual ♫
♫ It doesn't feel awkward
to be alone at all ♫
♫ I thought I wouldn't be able to do it
without you ♫
♫ But I'm moving on ♫
♫ But something feels missing ♫
♫ I guess I'm still there ♫
♫ Even in the life that repeats ♫
♫ I'm chased by time ♫
♫ I ended up becoming a grown-up ♫
♫ I got locked up in reality ♫
♫ I've never talked
about giving up before ♫
♫ But somehow I stopped walking ♫
♫ You're still in my heart ♫
♫ I spend a day missing you ♫
♫ I spend a year missing you ♫
-♫ This is how I live ♫
-♫ I miss you ♫
♫ I tried to draw you again ♫
♫ I wonder where you are
oh, you're right in front of me ♫
♫ Are you going to catch her coward
step one don't stop ♫
♫ I will make you real
I don't regret it ♫
♫ I can't forget you ♫
♫ Come back to me ♫
♫ Even if it is another same ending ♫
♫ I spend a day missing you ♫
♫ I spend a year missing you ♫
♫ This is how I live ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ I spend a day trying to forget you ♫
♫ I spend a year trying to erase you ♫
♫ This is how I live ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
I love Jeong Min's voice.
[Girls watching give them a big hand.]
Amazing.
[The Masters also cheer for them.]
That was great.
Is it the same team that cried?
[Lee Hye Won]
[Ahn Jeong Min]
[Zhou Xin Yu]
[Leung Cheuk Ying]
[Kawaguchi Yurina]
[Kubo Reina]
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
-I'm really touched.
-Right?
-I was surprised.
-Right.
-I got goosebumps.
-I know.
-Right?
-They pulled it off so well.
[Touched]
How did you like the performance?
I got to see a different side of Hye Won.
When people sing with a trembling voice,
some are hard to stand
while some make you want to hear it more.
Her case was the latter.
I really loved it.
Zhou Xin Yu.
During the mid-checkup, I was worried
[if she could pull it off.]
But she rapped here
like a different person.
Yurina.
She mostly stared at the floor
when she sang
during the mid-checkup.
But she didn't seem nervous today.
It was good to see
that she was enjoying it at ease.
That's exactly what I wanted to see.
When she's in charge of something,
she carries it out more than 100 percent.
That's probably why the Planet Guardians
chose her to be number one.
Her parts were quite tricky.
[Especially, when she sang in harmony,
the notes were completely in tune.]
Thanks to her support,
Reina was able to show off
her explosive singing voice.
This is so touching.
Great job today. I loved it.
-Thank you.
[They step off the stage with light steps
due to the Master's praises.]
Great job.
Well done.
We got compliments.
[The "Missing You" Team members
embrace each other for the hard work.]
Thank goodness.
You're the best, Yurina.
You're the best.
[This mission gave me]
[the biggest sense of achievement.]
[I realized once again
just how joyful it is]
to get complimented.
It made me shed tears of joy.
It's really not easy to improve this fast
for someone
-Right.
-who speaks a different language.
Right.
That's really surprising for me.
Just imagine that
-we have to prepare a performance
-Right.
with that country's language in a week.
-That's impossible.
-Yes, these guys are incredible.
-Gosh, I got goosebumps.
-Right?
-They're unbelievable.
-I wouldn't
be able to do it.
[The Masters are proud of them
for doing their best.]
Up next.
The singer of this song has
a clear, expressive,
innocent, and explosive voice.
She's a legendary singer.
[Looking forward to it]
It must be "Fate."
This song is a soundtrack of the movie,
"The King and the Clown."
"Fate" by Lee Sun Hee.
It's such a difficult song.
I love this song.
["Fate" Team steps onto the stage
in white dresses.]
[Sighing]
I've got the biggest concern
for this team.
But they're all good.
They are.
-Four of them are in Top 9.
-I know.
They're all good.
Four of you are wearing
[During the Mid-checkup
of the Connect Mission]
-There are four.
-a purple vest.
-Who's the leader?
-Me.
[Shen Xiao Ting became
the leader of the team.]
Shen Xiao Ting.
Who's doing the killing-part?
-Ye Seo.
[Kang Ye Seo, the youngest, Killing-Part]
Oh, it's Ye Seo. I'm getting so curious.
Okay. Get ready.
[What kind of choreography will they
have come up with?]
-Okay.
["Fate" Team presents the dance
among the expectations.]
[The dances don't match
due to the different hand gestures.]
[They make continuous mistakes
as they have not mastered it yet.]
No matter how hard
you practice this choreography,
you can't perform this on stage.
Your "Fate" performance is all about this.
[There were only repetitive hand gestures,
and no memorable moves.]
From start to finish.
Nothing caught my eyes.
Even Ye Seo and her killing-part.
I couldn't even tell
it was the killing-part.
I felt at a loss.
[I was really worried and nervous.]
-Is Ye Seo crying?
-She's crying?
-Why?
-Oh, no.
-She's crying.
["Fate" Team took to the stage
with worries.]
[Will they have prepared a performance
to satisfy everyone?]
["Fate" originally by Lee Sun Hee]
[The current standing for the voting
will be revealed from now on.]
[Girls Planet 999, 2nd Global Voting,
Current Status]
[K-Group's Current Voting]
[Kim Da Yeon]
[C-Group's Current Voting]
[Chen Hsin Wei]
[J-Group's Current Voting]
[Kamimoto Kotone]
[Dear Planet Guardians,]
[Girls Planet 999, 2nd Global Voting]
[Girls Planet 999's second global voting
will end in a week.]
[You can vote at UNIVERSE app, the
official platform of Girls Planet 999.]
[As Planet Guardians, you can vote]
[once a day on the official app
to protect their dreams.]
[In this second global voting,
you'll vote for individuals, not cells.]
[The second global voting is individual.]
[A total of 30 contestants,]
[the bottom ten from each group
will be eliminated.]
[First, access the voting screen]
[Vote]
[and pick nine contestants
that you want to support,]
[three from each group.]
[Press the final submission button]
[Confirm Votes]
[Vote Complete]
[to complete your vote.]
[The voting result will reflect
50 percent from Korean votes]
[Korea 50 percent]
[and the other 50 percent
from global votes outside of Korea.]
[Global 50 percent]
[The number of votes
will be applied as points.]
[Planet Guardians!]
[Whose dreams will you protect?]
[The second global voting
of Girls Planet 999]
[will close at 10 a.m. on September 18.]
[We'll now reveal the new songs
for Creation Mission,]
[the third mission of Girls Planet 999.]
♫ You're my ♫
♫ You leave like a snake ♫
["Snake" is a moombahton song
describing a mysterious]
♫ You pass by the moment
we run into each other ♫
[and powerful snake whose plan is
to steal everyone's hearts.]
♫ You leave like a snake ♫
♫ Here in your heart ♫
♫ Why does it feel like it ended
when it hasn't even started? ♫
["Shoot!" is a song from the genres
of synth-wave and synth-pop]
♫ This could be the start ♫
[which is a cheery song about girls
who remind us of Murphy's law.]
♫ Of being honest ♫
♫ Maybe or maybe not,
you're cool in the midst of this ♫
♫ What's good? ♫
♫ Maybe or maybe not,
why does it have to be today? ♫
♫ What's good? ♫
♫ You plus me equals love ♫
["U+Me=Love" is an uptempo electronic
dance song with a rhythmical melody]
♫ It's you, touch me, love me ♫
[about the formula of you and I
making big love.]
♫ You and I shine brighter than love ♫
♫ Our love is unstoppable ♫
♫ You plus me equals love ♫
♫ Don't hesitate, don't stop ♫
♫ Be excited, shout out loud ♫
["Utopia" is a dance-pop song
with an energetic melody]
♫ At where I have been waiting
for so long ♫
[portraying the hopeful message from the
girls who try to fulfill their dreams.]
♫ I've been waiting ♫
♫ Let's fly high ♫
♫ It's right before my eyes ♫
♫ My utopia ♫
[Dear Planet Guardians,]
[match the girls that would suit
the newly revealed songs yourself.]
[On the official app,]
[Using the Girls Planet 999 official
platform application,]
[pick the girls
who would match each song the best]
[choose the most suitable person
for each song of four songs.]
[and press the final submission button.]
[Then click final vote submission]
[to participate in the new song matching.]
[The song matching vote to decide]
[From September 10 at 10:30 p.m.]
[to September 11 at 10:30 p.m.]
[who will perform which song
will end in 24 hours.]
[You can participate once
within the period.]
[Whose dream will you protect?]
[The new song matching vote is open.]
[The competition]
[for benefits continues.]
♫ Let's go to my house ♫
It's impressive.
♫ I'm the mafia ♫
[A fierce performance to get
270,000 points benefit.]
♫ I'm the mafia ♫
[It's awesome.]
♫ Can you hear me ♫
[Explosive singing skills and
emotional performances]
♫ Trying to lock ♫
[And]
[What's that?]
[I'm so touched that I'm thankful.]
What kind of life did they have?
[I have the results
for Combination Mission.]
[Who will win the first in each
group of 3, 6, 9 groups?]
The first place goes to
this team.
[I'd never imagined it.]
[I'll make it to Top 9.]