[English subtitles are available]
Gu Yiye!
Yiye!
Everything's fine?
Great.
What are you doing?
I'm going to the division commander's.
He's not around.
Then I'll wait for him.
There's no point in doing this.
Then what should I do?
Alright,
we all saw your act just now.
The division commander won't like it.
Act?
I wasn't acting!
I joined the army with great ambition,
and I even gave up gaokao.
For all these years,
I've been preparing
to become a soldier.
I trained infantry technique by myself,
and did physical training.
I learnt military history on my own,
and taught myself tactical knowledge.
I am more suited to the army than anyone else!
How could you say I'm not the one?
How could you make me retire?
And what?
And,
I know I should not be
saying these now,
but they are stuck in my throat.
Even it’s just acting,
please let me see the division commander
and finish my lines.
It's already time for you to bow and step down.
Lines?
They used to call me a book worm,
but I say you are the book nerd!
Have your father told you
the difference between military institutes and common colleges?
At the artillery reconnaissance class,
he once said
that we investigate functions for the death,
and use cannons
to write them down.
This is the difference
between military institutes and common colleges.
Common colleges teach knowledge,
but military institutes
put what you’ve learnt into practice
by blood and fire.
You,
you might have more knowlegde than others,
but in the class filled with blood and flames,
destined for iron and volition,
you don't have advantages
to anyone else.
To you,
this is a test,
a test of life.
Soldiers are special individuals.
Maybe one can be here
out of their love towards military,
but they definitely can't
stand all the way through with their initial enthusiasm.
Of course loving to be a soldier is great,
but you need more than just passion
to wear this uniform.
If you can't understand this,
leaving right now
might be a good choice.
I'll never leave.
[Reinforce Combat Readiness.]
Excuse me,
have you seen
a tall, thin new recruit?
His name is Gu Yiye.
No. Comrade,
you can't enter here.
Comrade,
Gu Yiye is fine,
you can go back now.
Did you ask for leave?
Running around like this.
Hurry up and go back to your troop.
Yes, Sir.
1, 2, 3, 4.
[Create a new situation with revolutionized troops and modernized construction.]
Gao,
Gao, you see,
you are about to retire to local.
You really should work hard,
and be that ten-thousand-yuan household.
Gao,
I do know a way
to let you stay in the military.
Just marry a woman soldier,
then you get to be a soldier's dependant!
Piss off!
Yeah,
that's a way.
Stop pretending!
All of us saw clearly that
you just like that woman soldier
whose family name is Jiang, right?
Really?
Stop it. I'm telling you,
that's just revolution friendship.
Now that I'm not going to stay in military,
this revolution friendship should stop here.
Niu,
- These clothes... - What?
Gao.
- I don’t need them anyway. - No.
You can keep this uniform
as a souvenir.
Wearing this army green
without a red star
and two red flags on
is really a pity.
What are you thinking about?
Not gonna thank me?
Gao,
it smells.
I'll suffocate you!
[Proud of a peaceful motherland, happy for a wealthy society.]
- Yes. – It can’t be true.
Come and play.
We'll wait for you.
- Gao. - Gao.
I think you'll do great.
Gao.
- We’ll walk you out. - Don’t bother.
Just rest.
Say hi to the woman soldier.
Yeah, I'm just going to the woman soldier's,
why are you all following me.
You guys just take a rest, I'm going.
Goodbye, comrades.
Good bye!
Dear comrades,
you said goodbye to your friends and family,
leaving home for military.
That's devotion.
But me,
I came to the military alone,
to seek refuge.
You don't know
that I'm the one
who has nowhere else to go.
And now,
I'm leaving you.
Brother,
where are you?
I miss you.
Deserter from the new recruit company?
Had a cramp.
Who wears that suit to swim?
There's no way you can swim.
I'm fishing here this afternoon,
and I saw you hemming and hawing
right here in the water.
You made me
stare at you for hours,
and I can't even fish.
You are an old soldier, right?
Have you fought in a war?
I’ve faced some enemies.
But I still can't be compared
with those veterans.
Then you are half the known kind.
I'll tell you something about our maneuver.
You haven't eaten anything all day, so you must be hungry.
There are two eggs in the bag,
go ahead and eat.
Yiye,
the girl at the train station last time,
was she your girlfriend?
No.
No?
I saw her crying real hard,
so she must like you very much.
Actually,
being a soldier is not like a monk,
you don't have to be like that.
I know,
but I'm so determined to be a soldier.
I can't hurt her.
Way to go, really ruthless.
But, speaking of this,
being in a relationship with a soldier
is really not easy.
Few girls
can be compared with my Xiu.
Xiu? Who's Xiu?
My girlfriend.
We've been together for 2 years.
I'm not afraid of being a joke.
We only met 3 times.
After we get back,
I'll show you her picture.
She's really beautiful.
I originally thought this time,
after teaching you guys,
I'll take time off to get married.
Now,
not in the mood for anything.
Sergeant,
we are retired.
So we won't affect your selection of the honored sergeant.
Do you think I should
blow up Army B's train?
I think...
Stop thinking.
Old soldier,
if I didn't
blow up Army B's train,
Division 234's people
would have been blown up way before.
Also,
hadn't I fired that signal shell,
Division 234 would have been cleared at Zhangmu,
right?
I saved him twice,
and now he's firing me!
So you are feeling wronged?
Not wronged exactly,
just pity.
I think being a soldier is nice.
If I stay in the troop,
I can do a lot more great things.
I assume a dummy like you
must be raising pigs in the army.
It's fairly normal
that you don't understand what I said.
That's fine, just pack up and head back.
Don't keep talking with me.
I'm not going to suicide.
Don't worry,
Won't suicide?
Then why did you stayed in the water for hours.
I have no place to go.
You fool man,
can't you just go back home
and live an ordinary life?
Old soldier,
why did you join the army at first?
Me?
I have to think about that.
Don't talk about me, it's about you.
Me?
There's nothing to say about me.
I'm an orphan.
I didn't have a home at first,
then my brother took me home and brought me up.
[Thanks benefactor for raising this kid.]
My brother is awesome.
He's a war hero.
He died on the battle field.
Why are you like that?
Don't you believe me?
Come, come, come.
Back then,
they gave me this suvenir. Look,
to the most lovable person.
Wow,
you can read!
Your bond with your brother is tight.
I always miss my brother.
And when my brother was gone,
I became very afraid of being alone.
In the village,
I always asked other children to play with me.
Since then,
I started to be really afraid of the dusk.
Because after the sun set,
and the other kids went home,
I was all by myself.
Then I went working in a mine.
But I was in the mine all day,
and I couldn't see the sun year after year.
It’s so boring that I quitted.
I felt like I should
serve my country like my brother,
so I joined the army.
Do you know what about the army
attracts me most?
What?
The life there.
I finally found
that there's a place in the world,
where everyone eats together,
sleeps together and trains together.
We help each other, and are united.
From then on I wouldn't be alone.
I was determined
that I'll
work hard,
do my best in the army.
But they fired me.
And you feel wronged?
The worst you may face
is just be like the old days.
Old soldier, you don't know,
when a homeless man
finally knows what home is like,
even if it's not that great to him,
he won't want to go back to the old days.
I knew a guy in the army,
he liked bragging all day,
feeling like he was so great,
but he was actually a nerd.
Always talked about the planes,
tanks, and cannons.
The male leader praise him, and the female soldiers were attracted by him.
Actually,
that's a kind of addiction,
right?
There are all kinds of addictions.
Cigarettes, alcoho...
I'm different,
I'm addicted to crowds.
I just like how lively the military is.
Old man,
what are you addicted to?
Fishing?
I'm short-tempered.
I get high blood pressure easily.
The doctor told me to fish to treat my temper.
But hearing you,
I think you really got the point.
I'm addicted to being a bad-tempered man,
and fishing can't treat that.
New recruit,
you've been harping a lot,
now listen to me for a second.
Actually, I don't like fishing at all,
but I've been doing it for more than 20 years.
I rely on it to be patient.
People who wish to get satisfied have to pay the price.
If you think the military
is the most interesting place in the world,
then you'll stay here
and feel
the happiness and freedom you can't find elsewhere.
Then what price do I have to pay?
Get up.
Up.
Don't play mysterious, old fellow.
Tell me what it will cost me.
Will they dig out the guts or get my brain cooked?
Or cut off the limb?
Everything.
All the things you think of and don't think of.
This is the most costly experience.
Strange old fellow.
[People's Liberation Army 53082 Force]
One, two, one.
One, two, three, four.
Sergeant Zhang.
Hey, Shao,
is it your shift today?
Yes, Sir.
Sergeant.
What's wrong with your leg?
You little recruit,
don't you recognize this?
Neither thunder in the sky nor ghosts on earth
are as painful as rheumatism.
An old illness.
Shao, why did you speak of it?
Sergeant.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Here.
How about this?
Please sit here,
[People's Liberation Army 53082 Force]
and I’ll push you forward.
No, I'm fine.
I'm almost there.
Sergeant.
Report!
Come in.
Division commander.
Did you fire the flare?
Report!
No.
The one I hit was a stink bomb.
Then why don't you explain it?
I wrote it in the general report of the exercise.
Division commander,
I wrote it, too.
They might have overlooked.
What happened in the war
must be truthfully recorded.
You shouldn't take this reward.
Yes, Sir.
I will accept everything that is done to me.
Well,
the division owes you a promotion
from the last fighting competition.
Let me help you sort it out.
I'll compensate you with a promotion this time.
Thank you, division commander.
But,
I feel shame about it.
You shouldn’t show your shame to me.
You should say it
to the recruit who fired the flare.
Yes, Sir.
I'm on to him right away.
Not now.
He is still in
some kind of trouble now.
It will be too much for him
to let him know this.
Division commander,
maybe we can apply to superiors for a reward for him?
Bullshit.
What happened in the war
must be truthfully recorded.
He knew nothing
when he fired that flare.
What's fun?
Division commander,
you just told us to recorded truthfully,
but now you're talking about the opposite right now.
I'm confused.
People who haven't fought don't understand.
There are many heroes in war.
And there are many heroic behaviors too.
But very few people get a military merit badge.
The standard of reward
needs to be measured.
Yes, Sir, I will learn.
As to that recruit,
we will treat him fairly.
Attention!
Can't you hear the “Attention“?
Don't stand there.
Come and sit, bro.
Gu Yiye, Gao Liang.
According to the urgent notice from the mission,
you two,
instead of being withdrawn from the military, you two stay and
being informed and criticized.
Instructor.
Instructor, what is that means?
I haven't finished.
Gu Yiye is forced to stay.
Gao Liang,
should ask for his own wishes.
If he do not intend to continue to serve in the military,
He can withdraw from the army.
Instructor.
Who wrote the note?
You shouldn't ask this.
Who has fire?
Who has fire? Fire?
No, no.
Let me do this.
Gao.
Gao, you.
[Ready to fight]
[No. 9 New Recruit Squad]
Salute!
Your new company commander
will be in place
from tomorrow.
Give you recruits an advice,
all of you,
Throw away the way you thought
before you joined the army.
Train well and obey the management.
Let the regiment 720  no longer be
left behind.
Go for it!
Understand?
Yes, Sir!
Great.
Now I'd like to introduce you to the
new class vice president,
Zhao Hongliu.
Here!
Zhao Hongliu,
introduce yourself to everyone.
Reporting to everyone!
Oh, no, it's,
reporting to the instructor Lu and everyone!
My name is Zhao Hongliu.
But I'm not an Air Force family member,
my father was in the Army.
He wanted to be a bomber pilot,
but he didn't pass the exam,
so he wanted me to pass it.
I...
Turns out you failed, too.
Yes.
I didn't pass the pilot recruitment test.
So I chose here.
My father was in the
division 234 of the army A when he was alive.
Zhao Hongliu.
Lead the group properly.
Your father
will be proud of you.
Here, everyone,
Applause for your
vice president Zhao.
Great.
Instructor,
who is our
new division commander?
Report!
Come in, Hanyong.
Jianshe,
make him a glass of water.
Colonel.
Hanyong.
I've got a good news for you.
I've got your new job
arranged.
You're not asking me to lead new recruits, are you?
As a soldier from the Night tiger company of regiment 720,
you are smart.
Though the Night tiger company is famous,
but you are more than that.
So the group attaches great importance to you.
They see you as the best person to lead new recruits.
They want you to help the regement 720
from the very start, from the recruits.
To create new power.
How is that?
Can you feel the energy from it?
Colonel.
I am not exalting myself.
With my reputation and ability,
I'm better suited to lead a pacesetter company.
I was wasting my time with you.
Don't you understand?
The pacesetter company?
You wish.
The pacesetter company was already being brought.
Report!
Come in.
Why you are here?
Colonel.
I told him to come here.
I need to consider
the decisions from the regiment.
To be honest.
The assignment of me to the regiment 720
is already make me feel hard to accept.
I look down on your regiment.
Life is so short.
The military career was shorter.
I just want to show my talent
in the armed forces
in such short time.
Since now I don't have that chance anymore,
I can't achieve what I've been dreamt of.
Now I just got one thought.
Leave.
[Report of transferring to civilian work]
This is the transferred to civilian work report of mine.
Wait!
Lu Pingfan.
What do you mean?
Let us go straight
in front of the colonel.
We've selected the recruits
with highest quality
and made them a company.
The colonel chose you as their leader
he wants you to train them to be a pacesetter company.
What?
You feel not being treated right?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so conceited?
Lu Pingfan.
I don't blame you for despising Regiment 720.
I will not force you to stay
using my power.
It's ok for you
to be conceit.
But I hope that you, being a student,
have the qualification to be conceited.
The training for new recruits is not a long time.
I believe that these several months for training
will not take up much of your time in your limited life.
If you are capable of
training this company
to a high level
that even division commander acclaim your work,
I will not hesitate to approve you transferring to civilian work.
Colonel,
I understand why the company transferred us
to the corps.
But to tell you the truth,
Regiment 720
leaving the valley
with one or two
model companies only
will not be enough.
If you can accept the challenge,
then don't negotiate with me.
Just obey orders.
- Colonel, the model soldier... - And you.
You can blame as well,
but that will be useless.
You have connections with the division commander,
thus you're his own clique.
You are even not qualified to negotiate with me.
It has been decided that
you are the commander of No.3 new recruit company.
Dismiss.
Don't expect me to treat you well.
You're not nowhere near
being a qualified sodier.
The star on your head
- Front dress. - and the badge around your neck
are given to you on credit.
Goose-stepping breaks up movement.
All of you!
One.
You will not be a real soldier
- to wear them - Turn around!
until you're qualified.
Before then,
I will not show you any mercy.
Be careful.
Squat half step forward!
A soldier should act like a soldier.
All of you, stand up straight!
Dress to the right!
26 minutes.
Were you all crawling here?
All of you, get up!
Keep running!
Those who can't finish within 22 minutes
can all piss off!
Our company will not tolerate with these trash!
Get up! Get up!
Keep running!
Run!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
[Reinforce combat readiness, ready to fight.]
- Practice swinging arms on the spot. - Forward march.
These female soldiers
are all directional soldiers of the division headquaters.
Originally,
they'll be trained by the divisional training unit.
But the site and barracks
were washed away by the flood.
Therefore Regiment 720 took up the place.
It's a test from the division headquarter to our Regiment 720
for training these female soldiers.
You have to be strict
and control the management ability.
Colonel, don't worry.
These female soldiers
are beside the vegetable garden.
The material warehouse has been vacated.
[Struck root in the camp.]
It's far away from where the male soldiers are.
It's a whole garden away,
and it's a separate yard.
But there's not canteen in the warehouse.
So they might be eat with
No.3 new recruit company.
What trouble will it take to set up a cooking bench?
Some veteran just left, didn't they?
Most companies have no cooks.
Nobody cooks for them.
Tell Qin Hanyong and Zhao Hongying.
Keep an eye on them.
Nothing can go wrong.
Yes, sir.
[Who knows the dishes food, each grain is hard.]
Sit down.
Let's eat.
Be careful! Don't touch me!
It hurts!
That hurts so much!
Don't complain. My leg was hurt as well.
Our company commander
may probably be just started.
I can't.
Today I'll go to the clinic
and ask them to give me a sick note. Whatever.
I will not go.
No. 3 company!
Stand up!
Listen to my order!
No. 3 company, all of you!
Lay low and crawl.
Target,
barrier site.
No. 9 squad in the lead.
Let's go!
Hurry!
Eat!
Don't look!
Hurry up!
Are you turtles?
Even though Gao Lianggu is just nearby,
nobody dare to greet.
Strict diciplines and orders
are everwhere.
We need to get used to obey.
Personality, in this place,
is no more that tofu-shaped quilt.
It's unification that matters.
Be serious and lively.
Be tenacious.
Comrade,
we met among crowed people.
You want more punishment, right?
One, two, three, four!
[Never shed tears even for bloody sweat. Never be left behind even being peeled of the meat.]
Did you not learn the rules of internal affairs?
Lights-out has not been blown.
All lying in bed.
It hurts.
My leg.
Where's Niu Mancang?
Being punished by the company commander
for being in the last place in the traning this afternoon.
Applying fertilizer in the garden.
And he said that
as long as you're the last place
in the training,
applying fertilizer will be the punishment.
This is so-called working hard and aiming high.
You have more information
than me being a squad leader.
Because I was the last but one this afternoon.
I would be the last
if not pushing hard
in the end of the training.
Okay, stop chatting.
Go wash up.
Working hard and aiming high.
Only working fertilizer,
and no aiming at all.
What do you want this time?
No, Qin Dapao
was just being sarcasm.
I'm telling you,
if Qin Dapao
bully me,
I'll fertilize the wall
in the company well.
Come on!
You want to be dropped out again, don't you?
No, Gu Yiye,
don't you know a lot of information?
You tell me,
are there any new recruits
being trained to death like this?
Is he reaonable? Isn't he insane?
He's insane.
The training of new recruits
should focus on being familiar with the environment
and shaping personalities,
instead of training them to death
which will injure them
and enhance negative mentality.
As for the reasons of training like this,
I think there are two possibilities.
First of all,
the colonel wants to have achievements.
Rights.
That's why.
I'm telling you
that Qin Dapao wants to train the poor soldiers into good ones.
Seconly,
there's not enough time.
What's not enough time?
Come on.
Look.
[Honor]
[Training hard for killing enemies. Ready to fight anytime.]
[Devote youth for national defence. Struck root in the camp without regret.]
[Learn from Lei Feng and be helpful to people.]
[Cannon, ready anytime.]
Bastard.
[No. 9 New Recruit Squad]
Guys.
Come on, get up!
Get up, get up!
Bananas.
Eat bananas.
Vice squad leader,
eat more while the squad leader
is not here.
You must be hungry.
Are these planted by fellow-villagers?
Wile bananas.
♫ The western mountains are red as the sun sets. ♫
♫ The soldiers hit the target and return the camp. ♫
♫ Return the camp. ♫
What the hell.
I'm scared to death.
What's so funny?
Did I look happy?
Come on, what happened?
I can tell you what happened,
but,
you have to promise me one thing.
Come on.
Lend me your watch.
I don't want to hear.
[Toilet,  Attention to hygiene, Save water.]
Don't tug on me. I don't want to hear.
Keep it down. What are you doing?
I'll tell you.
That's between you and me.
Never talk to anyone else.
Come on! You're killing me here.
I think of you as my brother.
Come on!
Really.
Shh.
Keep our voices down. Why were you so happy?
Tomorrow, tomorrow I'll run in the last place.
Don't you take my place.
Go back.
- Don’t you take my place. - I won’t.
It's so soft, isn't it?
It looks delicious.
Watch out. Be careful. Don't smash it.
Sweet, sweet.
Taste good.
There's more.
Give me more, give me more.
Guys, Hongliu is not here as well.
We have to bring back some to Hongliu.
We should not leave him behind.
Gao is not here. Bring him back some of these.
That's strange.
I can understand
why Zhao Hongliu and Niu Mancang are not here.
But why didn't Gao Liang show up?
He would pratically eat up the whole tree
if knowing that there's bananas here.
Gao, Awesome.
Trick them to pick bananas,
while we come here to check on the girl soldiers.
Don't be disgusting!
I'm just checking on the new girls
and see whether they need some help.
We're all neighbors from now on.
[Devote for national defense]
Check it out.
Hello girls.
Come on.
Why are you all here?
Don't you know how to count?
We're just two people.
You two are here.
We're here.
How come you all come here?
We need to share each other's fortunes.
Therefore we will definitely
share tasty foods with our girl comrades.
Right?
Girl comrades,
come here and have some wile fruits.
These are not enough for all of us.
Here's more.
They're all yours.
One more.
Gao Liang.
Hey, Gao Liang.
Hello, Sir Jiang Nanzheng.
I'm asking you, where's Gu Yiye?
Gu...
I'm asking you a question. Why are you mumbling?
Gao,
they did not lay eyes on you.
You're no more than a mailman.
Piss off. Get out!
Sir Jiang Nanzheng.
I'm telling you,
Gu Yiye
will turn up his nose at the sassy girl soldiers like you.
Gao.
Sir Jiang Nanzheng,
falling in love with someone who doesn't love you back
is hard
and has no future.
If you cannot stop it,
just keep it to yourself.
In the end,
it'll work out.
- You wait and see, Gao Liang. - Girls.
What are you doing?
Have you finished your work?
And you!
Get down!
Or I'll report to your company commander.
This is too high.
For the first task of today's squad meeting,
I'll announce a good news.
Our squad wans ranked
as the model squad in our platoon.
Report!
Speak!
Squad leader,
how come we can be model squad?
Model squad
means that each one of you
can be the model of our platoon.
This honor
means that we have made
much more effort than others.
Being a model squad
means that we need to be strick with ourselves.
In the mix-training between male and female soldiers,
the most important thing is
the relationship between male and female soldiers
which will influence our work and training.
Therefore,
what happens today,
strickly speaking,
is not permitted whatsoever.
Here,
I'll announce a rule.
During the training of new recruits,
the female soldiers and male soldiers
must not contact with each other except for work.
Remember,
in the troops,
discipline is an iron.
Those who violate it will bleed.
Understand?
Understand.
Jiang Nanzheng.
The yelling of Gao Liang on the wall
enlightened me.
The exciting moments with Gu Yiye
such as relaying secret messages,
saving Division 234,
and the worry and concerned
upon hearing him being dropped out,
were like
the start of a dream.
I can smell the taste of freedom when wind blows by the weeds.