♫ Misty dawn and tender dusk ♫
♫ Boy in uniform
galloping under the blinking stars ♫
♫ His eyes are so loving,
determined, and happy ♫
♫ Looking back
What transient beauty ♫
♫ Winter, the season of falling snow ♫
♫ But you have spring in your arms
The whole world smells like flowers ♫
♫ During the sunny summer days
Our feelings grow stronger ♫
♫ I'm so in love with you in autumn
Every falling leaf speaks of my love ♫
♫ Dancing and swirling in the air ♫
[FALL IN LOVE]
[EPISODE 6]
Madam,
this is the Five Phases Amulet
you requested.
It can care for the primordial spirit,
bless you with peace and good luck,
[FIVE PHASES AMULET]
and dissolve the evil spirit in your life.
May you
keep it carefully
and be safe and happy.
Thank you, Master.
I'm not cold.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best
to keep you safe.
Since you try to protect me,
I will return the favor.
Cui Jie?
This is my nephew.
What did you do?
Uncle.
This man.
When Miss Mu was
at her mother's wake yesterday,
he broke into Fayuan Temple
and tried to do something indecent.
You!
He said he worked for Ms. Mu.
And Ms. Mu
ordered him to do that.
Me?
It pertains to Ms. Mu's reputation,
so I brought him here on purpose
and handed him over
to you for questioning.
What's wrong with you?
When did I let you go to Fayuan Temple?
How can you do such a heartless
and evil thing?
You got no conscience!
You!
Bastard!
Even a dog won't bite its owner.
Guang Yao.
I'll leave him to you.
Beat or punish him as you wish.
This has nothing to do with the Mu Family.
Uncle! Uncle!
How can you think that I would do that?
I would never do such thing!
I… I wouldn't do that!
It's as if a toad tried
to swallow a swan!
But
Cousin Wan Ting said…
She said…
What did she say?
She said that my aunt
intended to marry Miss Mu with me.
And so
she asked me to go to Fayuan Temple
to meet Miss Mu.
She said if I was fond of her,
I can molest her.
What?
What I said is true!
Help me! Help!
Aunt, help me.
Cousin Wang Ting really said this to me.
No way.
Is he telling the truth?
My lord,
do you think I could possibly say that?
Go and bring Wan Ting here.
Hurry!
Wan Ting.
This bastard snuck into Fayuan Temple
and tried to rape Wan Qing yesterday.
He said you told him to go there.
Is this true?
I didn't.
Cousin,
how could you say that?
I didn't do anything wrong to you!
How could you say that?
You did tell me that!
You said…
You said that Aunt
intended to have Miss Mu marry me.
You told me to go to Fayuan Temple
to meet her.
That if I like her,
I can rape her.
What are you talking about?
Father.
I'm an unmarried girl.
How can I let you do such a thing?
You did say that!
You specifically went to
Jinlou to look for me.
Young Master Cui.
[CHECK: TWO THOUSAND SILVER DOLLARS]
[MU WAN TING]
Let go of him.
It's the young lady from the Mu Family.
My cousin!
Let's go.
Those servants were all witnesses!
If you didn't tell me,
how was I supposed
to know about Ms. Xiao's funeral
and how Miss Mu was at the vigil?
I did
run into you at Jinlou yesterday.
And I happened to see you
being chased around due to debt.
So I helped you pay it back.
Cousin.
How can you say that about me?
You told me
Miss Mu from Japan grabbed your spotlight
so you asked me to help you
take revenge.
Did you not tell me that?
I didn't.
You're lying.
You.
My lord.
It's all my fault.
I spoiled you
too much,
so you are now behaving irrationally
and saying things.
But she may have
just used words without thinking.
She can't do such
harmful things.
You said
Miss Wan Ting ordered you.
Do you have any proof?
Proof?
Yes, I do.
That check.
That's the evidence!
Check?
Yes.
Wan Ting.
Is there such a thing?
I…
You asked me
for a check yesterday.
You said that one of your classmate's
family members was in trouble,
and you had to help him pay off the debt.
Did you lie to me?
Tell the truth!
Father.
I did
bump into him yesterday.
But I did it
because you were part of my family.
I didn't want to see
your fingers get chopped off
and disgrace our family.
That's why I helped you
and didn't tell Moth--
You!
Mu Wan Ting, you have to tell the truth,
or you will get me killed!
Do you understand?
Please tell the truth.
You said it was a reward!
A reward!
- I'm not lying.
- Reward!
If you don't believe me,
call the men at Jinlou here,
and they'll confirm it!
Wan Qing.
It's your father's fault.
I didn't think it through.
I should have let someone be with you.
Of course,
Wan Ting also has her issues.
If she hadn't said something wrong,
it wouldn't let the shameless guy get
the chance to do it.
For the sake of
Wan Ting's
unintentional mistake
that she also admitted to,
please forgive her.
Please?
Sister.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I was also used by others.
Please forgive me.
Please?
It's up to you, Father.
You shall be grounded for a month
and won't be allowed going anywhere.
Mother.
Thank you.
Otherwise, I wouldn't know what to do.
Whatever you do,
you should consider
the immediate consequences.
Do you know how dangerous things are
these days?
I know. I was wrong.
Whatever you do in the future,
don't do things by yourself.
Come discuss it with me first.
But this time,
that bitch got off easy.
Don't worry.
We have plenty of time,
and we will get our chance.
I can't believe
Uncle Mu would accept
those explanations so easily.
Because in his mind,
he couldn't believe
Wan Ting would do all of that.
It would've been futile
to keep trying.
I really hate that.
How can he not think about you?
You don't have to fight for me.
When my brother died,
Father immediately brought
Aunt Cui and Wan Ting home.
This is nothing.
I understand.
I'm worried about
you staying by yourself
in a family like this.
I'll figure something out.
Come in.
[FILE BOX]
Guang Yao.
I told you to give me some time.
Please stop pestering me.
If you need more time,
I'll give it to you.
As long as you're not afraid of
running out of money,
I can have a longer discussion
with you.
Guang Yao.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
I came to see you
not because of the program,
but for another matter.
I'd like you to give me a favor.
Are you asking me to help you?
Fine.
I'll do whatever if I can.
It's not a big deal.
I want Wan Qing
to be my foreign language secretary.
Wan Qing has agreed.
Are there any problems with that?
If it's for work,
I'll get you a secretary
from the Commercial Press
who can speak five languages.
Wouldn't that be better?
Wan Qing is good
at both Japanese and English.
And for Mu Family's sake,
if you want to make good deals
with the Municipal Council in the future,
she can also help.
You're right.
Fine.
Let Miss Mu come to work tomorrow.
If she can't work alone,
I'll find her a helper.
I've known her since we were young.
I know her well.
I'm sure
she will do her part.
I'll go and tell her.
I thank you
for her.
Don't bother.
Who cares if you knew each other before?
[FIVE PHASES AMULETl]
That's enough.
Morning.
Good morning, Ms. Cui.
Good morning, Uncle.
Good morning.
Please have a seat.
Did you sleep well?
Eat a lot.
You have to go to work later.
Okay.
My lord, have the porridge.
Thank you.
Guang Yao.
Commander Tan called just now.
He wants
Wan Ting to be your foreign secretary.
And all formalities
have already been completed.
Uncle.
I clearly told Commander Tan
to have Wan Qing go.
Commander Tan said,
Wan Qing is in mourning for her mother.
And regarding the kidnapping…
He feels sorry for Wan Qing.
So he thinks it's better to let Wan Ting
be your foreign secretary.
To avoid embarrassing everyone.
Commander Tan.
He really went back on his word.
Guang Yao.
In fact,
Wan Qing and Wan Ting.
Whoever is your secretary
is fine.
As long as you think she works.
Madam.
The Command has high requirements
for a foreign language secretary.
Someone who speaks English, Japanese,
and Chinese.
I'm afraid Wan Ting
is not a good choice.
Brother Guang Yao.
When I was in school,
I wasn't good at studying.
But now I've
tried to catch up.
You don't even let me try.
How do you know I can't?
Miss Wan Ting.
This is a job,
not a children's game.
Guang Yao, you probably do not know.
Once Wan Ting works hard,
she would do well.
You
should give Wan Ting a chance, okay?
Brother Guang Yao.
Since Wan Ting wants to try,
let her do it.
I'm also tired today
and would like to take a rest.
Yes, Wang Qing.
You look so exhausted
after the past two days.
Since you came back from Japan
and have been busy
with your mother's funeral,
you haven't been able to take a rest.
I happened to stew
a good blood swallow soup.
I'll send it to you
when it's ready.
It'll be good for your health.
Thank you, Aunt Cui.
You're welcome.
Brother Guang Yao, you should eat more.
And we're going to work later.
I'm full. Enjoy your meal.
Mother, Father. I'm leaving, too.
Brother Guang Yao, wait for me!
Brother Guang Yao.
Let me hold the door for you.
Brother Guang Yao,
come and sit in the back with me.
Let's go.
As long as you are willing to help me,
I will give you 10,000 silver dollars.
20,000 silver dollars.
Tan Si.
The tea is a bit weak today.
I'll go check it out
and make a new one.
30,000 silver dollars.
How about 30,000 silver dollars?
Miss Mu.
You may leave, please.
50,000 silver dollars.
I'll give you 50,000 silver dollars.
Tan Si,
pour the tea for her.
[THE DEFENSE COMMAND OF SHANGHAI]
Commander,
are you going out?
Here comes Miss Fifty Thousand.
Hello?
Isn't this your first day at work?
Why didn't you come?
Stop pretending.
I got something to ask you.
Let's meet at the usual place.
Okay.
I was stopped
when I was about to go out.
Your sister is going too far.
Stop acting.
Do you know
how important it is for me
to be the secretary?
Of course I know.
As a secretary at the Command,
your status with the Mu Family
will be totally different.
You still did that after knowing?
Did Mu Wan Ting pay you?
Yeah.
You're right.
But your sister was really generous.
I couldn't say no.
Commander Tan.
You're the one who worked out
to cooperate with me at the beginning
and even set some ground rules.
The first rule
is to trust each other and be consistent.
I can't believe you're ungrateful now
because of a few pennies.
That's a lot of money.
It's 50,000 silver dollars!
I'd like to take it.
At the time of my mother's wake,
I thought you would be a reliable ally.
But I didn't expect you
to be so ungrateful so fast.
We shouldn't work with each other.
Let's go our separate ways.
[FIVE PHASES AMULET]
[THE SUPERVISOR'S OFFICE]
[THE BUSINESS OF THE TELEGRAPH OFFICE]
Your job today
is to translate those two documents first.
Brother Guang Yao.
Look.
I read the Japanese document
for a long time
but only understood one sentence.
And this English one.
I can't read it at all.
How about like this?
You dictate
and I'll take notes.
Sorry.
I got many files here.
I don't have time today.
Look things up in the dictionary
if you don't know.
Miss Wan Ting.
Welcome.
Your arrival
has given the Command a glow.
On behalf of all the men in the Command,
I extend a warm welcome to you.
Thank you.
But let me set things straight.
I'm the secretary of Brother Guang Yao,
not yours.
Okay.
Since Commander Tan welcomes
Miss Wan Ting so much,
you shall talk with him first.
I have something to do first.
Why are you leaving so suddenly?
Brother Guang Yao.
What about the file?
Let me take a look.
[THE BUSINESS OF THE TELEGRAPH OFFICE]
This is really hard to translate.
I've told him
to get a translator
from the Commercial Press.
He has a tender heart for fair ladies.
Well.
Use the dictionary
and give me a call if you need anything.
[THE FIREARMS ROOM]
Supervisor Xu.
[SUPERVISOR XU OPEN]
This is from our Commander.
What is it?
These are tickets to Miss Gu Yue Shuang's
film premiere.
He hopes you and Miss Mu Wan Qing
[TICKET TO THE GRAND THEATER]
could attend it together.
What exactly is
your Commander up to?
He asked me to tell you,
he will do what he promised you.
But you can't be aggressive
when facing a woman.
You'd better know how to do one thing
under the guise of another.
Your Commander
has really experienced a lot.
[URGENCY]
[A NEW CHINESE-ENGLISH DICTIONARY]
I told him
to get a translator
from the Commercial Press.
He has a tender heart for fair ladies.
Hello, is this the Commercial Press?
Yes.
I need a translator
who can translate quickly.
Now.
[PURPLE TOWEL]
Brother Guang Yao. How did you get back?
Today
is the premiere of Gu Yue Shuang's film.
Commander Tan has given me two tickets.
[TICKET TO THE GRAND THEATER]
I'd like to invite you to see it together.
What on earth
is Tan Xuan Lin doing?
Well?
Don't you want to go?
I want to go.
I'm also a fan of Gu Yue Shuang.
I really enjoy watching her movies.
[THE DEFENSE COMMAND OF SHANGHAI]
[RETURN TO YOUR HOMETOWN]
[VANITY FAIR]
[THE DEFENSE COMMAND OF SHANGHAI]
Are you Mr. Wei
from the Commercial Press?
Yes.
Were you in need of a translator?
Are you good at English and Japanese?
Yes.
I told you.
If you do well,
[MAIL BOX]
I can double the price.
And come here every day.
Well, Miss.
Am I working inside?
You'll send it back when you're done.
After two hours,
come downstairs, and I'll retrieve it.
Here.
[DOCUMENTS]
Let's go.
Stop!
What are you doing here?
I was here to receive a file.
What file? Show me.
What are you doing?
- Don't move.
What are you guys doing?
You transmitted a confidential file out
in secret.
You'll have to face the military court.
This is from your Supervisor Xu.
He's the one I asked for help.
I'm the secretary of Supervisor Xu.
We need to lock you up now
until Supervisor Xu gets back.
I'm Supervisor Xu's fiancee.
Are you his secretary
or fiancee?
I'm the fiancee and secretary.
Do you understand?
I see.
You're a soldier's wife, aren't you?
What nonsense!
You two.
Call Brother Guang Yao back
and tell him straight.
Sorry. Supervisor Xu is not here.
We can't find him.
You two
should come with us first.
Move.
Go.
Hurry.
- Go.
- Hurry.
Go.
[MISS GU YUE SHUANG]
[NEW FILM]
Supervisor Xu.
Miss Wan Qing.
Miss Gu.
Congratulations on the new movie.
Thank you, Supervisor Xu.
Commander Tan.
Thank you for your tickets.
It's nothing.
Brother Guang Yao. Let's go inside first.
Let's go.
Please.
It's our turn.
Hello.
- Thank you.
VIP seats in Hall One.
It's a love seat.
Please.
Thank you.
Who set them a love seat?
I did. I've come this far.
Today is the launch of my new movie.
Please try to smile.
Miss Gu.
Here. Miss Gu.
Here.
This way. Miss Gu.
Okay.
Miss Gu.
Junior Marshal Su. Junior Marshal Pei.
Commander Tan is also here.
Mr. Su, thank you
for coming in without an invitation.
Miss Gu's new movie is on.
And I'm your fan.
I've been paying attention.
Pei and I are here to support you.
Miss Gu. You're welcome, right?
Of course.
You guys.
Set Junior Marshal Su
and Junior Marshal Pei
a love seat.
Let's go.
[FAIRY SENDING FLOWERS]
Please.
A love seat.
[THE SING-SONG GIRLS OF SHANGHAI]
Miss Gu is pretty.
Yeah.
Have you seen her film before?
Nope.
Little Uncle.
Are you jealous?
So you pulled a stunt on Mr. Su?
No.
Excellent acting.
Yeah.
It's great.
Please enjoy the movie, okay?
Fine.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Pei.
Sorry, man.
I have to put love
before friendship this time.
Mr. Su, there's someone here.
Nobody's here, right?
I'll say a few words and leave.
[BATHROOM]
I told you to go your separate way.
Why are you stopping me?
Today,
you left this, and I found it.
I told you I didn't want it.
I've been curious,
why did you throw it away
after arguing with me?
I was in a bad mood, so I threw it around.
[FIVE PHASES AMULET]
You didn't put a spell on me, did you?
You really got a suspicious mind.
I found it,
so it's mine.
I'll go back and study it,
and I'll deal with you
after I know what it is.
Crazy.
I'm not as good as him?
When it comes to family,
talent,
and appearance,
he has no advantage over me.
I really don't know you well, Mr. Su.
Please leave.
What are you going to play this time?
Nothing.
I swear.
I'm not lying to you this time.
I'm here to give you a present.
We're done talking here. I have to go.
Excuse me.
She's still not interested in me.
Gu Yue Shuang
is definitely my failure
in love.
You've seen so many of her movies
but made no progress at all.
How do you know?
Pei.
I really got hurt.
I need your consolation.
Piss off.
[CORRECT YOUR MISTAKE
KNOW COURTESY AND SHAME]
Miss.
I was really unlucky
picking your job today.
How dare you ask an outsider
to translate that confidential file?
Even if you don't fear death,
I do.
The seal is so small.
Who can see it clearly.
Furthermore,
if I had known it was a confidential file,
I wouldn't have asked you.
When your boss comes,
you have to make things clear.
Don't get me into the military court.
What the heck?
He is my fiance.
You'll see!
When Brother Guang Yao gets here,
he will surely punish
the two guys for me.
But it's probably late.
How come you fiance hasn't come back yet?
Somebody get in here! Come one!
I need to see Brother Guang Yao.
Is anybody here?
Don't shout.
I told you Supervisor Xu is not here.
Stay there.
How dare you shout at me?
Wait, I will punish you later.
[CATHAY THEATER]
Here. Take it.
Thank you.
Sir, buy a flower for your madam.
Each flower is one dollar.
Okay. I'll pick this one.
How can you call
such a pretty girl madam?
You should call her sister.
Kid,
you know a lot about business.
Come on.
I'll take all these flowers.
Here you are.
Thank you, Little Uncle.
Here.
The money.
Keep the change.
Including his flower.
Thank you. Uncle.
Go.
Commander Tan,
you get a cluster of flowers.
But I'm the only one here.
It's quite fit for the scene.
So I said you're a cultured person.
I'm a rough guy,
and I don't know how to say nice things.
But what I do know is
if the beauty likes it,
the more the better.
It seems that Commander Tan does not know
the sense of cherishing
the only thing he likes.
Thank you for your flower,
Brother Guang Yao.
I like it very much.
In that case, I shall leave you two alone.
I'll leave first.
See you at the Command.
Let's go.
So pretty.
[ORIENTAL BRASSERIE]
Brother Guang Yao.
Sorry, Miss Wan Ting.
My men are such fools.
They didn't know you.
I'm sorry you were wronged.
Yeah, exactly.
The two men are so stupid.
They shut me in there
without saying a word.
Commander Tan.
You should teach your men well.
Of course, I'll teach them.
Listen.
Do you hear that?
They are being punished.
Okay.
But how come you are here?
Where is Brother Guang Yao?
You mean Supervisor Xu?
He seems to have gone to the film premiere
with Miss Wan Qing.
Now,
the movie should be over.
What? Watch a movie?
Didn't you know?
Miss Wan Qing is a fan of Gu Yue Shuang,
so Guang Yao Bro
asked me for two VIP tickets.
I guess it's the love seat.
Miss Wan Ting.
Please go back, Mr. Wei.
Don't tell anyone about
what happened today.
You may stop.
It might still be needed tonight.
Yes.
You.
Military secrets should be
kept confidential.
How can you
not understand?
Mother.
I worked hard
all day there.
I didn't even have lunch.
But that bitch
asked Brother Guang Yao
to go to the movie premiere.
I worked all day long,
but she took advantage of it.
It really hit me.
Are you still blaming others?
You do things without thinking carefully.
Please.
What are you doing?
You.
Are you going to fight with Mu Wan Qing?
You screwed things up.
Do you want Xu Guang Yao
to see your mistake?
Mother, I worked all day
and went to jail.
Yet, they could stay together?
I quit.
Screw being his secretary.
Screw his Command.
I'll never go there any more.
It's better if you don't go there.
On your first day at work,
you make a mistake
by leaking military secrets.
If time goes on,
I don't know what mistakes you will make.
If Warlord Xu finds out,
how can you have a good image?
Well. If that bitch goes there,
wouldn't it be cheap for her?
She'll spend every day
with Brother Guang Yao.
The Command is a military agency.
She goes to work as a secretary.
She has to work.
You think she's dating?
Forget it, I won't go.
Well. You.
You're foolish.
It's 50,000 silver dollars
in exchange for one day of work
at the Command.
It's all for nothing!
Please. Miss Secretary.
Yes, sir.
[THE DEFENSE COMMAND OF SHANGHAI]
[AROUSE ALL EFFORTS
TO MAKE THE COUNTRY PROSPEROUS]
Miss Wan Qing.
Welcome.
I would appreciate your guidance later.
You give me a great honor.
You're the secretary Supervisor asked for.
Of course I'll take care of you.
I have also prepared
a special office for you.
Even Miss Wan Ting didn't
get such treatment.
Let's go. Let me show you.
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫ Go back to
the starting point of our meeting ♫
♫ I immediately saw ♫
♫ your charming face ♫
♫ The sea is as wide as the sky ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫ to let the world
of mortals fall with us ♫
♫ If I forget your outline ♫
♫ How to piece it together ♫
♫ The memories
that bring me back to life from afar ♫
♫ Let's embrace
either during sunrise or sunset ♫
♫ In this world of chaos and confusion ♫
♫ I have exhausted my desolate life ♫
♫ Even if my vision is blurred ♫
♫ I'll sing with you on horseback ♫
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫ Go back to
the starting point of our meeting ♫
♫ I immediately saw ♫
♫ your charming face ♫
♫ The sea is as wide as the sky ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫ to let the world
of mortals fall with us ♫
♫ If I forget your outline ♫
♫ How to piece it together ♫
♫ The memories
that bring me back to life from afar ♫
♫ Let's embrace
either during sunrise or sunset ♫
♫ In this world of chaos and confusion ♫
♫ I have exhausted my desolate life ♫
♫ Even if my vision is blurred ♫
♫ I'll sing with you on horseback ♫