♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 14=
(Egret Villa)
That's amazing!
You are so brilliant.
Oh,
Landlord Lu,
why did you build such a mansion
in a place where a family
was slaughtered?
Murong Chen,
stop talking nonsense!
It's scary.
It's not me who said it.
It's from a book.
Book?
What book?
The one that Chang Kong usually reads,
World Memoir.
Me?
Yes,
I read it a lot.
The book said that
11 years ago,
Jing Yue Sect was
leading the martial arts circle
and did evil things.
The leader Yu Qingzhu wanted to
practice Blood Moon Power and forced
Cereus Villa to hand in
the blood night-blooming cereus
they had been developing for years.
It's said that this flower
blooms only once per 100 years.
Of course, the landlord of Cereus Villa
would not be willing to hand it over.
So, Yu Qingzhu slaughtered them all
out of anger.
She killed more than 100 people,
stole the blood night-blooming cereus,
and then burned Cereus Villa
into ash.
Which means
this place...
No. No. No. It's not possible.
It just occurred to me too.
Oh, Chang Kong,
the Cereus Villa mentioned in the book
seems to be this place, right?
Yes, Your Highness.
Such a street flimflam.
It's all bullshit.
I can't believe that you
actually bought it.
Exactly.
Are you saying that it's not
true that Jing Yue Sect
slaughtered Cereus Villa,
or it's not true that Egret Villa
used to be Cereus Villa?
As far as I'm concerned,
none of them sounds reliable.
Murong Chen,
stop reading that kind of raving books
or scaring others.
I...
I did not try to scare you.
If you don't believe it,
you can ask Landlord Lu about it.
Landlord Lu?
I'm just a businessman and
I don't know much about
those historical stuff.
I bought this villa last year,
but back then,
I did so only because
the land was cheap.
As for what happened here before,
I have no idea.
I'm sure that
you were fooled by someone
and bought this haunted place.
Save it, Murong Chen.
It's getting dark.
I've prepared nice rooms for everyone.
After having dinner,
I will lead you to the rooms to rest.
Thank you so much.
After this long journey,
we finally had something nice to eat
and a place to sleep.
What's on your mind, Murong Chen?
You all think
this Lu Feibai is not suspicious?
You just had a meal that he provided
and now you are talking bad behind him?
Come on.
I think he's quite a nice person.
What's nice about him?
He's good-looking,
full of wisdom,
good at business,
straightforward, welcoming and friendly.
Isn't he nice?
You've only known him for one day,
and you are now complimenting him.
You can ask Xiao Ai and Zhe Xiang
and see if they feel the same way.
Why are you all so easy to be fooled?
- Easy to be fooled?
- Actually,
I think that Lu Feibai
is a nice person.
Song Che,
how could you get bribed
only by a meal?
No.
I did not like him
when I just met him.
But look,
you talked about
such horrible things that
happened here before,
and you were saying
this place was haunted.
But he did not haggle over it
or drug you in the meal.
Based on that,
he seems to have a lot of tolerance.
How does it make him have
tolerance just by not drugging me?
What kind of logic is that?
Then you tell me,
why are you so sure
that he's suspicious?
I have proof.
What proof?
My proof is that
when I asked him about
why he bought this place,
he
smiled at me.
I'm not finished.
Listen to me.
Well,
when we just got here,
he showed two personalities, didn't he?
He was very nice and friendly
when he welcomed you ladies,
with passion.
However, in front of Song Che,
Chang Kong and me,
he was cold
and indifferent.
However, he smiled at me in the room.
There must be something wrong with him.
Murong Chen,
you should've tried to
make up the story better.
So
none of you believe in me?
Alright.
Everyone must be tired.
Let's all go back to sleep.
Let's go back to sleep. Let's go back.
Sleep, sleep, sleep.
You should sleep early. Sleep.
Good night, Mengmeng.
Let's go.
Mengmeng.
Why are you back...
Have a seat.
Sit down, sit down.
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
It's okay if they don't believe me.
But it's different with us.
Why don't you believe me, either?
I know what you are thinking.
Think about it.
This Egret Villa
made such a cunning movement to
purchase so much pigment
from Qian Xiu Workshop.
Not to mention that Lu Feibai
was specialized in
fake goods business.
So it was totally
possible for Lu Feibai
to be the leader behind this.
Then why were you...
But have you ever considered that
the signature on
Qian Xiu Workshop's account book
is Egret Villa
instead of Lu Feibai?
You are saying...
I'm saying that
think about it,
Egret Villa is such large-scaled.
There must be lots of
people ruled by Lu Feibai.
Yes, it is possible
that Lu Feibai did it.
But it's also possible that
one of his subordinates did it
by covering it under
the name of Egret Villa.
If we act so hastily
and question Lu Feibai,
it is not only highly possible
for us to point at the wrong person
and wrong him,
but also alert the enemy
and scare away the
real person behind it.
You have a point.
Don't tell me that you are saying this
because he's gentle, passionate
and considerate.
Why are you reciting my lines?
No, I mean,
do I look like that kind of person
who only cares about handsome guys?
Definitely.
But you're right.
Even with such handsome,
good-looking guy like me,
you were also...
OK, I see.
Murong Chen,
if you really think like that,
let's separate.
- Wait.
- Anything else?
Where are you going?
I'm going back to my room.
Here...
This room is yours.
Go back to your room.
Alright.
I'm being serious.
This Lu Feibai is the
most suspicious one.
I will find proof to show you.
What's your plan?
Aren't you afraid that
we might alert the enemy?
It's time now.
It's easy to get things done at night.
There must be something wrong with
gathering at such late night.
(I paid close attention to
this place in the daytime,)
(and I didn't find anything suspicious.)
(What exactly did I miss?)
(It's cold,)
(which means that)
(those people were here just now,)
(but did not turn on the light.)
(No light was needed,)
(which means this is
not their destination,)
(but just a passway.)
(Vase, cup, red coral,
and luminous pearl)
(are all movable.)
(They can't be the switch.)
(Then it must be...)
This painting is real.
The real may be fake,
and the fake may be real.
This Lu Feibai is so interesting.
Among so many fake things,
there's actually something genuine.
(Secret Chamber of Egret Villa)
So many!
Such a businessman.
Who is it?
Mengmeng, it's me,
Lu Feibai.
Childe Lu.
Why did you come here at this late time?
I'm delivering some quilts for everyone.
That's so nice of you.
As the landlord, you deliver
the quilts on your own?
I was neglectful and
I'm trying to do my best.
Then, rest well.
Good night, Mengmeng.
Wait.
Landlord, are you going to deliver
the quilts for everyone else?
- Yes.
- (Holy shit.)
(Murong Chen is not
in his room right now.)
Well,
Childe Lu,
would you like to have a cup of tea?
I have some business-related topics
that I would like to discuss with you.
Sure.
Sit down, please.
I will drop the quilt first.
- You can go back first.
- OK.
(Why is he still not coming out?)
(Did anything happen?)
(Why is she here?)
Is this the best you
can do, sneak attack,
when you can't beat someone?
Who said that I can't beat you?
I was just testing your
reaction speed.
At Yun Xiang House,
in the Fog Forest,
and along the way,
you never won me.
I have reasons
which prevented me
from using my best power.
You are so good at comforting yourself.
You...
There's no use to talk to you more.
Get ready.
Limited edition.
Designer collection.
Celebrity favorite.
Special offers.
Clearance sales.
Purchase limitation.
Double 11.
Double 12.
Mengmeng is such a
rare talent for business.
How did I never think about
the ideas that you mentioned?
(No, I'm not a rare talent.)
(In reality, my purse was drained)
(because of all these
marketing strategies.)
(Why is Murong Chen
still not coming back?)
(I've already shared
everything I can think of.)
(If he doesn't come back soon,
there's not much I can do.)
It was very helpful to discuss all these
with you tonight.
I will deeply study about
these strategies after I get back,
and I'm sure that they will
help me become more successful.
Childe Lu,
I suddenly remember that
there's one more strategy,
a strategy called...
monthly renewal.
Monthly renewal?
[*Renewal sounds like pimping in Chinese]
Right.
I'm afraid that this kind
of business is a little...
No, you are getting me wrong.
It's not the kind of renewal
that you are thinking.
This renewal is
actually a VIP policy.
VIP?
What is that?
VIP
is a kind of membership policy.
Why are these two fighting each other?
You gave up?
Are you scared of me?
I should actually get going.
It's getting too late.
Well,
Childe Lu,
then I will see you off.
Thank you for the treat.
Don't forget to have breakfast.
However, Zhe Xiang.
You went too far, didn't you?
He picked up the fight first.
I just wanted to practice
with this woman.
Who would know
this woman is so brutal?
I actually think that
Zhe Xiang is very nice.
You picked up the fight,
but she didn't beat you to death
or get you handicapped.
It seems that she has tolerance.
Murong Chen, you...
I...
Don't move.
Childe Lu.
Is he OK?
Please forgive us.
These friends of mine were too active.
Sorry for the trouble.
We might have to bother
you for one more day.
I've said that
you can stay as long as you want.
I would like to discuss more
about business strategies with you.
This is the medicine
for treating injury.
Thank you.
Then I will leave for now.
Please come to me whenever
you need something.
Of course,
feel free to bother me for no reason.
OK.
You are sure that you saw it last night?
What?
Are you still believing
that he's innocent?
Just because
you spent the whole night
talking about business with him?
Murong Chen,
what kind of words are those?
You think I enjoyed talking with him?
You didn't know how much effort
I put into convincing him to stay
the other night just to cover for you.
I've told him everything.
The next thing I could think
of is to knock him off.
Did you really think this way?
Otherwise?
I really don't know what is
in your head.
I'm thinking about you.
What?
I way saying
I'm thinking about
bringing you to the basement.
Everything would come into light then.
Here.
There's really a secret path here.
Quickly, go inside.
There's a snake.
Snake! Snake!
Where is it?
- Where is it?
- Snake!
Where is it?
You didn't see them yesterday?
No, I didn't see them yesterday.
Why did they show up today?
Why is it not moving?
It's OK.
It's just a rope.
You can come down.
Really?
It's OK. I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
It's really a rope.
It scared me to death.
Over there.
Let's go.
Murong Chen,
didn't you say that
this place is full of fake blood
night-blooming cereus?
It's so strange.
I'm sure that I did...
Why are they gone just in one day?
Come on, Murong Chen.
Are you bringing me here for fun?
No, I actually saw it yesterday.
This is where Lu Feibai
makes fake stuff.
If you want drinks,
you can just say it.
I'm a generous person,
and if you ask me for it,
I would definitely give to you.
Why are you all here?
Brother Lu said that
he has medicinal liquor
for me to recover sooner,
so he took all of us here.
Medicinal liquor?
Such a nice move, Lu Feibai.
I can't believe that you
brought everyone here.
Seems like the guilty
party files the suit first.
I don't know whether
I did something wrong
to upset you
and make you talk bad about me.
I think he's just envying you.
Song Che,
can you think before you do anything?
You are the one who made a mistake.
Why are you blaming me?
- Me?
- I know.
I'm like an old friend with Mengmeng
and we got close to each other.
I'm afraid that you're
upset because of that.
But I just...
Although I own this
villa and all the businesses,
and I may look like that
I have had everything,
actually I don't have any friends.
Seeing you all here
to visit the villa,
I'm really happy.
Yes.
Childe Lu is treating us really well.
I also know that
I met Mengmeng by chance and
there's not much I ask for.
I only hope to have some talk
with her as friends.
If she can smile back from time to time,
it would be more than enough for me.
Does it make me so guilty to just
have such little wish?
I don't deserve to be loved,
but can't I at least have the right
to like someone in silence?
Brother Lu, I can understand
how you feel right now.
It's so hard.
We have been gone through
so many things together.
We were there for each
other during hard times,
and nothing could stop it.
We ate together,
and slept together.
Through this journey,
I've been taking care of everyone.
But I didn't expect that
I would lose to this man
who we all just met.
You only care about the new people
and ignore the old friend.
Since now I know this,
I should just leave.
Murong Chen.
Wait up.
You are not going to
keep me from leaving?
Then I will leave for real.
Childe Lu,
excuse us.
Wait for me.
- Murong Chen.
- Your Highness.
Look at you.
Murong Chen, what are you doing?
Didn't you only trust that toy boy?
Why did you come out?
When did I say that I trust him?
Then why didn't you say anything for me?
Under that situation,
did you two leave any
room for me to jump in?
I don't care. I'm mad.
Like the kind of mad that can't
be relieved no matter what you say.
Are you pouting now?
You don't believe me anyway.
I believe you.
Why?
You are a guy who
has a pampered guy look,
is self-centered,
has low tolerance,
and likes to argue a point to death.
So that is how I am
in your heart.
But you love and hate frankly.
When you like someone,
you just like this person.
When you hate someone, you just hate.
You like gossiping about other
people in front of them
and talking bad behind them,
but you would never
scheme or try to set anyone up.
You will not and
you don't like to bother
to do anything like that.
It seems like you do
know something about me.
Otherwise?
Do you think that the time we
spent together was all for nothing?
Also, don't forget.
We are teammates.
How would I not trust my own teammate,
but to trust a stranger?
Then,
about what he said,
do you actually have no feeling at all?
To be honest,
it is impossible to not
have any feeling.
You...
At first,
I thought it was just a bad fate.
But soon I realized that
he was just making the buzz
and trying to take the lead.
People are
emotional animals
who can easily fall into the
emotion traps set up by others
and lose what they've
been holding on to.
In this way,
people's standpoints are easily changed.
So he could achieve what he wanted.
Seems like you are not stupid.
Do you actually think that
everyone is like you?
Right.
I'm the stupidest person.
Well, just stop getting mad
at Xiao Ai and Song Che.
They've been emotionally controlled
by Lu Feibai unconsciously.
Their thoughts have been changed
without knowing it.
Although I couldn't follow,
I can forgive them
because of what you said.
Let's get down to business.
As far as you're concerned,
how is it possible for
an underground workshop
to transfer such large amount of stuff
within one day?
I've checked carefully.
This is the only entrance
to the secret path.
Then how did they
transfer all these stuff during the day
without any of us knowing it?
Don't tell me that...
Can it be that...
- they have never been transferred out.
This Murong Chen is going too far.
Brother Lu,
don't mind it.
It's fine.
I'll go get the
medicinal liquor for you.
Thank you so much.
Sorry, Landlord Lu.
I was acting recklessly.
It's OK.
It's just a little misunderstanding.
I didn't mind it.
I thought Childe Lu wanted
to offer us drinks.
I will suit myself then.
Childe Lu,
don't you want to share
good liquor with us?
How come?
I just want to introduce
some good liquor to you.
I know a lot about liquor.
Don't bother.
I can do it myself.
Murong Chen,
you are so unabashed.
How can you still drink his liquor?
Song Che.
This...
This is the blood night-blooming cereus.
It's the fake one.
Lu Feibai,
what else do you want to say?
I have nothing to say.
Holy shit.
Lu Feibai,
you are the sanctimonious liar.
Are you behind
all those
messed up things in the world?
Say it.
Where is the real
blood night-blooming cereus?
I don't know.
I have never
seen the real one.
You are a liar.
It doesn't make sense
that a person who makes
fake blood night-blooming cereus
has never seen the real one.
Mengmeng,
there's no use to say more.
I will chop his hands and feet off
and make him tell the truth.
Stop it.
Don't go that far.
He should do it.
You should do it.
I chop...
Don't. I will tell the truth.
About half a year ago,
there was a customer called Mr. Xi
who gave me a blueprint
and placed a huge order
to make me mass-produce
the fake blood night-blooming cereus.
I'm just a businessman.
I will do whatever
the customer asks for.
As for the buyers of the fake flowers,
I have no idea.
Mr. Xi?
Who is Mr. Xi?
How old is he?
How does he look like?
I don't know.
He said that he doesn't know.
I chop...
Mr. Xi has only been here three times.
One time for placing the order,
one time for checking the goods,
and the last time for re-ordering.
He wears black outfit and bamboo hat
every time he visits.
So I've never seen his face.
The only thing I know is that
he sounds like in the 40s.
I don't know anything other than that.
Then try to remember more clearly.
What other features does he have?
There's a special floral smell on him.
It smelt like sophora flower.
Sophora flower?
Chang Kong.
Is it this smell?
Yes.
This is it.
Sophora flower
is the most famous flower in Hui Zhou.
Hui Zhou?
That means that...
Exactly.
Cang Yun Kingdom.
Hui Zhou.
(Egret Villa to Hui Zhou)
(Hui Zhou)
Hui Zhou,
I'm here.
This is Cang Yun Kingdom.
Isn't it pretty?
Well, it's almost as pretty as Ruo Shui.
(We are finally sending
Murong Chen away soon.)
Song Che.
Why are you laughing so wildly?
Nothing.
As soon as I think about that
we are going to solve a
legendary case,
I cannot help feeling happy.
That is so pretty.
Yes.
Go.
(Hui Zhou Street)
Get off my way.
Get off my way now.
(Ye Fei'er)
Ignorant people!
Get off right now.
How dare you catch my whip?
You ignorant unruly people!
Oh no. These two people
are about to fight.
You do have some skills.
You hurt people on the street
and commit crime on a horseback.
Let me teach you a lesson.
You lawless shrew.
Stop it.
(Sai Pan'an)
Let's not waste time on this
over our business.
It's none of your business.
Go away.
Zhe Xiang,
let's stop it.
Hit her.
Stop eating.
What does it have
anything to do with you?
I thought that
women in Ruo Shui Kingdom
are already mighty enough.
I didn't expect that
the women at Cang Yun Kingdom
are even more mighty.
You are wrong about it.
It's rare to see women like this.
Chang Kong.
The women in Cang Yun
Kingdom are like water...
Don't you dare. Don't you dare. Tell me
do you dare to do it again?
Dare to do it again...
No. No. No. I don't dare to do it again.
Don't you dare. Don't you dare.
I really won't.
Like water?
Like water that submerges the mountain.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪