[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 4]
You are awake!
Have a drink?
No!
Don't be nervous,
you don't need to take the responsibility.
Why should I take the responsibility?
Normally speaking,
I wouldn't touch you at all.
What do you want?
Why are you so nervous?
I will let you go.
We are adults,
and everything we did was out of passion.
So I won't blame you.
Su Bei,
what are you plotting?
I'm tired,
and I want to get some sleep.
If you don't want to go now,
you can also continue to sleep here.
Have you really regarded yourself
as my wife?
Am I not?
I warn you!
Don't fancy me.
You're just my nominal wife.
I can still get rid of you
even you slept with me.
You don't need to stress that again.
I have kept it in mind.
That's great.
I don't want to embarrass you.
So,
don't conduct shameful behaviors.
Do you know that I may lose the whole Eminence
just because of what you did.
You don't believe me？
It doesn't matter whether I believe you or not.
You need to make the public and the media
believe you.
If you leave now,
you can at least reserve some dignity.
I'm no longer the weak Su Bei
seven years ago.
The boss gave you this.
[Five hundred thousand cash check]
Do keep the secret!
You should know what to say
and what not to say.
You know my boss has a bad temper.
I get it, get it!
Since we have common interests!
[Five hundred thousand cash check]
It will do no good to me
if something bad happens to him.
I will firmly keep the secret.
And I'm gonna "forget" all of it.
Come!
Wait!
Tell me,
am I so handsome
that both men and gods would be jealous of me?
Yes, you are
not only handsome but also rich.
Both men and women would be jealous
of what you own.
That makes sense.
Su Bei not only wants my money
but also me.
What happened?
You slept with her?
That was because I drank too much.
What?
Did she take the first step?
No,
it definitely was me.
Impossible.
I know that
you can't drink much.
You can be drunk easily.
Then you sleep like a dead pig.
So I always have to send you...
Go to put the financial reports
and project proposals from 2014 to 2019
in order.
Me?
You can't take revenge on me through work.
Only one minute left for you.
Fifty nine,
fifty eight,
fifty seven,
fifty six...
What the...
What?
Are you really a woman?
Do you need to find out the truth yourself?
You...
Aren't you shameful for saying something like this?
What are you doing?
I'm just helping you pick up documents.
Are you afraid of me?
Of course not.
Which department do you work in?
You want to know something about me?
I'm the assistant of Annie, President of
the Eminence Starlight Agency.
My name is Ye Ting.
You want my Wechat number?
Don't you know the rules of our company?
Go to register at the human resources office,
and then you need to be trained for a week.
Hello.
I have found the documents.
Just give me five minutes,
or three minutes!
I'll be there right away.
Asking me to work overtime
so urgently.
But I have no interest
in spending the night with him.
Have you heard what I told you?
SA Yun, if you want to
arrange my work,
please report it to Annie first.
A crooked stick
will have a crooked shadow.
I‘d better stay out of this.
Work overtime?
[The Gu's Group]
Mr. Gu, are you still having a headache?
Coco,
the skin of your hands feels so smooth.
Don't make fun of me.
Come in!
Mr. Gu,
I've signed our endorsement contract
with the Eminence Starlight,
please have a look at it.
What Eminence Starlight?
How dare you sign the contract?
Are you an idiot?
Are you?
Are you happy when seeing me
be scolded by my dad the other day?
Now my credit cards have been suspended！
Are you satisfied?
You know perfectly that
Su Bei was setting a trap for me.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Gu Yan!
You know what.
You're a just a damn bastard!
No matter how I irritate him,
the Gu's Group still has nothing to do with you.
Get out of here!
Don't bother me anymore.
Mr. Gu,
don't forget your appointment
with Mr. Xian and Mr. Liu of Ji Cheng
to play golf.
Chairman let me tell you
to behave modestly.
Are you done?
I don't need you to tell me what to do.
Even about win or losing.
Get out of here!
Get out!
[The Gu's Group]
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me, do you have an appointment?
I'm Annie from the Eminence Starlight.
I want to see Mr. Gu.
Sorry,
Mr. Gu is having a meeting.
Well.
How long will the meeting last?
I'm not sure about it.
It doesn't matter, I can wait for him.
Okay, this way please.
I'm at the Gu's Group. What's the matter?
I heard that
Lu Nan is going to work overtime tonight.
It seems that he has a lot of work to do.
Okay, I see.
Annie, you're still here!
I'm about to leave.
I heard that you had waited here,
drinking coffee for a whole day.
I should have been in Mr. Gu's office
to get some fresh ground coffee.
Unfortunately, he seems to be busy today.
So I shouldn't have come today.
Sorry.
Our cooperation may
need further negotiation.
Never mind.
Every cooperation is reached
through negotiation, disagreement and re-negotiation.
That's the normality.
I'm afraid that it's not that simple.
I understand.
You have a high standard when selecting partners.
But I think the high standard
can be either a barrier
or an open door
if you can reach it.
Am I right?
Okay,
since you have prepared
to open the door,
I shall wait to see it.
It's late.
Tomorrow,
I need to go to the eastern suburb
with Mr. Gu to play golf.
I need to go home and have some rest now.
Let's have a raincheck.
Okay,
thank you.
You are welcome.
See you then.
Eastern suburb!
12350.
Verification failed.
I didn't expect that I could see you to be crazy
in my whole life.
It's so nice of you to cancel my overtime work.
You really don't want to have some liquor?
You think I have the time?
A saying goes that
only when the woman gets drunk
can the man get the opportunity to approach her.
I'm looking out for your best interests.
I think you are not busy enough.
I should give you more work to do.
Have you got the information I want?
I'm still investigating.
Can't you be Su Bei's spy?
I'm only loyal to you,
I promise.
I only serve you.
Then I think you lack work ability.
And you can't work efficiently.
Maybe
I should hire a new special assistant.
You don't need to worry about it.
Just have a good rest after work.
I'll get the things done,
and make sure that you know clearly
about everything.
Verification failed.
It's dawn!
Just four o'clock, it is early.
No,
today is May twentieth,
[the day for expressing "I love you"]
so there must be many people
registering for marriage.
We have to get to the civil affairs bureau early.
But I still want to sleep for five more minutes.
It doesn't matter.
I can hold you in my arms and get you there.
You can just continue to sleep.
Come!
Wedding anniversary.
Verification passed.
Su Bei!
Where is she?
Why are you in my room?
There's no hot water in my room.
So I came to your room for a shower.
Then you even borrowed my shirt to wear?
I forgot to take mine.
I'll wash the shirt
and give it back to you tomorrow.
Just throw it away.
I don't wear shirts that are worn by others.
But,
it's a pity.
I like this shirt.
Mrs. Su,
being wet at night in my room,
are you so eager to attract my attention?
It's all in your head.
I just feel hot after taking the shower.
No matter what you do,
your efforts will be in vain.
I warn you,
don't enter my room anymore
without my permission.
It was just an accident.
Don't take it so seriously.
Otherwise,
you're sure to lose, Mr. Lu.
[Color may be very simple.]
By the way,
I'm going to talk about the endorsement
with Mr. Gu tomorrow...
Stop here!
Don't talk about work at home, thanks!
I didn't expect that
you can read when the book is upside down.
[Panda Nana: gaining 60-million-yuan
series-A funding]
Yun Fan,
get someone to install surveillance cameras
at every corner in my house tomorrow morning.
Don't you know how to play golf?
You can't even strike a ball into the hole.
Useless！
Brother, Dad told us
to be modest in front of Mr. Xian et al.
The old man is so bothersome.
I can't even enjoy playing golf.
It's even a bummer to win a game.
Gu,
you're no good at golf.
We beat you by two putts.
You're a senior, Mr. Xian.
It'll be embarrassing if I win.
You mean
you were not doing your best?
I'm flattered, Mr Xian.
We've tried our best
to win this round.
We just don't have the talent.
Please give ground to us in the next round.
You should've said so sooner.
We'll go easy on the next one.
Or you may think we bully young people like you.
Gu Yan.
You're really a flatterer.
They say dad brought you home
and raised you as a dog,
since you're so docile.
Mr. Gu, you played well.
It doesn't help the situation.
You just narrowly lost the game.
All my skills went to waste.
It's your turn, Gu.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Brother,
you know I'm never as good as you.
Young man,
don't force yourself.
Who the hell you think you are, old man?
You really think I can't beat you?
Hurry up. We have to beat him today.
Why do you always drop the ball at a critical moment?
You are useless.
Mr. Gu,
need any help?
From you?
Don't underestimate me, Mr. Gu.
If I win,
let's sign the contract.
No problem.
It's a deal.
Awesome.
Interesting.
How's that, Mr. Gu? I'm not bad, am I?
Not too bad.
Mr. Xian, Mr. Liu.
Sorry for that.
That was a good one.
You are flattering me, Mr. Gu.
We'll have good cooperation in the future.
You ruined my big deal,
and you want to cooperate with me?
Zhao Long.
Pay her.
Give her the highest level of sparring pay.
Yes.
Mr. Gu.
It's not appropriate, is it?
Mrs. Lu.
You are just not sophisticated enough to trick me.
[Colored Silk House]
Here's all the information you asked for.
[Personal Information]
[Induced abortion operation]
Induced abortion operation?
How did this happen?
When we searched Ms. Su's medical records,
we found a file in a private hospital showed that
Ms. Su had had an abortion
eight months after she came to Italy.
The fetus was nine weeks old.
Who's the father?
We didn't get that information.
Ms. Su had contact with many male friends
and staff at that time.
And it's been a long time,
so some of the information is hard to find.
I see.
Don’t tell anyone
about this.
I won't.
Why are you absent-minded?
I cracked the code of Lu Nan's safe.
Did you find the fragrance brocade?
No.
He came back
before I could open it.
Then why are you upset?
The combination to the safe
is the date of our wedding anniversary.
Didn't he forget about you?
How could he
remember your anniversary?
If you can't figure it out, forget it.
Here.
This is the project investment information
during Gu Chengze's tenure as president of Gu's Group
you asked me to collect.
[Equity Interest Pledge Agreement]
[Pledgor: Gu Chengze]
It seems that Gu's group has some infighting.
I heard that Mr. Gu
is meeting my sister tonight.
I'll join in the fun.
♫ Will we meet again? ♫
Bravo!
- Bravo!
Mr. Gu.
Let's have a toast to Mr. Gu.
Here, com on.
Here, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu.
You sang beautifully just now.
Well…
Just let me endorse Kong.
Okay,
but I can't give the job to you for nothing.
Mr. Gu, Su Bei always bullys me.
If you don't help me,
then I'm not gonna be able to stay in Eminence.
You can turn to me then.
I'm always tender to women.
Then that's a deal.
Sorry, I'm late.
Why are you here?
Didn't you ask me to meet with Mr. Gu?
I didn't.
She had the gall to show up.
I was just going to compliment you
for knowing I like to deal with beautiful women,
and asking your sister to join me.
She's not my sister.
Now that you're here, come and sit down.
We all have different destinies.
We have the same father, but we live different lives.
I am the president of the Gu's Group.
But look at Gu Yan.
He's just a sidekick.
You're right.
But Manni,
why can't you beat Su Bei?
In terms of appearance, you are even.
But in terms of intelligence,
you're not even as good as Su Bei's little finger.
The endorsement is very important.
I'm a little worried about giving the job to you.
What?
But Mr. Gu...
Didn't you just promise me
the endorsement of Kong?
Verbal promises do not have the force of law.
You have to sign a contract.
That makes sense.
Why do you have to vie with me, Su Bei?
What do you mean?
Mr. Gu has his own judgment.
How come I vie with you for the job?
You think Mr. Gu is stupid
or incompetent?
You…
No...
That's not what I meant.
Su…
Su Bei's trying to drive a wedge
between us.
There's nothing between us.
I always
take the side of my friend.
This is the way I am.
I can only do business with you if we're friends.
Then I'd like
to be your friend.
I have a big show tomorrow, Mr. Gu.
My face will swell if I drink too much.
That won't be good.
Yeah.
I don't like making people do things they don't like.
If you think the big show is so important,
you can forget about the endorsement.
Su Bei,
the endorsement is yours now.
Thank you then.
No...Mr. Gu...
That's not what I meant.
Manni, don't put Mr. Gu in an embarrassing position.
Su Bei, you’ve gone too far.
It's quite a drama.
Sorry for that.
Excuse me for disciplining the subordinate.
Mr. Gu,
when should we sign the contract?
What contract?
You sisters are stupid.
Can't you see I was tricking you?
So Mr. Gu played another trick, huh?
It’s all right.
I have a very nice present for you.
Look.
It’s a surprise.
[Equity Interest Pledge Agreement]
[Pledgor: Gu Chengze]
Get out of here.
Go.
Are you ready to sign the contract now?
I can sign it.
But you need to keep your mouth shut.
You may rest assured.
I still have
work ethic.
Thank you.
Su Bei.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. My feet hurt a little bit.
Let's go. I'll get you to the hospital.
Do you want me to walk you in?
Don’t bother. I can do this myself.
Thank you for your help today.
I was able to get the information that
Gu Chengze pledged the shares as security for a loan,
thanks to you.
I'll always remember with gratitude
the favor you did me.
You know it was me?
There's no way anyone in my company
could have access to such confidential information,
except some insiders.
But you're the only one who knows Gu Chengze so well
and is willing to help me.
I just did
what I think is best
for my brother and Gu's Group.
I couldn't talk my brother out of certain things,
so I had to find another way to deal with it.
After all, you knew
my position in the Gu family.
It's all right. So did I.
In that case,
aren't we
in the same boat?
Can I be your friend?
You are my friend.
Be careful.
Go.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to take back what I just said.
I wonder if Mr. Gu
would walk me in.
My pleasure.
Go.
Be careful.
Do you mind?
I'm honored.
Su Bei.
Sweetheart.
Annie hurt her leg. So I brought her back.
Don't bother.
Wait.
It's prescribed by the hospital.
Apply it on her when you get back home.
You don't need to worry about my wife.
Su Bei.
I want you to remember you are my wife
before you do anything.
I think someone told me
we were married in name only.
We're still married.
So you admit I'm your wife?
Be serious.
I want you to
avoid any physical contact with any other man.
You’re being jealous.
Jealous?
I just don't want to be embarrassed
You like me.
I like you?
Marrying you is the most ridiculous thing
I've ever done in my life.
Since you don't like me,
don't try to manipulate me.
I'm not your personal property.
I am a person who can think independently!
Think independently?
You mean evil thoughts.
I know
why you moved here.
Stop trying to get in my room.
I already have the cameras installed
in my house.
If you dare to do that again,
it's gonna be more than just throwing you out of the house.
You sent me to Italy seven years ago.
Where do you want to send me now?
Jail?
Su Bei.
Don't put me to the limits.
Not divorcing you
is the best I can do.
Whatever you want from me,
I'm not gonna let you get it.