[English subtitles are available]
Your Highness,
the Royal Army is ready.
We can set off anytime.
Wait for a bit longer.
Yes.
Your Highness, it's morning now.
Shall we leave?
Give me another minute.
Whom is His Highness waiting for?
It has been four hours already.
His Highness must be
waiting for his lover.
That makes sense.
No one knows how long it takes
before he can come back and see her again.
It's worth waiting.
I wonder
what this girl looks like.
Let's go!
Yi, what are you thinking?
I'm thinking of Teng.
Teng,
we will break through the Redbud Pass
and destroy the Northland's army this time.
Yi,
there are no winners on the battlefield.
Because whoever wins
also pays a terrible price.
As the crowned prince,
I want to make sure
the world is free of war
and all people can live in peace.
Cheers!
I overestimated the Northland's army.
They were so easily defeated
and had to retreat.
Should we attack the Redbud Pass tomorrow
while our morale is still high
and get them out of the Pass once for all?
Da,
the Redbud Pass is easy to defend
but hard to attack.
I'm afraid that things can't be this easy.
I've already sent scouts to the Pass.
Shall we wait for a few more days?
We can make our plan
after army provisions led by Xiu arrive.
Yi, you're being overly cautious.
The Northland's army suffered heavy losses
and had to run back to the Pass.
If we don't start the attack soon,
are we giving them time to recover?
I know you want to win,
but we can't make a move
without careful thought.
The Redbud Pass is full of secret passages.
It's extremely dangerous.
Even Teng...
I'm not Teng!
We are in a different situation now.
Yi, don't forget
who the Commander is.
Da...
I agree with the Commander.
We will be running out of food soon.
If we wait any longer,
we'll be giving our enemy time to rest.
If we want to fight,
we need to do it fast.
I don't think so!
All of our soldiers
are suffering from frostbite.
We shouldn't act rashly.
Know yourself as well as your enemy.
We shouldn't make decisions
until the scouts come back
with information about the Pass.
Do you know that speed is everything?
But we can't put our soldiers' lives
at risk!
Enough!
Dismissed.
Yes, Commander.
The shadow of geese reflected in the water
and the plum flowers withered.
There is nothing around
except for the flying snow,
making the night as clear as day.
Si Yan,
are we
looking at the same moon?
Qi Yi went to the front.
Jack got angry and refused to come out.
Even Tong Rui went back to the Min Mansion.
Did she go to the Min Mansion
or did she finish her task
and go back home?
It seems that
I'm the only one left here.
Don't just focus on building your muscle.
You can't work out on an empty stomach.
Have some rest.
I can't.
I won't eat.
I was not strong enough.
That's why His Highness didn't select me.
Or,
I would be in the army
with His Highness
and fight the enemy.
Little Wan!
Help! Mouse!
Where is the mouse?
Help me!
I will protect you!
You will be alright!
Si Yan.
Si Yan!
What are you doing here?
Such a coward!
How can you fight the enemy?
These carbohydrates are not allowed
while building your muscle.
Let me help you with this.
Tangier made this for me.
Give it back.
Si Yan, look what you did.
What's wrong?
It's so...
so delicious.
Aren't you overreacting?
It occurs to me that,
while we are having delicious food here,
the Northland
is cold
and is short of food and clothing.
I wonder if His Highness has enough food
and stays warm.
His hands got serious frostbite
the last time he came back from the Northland.
I wonder if everything goes well with them.
Si Yan,
should we go to the temple some time,
burn the incense,
and pray for all East City's soldiers
to come back safely?
I won't join you.
I don't have these superstitious beliefs.
Does the war in the game
really cause death?
Dear Bodhisattva,
please make sure Qi Yi's safe
and let him come back soon.
Watch out, my lady.
No worries.
I'm fine.
I've been anxious these days.
I feel better
being here.
My lady,
don't worry.
My lady.
Dear Bodhisattva,
I've been fasting and chanting these years.
I only wish for
peace in the world,
but now
the East City is at war again
and Yi went to the Northland.
I don't expect him
to make achievements in war.
I only want him to return safely.
My lady,
didn't His Highness say that
everything is alright in his letter?
Don't worry too much about him.
That's exactly what I'm worried about.
He always reports good news
rather than bad ones.
Did he have frostbite again?
Frostbite?
It breaks my heart when I think of this.
They have doctors there.
Don't worry.
I'm sure he will take care of himself.
Dear Bodhisattva,
please let my son return safely.
He can do whatever he wants.
He can marry whomever he likes.
Don't waste time on this.
The cream for frostbite
can't be made within one or two days.
Indeed. Do you see how much smoke there is?
Why is it burnt again?
This doesn't make sense.
Si Yan,
you don't even control the heat.
Of course, it was burnt!
Stay away if you don't want to help.
Leave me alone.
You can make jokes about anything,
but this is about the war.
It's about human lives.
We have to take it seriously.
Why are you doing this?
My elder brother is also in the front.
I don't want people
to make jokes about this.
Li,
people from the East City
killed your father.
You must find the heartbreak grass recipe,
throw the East City into chaos,
and revenge for your father.
You're the descendant of the Yun family.
You need to shoulder your responsibility.
Yun Li,
are all provisions loaded?
We're putting extra men on it.
The provisions
are urgently needed this time.
I don't know if we can make it in time.
Use the waterway.
I'm sure we can.
Look at this.
The mountain roads in the Northland
are rugged and full of bandits,
but the river is slow-moving.
We can save a lot of time.
Your Highness, bad news.
The provision boats overturned!
Get the horse ready.
Your Highness.
What happened?
How could the boats
suddenly overturn?
I'm new here.
It was my first time
to escort the provisions.
Yesterday...
Manager Ruan,
there aren't any joiners
to reinforce the boats.
The boats will easily leak.
I asked you to load the provisions.
There's no time for that nonsense!
Move!
My family has been repairing boats
for generations.
That's why I...
Enough!
I think you're just lazy!
Just leave
if you don't want to work!
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't given up so easily,
this wouldn't have happened.
Where is Manager Ruan?
I...I have no idea.
Make sure he receives treatment.
Yes.
Your Highness, we're in trouble.
The granary is on fire.
Let's go!
The boats overturned
and the granary was on fire.
We can only get food from other places.
It will take
at least several months to arrive here
with such a great amount of food,
not to mention sending it to the north.
Our soldiers won't make it till that time.
The only solution we have now
is to borrow food from our people.
We can't.
We had several floods these years.
People already had a poor harvest.
We can't give them more burden.
Then what should we do?
You can start with the food
reserved by the noble and the rich.
Dismissed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Those people are cunning.
How can we persuade them to donate food?
Exactly.
Here's the order from the king.
The war in the Northland is urgent.
Our soldiers are out of provisions.
The nobles and wealthy merchants
are hereby ordered to donate food
and set an example for everyone.
Everyone is encouraged
to show their support to our army.
Ms. Qin arrives!
Ms. Min arrives!
This way.
The wife of the minister arrives!
I'm sure that
all the beautiful ladies here,
including sisters, aunties, and grannies,
are quite wealthy.
However,
no money is needed today.
We only want food.
Food?
If you don't have a food reserve
in your house,
I'm afraid you won't be able to join
this charity auction.
This is the time
to show your connections and abilities.
Please encourage people you know
to help and to support
our soldiers
who fight in the front!
Agreed!
The East Mansion
collaborated with Forever Young
and made this VIP makeup set.
They were customized to your skin type.
It has everything you need,
from skincare products
to makeup products.
I'm sure you will look ten years younger
after using them.
Wait, I'm wrong.
You will look like you're eighteen!
We only have a limited number of products.
Only the most important people
can have them.
There are only ten of these.
Ten!
People with a higher price take them home.
Only ten?
We have to bid for them?
I also invited a special guest here
to show you our products.
Let's give him a round of applause!
Great!
Prince Bao! He is so handsome!
Prince Bao!
Easy.
Just do what I taught you.
You can do this.
Si Yan,
I don't think I can.
Why?
Even if you don't trust yourself,
you have to trust a beauty blogger.
Who?
Never mind. Let's get started.
Hurry.
Oh my god!
Girls, here we go!
This is the Palace Makeup Service‘s
limited edition product,
joined colors floral blush.
There are five different colors.
Five colors!
Look at this color.
If you wear this,
your cheek will be
as pink as a juicy peach.
What are you waiting for?
Buy it!
1,400 lbs of grain.
2,800!
7,000!
Three,
two,
one.
Sold!
Joined colors floral blush for Ms. Min!
Congratulations!
It's getting more and more competitive now.
This is the Beauty of Moment shadow palette.
1,400 lbs of grain to start!
Only 1,400?
Oh No!
You...you...
you missed a zero.
I missed a zero?
That's fine.
I already said 1,400.
1,400 it is then.
We can't do 1,400.
It's too cheap.
We'll be at a great loss.
Your Highness,
they are my important guests.
Can you do me a favor
and start with 1,400?
What do you say?
She's right!
Yes.
1,400 is not possible.
I can sell one or two sets at this price,
but they want fifty of this.
Fifty?
Such a great amount!
I can't imagine how much money we will lose.
No, I can't do this.
Don't be so stingy.
Why are we making these makeup products?
On a narrow scale,
we want our guests to be happy.
But on a larger scale,
it shows the Makeup Service's support
to soldiers who protect our country.
Am I right?
Yes.
I already said 1,400.
1,400 it is then!
Let's start the bid.
I want ten sets.
Twenty!
I'll take all of them.
How can you buy all of them?
There are so many left.
How dare you buy them all?
Calm down, everyone.
I can assure you that
you'll get as many as you want.
I want it as well.
Me too!
Count me in!
Your Highness.
Any news?
It's hard to locate the sinking boats.
We didn't find the provisions.
Any news from the East Mansion?
How can they get enough food
within such a little amount of time?
If we don't do anything,
I'm afraid that
soldiers in the front
won't survive any longer.
Your Highness, look!
We've got provisions!
Si Yan.
You killed our wolf god.
We will offer you as a sacrifice
to the wolf god
for success against the East City!
Sacrifice!
Our army is bearing down upon the border.
Even the wolf god can't save you.
Let me go!
I can ask the East City's army to retreat!
Today,
you will be the human sacrifice
for the wolf god!
Wait!
My lady,
you can't go to the Northland alone.
I've heard that
the King of the Northland keeps a leading wolf.
It is all white
and very smart.
I wonder
if it's true.
I've heard that
there is a mythical beast in the Northland,
a leading wolf.
What?
Do you want to see it?
You?
I can't,
but I know a man who can.
Who?
Your Majesty, this woman is very cunning.
We can't trust her.
I'm telling you the truth!
All we do is wait.
How long should we wait?
Where is Prince Yi?
He left early this morning.
Your Highness.
Where is Yi?
He is the Vice Commander.
How could he leave at this critical moment?
Please calm down, Commander.
The scouts we sent to the Pass
all disappeared.
The Vice Commander thought
there might be traps.
So he took some people to the Pass.
He especially mentioned that
we should stay put
until he comes back.
How can you
let the Vice Commander eat this?
He asked to eat the soldier's meal himself.
Whoever lies to him
will be punished.
We received a letter!
Where is it from?
The envoy from the Northland sent this.
They're struggling for nothing.
What tricks are they playing?
From this moment,
I'm yours.
This token represents me.
We'll never be apart anymore.
Does this token look familiar to you?
Come to the Blackwater Valley
if you want to see her.
Get the horse ready.
Yes.
Split up!
Figure out how they deploy their troops
and meet at the gate after midnight.
Brother,
do you think the heavenly army's legend
in the Pass is true?
The Northland's Commander Wei Xuan
just succeeded to the throne.
Although the city
has been in lockdown for seven days,
they are still able to fight
and they have continuous food
and human supply
delivered here.
I think there should be a secret passage
to the Northland's military camps.
Let's split up and search for it.
Meet here
four hours later.
Scouts! Keep them alive!
Yi,
I found the secret passage!
It's under the water prison at the gate.
We don't have time for it today.
Let's get out first!
Catch them!
We need to get into the water prison.
Don't you really believe that
a token is enough
for the Prince Da
to risk his life for me?
Don't be stupid.
That's not possible.
That's the prince token.
You're really important to him.
You should wish that he will come here.
If he won't come here,
I will feed those wolves with you.
However,
if he does risk his life for a woman,
I will look down on him.
Commander, this is clearly a trap.
You shouldn't go here.
Since no one comes here to save you,
you're useless to us now.
Take her to the wolves
and feed them.
Commander!
I have to go there.
This is the order.
Wait.
Let her go! I'm here!
Wait!
Qi Da!
Tell the Commander
that we already had enough information.
Send the troops as soon as possible.
Yes.
Did we receive news from the East City?
Cream for frostbite.
Give this to the doctors
and ask them to make the same set.
Yes.
I think of you.
I miss you.
I love you.
So mushy.
If he doesn't see this, then that's it!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, bad news!
The Northland
sent us a letter of surrender.
They...
they caught the Commander.
Who do they think they are?
The East City's Commander
was easily caught by me.
Let's drink!
Your Majesty, you're wise!
You didn't keep your promise!
You promised to let me go,
but you prisoned me again.
Why did you do this?
Let her go then.
We have Qi Da in our hands.
I guess she won't just run away.
Am I right?
You really helped me this time.
Here's to you!
I will kill Qi Da
to worship the wolf god
after the East City surrenders tomorrow.
We can take our time to catch up then.
You are so
short-sighted.
What do you have to say?
Do you really think that
catching Qi Da will solve everything?
I'm afraid that
it's too early for you to celebrate.
Why?
I didn't finish my words last time.
The man I was talking about
was not Qi Da.
The East City's army has another mainstay.
He is the one
that you should be worried about.
Do you mean Qi Yi?
That's right.
Prince Yi is better in brains and martial arts
compared with Prince Da.
Apart from that,
Prince Yi is the First Lady's son.
Without Prince Da,
it's only a matter of time
before Prince Yi becomes the king.
Several years ago,
you killed Prince Teng
during the fight between the two countries.
Prince Yi will be your greatest threat
if he succeeds to the throne.
I assume that
you don't want to see this happen.
Go on.
Why not let Prince Yi replace Prince Da?
If you have Prince Yi with you,
you can ask as much territory
and war indemnity as you wish.
Also,
Prince Da will appreciate your help.
If he succeeds to the throne,
he won't forget the person who helps him.
The East City and the Northland
can be allies someday.
Two birds with one stone.
You're beating around the bush.
Don't you want me
to focus on Qi Yi
so that you can save your lover?
But you're right
about Qi Yi.
He weighs much more
than a few cities and money.
If I have him,
I can have two discussions
on the compensation.
So you mean...
you're not the only one
who wants to make use of Qi Yi.
I've said that you helped me!
I have to treat you well.
Give her two maids
to take care of her.
Yes.
Thank you.
Your Majesty,
are you going to exchange prisoners
as she said?
What she said is right.
Qi Yi
is the real threat to me.
If he becomes the king,
he won't forgive me
for the things I have done.
Your Majesty,
will Qi Yi come here?
I've heard that
those two are fighting
for the crowned prince's position.
If this is not Qi Yi,
I won't take the risk.
Qi Yi
is like his brother Qi Teng.
They care more about camaraderie
than anything.
Hurry!
Emergency!
Prince Yi is in danger!
Prince Yi?
Did you hear the news?
In order to save Prince Da,
Prince Yi agreed to be
the Northland's prisoner.
Qi Yi will die.
You can't change this.
What kind of characters
can't even survive the second level?
Like bosses in the basic levels,
Miss Si Yan.
Also, monsters in those role-play games.
I have to find ways to save Qi Yi.
Luna, come out.
I know you're secretly watching me.
Come out!
The stupid game is crashed.
I can't go to the Northland.
What is this place?
I need to restart the system
and unlock the rest of the map.
If the master hadn't asked me
to keep you alive,
I would have killed you,
an idiot who failed the task several times.
Tell me,
why do you want to meet me here?
It's hard to take action
when the East City's filled with people.
I could only win Qi Yi's trust first.
This is a precious opportunity.
I will kill Qi YI in the Northland
without raising any attention
to show my loyalty.
Please give me another chance.
Isn't this game too intelligent?
Everything is back to normal
once I said I would kill Qi Yi.
Problems will be solved in the end.
I need to see Qi Yi first.