♪You're my girl♪
♪You're the loveliest in this world♪
♪I'm confessing my love to you♪
♪Giving you all my love♪
♪You're my girl♪
♪You're my cute little goddess♪
♪You are the one, the one I want♪
♪Forever mine, mine♪
♪You're the cutest, pretty girl♪
♪I just want to hold your hand♪
♪I've written too many love songs♪
♪No amount of lyrics I can think of♪
♪can describe how I feel♪
♪You know, hey girl♪
♪I'm not being ridiculous♪
♪Seeing you happy is enough for me♪
♪I just want to tell you♪
♪I love you so♪
♪Shooting out my love, "Biu, biu, biu!"♪
♪You're my girl♪
♪You're the loveliest in this world♪
♪I'm confessing my love to you♪
♪Giving you all my love♪
♪You're my girl♪
♪You're my cute little goddess♪
♪You are the one, the one I want♪
♪Forever mine, mine♪
♪I like it when♪
♪you squint and giggle as you look at me♪
♪you purse your lips when you're shy♪
♪I like it when♪
♪you hug me♪
♪That's the you that I like♪
♪Because it's you, I like everything about you♪
[Assistant of Superstar]
[Episode 10]
Why are you so quiet?
Nervous?
Okay.
Let me help you.
Yao Yao and I have been good friends
for almost four years since our freshman year.
Although some unpleasant things
happened between us recently,
I still hope
that you and I
can continue to be best friends.
However,
why did you approach Yin Jiu behind my back
even though you know he is my boyfriend?
(No way.)
(She even steals her bestie's boyfriend.)
She looks like a decent person,
yet she did something so shameless.
She even has the cheek
to attend the birthday party.
Shame on her.
Stealing her bestie's boyfriend.
That's disgusting.
It's truly unfortunate
to have a friend like her.
Look at her.
She seems to have admitted it.
(Say something.)
Say something.
Is it true that only a girl who is not loved
will steal others' boyfriends?
You Xi.
Why didn't you call me when you are in need?
I...
Don't be afraid.
I am here.
Next,
let's move on to our next section.
I am today's special guest speaker.
Good evening, everyone.
What the heck.
Isn't that supposed to be me?
First of all,
♪No amount of thinking is going to help♪
I want to wish Miss Tong
a happy birthday,
and I hope that she could stay beautiful forever.
♪But three minutes later it all ebbs away♪
You said Yuchi Yao Yao stole your boyfriend.
But they were in a relationship
two years ago.
♪Yet enjoy being passive♪
You and Yin Jiu have only been together
for only a few months.
So everyone should know
who actually stole
the boyfriend from her friend.
No way.
It was her who stole her bestie's boyfriend.
♪In the age of sound and fury♪
I'd never expected that Miss Tong
would be such a bad person.
Shame on her.
♪The beat is restless and it's hard to think♪
Besides,
our protagonist Mr. Yin,
when you were cheating
with your girlfriend's bestie,
has it ever crossed your mind
that what you did
would ruin their friendship?
♪The days go by♪
You said no one would love Yuchi Yao Yao.
But I don't think so.
Yuchi Yao Yao is
innocent
and kind-hearted.
She'd never defend herself
even when she was wronged.
She is perfect except for
her low EQ.
In my view,
she is the girl that everyone loves.
She can stay up all night
to mend a blanket
that she thought was important to me.
Even though
the outcome isn't so great.
When I made mistakes,
she would criticize me
with no mercy.
Even little kids understand that.
Why don't you get it?
When I was sad,
she would stay by my side to comfort me.
Even though
she's pretty bad at it.
She could even
fight for me.
Even though
I was more worried that she would get hurt.
No, no.
No photos.
There's no need to take photos.
Actually, I've always wanted
to tell you something.
You Xi is out of his mind. Out of his mind.
Stop.
Stop. Stop him.
Stop him.
You must
suppress this news at all costs.
It's can't be publicized.
No headlines.
Or else we will be doomed!
Stay away from me!
You Xi,
this isn't over.
Mr. You,
you can let go now.
Let's...
Let's go home.
Or
if you want to go somewhere,
I...
I can go with you.
The amusement park?
Or the cinema?
Or...
Mr. You,
I want to take a walk alone.
you could go back first.
I want to stay alone.
Mr. You,
you will be cold.
No way.
I'm in good health.
Not cold.
Not at all.
Mr. You,
you've got a runny nose.
Yao Yao,
how did you get
enochlophobia?
[Philosophy and Culture of China]
[Academic Talk]
[Art Lecture]
Yuchi Yao Yao, you'll be next.
Please get ready.
Okay, right away.
Mom, where are you?
It's almost my turn.
Don't rush me.
I'll be there right after
I cross this intersection.
Mom.
If I hadn't asked my mom
to deliver my speech draft,
she'd be all right.
It's all my fault. My fault.
My...
It's all right.
It's all in the past now.
Actually...
I actually haven't finished my words
at the birthday party.
Do you want to hear it?
If you want to hear it,
I will tell you.
I know
it is not pleasant
to be my assistant.
I am strict
and always
boss you around.
If you really feel unfair,
you could be my...
be my girlfriend.
If so, I will spoil you
and I can also cook for you every day.
I'll do whatever you ask.
Isn't that a great deal?
Yi,
review the guest list for tonight,
and find out who brought the phone in
by checking the security footage.
We must do
whatever it takes
to delete all the photos.
Wu,
keep an eye on the news outlets.
If you see anyone trying to publish the news,
be sure to use all connections
to intercept it in advance.
(Okay.)
Jiu,
look into Weibo, Douban, Tianya, and other forums.
If there's a whiff of trouble,
nip it in the bud.
Qi,
Qi.
Maury,
bad news.
Mr. Tong wants to pull the plug.
The crew wants to take Yuxi out.
What?
You Xi,
you ruined the birthday party
of Mr. Tong's daughter.
They got annoyed
and told us they would
withdraw the capital if we don't get you out.
Is that all there is?
Yes.
That's fine.
I'm already done with this.
You Xi,
can't you see that it's a critical time?
Are you kidding me?
Not at all,
I'm really serious.
You...
Lower your voice.
If the little blockhead hears about that,
I...
Mr. You.
Da Zhuang.
You are awake.
Go brush your teeth and wash your face,
and get ready for breakfast.
I heard everything.
It's all my fault.
I'll go and apologize to Tong Jin.
Yes. Do it now.
Come back.
Who says it's your fault?
It doesn't matter.
I can't get you into trouble because of this.
I will talk to her.
Go now.
Come back.
You're not the one who got me into trouble.
I'm the one who scolded her.
What do you have to do with it?
You can't go without my permission.
Sit down.
Eat the noodles.
Have a try, I just learned it.
No, not in the mood. Put it away.
Tell Mr. Zhang,
I'll be at the office soon.
Maury, it's not Mr. Zhang.
It is the crew of The Founding
of the Three Kingdoms.
They said there is
something important to talk about.
They are so fast.
Follow my instructions.
Get the letter of termination ready in advance.
They are the ones who
will the cancel contract without cause.
It is their fault.
Maximize our interest
in the termination clause.
Try to recover the loss as much as possible.
Okay, Maury.
Look at that.
They are calling us.
What did I do in my previous life
to become your manager?
I'm leaving.
Enjoy your meal.
Take care, Da Zhuang.
[What happened yesterday was my fault.]
[Tong Jin, what happened yesterday was my fault.
Please don't be mad.]
What are you doing?
Mr. You.
Give it to me.
You still haven't blocked her yet?
And you even sent her this message.
"What happened yesterday was my fault."
"Please don't be mad."
Mr. You.
This is all my fault.
I'll apologize to Tong Jin,
and ask her to talk to her father.
Apologize to her?
Mr. You.
[You, the upstart fake bestie,
could only ask your father for help.]
[Shame on you. Just withdraw your capital.
I'm already done with that.]
[Don't let me see you again
or I'll scold you.]
[Tong Jin]
Apologize?
No way.
[Yao Yao]
You Xi.
Yuchi Yao Yao.
I'm not gonna let you two get away with this!
Mr. Cui.
We can end our contract,
but You Xi
didn't break any terms of the contract.
You are the ones who are trying
to cancel the contract without cause.
So...
[Records of the Three Kingdoms]
[Records of the Three Kingdoms,
Spring and Autumn Chronicles]
Mr. You.
Finally, I don't have to read books. That's great.
But you've been preparing
for this role for so long.
Now you have to give up.
I wanted to quit long ago.
Besides,
there are many roles for me.
They have to wait in line.
Coming.
Quick. Let me in.
Let me have some water first.
What happened?
What on earth is going on?
As soon as I arrived at the company,
I sensed hostility.
So I thought there
was definitely no goodwill coming from this.
Therefore,
I've made all the preparations
without any flaws.
Get to the point.
The point is
they won't terminate the contract with you.
Really, Da Zhuang?
What really happened?
Actually,
here's what happened.
You're the ones who
will cancel the contract without cause.
So...
Maury,
you get me wrong.
We come here
not to cancel the contract.
Won't Tong Tian Ming pull the plug?
Of course, he will.
Why not?
So we
just canceled the contract with him.
Are you kidding me?
Maury.
Allow me to introduce them to you.
This is Mr. Wang
and this is Mr. Li.
They both
want to invest in The Founding of
the Three Kingdoms.
They also requested
to discuss this with you
face to face.
Really?
Yes.
I think this play
is very promising.
Especially the role of Lv Bu,
[*A military general in the Three Kingdoms Period]
it is tailored for You Xi.
It has to be him.
If You Xi is willing to take the role,
I will
double my investments immediately.
Thanks.
My fan.
He must be my fan.
How else could it be such a coincidence?
Appearing just at the right time,
he probably finds what happened
to me to be extremely unfair
and feels sorry for me.
That's what
I thought first.
But
with my professionalism,
I did a background check on them.
[Resume]
These three successful people
work in different fields
and have never crossed paths.
But
[Ye Fei Ming]
they have one thing in common which is...
[Heaven rewards the diligent]
Dad,
I got you
into trouble this time.
I have been teaching for decades.
It's normal to have some connections.
Yao Yao,
why didn't you tell me
when you broke up with Yin Jiu?
Dad,
I don't want you to worry about me.
Yao Yao,
I'm your father.
I would like anything
that you are fond of.
Dad,
what are you talking about?
When did you and You Xi
start dating?
Dad,
you got me wrong.
There is nothing between Mr. You and me.
What?
Then why would he kiss you
in front of all those people?
How did you find out?
Yin Jin told me.
Yin Jiu?
What he told me is
that he only started dating Tong Jin
after you
started dating You Xi.
How could Yin Jiu
know my daughter
better than I do?
I'm your dad after all.
Anyway,
there is nothing between Mr. You and me.
I've been through it all.
Back in those days,
when I was dating your mother,
everyone
in our university
knew about it.
But that didn't bother me at all.
I...
Yao Yao?
How did it do?
What did your dad say?
He said
nothing.
Never mind.
I'll go in
and thank your dad in person.
Mr. You,
there's no need.
My dad
is busy marking the papers now.
Let's just leave him alone
and go home.
We'll go home and do our homework.
Homework?
I've lost it.
Lost it?
Mr. You,
why did you throw all your textbooks in the bin?
It took me such a long time to find it.
I thought the contract was terminated.
God knows why that didn't happen.
I got all your homework back.
Are you hungry?
I can make rice dumplings very well now.
I'll make some for you.
I can do the homework later.
Mr. You, I...
Mr. You, hurry up.
We have class later.
Last time, we talked
about The Gathering of Heroes.
We haven't finished the chapter of
Jiang Gan Is Trapped.
Today, we are going to learn Three Visits to...
Shut up.
This is your spoon.
So what?
Don't want to share the same spoon?
Aren't you a neat freak?
I was,
but now I'm not.
Eat more of the sweet dumplings I made.
Where did you get scalded? Let me blow it for you.
[Spring and Autumn Annals]
In 280 AD,
Western Jin defeated Eastern Wu
and united China.
Then,
the 60-year
Three Kingdoms Period
was over.
Boys and girls,
that's the end
of our final class.
[Crew of The Founding of the Three Kingdoms]
During ten days of training,
[Training Target]
I've noticed the growth and progress
of each one of you.
[Poem]
As a teacher,
I am both moved and pleased.
Hope you guys
remain true to your original aspiration
and take your roles seriously.
Bring this glorious history
to more people
and pass on the time-honored
Chinese culture.
Thank you all.
You Xi,
do you have any questions?
I would like
to recite a poem to everyone.
Which one
would you like to recite?
"View of the Blue Sea".
My favorite poem is "View of the Blue Sea"
written by Cao Cao.
You should recite it
when we get the chance.
"I come to view the boundless ocean"
"from Stony Hill on the eastern shore."
"Its water rolls in rhythmic motion"
"and islands stand amid its roar."
"Trees on trees grow from peak to peak".
"Grass on grass looks lush far and nigh."
"The autumn wind blows drear and bleak"
"The monstrous billows surge up high."
"The sun by day and the moon by night".
"They appear to rise up from the deep."
"The Milky Way with stars so bright"
"sinks down into the sea in sleep."
"How happy I feel at this sight!"
"I croon this poem in delight."
Well done!
[A hero is not afraid of the road ahead]
(Say cheese.)
(Just for a second.)
Three, two, one, cheers.
Uncle You,
the training is over.
Let's take a picture. Come on.
We'll be in the crew soon. Don't need to.
Come on, just take one.
The hand gesture.
Three, two, one.
Pretty good.
[A hero is not afraid of the road ahead,
fighting on the territory of Three Kingdom]
(-Professor.)
We are taking pictures.
Yes, yes.
I'll take one with you.
I'm coming.
Come on, come on.
Come, come. Here.
Three, two, one. Cheers.
Yao Yao,
why don't you join them?
One, two, three, cheers.
By the way,
I have something for you.
Here you are.
You left it last time.
Sorry about that.
I left in such a hurry last time.
Thank you.
That's great.
(One, two, three, cheers.)
Look over here.
One, two, three.
This time,
it is the hairpin you dropped.
(Professor, come here.)
(Let's take pictures together.)
Come on, come on.
Who will press the shutter?
Mr. You.
Yellow doesn't suit you,
nor does this pattern.
No, no.
You shouldn't wear a hairpin.
Just remove it.
Okay, come on.
You Xi,
come to
my office later.
Okay.
[Teachers' office]
Mr. You.
Yao Yao.
Why are you here?
Your, your dad
told me to wait at the door.
Wait a minute.
Mr. You,
don't touch anything
when you go in.
Or else...
Or else?
There was once a student,
who accidentally broke the ornament
in my father's office.
And then...
And then?
He dropped out of school.
Since then,
no one has seen him again.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Wait...
You are here.
Sit,
and have a drink.
It's hot.
I'll pay for it.
Is that OK?
Sit down.
It's just a fake.
Young people like you
are always careless.
I would feel worried
if I put a real one here.
I only told you
about this.
Don't spread it.
But
Yuchi Mu...
You mean,
she told you
about the student who dropped out of school
because he broke my ornament?
In fact,
the reason why he dropped out
was because of the demolition of his house.
He dropped out of school
to inherit the family property.
What does it have to do with me?
Since they put it that way,
I just took advantage of it.
That way,
they'll behave themselves
when they are in my office.
That's clever.
By the way,
I haven't thanked you
for the venture of
The Founding of the Three Kingdoms
last time.
Also,
thanks for the note
you gave me in secret
when I went up to the podium.
The note?
What note?
I have no idea.
Professor,
why did you
ask me to come here?
I shouldn't have gotten involved
with the business of you young people.
But
Yao Yao is a special case.
I know all about it already.
You know all about it?
And the reason
why Yao Yao has the fear of crowds.
Do you know it too?
Yes.
You Xi,
Yao Yao has never
mentioned this matter
to anyone.
If you
can't make Yao Yao happy,
I hope you can leave her as soon as possible.
Because as a father,
I don't want my daughter
to get hurt again.
[Crew of The Founding of the Three Kingdoms]
Mr. You.
[The Founding of the Three Kingdoms, Yuchi Yao Yao]
What did my dad tell you?
Well, many things.
Would you like to hear the story of you
being late for school
and cried while chasing a bus when you were seven?
Or the story of you being chased by a rooster
in the yard when you were three?
I...
Why did my father tell you those?
I am really, I...
Mr. You,
my dad was lying to you.
Don't believe him.
Why does it sound real to me?
Mr. Zhang,
you may rest assured.
I've already dealt with all the things.
I transferred the money,
and wipe out the photos.
I promise
that there are no loose ends.
Okay, Mr. Zhang.
Bye.
These people are too greedy.
I can't believe
that they are asking for this much for one photo.
Is this an ordinary photo?
It is a photo of the top celebrity, You Xi.
Listen,
even if there were two more zeros
at the end of this number,
I would still pay for it
without any hesitation.
Shen Yi Ling,
you act so fast.
I'll call the press right now.
Wait.
It is not the right time yet.
When is the right time
if it isn't now?
Do you know how leopards hunt?
Every time the leopard sees its prey,
it inches closer and closer
with hardly a sound.
Until it gets to the vantage point,
then it pounces.
That's how
to get a real kick out of them.
He got away by luck last time.
I'll see
how he could turn things over this time.
Hello, Mr. Song.
You Xi.
You are the new actor signed by the company.
Congratulations to You Xi!
The number of his Weibo followers
has exceeded 10 million!
Regarding the OJ endorsement this time,
they've chosen...
You Xi.
Take a look at this.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, You Xi.
Finally,
I'm at home.
No exams, no early mornings, no classes.
[Spring and Autumn Annals]
What's wrong with you?
The training is over.
What are these books for?
The training is over,
but we haven't finished Chancellor Zhong yet.
There are still five days left before
you meet with director Wei Ran.
How many days?
♪The world is so big♪
♪One word from you makes me melt♪
♪Watching you decorate this little home♪
♪It's bursting with happiness♪
♪The vibrance of Spring and Summer,
the temperature of Autumn and Winter♪
♪They're all picturesque♪
♪Along with the colors of the sunset♪
♪There's no reason not to treasure what we have♪
♪I'll be with you when you're in tears♪
♪I'll spoil you so you don't cry your makeup away♪
♪I'll take you wherever you want to go♪
♪You're my woman♪
♪I want you to be my goddess forever♪
♪I'll gently light your lamp
in the quiet of the night♪
♪I'll hold you in my arms
and let you sleep soundly♪
♪I'm your man♪
♪I will take care of you wholeheartedly♪
♪I'll follow the perfect script in your heart♪
♪You're the one who makes it all possible♪
♪Who makes love complete♪