Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Time Flies and You Are Here
Episode 28
The journey is long, hoping that the
wind will blow me to the eastern ocean
Baichuankou
Hanchen.
Did you receive any news?
Just like you thought.
300,000 piculs of provisions
were destroyed in the fire.
200,000 piculs were hay.
None of the transporting officials survived.
Right now,
it's another unsolved case.
At the capital,
Grand Secretariat Qin is
investigating this case covertly.
According to the letter,
apparently...
A year ago,
His Majesty inspected the accounts of
both Jingxi and Jingdong.
The funds meant for military salaries
were used to
make up for the deficits
by the officials.
As for the reason both
treasuries were empty,
I'm afraid only
Grand Chancellor Xu knows.
Besides that...
Spill it.
The Crown Prince is involved as well.
The Crown Prince is still young.
He had no idea that he's being used.
However, Noble Consort Cao
watched idly
while the heir to the throne
was made into pest.
What's your plan?
Grand Chancellor Xu
involved the Crown Prince
to protect himself.
Even if His Majesty
intends to investigate
and finds out the truth,
His Majesty has no choice
but to let it slide.
This geezer
made the Crown Prince
his chess piece.
If the title of Crown Prince
was given to someone else,
what could he do?
Excuse me.
Make way.
Mr. Liu.
Douzi, hurry up.
Find it.
I'm trying.
Ranking board
Did you find it?
Please be patient.
Ranking board
233rd, Yan Boyang
Master!
You got it!
Where?
There!
You attained the 233rd place!
I passed!
Yan Boyang
I passed the imperial examination!
Mr. Liu, did you see that?
Congratulations, Mr. Yan.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
All right. I need to go.
I need to share this
great news with Minggu.
- All right.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Please excuse me.
Master.
- Slow down!
- Minggu!
- Master!
You heartless people.
General Zhao is guarding
the borders for us,
yet you slander him.
All you do is talking nonsense.
Get out of here.
Forget reasoning with them.
Let's just beat them up.
Stop it.
I'll kill you.
Stop it!
What's wrong?
The rumor is known everywhere.
In order to seize victory,
General Zhao sacrificed
more than 10,000 soldiers.
Since he did it,
why can't I tell the truth?
You know nothing,
yet you're spewing nonsense.
Get lost!
You...
You feisty tramp.
You lying scholar.
Lying scholar.
Feisty tramp.
What are you doing?
Who are you calling a feisty tramp?
Have you passed
the imperial examination?
How atrocious.
I...
What?
Get lost.
Get out of my sight.
Let's go!
Get lost.
There's nothing to see here.
That's enough.
Boyang.
Get out of here.
Disperse.
Did you pass?
Go.
That's great!
You finally did it!
Here. Let's cheer for this.
Here.
Today is a great day.
Although
I'm at the 233rd place,
it's not exactly the best.
But no matter what,
I'm a Jinshi,
right?
Minggu,
when are we going to...
Come on.
That's all you know?
Don't bring it up till
you start to make money.
Previously,
you promised you'd marry Boyang
after he passed the examination.
That's right.
Look at both of you.
I'm not done with you.
Zhao Xiaoqian
is the great General Zhao now.
After he returns in triumph,
he'd become an official
back at the city.
Public opinions will not hurt him.
On the contrary,
you're off defending him
with a broom every day.
If you keep doing this,
you will be known
as the feisty tramp around here.
Do you know he's returning soon?
Yes.
Everyone in the academy
is talking about it.
Well,
do you want to see him?
Xiaoman,
let's drink.
Here.
Cheers.
Look at me.
What am I talking about!
We parted ways long time ago.
By the way,
an old friend from Wujiang Prefecture
is coming to the capital.
Tomorrow night,
come over to my store.
I'll make you a garment
and make you pretty.
I'm going to tend to the store.
You should hurry back to the academy.
I'll see you tomorrow night.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Wait.
What's the rush?
Let's celebrate your achievement.
Really?
♪I've been thinking♪
♪I haven't heard from you for a year♪
♪Everything has changed♪
♪Dreaming of going on Fangzhou Road♪
Minister of Rites, He Yong.
Two gold goblets.
Minister of Works, Liu Cheng'en.
A piece of Sunset Painting.
Deputy Decal Minister, Shen Shidao.
One unit of
Celadon Hundredfold Crackle Vase.
Minister of Military Affairs,
Liu Shunchen.
A box of ambergris from
the Saracen Empire.
Directorate of Imperial Academy,
Lu Songqing.
Ten units of Tinggui Ink from Huizhou.
Official of Personnel Division
of East Road, Huzhou, Qian Yide.
A piece of Hidden Arhat Painting.
What about Shen Yan?
A month ago, General Shen
returned to the capital
with General Xu.
He did not garner the privilege
to participate in
the tribute of ministers.
They are
those who grovel before the influential.
Ignore them.
What's the current situation
in the capital?
Things are grim.
Although the accounts of
Jingxi and Jingdong
embezzled military funds,
no problems are detected yet.
Things are advancing
according to Xu Huan's plans.
Grand Secretariat Qin is unable to
oppose him alone in the capital.
He said he let you down
for failing to protect the reputation
of the war of Baichuankou.
Right now,
the rumors about you
are spreading like virus.
They called you the
reincarnation of evil,
an aggressive warlord.
The situation isn't certain for now.
Are you sure
it's a good time to declare war
against Xu Huan right now?
Further adventures in finance and felony.
What do you think?
By the way,
there's another thing.
The Spring Exam ended not long ago.
Boyang passed the exam.
They all
know you're coming back.
Withdraw the spy from
Xie Family.
Capital
Shun
Excuse me.
Which prince could it be?
What a great commotion.
Don't you know?
General Zhao is returning
to the imperial court in triumph today.
His Majesty is honoring his return.
The Living King Yama is back?
Zhao Xiaoqian!
Shen.
Duke of Wuguo is back.
What should I offer as a gift?
If the gift is too expensive,
His Majesty would be unhappy.
Should I...
I shall offer him some fruits.
The returning general shall be
rewarded personally by His Majesty.
There's no need for you to
concern yourself, Chancellor Xu.
Civil officials like you don't
know how things work.
Duke of Wuguo has arrived.
Your Highness.
Chancellor Xu,
are you teasing the innocent again?
Back then,
you learned the Analects from me.
You were still a child back then.
Today,
you won the war
and returned in triumph.
You have a bright future ahead.
Duke of Wuguo returned victoriously
and magnified the glory of the state.
You have my deepest admiration.
The imperial meeting commences.
Deputy Commander of Guanxi Borders,
Commander of Xiongjie Army,
Zhao Xiaoqian
offers greetings to Your Majesty.
Long live the Emperor.
Baichuankou attained victory!
Congratulations, Your Majesty!
Long live the Emperor!
You may rise.
Let me take a good look at you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Hanchen of the Zhao Family
clad in Armour,
defeated the enemies at war.
His merit and contribution
to the state are vast.
I
have raised you right.
Hanchen
retrieved the lost territories
of Baichuankou
and attained victory.
I've decided to
promote Zhao Xiaoqian
as the Commander of Pengri Army
of Sixiang Province
and Commandery Prince of Julu.
Scholar Han Lin shall draft the edict.
The edict takes effect today.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Congratulations,
Commandery Prince of Julu.
Your Majesty,
I'd like to ask for
a different position.
Since I attained victory,
I do not have further requests.
I only seek to assume position as
the Imperial Grand Governor.
The Imperial Grand Governor?
I beg for Your Majesty's approval.
Su Chang Ji
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Madam Wang from the street said
General Zhao came back from hell.
I heard that he killed
countless lives at the borders.
He's aggressive and tyrannous.
He can't be suppressed.
You're right.
He returned to the court today.
Lady Su wouldn't allow us
to talk about it.
I'm not sure why either.
I heard
that he was pierced through
by an arrow at the chest,
but he survived.
He's the Living King Yama.
There's no doubt.
You're right.
What did you say?
What do you mean he was
pierced through the chest?
Well...
Spill it.
What's going on?
Xiaoman.
What's the matter?
He's injured?
Such rumor
is going around the neighbourhood.
I want to see him for once.
Just once.
Minggu,
can you ask Boyang to
deliver a letter for me?
All right.
Brat.
You caused a clamour
the moment you returned.
Father.
Come here.
Drink tea with me.
What's wrong?
You rejected my offer to grant you
the title as the Commandery Prince.
Are you capable of being
the Imperial Grand Governor?
If others can do it,
so can I.
Tell me.
Why the position of
the Imperial Grand Governor?
It's for the sake of my pride.
I'm bored of military positions.
I'd like to be serve
as a regular official.
Pride?
In the war of Baichuankou,
there were over 10,000 of casualties.
Do you know
what the public calls you?
An aggressive warlord.
The reincarnation of evil.
You're aware,
yet you're asking to be an official.
Do you know
that's the position for the Crown Prince?
As for the heavy casualties
in Baichuankou,
how will you justify yourself?
A good commander knows how to
defend when attack fails,
retreat when defend fails,
and escape when retreat fails.
Or else, one should die fighting.
I couldn't retreat
or run.
The only thing I could do was
to fight the enemy head on.
There's no rush.
Your Majesty may take time
to consider my request.
I can wait.
I
shall excuse myself.
I'm leaving, Your Majesty.
Hanchen
has indeed changed.
Chancellor,
the Imperial Grand Governor
has always been
the Crown Prince's position.
Right after Duke of Wuguo returned,
he asked to occupy the role
of the Crown Prince.
He's...
Chancellor.
The meeting at Ruisi Palace has ended.
His Majesty did not agree.
Thank you for the hard work, eunuch.
Do not panic.
His Majesty did not agree.
The war of Baichuankou
wasn't attained by him alone.
However, all the credits
went to him alone.
His Majesty is being partial.
Chancellor.
A few days ago, I heard that
His Majesty reprimanded
the Crown Prince
while His Majesty promoted and
rewarded Zhao Xiaoqian today.
Do you think...
A few days ago, I was told
that the military caused
a ruckus at the city.
I'm rather concerned with this matter.
Should I recruit men
to cause Duke of Wuguo some trouble?
Your request at
the imperial court today
must have evoked suspicion.
Chancellor Xu would
make an attempt soon.
You must take precautions.
Also,
Boyang delivered an invitation.
He wants to catch up with you.
Xiaoman will be there as well.
We're under
Chancellor Xu's surveillance right now.
I'm sure they are aware
Xiaoman and Boyang are in the capital.
The best way around
is to act as usual.
I understand.
Your Highness.
Zhu Momo.
You're still around.
Mother.
I'm here.
Kneel.
The memorial tablet of the eldest son,
Zhao Xiaojie
Let me ask you.
How many lives do you have?
How dare you request His Majesty for
the role of the Imperial Grand Governor?
Don't you know
that the Imperial Grand Governor
can only be assumed
by the Crown Prince.
You surely receive news quickly, mother.
Less than a day has passed since
the adjournment of the court,
yet you knew everything.
I'm afraid the Empress
found out even earlier.
If what you did in the court today
reached Her Highness,
she will think you want to
compete for the throne.
If you continue this farce,
you're going to lose your life.
It doesn't matter if she finds out.
Her Highness can't possibly
poison me as well.
You...
I did not come home
to argue with you.
I came to offer my respects to brother.
On the year of brother's death,
my fate was already set.
If you have time,
you may enter the palace
and talk to the Empress.
Since she failed to
discipline the Crown Prince,
the change of position
will no longer be up to her.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I hear that my trouble is lingering♪
♪The gentleness is my missing for you♪
Have you forgotten everything?
Hanchen.
You've finally arrived at the capital.
I wonder
if you still remember your
old friends of Wujiang Prefecture.
♪I'm blessed to have met you♪
♪The wind blows away the dust♪
♪Thinking back, it's what I experienced♪
♪The lonely heaven on earth♪
Why haven't they arrived?
Give them some time. Do not eat first.
He will be here soon.
Zhanzhi.
Boyang.
Hanchen.
Xingzhou.
Let me take a good look at you.
You brat.
You are lucky indeed.
You were pierced through
by an arrow at your chest,
yet you came back alive.
You're doing great yourself.
You ranked the 233rd place.
I almost ended up last.
How about asking His Majesty
to promote me to
the 33rd place instead?
Let me enter the Hanlin Academy as well.
Forget it.
Let's all grab a seat,
233rd place.
You need to work harder.
Here. Have a seat.
Come on.
Have a seat.
I heard that your father was promoted.
Your brother
had two kids in the same year.
What's going on?
Did he marry a concubine?
Don't be ridiculous.
My sister-in-law gave birth to twins.
Isn't that right, Minggu?
Yes.
Let's put this aside.
We haven't met in three years.
Bottoms up.
A toast to the survival
of Xingzhou and Hanchen.
- Here.
Cheers.
I heard that
you were injured at Baichuankou.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hanchen's injury wasn't severe.
Don't worry.
Baichuankou was rather chilly though.
His knees would hurt
when it started to rain.
It's not a big deal, right?
You must take it seriously.
Have you consulted the physician?
Are you married?
You're no longer young.
There's no time to waste.
No one has proposed to me yet.
Don't worry.
Take your time.
Once you find someone,
I'll offer you the endowment.
Zhao Xiaoqian, what do you mean?
Marriages and funerals
are natural events.
I'm just concerned about Xiaoman.
Zhao Xiaoqian!
Pay for my son's life!
Who are you?
Return my son to me!
If it wasn't for your greed for merits
and ignored the lives of the soldiers,
my son wouldn't have died!
Return my son to me!
If you're able to kill me,
I'll pay for his life with mine.
What do you say?
You aggressive warlord!
You're the reincarnation of evil!
You will die a nasty death!
I'm not in the mood.
Let's meet up another time.
Xiaoman.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
What's the matter?
Xingzhou said
your knees hurt when it rains.
What kind of pain do you experience?
Back at Yuyangli Village, I...
Stop bringing Yuyangli Village up.
There are plenty of
imperial physicians in the palace.
It's none of your concern.
The old man just now...
What's wrong?
A war comes with deaths.
There are plenty who have suffered.
It's no big deal.
Why?
Are you disappointed?
How could this be?
Everyone
called you an aggressive warlord
who only cares about merits.
The public said you coveted after
power once you returned.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Lady Xie.
No matter what you say
behind my back,
in public,
you should address me as
the Commandery Prince.
This is the capital.
The situation is very complicated.
I do not have time to
take care of the insignificant peasants
like you.
You should take care of yourself.
All right!
I'll be cautious.
I do not need your concern!
You fool.
He's currently a man of power.
He has no time for you.
You're still thinking about him.
You're a fool.
You're dumb.
You're pathetic.
You want to give me the endowment?
I do not need your money.
In the past,
I was the one who left you first.
What am I afraid of?
Did you think I went to see you
for reconciliation?
In your dreams!
I just wanted to see
if you're dead.
I'm not dead.
Are you proud of your position
as the general?
You're disturbing me even in my dreams.
Yes.
I'm afraid you'd hit me during the day,
so I had to come in your dreams.
That way, it wouldn't hurt
when you hit me.
Are you still mad at me?
Yes.
I'm extremely mad.
Go away.
We're done.
Be on your own way,
and I'll go my own.
What if I want to join you on your path?
It's too narrow
for two.
Stop laughing.
You're terrible.
Yes, I am.
You refused to see me.
You wanted to marry me off.
You wanted to offer me the endowment.
Who do you think you are?
Are you my father?
Stay away from me.
You traitor.
You heartless man.
You're worse than animals.
You're heartless.
You're my woman.
When I hurt you for a bit,
it will hurt me ten times more.
How could I possibly forget you?
You wanted to marry me off.
Ridiculous.
Try and marry someone else.
If you do,
I'll stop it no matter what.
Really?
Yes.
Go to bed.
Dream of this when you're asleep.
In the dream, we'd be married.
I'll take you openly as my wife.
All right?
Studio of Artlessness
I've investigated the case.
The old man
was sent by Chancellor Xu.
What do you plan to do next?
I'm going to request His Majesty to
betroth Shen Zhaowen to me tomorrow.
The plan goes on.
It was indeed just a dream.
Sister.
Where have you been?
You even skipped breakfast.
Hurry up and eat.
Someone treated me to crustacean.
Xiaoman.
An old friend from
Wujiang Prefecture is here.
Congwen.
Stop standing around.
Hurry up and treat Congwen
to some good food.
We have no more food at home.
Go on.
Let's take a stroll outside.
I haven't taken a morning stroll around
the capital in a while.
The eight views of the capital
include the spring landscape
of the capital.
Last year,
you did odd jobs
for Teacher Liu.
I was told that you became
a teacher this year.
Don't tease me.
With my proficiency,
I'm not eligible to be a teacher.
I'm just teaching
the Thousand Character Classic now.
On the contrary,
you'd come to the capital
every spring to teach.
It must have been tough.
Well, I did not return this time
only to teach.
Have a seat.
I brought you some rice cakes.
Thank you.
Did you meet him yesterday?
Before his return,
I didn't believe
the rumors.
Hanchen is a righteous man.
However, yesterday,
an old man accused him
of coveting merits
and sacrificing his son.
The old man looked
so frail and helpless.
In the span of three years,
do you think someone
could change completely?
You should ask him yourself.
In your heart, he may
be kind and righteous.
However, in your eyes,
he'd treat others as nothing but ants.
Your heart is questioning
why he ended up this way.
However, you refuse to believe
the claim of others.
Only if you ask him yourself
can you obtain peace in your heart.
Your Majesty,
the victory in Baichuankou
came with heavy casualties.
If the court offers compensation,
it will cost a hefty sum.
I beg for your pardon, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I think we mustn't conserve
on the compensation.
The soldiers sacrificed
themselves for the state
and fought the enemy bravely.
If the soldiers' families
are not cared,
it will hurt the morale and patriotism
of the fellow soldiers.
If the state is under
the enemy's attack in the future,
no one would be willing to
fight the war at the cost of their lives.
What do you think, Hanchen?
Your Majesty,
the decision
lies in Your Majesty.
I have a request
I would like to make for myself.
Speak.
I'm well past the age of 20.
Your Majesty granted
the Commandery Prince's Mansion to me.
The mansion
needs the Commandery Princess.
How ridiculous.
He intends to marry a wife
right after returning from war.
Do you have someone in mind?
Commandery Princess Rong'an,
Shen Zhaowen,
grew up with me.
I have deep feelings for her.
I beg for Your Majesty's approval.
Kunning Palace
You're all dismissed.
Leave Wang Xian to serve me alone.
Chancellor Xu conveyed a message
from the court.
Commandery Prince of Julu
asked for the office of
the Imperial Grand Governor previously.
During the court meeting just now,
he requested to marry
Commandery Princess Rong'an.
What did His Majesty say?
Luckily His Majesty didn't approve.
After winning the war,
he forgot his own place.
It was my negligence
for failing to eliminate him
together then.
Inform Chancellor Xu.
I'll leave the matter to him.
Yes, Your Highness.
What's the matter?
Is there something else?
According to Chancellor Xu,
Commandery Prince of Julu is coveting
the position of Imperial Grand Governor
to replace the Crown Prince.
How dare he?
Chancellor Xu also said,
he must be annihilated.
He already has a plan.
Chancellor Xu said,
in order to protect the Crown Prince,
Your Highness must...
After achieving victory in war,
he's after the role of the Crown Prince.
He wants to marry the daughter
of Commander of Majun Province.
Although Zhao Xiaoqian
is not the rightful heir,
his ambitions are daunting.
He has been suppressed for a long time.
Once he retaliates,
he is capable of causing a turmoil.
Does that mean
Zhao Xiaoqian is after
something greater,
like the position of Crown Prince?
Since he pursues something
beyond his place,
why not
eliminate him?
Do you know that
how I landed the position
of the grand chancellor?
I keep no one
who gets in my way.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪