Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 23=
(I drink wine and tea to myself
whenever I'm bored)
(Bailu Academy)
(Jingnv Pavilion)
Did Zhao Xiaoqian agree just like that?
Yes.
I found it strange, too.
He forbade me from
doing anything before,
but he changed his mind suddenly.
That's good.
Minggu.
Have you reconciled with Yan Boyang?
Why is Lady Xue absent today?
I heard she's going for
a blind date today.
A blind date?
Who is the potential candidate?
Yan Boyang.
Haven't you heard?
Yan Boyang?
Also,
Xie Ruying is getting married as well.
Xie Ruying?
Who is it?
Who is she marrying?
Apparently, to the first son
of the Prefect of Tongzhou.
However, he's rather ill.
Did Yan Boyang really go
for a blind date?
Xie Li,
why are you following me around?
I go to meet my sister.
She's going to tutor me.
From now on,
I might not be able to attend
school with you anymore.
I'm leaving soon.
Where...
Where are you going?
My father received an order
to work in Tongzhou.
My mother shall accompany him.
I have no choice but to follow as well.
When are you leaving?
In these two days.
This is for you.
If you leave now,
won't you attend
the rest of the classes?
Perhaps, you could talk to your mother.
You're still young.
You need to study.
There are schools in Tongzhou as well.
Actually,
I have a lot to say to you.
Sister Su told me that
I must confess...
All right.
My house is right there.
There's no need to send me.
Goodbye, Xie Li.
Fenniang!
Yearning lasts forever.
Memory lasts forever.
Impermanent yearning seems boundless.
If I knew how agonizing it'd be,
I wish we haven't met at all.
(Dear Minggu, how I wish I can confess
my feelings for you.)
(Duke's Mansion)
Greetings, Duke of Wuguo.
Call me your brother-in-law.
Duke of Wuguo.
Brother-in-law.
I'm going to beat you up.
I was told you did badly
in your studies.
Your sister is concerned.
I've decided to teach you personally.
Before Chinese New Year's Eve,
you should fail everything.
If you fail everything,
I'll give you a pony, okay?
Come on.
What a good boy.
Keep that in mind.
Confucius said,
it's always a pleasure
to practice what you learned.
It's always a pleasure
to meet a friend who could teach.
It's a behaviour of a gentleman
to remain calm when misunderstood.
Memorize it.
It's always a pleasure
that's
not a behaviour of a gentleman.
It's always a pleasure
to practice what you learned.
It's always fun
to meet a friend who could teach.
It's always a pleasure.
Remain...
Remain misunderstood...
It's a behaviour of a gentleman
to remain calm when misunderstood!
You...
Kids these days surely are dumb.
They should just beg for food
by the streets by
Chinese New Year's Eve.
Memorize it!
It's...
Stand upright!
It's going to snow
during Chinese New Year's Eve.
Brat, come over here!
Brother-in-law!
(Lotus Garden)
Hold it right there!
Brat!
What's wrong?
Stop running!
Get over here!
You...
That's enough.
I'll handle it, okay?
What's wrong?
What aggravated you?
That brat
can't even memorize
the simplest Analects.
He's doing it on purpose.
I told you so.
It's difficult being a teacher.
No matter how dull he is,
I'll succeed.
That's enough.
Let's talk inside.
Let's go.
Calm down.
Were you eavesdropping
out here just now?
You're gloating.
I wasn't.
Don't accuse me.
I'm here to
talk to you about Yan Boyang.
What's going on with Boyang?
Recently,
Boyang is squabbling with Minggu.
He looks pretty upset.
How about this?
Let's invite them over tomorrow
and we will talk it out.
What do you think?
Since when
are you concerned about them?
Of course I'm concerned
about my brother.
Yan Boyang is ridiculous.
He's a man,
yet he'd bicker with a lady.
It irritates me.
I understand.
All right.
Let's go.
Do not change the topic.
Were you eavesdropping
out here just now?
I wasn't.
I swear I wasn't.
I just missed you
so I came by to see you.
Let's go.
(Half of spring has gone.)
One's yearning
is found on the fragrant lilac.
The beans...
The beans are gone.
Why aren't you going?
We've talked to Yan Boyang.
Hanchen and I are getting married soon.
Will you still refuse to reconcile?
I won't go, period.
What's that?
A love letter from Luming Pavilion.
A love letter?
(To Minggu)
To Minggu?
(From Zhanzhi)
My feelings are genuine.
Believe me.
Minggu.
Zhanzhi?
You invited me to Duke's Mansion
tonight, right?
I'll go.
(Teachers' Office)
Look at Xie Li.
He's still young
yet he wrote a love letter.
He expressed his feelings
to Fenniang.
Matters of love belong
to the young.
However, it's a bit too early
for Xie Li.
Where's the letter?
Did you see the letter?
I collected it
from Fenniang this morning.
Why isn't it here?
So many people are here.
There are no outsiders.
Where's Yan Boyang?
Why hasn't he arrived?
Mr. Yan is here.
I'm so sorry.
So sorry.
I'm late.
Come on in.
Here.
Why is Yanwan here?
In the afternoon,
I was shopping with Yanwan,
so we came by together.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Everything is fine.
That's right.
Boyang was kind enough
to accompany me as
I shopped for some cosmetics.
Lady Su wants to drink.
You shouldn't stop her.
This is fine wine.
This is Bixiang.
It's not as strong.
Drink to your heart's content.
Of course.
This wine is perfect for you.
Your body is rather frail.
This wine will warm you up.
A little will do no harm.
What do you think?
How about this?
I
was late.
I shall take a shot as an apology.
Such fine wine.
The quality of wine
can be measured by a sommelier.
As for a quality of a person,
one can truly tell after
spending time with them.
Yanwan.
Yanwan,
eat more.
The dishes are turning cold.
You're getting yourself drunk.
Getting drunk or not
shows no difference.
Some people
could never sober up.
Yan Boyang.
What?
You're right.
Some people could never sober up.
Getting drunk or not
shows no difference.
Xue Yanwan has company.
No matter how drunk she is,
someone would send her home.
I'm not the same.
I'm afraid I can't drink anymore.
I have matters to attend to.
I shall take my leave.
Su Wei.
Boyang,
Minggu is a lady.
We're all friends.
What are you doing?
You're my friends.
She's not.
Are you done?
Do you feel good about this?
Are you even a man?
How ridiculous.
Let's go.
Thank you for the hospitality.
I shall head home.
Wait.
Yanwan.
Allow me to send you home.
What's wrong with Yan Boyang?
We haven't met in a few days,
he's already so concerned about Yanwan.
You are wrong about him.
He just wanted to provoke Su Minggu.
He's a fool.
If Su Minggu left for real,
he'd be bawling his eyes out.
What do you mean?
You truly are a fool.
Can't you tell Yan Boyang's feelings
for Su Minggu?
What about your feelings?
Let's go make some babies.
Let me go!
Lady Xie!
Put me down.
What's the matter?
Lady Xie,
Li'er refuses to study again.
I lectured him,
but he wouldn't listen to me.
He even asked me to play with him.
All he does is play.
He refuses to study.
He wants to cook Shengwu
and Chunniang up as well.
I'm going to give him a lesson.
Calm down.
There's an order to everything.
You...
Get up!
It hurts!
Really?
What were you doing?
I told you to copy the Analects.
Are you done?
You're still young
yet you refuse to learn.
The person I love is
not going to school anymore.
You little brat.
What do you know about love?
I'm asking you.
Why aren't you doing your homework?
Leave me alone!
Have you ever liked someone?
Have you ever missed
someone so much that
you can't sleep,
yet you're eager to
meet her in your dream?
I...
You adults know nothing.
All you care about is homework.
I'm done with study.
You brat.
Hold it right there.
Get back here!
Calm down.
I can't.
What's the problem?
That brat.
I told him to do his homework.
He was off doodling.
If you hit him,
would he stop?
When I was young,
I hated the teachers who hit me.
If you hit him for real,
he'd hate you for sure.
What should I do then?
In my opinion, education
should start from the beginning.
Forget about Xie Li.
We should focus on our kid.
Let's give birth to
a principal graduate.
That's all you ever think about.
You do not even care
about Xie Li's study.
Get out of here.
Get out.
You irritate me.
Calm down.
- Go away.
- Will you calm down?
There's no need to give birth
to a principal graduate.
Go away.
Let's give birth to a runner-up.
Please calm down.
They all
aggravate me.
Open up.
Yanwan.
I...
Yanwan, I'm sorry.
What's it?
Are you sorry for not
informing me beforehand
about the act you put on?
I...
It's fine.
I could tell you and Minggu are in love.
Therefore,
you didn't have to use me
as an excuse.
You're mistaken.
Minggu doesn't have feelings for me.
So you came to me?
No.
I don't mean it.
However, I have to obey
my parents.
I've never seen you
so obedient.
If you were obedient,
you would have been
married to Ruying by now.
No, I...
No matter who you have feelings for,
I, Xue Yanwan,
am not a lady nobody wants.
If my husband's heart
belongs to someone else,
and I insist on marrying him,
it's beyond shameful.
I, Xue Yanwan,
am not concerned about a man.
I'll get married when I want to.
Yan Boyang,
if you'd like to marry me,
you should forget Lady Su first.
Old Madam Su,
Lady Su is here.
Grandmother.
Did you ask for me?
Minggu.
Come here.
Sit right here.
Recently,
I've been ill.
Your parents have been
managing the matters of the household.
They are reluctant to trouble you.
I know.
Don't cry.
Just keep this in mind.
No matter what happens in the future,
remain upright.
Keep your chin up.
Grandmother,
I'm an adult now.
I want to share your burdens.
I'm capable of doing that.
From now on,
I'll learn what I do not know.
I'll master them all, grandmother.
Child.
As your elderly,
we do not expect anything from you.
All we wish for you
is health
and happiness.
We hope you'd find a good husband.
Yan Boyang
is a good kid.
I could tell
his feelings for you.
When faced with hurdles,
try your best to overcome them.
Put the result aside.
Do not opt for shortcuts.
Otherwise, you'd regret
this deeply
for the rest of your life.
Grandmother,
what do I do if I'm uncertain
about my feelings?
Silly child.
If it affects you so much,
that means it matters to you.
Stop thinking too much.
Stop hesitating.
He's a good man.
Don't let him be taken by someone else.
Grandmother.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(I'm in a good mood today.)
(That's why the weather
today is fine as well.)
(They might have nothing
to do with each other.)
(However, my mood)
(changes according to yours.)
(I'm happy when you're happy.)
(When you're upset,)
(I no longer know what
it means to be happy.)
Tomorrow at noon,
I'll see you at Xiang Bridge.
Yours, Zhanzhi.
At noon tomorrow?
Zhanzhi.
Grandmother is right.
No matter what hurdles I face,
I must overcome them.
(Bailu Academy)
Lang Mengzi,
Yanwan didn't show up today?
He's on a date with Yan Boyang.
If the marriage is confirmed,
she'd be his first wife
and she will not attend school anymore.
Lady Xie.
Something went wrong.
Li is gone.
Duke of Wuguo sent for you.
What?
Xiaoman is here.
What happened to Li'er?
Was he absent from classes today?
He came by this morning,
but he was gone in a wink.
We searched the entire academy.
No one has seen Xie Li.
Did something happen at home
so he returned?
No.
He has been
staying at Duke's Mansion
the last few days.
Nothing happened at home.
Where could he go?
Is it because
I reprimanded him yesterday?
This is bad.
Wujiang Prefecture is huge.
What if he was abducted by
the human traffickers?
Do not panic.
I've sent men
to check the mansion
and Residence of the Su Family.
Let's search the streets first.
All right.
Xingzhou,
return to the mansion and inform Liangji
to increase the manpower.
If we fail to find him,
head to Arms Instructor Qin
outside the city.
All right.
Let's go.
Slow down.
We agreed to meet at Xiang Bridge.
Where is he?
Sister Su.
Li'er.
What are you doing here?
Are you absent from school?
I'm waiting for a friend.
We agreed to meet here.
I wrote her a letter.
What did you say in your letter?
Today at noon,
see you at Xiang Bridge.
Zhanzhi.
Zhanzhi?
Yes.
Zhanzhi has been thinking and
yearning for you.
(From Zhanzhi)
- Li'er.
Li'er.
Excuse me.
Have you seen a kid this tall?
Have you seen
a child with a book bag?
He's around this tall.
No.
Thank you.
Li'er.
Have you seen a kid this tall,
carrying a book bag?
No.
Thank you.
Where
could he be?
Don't worry.
Xie Li will be fine.
He's probably playful
so he's out playing somewhere.
It's all my fault.
I reprimanded him yesterday.
He's still young.
He couldn't take it.
Why did I
scold him?
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
Let's question him when we find him.
All right?
Your Highness.
We found him.
Where is he?
Sit right here.
What's going on?
I wanted to write a letter,
but I didn't have large vocabulary.
I didn't want Fenniang to laugh at me.
While strolling on the streets,
I found a letter.
(From Zhanzhi)
I copied everything down
exactly.
Except to meet at the bridge,
I wrote that myself.
(From Zhanzhi)
Why do you have that letter as well?
I gave it to Fenniang.
(Do you still remember that)
(back at Mount Kunyan Temple,)
(you got me out of trouble?)
(Back then, I knew)
(you were different from the rest.)
(You're genuine and loyal.)
(You're a lady yet you
possess qualities of a man.)
(Every time when I'm in trouble,)
(you always came to my rescue.)
(To others,)
(I may be unreliable,)
(but before you,)
(I really want to be bold.)
(Sometimes, I thought to myself,)
(if I had confessed)
(my feelings earlier,)
(could things)
(have ended up differently?)
(After falling in love with you,)
(I came to realize what it means for)
(the longing to disappear,)
(only to return thereafter.)
Did you
pick these up and copy them?
Xie Li.
Why are you here?
Do you know how worried we are?
Minggu,
what are you doing here?
Sister Minggu and I are on a date.
You...
Do you know where Yan Boyang is?
Boyang is at Taiping Tavern.
He's having a meal with
Prefect Xue and his family.
What's wrong?
Minggu.
Do you know everyone
is out looking for you?
Why did you run away?
Why are you crying?
I...
Just apologize for your mistake.
I'm sorry, sister.
Don't be mad.
I can no longer
see Fenniang whom I like.
Fenniang?
Who is Fenniang?
Fenniang is a student
of the academy.
She's leaving for Tongzhou today.
She will not come to school anymore.
I'll not be able to see her again.
All right. Stop crying.
I'll take you to her.
Along with your sister,
we will find Fenniang with you.
Are you coming?
Yes.
Hurry up and apologize to your sister.
Sister, I was wrong.
Don't be mad at me.
Do not disappear like this anymore.
Do you understand?
Let's go.
Where is he?
Lady.
Which room is the young master
of Bureaucrat Yan in?
Bureaucrat Yan?
West room on the second floor.
All right.
Thank you.
(Yayi Workshop)
We invited your family over today.
Yanwan is a great child.
I know that very well.
This hairpin
was chosen by Boyang himself.
Let him help you put in on.
Boyang.
Yan Boyang!
Who is this?
How unruly.
Minggu.
What are you doing here?
Madam Yan.
Madam Xue.
My apology.
Come with me.
Boyang.
What's going on?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Yanwan,
I need to talk to Yan Boyang.
I'm really sorry.
Please go ahead.
Come with me.
Boyang.
Let's go.
Mother.
- Yan Boyang.
- Mother.
Boyang.
Mother.
Look at this child.
I do not want to marry.
I do not want to marry to Yan Boyang.
Su Minggu.
What's wrong with you?
How could you
drag me out like this?
What do you want?
I read all the letters
you wrote to me.
You can't restart your past.
Let bygones be bygones.
Longing is found on the fragrant lilacs
as they bloom in spring.
I hope you'd understand
my true feelings
and believe me.
I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm sorry.
Boyang,
I'm the heir to Su Chang Ji.
I've always been just and honest.
I thought I was frank and forthright.
I haven't wronged anyone.
However, in terms of love,
I've wronged you.
All I cared about
were things out of my reach.
I neglected you who never left my side.
In the past, I was ignorant
of your feelings for me.
All I cared about was Xingzhou.
I cared about no one else.
I didn't know
that someone has been
by my side this whole time.
I was foolish. I was dumb.
I did not cherish what I had.
I pushed you away.
I took your effort for granted.
My grandmother told me that
I must overcome all the hurdles I face.
I cannot take the shortcut
or I'll regret it.
I didn't know what it means
until I realized
you and Xue Yanwan are getting engaged.
That's when I realized
how sad I was.
Boyang.
Thank you for your kindness.
Thank you for all that
you've done for me.
I dragged you out and talked nonsense.
I must have ruined your mood.
You should head inside.
I shall leave.
Minggu.
Su Minggu!
Stand right there!
I do not want Xue Yanwan.
I don't want anyone else.
Since the beginning,
you're the only one I loved.
Even if you do not feel the same,
even if you're in love
with someone else,
even if I'm only a friend to you,
keep this in mind, Su Minggu,
I will
only love you for the rest of my life.
Stop screaming.
Stop embarrassing me in public.
I'm dumb.
I'm not a man of ambition.
I might not be good enough for her.
Will you
talk to her on my behalf?
I'm willing to stay by her side.
I'll cheer her up when she's upset.
When she's bullied,
I'll be the first to protect her.
I'll only
be nice to her alone.
Can she give me a chance?
I'm not as good as you described.
You're perfect in every way.
So perfect that I'm
willing to wait for you
to fall in love with me
and until you're willing to marry me.
I'll wait for you.
Su Minggu.
I love you.
♪I'm blessed to have met you♪
♪The wind blows away the dust♪
♪Thinking back, it's what I experienced♪
♪The lonely heaven on earth♪
We couldn't make it.
Xie Li.
When I was young, my brother told me
that if you speak to the valley,
it'd reply you.
Would you like to try?
Fenniang!
Where are you?
Did you hear that?
As it echoes through the valley,
it might reach Fenniang.
Give it a try.
Fenniang!
I've always wanted to be
your best friend!
Fenniang!
Sister, did you hear that?
I heard it.
Fenniang!
Xie Xiaoman!
I love you!
Fenniang!
Xie Xiaoman!
Hurry up and marry me!
Let's give birth to a cute baby!
Xie Xiaoman!
You're allowed to be a teacher!
After you marry me,
do not ever shut me out of your room!
Do you hear me?
Fenniang!
I'll be waiting for you
at Wujiang Prefecture!
Fenniang!
I'll be waiting for you
at Wujiang Prefecture!
I've always wanted
to be your best friend!
Fenniang!
(Residence of the Xie Family)
Lord,
this is Su Chang Ji's ledger.
The time has come.
Old Madam Su's body
is failing.
I intended
to offer you the store of Su Chang Ji
a long time ago.
Are you serious about seizing
Su Family's possessions?
Old Madam Su's body
is failing her.
With your help, after it's done,
Su Chang Ji's ledger?
marry your daughter off to Tongzhou,
I'll give the store back at
Tongzhou as a token of
appreciation.
That could be considered
endowment for your daughter.
What do you think?
Good idea.
Princess Consort Pu has arrived.
(Duke's Mansion)
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪