Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Time Flies and You Are Here
Episode 25
Life is like a dream and
another autumn has passed
My Lord.
The agreement
was indeed written by Su Feiyun himself.
See for yourselves.
Agreement of property distribution
This is impossible.
Su Huazhong,
do you concur that this was
your father's penmanship?
Yes.
Lord Yan.
This matter is strange.
If the agreement was real,
why didn't Su Tingshan
submit the document along
with the appeal beforehand,
but presenting it
when things aren't looking up for him?
Something is wrong
with it.
Your Highness, you're neither
the defendant
nor a witness.
Your presence in the court
is an exception.
However, you disturbed the court order.
I have no choice but to
cast you out of the court.
Guards.
Yes.
But...
Escort His Highness out of the court.
Your Highness,
this way, please.
Lord Yan,
what do you mean by this?
Escort His Highness back to his mansion.
Do not touch me!
Move it.
Yan Nengfu,
what do you think you're doing?
Let's go.
Do you know who I am?
Hanchen,
you're injured.
Let's go.
- Yan Nengfu!
- Do not overexert yourself!
You're foolish!
Be careful!
- Be careful!
- You're foolish!
Hanchen, be careful.
Wait.
You can't do this.
Be careful!
- Hanchen!
- Be careful!
What do we do?
Lord Yan,
my mother delivered a message.
The document Su Tingshan presented
does not consist of a seal or signature.
It was just a draft.
It's not an authentic agreement
of property distribution.
It cannot be considered
an official document.
Yes.
It was the wastepaper
in my father's study
stolen by this thief, Su Tingshan.
These are my mother's words.
The attendant may testify.
Yes, I can testify.
You may send the guards
to the Residence of the Su Family
to ask Old Madam Su directly.
Yes, Lord Yan.
The plaintiff, Su Tingshan,
submitted the forged evidence.
It's a blatant scheme.
The conclusion of this case
is very clear.
Why aren't you making the judgment?
That's right!
How absurd!
You have no rights to speak here!
Old Madam Su.
My daughter and granddaughter shall
inherit my stores and possession
Momo.
Are Huazhong
and Minggu's winter clothes
ready?
Old Madam Su,
don't worry.
They are all ready.
Old Madam Su.
Old Madam Su!
Madam Su!
Madam Su.
Old Madam Su...
Old Madam Su passed away.
What?
- Dear.
- What?
What happened to Old Madam Su?
Mother!
Yan Nengfu!
Why are you doing this?
Ground him in the mansion!
How dare you bend the truth.
Mother!
Let me go!
Yan Nengfu!
Let's go.
Mr. Yan.
Yan Nengfu!
What happened to Old Madam Su?
Dear.
Declare the verdict.
In regards to the dispute over
the ownership of Su Chang Ji
in Wujiang Prefecture,
the court has inspected
all the evidence presented.
All the seven stores
in Wujiang Prefecture
will be returned to Su Tingshan.
Su Huazhong and her families
have ten days to cede
the properties over to Su Tingshan.
They are to submit the tribute received
from the last three years.
If further troubles are caused,
stricter punishments will be enforced.
The case is closed.
Court is adjourned.
Lord.
Such brilliance, Lord Yan.
Lord, that's unfair!
Lord, such injustice!
Lord!
Sister-in-law.
That's unjust!
- Lord!
- We're wronged!
Sister-in-law.
Su Tingshan,
you thief!
You're despicable!
The law is fair and just.
Even the relative of royalty
submits before the law,
not to mention commoners like us.
Get out of my way!
Su Tingshan.
Calm down.
The relative of royalty?
Mother.
Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law, calm down.
Xiaoman!
Amitabha.
May Buddha bless
the peace of Prince Pu's Mansion.
May the household be blessed
with wealth and power.
Princess Consort Pu.
We shall be feared by all.
I need to see you.
Send her in.
Do you know
it's a sin to lie before Buddha.
So?
Regarding the case of Su Family,
did you bribe the magistrate?
There's no need for me to
bribe a mere local officer.
I'm asking if you were the perpetrator.
Yes.
You vile wench!
Let go of me!
In regards to the case of Su Family,
I barely put efforts.
All I did was to give it a little push.
You clearly had a defect
that others can use against.
Just like Zhong Ziyan.
Xingzhou's incident was
caused by you, too?
What are you trying to do?
More than that.
Brother?
What did you do to my brother?
Nothing has happened yet.
He's currently imprisoned
and being fed with prison meals.
If you insist to
marry Hanchen,
I can't promise
his safety.
You're aware of
how huge the capital is.
Terrible things happen at any time.
Besides, many more people
will experience these bad things.
This is all because of you, Xie Xiaoman.
You're the catastrophe
to the people around you.
What do you want from me?
Let her go.
I'll give you one last chance.
Leave him. What do you say?
What a relative of royalty.
What a benevolent woman.
How disgusting!
Stop putting up an act
by being a vegetarian and praying!
The deities you're praying to
are looking over you!
You'll receive divine retribution!
Deities exist.
When you're thrown
into the pits of hell
and suffer the torments of hell,
know that you deserve it all!
Your Highness.
Lady Xie.
You're home.
I wasn't able to pick you up
from the court just now.
His Highness...
Tell Zhao Xiaoqian
to meet me by Xushui River
at this hour tomorrow.
I need to talk to him.
Your Highness!
Lady Xie...
What's the matter?
Spit it out!
Su Family lost the court case.
Lady Xie returned
and went to meet
Her Highness at the chamber.
After that...
After that, she left.
She left a message,
asking you to meet her
by Xushui River tomorrow.
I'm not sure what's going on.
Your Highness.
Her Highness
refuses to see anyone at the moment.
Get out of my way.
Your Highness!
What did you say to Xie Xiaoman?
I only asked about
the case of Su Family.
You were the perpetrator, weren't you?
An honest and upright
official like Yan Nengfu
was tainted by you.
Why did you do such a thing?
Why are you forcing
Xie Xiaoman out of here?
Are you doing this to force me
back to the capital?
I'm doing this for your own good.
I want you to lead a good life.
Have you ever thought about it?
For the past year,
nothing good happened to you.
You were demoted as the Duke
all of a sudden
and grounded within Wujiang Prefecture.
What's next?
Your life could be in danger.
How did you know
what's important to me
and what's not?
You took away everything
that matters to me.
If I've decided not to live,
don't even think of
surviving on your own either.
You want
me dead?
You can't
possibly go against the palace.
Don't you know
how your brother died?
How did my brother die?
What happened in the palace?
Make yourself clear!
Amitabha.
Why?
Grandmother!
Stop it, child.
Open up!
Boyang!
Let me out!
Stop it.
Open up!
Boyang.
Stop it, Boyang.
- Father!
- Boyang,
don't blame your father.
Your father didn't have a choice.
Let me out of here!
- Open up!
- Listen to me.
Open up!
Don't blame your father.
Why?
We're just a chess piece to others.
Don't blame your father, all right?
Boyang.
Why?
Da'e Noodles
Xiaoman.
What happened to the case of Su Family?
Why did everyone say...
If I could watch the snow with you,
it'd be great.
Xiaoman.
What are you saying?
What's going on?
Did my mother
say something to you yesterday?
Did you know that
they all said
it's not going to snow here
in Wujiang Prefecture this year.
The snow in Wujiang Prefecture
is a rare sight.
I was just thinking.
If I could watch the snow with you
by the warm fire
while drinking warm wine,
how great it'd be?
Xiaoman.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Your mother wants me to leave you.
I agreed.
We shouldn't get married.
Let's stop meeting
each other, all right?
No.
I can't agree to this.
What happened?
What did
my mother say to you yesterday?
Don't worry.
With me here,
everything will be...
Hanchen.
But, we lost the court case.
But, Old Madam Su passed away.
But, my brother
is about to be imprisoned.
Do you understand?
Our marriage
isn't just about us.
It will implicate others as well.
Previously,
I really wanted to marry you.
I used to think
the problems between us
were due to the fact
we weren't a true couple.
However, I've come to realize now.
It's not
because we aren't truly married,
it's because
we can never
be together.
Hanchen.
I'm sorry.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I disagree!
I said I disagree!
I'll resolve everything,
except for this!
I disagree!
You can't agree to this either.
A day later
Bailu Academy
Bailu Academy has been educating
students for a few decades.
We have been
honest and honourable.
We instilled knowledge and
morality into the students of Wujiang.
Our contribution may not be huge,
but our efforts are honourable.
All of you educated under my care
and taught the ways
of the righteousness.
Our consciences are clear before
the heaven and the people.
However, I'm incompetent.
I failed to protect the academy
for all of you.
Bailu Academy
is shutting down.
Fellow teachers,
why are you all so disheartened?
We worked very hard.
We can now take a break.
We may quit as teachers
and live like wandering intellectuals.
Cheer up.
Principal.
It's due to the change of circumstances.
Nobody is to blame.
Do not blame yourself.
That's right.
With reunion, comes separation.
Everything comes and goes.
If we're able to reunite
in the days to come,
I, Gao,
will serve as a teacher
at your new academy.
Thank you for the favour.
Fellow teachers,
after leaving the academy,
do not forget to uphold education
and answer the questions
and wonders of people.
Teach, nurture,
and develop civilization.
Of course.
My cousin brother
coaches the kids in the capital cuju.
I'll head to him
and nurture
young talents of archery and riding.
I, Gao,
shall return to my hometown.
I'll teach the illiterate
and cheeky kids
to write and read.
Teacher Liu.
What are your plans?
I will head to the capital
to establish an academy for ladies.
I intend to pass down the knowledge
and etiquette to ladies of the world.
That's commendable.
Teacher Liu has always been far-sighted.
You always contribute to the ladies.
You deserve our admiration.
What about Congwen?
What are your plans?
I just returned from the capital.
I have been around.
I'm planning to travel down
south to further my studies.
All good things come to an end.
I shall replace tea with wine
as a toast to all of you.
Principal.
The official documents
are not released yet.
The students still have
one more test to go.
I wonder if we could postpone
the closing of the academy.
At this point,
I'm afraid the magistrate
will not allow this.
Your Highness,
I found the person that
you were looking for.
He's currently in the barrack
of General Xu at Tengzhou.
But, General Xu is leaving soon.
You're looking for Fuweng?
Why?
A few days ago,
I learned that there was a conspiracy
about my brother's death
from my mother.
Could the death of
Duke of Yongguo be related to...
Yes.
The Empress.
I've resided in Wujiang Prefecture
for many years.
I stay away from the matters
of the imperial palace,
but they refuse to let me go.
Everything that has happened
wasn't coincidental.
What do you plan to do?
I'm meeting Fuweng.
I shall investigate the true cause
to my brother's death.
Perhaps, I may be able to resolve
the dilemma of Xiaoman.
By the way,
are you aware that Bailu Academy
is shutting down?
Grand Secretariat Qin and
Chancellor Xu are in dispute.
Chancellor Xu
made Li Guangwen the scapegoat.
The one who has been
funding Bailu Academy
in secret was Li Guangwen.
After investigation,
Bailu Academy will be shut down.
Master,
let's go home.
Master.
You've been standing out here
the whole night.
Look...
Master.
Funeral
Members of my family
shall heed my last words
for the generations to come.
Do not allow your ambitions
to be swayed by poverty.
Do not allow anger to
disturb you.
The revival of the household
shall be within reach.
Mother!
Document
All of Su Family's assets
will be given to Su Tingshan
What's the problem?
The verdict was altered.
In Tongzhou and Wujiang Prefecture,
Su Family's businesses,
stores,
properties, houses,
fields and lands
are all taken by Su Tingshan.
Document
There is no justice.
This is too much!
I'm going to confront him right now!
- Minggu.
Luckily I still own
a couple of stores in the capital.
Don't we even have the rights
to seek justice?
I refuse to believe this!
- I refuse to believe this!
- Hold it right there!
Members of my family
shall heed my last words
for the generations to come.
Do not allow your ambitions
to be swayed by poverty.
Do not allow anger to
disturb you.
The revival of the household
shall be within reach.
But, mother,
- We...
- Stop it.
Our family is safe and sound.
It's better than anything else.
From today onwards,
focus on the funeral and rites.
Do not bring this up ever again.
In memory of my late mother
I need to talk to you.
How are you recently?
I'm leaving for a few days.
When I'm not around,
please take care of yourself.
It's getting colder. Put on more layers.
The academy is in trouble.
In a few days,
the magistrate might approach you.
When I'm not around,
don't oppose them directly.
Don't worry.
I'll resolve everything
and come for you after.
Wait for me.
The painful farewell at Nanpu.
The autumn wind blows,
amplifying the sorrow of separation.
Once you say goodbye,
do not turn back anymore.
This is the last poem of the day.
It's also my last class
for all of you.
What does teacher mean?
The academy is in a predicament
and it's shutting down.
From now on,
I'll no longer be your teacher.
Why is it shutting down?
What's the matter?
You may have heard the rumors.
Due to certain issues, the academy
was implicated.
The magistrate has orders
to confiscate and
shut Bailu Academy down.
The academy is forbidden
from teaching anymore.
How could this be?
Do not turn back.
Separation and union
are parts of the journey.
Although you're ladies,
you're literate and knowledgeable.
I hope you will all
keep up the good work
and seek improvement diligently
to obtain a bright future of your own.
However,
you said,
before Chinese New Year's Eve,
there will be an examination
for Jingnv Pavilion.
I spent the whole year preparing
in order to score good grades
and make my mother proud.
How could the academy
shut down just like that?
I do not believe this.
I will not allow this!
That's right.
We have yet to take our exams.
Yes.
We haven't taken our exams.
Teacher Liu.
Let us take the exams.
Please make a request.
It will work.
That's right.
Please do your best.
It should work.
One winter passed,
and everything changed.
Grandmother...
Grandmother passed away as well.
Did you know?
I never liked taking exams.
However,
it's different this time.
I really want to score well
and show grandmother
so she could be at ease.
I can't believe
we are no longer allowed
to undertake the examinations.
Minggu.
I need to talk to you.
Do not call me Minggu.
I have nothing to say to you.
At this point,
everything you say is meaningless.
I know it's too late to explain myself,
but can you stop ignoring me?
Tell me.
What can I do to atone for it?
- I...
- Atone?
What are you going to do?
Can you resurrect my grandmother?
Can you?
I...
Help!
The authority is
shutting the academy down!
Guys!
What's going on?
What's happening?
What are you doing?
Move out of the way!
Bailu Academy
What are you doing?
You can't close the academy down.
Get lost.
You can't enter.
Hurry and get out of the way.
The academy is closed down.
Pack up and leave!
What are you trying to do?
Why are you shutting our academy down?
Move out of the way!
Do you have the document?
You have no rights!
Where's the document?
You can't enter.
I'm warning you.
The academy
is currently under the magistrate
of Wujiang Prefecture.
No.
Classes have yet to end.
The principal hasn't said a word.
You're not allowed
to shut the academy down.
That's right!
Xie Xiaoman.
You're involved in everything.
Listen to me.
The academy is under the authority.
Are you expecting us to believe that?
Do you have the document?
That's right!
You can't close the academy
without the document!
Present the document!
How absurd!
Is this
that education you received?
I'm telling you.
How dare you disobey?
I'll arrest you all!
Do it then!
How dare you?
We're not afraid of you!
You have no rights to arrest us!
Let's see who got the nerve!
Come on! I dare you!
You can't close the academy!
No!
Minggu!
Did you push her?
What are you doing?
Mr. Yan,
you're overstepping your bounds.
I have more to show.
Give it another try.
You're all rebelling.
Arrest them all!
All right!
Arrest me first.
I was about to check with my father.
Why are you shutting
the academy down before
the official document is here?
- That's right!
- Where is the document?
That's right! You have no rights!
You...
Lord,
he's
still the son of Lord Yan.
What do you think?
Fine.
Let's see how long you can last.
Let's go!
Get out of here!
Move it!
Get lost!
Bailu Academy
Get out of here!
Get lost!
Do not show up ever again!
Leave!
Get lost!
Don't come to our academy!
Get out of here!
Leave!
Don't come to our academy!
Residence of the Su Family
Minggu.
Are you planning to
cut ties with Yan Boyang completely?
I know it isn't Yan Boyang's fault.
However, under such circumstances,
I cannot allow my mother
to handle Su Chang Ji alone.
I have to help her.
That's the end for
Yan Boyang and I.
Xiaoman,
will I be able to
manage Su Chang Ji like my mother?
You can surely do it.
I believe in you.
Where's the Minggu I know?
I'll be honest with all of you.
Su Chang Ji is in trouble.
Since the beginning, Su Chang Ji
started off with minor businesses
and eventually developed
into a textile workshop,
and finally,
the current reputable textile store.
Our reputation was
widespread through the state.
We were once at the pinnacle of glory.
Everything was built and accumulated
from scratch with the effort
of my parents.
However, I, Su Huazhong failed
to protect the family business.
I fell into a trap
of the malicious thugs.
Here are my savings.
Distribute them among yourselves
and go on your way.
Madam Su.
It's been many years.
You took great care of us.
You don't owe us anything.
It's the other way round.
Madam Su.
What do you plan to do next?
If you're venturing into a new business,
we're not leaving.
We will strive alongside you.
That's right.
Right now,
there are many matters to attend to.
As for the rest,
I haven't figured out yet.
We still possess
two new stores in the capital.
Mother,
let's start over in the capital.
Minggu,
do not interrupt when
the adults are talking.
Mother,
I'm not a child anymore.
Everyone calls me
the successor of the business.
Today,
I'm going to perform my duty
as the successor.
Mother, you know
the textile industry best.
You could tell
the quality of any textile
by one touch.
With this skill,
you don't have to worry
about reopening
Su Chang Ji in the capital.
Father is meticulous with the accounts.
He may help with the account.
I'll learn the operation of a store
and help manage the business.
I believe that
the capital is a huge place,
there will be a spot for us.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪