Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Time Flies and You Are Here
Episode 27
We're to be loyal
to the Emperor and the Imperial Court
Hurry up.
Paste it properly.
That's right.
His Highness is back.
Your Highness.
What happened again?
Your Highness,
today is the Chinese New Year's Eve.
We have no idea where
His Highness went
and he has yet returned.
I'm afraid...
At this point,
if he's still so obstinate,
he'll end up with nothing.
Your Highness, haven't you taken enough
from me?
Princess Consort Pu who
has a noble status
enjoys glory and riches,
and is admired by the people.
However, perhaps no one knows
all of this was exchanged
with others' lives.
Your Highness,
today's the Chinese New Year's Eve.
Her Highness
has been waiting for you
for the reunion dinner.
Scram.
It isn't your place to speak.
Leave.
Leave, all of you.
Without my order,
no one is allowed to enter.
It's the Chinese New Year
and you lost your temper
in my room for no reason.
That's the manner
in Duke of Wuguo's Mansion?
No reason?
Mother, you even have the guts
to say I lost my temper for no reason.
You must've done too many bad things.
As a result, you lost
a sense of judgment.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Am I wrong?
Look carefully
at the grandeur of this mansion
as well as your clothing and jewelry.
Just name one
that wasn't exchanged with
my brother's life?
Sacrificing your own son's life
to retain your own honour,
our family
indeed has a tender mother
and filial sons.
We're upright in conduct.
It's really enviable.
Outrageous!
What are you saying?
I don't know what you are talking about.
I've found Fuweng
and found out
the truth of my brother's death.
Do you think I don't know anything?
Do you think that I'm still a child?
I know
you've always felt resentful
towards your father and me
for sending you to the imperial palace.
Do you think I wanted that?
Do you think I wasn't feeling sad?
I remember you won't let go of me
and pleaded with me while crying.
I was heartbroken, too.
I pleaded with His Majesty
and the Empress,
but all was in vain.
What else can I do?
That's the imperial palace
and the Emperor of a nation.
Can I go against them
or fight with them?
I
could only resign to fate.
What's to blame is,
as mother and son, you and I
are destined to be separated.
Yes.
We aren't destined to be mother and son.
So, having killed one of your sons,
are you going to kill the other now?
I'm still your mother no matter what.
I told you to return to the capital
in order to save your life.
I've decided to go to the battlefront
and go to Baichuankou with General Xu.
What?
Zhao Xiaoqian,
I gave birth to you and raised you
so you could leave my side again?
Why?
Why are you risking
the future of the entire
Prince Pu's Mansion?
When my brother was killed back then,
you were also this cold-blooded.
You always put your own benefits first.
You've never thought about my feelings.
Do you know what
returning to the capital
means to me?
Hanchen.
Making myself the opponent's prey!
Do you know
what going to the battlefront means?
I don't care!
At least I'll survive
and stop being manipulated by others.
It's my final chance.
I've already decided.
Even if I die,
it'll be at Baichuankou.
Your Highness,
you're finally back.
How long have you been
my mother's spy in this mansion?
Your Highness,
I've followed you for so long.
You...
You've wronged me.
Sell her off to the southern region!
Your Highness.
Don't ever let me see you again.
Princess Consort.
Your Highness, save me!
Zhu Momo!
Zhu Momo, save me!
Lotus Garden
♪I hear that my trouble is lingering♪
♪The gentleness is my missing for you♪
What should we do?
Today, Old Madam Su
was telling us to have a baby.
Old Madam didn't say that.
It was aunt who said so.
Don't take it to heart.
♪I'm blessed to have met you♪
♪The wind blows away the dust♪
♪Thinking back, it's what I experienced♪
♪The lonely heaven on earth♪
Lotus Garden
Brother-in-law. Sister-in-law.
You're here.
Happy Chinese New Year.
Brother. Sister-in-law.
Uncle. Aunt.
Come on.
Happy Chinese New Year.
Serve the dishes.
Let the feast begin. It's ready.
The dishes are turning cold. Come on.
That's good.
Come on.
Come on, Xiaoman.
I'll pour you a cup of wine.
Sure.
Come on, fill the cups.
We just held a funeral,
so all the ceremonies are simpler.
After the Chinese New Year,
we'll depart.
Sure.
Everyone says the new year
is a challenge.
But the way I see it,
what's even more challenging
are the weals and woes
in the coming year.
Woes or not,
we've gone through it all.
No matter what,
our family is well.
No matter how tricky it is,
it's good that all of us are around.
That's right.
Whatever challenge there was,
we've gone through each of them.
It's the Chinese New Year.
Let's not talk about the sad past.
From now on,
we'll surely become better and better.
Our family
will gain harmony
and prosper in all endeavours.
We'll prosper.
- That's right.
- We'll prosper.
If the family lives in harmony,
all affairs will prosper.
That's right.
Rise joint by joint
like "chicken flowers".
It's rise joint by joint
like sesame flowers.
You only know how to eat chicken.
Come on. Come on.
Lady.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Bottoms up.
Lady Xie,
the concierge outside passed this,
saying it's for you.
To Xiaoman
Who left the letter?
I don't know,
but I recognize this pot of soil.
It's the pot His Highness
used to pray for a child
on the Lotus Garden's platform.
Residence of the Su Family
I'm back.
Xiaoman.
It has been a while.
Residence of the Su Family
I came this time
to bid you farewell.
That's all you came here to tell me?
Yes.
I'm afraid this time,
I'm really going to the battlefield.
Serving the nation
is quite good.
What about you?
Me?
I'm going to the capital
after the Chinese New Year.
My aunt opened up a new shop there.
Teacher Liu is also setting up
an academy there.
I'm going to teach there.
I'm going to be a teacher.
Great.
That's what I like about you.
Live on and never admit defeat.
Residence of the Su Family
The first snow is here.
Yes
I saw it.
We saw it together.
I'm sorry.
♪Cherry blossom withers♪
♪It ends before my eyes♪
Remember.
There's only one Zhao Xiaoqian
in this world.
You mean the world to him.
♪The horse has gone far♪
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Keep going
further and further.
♪It hurts me and it's borderless♪
♪I can never see you again♪
Press forward with indomitable will.
Best of luck.
♪Lonely grass in the wild,
I'm wandering around♪
Happy Chinese New Year.
Happy Chinese New Year!
♪I cry for you in my dreams♪
♪I can hardly remember when I'm awake♪
♪Lonely grass in the wild,
I'm wandering around♪
Qingtai Gate
♪If the fire is not put off♪
♪It'll burn again in spring♪
♪There's only gloomy day here.♪
♪Unrelated to happiness or sadness♪
♪Leaving me in the faraway romance♪
♪How should I mention♪
General Zhao.
♪Your name?♪
Did you forget someone?
Your Highness needed a learning partner
when you were studying.
In the future, when you draft
the military orders in the camp,
won't you also need one
to prepare the brushes and ink?
Life in the camp is full of danger
and difficulties,
unlike the easy life in
the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
You've really thought it over?
Since the masters are
not complaining that it's difficult
or tiring,
how can those who serve
become so picky?
What about your family?
What about the imperial examination?
Attain the fourth rank by the age of 30.
Enter the privy council at 40.
Become the grand chancellor at 50.
What about those?
You won't follow that path anymore?
Did Your Highness think,
as your learning partner,
I'll watch my master
go to the battlefield alone?
If you'd cherish my talent,
I'd fight till the end for you.
I, Zhong Ziyan, am willing to serve you
as your foot soldier.
Mr. Li,
my lady gives this to you.
Where's Xiaoman?
She said
you'll understand
after reading the letter.
Your time to shine will come.
Seize every opportunity.
She said
you'll always be
the most talented scholar to her.
She hopes that
you'll continue to write books.
As long as you don't give up,
that day will come when you'll
be crowned with eternal glory.
I should go.
Goodbye, Mr. Li.
Father!
Please show some mercy!
Allow me to attend the imperial academy
in the capital!
I promise I'll do my best
to get a rank to glorify you!
Father!
I'm begging you!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
In the new year,
I hope all is well with us.
Wangchao Gate
Madam,
it's about time
to depart.
Qingtai Gate
Let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go. Get on the carriage.
Minggu.
Let's go.
Minggu!
Wait for me!
I'll go with you.
Yan Boyang,
stop fooling around.
I'm not.
I've got my father's permission.
I'm going there anyway,
so I might as well get
some companions.
We can look after each other.
Are you not fooling around?
This is a big deal.
Cut it out.
You wouldn't know this,
but I'm going to attend
the imperial academy in the capital.
My father has written a letter
to his friend who is a teacher
at the imperial academy.
Everything's been arranged for.
Now that the school is
about to open soon,
I need to enrol.
Minggu,
we'll be at the same place again.
It's great.
The journey there is not easy
and we'll be miles away from home.
Have you really thought it over
to go with us?
Of course.
I'm a grown-up now.
Since you're going,
you need to score well in
the imperial examination
and bring glory to the family.
If you're still fooling around
when you're there,
I won't talk to you.
Rest assured.
I'll definitely
become more mature bit by bit.
I'll be responsible
for my choice and future.
There's no seat for you
on our horse carriage.
Don't worry, Lady Su.
Our carriage is going
to be here anytime.
In order to see you,
he even outran the carriage.
Oh, right.
If you feel drowsy or
sleepy on the way,
just tell me.
I'll pick fruits for you.
All right.
It's going to turn dark soon
if you keep talking.
Let's go.
Get on the carriage.
Be careful.
Capital
Congratulations.
Wishing you lots of prosperity.
- Great!
- Congratulations.
Su Chang Ji
Congratulations.
Come on in. Come on in.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Welcome. Welcome.
Keep up the good work, Young Madam Su.
Keep up the good work, Teacher Xie.
Come on in. Come on in.
Come on. Come on.
Thank you.
Imperial Academy
Lushan mountains often fool our eyes,
rolling range one minute,
towering crest the next.
The true portrait is always hidden
as we can only know someone from within.
Baichuankou
Both Baibao Village
and Taozhou
Baibao Village
have been regained.
General Xu also just sent
over a military update
Linzhou City
that they took over Linzhou City.
The bandits have all surrendered
over their weapons.
General is wise.
Now,
as long as we guard Baichuankou well,
perhaps in early spring next year,
we'll be able to return
victoriously to the capital.
We shouldn't underestimate our enemy?
Where's the scout sent out
a few days ago?
The scout isn't back yet.
Report!
General Zhao,
the scout from the front line
reported back.
Our enemy is approaching our army
since Baichuankou
currently lacks defense.
Moreover, our army is short of provisions.
I'm afraid
we won't be able to hold on for long.
What?
What should we do?
Yao Camp
is where our enemy stores provisions.
We can only obtain provisions
if we take over this place.
Send the order.
From today onwards,
every day when we cook,
use double the amount of firewood.
Also, double the flags
at each station.
Why?
Let the enemy assume our army
has a great number of soldiers
so they dare not act rashly.
Why bother?
The way I see it,
we should bring our remaining brothers
to rush out
and kill them all!
Most of our enemy's soldiers
are on horseback
whereas we have more foot soldiers.
We mustn't leave our camp
to fight with them.
Hang the truce sign high
in each camp every day.
If there's anyone
who answers the enemy's challenge
and goes on to fight,
whether it's a win or otherwise,
he'll be executed.
Yes.
Mr. Shen,
don't you want to kill the enemy?
You and I will bring
200 soldiers tonight
to rob the enemy's channel
to provisions.
How's that?
Yes!
Set off a homing pigeon
to inform General Xu.
At 11 p.m. five days later,
our army will leave to rob
the enemy's camp.
When that happens, if General Xu
doesn't rush back to our aid,
we'll fight till death,
and Baichuankou will also
fall into the enemy's hands.
Yes.
Report, General Zhao!
This is bad!
The enemy will break in soon.
Listen here, everyone.
Today, even if we fight
to the last soldier standing,
we must guard Baichuankou until we die!
Yes!
Hanchen.
Charge!
Kill!
I'll resolve everything,
except for this!
I disagree!
You can't agree to this either.
There's only one
Zhao Xiaoqian in this world.
He cherishes you like his own life.
Residence of the Su Family
Keep going
further and further.
Press forward with indomitable will.
Best of luck.
Kill!
Three years later
Capital
Continuing from last chapter.
In the battle at Baichuankou,
millions were killed and
so much blood was shed
as to float the shield.
10,000 deceased soldiers from our army
wandered everywhere
and wailed at night
as ghosts
since there weren't burial or rituals.
However, there's this army camp
they dare not get near to.
This camp...
Now,
rumors spread in the capital,
saying that General Zhao is evil.
A general's victory is built upon
thousands of sacrificed lives.
Our General Zhao
would sacrifice anyone
for military merits.
I agree.
Crows caw is heard everywhere.
The soldier opened
the camp curtain carefully.
Their General Zhao
showed his true form on
the night of full moon.
He has the face of a buffalo,
with wings sprouting from his back,
He has three heads and
three pairs of arms.
He's made of steel,
as if the Living King Yama.
Bravo! Bravo!
Grand Chancellor, Xu Huan
We won the battle at Baichuankou
by a narrow margin.
As people say, when
the Living King Yama is determined,
how can the ants in the den escape?
Waiting for the triumphant
return of the edict in peace
to finally take off the battle robes.
Do the people in the capital
call Hanchen the Living King Yama?
Well...
I'm not the one who said so.
I...
I'm just reporting what I was told,
Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
There must be a bad year
Guarding the Four Barbarians
What does it mean by
"there must be a bad year"
or "guarding the Four Barbarians"?
A bad year follows the war.
It originates from Tao Te Ching.
It means after vigorously
revitalizing the army,
there will be...
There will be a bad year.
What about
"guarding the Four Barbarians"?
You're the Crown Prince.
What are you afraid of?
"Zuo Zhuan,
23rd year of Duke of Zhao's reign"
The Emperors in the past
looked after the Four Barbarians.
It means the Emperor must
make all the regions to surrender
with his benevolence,
so there won't be a war.
Who taught you to write this way?
It's...
When will Hanchen return?
Your Majesty,
we received a letter a few days ago,
saying the army had
just left Baichuankou.
It'll take them about a month
to reach the capital.
I don't care if the Empress
told you to write this
or the grand tutor.
Remember, you're the Crown Prince,
not some literati
or sage.
The generals who protect the nation
and the people at the front line
fought the battle for three years.
If they return
to find your word,
"a bad year follows the war",
then they don't need
you as the Crown Prince.
Baichuankou
The memorial tablet of
the late soldiers of Baichuankou
Kneel!
First, kowtow to the war.
Secondly, kowtow to our comrades.
Thirdly, kowtow to
the souls of the deceased.
Get up!
The commander to offer sacrificial wine.
Offer sacrificial wine.
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share the plate for breast!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make your lances shine!
Your foe is mine!
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share the coat and vest!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make our halberds shine!
Your duty is mine!
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share kilt and the rest!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make our Armour shine!
March with your hand in mine!
It's 9 a.m.
Get up!
Qiu Da'er, archer of fifth camp,
from Liujia Village, Yongzhou.
He's been in the army for eight years
and was shot to death by arrows
in the fight at Gu City.
Deputy General Wang Zhi,
canon fighter of third camp,
from Yangwu, Chenzhou.
He joined the army three years ago.
He died of illness.
Ruan Xiaoyi,
military officer of eighth camp,
from Shihe Village, Xiuzhou.
He joined the army one year ago.
He died when guarding the city.
Qin Wei, foot solider of fourth camp,
from Zhehai Village, Jizhou.
He's been in the army for 20 years.
In the fight at Cliff Liang,
he was killed after being
encircled by the army.
Huang Liu, scout of second camp,
from Yudong Village,
Xingyuan Prefecture.
In order to safeguard the escort
of the last batch of provisions,
he was shot dead by a fire arrow.
Put down my brother!
Put him down!
I'm going to bring him back!
Why was it you who went?
Scout Huang Liu
used to be a deserter
and a local gangster
in Wujiang Prefecture.
He joined the army three years ago
and followed General Xu to Baichuankou.
In the battle to guard Gu City
over three months,
there was a shortage of provisions.
In order to safeguard
the last batch of provisions,
he went out the city gate
alone for the coordination
and was killed by a fire arrow.
Huang Liu,
Gu City
is protected.
General,
my brother and I
joined the army after
listening to your words.
You said, as a man,
we have to aspire for the great,
to fight on the battlefield,
and to protect our nation,
but does the nation
even value our lives?
Why we still haven't got the provisions?
Our brothers...
Did our brothers die in vain?
Get up.
Get up!
Bring the corpse away!
Light the fire!
Rest in peace!
No one will die in vain.
About the provisions,
I'll definitely give you an explanation.
Brothers,
wash up and pack your things.
We
are going home!
Yes!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪