Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Time Flies and You Are Here
Episode 29
Everything has changed,
dreaming of going on Fangzhou Road
How impressive.
That is impressive.
Minggu,
check that out.
That looks fun, too.
The temples outside the town
must be more interesting.
Let's head inside.
We can't.
The graduates are revealed
for the first time in the capital today.
It's an important occasion.
If you do not show up,
what happens
if your husband is abducted?
Get lost.
Come on! Who wants to be your wife!
It's so crowded.
How lively.
There are so many fishes.
Can you give me some of the fish feed?
There you go.
Thank you.
What is Xie Xiaoman doing here?
We were schoolmates.
I invited her here.
Fellow graduates,
today is the Qionglin Banquet.
By His Majesty's grace,
the Jinming Lake is open to public
in order to celebrate
the scholars who passed the exam.
Instead of focusing
merely on verbal discussion,
in conjunction to the sages
and people of the nation,
the contention of different schools
of thoughts is encouraged.
Bravo!
- Bravo!
Release the banner.
The stability of the state lies in
benevolent policies, not evoking fear.
Today's topic is
"the stability of the state
lies in benevolence, not violence."
It is coming at you.
Qionglin Banquet
The stability of the state lies in
benevolence, not violence.
Allow me
to voice my humble opinion first.
The emphasis on benevolence
instead of violence
in order to defend a state
relies essentially on the wisdom
of sages in governance
instead of strong defense
and tyrannous rulership.
In ancient times, under the reign
of King Jie of the Sanmiao Tribe,
and the reign of King Zhou of Shang,
during critical times,
although the territories
were fortified,
these rulers
failed to uphold morality,
failed to implement
effective governance,
and failed to protect their people.
In the end,
their territories were subjugated.
Everyone born in this world
has people
they care about.
In the War of Baichuankou,
of 30,000 soldiers, 10,000 were lost.
A victory gained this way
evoked agony and anger from the people.
This is unjustified.
Fellow gentleman,
are you addressing the topic
or disparaging others?
Do you know that the commander
of the War of Baichuankou
is present as well?
Since the Warring States period,
Gongsun Qi
employed military knowledge
and strategies,
assembled remarkable approaches,
and shocked the world.
Despite his brilliant
achievements in war,
the people he killed were countless,
he was no different from a mass murderer.
Right now,
a certain commander in our empire
is imitating such cruelty and atrocity.
By the excuse of annihilating the enemy,
he satiated his blood lust
through the war.
As time passes,
the order and morality of
a nation will be destroyed.
You're full of nonsense!
Don't take it personally.
Fellow scholars,
you're all disciples of the Emperor.
All of your arguments are sound.
However,
it seems like
you've all deviated from the topic.
Who are you?
I'm just here to have fun.
Since you're all disciples
of the Emperor,
I'm sure you're tolerant
and broad-minded.
The topic of the discussion is
we should emphasize benevolence
instead of violence.
However, in my opinion,
the stability of a nation
lies in both benevolence and violence.
Circumstantial advantages and
the political attitude of people
are different things altogether.
Although I'm just a commoner,
I understand that in contention,
there are always two sides.
Marching through war
is a way to subdue
the world with violence,
yet it's also a manifestation
of strong defense power of a nation.
Just like how the combination
of healers and fighters
leads to the security of a nation.
The one you're going against is me.
As for the discussion of teachings,
I'm ignorant.
However, there's one thing I know.
According to the Rites of Zhou,
those who sit in peace
while contemplating policies
are of nobility and royalty.
Those who implement
policies through action
are the literati.
Do you intend to overthrow
the Zhao Family
and replace us as royalty
or do you intend to
serve the state as a literati?
I'm rather curious.
Lingniang,
I'm bored already.
Let's take a stroll by the lake.
All right.
Look at Zhao Xiaoqian.
Xiaoman.
Look at you.
Your Highness' demeanour
is eminent and incomparable.
Even the Qionglin Banquet
has to succumb to your grandiosity.
Lingniang,
he proposed to you.
You must watch out for this man.
Brother,
don't be ridiculous.
Watch your mouth.
Xiongjie Camp's reputation
was ruined because of you.
Because of me?
The public called you a murderer.
Your Highness.
Lady Xie seeks an audience.
This show
has ended even after three years.
If you do not meet me today,
I'm not going anywhere.
Come with me.
You want to talk to me, right?
What's it?
I...
I made you knee guards.
During rainy days,
if your knees still hurt,
put them on.
They're made with medicinal herbs.
They will get rid of the cold.
My father uses them
when he suffers from arthritis.
Give them a try.
Did you come to see me
for these?
I...
In the end,
you just wanted to ask me
if I sacrificed over 10,000 of lives
for my greed to attain merits.
I wanted to ask you
what's going on recently.
Why would the Qionglin Banquet
end up this way?
What are you expecting
from me?
Xie Xiaoman.
You're pretty impressive.
You were the one who
left me in the first place,
yet you come back to me now.
Do you think I need
the knee guards you made?
What I need is women.
What's wrong?
Right now, it's your turn
to beg for my attention.
Is this what you've become
after three years?
How do you like me now?
I like.
I like very much.
Your Highness is splendid.
I'm afraid I can't keep up!
Hanchen.
Bad news.
Chancellor Xu has begun to take action.
I received secret information.
Tonight after the Qionglin Banquet,
they placed an ambush
at Tianshui Alley.
When you pass through Tianzhu Road,
do not take Tianshui Alley.
I've dispatched the covert guards
to keep you safe.
Got it.
Why did you invite
Xie Xiaoman over?
I just wanted to catch up with her.
- Where is she?
- Be honest!
I genuinely wanted to...
I just wanted to...
What's wrong?
Are you afraid?
Just because you're
the Commandery Princess Rong'an,
don't think I dare not
lay a finger on you.
Let me ask you again.
What's your purpose of inviting
Xie Xiaoman to the Qionglin Banquet?
I wanted to see whether
Commandery Prince of Julu
who asked for my hand in marriage
loves me
or her.
How will you do that?
Zipei...
Zipei placed some informants
around the entrance.
Hanchen.
Your Highness.
Young lady.
What do you want?
What do we want?
What do you think?
After her!
- Hold it right there!
- Do not run!
Hold it!
- Hold it right there!
- Stop running!
Tianshui Alley
Hold her!
- After her!
- Hold it!
Hold it right there!
Hurry up!
Stop running!
- Hold it!
- Stop running!
Do not come near me.
What?
If we do not go near,
you'd grow
impatient.
I'll kill myself if you get any closer.
How impressive.
Do you even want a corpse?
Fine.
Give it a try.
Sure.
I'll give it a try.
Big brother!
Do not make a move!
Did they hurt you?
No.
Show up in the capital again
and I'll kill all of you.
All right.
Get out of here.
Let's go.
Don't go.
I've helped you.
Why are you holding me?
If you do not explain yourself,
I'm not going to leave you.
Leave.
I'm asking you to go. Do you hear me?
You want to know
how I end up like this?
Fine.
Try to experience death
at Baichuankou.
Try to experience
how it feels watching over 10,000
of soldiers dying before you.
I returned to secure a wealthy life.
You intend to stop me?
Get over yourself.
You've changed.
We all changed.
So did you.
Get out of my sight.
Zhao Xiaoqian!
Why do you intend to assassinate me?
Zhao Xiaoqian,
you evil commander!
You have no regards
for the life of others!
For the over 10,000 of
deceased soldiers at Baichuankou,
I shall avenge
my son!
Return my son to me!
Even in his death,
my son would haunt you forever!
What's the name of your son?
My son is Zhou Shixian!
Lieutenant of Camp 57, Zhou Shixian.
He served the army for two years.
During the war at Gu City,
he died guarding the city.
Even at the last moment,
your son did not surrender to the enemy.
For my sake,
for the sake of the people,
and for the sake of his father,
he guarded the city.
He was a good soldier.
He was also a good son.
Sir,
you're being used.
If you'd like to take revenge on me,
hurry up and leave.
Watch out!
I'm the one they're after.
Run now.
After him!
Hanchen.
Mr. Zhong.
A report from the spy.
After waylaying at
Tianzhu Road for hours,
His Highness was nowhere to be seen.
I'm going to dispatch the troop.
Inform Mr. Liangji
to search for His Highness.
Yes.
Get on the boat first.
Hold it.
Do not move.
Put your sword down.
Kneel.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
There are pursuers on land.
There's an island across the lake.
We may take a breather there.
Are you all right?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Don't worry.
The arteries are unharmed.
The bleeding will stop in a while.
Get some sleep.
When the sun comes out,
they'd find us.
You're injured, too?
Let me take a look.
It's fine.
Who did you offend?
Why are they trying to kill you?
Too many people died
in the war.
Grudges were built against me.
Since they failed to kill me today,
more will come tomorrow.
You should distant yourself.
That's why
you pushed me away.
You're worried of implicating me.
If I do not push you away,
are you going to stay?
You're wrong.
I'm not pushing you away on purpose.
It's because you no longer
mean anything to me.
You're lying.
If I mean nothing to you,
why did you save me?
you should've abandoned me just now.
Why did you bring me here?
Don't you get it, Xie Xiaoman?
In the past,
I loved you more than anything.
That was the past.
Do you live in the past,
Xie Xiaoman?
That's why
you're marrying Shen Zhaowen?
Yes.
Do you like her?
Look me in the eyes.
Do you truly like her?
Yes.
You're right.
I've been living in the past.
I'm a great joke.
I'm being ridiculous.
I shouldn't have come to look for you.
At this point,
why am I still so pathetic?
Don't worry.
I'll no longer bother you ever again.
I wish all the happiness for
you and Shen Zhaowen.
Thank you.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Report!
General,
the second troop sent
a report in the morning.
The provision that was expected to
arrive at Xiliangkou during
wee hours has yet to come.
To General
Great smoke was noted at the west.
Reconnaissance was dispatched.
The seventh year of Fengheng.
Spring.
Su Chang Ji opened up a store
in the capital.
Xiaoman went to the Wujin Academy
and became the disciple
of Teacher Liu.
A huge number of enemy's Calvary
is invading.
Please dispatch soldiers in defense.
♪It ends before my eyes♪
♪You're disappearing from my life♪
To General
The seventh year of Fengheng.
Winter.
Xiaoman has finally become a teacher.
That's great.
♪The horse has gone far♪
♪Perhaps you♪
♪Will forever be gone♪
The eighth year of Fengheng.
Autumn.
Xiaoman fell greatly ill.
I wonder how she's doing right now.
♪I can never see you again♪
♪Lonely grass in the wild,
I'm wandering around♪
The ninth year of Fengheng.
Winter.
Xiaoman is 20 years old.
♪I cry for you in my dreams♪
Happy birthday.
What about Xiaoman?
When you return,
what do you plan to do with Xiaoman?
Xingzhou.
Our return to the capital this time
may invite grave danger.
I might probably die in the capital.
You might, too.
Do you regret it?
No.
I do though.
Regarding the loss
of provisions at Baichuankou,
I'll not let that slide.
In order to eliminate
Chancellor Xu and his party,
I must become
the Imperial Grand Governor.
Are you saying
the evidence could be found
in the magistrate office?
In order to seize
the governance of the capital
and investigate this matter in secret
without their detection,
I have to show them that
I aim at something else.
After the throne?
Become the Imperial Grand Governor,
request to marry Shen Zhaowen,
openly covet after the throne,
and investigate the correlation
between Chancellor Xu and
the loss of Baichuankou's
provisions covertly.
No, Hanchen.
This is too dangerous.
Not only Chancellor Xu
would eliminate you,
even His Majesty would not allow this.
Xingzhou.
Many lives at Baichuankou
were trusted with me.
I failed to bring them home.
These lives
are debts I have to pay.
My life
was long given to Baichuankou.
My life doesn't matter.
You and Xiaoman are different.
You must stay alive.
Find this person for me after
returning to the capital.
Li Guangwen.
After finding him,
leave the capital with Xiaoman.
Do not return no matter what happens.
If I'm still alive,
I'll find you guys.
After this,
I may commit grave crimes.
I'll be penalized by the public.
Perhaps, we may not be
able to enjoy a drink
just like the old days anymore.
Perhaps...
Perhaps, I might even hurt her.
However,
I want you to keep this in mind.
I'll always be the Zhao Xiaoqian
you used to know.
If I die,
spare
these from her.
Your Highness!
Hanchen!
I'll arrange someone to
pick you up after I leave.
Hanchen!
Hanchen.
Are you all right?
Are you injured?
Xingzhou told me that you were missing.
We searched the entire night for you.
I'm fine.
Inform Xie Family to pick her up.
Come with me.
You asked me yesterday
if I genuinely want to marry you.
I'll give you my answer today.
Hanchen,
we can talk tomorrow.
In future...
The answer is no.
Everything you've done in the past,
I may let them slide.
Perhaps, I have yet made
things clear to you.
Marrying you
is but a play for power.
I told you this before.
I may repeat myself.
It's only a play for power.
There are no feelings attached.
It was my fault for giving you
the wrong idea.
Hanchen.
I'm sorry.
You wondered
whom my heart belongs to.
Today, I can also
tell you the answer clearly.
It's Xiaoman.
It was her in the past.
It's the same right now.
In the future,
it will still be her.
I'm sorry.
Hanchen!
Commandery Prince's Mansion
Hanchen,
this was found on the assassin.
This case has been
reported to the imperial palace.
Grand Chancellor's Mansion
Chancellor Xu wouldn't have thought
that his assassination
would work if I was dead.
I'm not dead,
so he has done me a favor.
He's shooting himself in the foot.
He has been the grand chancellor
for over 20 years.
I'm afraid he's used to
doing whatever he wants,
but he's going to fail by the hands
of an insignificant man like me.
What are you planning to do?
I'm entering the imperial palace
to ask for a position.
Are you planning to
threaten His Majesty?
Are you serious?
Xiaoman.
Congwen.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
The boatman is an old friend of mine.
I spoke to him.
He'll not reveal this incident.
Don't worry.
As for the reason you
spent the night out,
I'll not question you either.
However, your family is concerned.
The neighbors may
gossip here and there.
Do not let it affect you.
I don't want you
to experience such slander either.
Xiaoman,
will you marry me?
Three years ago,
I missed out on you
due to my indecisiveness.
After three years,
I do not want to repeat
the same mistake again.
Xiaoman.
Marry me.
Allow me to fulfil your dreams.
We shall leave this place of strife
and live our lives as
regular husband and wife.
Will you say yes?
I'll repeat myself.
The governance of the capital
belongs to the Crown Prince.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Are you coveting after my throne?
I dare not.
The Crown Prince is still young.
Chancellor Xu is tyrannous.
I'm the Commandery Prince of Julu
Your Majesty granted personally.
In broad daylight,
he attempted to assassinate me.
Your Majesty claimed
that I wanted to rob the title
of the Crown Prince.
Your Majesty, don't you know that
they want me dead?
Shut up!
I may keep quiet,
but the soldiers in Baichuankou
will not be able to.
What did you say?
I said,
I may keep quiet,
but if the entire nation learns
that the Emperor of the nation
and the Grand Chancellor in office
would openly assassinate a general
who just returned after a victory,
the people will not keep quiet!
Your Majesty's reputation
would be at stake.
The soldiers in Baichuankou
would not let this slide, too!
If you do not want anyone
to find out about this,
please grant me the title
of the Imperial Grand Governor.
Grand Chancellor's Mansion
All shall heed.
By the grace of god and heaven,
for the sake of the greater good,
for the honourable deed
of fighting the enemies
to defend the stability of the state,
such achievement has brought
blessing to the nation,
and secured the foundation
of the state.
My nephew, Xiaoqian,
displays loyalty and bravery.
At the same time, he upholds
the teachings of a gentleman.
He is a great defender of the state,
with merits of quelling
the war by the borders.
Alas,
a secure state brings peace.
The state's reputation
ought to be upheld.
I know my son well.
With a clear conscience
towards the forefathers,
Xiaoqian shall be promoted as
the Imperial Grand Governor.
All shall heed the imperial edict.
Lady Shen.
You might injure yourself.
He said it!
He has no feelings for me.
He only has feelings for Xie Xiaoman.
Even if I'm injured,
nobody would care.
Since Zhao Xiaoqian
does not care about my feelings,
he can't blame me for being ruthless.
I refuse to believe,
for the sake of Xie Xiaoman,
he'd...
He'd make Shen Family an enemy
at a moment like this.
Su Chang Ji
Get out of the way!
Get out of here!
Get lost!
Officer!
Shut the place down.
Officer.
Let's talk it out.
What are you doing?
Su Chang Ji can no longer
open the store here.
What?
Why not?
Who do you think you are?
Su Chang Ji has
signed a contract.
You can't violate
the terms just like that.
Are you the shopkeeper?
Yes, I am.
Officer.
It's me.
I'm the shopkeeper.
She's my daughter.
You may speak to me.
A few days ago,
Commandery Princess Rong'an
bought some silk from your store.
She claimed the goods to be fake.
That's impossible!
We...
We would never sell fake silk.
We're Su Chang Ji of Wujiang Prefecture.
I'm sure you've heard.
It must be a misunderstanding.
Arrest him!
Move it!
- Officer!
- Father!
Minggu!
- Let's talk it out!
- Release my father!
Do not resort to violence!
You're abusing your power
and bullying the commoners!
You accuse Su Chang Ji
of selling fake silk!
Check it yourself!
There isn't any fake silk!
Go ahead!
Commandery Princess Rong'an
said the goods are fake.
You can't
possibly deny that.
To Xie Fu An
Commandery Princess Rong'an?
Shen Zhaowen?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪