Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Time Flies and You Are Here
Episode 26
It's cold and passers-by are hardly
seen, there's no point staying here
All the shopkeepers here
have taught me a lot.
You've contributed greatly
to Su Family over the years.
Our family
has decided to start over
in the capital.
I wonder if you all
are willing to follow us?
I'm willing.
Lady Su,
count me in.
Count me in.
- I'm also going.
- I'm willing.
All right.
I'm also going.
When I first arrived in
Wujiang Prefecture,
you two took care of me.
Sister-in-law, if you don't mind,
when you arrive at the capital,
even if you ask me to run errands,
I'll never complain.
Let's go all together.
I don't know how to do business,
but I'm at least capable of chores
like laundry and cooking.
Su Chang Ji
is thankful for everyone.
Since it has come to this,
I just want to ask everyone.
What exactly makes
Su Chang Ji prosper until this day?
Is it the few shopfronts
which were snatched by that thief?
No!
Su Chang Ji relied on all of you
being honest in running the business
without selling inferior products.
That enabled Su Chang Ji
to grow into this scale today!
I, Meng Hanru,
thank everyone.
Winter is here.
Grandmother passed away.
The academy is also shutting down.
It seems like
everything's changed overnight.
Sometimes, I keep thinking to myself
why I went through
such tribulations this year?
The worst of it
is that I met you.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
how are you doing?
Where are you?
When we first met,
it was Insects Awaken.
We used to think
winter is still far away.
There's a long way ahead
and there are many things to be done.
But somehow,
there's no more time left.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
where are you?
Did you see the snow?
Zhao Mao,
when I meet Fuweng,
what do you think he'll say?
If I do my best,
will Xiaoman stay?
I gave you so much food.
You even had peach blossom shortbread.
You're useless.
Eat away.
Ladies,
we'll get going.
Take care.
What's wrong?
Don't cry.
To Congwen
Congwen.
Xiaoman?
Xie Ruying gave me this.
She asked me to pass it to you.
To Congwen
Congwen,
are you also leaving?
My father was demoted
and the academy also closed down.
Staying here won't help with anything.
Demoted?
Something happened to your family?
But I've never
been a young master from
an official's family.
However, going to
the capital this time,
I was given cold shoulders.
Before I got to do anything,
I had become the son of
an accused official.
Come on.
Let's have a chat
and watch the scenery
of Fengxue Pavilion.
What do you think?
I remember, back in Yuyangli Village,
we even roasted sweet potatoes together.
Just like today,
we like to warm our hands
near the stove.
So it's me who was ignorant for
asking you to join me
in getting our hands dirty.
But I liked it a lot.
Congwen, you said something happened
to your family in the capital.
What happened?
My father and I
used to have conflicts.
I thought many things that he did
were wrong.
I thought that there's no transparency
when it comes to politics.
But when I went back this time,
I saw with my own eyes that
he built a tall tower
and entertained the guests
before the tower collapsed,
only then I realized
many things
don't matter that much
between father and son.
He's my father,
not my enemy.
But it's all for good.
In the future, without the burden
of my family background,
I can be a commoner,
and continue to travel
to walk my path
and write my books.
Do you agree with me?
I don't know.
But what matters is that you feel happy.
Did Princess Consort Pu make
things difficult for you?
The reason Princess Consort Pu
came this time
was actually to make me
leave Zhao Xiaoqian.
In the beginning, I wasn't willing.
But later,
grandmother passed away,
and Su Chang Ji was also gone.
Even my brother was almost put to jail.
So, I agreed to it.
However,
after leaving him, I realized
my true feelings.
Am I really silly?
In the past,
I just thought that
he's a rich man's son.
That I had poor fate for
being forced to marry him
as a concubine.
I kept thinking about leaving.
However, as time goes by,
I began to develop feelings for him.
After our farewell,
I then realized
I had thoroughly
acknowledged him as my husband.
I fell in love with him.
However, Congwen,
why didn't anyone
tell me
liking someone
can be so painful.
Why do I think of him
every single moment?
When the weather gets cold,
I'll worry if he'd catch a cold,
whether he has eaten enough,
or has a good night's sleep.
I know we won't end up together,
but I couldn't forget him
no matter what.
But it's already ended, right?
Since it's come to an end,
if you couldn't forget about him,
then you should move on,
okay?
Don't worry.
With me around,
I won't let you feel wronged.
My feelings
are written in the book.
Lonely Boat At Night, volume four
I'll wait for you...
This is bad! Something happened!
Those people are here again!
What are you doing?
Why are you here again?
Who gives you the right
to close our academy?
That's right! What are you doing?
Yes! Who gives you
the right to close our academy?
Bailu Academy
Yes!
Didn't we agree to wait for
the document?
We still have an examination
coming up in a few days.
Let me tell you.
As long as the document is not here,
don't even think of closing our academy!
That's right!
You can't close the academy! No way!
Mr. Yan,
it's bad enough that
other students aren't reasonable.
Why are you taking the lead
in stirring up trouble?
I'm stirring up trouble?
- I...
- Boyang.
Calm down.
Let's talk nicely.
Congwen.
We just want to buy
a few more days
to sit for the last examination,
right?
That's right!
We want to take the examination!
You want to take the examination?
Yes!
Then take the civil examination
at the imperial college.
What's so great about
a mere academy's examination?
What's there to take?
Ridiculous!
You're saying we're incapable?
Fine.
I'll show you
that we're capable!
Boyang!
- Boyang!
Arrest him!
Boyang!
Let him go!
Bring him away!
Don't you dare touch him!
You can't arrest him!
Boyang!
How could you arrest him?
Let go of me!
Boyang!
- Boyang!
Yan Boyang!
Why are they arresting him?
Let's go to the magistrate court!
Let's talk to Yan Nengfu!
Come on! Let's go!
Let's go to the magistrate court!
Magistrate of Wujiang
We want to talk to Lord Yan!
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
You can't enter!
We want to take the exam, Lord Yan!
We want to talk to Lord Yan!
Back off!
Ridiculous.
All we want is to take the exam.
Why can't we?
What's the reason?
I've never seen you being so concerned.
When it's almost over,
you're causing this ruckus.
What's in it for you?
This is ridiculous.
We don't want the academy to close down.
What does it have to do with
what's good for us?
Besides,
the teachers from Bailu Academy
taught us much more
than you did.
Why should our academy shut
down just because you said so?
You...
You unfilial son.
I'm carrying out my official duty here.
It's not up to you.
Moreover,
if you're really so capable
and have high ambitions,
you should stop
doing this kind of silly stuff here.
Become one of the top scorers
in the imperial examination
before you negotiate terms with me.
I'm silly
and I'm negotiating terms with you.
So what?
You...
Fine.
Today, I'll teach you
how to be humble!
Guards!
Yes!
Beat him!
If I'm able to take it today,
you'll promise me this once.
Beat him!
We want to take the exam!
We want to talk to Lord Yan!
What are you all doing?
Boyang!
Go away!
Boyang, are you listening?
We want to talk to Lord Yan!
We didn't break any law!
We want to take the exam!
Don't push us!
We want to talk to Lord Yan!
Students!
Go away!
Lord Yan!
Students!
Ladies and gentlemen,
on behalf of all teachers,
we thank you all
for what you've done for Bailu academy.
I'm deeply moved
by what everyone did for the academy.
However, I'm also thinking
while Bailu Academy is
teaching all of you
knowledge and classics,
we've forgotten to teach you
the ways of the world.
As the saying goes,
"think twice before acting."
However,
Lord Yan won't give us
an extension.
Bureaucrat Yan has his own standing.
Even if you have something to say,
you mustn't be rash,
and should choose the right way.
Regardless of what will
become of Bailu Academy,
since you're our students,
please remember the academy's teaching.
All right.
Don't talk loudly or shout here.
I'm the principal.
I should be the person who
negotiate with them anyway.
Principal.
- Principal!
Let's see if you'll still be stubborn.
You...
Hancai.
Stop! Stop!
Principal,
you're also here.
Look.
He was making a scene.
I...
I'm just carrying out my duty.
I know. I know.
As the Bureaucrat,
official matters are more important.
You have your own challenges and stand.
However, the youngsters
are really reluctant to let go.
Since they're about to graduate soon,
I hope you'll grant this wish.
Principal,
please don't make things
difficult for me.
You were a student of Bailu Academy.
Standing up for broad vision,
righteousness and good faith.
Why?
Now, you only see the law
and become unsympathetic?
Although you're the Bureaucrat,
you're also a father.
Even the youngsters are
doing this for their ambitions.
If you say Zhanzhi's being ridiculous,
to me, this is
Zhanzhi's proudest moment as a youth.
I'm glad.
I'm making this appeal
on my students' behalf.
Lord Yan, please grant us an extension.
Principal!
Don't do this.
All right.
Forget it.
I'll agree to it.
Thank you.
I'll forgive you
for the sake of the principal.
Focus on the examination properly.
Let's see how you will score for the exam.
All right.
See you.
Boyang.
Principal, thank you.
We should thank you instead.
Go home and recuperate,
and prepare for the examination.
Sure.
Principal's here.
- He's here.
Principal.
- Principal.
How did it go?
Everyone,
Lord Yan has agreed.
Go home to prepare for
the examination.
Great!
- Great!
Now we can sit for the examination!
Great!
- Great!
Now we can sit for the examination!
Yes!
Great!
Now we can sit for the examination!
We're taking the exam!
Yan Boyang!
Yan Boyang, are you in there?
Minggu?
Don't come up here.
I just got spanked.
It's too embarrassing.
Does it hurt?
No.
Boyang, you're so silly.
Why did you take the beating?
I know I'm silly.
I also know there's nothing
I could do well,
and I always make you angry.
And your family's case, too.
I...
I've thought about it these few days.
I can't blame you for that.
It's my fault.
I was too wilful in the past.
Most of the time,
my mother and grandmother
bore it for me
and take care everything for me.
Now, it's different.
Grandmother has passed away
and Su Chang Ji was also gone.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to the capital.
My mother and I
will reopen Su Chang Ji in the capital.
You're leaving?
You...
Are you sure you're all right?
Please don't leave.
I'm the successor of Su Chang Ji.
I have to be responsible for this.
I thought that
we'll be together forever.
Forever?
Yan Boyang, you're so silly.
In this world,
nothing will last forever.
In that case,
bring more clothes with you.
The northern region is
really cold in winter.
Take care.
Yan Boyang,
we're adults now.
At home,
don't upset your parents
or be idle every day.
Girls don't like it
if you do that.
I know.
Don't worry.
Today, you're like
a great hero to me.
I seem to have fallen for you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Military Office of Tengzhou
Your Highness.
Rise quickly.
What happened to your arm?
Was it Her Highness's doing?
Your Highness.
You've suffered
over the years.
What exactly happened back then?
How did you break your arm?
Also, how did
my brother die?
Your Highness,
I remember it was autumn.
Your Highness was flying the kite
in the imperial palace,
hoping Prince and Princess Consort Pu
would see it.
However, it was suddenly very windy
and the kite's string snapped.
Your Highness didn't know that
the kite
landed on Kunning Palace
and right in front of Her Highness.
Her Highness was frightened
and her baby was affected.
She gave birth on that night.
I know.
The baby was dead.
The imperial physician said
the baby was already dead for days,
but Her Highness
couldn't accept it.
She thought...
She thought
it's all Your Highness' doing.
Having lost her son,
Her Highness lost her composure.
That's why...
That's why Duke of Yongguo
pleaded guilty for your sake.
Her Highness was the one who
sentenced him to death?
That's why she
used Prince Pu's Mansion
as an excuse for years
to monitor me.
To get me to return to the capital,
she sent Lingniang
and my mother
so that I...
So that I can't seek revenge.
So I'll
forever be within her control.
Am I right?
Your Highness,
Duke of Yongguo and I
hoped that you'll carry on
with your life.
Your Highness,
don't ask anymore.
What good will it do
even if Your Highness know all these?
Your Highness.
General.
Come on. Cheers.
Sure.
Brothers,
let's take over Baichuankou.
Master, did you know
when my brother passed away,
I was asked to leave the capital
and stay away from the disputes?
I used to think Her Highness
was worried the throne would
fall into others' hands,
so she kept going against me.
I thought my brother
was worried that I would get into
the fight for the Crown Prince's title,
so he asked me to leave.
After so many years,
this is the first time I've found out
it was all because of a kite.
For so many years,
this is the first time I've found out
the price for me to leave the capital
was my brother's life.
Life is uncertain and unexpected.
Certain things
aren't your fault.
Not my fault?
I used to think
I could protect everyone around me.
And now?
Fuweng's arm is broken
and brother is dead.
I couldn't protect any of them.
Master,
I just found out today that
I'm just a joke.
That's how the rule of the world is.
Only the strong survive
while the weak perish.
It's the same for the imperial court.
When the corrupted officials
are in power,
only the strong can contend with them.
Hanchen.
I don't believe
staying in Wujiang Prefecture
over the years
has worn out your indignation.
I also don't believe you came
to Tengzhou today
just to meet Fuweng.
I wanted to protect
the people around me,
but I just realized today,
if someone wants to harm her,
I could
do nothing.
Tens of thousands of Xiongjie Camp's
soldiers are rushing to Baichuankou.
May I know
if there's a place for me?
You've really considered it through?
Yes.
I want to protect the people around me.
I'm going to Baichuankou
to establish military merits
and fight for military power.
I can return to the capital,
but I'll do so
victoriously.
Do you mean it?
Hanchen,
please fight along with me!
Master, thank you.
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share the plate for breast!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make your lances shine!
Your foe is mine!
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share the coat and vest!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make our halberds shine!
Your duty is mine!
Are you not battle-dressed?
Let's share kilt and the rest!
We shall go to the front line!
Let's make our Armour shine!
March with your hand in mine!
Today,
you're having your last examination.
Each one of you will
write an article with the title
"To Each His Own Ambitions".
I hope all of you will take it seriously
to write your own ambitions and wishes.
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures♪
♪Find right companions♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures♪
♪Find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
Bailu Academy
Time's up.
Everyone,
stop writing.
Bailu Academy has been established
in Wujiang Prefecture
for 30 years
to this day.
The passage of time is just
like the flow of water,
regardless of day and night.
In this world,
it's as if a white steed
flits past a crack,
it's a brief moment.
This will be my last lesson
with all of you.
Gentleman respects fate.
Think twice before acting.
Since the establishment
of Bailu Academy,
my biggest hope
is for each and every
student of this academy
to be a gentleman who
is upright and just.
Gentleman respects fate.
Be it the world, personally,
or the academy itself.
I've always told you,
as a student,
you must keep in mind that,
we study for heaven and earth,
for the people,
and for the saints of the past,
and safeguard world peace
for all ages.
However, in this peace,
more than anything,
what you should explore
is yourselves.
Principal!
Principal, this is bad!
Principal! Principal!
Magistrate Xie is here
with the officers.
They're at the entrance,
claiming they're here
to close the academy.
What's going on?
I thought it's not time yet?
That's right.
They're bullying us.
Yes.
This won't do.
They can't shut down the academy.
Silence. Silence.
Grass or gravel,
they're just external objects.
We have things which
they can't take away from us.
A gentleman establishes his
heart for heaven and earth.
Although it can contend
with the external realm,
if the aim
is to change the world,
that's a fool's way.
Change what you can change
and establish a person's
heart for heaven and earth.
Accepting what you can't change
is how a gentleman respects his fate.
All protesters
must think twice.
That's a gentleman's way.
Be it boys or ladies,
I hope you'll be broad-minded
and not a partisan,
coexisting harmoniously and
maintaining difference.
Only if our generation
strictly abides by it,
the good fortune of our home country
will last for a long time.
The riverbank of five lakes!
An institution of higher education!
Confucius is standing
without peer among the early masters!
Continue this tradition
of the sages of the past!
The six Classics, since he
has cast and molded them,
ring out the resonant
music of bronze and jade!
A gentleman with virtue
with extensive knowledge!
Everyone,
you've graduated from studies.
Jingnv Pavilion
Xiaoman,
what do you plan to do next?
My family has decided
to go to the capital.
I'm also going with them.
Once we're there,
I might help out at my aunt's shop.
As for the rest,
I haven't thought about it yet.
What about you, Teacher Liu?
I plan to go to the capital
to set up an academy for ladies.
Having stayed for so many years
in Bailu Academy
I've come across many
intelligent young ladies.
I realized
there should be a place
for ladies to focus on
studying to change their destiny.
I happen to need an assistant.
If you're also going to the capital,
you can join me
in teaching at the academy.
We can also finish compiling
the historical books of women
we've yet to complete.
What do you think?
I've always wanted to be a teacher,
but I'm not knowledgeable
and lack experience.
By then, I hope you
will give me a chance
to stay by your side
to handle miscellaneous tasks.
This is my address in the capital.
You can contact me when you're there.
Teacher, please wait for me.
Xiaoman,
I hope this letter finds you well.
I'm writing you this letter
to express my gratitude.
I'm sure you're curious,
but similarly, you wouldn't know
Congwen, who to you,
is capable of doing anything
was once lost.
It's funny.
When Yanniang left,
I didn't know what to do in future.
I believed that no one
would appreciate
my writing.
While struggling,
I lost my original intention.
Sometimes, throughout our lives,
we're always struggling between
others' recognition and our own choices.
If our own wish is fulfilled,
others might be disappointed.
If we're to follow others' advice,
we might lose ourselves
in the process.
If it wasn't because of you,
how will I find out
even if I'm just
a lonesome soul in this world,
there's someone who understands me
and appreciates my talent.
This kind of understanding
is a dream coming true to me.
I've decided to pen it down
and write you this letter
because I want you to know
you are
a good lady who is hard
to find in the world.
I like you
and I wish you'd feel the same for me.
I'm not afraid
of the tribulations today.
I hope to share
sorrow and joy with you.
On Chinese New Year at 5 a.m.
I hope to see you at the market
on Yue Bridge.
Yours truly, Su
Lonely Boat At Night, volume four
Bailu Academy
Sealed
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪