♪Confessing to the moon
in the rustling wind back then♪
♪Like a boat being swallowed up
among the cities♪
♪Watching the flowers fall in unease,
worries and troubles fill my mind♪
♪Am I going to where I want♪
♪To stay or to leave, you decide♪
♪Nations are different♪
♪One without desire
is one that is not alive♪
♪Looking at the sky side by side♪
♪We've gotten closer with time♪
♪One glance,
the city of Chang'an is bare♪
♪Among the ridiculous people
and things is me♪
=Dream of Chang'An=
=Episode 26=
Ziyuan.
Sir.
We noticed a suspicious person
by the side yard.
- Chase after him.
- Yes.
This is bad.
It's too late.
I'll delay them.
Take care of Princess.
Hurry.
No.
You two go.
I'll delay them.
I'll also take revenge.
Do that another day.
I can't lose this opportunity.
With the Princess gone,
Qiu Ziliang surely won't let this go.
If he investigates,
the citizens will suffer again.
I should just
end this right here.
But...
I'm not doing this to help you.
It's just that Wang Lin must die.
Ziyuan.
Cheng Ruoyu.
Someday...
If that day really comes,
you must clear the names
of the thousands of heroes
in the Morning Dew Rebellion.
Your Majesty.
Yu'er is gone.
I've asked the guard already.
She left the palace in the afternoon
and hasn't returned yet.
Send people to find her.
Yes.
What do you want?
I'm here to bring you out.
Bring us out?
You want to help me?
Why?
You'll see when you go out.
Come with me.
Sir!
Sir.
The west yard is on fire too.
Put it out.
This must be a diversion.
Sir!
Sir.
The fire is out.
But we didn't catch the assassin yet.
Continue going after him!
Yes.
Don't go inside.
But I hear something.
When Eunuch is inside,
no one is allowed to enter.
But Princess is inside,
Eunuch is so bold.
Follow this path,
and you can get out.
You haven't told me
why you're helping me yet.
You'll find out in the future.
Where are you going?
It's so late,
and you're not home yet.
Why are you here?
I came to thank you.
There's nothing to thank me for.
In order to make Qiu Ziliang trust me,
I can only give him Liu Misha.
But if I give her to Chess
of Generals Camp,
with Qiu Yanzhi there,
you won't be able to get her out.
But it's different if I give her
to Wang Lin.
Qiu Yanzhi, who has
unfathomable motives,
might be able to help you.
Now,
return Liu Misha to me.
I definitely won't give Princess Misha
to you.
No.
You will,
or His Majesty
will die.
Chess Overseer.
Cheng Xi suddenly appeared
at the back of Wang Lin's Residence.
We don't dare to make a move
on our own.
Please provide instructions.
Cheng Xi is at the back door?
Yes.
She's blocking Cheng Ruoyu.
We fell for the trick.
She intentionally kept Liu Misha
here with Wang Lin
in order to catch us
when someone comes to save her.
What should we do then?
Is the person we sent reliable?
Yes.
Good.
Command everyone to leave.
We didn't come here tonight,
and we didn't do anything.
- All right.
- Yes.
If Qiu Ziliang finds out
that Qi Yan
sent you to save Liu Misha,
based on his personality,
he won't hold it in
until the appointment ceremony.
And at this time,
His Majesty
got seriously injured because of you.
Any soldier
can kill him.
His Majesty doesn't know
that I came to save Liu Misha at all.
I believe that,
but will Qiu Ziliang believe it?
So give me Princess,
and this matter will be over.
I'll handle things on Wang Lin's side.
I'll also
treat Princess well.
And you can stay
at His Majesty's side,
let him recover quickly,
and continue fighting
against Qiu Ziliang.
That's three birds with one stone.
Wang Lin is dead?
Yes,
together with Princess Misha.
What exactly happened?
Official Wang drank too much last night.
Fire broke out in the residence.
He was worried that something
will happen to Princess,
so he went to check.
Then
he played around with Princess,
but things got out of hand,
and fire broke out again.
Then they both died in the fire.
I especially instructed him
to watch Liu Misha well.
But he...
How can two fires break out
for no reason?
The first time was because
the chef in the residence
wasn't careful.
The fire was quickly extinguished.
The... The second time...
The second time... Well...
Official Wang likes to play...
play with candle wax.
And...
Are you sure
that Wang Lin and Liu Misha
are the ones who died?
The guard saw Official Wang go inside.
Back then, Princess was fine.
I actually came today
to ask
who will replace Official Wang
now that he's dead.
Sir.
What do you think of Shi Yuan?
He's been working for you
for many years.
He may not be as capable
as Official Wang,
but...
But he's loyal.
Let's use Shi Yuan then.
Yes.
Jiang Ding really
told Qiu Ziliang that?
Yes.
Official Qiu already agreed
to let Shi Yuan take over
Wang Lin's job.
So
Cheng Xi bought Jiang Ding off?
Cheng Xi's plan
hits three birds with one stone.
With Wang Lin dead,
I'm afraid that his replacement,
Shi Yuan,
also works for Cheng Xi.
She hit three birds with one stone.
She used us
and Cheng Ruoyu.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Yu'er...
Yu'er is back.
What's the matter?
Madam.
Zhenwu's reply arrived.
This is great.
They agreed to our condition.
Next,
we just have to wait
for the appointment ceremony
on the 16th next month.
But Master Thirteen
hasn't agreed yet.
Thirteen had been in seclusion
for too long.
He has become silly already.
He can't call the shots in this matter.
In the end,
if he really disagrees, forget it.
I'll do it myself.
Madam, you...
What's the matter?
Can't I become
the second female emperor?
You're adept in both the pen
and the sword.
You're far better than
the female emperor back then.
If that happens, it's fate.
Rise.
I can't accept it.
I really can't accept it.
I was so close.
I could have
saved Princess Misha.
But Aunt...
It was Aunt.
Since she wants
this position so much,
she can take it.
Your Majesty.
But how long can she occupy
this position?
Who's there?
It's me.
Why are you here?
There's no time.
I'll make the long story short.
Are you willing
to fight Cheng Xi with me?
What I meant is
to totally ruin her reputation
and crush her,
so that she can no longer make
a comeback.
Can you
do that?
What happened?
Did she agree?
She's still hesitating.
I knew that Little Fish
couldn't do it.
After all,
Cheng Xi raised her.
Then we must find another way.
I must win against Cheng Xi.
I can't let her ruin
my plan for revenge.
(I want you to do two things.)
First.
Find out Cheng Xi's identity
from Li Rong.
Now, we already know
that she's a descendant
of the Qi clan.
But who were her parents?
What was her name?
And how did she hide her identity
and entered the palace?
As her confidant,
Li Rong must know something.
Second.
After finding out,
expose Cheng Xi
in front of Qiu Ziliang.
Between Qi Yan and Cheng Xi,
you can only choose one person.
You can only choose one person.
Cheng Xi wants Qi Yan dead.
And if you
expose Cheng Xi
in front of Qiu Ziliang,
based on Qiu Ziliang's style,
Cheng Xi will surely die.
(Why)
(must that person be me?)
Only you
can make it believable.
(Yu'er.)
(There are some things)
(that I can't find out,)
(but you can.)
Do you still remember
how you left
Wang Lin's Residence?
That woman beside Wang Lin
works for you?
Yu'er.
Now, only you
can save Qi Yan,
me,
and all of us.
(Save Qi Yan,)
(save me.)
(Save Qi Yan, save me.)
(Save me.)
(Save all of us.)
Who are you?
Don't come any closer.
Who's there?
Don't come near me.
It's so noisy.
It's the middle of the night. Who...
Yu'er.
Your Majesty.
Don't come any closer.
What are you doing?
Yu'er.
Your Majesty.
My heart is like a sword.
suppressing the wicked
and eliminating evil.
My sword is like my heart,
protecting the nation
and being loyal to the emperor.
Yu'er.
Your Majesty.
I'll surely save you.
I want to save you.
Yu'er.
I'll save you.
All right.
I'll wait for you to save me.
Do you know
about her headaches?
Your Majesty.
I knew
about this matter before.
But this is the first time that I saw
how serious it is.
How was she injured?
Huaizhi.
I found my niece.
This is my niece,
Yu'er.
Where did you find her?
There was famine back home.
My elder brother and his wife
left home with her,
but human traffickers
took her along the way.
She was seriously sick.
The human traffickers thought
that she wouldn't recover anymore,
so they threw her away.
Good thing Yu'er was lucky.
His Highness Prince Guang saved her.
A while ago,
didn't I ask for medicine
from His Highness?
I recognized her immediately.
By the way, Huaizhi,
can we change her surname
to Cheng as well?
As you know,
I have an enemy before,
and I was forced to be on the run.
I can't return home either.
All right.
It's good for her to have
the surname of Cheng.
This child
is very lucky
to have met you.
Yu'er.
Child.
Her head is injured.
She also doesn't remember
anything in the past.
And she often has nightmares.
His Highness Prince Guang said
that she must continue
receiving treatment for some time.
Yu'er.
Don't worry.
From now on,
not only will your aunt
take care of you,
I will take good care of you too.
That was what Cheng Xi...
Now, I should call her Qi Xi now.
I had no doubts about that story.
All these years,
I didn't really talk about the past.
I was afraid that she'd be sad.
On hindsight,
a lot of aspects
don't fit.
It means
that from the very start,
it was only Cheng Xi
who claimed that Yu'er is her niece.
Am I right?
Yes.
Summon Uncle.
Uncle, what do you think?
When Cheng Xi went to me that day,
she saw Yu'er
and said that she's her niece.
I asked how she was sure about it.
She said that aside from her looks,
she recognized
a birth mark on her.
How did she know about that?
Come to think of it,
she probably saw it beforehand.
That was why she said that.
I didn't doubt her,
and I hastily
gave Yu'er to her.
Your Majesty, forgive me.
Why are you saying that?
Cheng Xi has been hiding her identity
for so many years.
She even fooled me and Huaizhi,
let alone you.
No medicine can cure
Yu'er's illness.
And I don't know when she'll have
another attack.
As of now,
we can only let her calm down
and not receive
any external stimulation.
Otherwise...
(I was wrong back then.)
Your Majesty.
What's the situation
in Zhenwu and Lucong?
In Zhenwu,
since Princess Misha hasn't been back
for so long,
they're starting to be impatient.
In Lucong,
like Chen Yintai,
Zhang Jiang is requesting
a tally and ceremonial axe
but because of the lesson learned
from the previous example,
he doesn't dare to do anything.
All right.
I need you to do
another thing.
Your Majesty, please tell me.
Investigate
Yu'er's real identity
as well
as the interactions
between Uncle and Cheng Xi
all these years.
Your Majesty.
Do you really think
that she...
It's not that I don't trust her.
If Yu'er isn't Cheng Ruoyu,
but someone Cheng Xi
intentionally placed on my side,
then there must be a special reason.
I
asked Uncle to take her away before.
Yet he encountered
obstacles repeatedly.
I never believe
in coincidences.
There must be a reason.
Yes.
Go.
Who are you?
Official Jiang.
Do you like this gift?
My... My son.
Jiang Ding's wife is very fierce.
She never had a child
after many years.
He has an illegitimate son
that he's been hiding from his family.
I captured his son,
and he confessed indeed.
What did Cheng Xi promise him?
The position
of Shencai Army General-in-Chief.
Between power and family,
family is more important indeed.
And I promised him
that after we succeed,
the General-in-Chief position
will still be his.
Watch him well
to avoid him from going back
on his decision.
Don't worry.
Is it
Shi Yuan's turn next?
Have you checked his background?
He only has one weakness.
He loves drinking.
That is a very good weakness.
Why am I here?
Where is His Majesty?
Why are you still here?
I heard already.
You're not the real niece
of Cheng Xi.
Now that Cheng Xi's conspiracy
has been exposed,
out of kindness,
His Majesty couldn't bear to kill you.
But how can you
stay here so shamelessly?
I'm only staying here
to protect His Majesty.
Who is protecting whom?
Forget about
all the troubles that you caused
His Majesty before.
Just this time,
you suddenly went crazy
and almost killed him.
If you really want to help His Majesty,
you should go to Cheng Xi
and kill her,
then kill Qiu Ziliang,
and completely eliminate
His Majesty's troubles.
You shouldn't stay here
and drag him down
in the name of protecting him.
Do you want to tell me
that you can't kill Qiu Ziliang
and you can't bear to kill Cheng Xi?
You're useless.
That's enough.
Your Majesty.
From now on, without my permission,
don't enter my bed chambers.
But she can lie down
on your bed?
She's my Sword Bearer,
and she's seriously ill.
Sword Bearer?
Your Majesty, why are you fooling
yourself and others?
Don't mind her.
Did I really
almost kill you?
No.
You
saw me
and immediately stopped.
So
how can you harm me?
What's the matter? Do you feel guilty?
I'm really fine.
Am I not well?
His Highness Prince Guang
visited you yesterday.
He said that you can only rest
to recover.
I know.
You're sad about your aunt.
I'm the same.
No matter how hard life is,
it must go on, right?
Uncle.
I've had headaches before,
but I've never had hallucinations.
But this time,
I saw many people wanting to kill me.
All of them
were wearing Shencai Army attire
and looked very fierce.
I wanted to retaliate, so I...
Yu'er.
His Highness Prince Guang
also mentioned yesterday
that from now on,
as long as you don't receive
any external stimulation,
this
won't happen again.
Uncle.
Perhaps
I really should leave this place.
To His Majesty,
I am
a latent danger
and also a burden.
Silly girl.
You keep saying silly things.
Where can you go if you leave?
I sent someone to watch Cheng Xi
and Li Rong.
They've only been staying
in Official Qiu's residence.
They didn't go out.
In that case,
there's only one possibility.
Liu Misha is in Qiu Ziliang's residence.
Then I'll go and check again.
There's no need.
She wasn't there last time.
That was why Cheng Xi
allowed you to check.
Now,
if she's really
in Qiu Ziliang's residence,
they must have prepared a trap
for you.
What should we do then?
At this point,
Little Fish
is still hesitating.
She's so indecisive.
She's very sentimental and loyal.
It's a pro and also a con.
Let's set aside Liu Misha first.
How are things on Yuan Xing's side?
I bought off
some of his concubines and staff
to tell him things
and stimulate his dissatisfaction
towards Shi Yuan.
It's taking effect now.
They just haven't told him
enough things yet.
We must make him
want to kill him.
You're here.
I want the map
of Qiu Ziliang's residence,
Aunt's location,
and also
your help.
Qiu Ziliang thinks
that he's the best in martial arts.
That's why security isn't tight
in his residence.
Based on your martial arts skill,
you should be able to sneak in.
But Cheng Xi
would arrange warriors of sacrifice
to make patrols.
You have to see
how you can avoid them.
Madam Li.
Yu'er?
Why are you here?
Go.
I want to ask you something.
I won't tell you anything.
Listen.
While no one knows that you're here yet,
leave.
If Madam finds out,
it will be bad.
Go.
Tell me
where Misha is.
I can't.
Tell me.
Yu'er.
I've been with Madam for ten years.
Aside from respecting her,
we're friends.
I won't betray her.
Where are you going?
Aunt and I
must have closure.
Now isn't the time.
Yu'er.
Listen to me.
Your aunt has her reasons.
Forget it if you won't help her.
But you must definitely
not fight with her.
Understand?
Then tell me
what her reason is.
You really want to know?
Why don't you ask me directly?
Because I know
that you won't tell me.
That's right.
Before we succeed,
I won't tell you anything,
so that you won't ruin my plans.
Even if you don't tell me,
I'll continue bothering you,
and I'll still ruin your plans.
I warned you before.
If you want Qi Yan to live,
don't do anything stupid.
Even if I do that,
His Majesty will still die.
Not necessarily.
Perhaps, for the sake
of being part of the same clan,
I won't totally finish him off.
How is that different
from killing him?
That's Qi Yan's destiny.
Yu'er.
You still want to fight?
Aunt.
You and I must have closure
sooner and later.
Today,
I came to end this matter.
His Majesty won't be able
to block the sword for you.
It's not your fault.
If you were just a maid servant,
you wouldn't experience these things.
It's because
you're my weakness.
Do you think
that your martial arts skill
improved a lot?
Compared to me,
you're so far off.
Stop fighting!
Stop fighting, Madam.
Yu'er is immature.
Let's just talk to her.
Scram!
Yu'er.
You can't treat your aunt this way.
Put down the sword!
Madam Li, stay out of this.
Move!
You...
Madam!
(You keep saying that you want
to protect me,)
(yet you don't know)
(that you're the one)
(I want to protect the most.)
(I don't care who you are)
(and what kind of motive)
(Cheng Xi has for you,)
(as long as you're away from me,)
(you'll be safe.)
Cheng Ruoyu.
Wake up.
I have something
that I must tell you right away.
Thirteen is right.
Your martial arts talent
is above mine indeed.
I originally thought
that when you grew up,
you'd be able to help me
after being great in martial arts.
In the end...
Madam.
Madam, bad news!
Your Pill Making Room is on fire!
You're just a diversion.
You brought accomplices?
Princess Misha
is hiding in your Pill Making Room,
isn't she?
Watch her well!
It's just as you expected.
We did it.
We'll only be successful
after taking her to Qi Yan.
Let's go.
Yes.
Nice, Cheng Ruoyu.
I taught you martial arts,
and you're going against me.
If I had known,
I should have let you die
from that arrow to your heart back then.
Madam, don't be angry.
Yu'er...
Yu'er is just...
Let go!
It's so lively here.
She's inside?
Yes.
Don't worry.
Official Qiu had heard
the fight
on Cheng Xi's side now
and went to check.
Qiu Ziliang wants to know
what's going on,
and Cheng Xi can't speak the truth,
so she can only swallow her grievance.
But I'm afraid that Little Fish
won't be so lucky
in Official Qiu's hands.
That's why we must hurry.
It's up to Qi Yan next.
Tell me.
Why are you and your niece
fighting in the middle of the night?
Tell me,
so that I can do you justice.
Cheng Xi.
You go first.
I stabbed His Majesty.
That was why Yu'er was fighting with me.
I'm sorry to bother you with this.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's not a big deal.
But I heard
that you want to kill her.
I was just angry.
I didn't teach my niece well.
I regret it so much.
I'll teach her a lesson
on your behalf then.
I guarantee that she'll become
an obedient,
nice,
and sensible niece.
♪Life is a dream,
how long do happy times last♪
♪In the windy rain,
where will my heart settle?♪
♪The sword can't break this karma♪
♪Look how blurry
and lonely the world is♪
♪Fate can't do anything
about the bleak bonds of this world♪
♪Still can't let go of this life
as time goes by♪
♪Even the iron and golden dagger-axe
cannot extinguish the fire in my heart♪
♪Remembering the past
and letting time while away♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪