Our Secret
EP15
Senior
I'm so exhausted.
Really, I'm so exhausted.
It is myself who choose to be a re-attendee of College Entrance Examination.
I have no right to complain about this.
So no matter how hard it is or how exhausting it will be,
I cannot stop fighting.
But I'm also very scared.
I don't know whether I've made the right decision
to start all over again.
Xianxian
Compared with your peers,
you are good enough.
This is not enough.
It is not even close to the life I want,
and the person
I wish to follow.
The person.
You mean Zhou Siyue, right?
Zhou Siyue is so brilliant.
I used to think that we were at the same level,
and as long as I can work very hard,
I can go to the same university with him.
But he is too brilliant.
I just found out that
there's a large gap between us.
No matter how much I like him,
I cannot stand that I'm not good enough for him.
I'm afraid, one day,
someone may ask
why Zhou Siyue is
with me.
I don't think so.
At least,
I won't ask a question like this.
If I were you,
I won't be affected by others' voice
as long as I have made my determination.
Don't ask for too much.
That's the best answer.
Drink the milk and go to bed early.
Thanks, mom.
It's nearly midnight. Don't stay up too late.
Mom
Don't worry.
I'll go to bed early today.
Zhou Siyue
I miss you so much.
I'm so exhausted.
Really, I'm so exhausted.
School starts today, right?
Congratulations on becoming a student of Huaqing University.
I'm sorry.
For such a long time,
you have been so tired.
Thank you.
Hi.
Do you know how to get the Automation Department?
No, I don't.
What's your major then?
-I also major in automation.  -You major in automation, too?
Nice to meet you. I'm Yuan Fang.
I'm Zhou Siyue.
Boys and girls.
This is the first lesson for your new school life here.
I hope you can remember the eight characters
deep in mind.
Never forget our responsibility and mission.
You made a mistake on such an easy question?
Just this one.
You're asking too much of me.
You have so many excuses.
Silly girl.
What were you thinking?
If I did all these correct,
I would be the one who got 90 points.
So many excuses.
Professor Ye
-Good morning.  -Good morning.
My name's Dong Zhengfei.
For the member selection of the research group,
I've got an idea.
I'm thinking about designing a relevant network like this.
Please have a look when you're free.
Boy, it's good to have your own idea.
You can show this while attending the election later.
You may go back now.
Okay, Professor Ye.
Siyue
I'm just going to see you.
Professor Ye
This semester, you don't need to attend
the course of Introduction to Artificial Intelligence.
I've seen your homework.
It's beyond my expectation.
So I want you to
concentrate on the preparation for
the assessment of my lab.
Okay. I got it.
How's your father?
He's busy with the investigation.
But I believe the time will soon come to reveal the whole truth.
Okay. Don't worry.
Just focus on your study.
You are a promising student.
Thank you, Professor Ye.
Zhou Siyue, are you busy recently?
In medical field,
humanoid robots can be used in prosthetic
and organ transplantation.
Making use of the technology of humanoid robot,
powered prosthesis can be created
to help realizing paralytic patients'
dream of walking again.
We have such a handsome classmate.
He's in Class One.
It's said that he was recommended for admission from Shen Hai High School.
He's a brilliant student.
So in this respect,
a deeper research and investigation is still needed.
Wait and see.
He's mine.
Thank you.
There you go again.
Bravo! Bravo!
Thank you.
Good for you.
The applause thundered forth.
If you want to see him, just go.
He doesn't reply to my messages now.
He may be quite busy.
How busy can he be?
I'm a university student, too.
Just forget it.
I don't have time to see him.
Aren't you free during the National Day holiday?
Well, I'm free that time. But...
Then why are you hesitating?
You always want to
visit Huaqing University, don't you?
Just take this as a surprise for Zhou Siyue.
A surprise?
Where's the Automation Department?
Hello.
Hi.
My name's Xing Lufei.
I'm in Class Five of the Computer Department.
Can I make friends with you?
Well,
I listened to your report that day when attending the election.
And I think you are awesome.
So I want to discuss with you
some questions about study.
I'm sorry.
I'm quite busy today.
This is our lab.
At present, in China,
whether in terms of the equipment or technology,
it is in the leading position.
There are few such advanced laboratories
in the whole country.
Siyue, come and have a look at the equipment.
Sorry, I'm late. Professor Ye.
I went to a wrong lab just now.
New members are all here, now.
Siyue
As the group leader of your grade in our department,
you are responsible for the connecting with
your seniors.
The rest of you can visit the lab, now.
Okay. Thank you, Professor.
Professor,
I'm an intern team member.
Senior
Project progress data of the laboratory
can be found in the computer.
These are the relevant research topics.
You may read by yourself.
You top students
are all so unfriendly?
Why are you still here?
Because I'm curious about the world of you genius
and want to take a look with my own eyes.
To be honest, I think you are indeed a brilliant student.
As a freshman,
it is good enough to know
how to write the code.
While you are
ready to learn how to make robots.
What's this?
Don't touch things in the laboratory casually.
Siyue, congratulations.
You are the group leader now.
The research topic you reported last time was pretty good.
Thank you.
We can talk about it
someday when we are free.
Okay.
Look,
this is our school post bar.
Yeah.
How could this happen?
His son is right there.
He is the son?
Professor of Academy of Fine Arts in Huaqing University is suspected of academic fraud.
The son of him
was admitted to Huaqing University by pulling strings.
What's this?
Yeah.
It's him.
What's the matter? Are you okay?
I hope not.
Use the vulgar means of controlling the host to send information.
It seems that you want me to know that you did it
You must be mistaken.
I've sent a message to the phone that controls the host
by means of the network.
He posted this.
He did this.
Zhou Siyue
The academic misconduct of your father
is no news at all.
Stop arguing for him.
Hope you will never do things
you father has already done.
Finished?
Yeah.
What can you do with me?
Sue me?
Stop. Stop.
Stop it.
Calm down.
Yeah. Calm down.
Are you okay?
My ankle...
I sprained my ankle because of you.
Can't you take me to the school infirmary?
Let's go.
It hurts.
Zhou Siyue
I have to study hard for the examination.
Let's stop contacting each other from now on.
Perhaps,
from the moment I decided to repeat a school year,
the life tracks of us
have already been staggered.
I'm apart from everyone,
and my life gradually deviates from the original track.
I thought all can back to normal eventually,
but I forgot
that you have already
begun your new life.
We are about to usher in
December 21st, 2012.
It's said to be the end of the world in Mayan culture.
If one day,
we all disappear from the world,
who do you hope
to be with you that day?
What do you think the end of the world
in 2012 is like?
I think
it's just like what the movie has shown to us.
Earthquake, tsunami,
and volcanic eruption.
It's December 21st, now.
Who's with you?
If the end of the world is about to come,
I hope
there will be fireworks all over the sky
So that we can face death
with the last beauty.
The fireworks of the end of the world disappeared in the sky.
But it let me
see a new dawn on the night
before the coming of destruction.
If tomorrow is the end of the world,
the last one I want to see
is you.
Zhou Siyue
Wait for me in Huaqing.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to join Dong Zhengfei's research group.
Okay.
Good luck.
Boss
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Dong Zhengfei has recruited our members like this for weeks.
You don't know this?
Our research topic is humanoid robot.
There are many uncertainties.
She feels it's hard to continue the topic.
Do you want me to burn her boat?
At first, her academic performance was at the bottom
and no group but us accepted her.
Now she has learned the skills.
And the research is in the middle, she kicks down the ladder now.
Where can I find someone else to design the drive mechanism?
Don't worry. It's not that difficult to find one.
If we depend on your relations with others,
it is very difficult indeed.
Don't you aware that
in the beginning you was a loner?
You didn't talk with others
and they didn't know you.
So they all thought you were arrogant.
It's only me who want to stay and be in the same group with you.
Yeah.
I should really be grateful
for you being there with me.
That's not necessary.
We should try to find a qualified member, now.
Don't worry.
At worst, I can just spend more time doing it myself.
You only sleep for five hours a day, now.
Are you out of your mind?
You know I'm tired.
Then go back to work now.
Boss
You see,
I've stayed here for two days.
I'm longing to take half a day off this afternoon.
There are many new girls in campus today.
If I miss the chance to know them,
I'll regret all my life.
Always think about this stuff.
Just go.
Thank you.
I'll go now.
I don't know Zhou Siyue's new number.
Do you find him now?
Where's Zhou Siyue?
I don't even know where I am now.
This is unbelievable.
All have gone
in such a short time
A girl is just over there.
You may go now.
Good brother.
Wait, wait.
Do you know what to say?
No.
Buddy, come here.
Thank you.
You should be obliging
and take the girl and her luggage to the dormitory
in case of others offering help to her.
I got it.
Okay. Okay. Go.
Come on.
Hi, why are you here alone?
You must get lost.
You are going to the girls' dormitory, aren't you?
I'll take you there.
I don't go to the girls' dormitory. I'm going to the boys' dormitory.
Don't worry. I'm not a bad guy.
Look. I'm a volunteer.
It's my duty to help you.
No, thanks.
I don't need your help.
It's okay.
It's okay. Leave her alone. You rascal.
You always say that you are a volunteer
and do such things every year.
But bro, just now you...
What? What?
Who's your bro?
Save it.
There are many liars like him every year.
If you need
help and...
You bad guy.
Stop following me.
No, thanks.
Zhou Siyue's character and academic performance are all excellent.
He is handsome and modest.
If Dong Zhengfei gets the chance,
I won't agree.
He's not that excellent.
A crooked stick throws a crooked shadow.
I don't want to join his research group.
Something bad will happen sooner or later.
Girl
This is boys' dorm.
Girls can't go in.
I know. I'm a freshman.
I just want to find someone there.
No. You can't break the school rules.
Just two minutes.
Why don't you listen to me?
No way.
Stop this or I'll call the security office.
Zhou Siyue
Zhou Siyue, I've come here for you.
There is a girl downstairs in the boys' dormitory,
chasing her love.
Really? What a love story!
Zhou Siyue
The secret hidden in the bottom of my heart
was carefully
sealed in a dusty box by me.
But one day the box will be opened again.
I thought I had forgotten everything,
only to realize that I never really let it go.
Zhou Siyue
Ding Xian
Happy to see you.
I called you, but you didn't answer. I sent you messages and you didn't reply, either.
I thought you wouldn't see me again.
I've changed my phone number. I didn't tell you.
I want to say something to you.
Okay.
I like you.
Have you ever liked me?
Ding Xian
I don't want to be in a relationship right now.
It's getting late. You may go back now.
Work hard in the future
and don't come to me again.
We made an appointment to go to Huaqing University together.
And I worked so hard to try to follow your steps.
I made it.
I just want to know
whether you've liked me or not.
Liked or not.
Does it matter?
Ding Xian
Now we both have our own lives.
So what?
Zhou Siyue
Do you know my secret?
It's getting late. I've got to go.
Hi,
I want to ask
whether the patient in Bed 2 of Room 318 has paid the bill.
Wait a minute.
Bed 2 of Room 318, right?
Not yet.
Are you his family member?
You'd better pay the bill as soon as possible.
This can't be delayed.
Okay.
Hello?
Siyue, where are you?
Your father is ill.
What?
Now I cannot
even protect my families.
How can I be qualified to protect her?
Hi, dad.
Xianxian is so excellent.
You are a student of a century-old top university.
Have you visited the campus?
I'm too busy to
look around.
Hold on. You mother wants to talk to you.
Xianxian, have you arrived at your dormitory?
No, not yet.
I'll be there later.
It's near noon. Why don't you go to your dorm first?
What are you up to?
I should have gone with you.
Okay, mom.
I'll call you tonight.
I've got to go.
Don't forget to send me some photos.
Okay, mom.
Don't worry.
It was too late to get there today.
We'd better go earlier next time.
How is grandpa doing recently?
I heard that the winner of the gold medal in the Computer Department
is our direct senior.
What's his name?
It's you.
We are just talking about
whether our roommate is you.
Good for you.
Everyone in Class One knows you.
Here. Sit down.
No, you can sit.
Sit down. I'll stand here. I'm trying to lose weight.
Well, I'm Lou Feng.
I'm Ding Xian.
Nice to see you.
This is Ban Jiayu.
This is Xu Shasha.
You was dragged away by him, wasn't you?
I heard that the boy you like
is in Computer Department.
And he's super handsome.
Why haven't I heard of him before?
You don't know that.
I'll introduce the basic information to you.
In our department, there are two popular students.
One is Dong Zhengfei.
The other is
your Zhou Siyue.
No kidding?
I've heard about Dong Zhengfei
before the school starts.
But Zhou Siyue,
I have no impression on him.
Let me finish.
They have
something in common though.
They have totally different dispositions.
One is like fire
while the other is like ice.
You've just mentioned a robot...
Robot competition.
The award ceremony of the robot competition will be held tomorrow.
I think the winner will be Dong Zhengfei
or Zhou Siyue.
You are so noisy.
Never mind.
It's okay. I'll go with you tomorrow.
Start.
The end of the world.
The autumn sky is clear and the air is crisp.
Students from all over the country come to schools.
It's time to welcome new arrivals again.
A large number of freshmen
enter the university with their dreams.
Our reporter also followed the students...
No.
It's okay.
As we all know, embracing a long history, Huaqing University
is well-known in China
and it has always been the palace of knowledge
in the eyes of many students.
The Computer Department and Mathematics Department...
Here.
Eat an apple.
Is everything okay
in school?
Everything is okay.
Just rest assured and take good care of yourself.
That's good.
Don't be so tired like this.
You should take study as your priority.
Don't come here too often.
I'm fine.
Siyue is here.
You have left for quite a while.
Are you lost again?
Could you please think something better on me?
Have you found the cashier?
Of course.
Your mother is
qualified enough for handling all these.
Don't worry about this stuff.
Just study hard
and get the quota for going abroad settled.
Mr. Ye has told us
that you stand a great chance.
It's too early to talk about this.
It's not too late to think about it after dad gets well.
Then I'll go back to school now.
Call me if you need me.
Will you come this evening?
I'm kind of busy these days.
I'll come again on weekends.
You study so hard
and do several jobs.
Remember to have meals regularly.
Okay, I will.
I have to go now.
Siyue
Take good care of yourself.
See you.
Winning teams of the 2012 robot competition.
Please appoint representatives to the stage to get the awards in turn.
Let's welcome Li Minghao
and Liu Zhenghui.
The team from
the Department of Automation won the first prize.
Welcome
Dong Zhengfei.
Now, let's warmly welcome Professor Ye
to give them the awards.
He is just a representative to receive the award.
It's a team award.
Look at him.
It seems that he is receiving a personal award.
You are just jealous.
If you prepare for it earnestly,
how could he get the award?
Let's go. It's about to finish.
I now declare
the competition a great success.
Please leave in order.
Excuse me.
Sorry, I don't add strangers on WeChat.
Don't get me wrong.
I just want to ask that
you are in the same class with Zhou Siyue, right?
I want to see him.
It's you.
You are still looking for him.
We are in the same class,
but
we are not friends.
Classmates don't always mean friends.
You have come to the wrong person.