And now,
it's time for Kwon Ryoc
to choose his teammate.
Hey,
sit back down and stay there.
Kwon Ryoc,
please open your eyes.
Who could be standing behind you?
Please turn around.
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
Unfortunately, no one came forth.
I'll give you a second chance.
Is there anyone
who'd like to team up with Kwon Ryoc?
I guess they find you hard to approach.
Unfortunately, you have failed
to team up with anyone.
And now, Kwon Ryoc and Ma-ha
will get to choose.
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
Who do you want on your team?
I--
I choose Yu-jin.
Okay, I'll team up with Ryoc.
Lee Ma-ha will team up with Lee Yu-jin
while La Ri-ma will
team up with Kwon Ryoc.
Now, we have all our teams!
You four may return to your seats.
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
What a loser.
Here's the song choice
for Yu-jin and Ma-ha.
Yu-jin and Ma-ha.
The song you'll be singing
is of a male soloist from the 90s.
It's now time to see the last song choice.
Kwon Ryoc and La Ri-ma.
Which era will their song be from?
Kwon Ryoc and La Ri-ma
will be singing a song
by a male soloist from the 80s.
All the songs have now been chosen,
so let's check the final list.
[Teams, Song Category]
Big Little and Mirae,
boy band from the 80s.
Ju-ho and Soo-a,
female soloist from the 70s.
Si-woon and Yul, girl group from the 90s.
[Teams, Song Category]
Min-su and Se-ra,
coed group from the 2000s.
Do-jin and Hyuk,
coed group from the 2010s.
Hyun Woo-jin and Ri-a,
female soloist from the 90s.
Yu-jin and Ma-ha,
male soloist from the 90s.
Kwon Ryoc and La Ri-ma,
male soloist from the 80s.
And now, all the songs have been chosen.
You have until next week
to come fully prepared.
We'll look forward
to next week's show then!
[Teams, Song Category]
I can't believe you actually chose me.
Isn't that why you came out?
We'll do a good job, brother.
Ryoc, us teaming up is one thing,
but why didn't you choose Ma-ha?
We broke up.
-Did you dump her?
-Or did she dump you?
[Drink this while you work, guys.]
The work will be easier
since you're teamed up with Yu-jin.
Right?
Ma-ha?
What?
A penny for your thoughts?
["Like When We First Met"]
How about this song?
[Are you even listening to me?]
-What?
-Focus, will you?
Why is your head somewhere else today?
Sorry.
Which song was it again?
Let's just sing that one.
Without even listening to it?
We'll sing whichever song you want.
How's that?
It's not a song I can currently relate to,
but it'll definitely
hit close to home for you.
["My Old Story" by Cho Deok-bae]
[Byun Jeong-hui]
Is this what you wanted to tell me?
[Was Eun-jo really sick when he left NOG?]
-The song choice isn't the matter for us.
-No.
-You do it.
-Do it.
-No.
-It suits you.
-That's part of your charm.
-No.
-Rock-paper-scissors then.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors. Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Scissors, scissors, scissors--
Enough!
-We'll decide with a hanafuda deck.
-I don't think we can find one here.
-Why do you have that?
-I always carry it around.
I'm a true Korean, aren't I?
-Let me.
-Why?
["Trouble Maker"]
I'll do it.
♫ Briefly in the middle of the day ♫
♫ We meet on the phone ♫
That was great.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I'm glad.
-Woo-jin, you have another gig.
I'm sorry about this.
-But our practice--
-I have another gig to get to.
We'll practice some other time.
But when?
I'll sing this section
while you sing the next part.
How about we divide it like that?
I thought about it,
and it'll be better
from one person's perspective.
So why don't you sing the entire song
while I focus on harmonizing?
What do you think?
We'll give it a try.
["Hyun Woo-jin Injured in Car Accident"]
-It must be serious.
-He must've been badly injured.
I feel bad for Hyun Woo-jin.
It must've happened on his way to a gig.
But the show's tomorrow.
-Did you hear from her?
-She went to the studio.
How can she manage on her own?
I should probably
check the desk for cracks.
It's not like you to seem defeated.
What do you mean?
I'll do it.
We arranged the song together,
so we'll only have to practice it
a few times.
You are going to sing with me?
The network would be thrilled
to have me on the show anyway.
Right. Then I won't decline.
You must really be grateful.
Hence the blushing.
You can thank me some other way though.
Some other way? How?
Let's record the song first.
We're running out of time.
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
♫ Trouble maker ♫
♫ I stand before you
so that you won't forget me ♫
♫ I make your heart waver
so that you can't escape me ♫
♫ I steal your lips and run far away ♫
♫ I'm a trouble, trouble maker ♫
♫ Pick me ♫
♫ Trouble maker ♫
♫ Uno, dos, tres, vamos ♫
♫ I become a trouble maker
when I look into your eyes ♫
when I'm with you ♫
♫ A little more, more, more ♫
♫ As it keeps going ♫
♫ I can't control my heart anymore ♫
♫ I stand before you
so that you won't forget me ♫
♫ I make your heart waver
so that you can't escape me ♫
♫ I steal your lips and run far away ♫
♫ I'm a trouble, trouble maker ♫
♫ Trouble maker ♫
♫ I-hyeon and Ri-a ♫
♫ We go on a date ♫
♫ Down ♫
♫ Let's go ♫
♫ Your deep voice ♫
♫ That comes
from the other side of the receiver ♫
♫ No matter when I hear it ♫
♫ It always seems sweet ♫
♫ We promised each other ♫
♫ To meet up again tomorrow ♫
♫ Even though we're apart ♫
♫ You are my everything ♫
♫ Briefly in the middle of the day ♫
♫ It doesn't even have to be long ♫
♫ We meet on the phone ♫
♫ Just you and me ♫
♫ You and me ♫
♫ Yes, you and me ♫
♫ Our fun date ♫
♫ I love everything about you ♫
♫ Whenever I close my eyes ♫
♫ I'll then close my eyes too ♫
♫ You're always besides me
flashing that sweet smile ♫
♫ Not even saying a word ♫
♫ You're my date, your charming voice ♫
♫ The music plays ♫
♫ Your reflection in the mirror ♫
♫ Makes this feel like a dream ♫
♫ With you,
my love for you is old-school ♫
♫ This is how it is ♫
♫ From brief moments to eternity ♫
♫ I love everything about you ♫
♫ Whenever I close my eyes ♫
♫ I'll then close my eyes too ♫
♫ You're always besides me
flashing that sweet smile ♫
♫ Not even saying a word ♫
-Nice!
-Go, I-hyeon!
-I-hyeon, I-hyeon!
-That was the best!
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
♫ While rubbing my sleepy eyes ♫
♫ I read
the now crumpled letter you wrote ♫
♫ My heart that was only filled with joy ♫
♫ Was suddenly swept with sorrow ♫
♫ I saw the stain of teardrops ♫
♫ On the letters that spelled "goodbye" ♫
♫ My face that only knew of smiles ♫
♫ Was suddenly swept with shadows ♫
♫ Why did you leave me so suddenly? ♫
♫ How could you have
bid farewell so easily? ♫
♫ If only it were a dream ♫
♫ If only it were you
playing games with me ♫
♫ I now even regret the days
I spent with you ♫
♫ It shouldn't be this easy
to say goodbye ♫
♫ Just like the time we first met ♫
[Ryoc!]
From now on, your junior, Lee Ma-ha,
will show lots of support
for my senior, Kwon Ryoc.
Go, Kwon Ryoc!
♫ If only it were a dream ♫
♫ If only it were you
playing games with me ♫
♫ If only it were a dream ♫
♫ If only it were you
playing games with me ♫
♫ I now even regret the days
I spent with you ♫
♫ It shouldn't be this easy
to say goodbye ♫
♫ Just like the time ♫
♫ We first met ♫
Check them out.
♫ Do you still remember ♫
♫ The lonesome and forlorn alleyway? ♫
♫ Well, I still do ♫
♫ The days I spent in heartache ♫
♫ Not able to tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Were you aware of it? ♫
♫ You were childish ♫
♫ To try to take everything from me ♫
♫ Oh, how heartless you were ♫
♫ You heartless one ♫
♫ Were you too shy to say anything? ♫
♫ Or didn't you
like me enough to say it? ♫
♫ I still can't tell ♫
♫ Oh, heartless one ♫
♫ Are you once again trying ♫
♫ To take everything from me tonight? ♫
♫ How childish of you ♫
♫ How immature of you ♫
♫ Do you still remember ♫
♫ The lonesome and forlorn alleyway? ♫
♫ Well, I still do ♫
-♫ The days I spent in heartache ♫
-Let's break up.
♫ Not able to tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Were you aware of it? ♫
♫ If you get to hear this song ♫
♫ Please come back to me ♫
♫ I'm here waiting for you ♫
♫ Tonight, tomorrow night ♫
♫ And the night after that ♫
♫ Forever ♫
♫ I will await you ♫
[Kwon Ryoc and La Ri-ma,
1st place, 274 points]
Kwon Ryoc, this is something
I never expected you to do.
I'm definitely right.
What did I tell you?
[Kwon Ryoc and La Ri-ma,
1st place, 274 points]
Smile!
I'll have to decline.
What gives?
Are you looking down on us
because you're a celeb?
He is.
Are you looking down on me or what?
What's with that look?
It looks like you're going to hit me.
Hit me. Then hit me.
It'd be a good experience
to be hit by a celeb.
♫ The days I spent in heartache ♫
♫ Not able to tell you that I love you ♫
♫ Were you aware of it? ♫
♫ If you get to hear this song ♫
♫ Please come back to me ♫
♫ I am ♫
♫ Still waiting ♫
You all did well with the commercial
and "Y.M.S.A."
You don't have any gigs for a few days,
and you've been really busy,
so you should take a break to recuperate.
I'll sleep as long as I want.
But you slept all the time.
I was so stressed about "Y.M.S.A."
that I tossed and turned a lot.
-Not because of I-hyeon?
-What are you talking about?
Why would you talk about him now?
I'll visit my mom.
I want to eat what she makes for me.
Where is Hyeon-o?
What happened?
I told you to stay low!
"Idol A Goes on the Rampage
in the Middle of the Night"?
That's not true!
They picked a fight with me first!
Why did you even go to a pub?
The higher-ups know about this already.
They're talking about replacing you!
And we'll be merging with NOG soon.
-NOG?
-You get what I mean, right?
This is a very crucial period.
That means people who cause trouble
might be dismissed!
We'll have a brief meeting
and head to the set afterward.
Shall we listen to the radio?
-Dae-gwon
-Yes?
-Let's change the station.
-Sure.
What's wrong with this today?
The weather's great today.
♫ Show me, I'm sorry, I'm a little busy ♫
♫ Tell me, I'm your Tea Party ♫
[Caution, vehicle exiting]
[NOG Entertainment]
What do you think you're doing?
This is all because of you.
You stole my place from NOG,
and now you've ruined my life.
-What?
-It started on the day you joined.
We picked the members of SHAX
through an audition.
You know that well.
An audition? As if.
I was supposed to take your spot.
It was all decided.
I could've become a member of SHAX.
You...
Fine. I'm sorry if I hurt you.
What are you doing?
Hyeon-o.
-Stop it.
-Move.
Stop it already!
Who cares if you're signed
with NOG or Music Holic?
-What did you say?
-It doesn't matter where you belong to.
You know very well
what the real problem is.
Think about the time and sweat
you put in for your dream.
Don't live your life with regrets
like a coward.
You're such a showoff!
I'll just have a meal with my mom.
I didn't say anything.
I'll be right back. Make sure to stay put.
Have a great time.
[NOG]
I look forward to working with you.
Likewise.
["NOG Entertainment
Takes Over Queen Entertainment"]
[Queen Entertainment is the agency
La Ri-ma is signed with.]
-Did you know about this?
-About what?
["NOG Entertainment
Takes Over Queen Entertainment"]
I did hear NOG was looking for companies
to take over.
[Queen Entertainment]
What do we do now?
What if we get kicked out after the merge?
I'm sure some of us will be kicked out.
I practiced with all my might
for my debut.
Those jerks.
I thought it'd be
a good chance for you too.
You went through a lot in our agency
because it was small.
-Sir.
-Yes?
I liked working with Queen Entertainment.
You had an eye for talented kids
and didn't save on the creative lessons
for the trainees.
Although it wasn't a big agency,
I was proud of it.
But since when did you
start selling talents for money?
That's not it.
You sold me out
to fire all those trainees?
Why would you mind them?
They have their own paths.
This is all about business.
[CEO Hwang Yong-tae]
I put you where you are
with all my hard work.
Exactly! I opened a door
to a whole new world for you.
-World class!
-Mr. Hwang.
You still have no idea who I am.
What are you doing?
[Queen Entertainment]
Oh, my. Your nameplate must've
been fake too. It shattered right away.
-You crazy wench!
-You get it now?
I'm a crazy wench.
You should live your life, Mr. Hwang.
I can't just move to that agency alone.
This relationship is over.
-It's all about business.
-What?
It's not me who ended our contract.
It's you, Mr. Hwang.
If you're going to sue me,
use a top-class lawyer.
Don't use a lousy one. It won't be fun.
Okay?
[Sarang Orphanage]
Why is no one home?
I told her I was coming.
Mom!
What's going on?
Why is no one home?
It's strange.
Where did everyone go?
-Ma-ha!
What was that?
How have you all been?
You're here.
It's been so long, Ms. Jeong.
I have to bring in the laundry
and make side dishes.
I'm glad you're here to help.
Put your luggage inside and help me.
Yes, ma'am!
Let's go.
-Ma-ha, wait for me!
Ma-ha!
Let's break up.
[From now on, your junior, Lee Ma-ha,]
[will show lots of support
for my senior, Kwon Ryoc.]
[What would've happened
if I didn't say that?]
[What would've happened]
[if I held Ma-ha back?]
Ma-ha
must've had a really hard time.
I feel so bad.
I didn't even try to understand her
and whined about my feelings.
I think she needs some time.
So don't worry too much.
She'll return all bright after a few days.
Welcome.
-Isn't that Kwon Ryoc.
-Oh, my.
-It's Kwon Ryoc!
-What?
-What is he doing here?
-Ryoc.
-I can't reach Ma-ha.
You want me to deliver all this by myself?
Would you rather do the dishes?
I'm back home after a long time,
and you're making me work so much.
Of course.
Who knows when you'll be back again?
I should use you when I can.
I'll go back to Seoul now.
No, you can't.
You came on your own accord,
but you can't leave without my permission.
What kind of orphanage
looks after isolated senior citizens?
Why are you being so sluggish?
Hurry up and go!
Why do people call you Mother Teresa?
You're so evil!
[Sarang Orphanage]
-I'll help you.
-It's fine.
You should go.
I'm telling you this for the ninth time.
Isn't it hot? Aren't you tired?
Should I just call a meal service
for them?
Is it okay for you to be here?
Please just leave.
Are you sure it's that way?
[Jangnahangan-gil]
Could you go back a little?
It's this way.
If you're going to push, then push harder!
It's there.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you for this.
-Goodbye.
Let's go.
Go up.
I'll take it.
-It's up there.
-When are we eating?
Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
-Ma'am!
-You're giving us a meal box again?
-I'm so grateful.
-Thank you.
[Jangnahangan-gil]
It's this way.
[Dae-gwon]
Come on, Dae-gwon.
Hey! The wagon! The wagon!
I caught it. I caught it.
What do we do about the meal boxes?
Didn't you hurt yourself?
Here. It's for your hard work.
Now that we're done, you should go.
The breeze is nice up here.
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
Why did you call me?
Well... Can't I?
You said you're my fan.
If you don't promise me that
you'll pick up my calls, I'm not leaving.
This isn't what I had in mind.
What about the kids?
They must've been tired
after running around all day
because you're here.
All of them fell asleep
as soon as they lied down.
They have better stamina than me.
I know.
About that guy...
No, he's not my boyfriend!
I didn't ask.
You're too independent.
You should lean on me sometimes.
You told me to be more independent.
That's what you told me since I was young.
But that was
when I first started
accepting kids for our orphanage,
so they needed my help.
That's why I felt bad for you sometimes.
Seeing how you manage everything
on your own
makes me proud.
But it must've been really lonely
for you.
I did want to
have all of your attention on me
as the only daughter,
but I was really happy
to have you and Dad as my parents.
Really?
Of course. You have
a healing hand
that heals the kids with broken hearts.
A healing hand?
When I sit next to you,
my heart warms up right away.
How can I not love a mom like you?
I'm so sorry and thank you, my dear.
-Aren't you tired though?
-What?
You need to look after yourself too.
Are you calling me old?
But people still mistake me as a newlywed.
Sure you are.
Ms. New Bride, I made the bed for you,
so you should go to bed now.
Do you want to sleep with me today?
I'd love to!
[He must be gone by now.]
[Or is he still here?]
[Whatever!]
[Gosh, it's bothering me so much!]
I can't even sleep because of him.
Even if she doesn't mean it,
why couldn't she text me
saying I did a great job
and thank me for my trouble?
Gosh.
It's so cold.
Why is he still here?
It's cold by the sea.
Should I have brought a blanket?
Gosh, it's so cold.
It's so cold.
I guess he's leaving now.
[Dae-gwon]
Hey, Dae-gwon.
[Missed calls, Dae-gwon]
[Where are you?]
[Pick up your phone!]
[Dae-gwon]
[Where did you run to?]
[Hey, Ryoc!]
Gosh, it's so cold.
It's so cold.
What?
No.
No!
You haven't left?
-May I borrow some money?
-What?
I ran out of gas.
You should've called someone.
If I do, Dae-gwon might faint.
That car is his treasure.
I'm so tired
from trembling through the night.
It's so cold.
Are we all done now?
I'll give you a ride. Hop in.
It's okay. Goodbye.
Enjoy your lunch. Eat everything.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Eat up.
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Don't be so mean
to someone who came to help.
That's not what I meant.
So you two were friends for a long time?
I thought he only looked handsome,
but he has a kind heart too.
He came out here to volunteer.
And he helped out yesterday too?
I was a bit clumsy yesterday,
but I can do better today.
Come on, Dae-gwon.
It looks like you came
without telling him.
You should go.
Ma-ha, I want a rolled omelet.
A rolled omelet? Okay.
You should fight with her
from time to time.
She came home for the first time in months
thanks to your fight.
I'll fight her from time to time.
Leave it to me.
A cute bickering, lovey-dovey. Okay?
Lovey-dovey.
All right, I have your egg omelet.
Who ordered this?
I did!
-Try some.
-Thank you.
Don't mention it.
I told you to go,
but you just won't leave.
Why do you suddenly pop up
and make my life hard?
Do you hold a grudge against me?
Why did you suddenly show up?
What are you trying to do?
You wanted to break up.
Let's at least stay in touch.
What?
You know,
as a senior and a junior, as fans.
We can do that, can't we?
There's no reason
to treat each other like strangers.
The padded jacket incident.
Do you remember that?
I realized how sensitives fans are
when that incident broke out.
They take notice of my feelings
even before I realized them myself.
We're people
who have to receive things from them.
We need their interest and love.
If we stay in this relationship in secret,
our fans will end up catching on to us.
And Tea Party
just began to get people's attention.
I want to make Tea Party work
with Ri-a and Hyun-ji.
So I can't get involved in a scandal
with you.
Ma-ha.
If you forgot
all about SHAX, Tea Party, and Fins,
how would you feel?
How do you feel about me now?
Don't you see anything?
What am I supposed to see?
The hidden truth.
Gosh, you're supposed to spot it.
This is...
I wonder what Eun-jo is up to.
[Bucket List]
[Jang Yu-ri rests here.]
[Republic of Korea, Passport]
[CEO Park Jin-man]
La Ri-ma just left Queen Entertainment.
What should we do about Queen?
We already made use of the publicity.
-Why should we care?
-I understand, sir.
-It's time to give out the press release.
-Sorry?
That all of SHAX are
planning on resigning the contract
after the MML Festival.
Leak it out to the media,
and make it look promising.
Yes, sir.
You may go.
Let's walk together.
-Ryoc, how many times do I have to...
-Please let me
walk the same journey as you do.
Ma-ha.
I'm sorry I let you go.
And I'm sorry I hid like a coward.
Please let me
hold your hand once again,
Ma-ha.
Pick it up. He's waiting for you.
I'm waiting for your answer too.
I'm not leaving
until you give me an answer.
So tell me how you honestly feel.
What do you want to do at this point?
What am I supposed to do?
We should go back now.
Did you clear out your schedule?
What do we do
once we go back to Seoul?
Why?
Are you worried?
Of course, I am.
Ryoc, you went easy on her, right?
Did you keep the speed limit?
You won't make me pay a fine
for speeding or illegal parking?
You know,
I took such good care of you
that your career is spotless.
I hope you also didn't hurt my baby.
Why won't you say anything?
-Dae-gwon.
-What now?
I want to publicize my romance.
Are you crazy? You're going public?
Have you gone insane?
What did you just say?
He just dropped a nuclear bomb.
Publicizing your romance?
You've gone crazy.
I knew something wasn't right
the moment he came to the cafe.
I'm sorry everything came down to this,
and I was scared
this might affect SHAX negatively.
So I tried to hold myself back,
but I can't do this.
Please understand me just this once.
I know. I know that I'm being selfish.
But I can't live like this.
Please let me do this.
Ryoc.
I don't want to fool you and Fins.
That's why I thought of this.
This is all for the best,
-going public.
-You lunatic!
Fine, let's tell everyone.
SHAX shares everything with the world,
so let's tell them everything.
Fine, do it. Go public!
Calm down.
Why didn't you tell me first?
I'm sorry.
Don't forget
just because you're a big shot.
I'm the leader.
You should've told me first
before you dropped that bomb.
I'm sorry.
I knew how hard you work for SHAX.
That's why it was harder to tell you.
Please trust me, though.
I won't let this hurt SHAX...
I don't want to lose you
just as we lost Eun-jo.
SHAX will keep going
to the very end.
Jae-u.
Why are you bringing Eun-jo into this?
I'm willing to do anything for our team.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Now that I actually took his hand,
I'm starting to get scared.
And the reality hits me very hard too.
But
I don't want to deceive my feelings
or other people
any longer.
What now?
It's because they have nothing to lose.
No, that's not what I meant.
I get how you feel.
I get it.
But this isn't the right timing.
We need to take a special measure.
They're making so many of us concerned.
Kids, I'm busy.
I have to find an agency soon.
I got many people on the payroll.
I need to release my song too.
What about my song?
When will you be finished?
First off, we'll be the only ones
who know about this.
And you all agree
that it's too early
to publicize their relationship, right?
Then where will they meet?
-If we stop them...
-He'll do anything to see her.
I'm worried they might
end up getting caught by stalker fans
while they drive around.
And the secret place is finished.
They can't be at a park or a mountain.
I'm sure they'll manage.
-No!
-They'll get caught soon.
-Whatever. I'm done with this.
Why do you act like
this doesn't concern you?
Then what? Should I get them a hotel room?
-A hotel room?
-What?
-What hotel?
-Are you crazy?
-How can you say that?
-They'll manage.
-We can't let...
-Nonsense.
Hey! All of you.
Has any of you ever dated?
-The safest hideout is your dorms.
-Dorms?
-Can they be at yours?
-No.
People have their eyes on us.
No, it'll be too uncomfortable.
-What about yours?
-What?
Well, I...
Our neighborhood is pretty quiet.
-And only Ri-a and Ma-ha live there.
-Hyun-ji.
Okay, then they'll meet there. Happy?
No, wait.
I practiced all these.
I practiced so much.
I'm glad they could
eat here and have coffee here,
but why do I feel lonely?
Right, Ryoc.
I need to get something from you.
-What is it?
-One second.
All three of them are cute.
Where have I seen her?
If you aren't here for an inspection,
take a seat.
So who's she?
Oh, Annie?
-Annie?
-A former member of OMEGA-3.
Ma-ha joined us when Annie left.
Ryoc.
I'll be done with this
once I get you to sign it.
[Let's be stars! Go, Ma-ha!]
Eun-jo.
[Epilogue]
[9:39 p.m., December 17th, 2016]
Where did he go in this snow?
I should be taking you home.
Forget it.
I'm sorry I couldn't walk you home.
You'll get cold. Hurry up and go home.
Call me when you get home.
Bye, then.
Who is she?
Ryoc.
She's my girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
-Today was our 3,000th day anniversary.
-Your 3,000th day?
You've secretly been with her
for 3,000 days?
Ryoc.