Your Highness has not recovered from his injuries
How can Your Majesty let you now
Leave for Nanjing
Royal Guards have found out
The middleman who made contact with the assassin
When they arrived,
People have committed suicide
But the identity of that man
Very unusual
Do you remember
When I was eight years old
Grandpa Huang himself
Recruiting government troops from the people, avant-garde young troops
Follow me to practice martial arts and train soldiers
He used to be a soldier in the young army
This is clearly a structure
How can Your Majesty believe
What about this nonsense
This man not only alienates our father and son
And tried to transfer me out of Beijing
His heart can be punished
Please take your highness to dinner
He is a man of integrity
Strong character
However, those who are rigid are easy to fold
Get involved in officialdom too early
Is not necessarily a good thing
I'll find a way
Let him out
Exercise for a few years
Treat him with full wings
Someday
It must be the pillar of the country
He cares about the world and his home country
Often lenient with others
Be strict with oneself
Especially when it comes to family
The constraints will be too strict
I'm afraid you won't get used to it
That's right
I forgot
You're so nice
How could he say you
Your Highness
What exactly do you mean
Aren't you leaving the palace
Your Highness wants to release me from the palace
But the Empress
I have my own way
Have nothing to do with others
Your Highness didn't deceive me
But why
I haven't seen you for a long time
Laugh so happily
At least he can make you laugh
Waiting for your husband to sing along with your wife in the future
And harmonious
Don't know
Will you still remember this study
Will you remember me
His Highness said he was
Who the hell is it
Let's go
Or I'll go back on my word
Your Highness promised me to leave the palace and marry
But no matter how good that person is,
But not my sweetheart
Who is your sweetheart
It's nobody
Your Highness
This steamed chicken made by Guiqi
It is made of Angelica sinensis
And chicken stewed with roasted Astragalus membranaceus
People with loss of qi and blood after illness
Use the best
I know you have a bad appetite recently
You can use some
It is of great benefit to your injury
And said you didn't care about me
Your Highness misunderstood
It's a prescription prescribed by Dr. Sheng Tai
We're just
It's just cooking according to the prescription
Your Highness
Dr. Sheng knows
Your injury has been delayed
Diet is the best way to dispense medicine
Therefore, I ordered people to send medicated diet today
Where is this Shengyin
What an old fool
Clearly told you to prepare meals
And asked someone to send it again
Handmaiden retires
Ali
You guys stand down
It's your highness
You don't want to say
I won't force you
Anyway
I don't have a few days to bother you either
I will go to Nanjing soon
Your Highness
Your injury is not healed
Don't overwork yourself
This is my father's order
This is the prince's fault
It is obviously my father who suspects me
Why is it my fault
Your Highness wants father and son to make up
You should let go of the estrangement
Sincerely to the emperor
Show your heart
You think I haven't tried
But every time
My father put me
Keep it away thousands of miles away
Maybe
Is that your highness used the wrong method
Well done
Recipe canon meal
Can I do it today
Go to the meal with you
When was the food bureau so unruly
A small palm meal
I also want to enter Ganqing Palace
Don't step down yet
Sosur meal
Meng Shangshi is slightly dyed with wind and cold today
You can't go to Ganqing Palace to deliver food
I just want to help Fang Dianshan
It's time to deliver food
Your Majesty
This snack
Originated from Lin'an City in Southern Song Dynasty
It is made of cheese and sucrose
Oysters are often called abalone
So this oyster-shaped snack
It is called abalone snail
This porridge is good
Handmaiden is a fire room
Cultivated chamomile seedlings cook porridge
The taste is refreshing and appetizing
Of course I know
This is the taste of hometown
Nanjing calls this chrysanthemum brain
Eat as soup
You recently
This benefit is really not small
Last time it was handmaiden recklessness
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
Father
Your Highness, be careful
It was all an unintentional loss
I won't blame you
Avoid
Your Majesty forgives the handmaiden
Handmaiden Thanksgiving
Handmaiden is listening to the Imperial Doctor
Since the banquet in Shangyuan,
Your Majesty was frightened
Be dizzy all the time
This reminds me of chamomile seedlings
Can treat vertigo and headache
This is the courage to try
Scared, huh
The handmaiden is really frightened
Hiding in the corner all the time
Trembling
Later I saw
The Imperial Concubine Empress is also next to her
This is a relief
Save the driver quickly
Rescue driver
Protect the Emperor
Your Majesty
Guo Guifei asked for an audience
Be absent
Yes
I'm going to the school yard this afternoon
Send dinner there
Yes
Father
Aren't you leaving for Nanjing
Why haven't you started yet
My son prepared a meal
Let's have dinner together
No need