Your Highness
An assassin
They are all carefully trained dead men
Only two people were left alive
One person died of serious injuries after being imprisoned
There is only one person left
Royal Guards
Is following his line down
As for the last yuan day,
Records of entering and leaving the palace
Hundred troupe song and dance artists
Craftsmen from the Ministry of Industry and the Supervisory Bureaus of Neifu
A total of 643 people
All personnel are registered
It will take some time to check
What do you think
Your Highness
Who is the real murderer is obvious
If Your Majesty and the Prince
The handmaiden dared to say
Can't get away from left and right
The handwriting of two princes
Come on, come on
Don't keep taking these things
To disturb your highness for illness
Can you do it?
Your Highness, lunch has arrived
Where is she
It's still out there
Your Highness Hat
Lord Mei
What happened last time
I am deeply disturbed
Always looking for opportunities
I apologize to you
Meals for me
Did you make it yourself
That's why
There is something wrong with the meal
I am to blame
I hope you will forgive me
That's enough
His Highness has suffered from insomnia recently
More ginseng should not be put in the soup
Excessive tonic is also prone to insomnia
Yao canon meal
How do you know
Your Highness didn't sleep well
Lunch delivered in the past
Your Highness hasn't used it up
Only lily jujube soup is used up
It can be seen that it is for peace of mind
Your Highness
You don't have to worry about things in court
Let's relax and recuperate
Your Highness
How dare a handmaiden reveal it
These things
Lord Mei
You testify for the handmaiden
I just stepped into that threshold
I smell a breath of blood
His Royal Highness is pale
The voice is weaker than before
Or don't hold on
Yeah
It seems that today
I can't visit my mother
So as not to be seen through
In a good mood today
Have a round
Your Highness
Can I have dirt on my face
You frequently look at me
I naturally have to misunderstand
Or I am today
Extremely heroic and natural and unrestrained
Extraordinary charm
His Highness finally smiled
On weekdays, I enter the door
Your Highness always smiles at each other
Today, since stepping over that threshold,
Your Highness has never shown his face
I almost thought
Where did you offend your highness
Shaoyuan
Are you married
Lord Mei
Let's go
The Imperial Doctor has already said it
I won't let you get up
But what about you
Have to listen to him
That's great
The wound opened again
You want to
Don't let the empress worry
Still covering the wound
Let others become
The Great Hero of Rescue
What the hell is going on
It's just skin injuries
Which is so delicate
Go and fetch my book
Your Highness
The food bureau came to deliver snacks
At your command
Bring people in
When did I ever tell you
Let her in
Yes
Handmaiden greets His Royal Highness the Prince
Your Highness hardly moved at lunch
Meng Shangshi charged the handmaiden
Send some cakes
You're awake
Don't get up
I just came to see you
I fear
I said there was no need to be polite
You're hurt
Prince Xie
No
I want to thank you
It is my duty to protect the driver
I dare not bear the word thank you from the prince
You protected the emperor for me
Fulfill one's duty as a son
Should be thanked
But
In the past, ministers only acted on orders
There are occasional offenses
I also hope your highness Haihan
You can thank me again
I didn't come to see you
I'm here to kill you
Grandpa Huang said
You know the military
Military machine change
Suppress bandits and counter-insurgency
Repeatedly make outstanding achievements
I thought your ambition was just martial arts
But now it seems that
This room is full of classics and history
Landscape travel notes
We just know
You dabble in a wide range
Have lofty aspirations
The emperor suspected that his ministers had little knowledge
Order me to read more books
But I am a warrior
I can't stand poetry and songs
But find some books to fill the facade
Let the prince laugh
Is it
Nature
Lord You
His Royal Highness the Prince
Just
Let's talk about it some other time
To His Royal Highness the Prince
Why is Father Liu here
Lord You
Take the decree
The emperor gave you adult
Death-free gold medal
You adult handmaiden gives food by decree
Your Majesty's Oracle
Adult You is seriously injured
You can avoid a big gift
Put it here. You go first
I haven't congratulated you yet
Every cloud has a silver lining
Get a royal gift
Don't say the gold medal for avoiding death
I heard that Prince Lian
Everyone came to visit me personally
Get the royal gift from Emperor Taizu
The hero of Danshu Iron Voucher is expensive
All died of rebellion, and none of them were spared
Don't curse me
Today's Son of Heaven
The name of benevolence spreads all over the world
Lord You's blood won't flow in vain
Is it
Say a few jokes
Why should you be angry
According to this food list in the future,
Cooking for Your Majesty
Forget your promise
Rest assured
Not poison
Go ahead
What's the matter
Don't move
Don't do superfluous things
Young and ignorant
I always hope to meet someone
Someone who can dress my wound
Unfortunately, I didn't wait
Today
Just let me mind my own business one more time
Then I'm a little luckier than you
I'm waiting
Childe
Childe wake up
There is one closed there
A woman who has committed a crime
As for what crime she committed,
Why are you locked up there
How long will it be locked up again
No one knows
I'm curious
How can anyone be behind bars
Still so nosy
So I disguised myself as a beggar
Want to see what she really is
What kind of person is it
Steamed buns just coming out of the pot
Steaming steamed buns
Gadgets, gadgets, gadgets
Sachet sachet
Sugar-coated haws
When I found out that the world
There are times when such a fool really exists
I think
No matter what crime she committed,
I'll set her free
Did you see her last
No
The meal is getting cold
Let's eat first
Lord Mei
Please
Your Highness invites ministers to get together
I thought it was a joke
I didn't expect your highness to be so meticulous
Prepared meals
They are all my favorite foods
That minister is disrespectful
Your Highness
It is the food bureau that has the heart
Back to your highness's words
Your Highness ordered a banquet for Mei Yushi
Shang Food Bureau naturally does not dare to neglect
Mr. Shui Xin has a poem
Don't wait for the forest frost to ripen
When steamed, it will be made into Dongting fragrance
This is Dongting, isn't it
Lord Mei
This is made of chopped lotus
And orange leaves
With rice noodles and honey
Finally, wrap it in orange leaves
Steamed pastry
Sure enough, there is seed
The lingering fragrance of oranges
When I was a teenager, I read a section on pebble soup
A moment of curiosity
Have also taken
Cooking stones in clear springs
The so-called spring stone gas in the book
I don't realize it
It took a lot of firewood
Lord Mei is really good at joking
The reader is so arty
Isn't it ridiculous
Lord Mei
Su Yijian was drunk on a snowy night in Song Dynasty
Wake up thirsty in the middle of the night
See a pickle jar buried in the snow
Take it and drink it
I thought it was rare in the world
The sour soup
How can you compare dragon liver and phoenix gallbladder
But I answered that sentence
Food has no fixed taste
Palatable people are just precious
The ancients ate jade and drank dew
It must be the same reason
This room is stuffy and panicked
Let's go outside for a walk
Yes
What are you doing
Take it outside
Recipe canon meal
Take it out
Slow down, slow down
What is this dish
This
This is a young pigeon
This yellow fish meat
Can imitate the taste of crab meat
You have to talk to me about it
Your Highness
Have a cup of hot tea
Warm the stomach
Lord Mei
Don't keep your highness waiting for a long time
How
Your Highness is angry
It's all my fault
It's too speculative to chat with Yao Dianshan
That's right
I heard that Yao Dianshan is proficient in medicated diet
I happen to have something to ask for advice
Master Mei speaks heavily
I have something to say.
I
Your Highness
Your Highness has been unwell in recent days
How can you sit in the tuyere
Your Highness
Let's move in
Yao canon meal
In this world
There can be a diet for treating heart diseases
I think your highness is very ill
Lord Mei
Your Highness has a heart disease
It occurred to me that there was another urgent matter
Please accuse your highness for me
I'll go first
Lord Mei
This painting hasn't been finished yet
Come back tomorrow
What are you doing
Move in
Recipe canon meal
Stay step
Lord Mei
Please stay
You slow down
Don't run away
Grab her
What are you doing
Give it to her
Yao Dianshan said you were in the palace
I've been
Take this purse with you
This is what the restaurant should pay you
You were young at that time
I'm afraid you will spend it indiscriminately
Drop to theft again
I've been saving it for you
Now it is returned to its original owner
I'm leaving
Your Highness, please eat
You play the piano for me
Your Highness
Handmaiden's Hand
I can't play the piano now
Then I'll play the piano and you'll listen
Handmaiden dare not
Your Highness has not recovered from his injuries
How dare you overwork yourself
Yeah
I forgot
He is also good at the piano
When you want to listen to the piano,
Naturally, someone will caress you
Send her out
Yes
Chen
Father-in-law Chen
What did your highness mean just now
Yao canon meal
I don't want to criticize innocent you
Willing to keep one's mouth shut
So don't ask
How does your highness treat you
It's not that you don't know
How can you have the heart to break his heart
I break your highness's heart
What did I do
I have been with your highness since I was a child
Your Highness will always be
A high-spirited appearance
Never met him
So disheartened
You
You have gone too far
I go too far
Just
This shouldn't be what I said
You'd better help yourself
Your Highness commanded
Let me take you home myself
Please
Father-in-law Chen
What the hell did I do
Please
Sheng Tai Yi
Please, please
Yes
What does this mean
At the end of the day
Dr. Sheng will heal you
Until your hand is healed
Your Highness's orders have been brought to me
I'll take my leave first
How
Guilt
Why do you feel guilty
This lad is rude
But words collide with me
I would have held my heart to the bright moon
Who knows the bright moon shines on the ditch
You
This word is used here
But it's absolutely inappropriate
Look
Give it to me
I don't know how to draw
But this painting is so carefully drawn
It can be seen that the other party is deeply affectionate
Who won't be moved by this
I'm not moved
You have a heart of stone
If this were me
I'll leave some rubies behind
Emerald
Emerald opal
Won't stay
What kind of broken painting is this
Then what is this
Yin Ziping
This purse
But it's for men
To whom does this belong
Son, give it back to me
You tell me
You give it back to me first
Who is this man
You tell me to give it back to you
You give it back to me first
I'll tell you again
You give it back to me
To whom does this belong
Zi Jin
You give it back to me
Give it back to you
Whose
You give it back to me first
All right, all right, all right
Here you are
Light point
My hand
Inverse
Your Highness has not recovered from his injuries
How can Your Majesty let you now
Leave for Nanjing
Royal Guards have found out
The middleman who made contact with the assassin
When they arrived,
People have committed suicide
But the identity of that man
Very unusual
Do you remember
When I was eight years old
Grandpa Huang himself
Recruiting government troops from the people, avant-garde young troops
Follow me to practice martial arts and train soldiers
He used to be a soldier in the young army
This is clearly a structure
How can Your Majesty believe
What about this nonsense
This man not only alienates our father and son
And tried to transfer me out of Beijing
His heart can be punished
Please take your highness to dinner
He is a man of integrity
Strong character
However, those who are rigid are easy to fold
Get involved in officialdom too early
Is not necessarily a good thing
I'll find a way
Let him out
Exercise for a few years
Treat him with full wings
Someday
It must be the pillar of the country
He cares about the world and his home country
Often lenient with others
Be strict with oneself
Especially when it comes to family
The constraints will be too strict
I'm afraid you won't get used to it
That's right
I forgot
You're so nice
How could he say you
Your Highness
What exactly do you mean
Aren't you leaving the palace
Your Highness wants to release me from the palace
But the Empress
I have my own way
Have nothing to do with others
Your Highness didn't deceive me
But why
I haven't seen you for a long time
Laugh so happily
At least he can make you laugh
Waiting for your husband to sing along with your wife in the future
And harmonious
Don't know
Will you still remember this study
Will you remember me
His Highness said he was
Who the hell is it
Let's go
Or I'll go back on my word
Your Highness promised me to leave the palace and marry
But no matter how good that person is,
But not my sweetheart
Who is your sweetheart
It's nobody
Your Highness
This steamed chicken made by Guiqi
It is made of Angelica sinensis
And chicken stewed with roasted Astragalus membranaceus
People with loss of qi and blood after illness
Use the best
I know you have a bad appetite recently
You can use some
It is of great benefit to your injury
And said you didn't care about me
Your Highness misunderstood
It's a prescription prescribed by Dr. Sheng Tai
We're just
It's just cooking according to the prescription
Your Highness
Dr. Sheng knows
Your injury has been delayed
Diet is the best way to dispense medicine
Therefore, I ordered people to send medicated diet today
Where is this Shengyin
What an old fool
Clearly told you to prepare meals
And asked someone to send it again
Handmaiden retires
Ali
You guys stand down
It's your highness
You don't want to say
I won't force you
Anyway
I don't have a few days to bother you either
I will go to Nanjing soon
Your Highness
Your injury is not healed
Don't overwork yourself
This is my father's order
This is the prince's fault
It is obviously my father who suspects me
Why is it my fault
Your Highness wants father and son to make up
You should let go of the estrangement
Sincerely to the emperor
Show your heart
You think I haven't tried
But every time
My father put me
Keep it away thousands of miles away
Maybe
Is that your highness used the wrong method
Well done
Recipe canon meal
Can I do it today
Go to the meal with you
When was the food bureau so unruly
A small palm meal
I also want to enter Ganqing Palace
Don't step down yet
Sosur meal
Meng Shangshi is slightly dyed with wind and cold today
You can't go to Ganqing Palace to deliver food
I just want to help Fang Dianshan
It's time to deliver food
Your Majesty
This snack
Originated from Lin'an City in Southern Song Dynasty
It is made of cheese and sucrose
Oysters are often called abalone
So this oyster-shaped snack
It is called abalone snail
This porridge is good
Handmaiden is a fire room
Cultivated chamomile seedlings cook porridge
The taste is refreshing and appetizing
Of course I know
This is the taste of hometown
Nanjing calls this chrysanthemum brain
Eat as soup
You recently
This benefit is really not small
Last time it was handmaiden recklessness
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
Father
Your Highness, be careful
It was all an unintentional loss
I won't blame you
Avoid
Your Majesty forgives the handmaiden
Handmaiden Thanksgiving
Handmaiden is listening to the Imperial Doctor
Since the banquet in Shangyuan,
Your Majesty was frightened
Be dizzy all the time
This reminds me of chamomile seedlings
Can treat vertigo and headache
This is the courage to try
Scared, huh
The handmaiden is really frightened
Hiding in the corner all the time
Trembling
Later I saw
The Imperial Concubine Empress is also next to her
This is a relief
Save the driver quickly
Rescue driver
Protect the Emperor
Your Majesty
Guo Guifei asked for an audience
Be absent
Yes
I'm going to the school yard this afternoon
Send dinner there
Yes
Father
Aren't you leaving for Nanjing
Why haven't you started yet
My son prepared a meal
Let's have dinner together
No need