[English subtitles are available]
Here.
Let me show you how to use a tablet PC.
Try it.
Free at kisskh.me
You are using it quite well.
There's no need for me to teach you.
Grand Tutor, you are a genius.
Apparently, you still have Mu Tingzhou's memory.
What do you say about this?
As a Number One Scholar,
it's my basic qualities
to learn by myself.
You don't need to admire or praise it like this.
Compared with Mu Tingzhou,
you are even more confident.
What do you mean by this?
[2333 Lmao]
Secret code.
Secret code?
Interesting.
Why does this chair have wheels?
Because
it's easy to move.
Why do I need to move
sitting in front of the desk?
Um...
Here.
Let me introduce a good girl to you.
Her name is
[Baidu]
Baidu.
With her,
you can solve all your questions
anywhere at any time.
Anywhere at any time?
Where does she work?
She doesn't need a rest or a bath?
You don't have to worry about this.
Ask her. Ask her.
The scholars here
are so fickle.
[Be My Princess]
[Episode 7]
How about this.
I will ask Tingzhou's nanny, Auntie Zhao,
to take care of Her Highness's living.
What do you think?
No need.
As far as I can see,
it is for the best that I take care of Her Highness myself.
Mr. Mu, thanks for your kind gesture.
But please don't bother.
I'm fine on my own.
Her Highness is royal,
and she's female while you are male,
so I think that
it is more proper that
Auntie Zhao takes care of Her Highness.
Your Highness.
I know that
just like me,
you were poisoned by the wicked
and forgot all about the past.
In your eyes,
I'm Mu Tingzhou,
but my true identity
is Mu Yun.
Grand Tutor Mu.
OK, I know.
Thank you.
Grand Tutor.
Grand...Tutor?
Your Highness just called me Grand Tutor.
I suddenly felt that
so many feelings are welling up in my heart.
I know that
I will no longer be lonely
in this different world.
The two rooms we just passed,
one of them is mine,
and Xu Lin occasionally comes to live in the other one.
Who is Xu Lin?
You won't recall it anyway,
so let's talk about this later.
This whole floor is yours.
This is your bedroom.
This is the study.
Over there is the bathroom,
which has a whole set of sanitary equipment.
And deeper inside
is your gym.
What is a gym?
A gym is where you exercise
your muscles to build your body.
So it is a Martial Arts practice range.
It also makes sense
if you think this way.
Mr. and Mrs. Mu.
He...he...
-How does he feel? -Is he all right?
Still trying to adapt.
I can feel that
when his father and I
come near him,
he becomes very alert,
and more intense in his nerves.
This will make his illness even worse.
So
I can only have you take it over from here.
Xiao Zhao.
If anything happens,
call us any time.
OK.
Mr. and Mrs. Mu,
please feel assured.
After all, this is the place that Tingzhou is most familiar with.
Maybe several days later,
he will retrieve his memories.
[To replace RM-2 "Little Hound"...]
[R]
[RM-2]
Grand Tutor.
it's too late. You should go to sleep.
This is Master Jingling's old mine Duan inkstone.
It is a piece of art.
Invaluable.
How could you use it to grind ink?
If the inkstone is not for ink-grinding,
is it supposed to be used as paperweight?
Um...
This is ancient Yu Mi ink from the Qianlong era of the Qing Dynasty.
How could you unwrap and use it?
Do you know
how hard it was for you to get it from auction?
This is an antique,
not some ordinary ink sold on Taobao,
some buy-three-get-one-free ink or positive feedback reward.
Although the inkstone and ink are superior,
they are not that hard to get.
I have a Tianqing inkstone from the Tang Dynasty.
Later I will...
What later?
Show me what you have got later?
Let's talk about this later.
Whatever. You have already used it.
Grand Tutor, it is really late.
Don't you ancient people have the saying of
"work at sunrise and rest at sunset"?
That is true only for the villagers
who have nothing to do at night and are not willing to waste lamp-oil.
After I became an imperial official,
I have always worked very late, sometimes till 11 p.m. to 1 a.m.
If back then, we had these
convenient and long-lasting bright lamps,
it would have benefited so many scholars.
If you continue to look at the tablet PC
like this,
you will benefit the spectacles store.
Go to sleep soon.
Steward Xiao,
does Mu Tingzhou have a cell phone?
I want to say goodnight to Her Highness before sleep.
It broke due to the car accident.
But I have bought you a new one.
[Famous actor Mu Tingzhou was hospitalized due to a car accident, and was discharged from hospital this noon after recovery.]
Wei,
now you keep Mu Tingzhou company
in the identity of the princess.
Does this mean that
you have to stay with him from morning to night every day?
How many girls would die for that.
I just hope that
Mr. Mu can recover soon.
Xiao Zhao was right.
Even if my pretending to be the princess
cannot help retrieve Mr. Mu's memory,
but at least,
I can get him to cooperate with the treatment.
I can help him live.
During critical times,
it turns out Xiao Zhao can be counted on.
He is calm in the time of peril.
[Mu Tingzhou]
Mr. Mu...
Grand Tutor.
I, Mu Yun, greets Your Highness from afar.
Oh my god, such a big gesture.
Shh.
Go away.
I have said that
I'm not the princess.
I have also said for many times
that you are the princess of the Ning Dynasty.
It is quite late.
What do you call me for?
I want to know
how long has Your Highness been here?
I was born on October 18,
1998.
Native Chinese citizen.
My hometown is Su City.
I'm 23 years old.
Your Highness still look like 15,
not 23.
That is because 23-year-old me
played the role of 15-year-old princess.
Your Highness.
I'm very sad that
you can't retrieve your memory.
I just wish to find out
the wicked people that poisoned us
and press him for antidote.
And then I will lock him up in prison and interrogate him with heavy punishment.
Don't be so sad.
Grand Tutor.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Your Highness,
what do you do for a living here?
I used to be an interpreter.
I have just started acting lately.
The Grand Chief Cabinet Minister
is the first show I shot together with Mr. Mu.
I have something to do.
Excuse me, Your Highness.
Grand Tutor, you have finished your phone call?
What is it this time, Mu Tingzhou?
Why did you let Her Highness be a playactor?
Playactor?
I...
Talk.
In this era,
actors are respectable.
Ming Wei loves acting.
This is her personal choice.
There's nothing I can interfere with.
Others can do this, but not Her Highness.
Ordinary people must get on their knees when they see Her Highness,
how dare they see Her Highness casually?
Say it, how many shows has Her Highness been on?
Only one, the Grand Chief Cabinet Minister, with you.
It is undergoing post production,
and will be aired next year.
No airing.
Her Highness is royal and superior.
I won't allow you to treat her with levity.
I'm sorry but
here in this world,
you are not Grand Tutor.
You can't control anybody.
I must have owed you a lot in the previous life.
Ming Wei and you
both signed the shooting contract.
Even if you can persuade Ming Wei
to leave the acting industry,
the Grand Chief Cabinet Minister will still be aired as planned.
Besides, this is a serious drama.
It mainly shows what happened on the imperial court.
Ming Wei played the role of princess, and she was conservative in dressing.
Except for that scene with you and her...
Shut up.
Her Highness is as clean as ice and as pure as jade.
How dare you profane her?
Who is profaning her?
What are you doing?
Calm down.
It is my fault, OK?
Don't be rash.
I'm a criminal offending Her Highness.
I should kill myself as an apology.
You shot it through a protective film.
With a protective film.
Calm down.
Even if I didn't have intimate relations with Her Highness,
it was still great disrespect.
Her Highness can't shoot scenes like this in the future.
Then talk to her entertainment agent.
I will say it again.
We are friends,
so I can be understanding at all events.
But Ming Wei and Shen Su don't owe you anything.
I suggest you think it through before going,
or you may be rejected.
Even if I didn't have intimate relations with Her Highness,
it was still great disrespect.
Her Highness can't shoot scenes like this in the future.
A play
needs to be dramatic.
The plots of our relationship
have been emphasized by the scriptwriter.
Grand Tutor. Grand Tutor.
Grand Tutor.
Why didn't you answer me?
Any order, Your Highness?
Yesterday, Pingxi Royal Highness went to see the Empress Dowager
and asked to marry me.
Do you know that?
Congratulations, Your Highness.
His Royal Highness is not only royal and superior,
his talents are also outstanding.
Shut up.
He's going to make a perfect couple
with Your Highness.
Shut up, didn't you hear me?
So
you don't care at all, right?
I don't know what you mean, Your Highness.
You don't care at all
that I'm going to marry His Royal Highness.
If I marry him,
one obstacle will be eliminated for you,
so that you can marry that invalid
without any difficulty, right?
Looking at all the royal princes on the imperial court,
there's no one who can compete with His Royal Highness Xu in quality and appearance.
I personally think that
this is really a good match.
Please consider it carefully, Your Highness.
Don't reject easily.
OK.
It's good for you.
If there's no other order, Your Highness,
I will leave you be.
I hate you.
I will hate you for the rest of my life.
I won't forgive you, ever.
Do you hear me?
I hate you.
Why does this scene feel so real?
[Agent Penalty]
Who is this?
She said she is Auntie Zhao.
Pretty girls,
please come have breakfast.
Hello, Auntie Zhao.
Hi.
Come here.
Auntie Zhao, we...
There are only two of us.
This is too much for breakfast.
We can't finish it.
Why don't we eat it together?
I have already had my breakfast.
I didn't know what you like
so I prepared
all of them.
Come over.
Come and have a seat. Enjoy your breakfast.
Come.
Have a seat.
Come here.
Just sit.
Auntie Zhao.
Sorry to bother you.
I appreciate it very much.
You are welcome.
You are so beautiful, nice,
and kind.
Mr. Mu is so lucky
to be with you.
It's not what you think, Auntie Zhao.
Mr. Mu is a senior colleague to me.
We have acted in the same show before.
Well, I am speaking from personal experience.
I have been working at his place for years,
I know what this is about.
Well, I...
It's okay. Enjoy your breakfast.
Sure, thanks.
Just eat your food.
There's too much food.
Mom never cooked this much for us.
Mom cooks?
How come I didn't know about that?
Well, I had better drink this coffee.
See how beautiful the sunshine is today!
I'll take your quilts out
to air them.
Well, Auntie Zhao,
let us do it.
Don't bother.
See, I woke up early to prepare the breakfast
for you to have more.
Enjoy it before it gets cold.
Don't make me sad.
Make yourself at home.
Thanks, Auntie Zhao.
Go.
Grand Tutor.
I... I...
What's the matter?
Auntie Zhao came back.
Don't you have something to ask her?
Mr. Mu.
Madam Zhao.
You went to her place.
Was Her Highness satisfied with it?
Of course.
I did what you said,
starting from the most difficult chores.
The two girls were quite satisfied with everything
this whole morning.
Thank you, Madam Zhao.
Grand Tutor.
Don't forget that
it's a time when people are all equal.
No one is born to do chores.
It's okay.
I'm really happy that
he has learnt to dote on others.
Sir,
that lady not only has a good look
but also has a good temper and good manners.
You have good taste, Sir.
I'm Grand Tutor, Mu Yun,
not that Sir.
Yes, Grand Tutor.
Steward Xiao,
come upstairs later.
Don't take it to heart, Auntie Zhao.
Tingzhou is ill.
He even doesn't recognize his parents and me.
But he must have not meant that.
I've been working for him for years.
I know him well.
You say he has a mental issue.
In my view,
he just takes it too far in the character.
At the end of the day,
he just has a crush on that Princess.
Others see him as a Prince Charming,
but his life is plain and boring.
No love or desires.
What's the point of it?
Now he has a crush on someone,
I'm more than happy to see that!
Let's wait and see how he gets his Princess.
OK.
Auntie Zhao, you really are experienced.
An old ox makes a straight furrow.
Grand Tutor, you asked to see me.
I watched some of your shows last night.
Many of them are immoral.
I want to know
if all of the shows here
are such
an eyesore.
You learn it quickly.
Now you even know the word "eyesore“.
Her Highness is royalty.
I won't let any man take advantage of her
with the excuse of acting.
But you were the first one who took advantage of her, weren't you?
Well, not all the shows
have intimate scenes.
For example, you...
No,
Mu Tingzhou
never took parts in this kind of shows before.
So it's the actor and the agent
who need to reach an agreement.
In that way, the agent will check the script
before accepting the show.
However, Ming Wei is a novice in this industry.
It's not good for her to be so picky on the shows.
In your words,
as long as I become the agent of Her Highness,
I could protect her.
Last night,
I carried out thorough research on how to be an entertainment agent.
I have made up my mind,
from now on,
I'll be the agent for Her Highness.
I told you
she has already got an agent,
Shen Su,
a top agent from a top agent firm.
They have signed the agent contract.
Compensation is needed if anyone breaches the contract.
How much is the compensation?
No matter how much it is,
I'll pay for Her Highness.
You?
No, Grand Tutor.
Are you sure you brought money with you
when you time traveled
from the Ning Dynasty?
Since you said that
actors have a high social status in this world
and earn much,
it will not be a big deal
to pay the compensation.
So you are thinking about
using Mu Tingzhou's money
to pay for Grand Tutor?
Grand Tutor, when you were saying that,
didn't you feel guilty?
It's you who keeps emphasizing that
Mu Tingzhou and I are actually the same person.
Given that,
why can't I spend his money?
Alright, fine.
No. Grand Tutor.
Being an entertainment agent
is not something you can do well
just by staying up and surfing the internet.
Taking me as an example,
not only do I have to take care of your clothing, food, housing and transportation,
I also need to help you with contract negotiation
and script selection.
I meet the people you don't want to see.
I do the things you don't care to do.
If you fall sick,
I take all the responsibilities without complaint
and help you deal with all the trouble.
In the end, you may not even appreciate it at all.
See?
This is the life of an entertainment agent.
Do you want the Princess to hate you,
and get the opposite of what you really want?
However,
I do have an idea to help you do this in another way.
What do you want to exchange?
Tell me.
As long as I can protect Her Highness by her side
I will agree to whatever you say.
What?
Mr. Mu wants to be my personal assistant?
Ming Wei,
don't feel pressured.
It seems like Tingzhou is hired by you,
but actually in this way
it is good for his treatment,
so you don't have to pay him salary.
Instead, the Mus will give you a bunch of money
to show their appreciation.
No. No. No.
I don't need compensation.
It has nothing to do with money.
Please don't get mad at me,
I feel like your requests
is way too much.
Putting others aside,
if people see,
Mu Tingzhou, the Best Actor,
keeping a close relationship
with the new actress
and even serving her,
it will make a huge negative impact on Ming Wei.
I'm sure you understand.
Sure.
We have considered it.
So once I get your approval,
Tingzhou's parents and I
will hold a press conference
to make Tingzhou's illness
known to the public.
What do you think of it?
But
I feel that
Mr. Mu won't agree to
these requests.
Although he is the Grand Tutor now,
but when he regains his memory,
he will be angry.
Anyway, it's what the Grand Tutor wants to do,
not Mr. Mu.
Although Tingzhou is a stubborn person,
he can tell right from wrong.
We could put this
into the contract,
to try to minimize
the negative impact on you.
We will protect you
in legal and moral ways.
If you don't mind,
I could be your associate assistant
so I could provide professional services
and look after Tingzhou at the same time
to make sure you can work and live normally.
Your Highness.
Save your formality from now on.
It's not good to be seen by others.
Yes.
Let's get in the car.
Alright.
Your Highness, please.
Thanks.
Your Highness, this way please.
Thank you.
Your Highness, have some water.
Your Highness, please don't stand on ceremony.
Your Highness, let me get that for you.
Your Highness, the seat may be uncomfortable.
You can put this pillow around your waist.
Thank you.
That works too.
Steward Xiao,
drive slower.
Grand Tutor,
I appreciate what you've done for me.
But why are you doing this?
It's difficult being an artiste's assistant.
You have to get water for me when I'm thirsty,
and bring food to me when I'm hungry.
Sometimes when I'm in a bad mood,
I might even take it out on you.
This is my duty,
I do not want others to do it for me.
But
if you do this,
I will be spoiled.
Your Highness is precious,
you should be loved by the world.
So what if you are spoiled?
Is he flirting with me?
About that...
Grand Tutor.
Didn't you agree to see a psychologist?
Do you know what counseling is?
I looked it up on the internet.
I know the general idea of it.
I understand that
everyone thinks
I am Mu Tingzhou's illness.
Everyone wants to chase me out of
Mu Tingzhou's body.
Eliminating me is the objective
of this doctor.
Grand Tutor,
you won't be eliminated.
You will simply regain Mu Tingzhou's memories.
No matter whether you want to eliminate me or
ask me to die instantly,
so long as it's Your Highness' wishes,
I will abide by them
with no complaints and no regrets.
Your Highness.
Have some tea.
Grand Tutor.
Today,
we will have a simple chat
to understand each other.
There's no need to be tense.
I understand.
Alright.
Then could you first
talk about yourself？
I am especially interested
in your work.
Doctor Li.
Although you call me Grand Tutor,
I know that in your heart
you still think I'm Mu Tingzhou.
If that's the case,
why bother
to understand a fictional character?
I will never deny
or try to change
subjective truths experienced by my patients.
I just want to know
why they think that.
Even if everyone
thinks you are Mu Tingzhou
but
you insist that you are the Grand Tutor,
what I'm concerned about is the
reasons behind this.
Doctor Li doesn't beat around the bush.
That's good.
In that case,
let's talk about Mu Tingzhou.
Grand Tutor, why do you want to talk about Mu Tingzhou?
I have always been curious about
why a playactor would forget who he was
due to a show.
In my world,
this is unheard of.
I want to listen to Doctor Li's opinion.
Mu Tingzhou
is a very sensitive actor.
For every role that he acted,
he absolutely believed that
he was the character.
So,
when he successfully creates the character,
he probably also destroys himself.
If so,
is there any method
to get out of character?
Usually
what works best
is to find an
anchor in real life.
Daniel Day-Lewis,
an actor who has received three Oscars,
would return home
and engage in his favorite carpentry
after every role.
That was his anchor.
But Mu Tingzhou
doesn't have an anchor.
Besides acting,
he doesn't have his own life.
That sounds rather admirable.
He must love this profession dearly.
And that is the crux of his illness.
Acting is his whole life.
Besides that, he has nothing.
He gave his life
to this profession.
So, it's very difficult for him to get out of any character.
I only found out today
how much Mr. Mu sacrificed
to act.
I really admire him
but also feel bad for him.
Your Highness, there is no need to feel bad for him.
Everyone chooses their own path.
They ought to persevere on that path.
That is his duty.
It is certainly important to
take our careers seriously.
But
if a person only has is career
and gives up his happiness for that,
isn't it very pitiable?
If Your Highness feels so bad for Mu Tingzhou,
then all the more you should not anticipate his return.
Why?
In my opinion,
Mu Tingzhou is probably tired of his life.
He is tired of experiencing sorrow and happiness
in other people's stories.
He's tired and needs rest,
that's why he has fallen asleep for so long.
Thanks to that, I could wake up in this odd world.
If this is true,
even if Doctor Li really gets him back,
he would be unhappy.
Your Highness.
Please.
Wei.
Speak the truth.
In the beginning,
when you went to take care of the Best Actor,
I thought it was pretty fun to be able to be close to a big star.
But the situation now
is that once the press conference is held tomorrow
you will be famous in the entertainment industry.
Can you deal with that?
The Best Actor's Princess.
Once you have this identity,
you will be living
in the public eye.
What are you going to do?
Since I have already decided to help Mr. Mu,
I have prepared mentally.
Actually
I'm more worried
that you, mom and dad
will be pulled into this
once I attract media attention.
I'm also worried about mom and dad.
So it's best that you
explain this to them first.
I don't know whether this is right either.
You are my elder sister.
We are a family.
Everything that you do is right,
at least according to me.
Don't give yourself so much pressure, alright?
Let me give you a hug.
Don't worry.
I didn't expect Xiaoya to be so generous.
I just asked around.
One skirt costs thousands.
Of course.
She's a rich wife now.
If we, her companions,
are dressed shabbily,
it would reflect badly on her.
That's true.
This dress is rather pretty.
That's right.
Come, let's take a picture.
Alright.
We haven't taken one in ages.
Come.
Four cute shots as per usual.
[Encyclopedia of the Universe Encyclopedia of the Earth]
Steward Xiao.
Didn't you say that a press conference
is quite an important event?
Why aren't you prepared?
We won't be able to make it.
The press conference is tomorrow, not today.
Why is it tomorrow?
Because the Princess needs to go to Hongyuan Hotel today
to be a bridesmaid for her friend.
Didn't she tell you yesterday?
What is a bridesmaid?
Why does it sound like
a dowry maid?
Aren't you an expert on the internet now?
Ask Baidu.
[Bridesmaid]
Offensive and
unsightly.
[Picture of bridesmaid]
[The bridesmaid is really pretty, I'm falling for her.]