the future.
A dark desolate world.
A world in war, suffering loss ..
.. On both sides.
Mutants and the humans who dare to help them
fighting an enemy we cannot defeat.
Are we destined on this path?
Destined to destroy ourselves
like so many species before us?
Or can we evolve fast
enough to change ourselves?
Change our fate?
Is the future truly set?
They here!
Time's-up!
Sentinel!
Sunspot.
Let's go!
Blink!
No!
It's too late
assholes!
Come here!
Get your hands up!!
- Get down!!
- No!!!
No!!!
So few of us left.
Professor.
I found them.
- Bobby.
- Hey, Storm.
Hey kid.
Professor.
You made it.
Whenever the sentinels attack
Warpath spots them.
And I sent Bishop back to
warn us of the attack...
Before it happens.
Blink scouts the next side and..
.. Well then we leave before
they ever know we were there.
Because we never were.
What do you mean you were never there?
She projects Bishop back
in time a few days...
To warn the others of the coming attack.
She sends bishop back in time?
No just his consciousness
into his younger self
his younger body.
Wow!
This might just work Charles.
What might work?
The sentinel program was originally
conceived by Dr. Bolivar Trask.
In the early 70s he was one of the
world's leading weapons designers.
But covertly he had began
experimenting on mutants.
Using their gifts to fuel his own research.
There was one mutant who had
discovered what he was doing.
Mutant with ability to
transform herself to anyone.
Mystique.
I knew her as Raven.
We met when we were children
grew up together.
She was like a sister to me.
I tried to help her.
But only succeeded in driving her away.
She hunted Trask across the world.
And at the Paris peace accords in 1973
after the Vietnam war.
She found Trask
and killed him.
It was the first time she killed.
Was no last.
But killing Trask did not have
the outcome she expected.
It only persuaded the government
of the need for his program.
They captured her that day.
Tortured her
Experimented on her.
In her DNA they discovered the secret
to her powers of transformation
it gave them the key they needed
to create weapons that could
adapt to any mutant power.
And in less than 50 years
the machines that have destroyed so
many of our kind were created.
But it all started that day in 1973
the day she first killed
the day she truly became Mystique.
Do you wanna go back there?
If I can get to her
stop the assassination
keep her out of their hands
Then we can stop the sentinels
from ever being born.
And end this war
before it ever begins.
I can send someone back a couple of weeks.
Maybe a month but you're talking
about going back decades.
You have the most powerful
brain in the world professor.
But the mind can only stretch
so far before it snaps.
It would rip you apart. I'm sorry.
No one can survive that trip.
What if someone's mind has a
way of snaping back?
What if someone can heal as
fast as they're ripped apart?
Okay spread out.
Take you position.
So I wake up in my younger
body god knows where, then what?
You need to go to my house and find me
convince me of all of this.
Wouldn't you just be able to read my mind?
I didn't have my powers in 1973.
Logan you're going to have to do for
me what I once did for you
lead me guide me.
I was a very different man then.
You'll have to be patient with me.
Patience is my strongest suit.
You'll need me as well.
What?
After Mystique left Charles
she came with me
and I set her on a dangerous path.
Darker path.
It's going to take the
two of us side by side
at a time when we couldn't
be further apart.
Great.
So where do I find you?
Well..It's complicated.
Basically your body will go to sleep
while your mind travels back in time.
As long as you back there past and present
will continue to co-exist.
But once you wake up....
.. Whatever you've done will
take hold and become history.
And for the rest of us that will
be the only history that we know.
That will be like
last 50 years never happened.
This world
this war.
The only person who'll remember it
...is you.
Alright Logan I need you to clear your
head and to stay as calm as possible.
What do you mean?
If your mind gets rocky
it will harder for me to hold you.
You could start to slip
between past and future.
What if I need to get a little rocky ?
Think peaceful thoughts.
Peaceful thoughts.
Do you have any good news?
Well
you don't really age so you'll
pretty much look the same.
You won't have much time in past.
Sentinels will find us
they always do.
And this time we won't
be able to run. We'll have no escape.
This is our last chance.
You really think this will work?
I have faith in him.
It's not him I'm worried about. It's us.
We were young.
We didn't know any better.
We will now.
See you all soon.
This might sting a little.
Holy shit!!
It worked.
Hey what's going on?
- Gwen! Get dressed!
- Who are you?
Hey I don't know what's going on here.
What's going on is you supposed to guard
your boss's daughter not screwing her.
I didn't sleep with her.
- No?
- No.
I mean yes
I slept with her many times but...
Jimmy!
That wasn't me. That was the old me.
- I just got here like 20 seconds ago.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What happen to your clothes?
My wha...
Oh
Will you believe me if I told you
I was sent here from the future?
- Get out of here sweetheart.
- Yeah
we're gonna take care of this comedian.
No, you're not.
You gonna give me the keys to
your car and some money for gas
or you gonna wake up in a hospital.
Trust me I know how these things play out.
- Oh, because you're from the future?
- No
...because of these.
What the hell!!
Ahhh...Damn it.
Peaceful thoughts.
We are reviewing all of
our defense expenditures
and all the black books are being opened.
We can't support a weapon that
targets our own citizens
if these mutants as you described
are already living among us
then they are living here peacefully.
We haven't had an
incident in over 10 years.
After what happened in Cuba?
That was never confirmed.
We have very real enemies out there.
The Russians
the Chinese.
We are talking about a tenth of a
tenth of a tenth of our population.
- Allow me to read something to you.
- Please.
This was acquired by our
friends at the CIA.
It's in a dissertation
written by a mutant
at Oxford university.
And I quote.
To Homo neanderthalensis his
mutant cousin of homo sapiens
which is us.
Was an aberration
the arrival of mutated human
species: Homo sapiens.
Was followed by the immediate extinction
of the their less evolve kin.
Well
now..
We are the neanderthals.
Speak for yourself
Dr. Trask.
You know when you sent
our soldiers to Vietnam
without the weapons they
needed to win the war
you underestimated your enemy.
You heh, you do that with this enemy.
it won't be some border skirmish
halfway around the world.
This time the war will be for our
streets, our cities, our homes.
And by the time you see
the need for my program
it will be too late.
And you will have lost two
wars in one life time.
We're sorry
Dr. Trask.
But your sentinel program
it ain't gonna fly.
Can I help you colonel?
Just here to give my
boys a proper send off.
Sorry sir. But we have orders.
This is a quarantined area.
Stand aside soldier.
That's an order.
Attenhut.
At ease.
What is all this?
Lab reports blood tests. It's all
getting packed up and shipped back.
Where is it going?
Same place they are.
Trask industries.
Let's go gentleman
taking you out of this shit show.
Shipping home?
Not just yet.
What are you doing with those?
It's only gonna make the ride a little smoother.
We are transferring you to a
private facility where we can..
Run a few more tests.
Your men are not military.
Private outfit.
We're authorized to command these men.
These troops are going home.
Well colonel...
I don't believe you have the
jurisdiction in this matter.
I'm afraid I do son.
I'm sorry who are you?
The question is major.
Who are you?
Raven.
That's not my name.
- I had that.
- I know.
Let's move out.
Come on let's go.
Where's Erik?
I'm on my own now.
Let's go. Move it.
Hold that plane!
Keep going
I wouldn't wanna leave these boys
to this godforsaken country
Yes sir.
You're not coming with us are you?
My war is not over.
The enemy is still out there.
Where did they go?
The 4 privates where did they go?
They were headed towards the Tarmac.
Can I help you?
Ahh yeah what happened to the school?
School has been shut for years.
Are you a parent?
Sure as hell hope not.
- Who are you?
- I'm Hank.
Hank Maccoy I look
after the house now.
You are beast?
Look at you
guess you are a late bloomer.
I do not know what you're talking about.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
- Where is the professor?
- There is no professor here.
You're pretty strong for a scrawny kid.
Sure there is no little beast thing in here?
- Come on beast.
- Beast is not here.
- Come on beasty.
- Go!
Hey!!
I said the school is closed.
You need to leave.
Not until I see the professor.
There is no professor here.
I told you that.
Look kid.
You and I are gonna be good friends.
You just don't know it yet.
Professor!
Ahhh.....
Hank what's going on here?
- Professor.
- Please don't call me that.
Why, you know this guy?
Yeah he looks slightly familiar
get off the bloody chandelier Hank.
You can walk.
You're a perceptive one.
I thought Erik ..
Which makes it slightly perplaxing that you
managed to miss our sign on the way in
this is private property my friend
I'm gonna have to ask him to ask you to leave.
Well I'm afraid I can't do that because...
..Because I was sent here for you
well tell whoever it was
that sent you that I'm busy.
This gonna be a little tricky
because the person who sent me..
Was you.
- What?
- About 50 years from now.
50 years from now like in the
future 50 years from now.
Yeah.
- I sent you from the future.
- Yeah.
Piss off.
If you had your powers
you know I was telling the truth.
How do you know I don't have my.....
- Who are you?
- I told you.
- Are you CIA?
- No.
You were watching me.
I know you Charles.
We've been friends for years.
I know your powers came when you were 9.
I know you thought you
were going crazy when
it started all the
voices in your head.
And it wasn't until you
were 12 that you realized
all the voices were in
everyone else's head.
Do you want me to go on?
I never told anyone that.
Not yet no but you will.
Alright you've picked my interest
what do you want?
We have to stop Raven.
I need your help.
We need your help.
Think I'd like to wake up now.
What does she have to do with this?
So you're saying that they
took Raven's power and what?
They weaponized it?
Yep
she is unique.
Yes she is.
In the beginning the sentinels
were just targeting mutants.
Then they began to identify
the genetics in non-mutants.
Who would eventually have mutant
children or grandchildren.
Many of the humans tried to help us,
it was a slaughter.
leaving only the worst
of humanity in charge
I've been in a lot of worse.
I've never seen anything like this.
And it all starts with her.
Let's just say that for the sake of
The sake that I choose to believe you
that I choose to help you.
Raven won't listen to me.
No her heart and soul belongs
to someone else now.
I know.
That's why we gonna need Magneto too.
Erik?
You do know where he is?
Yeah.
He's where he belongs.
That's it
you're just gonna walk out?
Oh top marks like I said
you are perceptive.
The professor I know would
never turn his back
..on someone who lost their path
especially someone he loved.
You know..
I think I do remember you now.
Yeah we came to you a long
time ago seeking your help.
And I'm gonna say to you
what you said to us then
fuck off!
Listen to me you little shit
I've come a long way
and I watched a lot of people die
good people, friends.
If you're gonna wallow in
self pity and do nothing
then you're gonna watch the same thing
you understand?
We all have to die some time.
I told you there was
no professor here.
What the hell happened to him?
He lost everything.
Erik, Raven, his legs.
We built the school, the labs,
this .. this whole place.
Then just after the first semester
the war in Vietnam got worse.
Many of the teachers and
all the students were drafted.
I mean it broke him.
He retreated into himself..
I wanted to help do something so..
So I designed a serum to
treat his spine
derived from the same formula that
helps me control my mutation.
I take just enough to
keep myself balanced but
he takes too much.
I tried easing him back but he
just couldn't bear the pain
the voices..
The treatment gives
him his legs but
it's not enough
he's..
He's just lost too much.
You're not scared of me?
I always believed I couldn't be
the only one in the world.
Charles Xavier.
Raven .
You're hungry and alone?
Take whatever you want.
We got lots of food
you don't have to steal. .
In fact you never have to steal again.
And that's a promise.
I'll help you get her.
Not for any of your
future shots but for her.
Fair enough.
I'll tell you this
you don't know Erik.
That man is a monster.
A murderer.
You think you can convince Raven to change?
To come home?
That's splendid.
But what makes you think
you can change him?
Because you and Erik
sent me back here together.
The room they're holding him
in was built during the
2nd world war when there
was a shortage of steel
so the foundation is pure
concrete and sand no metal.
He's being held a 100
floors beneath the most
heavily guarded building on the planet.
Why is he in there?
What he forgot to mention?
Ahhh JFK
He killed him?
What else would explain the bullet
miraculously curving through the air
Eric's always had a way with guns.
Are you sure you want
to carry on with this?
This is your plan
not mine.
We don't have any resources
to get us in or out
it's just me and Hank.
I know a guy.
Yeah he'd be a young man now
grew up outside of DC
he could get into anywhere
just don't know how the
hell we're gonna find him
history provided the question
we have a phone book
I thought you'd be getting
ready for your trip sir.
I just came to grab couple of files.
Is that a new scarf?
It's nice.
Thank you.
Dr. Trask.
One second.
We added some names to the Paris meeting
thank you.
Is something wrong sir?
No.
It's nothing.
Would you mind typing up my itinerary.
I don't wanna miss anything.
What's he done now?
I'll just write you a check
for whatever he took.
We just need talk to him.
Peter the cops are here..
.. Again.
Guess what I didn't do anything
I've been here all day.
Just relax Peter
we are not cops.
Of course, you're not cops if you were
cops you wouldn't drive a rental car
how'd you know we got a rental car?
I checked your registration when you
were walking through the door
I also had some time to
kill so I went through your
rental agreements saw you
were from out of town
are you FBI?
No, you're not cops
hey what's with this gifted youngsters place
that's an old card.
He is fascinating he
is a pain in the ass.
What teleporter?
No, he's just fast.
When I know him he wasn't so young.
Young?
You're just old.
So you're not afraid to show your powers?
Powers? What powers?
What are you talking about?
You see some strange here?
Nothing anybody would believe if you told them.
So who are you?
What do you want?
We need your help Peter.
With what?
Break into a highly secured facility
and get someone out.
Prison break?
That's illegal you know.
Well only if you get caught.
So what's in it for me?
You the kleptomaniac
get to break into the Pentagon.
How do I know I can trust you?
Because we are just like you.
Show him.
It's cool just disgusting
built in 1943 the Pentagon is the
world largest office building.
Housing more than 25,000 military employees
stretched over 6 million square feet.
Where is the bathroom?
I need to pee.
Well, lucky for you, you'll have plenty to choose from
The building was constructed during ...
Thank you.
Yeah we're getting broadcast signal down here?
What's going on?
Damn it!! Call maintenance
get them down here.
....from a Japanese empire.
This month long battle...
Included some of the fearsest
fighting during World War II
in 3 seconds those doors are going to open
and 20 guards will be here to shoot us.
I know that's what I'm waiting for
what are you doing?
I'm holding your neck so
you won't get whip-lash
what?
Whip.....Laaaaaash
You're good. It'll pass.
It happens when I run.
Must have done something pretty serious.
What did you do man?
What did you do.
What did you do?
Why would they have you in there.
For killing the president.
Anything I'm guilty of is fighting
for people like us
you take karate?
You know karate man?
I don't know karate.
but I know crazy.
Ladies and gentlemen boys and girls
this is a code red situation
we are evacuating the entire floor so
that we my uh associate and I can uh
- secure the prisoner.
- Who are you?
We are special operations
CB, FE, CIED look
perhaps you didn't hear
me what first I spoke
it's imperative that you understand
we're in complete lockdown situation.
We have to get in to the 3rd floor
Oh I'm sorry
were you finished?
They told me you controled metal.
They?
You know my mom once knew a
guy who could do that.
Sorry I'm just not very
good with violence.
Charles.
Good to see you too old friend.
- And walking?
- Not thanks to you.
You're the last person in the
world I expected to see today.
Believe me I wouldn't
be here if I didn't have to.
If we get you out of here we do it my way
no killing.
No helmet.
I couldn't disobey you even if I want to.
I'm never getting inside
of that head again.
I need your word Erik.
No body move!
Hold it right there!
Charles.
Don't move!
Hands up or we will shoot!
- Freeze them Charles.
- I can't.
Hands up!
No!
If I could save time in bottle....
The first thing that I like to do...
Is to save every day
'til eternity passes away...
Just to spend them with you....
If I could make days last forever...
If words could make wishes come true..
I'd save every day like
a treasure and then..
Again
I would spend them with you..
But there never seems to be enough time..
To do the things you want
to do once you find them..
I've looked around enough to know..
That you're the one I want
to go through time with..
Thanks kid.
Peter thank you very very much.
You take care.
Yeah I saw your flight plan in the cockpit
why are you going to Paris?
Imagine if they were metal.
- Do me a favor and return it for me.
- Okay.
Peter...
Take it slowly.
Where did they dig you up?
You're gonna find this hard to believe
but ahh..
You sent me.
You and Charles
from the future.
How did you lose them?
The treatment for my spine affects my DNA.
You sacrificed your powers
so you could walk?
I sacrificed my power so that I could Slee..
What do you know about it?
- I lost my fair share
- Hah
Dry your eyes Erik.
It doesn't justify what you've done.
You've no idea what I have done.
I know that you took the
things that mean most to me.
Well maybe you should have
fought harder for them.
If you want to fight Erik
I'll give you a fight
- Let him come.
- You abandoned me!
You took her away and you abandoned me!
Angel.
Azazel.
Emma.
Banshee.
Mutant brothers and sisters all dead!
Countless others
- ..experimented on, butchered.
- Erik.
Where were you Charles?
We were supposed to protect them!
Where were you when your own people needed you?
Hiding!
You and Hank pretending to be
something you're not
Erik.
You abandoned us all.
So you were always an asshole
I take it we're best buddies in the future
I spent a lot of years trying
to bring you down Bob
how's that work out for you?
You're like me.
You're a survivor.
You wanna pick all that shit up?
General, maybe you should go slowly,
we have a long day tomorrow.
We are celebrating,
captain.
It's not every day
that we win a war
Much less against
the damn Americans
I'll get another bottle.
- My apologies.
- I assure you it was my fault.
- Do you speak Vietnamese.
- I'm a performer.
I speak many languages.
Let me buy you another drink,
unless you are
accompanied.
I'm alone.
A bottle of Johnnie Walker,
Please.
You go to the Dome tomorrow?
A beautiful girl
interested in politics ...
Appearances can be deceiving.
Show me more baby
Clothes off.
What's the matter baby?
you don't think I look pretty like this
Fancy a game? It's been a while.
I'm not in a mood for games, thank you.
Haven't had a real sip in 10 years.
I didn't kill the president.
The bullet curved Erik.
Because I was trying to save him.
They took me out before I could.
- Why would you trying to save him?
- Because he was one of us.
You must think me so foolish.
You've always said they would come after us.
I never imagined they'd
use Raven's DNA to do it.
When did you last see her?
The day I left for Dallas.
And how was she?
Strong.
Driven
- loyal.
- How..
How was she?
She was..
We were..
I could see why she
meant so much to you.
You should be proud of her Charles.
She is out there fighting for our cause.
Your cause.
The girl I raised she was
not capable of killing.
You didn't raise her
you grew up with her.
She couldn't stay a little girl forever
that's why she left
she left because you got inside her head
that's not my power.
She made a choice.
But now we know where that choice leads
don't we?
She's going to murder Trask
they're going to capture her
and then they're going to wipe us out.
Not if we get to her first.
Not if we change history tomorrow.
I'm sorry Charles.
For what happened I truly am
It's been a while since I've played
I'll go easy on you.
Might finally be a fair fight.
You have the first move.
The diplomats from all around the
world arriving here today at the
hotel royale.
It's a historic day as
the official ending of
the United States fierce military
involvement in Vietnam.
Now we have the south
vietnamese foreign minister
with other south
vietnamese dignitaries
the summit doesn't begin for another hour
the hotel has arranged a private room
upstairs for your special quest
That'll be plenty of time.
Good afternoon everyone
hello.
Thank you for coming.
Congratulations on winning this war.
Now I know you all have hands to
shake and photos to take downstairs
so I will get right to the point.
There is a new enemy out there.
An enemy that will render
your arsenals useless
your armies powerless and
your nations defenseless.
You'll need a new weapon for this war.
I call them "sentinels".
Named after the ancient guardians
that stood at the gates of the citadel.
They have the aeronautic
capabilities of a harrier jet.
Armed with guns that can fire off
more than 2,000 rounds per minute of
thermo-ceramic ammunition.
But size power speed
you can find that at Lockheed or Boeing.
No
What makes the
sentinels so special
Is the ability to target
the mutant X gene
The genetic guidance system that can
lock onto a mark half a mile away.
And won't trigger unless it
has identified the target.
With this weapon there'll be
no human collateral damage.
If I turn it on the system
couldn't even activate in here.
Unless...
...there's a mutant.
There has to be some kind of mistake.
My machines don't make mistakes.
What are you?
I assure you
I ..
No. Don't shoot it.
I assure you.
Do not arrest him.
I do not know what you're talking about.
Raven!
Raven.
Charles.
We've come for you.
Erik and I.
Together.
I never thought I would
see you again.
I made you a promise long time
ago that I would protect you.
I didn't. And I know I haven't kept my promise
Wolverine!
I'm going to keep you safe
I'm going to keep you out of their hands
Erik.
What are you doing?
Securing our future.
Forgive me Mystique.
As long as you're out there
we'll never be safe.
Erik.
Use your powers Charles.
Stop him.
He can't.
He is slipping.
He is slipping back.
I'm losing him.
Striker!
... finish what we started Wolverine
one day
Kitty!
Restrain him.
Erik!
Where am I?
Huh?
How the hell did I get here?
What? You came to us.
- Who are you?
- Charles.
Charles Xavier.
- I do not know you.
- Ahh?
What the hell is that?
Woah woah I can deal with this.
Just go.
Stop Erik.
Erik.
I'm sorry.
You are Logan.
That's Hank McCoy.
I'm Charles Xavier.
You spent the last couple of days with us.
You're on acid?
Somebody gave you really bad acid.
Yeah?
Just hold on tight we'll
get through this together.
- Oh god!
- Kitty.
She is wounded pretty bad.
I got him.
Professor.
What happened to you?
I just saw someone who's going to
bring me a lot of pain someday.
Where is Raven?
Gone.
- What?
- We have to get out of here.
Yesterday the Paris
peace summit was rocked
by the appearance of
unidentified assailants.
The likes of which the
world has never seen.
Mass hysteria has gripped the
nation as people ask
where did they come from?
Will they be back?
And most importantly
are they friend or foe?
That was lening
correspondant Toby Elliot
reporting from the Paris
peace summit yesterday.
What the hell are we dealing with here?
Off the record.
2 days ago
this man Erick Lehnsherr
escaped from a
maximum security prison
inside the Pentagon.
We believe that this woman is a
former associate of Lehnsherr's.
They were together in Cuba
the day of the crisis in '62.
He was also implicated in
Kennedy's assassination.
What about that thing?
We do not know what that thing is sir.
Actually we really don't
know what any of them are.
Yes.
Yes we do.
They are mutants.
He has the power to control metal.
Last I checked that's what most
of your weapons were made of.
And she can transform into anyone.
A general.
A secret service man.
Even you Mr. president.
She can walk into this office
and order a nuclear strike
if she was in the mood.
And that's only two of them.
Well do we have any countermeasures
any defense?
I was waiting for you to
ask me that question.
That's an experimental program sir.
Strictly off the books.
You're telling me these
mutants are out in the world
and our best defense are
these giant metal robots?
Many of the mutants looks like us.
My sentinels can tell the difference.
I have 8 prototypes ready to go
they're built out of a space age polymer
not an ounce of metal on them.
I wanna make a demonstration
I want the world
to know that we can protect them.
What do you need to get
these things operational?
I already gave that number to congress
unfortunately they elected to shut me down.
It's going to cost a bit
more to turn them on.
Whatever you need.
Oh and one more thing
if we do manage to capture them
I would like her for
research purposes of course.
How terrible?
What?
I mean, to be like that?
Like that?
Can you imagine?
How can she even look in the mirror?
Yes, I can.
From where did she come from?
You think she has any family?
Yes, she does.
If I see so much as a screw
I will jam this into your throat.
How did you find me?
You taught me well.
It's been a long time
since we were this close.
I missed you.
You tried to kill me.
So the rest of us could live.
What do you mean?
I received a message from the future.
Don't lie to me.
I never have
and I never will.
Humans use your
blood, your genes to
create a weapon that
wipes us all out.
I was only doing what I thought
necessary to secure our future.
So what's to stop me from killing you
right now and securing my future?
Nothing.
It doesn't matter anymore.
They have your DNA
your blood was on the street.
Whose fault was that?
Mine.
I've seen their plans.
They are creating a weapon
and now they have what they
need to take it further.
We have to strike now while
we still hold the upper hand.
I've seen too many friends die Eric.
I don't want a war.
I only want the man who murdered them.
This is war.
What happened to you?
Did you lose your way
when I was gone?
Are you still Charles's Raven?
Or are you Mystique?
Trask is the enemy.
Killing one man isn't enough.
It never was for you.
Good bye Erik.
What happened?
Come on, up
Can he walk?
He needs his treatment.
Hank I can hear them.
It's ok
I'll make it stop. I'll get it
hey
hey. Pull yourself together
it's not over yet.
You don't believe that?
How do you know?
As these go
this comes back.
They all come back.
Look
I'm still here.
She's still out there.
But we need your help Charles.
Not like this I need you.
We can't find Raven..
..Not without your powers.
I added a little extra
cause you missed a dose.
Charles.
Hank do me a favour.
Would you help me to my study please.
Come on, ok
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely not.
This creature is extraordinary.
Her genes could hold the
key to mutation itself.
I need more.
That's all they were able to scrape off
the pavement in Paris.
More than blood.
I need brain tissue.
Spinal fluid.
Bone marrow.
Imagine sentinels that could transform
adapt to any target.
If I just get my hands on her.
This girl could lead the program
forward, years, decades into the future.
How old is your son now Major?
Jason?
He's coming up on 10 now
if you can believe it.
8 years from fighting age.
And how many of our sons and brothers did
we just ship home in body bags?
Maybe 50? 55,000?
How many more in the other side?
Never before
in all of human history
has there been a cause which
could unite us as a species?
Until now.
You really hate mutants doctor don't you?
On the contrary I rather admire
them the things they can do.
I see mutants as our salvation.
And common enemy.
Common struggle against the ultimate enemy.
Extinction.
I believe our new friends are going
to help us usher-in a new era bill.
A new era of genuine and
long lasting peace.
Attention! Attention!
Transport departure in 2 hours.
Repeat.
When was the last time you were down here?
- Last time we went looking for students.
- A life time ago.
Welcome professor.
Raven is wounded
she won't be moving fast.
These are muscles I haven't
stretched in a long time.
Gosh!
- No!
- Who are you?
Charles!
Charles it's alright.
I'll go check the generator.
It's not the machinery
is it?
- I can't do this my mind...
- Yes, you can.
- It won't take it.
- It's just a little rusty.
You do not understand
it's not a question of being rusty.
I can flip the switches
I can turn the knobs.
But my power comes from here
comes from ..
And it's broken.
I feel like one of my students.
Helpless.
It was a mistake coming down here.
It was a mistake freeing Eric.
This whole thing has
been one bloody mistake.
I'm sorry Logan
but they sent back the wrong man.
You're right.
I am.
Actually it was supposed to be you.
But I was the only one who could
physically make the trip.
And ah I don't know how long I've got here.
But I do know that a long time ag..
actually a long time from now.
I was your most helpless student.
And you unlocked my mind.
You showed me what I was
you showed me what I could be.
I don't know how to do that for you
you're right
I don't.
But I know someone who might.
Look into my mind.
You saw what I did to cerebro.
You don't want me inside your head.
There's no damage you can do.
That has already been done trust me.
Hey.
- Hey Logan.
- Hey Jean.
- Kill me.
- I love you.
You poor..
..poor man.
Look past me.
No I don't want your suffering!
I don't want your future!
Look past my future.
Look for your future.
That's it.
Charles.
So this is what becomes of us?
Erik was right.
Humanity does this to us.
Not if we show them a better path.
You still believe?
Just because someone stumbles
loses their way
it doesn't mean they're lost forever.
Sometimes we all need a little help.
Oh I'm not the man I was.
I opened my mind
it almost overwhelms me.
You're afraid.
And cerebro knows it.
All those voices..
So..... much...... pain.
It's not their pain you're afraid of.
It's yours Charles.
And as frightening as it may be
that pain will make you stronger.
If you allow yourself to feel it
embrace it.
It will make you more powerful
than you've ever imagined.
It's the greatest gift we have
to bear their pain without breaking.
And it's born from the most human power
hope.
Please
Charles we need you to hope again.
Find what you were looking for?
Power is back on.
Yes.
Yes it is.
She's lost too much blood.
- She can't keep going like this
- we have no choice Bobby.
We can wake him up.
No.
They need more time.
I had a glimpse into the past
if we wake Logan now we may set off an
even darker course.
They need more time.
Raven stop.
Stop running.
Charles.
Where are you?
Back at the house.
..Where you should be.
I need you to come home.
I know what I need to do.
If you kill Trask
you will be creating
countless more just like him.
Then I'll kill them too.
Those are Erick's works not yours.
The girl I grew up with
wasn't capable of killing
she was good, fair,
full of compassion.
I have compassion
just not for Trask.
He's murdered too many of us.
Shut her down Charles
get in her head.
She's not letting me in
I'm barely holding on.
I'm not strong enough yet.
I know what Trask has done.
But
killing him will not bring them back.
It will set you on a path from which
there is no return
an endless cycle of
killing us and them
till there is nothing left.
But we can stop it right now.
You and I.
You just have to come home.
I have to .
You haven't changed at all
Charles.
Like I said.
I know exactly what I have to do.
Where is she?
At an airport boarding a plane.
Plane to where?
Washington DC.
Hey guys
there is something I need to show you.
We're going backwards in time.
This the system I designed to
record any news about Paris
over all 3 networks and pbs.
All 3? Wow
yeah and pbs.
Look what I found.
Tomorrow in front of the white house the
president will make his announcement .
He'll be joined by secretary
of defense Blair.
And has even sought the help of
renowned scientist Bolivar Trask.
His special adviser to combat
this mutant issue.
The White house is....
Raven doesn't realize but
if she kills Trask at
an event like that with
the whole world watching
then I came a long way for nothing.
And there's more bad news
I saw in a report.
They found traces of her blood in Paris.
For all we know they
already have her DNA .
She's all they need
to create the sentinels in the future.
Now there's a theory in Quantum
physics that time is immutable.
It's like a river you can
throw a pebble into it
create a ripple but the current
always corrects itself.
No matter what you do the river just
keeps flowing in the same direction.
What are you trying to say?
What I'm saying is..
What if the war is inevitable.
What if she's meant to kill Trask.
What if this is just simply who she is.
Just because someone stumbles,
loses their way.
Doesn't mean they're lost forever.
No, I don't believe that theory Hank.
And I can not believe that who she is.
Ready the plane
we're going to Washington.
You alright ?
Getting there.
Whatever happens today
I need you to promise me something.
You looked into my mind and you've seen
a lot of bad but
you've seen the good too.
The X-Men.
Promise me you'll find us.
Use your power
bring us together.
Guide us. Lead us.
Storm
Scott
Jean.
Remember those names.
There's so many of us.
We will need you professor.
I will do my best.
Your best is enough.
Trust me.
12 carriers inbound 10 miles.
They found us.
Thousands of people will
be gathered here today
they've come from all over the
world to witness history
along with news crews from
at least 50 different countries.
Thank you.
Can I see your invitations please?
Yes you may..
These two are with me.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Logan.
Please this way sir.
It's fine...
I haven't found her yet
but she has to be here.
President of the United States.
My fellow Americans
today we face the greatest
threat in our history.
Mutants.
I'm pregnant..
We have prepared for this threat.
In the immortal words
of Robert Oppenheimer.
Behold..
The world will never be the same again.
Can I help you?
No you can't.
Here they come.
This for you brothers and sisters.
Raven.
I have her.
Let me go Charles.
There. You see?
Secret service man
left to the stage.
- Got it.
- Go.
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't tell you to activate it.
I didn't.
Raven please listen to me.
We've been given a second
chance to define who we are.
Don't do this.
Gentlemen you cannot pass this point.
We can't stop that many.
No.
But we can slow them down.
Erik!
Moving through
moving through
Storm!
Take us to def-con 3.
Mr. president we are code red.
What's our air defense readiness.
What the hell happened out there?
I will fix it.
You said that before
I wanted to make a statement.
Now the whole goddamn world knows
we can't protect them.
I will fix it.
You damn well better.
Charles!
Is everybody okay?
Storm!
Behind you.
Now.
I'm probably not supposed to
ask this kind of a thing.
But in the future
do I make it?
No.
But we can change that right?
Do what you were made for.
Mutants.
Where are you?
I got this. Go.
Oh dear god
no.
So much for being a survivor.
One of them is in here.
No! No! No!
Don't kill it.
I need it alive.
What the hell has happened?
You built these weapons to destroy us.
Why?
Because you're afraid of our gifts.
Because we are different.
Humanity has always feared that
which is different.
But I'm here to tell you
to tell the world.
You're right to fear us.
We are the future.
We are the ones who will
inherit this earth.
And anyone who stands in our way
will suffer the same fate as
these men you see before you.
Today was meant to be a
display of your power.
Instead I give you a glimpse of the
devastation my race can unleash upon yours.
Let this be a warning to the world.
And to my mutant brothers
and sisters out there
I say this:
No more hiding.
No more suffering.
You have lived in a shadows in shame
and fear for too long. Come out.
Join me fight together in the
brotherhood of our kind.
A new tomorrow.
..That starts today.
All those years wasted fighting each other
Charles
to have a precious few of them back.
Mr. President.
Stand down! I said stand down!
You want to make a statement?
Kill me...Fine
but spare everyone else!
Very heroic Mr. President.
But you had no intention
of sparing any of us.
The future of our species begins now.
Mutant
mutants
you used to be a better shot.
Trust me
I still I'm.
Get out of my head Charles!
Raven
please do not make us the enemy today.
Look around you
we already are.
They not all of us.
All you've done so far
is save the lives of these men.
You can show them a better path.
Shut her down Charles
I've been trying to control you
ever since the day we met.
And look what that's got us
everything that happens now
is in your hands.
I have a faith in you Raven.
He's all yours Charles.
If you let them have me
I'm as good as dead.
You know that.
I know.
Good-bye old friend.
Good-bye Erik.
You sure you should let them go?
Yes.
I have hope for them.
There's going to be a time Hank.
When we're all together.
What about Logan?
Good morning Logan.
Late start. Hah hah ha.
Have a good lunch time. Good job.
- Thank you.
- Very good job.
Storm.
Jean.
Hi Logan.
Are you okay?
You're here.
Where else would I be?
Woh.
Easy pal.
Some things never change.
Good to see you Scott.
Ah ha.
See you later Jean.
Professor.
Logan.
Is everything alright?
Yeah.
Yeah I think it is.
You did it.
Did what?
Logan don't you have a class to teach?
A class?
To teach. What?
History.
History?
History I could use some help with that.
Help with what?
Pretty much everything after 1973.
I think the history I know
is little different.
Welcome back.
It's good to see you Charles.
It's good to see everyone.
Well
I had a promise to keep.
You and I have lot of catching up to do.
Yes.
What is the last thing you remember?
Drowning.
The past
a new and uncertain world.
A world of endless possibilities.
And infinite outcomes.
Can we?
Oh he is alive!
He is breathing
countless choices define our fate.
Each choice
each moment a ripple in the river of time.
What do you want us to do with him
major striker?
Enough ripples and you change the tide.
I'll take him from here.
For the future is never truly set.