[English subtitles are available]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 5]
[Baili's mansion]
I know you will be here.
You're not calling anyone to arrest me?
It's not you.
You're not the one
who killed my father.
You are smart.
How much do you know?
The wounds on my father
were just a cover up,
or even to frame you.
What really kills
was poison.
You know this too,
so you will definitely come.
Who is trying to kill my father?
Do you know what is my next step?
Autopsy on the body.
Not stopping me?
Even if you don't come tonight,
I will do it myself.
My father's death is a mystery.
If we can find out the true reason for his death,
he won't blame me.
Do it.
You can leave.
I want to see it for myself.
[Master Baili's Spirit Tablet]
[Minister of Ministry of Works from Southern Shaanxi: Master Baili]
What did you find?
He is poisoned.
What poison?
This is Workmen's Knot.
You can't leave.
What poison?
I can leave after killing you.
Why don't you try?
Shachi Venom.
Shachi Venom?
People die immediately after taken it.
It looks normal on the outside, but the organs are all destroyed.
Therefore you should
go after the poisoner.
Not me.
[Jiujing Pavilion]
What are all these?
[Inner Guards: Chen Wu]
Yuehua.
Archives left by Baili Yan.
Archives left by Baili Yan?
When were these sent here?
Why wasn't I informed?
Yuehua.
Imperial Attendant has left a command.
Without his permission,
[Inner Guards: Xu Yuan]
nobody can look
at Baili Yan's archives.
From South City's assassination
to Baili Yan's death,
I oversee them all.
Can't I have a look?
If not for your lack of competence,
Lu Zhi and the other two
would not be dead.
[Jiujing Pavilion]
Siyue.
I have assigned them to be in charge
[The Imperial Attendant of the Inner Guard: Wu Youjue]
of Baili Yan's case.
You have been out these days,
and must be tired.
Go home and take a good rest.
But I haven't found…
I do not want to repeat.
[New wine]
If not for your lack of competence,
Lu Zhi and the other two
would not be dead.
Gao Bingzhu.
What tricks are you playing again this time?
I want to talk to you.
Don't you want to know
how the informers of South City's
assassination died?
Who killed Chen Que
and the three inner guards?
And
why did Baili Yan
died in his study?
Don't mystify things.
Aren't you responsible for killing all of them?
I don't know about others,
but the three inner guards
are killed by Chen Que.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Chen Que?
Yes.
Any evidence?
I saw it with my own eyes,
but I don't have any evidence.
No proof.
How do I trust you?
I'm just telling the truth.
It's up to you to decide whether you want to believe.
Tell me.
Chunqiu Divine.
Chunqiu Divine
is gone a long time ago.
Is that true?
You can go find out yourself.
All I know is Chunqiu Divine
is about to make a big move.
So that means,
the South City's assassination,
the death of inner guards and Baili Yan,
are all their scheme.
Even Chen Que is
killed by our own people.
Yes.
Then why did you find me?
All Baili Yan's archives
are confiscated by the inner guards.
I want to take a look.
You made up a story
about a long gone institution
and thought I would bring you to the inner guards?
You might be
underestimating me.
Chen Que and the inner guards
died of physical assault,
only Baili Yan
died of Shachi Venom.
The murderers aren't the same person.
I think...
Baili Yan died
because he affected
Chunqiu Divine's plan.
If you don't believe,
we can check it out together.
If you don't agree,
I will go seek another way.
There are a lot of inner guards tonight.
See you at Changxia Gate tomorrow noon.
I'll bring you in.
[Baili's mansion]
Uncle, drink some tea.
[Master Xunshan: Liu Xiang]
I've been here for so long.
Where is your husband?
Erlang stayed awake
the whole night for his father.
He's still resting in the room now.
You have finally recognized
Erlang as my husband?
It's all my fault for being soft-hearted.
Ever since your father left the house,
I've pampered you too much.
That's why you're behaving
like this.
Uncle.
Uncle, here.
Since
I have married Erlang,
both our families
will be one.
The Baili Family
is facing adversities now.
We, the Liu Family
should not be bystanders.
Liu Ran.
We may see them as part of the family,
but they may not see us the same way.
Yuehua.
How come you're late today?
Anything?
Nothing.
Hold on.
Lift your head.
-Gao Bing…
-Li Beiqi.
I brought him here.
He killed three of our brothers.
How can you bring him here?
I'll explain
to you later.
Trust me.
Let's go.
[Inner Guards' Office: Case Archives Library]
[Jiujing Pavilion]
I want to have a look at the archives.
I don't want to be disturbed.
All of you go.
Yes sir.
[Jiujing Pavilion]
[Ministry of Personnel]
Gao Bingzhu. Here.
Baili Yan's archives
are all here.
I'll watch the door.
Don't forget what you promised.
Erlang, uncle is here.
Master Xunshan.
Have you seen Uncle Wu?
He went out to buy some candles.
You can tell me
anything.
When he's back,
ask him to prepare.
We will bury my father tomorrow.
It's not been seven days since Baili Yan's death.
Why the rush to bury him?
I have other things to attend to.
Please help yourself.
Erlang.
He is heartless!
You insisted on marrying him.
You won't have a good life!
Please don't get angry, uncle.
Uncle.
Since I've married Erlang,
I believe time will change things.
I have faith.
I can change his heart.
When you regret one day,
remember to come home!
[Jiujing Pavilion]
Imperial Attendant.
Didn't I ask you
to rest at home?
Why did you come again?
About Baili Yan's case,
I have some thoughts.
I would like to share it with you.
I want to have a look at the archives.
[Jiujing Pavilion]
We will talk it later.
Why did you follow me in?
Go out.
Imperial Attendant.
[Sulfur]
I think someone touched the archives.
[Hou, Bo]
[Ministry of Works]
I touched the archives without permission.
Please forgive me.
Wu Siyue!
Do you think all the inner guards
have died,
that you, as a woman,
have to investigate alone?
It's not that I'm arrogant.
It's just that I am sure
nobody in charge will
be as desperate as me.
Brother,
you and I are not from the extended family of Wu.
The reason we can achieve what we have today
is all because of the empress.
Ever since you took charge,
gossips were everywhere.
Now that the capital crime keeps increasing,
everyone is in fear.
If we don't solve this case,
the empress may hold someone responsible.
Brother…
I'm afraid you may be condemned.
Therefore,
I'm actually doing this
for the inner guards…
For you.
Shut up.
Don't try to patronize me.
Guards.
Here.
Yuehua is stubborn
and reckless in her duty.
Take her.
Yes sir.
I have
the Empress' Behest.
Who dares to touch me?
You challenge me in the name of the empress?
Don't forget.
I am your elder brother.
[Behest]
Take her.
-Yes sir.
Excuse us.
[Ministry of Works]
Erlang.
We have been searching all night.
Shall we take a break?
If we continue searching like this,
you may not be able to take it.
Erlang.
What are you looking for?
You won't know even if I tell you.
Liu Ran.
Erlang is looking for a poison
called Shachi Venom.
Shachi Venom?
We have been searching for a full day
and got nowhere.
I found it.
What does it say?
Shachi Venom originates from the West Province.
It turns turquoise under extreme heat.
The poison is lethal.
Once taken, one will die immediately.
It looks normal on the outside but the organs are all destroyed.
One day after the death, rashes appear.
However, if you inject a person with this poison,
it will sustain his life.
Hence, it costs a fortune.
It's gift from the West Province
to our country.
Erlang.
If so, the poison comes from the palace.
Not necessarily.
Some respected figures
may have the empress' blessing.
It's not a shocker
if they own it.
Besides, on the wedding day,
there were many respected figures like those
who came to
our Baili mansion.
[Inner Guards' Office]
[Details of copper]
[Record of shipping time]
Only this page has no official seal.
A mere lady yet
loves to investigate,
loves to swing swords,
fight bravely and fiercely,
loves to read all these archives.
If I don't read these archives,
how can I outdo the inner guards,
and protect the empress and the capital.
What a noble motivation.
If you want to protect the empress and the capital,
this is not the only way to do it.
We as extended family of the Wu.
If we can have a big social circle,
build a network within the ministers,
it would be much better than solving 100 cases.
In the end,
you just want me to be a typical lady.
What's wrong with
being a typical lady?
Look at you.
You have reached the marital age.
If there is anyone suitable, take into consideration.
Take it seriously.
Fine.
I'll take a look
at the third son of the Du Family, the six son of the Meng Family,
and the eleven son of the Cui Family
tomorrow.
For sure there will be one that
can be my husband.
You said it yourself.
Remember what you said.
Don't make promises you don't intend to keep.
[Behest]
I don't want you to get hurt out there.
I'll be waiting for your good news.
[Behest]
This place is not
for you to enter
and leave as you like.
Yue brings you in this time.
If you get arrested, she will be involved.
I can only let you leave.
I warn you, Gao Bingzhu.
You'd better stay away from her.
The next time I see you,
I will kill you.
Miss.
Someone gave you a note.
[Copper]
Erlang.
What happened to you early in the morning?
[Guest list]
Erlang.
You...
You're thinking maybe the killer
[324 guests]
is not Gao Bingzhu,
but all the people
who attended the wedding?
There are 324 guests
recorded here.
All of them were guests
of the wedding.
I want to scheme through these names,
and ensure they didn't
intend to kill my father.
Erlang.
There are 320 over names here.
These include respected figures
and officials,
relatives from the Baili Family
and the Liu Family.
How long will that take?
It has to be done.
Whatever Erlang puts his mind to,
it will not be wrong.
[Supervisor of the Ministry of Works]
Shen Fei.
How many wedding invitations
were sent out?
A total of 327.
Three were missing.
[324 guests]
[Supervisor of the Ministry of Works]
Huang An from Ministry of Works.
Wu Cheng from Ministry of War.
Gu Jia from Ministry of Rites.
Why didn't these three come?
Maybe they were sick?
Or they had duty to attend to?
If they got the invitation
and couldn't attend,
they would inform the hosts first.
Shen Fei.
Yes.
Get prepared.
Bring me to meet them.
Yes.
Erlang...
Excuse me.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Have a safe journey, sir.
Safe journey.
Bai Lang, how come you're here?
[Bootlegger: Bai Lang]
Master Wang.
Fine wine with perfect fermentation.
I bring them to you straight once I arrived.
Have a look.
Do you want one barrel or two?
Just in case you want more,
I brought two more barrels.
Miss, please come in.
This wine is good.
The security has tightened in the capital.
Security is up by 30%.
Not even wine from the West Province
could get in.
Where do you get your wine?
You are so smart.
To be honest,
there were two barrels
that I bought from others.
I was thinking of taking some commission.
I will forgo the commission.
I will charge only the original price.
You are quite honest.
I want them all.
Thank you, Master Wang.
I'll take them in for you.
Alright.
Stand there! Stand there!
-Don't run!
Bai! Don't run.
How dare you mix wine with water and scam us!
Stand there.
Don't run!
Want to catch me?
I am Bai Lang.
A mysterious man.
How could you catch up with me?
Childish.
Who's that?
Who?
Buddy, I made a mistake.
I really did not know about the wine.
Is there any misunderstanding?
You...
I'll explain it to you.
Master Wang, I...
Official Gao?
What brings you here?
You scared me.
I thought you were someone else.
Hey, buddy.
Just now I was…
Who did you scam again?
It's just the Wang family. He…
I don't scam anymore.
Alright. Mine is just a trifle.
Small matters.
It's not worth bringing up compared to yours.
I can't compare myself to you.
Once you make a move,
the whole city bends your way...
I haven't seen you.
Go quickly.
Go quickly. Go.
Make something for me to eat.
How unfortunate!
It's cold. Take what you have.
Official Gao?
Don't drag me in if you want to die.
Leave after you finish eating, alright?
Yes.
Back then
when you were the Unwelcome's Official,
you let me go once.
Over these years, you took care of me too.
Even though I am poor,
at least I know gratefulness.
Then…
If you're in a tight situation now,
you can crash here tonight.
I can crash anywhere.
Right.
Miss Liu has always
kept a room for you.
You don't even bother...
If you ask me,
go explore with me.
I'll take care of you.
We will earn money together,
eat together.
Just don't do
murderous things anymore.
Go explore with you?
Selling fake wine to scam people?
What are you saying?
Selling fake wine?
I'm just seeing the restaurants
selling wines at a high price,
I can't take it.
I'm just giving them a little punishment.
Protecting the citizens. Calling justice.
Alright. Sit down.
I'm here to ask you something.
What?
You ancestors are
Tang's waterway distributors of  Lianshan, right?
The waterway distribution of the capital,
you should know it best.
You're asking the right person.
Back then.
The prestigious carpenter Yuwen Kai
oversaw the whole project
and drafted the map.
That map includes
the flow and directions of
the capital's three rivers and seventeen streams.
However, it's a shame.
The map has been long gone.
Alright.
I, I have one here.
The copper for the Heaven project
are from Lianshan
to the capital.
Tell me.
Along the route,
which is the easiest to rob?
To rob?
Officer.
These are new batch of people.
They can't wait to start work.
Open the door.
Thank you, master.
Follow up.
Master, the people are here.
All of you here,
move the stones up.
The rest carry the timbers.
Bring them over there.
Faster. Work diligently.
What are you looking at?
Go quickly!
Gao Bingzhu.
What did I owe you
-in my past life?
-You two, go quickly!
I have to go through
this for you.
Such powerful strength.
Why is it so long?
Don't break that.
Be careful.
Alright.
Come.
Move this over there.
Those two corners.
Are you in charge of the copper?
You are?
I'm under the command of the empress.
I'm in charge of overseeing the project.
Master.
Keep it down.
Let me ask you.
When will the next batch of copper
be transported to the capital?
This...
I see there are some problems there.
If the copper is the reason
this whole project is delayed,
when the empress finds fault,
it will be horrible.
I wouldn't dare.
It will be within a month.
The leaders are urging.
Don't worry, master.
The latest batch of copper
will be arriving at midnight today.
However,
the few batches of copper lately
lack of pureness.
Therefore the production of it is less
compared to before.
You can't blame us.
Whose ships are in charge of transport?
Chuiliu Corporation from the Baili Family.
Chuiliu Corporation?
Gao Bingzhu.
Gao Bingzhu?
Be quiet.
Let me tell you.
I'll drink some water first.
I have seen it myself.
You didn't see it.
The Heaven building, even if it's half built,
it looks phenomenal.
It is remarkable.
And... What other adjectives?
It's extraordinary!
Go straight to the point.
Right.
I found the copper's transport ship
from Lianshan.
Chuiliu Corporation from the Baili Family.
Besides, I heard someone
at the smelting field said
that the purity of this batch of copper
is not as before.
As expected, something's wrong with the copper.
What can go wrong with copper?
When will the ship arrive from Lianshan
to the capital?
Midnight today.
Which place is the most convenient to make a move?
You have come to the right person.
The capital
is surrounded by rivers and streams.
The waterway leads to six other rivers.
But there are only three
that connect the Yihe River.
One of the rivers is too long,
too risky.
Another is too calm.
Where is the other?
Longmen.
Gao Bingzhu?
You... You really want to
rob the quarry?
You can't do that.
Robbing the government's quarry
can bring punishment.
It's a death sentence.
Furthermore,
you need to pass by the gate to Longmen.
The notice that shows you're wanted
is still all over the place.
The guards will be looking closely.
Fine. If you really want to die,
don't drag me along.
[Imperial Medical Bureau]
My mother was terribly sick that day.
I couldn't walk away.
Not being able to attend your wedding,
I beg your forgiveness.
Excuse me.
[Renhe Lane]
Be diligent.
Check meticulously.
Stand there.
Officer.
What do you have here?
It's wine from the West Province.
So much wine?
Where are you going?
Lately some ministers
are throwing a hunting party outside the gate.
They want us to send some wine
to boost the ambiance.
These ministers do know how to enjoy.
Hunting and partying.
Poor us.
Doing all the hard work.
It is indeed unfair.
Open it.
Officer.
If I open it,
the wine will lose its fragrance.
It'll be hard for me to sell.
At least you're smart.
Let them go!
Thank you, officer.
Go go!
Be diligent.
Check properly!
[Renhe Lane]
Yes sir.
Are you alright?
In order to send you out here,
I prepared three barrels of wine.
Leave the car. We will take the horse.
But they cost me a fortune.
How unfortunate!
Compensate me for the wine!
There. Look there.
[Yihe River: Longmen pier]
This is the way?
Yes.
This is Longmen.
Gao Bingzhu...
Can we not go?
It's not too late to return.
You're robbing the government's quarry.
If you do this…
Quick. Hurry up.
Load the cart. Come on.
Tie them tightly.
Be quick.
One. Two.
Quick, those at the back!
Quick.
Be careful.
These wooden houses are newly built.
Someone is still patrolling.
Those inside, be quick!
Don't put it crooked.
Tie them as tightly as you can.
There must be something fishy here.
It looks normal.
Are you thinking too much?
It's fishy. It's fishy.