Let's tear down the door later
Anyway, closing the door is useless
Yes
Lord You
Is this coming back to search for the palace maidservant who took the title again
Yu's confession
The Prince had ordered her to poison His Majesty's diet
Guanglu Temple Food Bureau is also involved
Meng Shang Shi
I'm sorry
According to Daming Law
Conviction of officials
A formal trial is required to finalize the case
I respectfully ask the Holy Judgment
Inside the harem
Gong Zhengsi is in charge of picketing the Imperial Palace
Today, I am the female official of Zhengwupin Imperial Palace
Even if you want to interrogate and detain
Should be detained in Gongzhengsi
Instead of Zhenfu Prison
Why bother the Royal Guards
This kind of case can't be tried by Gong Zhengsi
Had to wronged Meng Shang to eat
Take away
Wait a minute
The sinner Yu Shi is the one who denounced me
Or the whole food bureau
It is natural that no one knows if they want to go against each other
Good
Since it's just me
Just imprison and interrogate me
Meng Shang Shi
Your Excellency
Nayu's family
Openly arguing with Guo Bianfei at the flower banquet
May be holding a grudge for a long time
Do not hesitate to frame the prince
Involve the whole food bureau
Please also learn from you that you should not be blinded by Yu's family
When will it be your turn to speak
Lord You
Shang Shi Bureau is in charge of court meals
It is the most important place in the palace
If you want to be detained,
Why don't you detain me?
Let Meng Shang eat first
I'm also the duty
Dare not neglect and indulge
I have to wronged three people
Take away
Rest assured
You have no real evidence at all
How can you take people away easily
Just because of a sinner's words
As of today
Present noble people's meals
Have to go through careful interrogation
If there is a flaw
It's not Masahiro Miyagi waiting for you
It's Zhenfu's prison
Trust me
You don't want to know
What kind of a place is that
Zi Jin
What shall we do
I haven't sent anything to Zhuang Fei for three days
They guard like this
We can't get out at all
I still have to think of another way
Don't be rash
Quickly
This
Have something to eat
Even if you have to keep it
You can't stay water and rice all day, can you
Please
Come here
Walk over
Come
So fragrant
Come on, give it to me, give it to me
Come
Empress Zhuang Fei
Take down
How come every time I see you
Make me say the same thing
Take away
Your Excellency
It's just a little palace maid
Can't stand the scare
Take her for a walk in prison
Tomorrow's confession is all ready
Is it
She can say whatever she wants her to say
Keep it verbatim
Your Majesty
The palace maid of Shangshi Bureau has confessed
Princess Zhuang was imprisoned after the incident
Meng Shangshi disobeyed the imperial edict
Private palace maidservants deliver meals
It can be seen that Yu's Zhuang Fei
There is indeed collusion between the Food Bureau
Just take what you said to me
Yu and others conspired against each other
When and where to poison
Say it one by one
Lord You
Don't inflict heavy punishment on me
What does your Lord ask the handmaiden to say
Handmaidens are willing to confess
Father, did you hear me
The Royal Guards used heavy punishment to persecute innocent people
My son is really wronged
This is the command
How dare you talk nonsense
Tell the truth
Lord You
He insisted
Don't say we were plotting to poison
I just haven't had time to do it yet
It coincides with Yu Niangniang's bedtime
This is the opportunity to set fire
Yu Niangniang
The handmaiden didn't say anything
Didn't say anything about your illness
The handmaiden really didn't say anything
Yu Niangniang
Handmaiden handmaiden didn't say anything
Your Majesty
Yu Shi, she obviously harbored evil intentions
What's the disease
A palace maid who is still in the food bureau
How did you know about it
Handmaiden
Shake what
What do you want to say clearly
Your Majesty makes decisions for you
Yes yes
The handmaiden thought
Recently
Yu Niangniang's food list has changed greatly
There are often palace maidservants taking honey and candied fruit
The palace people talked privately
They said that Yu Niangniang was strangely ill
Your Majesty
The handmaiden has just entered the palace
I don't even know the way to the palace
Lord You insisted on taking away the handmaiden
Ask what conspiracy
Handmaiden really doesn't know anything
Your Majesty, forgive your life. Your Majesty, forgive your life
Father
My son is really wronged
Your Majesty
I asked the Imperial Doctor to treat Yu in court
An audience with Imperial Doctor Xuan Sheng
What's the use of checking
Why not tell you
The prince wants to kill your majesty
Because he's tired of waiting
Can't wait to be emperor
I
Be left out for many years
Suffering from the slow treatment and bullying of the whole palace
I'm tired of living
Yu's
Your Majesty doesn't often see you
But treat you well
How can there be so much resentment
How can you be so vicious
Want to bury all of us with you
Princess Zhuang
Do you think your Majesty really dotes on you
We're just royal thrushes
Oriole
They will be released one day
But we
You can only boil until you grow old
Drop to tooth drop
Your Majesty
Since I didn't mean it,
Why did you hurt my life, sire
Crazy woman
Chen Shengyin visits Your Majesty
Sheng Tai Yi
Please feel Yu's pulse
Yes
Check what to judge what
What's there to check
This pulse
This pulse is soft on the left
Right inch off
What exactly is the disease
From the pulse condition,
The patient has chest obstruction and heartache for more than three years
Nowadays, the medicine stone is ineffective
Time is running out
As for eating candied fruit
It must be heart failure and bitter taste
Your Majesty
You can kill me
Your Majesty, I beg you
Your Majesty
Your Majesty, you heard it with your own ears
Yu Shi, she has lost all hope
Holding the mind of dying with everyone
Male and female servants and others are wronged
Your Majesty's Sage
Return the innocence of male and female servants and concubines
Father
Such a terminally ill woman
Crazy talk, crazy talk
Is it trustworthy
Even if my son finds someone to coordinate
How can you find such a precarious person
Is my son in the eyes of my father
Is it really a fool who is wanton and frivolous
Father
Who gave you the courage to frame the prince
Say
I can't let you bury me
What a pity
Prince Ye
Don't blame me
Blame your good side princess
She openly bullied
I'm a poor man
I have to come to settle accounts with you
As long as your East House falls
What vengeance do I have that I can't avenge
The more people I have on the road, the better
Yu Shi, you still refuse to tell the truth
Grandpa Emperor
A few days ago
Someone sent an altar of gold to Yu's home
And promised to take care of her parents for life
Yu knows that his life will not be long
He promised to deliberately set fire to the prince
Nowadays, witness and physical evidence
The eunuchs who spread the news inside and outside are waiting for the decree outside the temple
Who is the mastermind
What do you say, Uncle
Zhu Zhanji
What have I got to do with this
Grandpa Emperor
After inquiry
Someone recognized
The one who sent the gold was the chief attendant of Han Wangfu
Fracture
This is a naked structure
Father
I have never seen this woman before
I didn't send any gold to Yu's family
Father, you have to believe me
If I want to frame the prince,
Be sure to go unnoticed
How can people claim to be people in Han Wangfu
Isn't this waiting to be exposed
Someone must have framed the prince
I want to alienate our royal flesh and blood again
Father Ming Jian, father
Don't worry, uncle
Say it slowly if you have grievances
Can I not be in a hurry
Who can not be framed in a hurry
My son is really wronged
Father Ming Jian
Second uncle, don't make a gaffe in front of the temple
Zhanji, you believe in your uncle, don't you
Tell Grandpa Huang quickly
Second uncle is wronged
Wronged
That's enough
Send Princess Zhuang back to the palace first
Yu's prison will be retried in the future
Yes
Your Majesty still thinks the food bureau is innocent
Let it go together
Father Emperor Father Emperor
You believe me, don't you
Big Brother
The third child
Please stay, Lord You
What do you want from Your Highness
Lord You
Do you ever think
What's so weird about this thing
This is not a conspiracy at all
Yu's life will not be long
And resent the rudeness of the Eastern Palace concubine
Want to burn everything
Will frame the prince
Involve innocent people
As for what to do with Hanwang
Since your majesty has not made a clear decree,
Nature can't be investigated
Please forgive my grandson
How do I feel
Witness and material evidence
It's like everything is waiting for me
As long as the truth comes out
It is good that the prince is safe
His Royal Highness Taisun, Wei Chen, retired
Empress watch your step
Thank you for just
Let's go
Why are you following me
Fuck off
Han Wang is so furious
What's the use
Release comes quickly
Look at you like this
It seems to have suffered a great injustice
How
Even you think I bought Yu's
Frame Prince
Isn't it
Buy off a terminally ill woman
To assassinate the father
Frame Prince
But also leave witness and physical evidence
In your heart
Am I so stupid
In this way
It's like someone deliberately alienated
Not Zhu Gaochi
It won't be Zhu Zhanji
Why
My eldest brother reads the book of sages
Believe in the art of leniency and saint
He can't do such a thing
As for the boy Zhu Zhanji,
More shrewd than Big Brother
How could you try to frame me
What about bringing trouble to your biological father
That is, someone deliberately led him to verify
Who could this man be
Pay tribute
Inverse
If it were you
Pass by many times
His Royal Highness Han Wang didn't recognize his own son
How
I recognize it now
See this tombstone
What else can't I guess
Take a closer look at you
Not born like me at all
It's more like that bitch
Sovereign, Sovereign, calm down
Sovereign
Bitch
King Wang Ye
Mother
After your mother died
You sneaked out of the palace
I sent people to find nothing
For so many years
Your appearance and temperament have changed greatly
When I first saw you,
Or will you have doubts
It seems that seven years ago
The body in Jinan looks like you
It's also the maze of your cloth
The emperor went out in distress
You have been meritorious in rescuing the driver
Since then, he has been transferred to Beijing
Go all the way to the top
But how strict is the selection of Royal Guards
Did the emperor know for a long time
A maid gives birth to a child
Never got an audience with the emperor's grandfather
Who will know who I am
Then neither should you
For a woman who disobeys her husband
Designing to frame one's biological father
Now you know what it's like to be wronged
My mother was innocently wronged and had an affair with others
I don't even have a chance to defend myself
She is more wronged than you
A hundred times more painful than you
Bastard
You can really ignore your father
Don't forget
The blood on you is mine
Is it
You don't listen to rumors
Confessed that my mother had an affair with someone
Maybe
I'm a bastard, too
After the death of Zheng
I once regretted it
It was too rash at first
I sent people everywhere looking for you
I searched all over the country
You hate me
I don't blame you
You have been very intelligent since you were a child
Has always been my father's favorite child
If it weren't for hindering etiquette
You should have been the son of my Han Wangfu
Pay tribute
If you don't want to go back with me,
I don't force it either
I hope one day
Can you call me Father yourself
Go ahead
I have something to interrogate alone
What I promised you has been done
What about what you promised me
Your younger siblings who were kicked out by your stepmother
I have asked someone to find it
And foster care in a family
They will grow up healthy and safe
As for the wolf-hearted man and woman
Will accompany you on the road naturally
I'm relieved
One more thing I don't understand
Say
You used me
Design and frame Hanwang
What is the intention?
Nature is
Back to my beloved father