♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 22=
Mengmeng.
Murong Chen, you finally come.
Mengmeng,
I come to take you back.
Great!
You all conspired to deceive me, right?
It's you who deceived me into
coming to Jing Yue Sect first.
Why can't I lie to you for once?
Zhe Xiang.
Sorry, Master.
When did you come to Jing Yue Sect?
Do you remember anything
before coming to Jing Yue Sect?
What are you trying to say?
I'm going to tell you that
your real name is Qu Yao.
What are you talking about?
I mean
your real name is Qu Yao.
And Qu Yeming is your real father.
So you knew I am
from Jing Yue Sect long ago,
and did not expose me,
just because I'm the
daughter of Qu Yeming, right?
Not exactly.
I saw more of your kindness
and justice in you.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have bothered to protect her
and take care of her.
You've just spent too much time
with Yu Qingzhu,
and forgot who you really are.
That's your bet.
What if you bet wrong?
I never bet on the evil of people,
but on the kindness.
How did you know I'd save you?
If you weren't here today,
I have other strategies.
If I die tomorrow,
Chang Kong will be the
next Tian Ji Pavilion owner.
He'll help me finish
what I have not done.
Do you think
all of these are worthwhile?
The individual will eventually fade,
but consciousness can be passed down
from generation to generation.
Just like
Uncle Qi entrusted
Tian Ji Pavilion to me.
I believe that
there will always be someone
who can finish what I have not done.
(Xue Fu Fragrance)
We can talk tomorrow.
What are you doing?
You!
Murong Chen,
how is he?
Is he alive?
(He's fine.)
Great.
Why did you bring all those men in?
Of course for developing
an imperial harem,
to enjoy the life
surrounded by handsome men.
(He told me to inform you of
the rescue plan.)
Didn't you say that
love is a matter between two people,
(What am I going to do?)
and cannot bear the third person?
I was too stupid,
and too naive before.
(To marry Song Che.)
You cooperated well.
Murong Chen,
I guess I've underestimated you.
Mengmeng,
thank you for trusting me this time.
This time,
I will never let go of your hand.
But unfortunately,
you cannot take her away today.
Brother!
Chen,
you shall take sister-in-law away first.
Just leave me alone.
Yu Qingzhu,
let them go.
You shall take sister-in-law away first.
Yu Qingzhu,
how dare you
take the crown prince hostage!
Don't say that in such a harsh way.
I do not take the crown prince hostage.
I just invited him to the wedding.
Yu Qingzhu,
what do you want?
What do I want?
I want to ask you.
Murong Chen, 5th prince
and Yun Ya,
Tian Ji Pavilion owner,
what do you want?
How did you fool my disciple to
steal the antidote for you
during the days
when I practiced Kung Fu?
So you knew all along.
Of course.
I raised you for so many years,
can't I tell from your
little mind and
little tricks?
So you knew all about it long ago,
and said nothing,
just for
luring us
into your trap today.
Yu Qingzhu,
let the others go,
and I'll stay.
5th prince,
you may have misunderstood.
Jing Yue Sect is just a small place.
There is no room for you.
You're certainly welcome here,
but I would never stand in your way
if you want to leave.
Are you really going to let us go?
Of course,
did you forget
what I said before?
If he comes to ruin the wedding,
I'll let you go.
Great! Your Highness.
However,
Jiang Mengmeng and Murong Yi,
you can only take one with you.
Crazy woman,
why should we listen to you?
Don't be afraid.
I'll get you out of here.
Song Che.
5th prince,
you cannot get all you want.
You can only take one of them
away today.
If you want to take Murong Yi away,
alright,
just leave me Tian Ji Token
of you.
But I have to remind you that
without the virgin blood of
Jiang Mengmeng,
I'm afraid that Murong Yi
won't live for long.
But if you choose Jiang Mengmeng,
I don't have any condition,
and you can just take her away.
What do you think?
Your Highness.
Once you lost Tian Ji Token,
you will not only lose Tian Ji Pavilion,
but also the peace of the world,
and the imperial court.
- I beg Your Highness to think it over.
- Murong Chen.
This is...
This is our last chance,
do you know?
Murong Chen,
there's not much time for making choice.
Chen,
that includes ten years of
your painstaking effort,
so you cannot give her.
I am sorry.
I didn't expect that
you could do this for Murong Yi.
- Your Highness.
Chen Yan.
Continue the wedding ceremony.
Take this traitor to the dungeon.
Zhe Xiang.
You stop.
If you want to keep her alive,
just continue the wedding ceremony.
So beautiful.
Mengmeng,
don't blame me.
I just wanted to test for you
how much Murong Chen loves you.
Now you should know.
Yes,
as clear as crystal.
Me,
Tian Ji Pavilion,
and ten years of painstaking effort,
cannot compare to
Murong Yi in his heart.
Maybe Murong Yi is his true love.
Alright.
See,
you are the most beautiful bride today.
Don't ruin your good mood
and this beautiful scenery
just because of
some unimportant people and things.
Put your clothes on.
It might make you feel better.
You don't get me wrong.
I didn't mean that. I...
I know.
In fact, this marriage
is not what you want.
You love Zhe Xiang.
Mengmeng.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
The reason why you liked me
is just because I am the heroine.
You liked me,
all because of the setup.
The setup?
What is it?
You can interpret it as
a destiny.
Destiny.
Song Che,
you have no idea how much I envy you.
You envy me?
Why?
Through the whole journey,
I've tried so hard
to get rid of the set plot line,
and choose the true love I really want.
In the end,
all of these are
just my fancy.
Even the rebellion and resistance
have been set in advance.
But you're different,
you are meant to be in this world.
Destiny is not watching you
all the time.
You don't demand it,
and just go with the flow.
Gradually you have your own thoughts
and have found someone you love.
You're really lucky.
I don't quite understand
what you said,
but I guess that was a compliment.
(Dungeon of Jing Yue Sect)
Don't you always
look down upon others?
Why?
Why are you not talking now?
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing at you for being pathetic.
What you do today is
what you will suffer some day.
So you're still talking like that.
Don't you get it by now?
That's how Jing Yue Sect works.
Today she can value you,
tomorrow she can abandon you.
The Sect master is ruthless to men,
and she is also
ruthless to women.
You still talk nonsense
when facing the death.
(Hui County Post House)
I am sorry.
I am the one who dragged you down.
Brother,
it's not your fault.
It's my choice.
That woman was right.
Chen,
I am a dying man.
You exchanged me with
sister-in-law and Tian Ji Pavilion.
It's not worthwhile at all.
Uncle Qi and his all men
saved me and Mengmeng
regardless of the danger.
He made me understand that
lives are all equal.
If we sacrifice one person
to save more lives,
that is not the true kindness.
But you've lost everything
for me.
I haven't lost yet.
I have one last card,
which Yu Qingzhu hasn't noticed yet.
Now we have to find Tian Ji Token.
These years,
I am 5th prince of
Cang Yun Kingdom and
Tian Ji Pavilion owner.
But I have not used
the identity of the 5th prince
or my imperial connections
in dealing with affairs in the world.
I understand.
The imperial court and the world
have been acting in separate ways,
and do not interfere with each other.
This is the principle that
our father has always maintained.
Jing Yue Sect has been provoking
in the world for many years,
but maintains the boundary
to the imperial court.
Father cannot do anything,
so he just turns a blind eye to them.
But what if Jing Yue Sect provoke
the imperial court on purpose?
Chen,
you cannot do this.
It's too dangerous.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Brother,
I have my own plans.
But,
I need you to do me a favor.
What is it?
You need to write a letter
as a crown prince of Cang Yun Kingdom,
asking Ruo Shui Kingdom for help.
Alright, alright, alright.
Stop it.
Look at you, you're absent-minded.
You tell me
how to practice?
Then I'll give it up.
Just let me go.
Don't even think about it.
Don't look at it.
That stuff is used too much,
and I'm immune to it.
Fine.
If you really don't want to practice,
then I'll tell you a story.
More than twenty years ago,
I have a friend
who fell in love with a man.
One of them lived in
the imperial court,
the other one came from the world.
Despite their mismatched status,
they fell in love anyway.
My friend believed that
true love can overcome all the barriers.
She believed even more that the man
can give her a lifetime
of true love and happiness.
Until one day,
that man
abandoned her because of
power and high position,
and married a woman with
a powerful family.
Then?
Then,
my friend was sorrowful,
and broke up with him totally.
But when she left this man,
she found out that
she was pregnant with his child.
Her family regarded it as
an insult to them,
and expelled her.
She was friendless
and helpless,
wandering alone in the world.
My friend gave birth to her baby
on the day that man got married.
But because that child
was in poor health condition,
the child died soon.
More ironically,
right on the day when that man
had got a high position,
my friend was burying her child.
She just stood there
from a distance,
seeing her beloved man
with his wife and child
being cheerful
and admired by all people.
Are you the friend that
you are talking about?
That man
is the king of Cang Yun Kingdom,
Murong Shuo, right?
Then Murong Yi and Murong Chen
are his children, right?
Yes.
He killed my child.
Now I need to kill his children.
He wishes for peace in the world,
while I'm going to
make a bloody mess of it.
I will keep him in the imperial court,
without the peace in his life.
So you established the
Jing Yue Sect, right?
Yes.
I have never
told anyone about this before.
Right.
Just like you said,
everyone thinks that
I'm a crazy devil.
But no one would blame this hypocrite
with high position
for being sanctimonious.
Then why did you tell me?
Today,
I showed you my wound,
in order to let you know that
one man
would pretend to love you
and do anything for you
when he has no other choices.
But once
he has better options,
he'll abandon you,
and hurt you ruthlessly
without any hesitation.
Murong Shuo is this kind of person.
So is his son.
This is man.
The true love that those stupid women
have been chasing for a lifetime
is so fragile.
I'll practice the Blood Moon Power.
Are you okay on your own?
Brother, don't worry.
There are some things that
I have to do on my own.
Ok.
Brother,
we'll meet soon.
Take care of the crown prince.
Yes.
Chen, you have to be careful.
Those moves that I've been practicing
are good?
You're really getting better
with your sword.
You're good with your sword, too.
Alright.
Keep your promise.
We help you this time,
and you'll help us meet the saint lady.
Hurry up.
I'll keep
my promise.
Did you go to that rouge shop
at the south of the city?
I have no time.
I...
Two sisters.
Aren't you the toy boys
of the saint lady?
What are you doing here?
Since the saint lady is newly married,
and she loves to be with Song Che,
or practicing Kung Fu.
So I have been ignored,
and I can only be alone in my room.
So lonely!
So I was just looking for two of you
to have a chat,
and to divert myself from boredom.
You guys have a lot of nerve.
Alright.
How about playing
Werewolves of Miller's Hollow?
Have a look? Ok.
It's getting dark,
and close your eyes.
Don't waste your time.
I'm not going to say anything.
Zhe Xiang.
Song Che.
It's me.
Why are you here?
I am here to rescue you.
How did they do this to you?
It's ok.
I get used to it
since I was a kid.
Since you were a kid?
How have you been living
all these years?
I'm going to get you out of here.
No.
Why?
Yu Qingzhu did this to you,
do you still want to
stay at Jing Yue Sect?
No.
I can't get out now.
Think about it. If I get out of here,
what about Jiang Mengmeng?
♪Wind blows, sand flies in battlefield♪
♪Who fights in the chaos♪
You didn't think about Jiang Mengmeng,
and came straight here
to rescue me, right?
Song Che,
I am kind of happy
that you did this for me.
There is one thing
I have wanted to give you,
but I had no chance before.
♪Do not leave again♪
You'll keep this
in case you need it.
♪What I wrote is all about you♪
♪Misty rain has come home, just do not♪
♪Do not leave again♪
Take care.
♪Letter sent from a long distance.
I am here waiting for you♪
Wait.
What?
♪Walls collapse, Enemy comes♪
♪Under the ancient road♪
♪Kill in the battle, fight in the war♪
♪Just for her♪
♪Misty rain has come home, just do not♪
♪Do not leave again♪
♪See the wind blows,
the missing goes on♪
♪What I wrote is all about you♪
♪Misty rain has come home, just do not♪
♪Do not leave again♪
Take care.
♪Letter sent from a long distance.
I am here waiting for you♪
♪Under the eaves,
I heard you dressed in white♪
Wait till I get back for saving you.
(Hong Lang Gao Chang)
What's that sound?
Oh no.
Murong Chen broke in.
We can't stop him.
Murong Chen?
How many people are there with him?
Just him.
Just him?
Yes.
You go and tell the Sect master.
Let's go and check it out.
He's trying to get in here
in that health condition.
Is he crazy?
Since you don't want to live,
we'll do it for you.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪