Your Highness
Brush the kebabs with this creamy ghee
Why use ghee?
back to His Majesty
Use different fires when grilling meat
such as firewood, charcoal
taste is different
different meat
Free at kisskh.me
The way of roasting is also different
such as the burnt
Originally a famous dish in Kaifeng in the Northern Song Dynasty
Brush with pepper brine when roasting
But Your Majesty's constitution is easy to get angry
The slaves deliberately switched to butter ghee
thank you your majesty
I have been waiting for a long time
stop baking
all old
father emperor
be careful
not very crisp
His Majesty
bake with ghee
Take the first bite
must be crispy
if crisp
It must have been overcooked.
father emperor
Father, do you remember?
once
Son ordered someone to come
Bring you roast lamb
It was Erchen's first time hunting.
downed ibex
this time
It is lamb ribs with more beautiful meat
more fragrant
burnt
i mean
That lamb was burnt last time you roasted
Completely inaccessible
because at that time
It was the first time my son came to bake in person
no experience
Yao Dianshan
Grilled meat is very greasy
Your Majesty used to have a toothache after eating it
how can you give
Souji Zen
I added to the seasoning
A pinch of slightly spicy thyme powder
Can remove fire and smell
Can also be seasoned
Your Majesty is eating
It is accompanied by the chrysanthemum drink to remove the fire
As long as it matches
Roasted meat can resist the cold
There is also the therapeutic effect of nourishing and warming
not to mention
at the banquet that day
Sushi and Hu Shangshi
Isn't it also grilled meat?
His Majesty
Slaves are careful
Meal prepared for you
what is this
Hurry up
Your Majesty please try
how to have shares
The taste of scallops
His Majesty said it
The fish belly is also specially added
winter bamboo shoots and mushrooms
Sea cucumber and scallops
Chicken Qing
pork to season
because of net oil
And the bread is tightly wrapped
Although the fish is grilled
yet fresh and not greasy
fragrant
This Roasted Mandarin Fish with Flowers
And nourish the heart
Remove oily smell
mandarin fish
rich and rich
good sign
why don't you eat
father emperor
When Erchen was practicing swords just now
the wind
some discomfort
Retired first
Xuan Shengyin
Yes
Unexpected day
you will also run
Your Majesty, come to please
Zijin
get out of my way
empress
go
go see
Your Highness
Free at kisskh.me
The slave's right hand is inconvenient
Forget it, Yuan Qi will come.
I'm afraid some people are clumsy
hurt me more and more
It's just bitter meat
why
And let me mention the wild lamb
thousands of miles
from Khurmus
brought back opal
see if you like it
back to your highness
slaves dare not say
Say it
forgive you
Gentleman far son near grandson
how
Famu is far from fire and near earth
in the heart of the emperor
Your Highness
Is the beloved good grandson
His Majesty
It is the eldest son who is to blame at every turn
often needed
You and the empress have come to considerate
that lasts forever
I'm afraid even His Highness himself thinks that
The emperor can successfully inherit the throne
There is a part of your credit in
That is naturally in your heart
Just one less for Your Majesty
Ru Mu Zhi Si
awe
You are too bold
your hands are not good
Back to His Highness
Imperial Physician Sheng's Rejuvenation
The injury has greatly improved
The two countries are fighting for strength
Form a team to win or lose
The winding road leads the way
Will keep the deep palace ring expedition
Take the risk and get out of the car
Flying guns across the river under the heavy city
Learn about military affairs
Seeing peace with success
This is the father
When I was the Crown Prince of the East Palace
A poem written to Zeng Zidi
The poem is about chess
hidden
when today
to establish peace and prosperity
Mind and Courage
you say so
more like me
Know more about my father
As soon as the emperor ascended the throne
Stopped the official purchase
Dozens of bursts
Disaster relief tax exemption
light-hearted
rest with the people
It is to rectify the government
open the way
past dynasties
There are some heroes who started a national business
There is a holy master who maintains ZTE
But as generous and merciful as His Majesty
A virtuous master who loves the people
also famous for later generations
Shine with the sun and the moon
If it comes to the emperor's holy
That's three days and three nights.
just one thing
Queen Mother
how are you here
I heard that your old injury relapsed on the school grounds
I specially accompany your father
come and see
so is your child
injured
Why don't you say a word
Worrying for the Queen Mother
It's all sons and daughters
let's continue
His Majesty
The slave's mouth is unobstructed
sin deserves death
no problem
what did you say today
I won't blame you
Your Majesty the Father
this bold girl
say your exploits
will be famous
didn't ask you
you just told me
Three days and three nights of merit can't be finished
The only thing wrong
what's the matter
a little lady
How dare you talk about the emperor
should be punished
Say
His Majesty
The slaves also listen to the discussions in the market
they said
them
say yes
they said
Traitors and criminals of the Jianwen Dynasty
have been subdued
just pity them
innocent wives
suffer from
shut up
Say
They are all implicated
or sub-lijiaofang
or become slaves with heroes
Some were even exiled for thousands of miles
dead in a foreign land
When His Majesty came to the throne
Zeng pardoned the world
praised by the people
Grace is like the radiance of the rising sun
Even sinners can be forgiven
But
This radiant light
Why can't I take care of myself
The most miserable person in the world
Out of madness, but not back
father emperor
This is just an ignorant girl
you are kind and generous
Don't compare with her
I inherit the throne
King's Landing
Can the world be wide
The complexity of common affairs
Can I be alone
I am making a request
sincere
But few speakers
Road is congested
Up and down
Fang You officials corrupt and miscellaneous
Tsunade is slack
Today there is a harem maid
actually told me the truth
How can I blame her
i said
merit must be rewarded sin must be punished
You are
back to your majesty
Slaves are the classic meals of Shangshi Bureau
Your Majesty bestows you a promotion
not soon thank you
The slaves thank the saints
take good care of you
Let's go to Nanjing when the injury is healed.
Thank you father for compassion
queen
Deal with the family members of the rebels
It was the will of the imperial examination that year
nowadays
if i forgive them
Wouldn't it go against the will of the Emperor Kao?
Where the harem maid
Don't talk about things outside the palace
Since His Majesty asked
The concubine had to answer
His Majesty is more than ten years old
served by Emperor Taizu
Naturally abide by the ancestral teachings
Emperor Ming's ancestral teaching has something to say
Extra law and punishment are intended to warn the world
Not the usual method used by the Shoucheng Emperor
Later descendants became emperors
Obeying the Law and the Great Rule
no penalty
Fear of misconduct
Injured innocent
The female family members of the back house are innocently affected
His Majesty forgave them
It is to follow the ancestor's teaching
queen
These words
is it in your heart
hold for a long time
Although the maid was daring just now
but said
His Majesty's thoughts
I am the queen of your majesty
Of course you should be worried
deliver an imperial order
The traitor in Jianwen
The main offender has been known to be murdered
Family first-time education department
Jin Yiwei
Coat of arms
and trainers and
Slave in the family of the hero
if there are survivors
Amnesty
You can be for the people
return the soil
Your Majesty Shengming
Your Highness
all right now
The slaves retire
you use me
Your Highness
His Majesty came suddenly
The slaves are also at a loss
think about it
I got injured on the training ground
The emperor will definitely come to test himself
You guessed he was coming
Your Highness
your mess
I can't find the north even if I hold my father and emperor.
your actual purpose
In fact, for
Exiled female relatives plead for mercy
Your Highness Misunderstood
really wronged
How dare a slave
not telling the truth
Your Highness
those innocent women
because of the family's fault
once relegated to
They are forced to entertain people with sensuality
humiliated
this unfortunate situation
How similar to my mother
Your Highness
The maid also helped you
if not
Your Highness has set off for Nanjing.
I really shouldn't
send you a rabbit
Free at kisskh.me
i should send a fox
just for you
Pretending to be good-natured in front of me again and again
It's all fake
I
fraud
Your Highness also lied to me
what
Your Highness said earlier that he would let me go
Are you telling the truth?
Your Highness lied to me that I didn't read the military book
I don't know what it means to retreat
You do everything possible
Just to deceive me
all right now
The slaves retire
It's true
let you go
also true
what are you going to do
don't push me
I have something urgent to report
Your Highness is busy
Your Highness
he broke in
he
Sister Yao
Sister Yao is back
Yao Sishan
Sister Yao
Yao Sishan is back
Congratulations to Sishan Hexi Sishan
Yao Si's hand is injured
But a blessing in disguise
Rewarded by His Majesty
it's really
Great luck
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Let's get together today
get together at night
have a good time, okay?
ok ok ok ok
alright, alright
We all take Sister Yao
Can't breathe
Sister Yao
later became a chef
Do you want to teach us how to cook?
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Sister Yao must teach us how to cook.
Yes, teach us more
teach us a little more
go go go go
go to work
Yao Sishan
The Queen's Concubine
Yao Sishan, don't move
Let's Jiang Si Yao
Diagnose and treat for you
her medical skills
Comparable to Ligong Recuperation Pansiyao
Even smarter
How is Jiangsi Medicine
Please report back to the Queen on your behalf
Yao Sishan's right hand
Great improvement
As long as the spoon does not go into the kitchen
will not strain the muscles
she is in good health
Just a little sullen
I think it's due to the daily fatigue
Just take a good rest
It's okay
I'll prescribe some more yakuju pills
Rejuvenating Qi and Treating Depression
tired
congratulations
What does this mean?
come in
stop her
let me go
open
Ali
old lady
I, Ali, canonize the crown prince and concubine
hairpin ring to use
must use the best
old lady
Prince Concubine
Crown Prince Concubine
Requires the gift of envoy canonization
Ritual can't be messed up
The Empress has already ordered
Let the old lady decide everything
Yes
East Palace is justifiable
prince of a country
Why risk sending someone to assassinate
If it's what the prince did
How can you send a young army to join in?
Isn't it a big fanfare to tell people
Who is the mastermind behind the scenes?
Doubtful about this
Your Majesty can't be trusted
I have my own opinion
you are seriously injured
don't worry
His Majesty
Everything is Jinyiwei
Poor verification
It's the minister's negligence
Your Majesty, please forgive me for three days
The minister must re-investigate
Find out the real mastermind
trouble
His Royal Highness arrives
father emperor
Erchen sent people to visit
just got the news
On Aoshan Lantern
artisan laying gunpowder
already on the night of the celebration
being silenced
Afterwards, the emperor took pity on the craftsmen
innocently affected
not only blame
Also to the unfortunate artisan who lost his life
be pampered
this person
also escaped
Jin Yiwei's interrogation
No wonder
The craftsmen of this strict trial
all living
who else
Doubt a dead man?
His Majesty
Evidence must be found in this man
his master
ten years ago
The old man of the Han Dynasty
King of Han
are you alright
Your Highness
You are recovering from a serious injury
come to defend me
I should be thanking you
This framing trick
really despicable
The emperor was only angry for a while
to be deceived
Your Highness, don't worry
It's something else
I am worried that someone will take this opportunity
The strategy of adjusting the tiger away from the mountain
Your Highness be careful
Do not leave Beijing recently
take good care
can be fished out
Okay
This placement
Pay attention to the location
Okay
The plate should be laid out layer by layer
don't get in the way here
not going out
I'm also the chef of the Food Bureau
palm meal
a pariah
This life ends here
Wait until I take charge of Shangshi Bureau
maybe still
How about some scraps for you?
His Majesty
It's windy here
Let's go back sooner
Chest tightness recently
let's go
Liu Gonggong
His Majesty is still worried about the assassins
Your Majesty is here
still rude
Shangshi Bureau tribute fresh pastries
May your majesty be happy
be careful
Thank you for your grace
how about sushi
but you're not alone
Will it please His Majesty?
It seems that I really underestimate you
not
Your Majesty Chrysostom
If there is something delicious
fun meal
allow me to offer
you don't know much
no medicine diet
How can I prepare myself for Your Majesty?
But it is
Just a moment of freshness
Wait until it's fresh
Let's see how to put you back in shape
Then you take a good look
How did I rise to the top
crazy crazy
What about Zijin?
except her
No one can control Yin Ziping
what about people
What are you doing?
come out
Your Highness
what are you doing
doorway
Ali
old lady
Can't go in there, old lady
Find them all for me
old lady
Free at kisskh.me
you slow down
Slower
room by room
find it out for me
line
Gotta find someone
old lady
I really can't get in there.
Ali
old lady
you slow down
Ali
grandmother
you are in the palace
Why don't you tell me
His Royal Highness
Don't be too polite
what grandma is looking for
i know where
real
didn't you hear
Grandma is looking for Ali
haven't brought it out
Yes
grandmother
Just now I have been listening to you shout
Ali Ali's
Probably looking for this cat
no
old lady
His Royal Highness in person
Named this raccoon slave
Inkstone
grandmother
I still have business here
you go back to rest
no
come
Don't hurry up and send the old lady back
Your Highness
slow down
His Royal Highness
I
come out
Chen Wu
Grandmother just passed away
call her back
Yes
Your Highness
really go you
Your Highness, what does this mean?
Why so afraid of my grandmother
Ali
where did i go all day
Where does Mrs. Peng Chengbo follow?
I really have nowhere to hide
Entered His Highness' study
anyway
They can't search here.
Your Highness, please forgive me
You even dare to use me
Why are you so afraid of her
Your Highness still remember
I am seriously ill
Is it about going out of the palace to recuperate?
The imperial physicians in the palace are helpless
If it weren't for the old lady, she wouldn't give up
Hire famous doctors everywhere
I'm afraid I'm no longer in this world
the hardest time
Only the old lady refused to abandon me
Old lady's recommendation
It is to consolidate the power of the Zhang family.
but she treats me
I can't be ungrateful
you really want to be a foodie
Don't look at Sishan and Shangshi
only one level away
It's really different
how old are you
I want to be the head of a palace
really shameless
Your Highness
mocking others so much
It's not what a gentleman does
I didn't laugh at others
I just laugh at you
Then I never knew Your Highness
Your heart is so bad
i never knew
Your heart is so deep
what are you talking about
You come to me on your own initiative
don't you just want me to pity you
take the initiative to cover up for you
you are waiting for me
Praise your mother in person
you are free
I'm being tortured now
It's all because of you
you use me again and again
never soft
I am to you
soft-hearted again and again
Take the initiative to help you carry everything
Is it fair?
Has your Highness thought about it?
Maybe I have nowhere to go
Go ahead
Yes
Your Highness
let's go
where to
Kunning Palace
Your Highness
Didn't you say it all
She won't get it this time
all her wishes
I want it all
just because i don't want to
see her sad again
Your Highness
it hurts
let go let go
get down to business
what are you doing
This is
i tomorrow
Meal for His Majesty
you help me see
is there anything wrong
Steamed pork belly
Burning sheep's head and hoof-stuffed chinchilla
These are too greasy
Don't repeat the mistakes of Yuehua before
You want to make Bazhen cake
I was about to ask you to teach me
His Majesty has been feeling unwell recently
This is the pharmacist
tell me
Bazhen cake can be prepared
Your Majesty's Weak Spleen and Stomach
And the miraculous effect of puzzle and soothing
fit for His Majesty
Ziping
You are obviously incompetent
We should take advantage of strengths and avoid weaknesses
Why do you suddenly think
Want medicine?
of course
not right
His Majesty
Guo Guifei today
See you for the third time
not see
Yes
Your Majesty Your Majesty
Your Majesty, are you alright?
His Majesty
imperial physician Xuan imperial physician
Please bring your majesty's meal list
princess
The doctor has checked
No blockages in meals
queen concubine
All meals
The minister has carefully checked
Nothing wrong with
Your Majesty suddenly fainted today
I'm afraid it's just a relapse of an old disease
It's about His Majesty's Dragon Body
not to be taken lightly
Dietary non-toxic
Doesn't mean they're innocent
Food is the same as Chinese medicine
if they collide with each other
harmful rather than beneficial
Still need to check
to draw conclusions
How can you say this is good?
This Eight Treasures Cake
who did it
back to the princess
Bazhen cake is made by slaves
Inside this eight treasures cake
what food did you use
Folk Bazhen Cake
yam medicine
White lentils and lotus seeds
And Poria coix
Hawthorn and Malt
The Eight Treasures of the Palace
It is the prescription prescribed by Yitai Hospital.
need to combine the last two flavors
replace it with ginseng
And deer antler
confused
mother
I just checked
Medicinal recipes used by the emperor on a daily basis
all included
Ganoderma lucidum deer antler Codonopsis
dose to a patient
enough is enough
Now the female chefs of Shangshi Bureau
Little knowledge of pharmacology
Dare to use medicinal food easily
Father emperor weak spleen
Supplement like this
This is not life
Are you sick?
queen concubine
Your Majesty has been in poor health recently
The Food Bureau is acting cautiously
The list of medicated meals should be reported to the Tai Hospital first.
Medicated diet prescribed by Tai Hospital
Pharmacy Division dispenses medicinal materials
What medicine to take and how much
all recorded
Never dare to make any mistakes
The person in charge of the pharmacy department of the Taiyuan Hospital
should also be punished
Knowing that the father and the emperor are empty and will not be compensated
Let the Shang Food Bureau make medicated meals
especially deer antler
frail person
Once overdose
just too much blood
even appear
hematemesis syndrome
In my opinion
The person who made Bazhen Cake this time
with a loving heart
Complete disregard for the emperor's dragon body
should be severely punished
Are you guilty?
Do not plead guilty to the queen
queen concubine
Your Majesty likes to eat meat
Irregular spleen and stomach
Physicians for
Free at kisskh.me
Replenish your body for His Majesty
Prescribing plenty of supplements
such as deer antler and ginseng
Lingzhi etc.
As the princess said
Too much supplements can also hurt the body
but
All medicines in the palace
and how much
They are all drawn up by the Taiyuan Hospital.
with medicated meal
There are many precious medicinal herbs
To prevent others from stealing for profit
There is also professional supervision
so
The Food Bureau can't decide the dose
you can
shirk responsibility, right?
so
When slaves deliberately use ginseng
simmered for hours
Ginseng into charcoal
Still quietly in the clear water of the noodles
Added raw carrot juice
raw radish juice
Yes
imperial concubine
Raw radish juice is cool
It can also reduce phlegm and stagnation
Detoxification
You can still breathe
dissolved in supplements
Excessive medicinal properties
Radish
It can also digest and appetizer
to His Majesty's body
absolutely beneficial
so
Your Majesty is sick
It has nothing to do with Bazhen Cake
It seems
you know
The medicated food prescription given by the Tai Hospital is inappropriate
Still hiding
Why hide the truth?
stop holding on
step by step
hot
You used to speak bluntly in front of me
With such courage
Why not put the truth
tell everyone
back to His Majesty
In the meal recipe of Bazhen Cake
with supplements
indeed to your majesty
Has the effect of nourishing the body
It's no fault in itself
It's just that His Majesty previously believed
Ginseng is added to the prescription
Deer antler is effective
The doctors
dare not disobey
Fear of overdose
If the slaves report truthfully
easily misunderstood
In case something goes wrong
will involve a lot of imperial physicians
And the women of the pharmacy department
It is better to start with Codonopsis and deer antler
to replenish vitality
Use radishes to calm down
You won't get sick
as a cook
More than just a delicious meal
also empathetic
get things done
still so lawful
as a chef
I really feel sorry for you
i think
Concubine thought
Let's make her a concubine