[English subtitles are available]
Who is playing?
Grand Tutor,
you are finally here.
I have been waiting for you for a long time.
Ming Hua?
You are Princess Ming Hua?
You promised me
to love me and protect me.
Why did you let me die alone first?
If there is another life,
I will never let Your Highness down again.
[Be My Princess]
[Episode 6]
[Capital]
Come on.
Grand Tutor,
you will definitely protect me,
right?
Slowly.
Yours looks more tasty than ours.
Ming Wei, you have already entered the working society,
but your personalities never changed.
Right.
Still so naive and kind of stupid.
What do you mean?
I'm stupid
so that you two can look smart compared with me.
Be thankful, OK?
Han Xiaoya
has set herself against you since we were in college.
Do you still remember?
She thought she looked better than Wei,
and tried to be the school beauty against Wei.
Right, right.
Except learning,
she competed with Wei in every field.
Even so,
you still agreed to be her bridesmaid.
We were classmates after all.
I have forgotten about these long ago.
Besides,
she said that
we three could choose the bridesmaid robes
as we like.
No matter how expensive they are, she will pay for them.
Really?
Great.
Let's choose carefully then.
Don't let her down.
Makes sense.
Look at the top of trending topics on Weibo.
Mu Tingzhou had a car accident.
He is still under emergency treatment.
[The Best Actor Mu Tingzhou had a car accident.]
Ming Wei.
the news of Mu Tingzhou's car accident is true.
We only know that he is in hospital now,
no other information.
Don't post anything on Weibo.
Wait for the official information,
understand?
[Xiao Zhao]
I heard about Mr. Mu's accident.
Can you tell me his condition,
if possible?
I'm really worried about him.
Hope he is safe.
Mr. and Mrs. Mu, please have some water.
No need.
The doctor is here.
What is his condition, doctor?
I need to make something clear
to you in advance.
You should better
be prepared.
[Shanghai Deda Hospital]
Mu.
Give way.
Mu Tingzhou.
Please give way, fans and reporters.
Please let us see him, ok?
How is Mu Tingzhou? I would like to go upstairs and see him.
[Mu, come on!]
Step backwards, OK?
Can I go see him?
Let me see him please.
It's all my fault.
Why did I refuse to take his car?
If I was with him at the time,
[Mu, come on!]
everything would be different, right?
Come on, Mu!
[The hospital has been blocked layer upon layer. Agent Xiao Zhao didn't answer the phone.]
[I heard about the accident of Mr. Mu. Can you tell me about his condition if possible?]
[I really worry about him. Hope he is safe.]
[Staff of the hospital divulged that the Best Actor Mu Tingzhou has passed away.]
How is Mr. Mu now?
Is it convenient for me to visit him?
Please reply
if you see my message.
Wei,
it is half past three in the morning.
You still up?
I cannot sleep.
I've never seen you fangirling before,
but you almost seem like a fan of Mu Tingzhou now.
I only hope
that he can be safe.
[The Best Actor Mu Tingzhou has passed away.]
What kind of news is it,
saying Tingzhou is dead!
It's not okay. We need to explain to the media.
Mr. and Mrs. Mu.
We cannot hide the condition
of Tingzhou anymore.
We need to tell the media.
I have informed everyone that I need to.
We need to face the reality
no matter how sad we are.
The person Tingzhou is most concerned about
is Ming Wei, the actress of the princess.
I will inform Ming Wei first
and tell her to come to the hospital.
I believe
this is also the wish of Tingzhou.
When will he wake up?
Come here.
He's awake now.
But it's still unknown if he'll recover.
Ming Wei, wait up.
I'm so regretful.
Why haven't I told him earlier
that I actually like him a lot？
Ming Wei.
If something bad really happened to him,
if I wouldn't have the opportunity to tell him ever,
will you regret it for the rest of your life?
Mr. Mu.
It's not bad. He's not disabled.
My honor to see you, Your Highness.
Oh my god, is he brain-damaged?
Mr. Mu,
shall we get up and talk?
I
am sloppily dressed.
Then,
go back to bed.
I won't see anything when you are under covers.
You haven't recovered.
Lying down helps your recovery.
Yes,
Your Highness.
Is he acting now?
Or is he just fooling with me?
He can't really be like this.
Your Highness,
please take your seat.
Why do you dress so oddly, Your Highness?
Did those wicked people force you to do that?
Mr. Mu,
it's not the case.
Please call me Grand Tutor, Your Highness.
I'm not used to
what they call me here.
But
you are not the Grand Tutor,
nor am I the princess.
I'm only the actress playing the role of princess,
Ming Wei.
It seems like they also poisoned Your Highness
to let you forget about the past.
You are the one who forgot about the past,
not me.
You are awake, my son.
Do you still feel sick anywhere in your body?
Tell me.
What's going on?
What... what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Tingzhou, you're awake.
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing, Tingzhou?
What's going on?
Who are you?
We just injected him with tranquilizer.
After he's come to life,
we will have doctors from the neurology department
and the neurosurgery department
to operate consultation for him.
He's condition now is...
Slay, slay.
Get out of my way.
I...
Who arrested me here?
Tingzhou.
Stop fooling around.
Who is this Tingzhou you keep calling?
You don't recognize your parents?
So you were trying to poison me and perplex me,
pretending to be my relatives so that I'll let loose.
Don't you know that
I've lost my parents since an early age?
You not only poisoned me,
but also cut my hair.
Don't you know that our body, hair and skin are given by our parents?
You intend to put me into this disloyal and disobedient state.
What are you talking about?
I've been a director for my whole life,
and I never saw an actor
is so brought into the character like you.
You got carried away.
Uncle and auntie,
can I talk in privacy with Tingzhou for a while?
OK?
OK.
Let's go.
Mu.
Grand Tutor.
We mean no harm to you.
You are very weak right now.
Can you put this down first?
Let's have a good talk.
You recognize me?
Then tell me.
Who sent you here?
Why do you imprison me here?
Who is this Tingzhou?
Where to start?
First I want to tell you that
the Ning Dynasty collapsed hundreds of years ago.
Nonsense.
This is called electric lamp.
This is called television.
This is called cell phone.
Come on, smile.
Look.
Electric lamp, television.
We've got them in every household.
Even three-year-olds know how to use a cell phone.
What you see right now is not magic,
nor illusion.
These are the wisdom
of hundreds of years of human beings' endeavor.
What can bring someone from dreams
to hundreds of years later,
if not magic or illusion,
must be witchcraft.
My turn now.
Please.
Tingzhou,
why do you all take me as him?
You are Mu Tingzhou.
You are the actor playing the role of Mu Yun.
What do you mean by actor?
To put it into ancient sayings,
you are a playactor.
How dare you compare me to a playactor?
No, no, no.
The identity and status of actors now
are equal with ordinary people.
A good actor
is actually very respectable.
I have a question.
Go ahead.
Before you woke up,
what happened on earth?
And where were you?
Abiding by His Majesty's edict,
I'm temporarily working as the Grand Tutor,
to teach the prince and princess.
Oh my god.
He's still in episode one of the script.
Do you trust me, Mr. Mu?
Your Highness is the only one I trust in this world.
Since you trust me,
can you listen to me?
Please, go ahead.
Mr. Mu,
you've always been
a very respectable senior actor for me.
Shooting the Grand Chief Cabinet Minister together with you,
I've perceived
your dedication into acting.
Perhaps that's why
you've mistaken yourself as
the role in the play after the car crash,
Grand Tutor Mu.
I've read all the scripts
of the Grand Chief Cabinet Minister.
After reading these,
I'm even more certain that I'm Mu Yun, the Grand Tutor,
and not what you call
Mu Tingzhou.
Why?
The scripts are ridiculous and unfounded.
We have a huge disparity in identity, Your Highness,
and I was entrusted by His Majesty.
How could I be obsessed with Your Highness for a lifetime?
This is why it's ridiculous.
Your Highness is naive and pure, royal and unattainable.
-How could you have feelings for me? -No way.
This is why it's unfounded.
If I'm really Mu Tingzhou,
I wouldn't have accepted
these plots that made no sense
so as to lose what I pursue.
This...
A play
needs to be dramatic.
The plots of our relationship
have been emphasized by the scriptwriter.
Since you've known that this isn't true,
why did you take it seriously?
They created this script
with the obvious intention
to sow discord between me and His Majesty, and Your Highness.
To cause chaos in the Ning Dynasty.
Drop it.
Mr. Mu.
You almost got me.
It's true that this play is a fiction.
So,
the Grand Tutor Mu is no real person.
There is only Mu Tingzhou in the world,
no Grand Tutor Mu.
Your Highness, if you want me to believe in these words.
Then I am not me,
you are not you either.
Without this relationship,
is there any difference between you and the others outside?
In other words,
I respect you
as a minister only because of you, Your Highness.
I trust you and respect you.
This is not right.
These vicious people had brought Your Highness,
they must not let His Majesty and Crown Prince go.
Maybe they have...?
I have to go and look for them.
Wait a moment!
They....
They are all fine.
Your Highness, you just told me everything was all just a play.
Why would you recognize that
His Majesty and Crown Prince exist now.
I, I was just....
in a trance
and memorized something.
Anyway, they are fine.
You don't trust me?
Your Highness, those villains must have drugged you and
messed up your memories.
I surely trust your
words.
But Your Highness,
the world is a strange place.
I have heard that
there are strange poisons in Miao area,
you could get illusions if you take one of the poisons.
And you would not differentiate between illusion and reality just like Chuang Chou Dreaming a Butterfly.
I do not know
how they had brought us
here and
what are their purposes.
But I will try my best to
find their weakness and
take you back.
How did this happen?
He seems seriously ill.
Thank God you have reacted fast,
otherwise I would need to find him a Crown Prince.
Miss Ming,
Tingzhou trusts only you for now.
So,
you have to do us
a favor.
What is it?
Miss Ming,
can you please help to
talk to Tingzhou during this period of time
as princess.
Try to guide him to do the psychological therapy.
Mr. Mu must have gotten the psychogenic amnesia.
Patients usually
launch self-defense mechanism after
suffering from a painful strike.
They would erase all the memories
which caused their pain.
Is it because he could not accept the fact that
the princess killed herself?
So that he chose to forget
what happened after.
It is reasonable that you say so.
Do you have any specific
treatment plan?
We can try hypnosis to
pull him back to the reality from the play.
I disagree.
He would resist badly if
we push him too hard.
He would strongly resist if we
use hypnosis as a treatment method.
So do you mean
there is nothing we can do?
I have something in my mind.
What is it?
Look,
he does not trust us now.
But he truly trusts the princess.
Mr. and Mrs. Mu,
I would love to help Mr. Mu.
But I feel
it is like quench a thirst with poison
if I do this as the princess.
It's a band-aid at best.
Most importantly,
I don't have the confidence to pull Mr. Mu out of the play.
Safe belt.
Miss, fasten your safe belt.
Don't think too much.
We cannot
help anything.
It's right that you have turned them down.
I am alright.
I am just...
I am just a little sad.
It turns out
there is nothing I can help.
If there is any way to
help Mr. Mu get better,
I would definitely do it.
But...
I understand you deeply,
but you cannot take over
this responsibility.
Maybe we have been worrying too much.
He would possibly memorize everything by
tomorrow morning.
Maybe...
I asked you to eat
not kill yourself.
Look at you,
how much you have gotten this weak.
When would you stop the resistance?
I would do whatever you say
only if you
let the princess go.
Grand Tutor,
please look at this world carefully.
Look at the cars on the road,
and the planes in the sky.
Think it through,
if we came up with all of these,
would it be very easy for us to exterminate the Ning Dynasty?
Then why would I trouble myself
to catch you and the princess.
Although my knowledge is limited,
I know that seeing is believing is not entirely true
in this world.
Mu,
please tell me what can I do to help.
I got nothing here.
Grand Tutor, can you tell me
how did you get this scar?
It is not written in the play about how you got this scar.
If you cannot tell immediately how you
got it.
It means Mu Yun is a imaginary character.
I was hurt by scissors.
Right, it was caused by scissors cut.
Mu, you have gotten your memories back?
My family was in straitened circumstances
when I was young,
I could only share a oil lamp with my mother
when night came.
I read in front of the desk and my mother
tailored and embroidered by my side.
The night fall early on that day,
my mother's eyesight was failing and
cut me accidentally with the scissors in her hand.
What about it?
Anything you want to say?
Well done, Mu.
One hell of a bibliography.
Nobody else can compete.
An endless play cannot demonstrate
a person's life.
You can only get to the princess
with such
despicable manners.
[Grand Chief Cabinet Minister]
Whatever you think,
for me this scar is the witness of our friendship
between me and
Mu Tingzhou.
[Xingqing Lane]
Mate,
you must have earned a lot of money by acting.
Sharing some money with us
should not be a problem, right?
Your senior is speaking to you, you cannot hear?
Wait for your butt to be kicked later.
Why are you standing there?
Let's run!
-Go after them! -Let's go!
Stop running!
Stop there!
There is nothing we can do, just crawl!
I would have gotten off if it was not for you.
Good for you by burning the bridge after crossing it.
It's wrong that I saved you?
Get in here!
You ran? You ran?
Let's get out of here, let's leave!
Mu Tingzhou!
Mu Tingzhou, are you OK?
Mu Tingzhou.
Mu Tingzhou,
if it was not for what you did,
my face would be ruined
even though my eye would not be blind.
So,
I owe you.
Otherwise, who would abandon his family business and
become an entertainment agent for you?
What is entertainment agent?
It's your house steward.
If I were Mu Tingzhou,
I must have became enemies
with you after this,
and asked you to stay away from me.
Tingzhou said the same thing, and you
are still saying you are not him?
Grand Tutor,
have you ever thought that
if everything we said is true,
if you are really confused by your memories?
Have you ever thought
that everything in this world
including you and me are
living in the delusion and
not knowing about it.
I just wake up ahead of all of you
and find out I am Mu Yun,
not Mu Tingzhou.
Even there is only one in ten million of the chance,
I would rather believe my own inference.
If people cannot even believe themselves,
they would live in fears
and cannot have a peaceful life.
Never mind, never mind...
Let's jump out of this dead loop.
How about
an exchange of mutually beneficial terms?
I would like to hear about that.
Let's do in this way,
we can each take one step back.
From now on,
we will treat you as Grand Tutor Mu.
But in exchange,
I want you to believe that
you are taken by an invisible power
to a few hundred years later.
Stop treating us with this hostile attitude,
will you?
What's my interests?
Under this circumstance,
I assure you I can do my best to satisfy
your need.
Let me leave this place immediately
and give me a place to live in alone.
No more restrictions to my freedom.
No problem.
And most importantly,
I want to keep in touch with the princess at any time
to protect her by myself.
This...
Ming Wei.
Here, take a seat.
What would you like to drink?
A cup of coffee, please.
Okay.
Ming Wei.
I will say it directly.
Tingzhou needs your help very much now.
I hope you can change your mind
and help him.
If there are other things that I can do
I will do.
But...
I understand.
Actually I agree with what
you said at the hospital.
This is the same way as injecting morphine.
And it can't cure the root of the disease
but fueling his addiction.
But Tingzhou's condition
is unusual.
There are no precedents.
No one can assure
which way is helpful for him,
right?
Before you refuse again,
please take a look at this first.
[I was born with a low social status, I do not dare to have relationship with you.]
This is after Tingzhou's accident
what I found in his notebook.
It is written the
notes of every show of yours.
[Princess Ming Hua was looking at him boldly.]
Has he ever shown this to you?
[Script Note]
These are the notes he took for me.
Why wouldn't he show me
or tell me about it?
Tingzhou is just like this.
Many people said he is cold
and unkind.
But that is because
few people can enter his heart.
Now
I don't want to hide it from you.
Tingzhou has done many things for you.
But he is unwilling to tell you.
When you shot the scene of Grand Tutor leaving the capital,
In order to help you immerse into the emotion,
he deliberately ignore you at the scene.
What happened today?
What is wrong?
You offend him?
How dare I?
Later, you were upset because of Cheng Yao.
He asks a leave for you from the director
to help you resolve the problem.
[Script Note]
Did you know
why would the Grand Tutor forget about the following plots?
The doctor said
that is because he is unwilling to accept the ending that
the princess committed suicide.
The death of princess
is his scar for life.
None of us would
put the pressure of helping him to recover his memory on you.
We just hope he will not close himself again.
Even if
it means he has to be the Grand Tutor for life.
It is still much better than to be
a mute man who does not talk for life.
[Script Note]
[At this stage, the psychological status of Princess Ming Hua has slight difference with that at the beginning of the story.]
At this stage,
compared with at the beginning of the story,
Princess Ming Hua has some emotional changes.
She is no longer the princess who has nothing to worry about.
She is filled with love.
And at the same time, the complexity in the court
makes her more mature.
It is me.
Mr. Mu, we are ready
for you to start shooting.
-OK. -OK.
[Princess Ming Hua Love of Grand Tutor Mu Yun]
[Shanghai Deda Hospital]
Mu Tingzhou, who was in hospital for a car accident
was just discharged from the hospital.
He appeared with no damage.
[Shutting down]
Ming Wei, sorry for
disturbing.
Come in, please.
Come in.
Greetings, Your Highness.
No.
Free of charge. Free of charge.
I thought we have agreed not to do this.
Right.
Your Highness is royal,
how can you live in such a small house.
Grand Tutor,
this is already a quite commodious room here.
Tingzhou insisted on seeing your place.
This...
It is fine, it is fine.
Mr. Mu,
I am good here.
Your Highness, do you live here alone?
I am with my sister.
She lives with me.
Sister?
Your Highness is the only daughter of His Majesty.
Where this sister comes from?
Where is this woman?
What does she want
to fake her identity and come to you?
No, Ming Qiao treats me well.
She has been accompanying me and taking care of me.
So,
is she your maid?
Grand Tutor.
I have told you.
In this society,
everyone is equal.
There are no maids now.
If there are no maids around Your Highness,
who is going to wash clothes, cook meals
clean and run errands for Your Highness?
Well, that....
I have arms and legs,
I don't need anyone to serve me.
Why do you stare at me?
Your Highness is royal,
how could you let her tailor her own clothes and burn wood?
You are mistaken.
Well, that...
I just buy clothes and order take aways,
It is not that hard as Mr. Mu has imagined.
Your Highness lives a hard life without knowing it which
makes me even more ashamed.
I have disappointed the late Emperor.
I...
even death cannot atone for the offense.
Don't do this, don't do this.
Grand Tutor, how about this?
I could ask Tingzhou's nanny Auntie Zhao
to take care of everything for Your Highness.
What do you think about this?
No need.
In my opinion,
I should take care of Your Highness by myself.