["California Love" by DW3 playing]
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Uh... ♪
- [chattering]
- [laughing]
♪ California... ♪
[Lucifer] It's a hell of a choice you and
the other angels have to make, brother.
The Silver City must be all abuzz.
Lucifer or Michael? I mean,
for you it's obvious, though, isn't it,
given the brotherhood we've forged
together carousing on Earth for millennia?
[laughs]
So, what's it gonna be, Jophiel?
Uh, I'll have a Red Bull vodka, yo.
[chuckles]
No, I mean for God.
[hesitates] No, you're right.
You're right. A drink first.
Excuse us, love.
I actually ordered you
something rather special.
You got Tito's?
I said special.
Grey Goose?
It's Belisario Viscount.
It's one of, if not the finest,
vodkas in the world,
1.3 million... never mind, just try it.
[grunts, mutters]
Ooh!
That's hype, yo. Mmm!
- Hype indeed.
- Mmm.
As I was saying,
I'm assuming you're Team Lucifer.
Yeah, uh, about that.
For sure, you and I,
we've always been tight.
And I'll never forget the time
you de-pantsed Napoleon.
- Little bitch-ass started spazzing.
- [laughing]
But you as God, bro, yeah...
I'm not so sure.
Well, it's true I haven't always
behaved in the most godly of ways,
but let's be fair, I've also been
a victim of Michael's smear campaign
for the last millennia.
You saying you didn't, like,
lead a full-on rebellion against Dad?
I'm saying, I'm not that guy anymore.
Being here on Earth has changed me.
It's given me the skills
and experience to do the job.
So...
can I count on your support, bro?
Dude, what's the catch?
- There's no catch.
- Come on, Luce, it's you.
There's always a catch.
The catch is
if I'm not God, then Michael will be.
What could be worse than that?
Michael's not that bad.
Sure, he's got no chill,
but he's been up in the Silver City
this whole time, at Dad's side.
He's, like, practically already in charge.
Exactly. Whispering in Dad's ear,
making him think he was
losing his powers in the first place,
all so he could take over now.
Yeah, Michael's kind of a dick.
He's a massive dick.
But he keeps the trains running, you know?
He... [groans]
Are you seriously telling me
that Michael has got your vote
because... because he's the Devil you know?
Do you have any idea
how ironically infuriating that is?
Sorry, Luce, I just don't see you as...
[blows]...God material.
[chuckles] What's up, girl?
Hey, cool if I hang for a while?
Everything's comped, right?
Love you, bro.
["More" by Sorry playing]
♪ I want more and more and more and more ♪
♪ I want most ♪
So what does being God's consultant
actually look like?
Look like? I don't quite follow.
Well, yeah, I've just been thinking
about this next chapter in my... our lives
and what it entails.
I mean, do I get to pick my own hours, or...
You can do whatever you want. [chuckles]
Well, do I need
to pull Trixie out of school?
It's mid-semester, not the best timing.
I mean, can I commute?
- Or does it not work that way?
- [sighs]
- Oh, God, does this mean I have to die?
- No, no, of course not.
And there's plenty of time to figure out
logistics when and if I become God.
Right, yeah, you're right.
I'm just trying to wrap my mind around
what all of this means, the weight of it.
Detective, you haven't handed in
your two week notice yet, have you?
No, not yet.
But I will, I mean...
You don't think
I'm getting cold feet, do you?
- My... my feet are warm as ever.
- [sighs]
Right, well,
maybe just chill them a smidge
because I'm not sure
I can convince my siblings
I'm the right angel for the God job.
Lucifer.
If anyone in the entire universe
can persuade them, it's you.
[sighs] No, you're right.
You're right.
What was I thinking? [laughs]
Shall we, future Mrs. G? [laughs]
[camera shutter clicking]
[Dan] Wow.
Quite the scene.
[Ella] I know.
I was kind of looking forward to
cracking open a nice bottle of zin later.
Now, not so much.
I get it.
Speaking of wine,
you know who'd be
a great partner to enjoy some wine?
- Um...
- My old partner.
Wow.
- Really smooth transition there, Dan.
- [chuckles]
Come on, just hear me out, okay?
- [sighs]
- Please.
- [sighs] Fine.
- Great.
So my good buddy, Carol Corbett...
- He's got a girl's name? I'm out.
- Yeah, but he's a guy and he's a good one.
We were partnered up in the academy.
- But then he had to move back East.
- Immature flight risk. Strike two.
He went back
to help his mother when she got sick.
But now, he's in town,
doesn't really know anybody,
and I don't know, I got this hunch.
I think you guys would hit it off.
Dan.
I appreciate the offer.
I really, really do, but I just...
The truth is, I'm finally at peace
with everything that happened,
and with myself, getting back to neutral,
and I really don't want
to throw a dude into the mix.
I get it.
I just think that you deserve someone
equally as great as you are.
That's it.
Aww.
- Think about it.
- [sighs]
What a tragedy.
Oh, I know, it's always sad when someone...
You're talking about the wine, aren't you?
Heartbreaking, yes.
Who's the victim?
Our oenophile is Jonathan Donnelly, 53,
a tech in the medical examiner's office.
Cause of death,
two gunshots to the chest, .45 caliber.
What about the bruises?
[Ella] Well,
it looks like he was tied down
and forced to drink wine for
a couple of hours before he was shot.
So you're saying he was water-Bordeaux-ed.
- [chuckles] That's actually kind of funny.
- Oh! Ah!
Do we know why he was here?
- Yeah, this is his wine locker.
- [Lucifer] Don't be ridiculous.
A man of the departed's stature and income
could never afford
such an exquisite wine collection.
- Great point.
- Yes.
I'll look into his financials.
[Chloe] Anything else?
So we also found a partial shoe print
from a wine puddle over there.
I doubt there's enough
to match with anything.
But we did get the victim's phone,
and a few days ago,
he got a really mean text
from someone named Mo.
"You screwed me. You're gonna pay."
I'll check the LUDs
and see who the number belongs to.
Thanks, Ella.
Hey.
What?
He's not gonna need it.
[chuckles]
No, while Ella runs the numbers, um,
there's just something I need to do.
Right.
I just wanted you all
to hear it from me first,
that I just put in my two weeks notice
because I'm retiring.
[crowd murmuring]
Um, many of my very best memories
have happened right here.
The good, the bad, the crazy. [chuckles]
[chuckling]
I know that the work we all do
can be incredibly challenging,
but I wouldn't want
to do it with anyone else.
And I appreciate
each and every one of you, so...
[inhales]
...it's not goodbye.
It's just goodbye for now. All right?
Thank you.
Did you know about this?
No.
But I got a pretty good idea
what it's all about. [sighs]
Or should I say who it's about?
- Hey.
- Hey, Dan.
- I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
- Oh, no, it's okay.
I get it. I think. [chuckles]
It's just...
- Wow. Wow.
- I know.
[chuckles] Ah!
I'm so excited for you, Chloe.
Thank you.
I, on the other hand,
am very mucho not excited for you.
I don't wanna solve crimes without you.
Come on, Decker, retire?
Is this really how it's gonna end?
What, you gonna take up scrapbooking?
You gonna foster cats, hmm?
I'm actually helping Lucifer
take over the, um, family business.
So you're both leaving?
Mm-hmm.
Cheers?
[shouts in Spanish]
[sighs]
This was my choice.
[Ella groans]
Sorry.
It's just...
Florida? You guys, that is so far.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's where
Lucifer's family business is, right?
- Uh...
- We'll be a, um... [clears throat]
...a tad north of Florida,
but, you know,
I'm still gonna be here for you.
I'm always gonna be around, you know,
but from a distance.
At least, I think that's how it works.
And, um, no need to worry.
For now, let's focus on the case.
Uh, did we find out
who sent the threatening text?
Mm-hmm. Odetta Watson.
Apparently, she's a psychic
with an office on Highland.
Oh, maybe she can divine us some clues.
Yeah, yeah, find out if I'm acquitted
of your murder after you abandon me!
[Lucifer sighs]
Let us all just breathe, open our chakras.
[Lucifer] Mind if I ask a few questions
before you get to yours?
- [Chloe] Mm-hmm.
- [Odetta] Shh! Listen.
The spirits are very loud today.
Yes, I think I can hear them.
Yes.
[Lucifer] My dad did give
some humans the gift, you know.
Maybe this is one of the real ones.
[Odetta] Excuse me.
Nothing.
Now...
Mmm!
I can feel your great uncertainty
in this time of change.
[gasps]
You are worried about a health issue.
[Lucifer] Um...
That could potentially develop due
to all the stress you are having over a...
professional opportunity?
Yes, I'm up for a big promotion
in the family business.
Right. Rig... oh, I can see it clearly now.
But there is strife within the family.
Right. 'Cause all families are functional.
And it seems you are not
the only one vying for the job.
Amazing. Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- My no-good, manipulative bastard
of a brother is trying to steal it out
from under me. [chuckles]
In fact,
there are just a few swing votes left.
Can you tell me how to convince
my siblings I'm the right man for the job?
[Odetta sighs]
[groans]
You must lean into your strengths.
Lean into my strengths, that's genius!
[snaps fingers]
[laughs] I'm sorry.
[clears throat] Go ahead.
[Odetta] Hmm.
I am sensing
you are the skeptic in the relationship.
How is she even doing this? [chuckles]
So, why are you here?
We are here about Jonathan Donnelly.
Who is that?
He's the guy that you've
been sending threatening texts to,
and don't bother denying it.
Your phone records show
repeated calls and texts to and from him.
Oh. That Jonathan, yes.
Yes, I didn't know you meant him.
I have read for him in the past.
If you're a real psychic,
surely you would've known that.
Actually,
my specialty is channeling the dead,
and since Jonathan is very much alive...
- Actually, Jonathan is very much dead.
- [Lucifer] Hmm.
Tortured and shot in his wine locker
shortly after receiving
your threatening text.
Hang on, Jonathan is dead?
- And you think I did it?
- How did you not see that coming?
Because she's not a psychic.
She's a con artist.
You advertise that you can locate
lost items from dead relatives,
and you know who'd be
the perfect accomplice in that scam?
A tech from the ME's office,
who has access
to bodies and their valuables.
That is absurd. I would never.
One call to a judge,
I subpoena your records.
I get proof,
and you go down for fraud and murder.
Hang on now.
I didn't kill anybody. Okay?
Why would I kill Jonathan?
Our hustle was genius.
He would steal a valuable off a body,
plant it somewhere and then use targeted
online ads to direct the family to use me.
Mm-hmm. And then you'd magically
find the family heirloom.
Yep.
You may not be a real medium,
but that is an excellent scam. Respect.
Oh, thank you.
You're very welcome.
But you see why I would be
a total idiot to stop that money train.
- Right?
- Where were you last night at 8:00 p.m.?
Giving a reading...
to a programming exec
at Fox.
Oh, good luck with that.
So, just say that story checks out,
do you know of anyone else
who would wanna hurt Jonathan?
Maybe one of the other families
found out that their stuff was being sold?
What do you mean "other families"?
The ones that didn't bite.
Jonathan would give whatever he took from
their dead relative to a fence named TJ,
and then TJ would sell it
on the black market.
Great. What's TJ's last name?
I don't know.
But I know that he works out of Hollywood.
Helpful.
[Dan] Boom!
Rainbow Lasso, which means I get to
take Mr. Narwhal and put him in my stable.
No, Dad, you can only throw Rainbow Lasso
if she's in your hand
at the beginning of your turn.
Oh, come on.
You know what? These rules are confusing.
Or maybe I'm just better
at building unicorn armies.
- [scoffs] Yeah, right.
- I win.
What?
Come on! Again?
- Want another shot at the unicorn title?
- [scoffs] Yeah.
But I go first because
I'm wearing the most colorful clothes.
[sighs]
Okay, fine.
I'll lend you my glitter scarf,
and then you can go first.
But you have to wear it.
[chuckles] I promise.
Okay. And I have to go find it.
[Dan] Cool. I'll clean up our mess.
[knock on door]
[hums]
Hey, what's up, man?
Hey, hey, hey, hey. [chuckles]
- Dan, I figured it out.
- What's that?
Uh, what I'm gonna do here
now that I've decided to stay.
- Oh, okay.
- [sighs]
- I'm gonna become a policeman.
- [both laugh]
I mean, I really like helping people,
and what better way to do that
than putting away criminals?
[both laugh]
You wanna be a cop?
Won't it be great?
I mean, we can even work together one day.
Oh, yeah, yeah, an angel and a detective
solving crimes, makes total sense.
[laughs, stops]
- [clears throat]
- You don't think it's a good idea.
No, it's just that...
Bro, you're a freaking angel.
- [sighs]
- You were almost God.
I mean, there's gotta be something
that better suits your skill set.
So you think it's a bad idea
because I wouldn't be any good at it.
No, that's not what I said.
It's just that...
there are different kinds of people.
Different kinds of jobs.
[scoffs]
You know something? Of all people,
I really thought you'd be the one
that would be most excited for me.
- Amenadiel.
- [door opens]
Okay, that... that's not what I mea...
[door closes]
It's not what I meant.
[Saraqael] Why bother, Lucifer?
You're not getting my vote.
Yeah, I supported you once
in the rebellion,
but then I had to suffer
Dad's passive-aggressive wrath.
And try climbing out
of that proverbial doghouse.
And it certainly doesn't
help your case that even Jophiel,
who, let's face it, is an idiot,
even he thinks your pitch is lacking.
- Truth is I'm only here as a courtesy.
- [both chuckle]
Saraqael. Sara.
What is it you truly desire?
You seriously think I'm going to fall
for your silly little parlor trick?
[chuckles] A not-so-wise woman recently
suggested I lean into my strengths.
Too bad she didn't
teach you how to cut your losses.
I learned I needed to ask
not what the angels can do for you,
but what can you do for the angels?
I have no idea what that means.
It means you're right.
I shouldn't try and convince you
I'd be a better God than Michael.
What I should do is
the one thing I can do better than anyone
and that is grant favors.
So, again, I humbly ask you,
what is it you desire?
[scoffs] I'm an angel, Lucifer,
I'm totally above the base passions
and petty desires
that humans fall prey to.
Oh, my God,
is that Michael Voltaggio?
You mean
Top Chef champion Michael Voltaggio?
- Why, yes, it is.
- [laughing]
- Hello, Michael.
- You're Lucifer's sister, right?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Michael, is that really you in the flesh?
I mean, you...
I just... I can't, I just, I...
You! [laughs]
Your egg yolk gnocchi is divine,
and I should know, because I am an angel.
But you, you are such a bad boy,
and I am feeling hungry. [cackles]
[laughs] Anyway, Michael, would you
excuse us for just a moment?
- Sure, I'll just be over at the bar.
- [Saraqael] Okay.
So, I have arranged for you
to have the full Volt VIP experience.
A Friday night reservation for life
at Estuary, his new restaurant in DC,
Michael's special recipe
for rice pilaf, and...
- ...his personal phone number.
- [gasps]
In exchange,
all I ask is for your support.
Wow, I mean,
I gotta hand it to you, Lucifer.
It's gonna be
really hard to say no after that.
Excellent. [chuckles]
Amazing, thank you.
[sighs] Well,
truth be told, Michael owes me.
How else do you think he won Top Chef?
That squab was inedible.
But still, I mean,
this is a really big favor to ask.
- Mmm.
- [gasps] You must really wanna be God.
Actually, why do you want it so badly?
Um, well, you know,
because who... who wouldn't want it?
[chuckles] Right.
[inhales] You know what? I actually
need to think about this a little more.
- Saraqael, I...
- I should go. [chuckles]
[huffs]
["Heretic" by Stop Dead playing]
♪ I'm a heretic
Don't wanna feel any shame ♪
♪ I start taking them down
And it all goes away ♪
♪ Everything is fine... ♪
Michael Voltaggio is the worst.
What are you talking about?
My campaign to become God,
it's hit another snag. It's a disaster.
It can't be that bad.
[Lucifer] Well, at least it's not boring.
Unlike this, our final case.
I mean, how many fences called TJ
can there be in Hollywood?
We've seen six already.
Well, we only have five to go,
and come on, you're not gonna miss this?
- Even a little bit?
- I'd rather have a colonoscopy.
[exhales] Well,
for me, it's the shoe leather,
the day-to-day chasing down
the boring long shots, you know? It's...
That's the fun part. I am gonna miss it.
You know what I am gonna miss?
That look in your eyes right now.
May... maybe you shouldn't quit.
What?
No, I want to.
I wanna be with you.
[exhales]
[door creaks]
[Chloe] Who leaves their door open in LA?
[Lucifer] No one. Lock's broken.
[scoffs] Hello.
Look at all these stolen goodies.
Oh, looks like we found the right TJ.
Oh! Vintage Rolex.
What sort of idiot thief would
leave this behind? It's worth a fortune.
Huh!
I bet this boot mark is gonna match
the one we found at the wine cellar.
Well, whoever searched this place
was definitely looking
for something in particular.
- I wonder if they found it.
- [man] Found what?
[Chloe] TJ Ross?
Who wants to know?
Detective Decker, LAPD. We're here to talk
about the death of Jonathan Donnelly.
Stay away. I... I don't wanna hurt you.
You? Hurt us? Adorable. [chuckles]
Come along now, TJ.
[TJ grunts]
[exclaims]
[groans]
[panting]
What was that?
[Ella] Size 13. Taken from the rubble
at TJ Ross' house.
Bigger than any of his shoes,
but it does match the shoe print
we found at the wine locker.
So whoever killed Jonathan Donnelly
also ransacked TJ's place?
They had to be looking for something
Jonathan stole off a corpse.
Given what was left behind,
I'd say they haven't found it yet.
But what is this object?
Who wants it? And why?
And where does our killer
buy his enormous boots?
It's all a mystery, isn't it?
A thrilling, tangled web
of discovery and contradiction
that you two are never gonna see because
you're running off to stupid Alabama!
She thinks we're going north of Florida.
We're definitely not going there.
- Alabama's actually really nice.
- You would think that.
Okay, everybody.
Let's focus on the killer.
Our priority now is TJ Ross.
We find him,
we find what the killer wants,
that might lead us to him.
So Lucifer and I will focus
on his friends and family.
And there are TJ's usual clients.
Yeah, but the client list we found
on TJ's computer runs in the hundreds.
I foresee great boredom in my future.
You know what?
Why don't I get started on that list?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I mean, it's your last case.
Least I can do is
help with the grunt work.
- Thank you, Daniel. Take one for the team.
- I got it.
- Hey, you.
- [Ella] Yeah.
You forgot this.
- What's that?
- It's my friend Carol's phone number.
- Dan, no!
- Come on, please.
You've gotta call him, please.
Please, for me.
Mi hermanita, por favor.
Yes! You won't regret it, I promise.
- Mm-hmm. He better be cute!
- [Dan] He's beautiful.
We still have to figure out what was
going on with that superhuman kick.
Are we dealing with someone celestial?
I don't know,
but I have a theory. I can check it out.
[sighs] Okay.
You go find out what TJ is,
and I'll track down where he is.
- Right.
- Okay.
[Mazikeen] Oh.
What do you think?
Mask?
No mask?
Maybe...
no mask?
Yeah.
You're right.
Nothing says wrath like my demon face.
[exhales] But I still feel like I need
something that says, you know...
"I've returned to fiercely
rule over you for all of eternity."
But like, not in a needy way.
Think murderously aspirational.
Well, I...
I like the blue one.
Yeah, you're not helping, Linda.
Okay, is it possible that
you're fixating on this outfit because
you're really worried
about something else?
Well, I am worried that Lucifer won't pull
his head out of his ass and become God.
No, I was actually thinking
that you might be concerned
about becoming the Queen of Hell.
What would worry me about that?
Well, maybe that you have a soul now.
And you might be worried that that soul
might hinder the joy you once felt
by torturing others.
Yeah.
The whole soul thing, it isn't for me.
I'm the one who grew it, so I'm just
gonna let it slowly suffocate and die.
Like I did with Chad.
Who's Chad?
Doesn't matter.
Okay, so, um, Maze, listen.
You grew a soul through the relationships
that you nurtured here on Earth.
Through the moments that you shared
with people who care about you.
Like me.
Are you really sure that you wanna just
suffocate
the wonderful times we've shared?
Oh, Linda.
I know what you're doing.
You don't want me to go so you're
covertly trying to get into my head.
No, I'm overtly trying to get
in your head. You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
- [door opens]
- The alternative is much worse.
Oh, there you are.
What are you wearing?
You look a bony xylophone.
Uh, Doctor,
would you excuse us just a moment?
I thought you'd never ask.
[Mazikeen sighs]
Have you heard of
any demons roaming the Earth lately?
Why?
There appears to be
a human with super strength
and a hurdling technique to match,
running around Hollywood.
I haven't heard of any.
But you never know.
The throne of Hell is empty, after all.
If you are concerned,
there is any easy way
for you to get the Underworld in check.
Yes, yes, get elected God
so I can make you Queen, I get it.
Just keep an eye out for rogue demons
and don't worry about the election.
I have it handled.
[Mazikeen] Do you?
Zadkiel is your last swing vote,
and he hates you.
Yes, he does.
But I have a plan.
I'm going to tell him something
I've never told anyone before.
What's that?
I was wrong.
I know, it's a miracle.
But as much as it pains me to say,
my rebellion was ill-conceived.
Why? Because
I did it for the wrong reasons.
I rebelled out of anger at Father,
out of a desire to prove
that I was better than him,
but I've changed.
I've spent my time on Earth
growing, getting over my...
[chuckles]...my Daddy issues.
I know how monumental his job
actually was and is now.
Those are big shoes to fill,
but I promise you, Zadkiel,
I will give it my absolute best.
Lucifer.
Wow!
That was well spoken.
Emotionally evolved.
Well... [chuckles]
Impressive.
Impressive enough to possibly
win over the Angel of Righteousness?
I mean, no.
It's always gonna be a no.
[chuckles] You don't wanna meet
Michael Voltaggio, do you?
I'm just here for the whiskey.
Jophiel said you bribed with top shelf.
[laughs]
And to watch you grovel.
Of course it was
never gonna work, was it?
All that nonsense about making peace
with Father and growing as an angel.
[chuckles]
Mm. You know,
the crazy thing is, it's all true, but...
[sighs]...it's not the whole truth.
You really wanna know
why I'm doing all of this?
Why I'm trying to become God?
I'm doing it for love. [laughing]
And it gets worse.
I'm doing it for the love of a human.
I am trying to be God
so that I can finally be worthy of her.
So there you have it, enjoy the top shelf.
[Zadkiel] This woman...
is she the gift Father made for you?
Her name is Chloe Decker,
and she is much more than that!
So yes,
I am doing this
for the wrong reasons again,
but do you know what? I don't care.
All I care about is her.
Which is why
I have to make this happen, and I will.
No matter what the costs.
With or without your vote.
[knocks]
Brooke Frier?
I'm Mrs. Frier.
Oh, I'm Detective Espinoza, with the LAPD.
Listen, we know that
you were a client of TJ Ross.
I'm not here
to trip you up about that, Mrs. Frier.
We have information
regarding a possible threat.
Somebody's after
one of TJ's stolen items,
and they've already killed somebody
trying to get it.
That's horrible.
Yeah. Yes, ma'am, it is,
and if I can find you,
well, then the killer can find you.
So I'm wondering if you've noticed
anything out of the ordinary?
You know, any strangers
lurking around or anything like that.
No, I haven't.
And if that's all, I should go.
Got a roast in the oven.
Sure.
Yeah, absolutely, thank you for your time.
You have a wonderful day.
Thank you.
[dialing]
[rings]
Hey.
Espinoza.
A possible home invasion.
Layton Street, Hancock Park.
Request immediate backup.
- [gun cocks]
- Hang up the phone.
[Ella] Two gunshots
to the chest, .45 caliber.
Same MO as Jonathan Donnelly.
I'd say it's definitely the same killer.
- [Lucifer sighs]
- [Chloe] Thanks.
Were they able to ping Dan's phone?
No. They must have turned it off.
I can't believe he came here alone.
I should have gone with him.
No, no, no, Ella, we can't go there.
Not yet, you know.
This house was ransacked too,
so maybe the killer
didn't find what they were looking for.
Which means they would
have incentive to keep Dan alive.
- Right. Right.
- Right.
So let's just do our job
and let's find him.
Okay.
Look at those flowers.
Looks like there was a scuffle.
He must have fought back.
[Ella] Guys.
He doesn't even have his phone.
This is bad.
No, no, this is Daniel.
He's... he's more than capable.
You're right.
Hey, hey.
I think there's something there, too.
Yeah.
Definitely seems like
there was some kind of fight.
Hey, you guys.
It looks like
there's something down there.
[Chloe gasps]
[exhales]
He left us a clue.
Dog tags.
French Foreign Legion, to be exact.
Been using the same one since the '40s.
- Got a name?
- [Ella] Yep.
Sayeed Faisal. Algerian.
Dishonorably discharged.
He's been linked to a ruthless
mercenary group led by this guy,
Vincent Le Mec.
We got running guns, kidnapping, murder,
so he's impossible to find
because they never leave witnesses.
This is all my fault.
I've been so focused on finding TJ
that I forgot the detective work,
and now Dan's...
No. You said it yourself.
We can't go there.
Exactly.
We are gonna find him, you guys.
We're gonna find him.
Who took Dan?
I'll kill him. Hmm, this guy?
Who is he?
Vincent Le Mec, he's a French mercenary,
and we have no idea where he is.
I'll find him.
I have no doubt, Mazikeen,
but time is of the utmost essence.
We need all the help we can get.
You know who's good at finding criminals.
Other criminals.
Lucky for us,
there are a lot who owe me favors.
Which favors do you want me to call in?
[sighs] All of them.
[shouts]
[groans]
[panting]
Where is this man?
I have no idea who he is.
[grunting]
What about now, hmm?
[grunts, exhales]
I don't know.
- I swear.
- [Vincent] Hmm?
And this?
Hmm?
Why are you showing me a grave?
Is this supposed
to be some sort of threat?
[chuckles]
- [gun cocks]
- [Vincent] You're lying.
- You're lying!
- [groans]
I'm not.
[gasps, panting]
- [grunts, groans]
- [cell phone rings]
Hello.
Police?
[speaks French]
- Okay, d'accord.
- [beeps]
So we've got a guy with superhuman
strength running around LA.
Maze and I don't think he's a demon.
Could this be Michael-related?
No, I talked to Remiel.
Michael's still in the Silver City.
Yes, but couldn't TJ be doing his bidding?
But why would Michael
use a lowly jewelry fence?
And it still doesn't explain
TJ's super strength.
Or how this could even
help Michael win an election.
Got a list of places
the mercenaries could be.
Great, how many?
- A lot. [sighs]
- [Chloe] Okay, we divide and conquer.
The angels take the furthest location,
and this time, nobody goes alone.
Désolé, monsieur, it's not personal.
[Dan mutters]
What?
[Dan mutters] I'm tired.
What did you say?
[grunting]
[shouts]
- [snaps]
- [grunting]
[panting]
[gunshot]
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
[sighs]
[man speaking indistinctly
over police scanner]
All right, you take the east end.
[coughing]
[Chloe gasps] Dan.
- Dan.
- Chloe.
It's okay.
You're okay.
We're gonna get you help. Cacuzza!
C-Caleb.
What? Stop.
Save your breath. Save your breath.
Get help, now!
[Dan] Listen. Listen to me.
I held on to tell you, it's Caleb.
- Caleb.
- Okay.
Okay, Caleb. Okay, I hear you.
Listen to me,
you're gonna be okay, all right?
- You're gonna be okay.
- [panting]
- It's too... it's too late.
- Just breathe.
It's not too late, stay with me, breathe.
Breathe. Breathe.
Tell Trixie...
No!
- Tell Trixie that I love her.
- No.
[sniffles] Tell her that I'm gonna miss
making unicorn armies with her. [laughs]
No, Dan, no, you tell her yourself, okay?
You hear me? You stay with me.
Stay with me.
Look at me, breathe. Breathe.
- I'm so scared.
- Don't be scared, just breathe.
[panting]
Goodbye, Chloe. Goodbye.
- [Chloe] No, baby, don't go.
- [gasping]
[Chloe] Don't go.
[sobbing]
Here!
- [man] Come over here!
- In here!
[shouts] Come here!
- [man] Go, go!
- [crying] Stay with me, stay with me.
["Wish We Had More Time"
by Alice Boman playing]
- [EMTs chattering]
- [crying continues]
- [Chloe groans] Stay, stay.
- ♪ I am lying here... ♪
Hey.
- ♪ In the blue light... ♪
- [Chloe sobs]
[siren wailing]
♪ Waiting for you ♪
♪ To turn around ♪
♪ And when you take me ♪
♪ In your arms ♪
♪ Make me forget ♪
♪ It's for the last time ♪
♪ I wish we had more time ♪
♪ There's no tomorrow ♪
♪ There's no past ♪
♪ There is nothing ♪
♪ But this feeling ♪
- [Trixie] Where's my dad?
- [shuddering]
[sobbing]
Hi, baby.
- Come here. Come here.
- Where is he? Where's Dad?
[Chloe] Come here, honey.
[Trixie sobbing]
[sobbing] I'm so sorry, baby.
Listen to me, babe.
Daddy's gone, okay?
No, no, you're wrong!
No, go in there and tell him to get up.
Tell him it's time to come home.
[sobbing]
No, no, it's okay, Maze.
Don't cry.
It's gonna be okay. It's not true!
[sobbing]
Please tell me it's not true, Lucifer.
I know you'll tell me
'cause you never lie.
So tell me it's not true.
My dear, sweet child.
I can't.
[sobbing]
I want my daddy!
[gasps] I know, baby. I know. I know.
I know. I'm so sorry.
I know, baby.
Did they get who did this?
Not yet.
Why, Lucy?
Why did this happen?
Foreign mercenaries hunting down
stolen objects from dead bodies.
A supernaturally strong human,
Dan's dying words
about somebody named Caleb.
I don't know.
[inhales] None of it makes sense.
Wait.
- Caleb?
- [sighs]
I think I know what this is about.
[huffs]
[wings flap]
Michael is involved, after all.
[panting] How'd you figure that out?
Caleb.
Lucy, Caleb Mayfield
was the boy who was killed.
I tried to help him.
Yes, I helped you in the aftermath, but...
what does Caleb have to do with Michael?
Before Caleb was buried, I...
I laid my necklace on his body.
You did what?
Somebody obviously came looking for it.
But it wasn't there.
The tech in the coroner's office
must have stolen it from the body.
And Michael hired
the mercenaries to find it,
and then they tortured and killed him,
but he didn't have it either because...
TJ the fence has it.
Which explains his super strength.
It does? How?
Well, think about it.
Every piece
of the Flaming Sword has a power.
Azrael's blade is death,
the hilt, to find love,
and your necklace is
the strength that binds them together,
strength that apparently lends itself
to whoever's in possession of it.
But my necklace has been
in human hands before.
It's never granted
any of them super strength.
Well, the hilt was only activated
when Azrael's blade was on Earth.
I suppose the same
could be true of your necklace.
Wait, but I thought you threw
Azrael's blade into Mom's universe.
I did.
But I also just sent Gabriel there
to send her a message,
and something tells me
she did not return empty-handed.
So Gabriel's working with Michael.
Smallest of our problems, brother.
Biggest being, Michael is trying
to assemble the Flaming Sword.
He's not trying to win an election.
He's trying to win a war.
[panting]
She's finally asleep.
[Lucifer sighs]
- Here.
- No, I can't.
[sobs]
It should have been me,
going to that house.
No, that's what I've been
trying to tell you, Detective.
This is all part of Michael's plan.
This is his fault, not yours.
I just keep playing it
over and over in my mind. I just...
[exhales]
This was my case,
and I let him go alone, and now he's...
[gasps] Please tell me that
this is all for something bigger, please,
that... that you're gonna win,
that you can... you can fix this.
That you're gonna be God.
[exhales] For that to happen,
[sighs]...I'll most likely have to
go to war with Michael, it seems,
and I don't have the greatest track record
when it comes to waging wars in Heaven,
and insult to injury, I didn't manage
to convince a single swing vote.
Zadkiel said no, surprise, surprise.
[inhales, exhales]
Honesty.
The engineer of my demise.
[sniffles] What does that mean?
Well, in a fit of candor,
I told him the real truth
as to why I was doing all of this,
and it went over like a lead balloon.
What's the truth? Why are you doing this?
Why do you wanna be God?
[sniffles]
[sighs] Because if I'm God,
then I'll finally be worthy...
of... of you.
So you're telling me...
[inhales]...that Trixie is in there
right now crying herself to sleep
and the real reason that
she's gonna grow up without a father
is because you still
don't know how I feel about you?
How is that even possible?
[shudders]
If that's the case, Lucifer...
then your brothers
and your sisters are right.
You shouldn't be God.
Excuse me, um, Ella? Are you Ella Lopez?
Yeah.
Hi, I'm...
I'm Carol Corbett.
As in...
The guy that
Dan was trying to set me up with. Right.
Yeah, yeah, um... [chuckles]
Look, I'm sorry to even... [exhales]
You know, I just...
Dan was always
just looking out for me, you know?
Yeah.
Me, too.
I think he was always
looking out for everyone.
Yeah, yeah, he was. [chuckles]
Uh, speaking of which,
there's a friend I need to talk to.
Of course, yeah. [sighs]
Hey, save me a seat, will you?
For sure. I will.
I know.
I can't believe he's gone.
Last time I saw him...
I said some things
that I can never take back.
I know. He told me.
He did?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I was considering becoming a cop and...
I don't think
Dan thought it was a good idea.
[chuckles]
That's where you're wrong, Amenadiel.
That's what I came over here to tell you.
Day he died...
he turned in your application
to the Police Academy.
[both sigh]
At least we both know
he's in a better place now, right?
Yeah.
There's something I have to tell you.
I went to see Dan in Heaven.
Oh.
Let me guess.
Swimming in a vat of chocolate pudding.
He's not there, Lucy.
What?
He's not there.
Dan isn't in Heaven.
I just...
I went to check and...
But that would mean...
No.
No, Daniel dealt with his guilt.
He told me as much.
Lucy, you and I both know that guilt is
much more complicated
and deep-seated than we're even aware of.
That isn't...
[huffs] It's not fair.
None of this is.
When I first arrived
in Los Angeles, I was angry.
[chuckles]
I was angry and confused
about my place in the world.
I didn't know how to connect with people.
But Dan...
Dan did.
And he taught me how to be a good friend.
How to be a good father.
He taught me...
how to be a good man.
Because he was a good man.
The sad thing is
I think he forgot that sometimes,
but he was a good, good man.
Always trying to do right by others.
Always trying to do better.
Even though he was already
the very best of us.
What happened to Dan...
it isn't fair.
And you have every right
to feel angry about it.
But...
you can take comfort in knowing that...
that Dan is in a much better place.
Dan...
you are, and you...
always will be my best friend.
I'm gonna miss you, buddy. [sobs]
I'm really gonna miss you. We all will.
[sobbing]
And, uh...
[sniffles]
...I promise you that whatever happens,
from this day forward,
I will always try and do better.
[sniffles]
[Lucifer sighs]
I found them.
[Ella singing in Spanish]
[in English]
♪ The good times that made us laugh ♪
♪ Outweigh the bad ♪
[Ella singing in Spanish]
[Lucifer in English]
♪ I thought we'd get to see forever ♪
♪ But forever's gone away ♪
♪ It's so hard ♪
♪ To say goodbye ♪
♪ To yesterday ♪
[both in English]
♪ I don't know where this road ♪
♪ Is going to lead ♪
♪ All I know is where we've been ♪
♪ And what we have been through ♪
♪ If we get to see tomorrow ♪
♪ I hope it's worth all the wait ♪
♪ It's so hard to say goodbye ♪
♪ To yesterday ♪
♪ And I'll take with me the memories ♪
♪ To be my sunshine ♪
♪ After the rain ♪
♪ It's so hard ♪
♪ To say goodbye ♪
♪ To yesterday ♪
[man] Ready! Aim! Fire!
♪ It's so hard to say goodbye ♪
♪ To yesterday ♪
We found the people who killed Daniel.
We made them pay.
Okay.
And how did that make you feel?
[huffs]
That's irrelevant.
My feelings don't matter.
Yes, they do.
You're grieving.
It's important to acknowledge that.
[chuckles]
Such astute insight
from the doctor, once again.
You know,
you are very good at what you do.
But your job should simply not exist.
You don't think helping people
cope with pain is important?
I don't think pain should exist.
I see.
But that's life, Lucifer.
Pain is inevitable.
The suffering, that's optional.
[shouts] Do not counsel me
on suffering and inevitability!
There are no words to convince me
that the system isn't broken.
Trixie shouldn't have to suffer the pain
of seeing her father
ripped from her like that,
and... and Daniel shouldn't be de...
Dan should not be dead.
The system is not only broken.
It's unjust.
Lucifer.
You can't control all the bad things
that happen in this world.
Only how they affect you.
That's where you're wrong.
See, there is something I can do.
Before, I wanted to be God
for the wrong reasons, but now,
I no longer want to be God.
I have to be God.
Lucifer, what does that mean?
It means...
[gasps]...that we are going to war.