Yo, boss! Johnny's gotta make water!
No chance, man. Shut up!
Oh, he's peeing!
Johnny's peeing all over the seat!
[prisoner] What are you
fucking around for, man?
[guard] Damn it, Johnny!
[prisoners chattering]
- [guard] Really? What's your problem, man?
- [grunting]
- [straining]
- [prisoner] Get him down!
[grunting]
[shouts]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
[engine revving]
[grunting]
[shouting]
[screaming]
[metal creaking]
- [chattering]
- [laughing]
[piano playing off-key]
[Michael] You know,
I always wondered why a piano.
You're supposed to be the edgy one.
Wouldn't a guitar be more, uh...
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Lucifer! Lucifer. Lucifer.
I am not here to fight.
Oh, well, I am most certainly am!
[panting] Well, then what would happen
to all these poor,
fragile humans, dear brother?
[gasps]
It's all right, everyone!
Just a little brotherly squabble.
[chuckles]
- It's fine. It's fine. Music up.
- [dance music playing]
[Michael] And besides,
I mean, really, what's the point?
I've already won.
I've assembled the Flaming Sword,
and thanks to it, and...
[chuckles]...my charms, of course,
I have got
the majority of angels on my side.
And yet, here you are. Why?
To avoid bloodshed, brother.
To keep our siblings safe. To make peace.
I am here with an offer.
[scoffs]
There is nothing that you could offer me.
Hmm. [chuckles]
What about a throne?
[laughs]
Are you offering me my old job?
I take Heaven. You take Hell.
It's kind of poetic if you think about it.
And, uh, I will let you rule down there
however you see fit.
Oh, gee, thanks, bro.
But been there, done that, tried the veal.
Ah-ah-ah!
But I haven't told you the best part.
Chloe will be down there with you.
I mean, talk about happily ever after.
What are you talking about?
That's impossible.
Even if you become God, you wouldn't have
the power to force her soul down there.
Only someone's guilt
can take them to Hell.
Exactly.
Think about it.
The father of her child is dead
because of a case he was working for her.
Did you do all of this?
Did you have them take Daniel?
No, no, no.
That part was just a very happy accident.
But when they
told me they had him... [laughs]
oh, brother,
I realized I had a golden opportunity.
So you...
you told them to kill Dan?
You're welcome.
- [Lucifer inhales]
- [grunts]
[chuckles] Easy with the temper, brother.
Dan is in Hell because of you!
Well, technically,
it's because of his own guilt,
which he really
should've gotten over by now.
[shouts]
Forget about the past, brother.
Focus on the future.
Your future.
With Chloe.
[chuckles]
[Michael] You need time
to think about it. I get it.
But just so you know,
the vote is tomorrow.
And I'm holding it here on Earth
so you can attend.
You know, because of the whole
"you're banished from Heaven
and would be instantly incinerated
if you returned" thing.
[chuckles] Though,
that would be fun to see.
Brother.
I am offering you
a chance at a happy ending.
I hope you take it.
Linda.
[chuckles]
See?
This is what caring about people gets you.
Sitting around like idiots,
getting all emotional over inanimate junk!
So can we please just stop with
the crybaby bullshit and get this done?
[gasps]
[shouts]
[Linda] Maze.
Maze, honey, it's gonna be okay.
What is that?
[sobbing] It's the T-shirt that Dan...
had to steal from Chloe
after I knocked him out
and dumped him naked at her house.
[sobbing] I still...
I still don't know
how he fit his stupid ass in this thing.
[chuckles, sobbing]
I miss him.
- [crying]
- [Linda] Maze.
[sighs] Okay.
[wailing]
Okay.
It's okay.
It's true.
It's true,
sometimes when you care about people...
you have to go through pain and loss.
But that's the price of joy.
[Amenadiel] She's right, Mazikeen.
In order for none of us to be sad,
we would have had to have never met Dan.
You wouldn't want that. None of us would.
[sobbing] Mnh-mnh.
Like... like when...
when Dan and I
pul... pulverized that gang together.
It was beautiful.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Exactly.
And remembering, um...
sweet times like those...
are what helps heal the hurt.
[Linda] Because trust me...
never loving anyone
is far worse than loss.
[elevator bell dings]
[Lucifer] Thank you for coming, Detective.
- Yeah.
- Um, how's Trixie?
Uh, she's, you know,
she's with my mom and Dan's parents.
She's a strong little girl.
She's just having to be stronger
than she ever should right now.
Listen, I know
that you asked me to come here,
but I just wanna get
something off my chest first. Um...
You know the argument
the other night, it...
It just... we were both stressed,
and, um, it was emotional and...
There's no need, Detective.
You were right.
You were able to say
the thing I couldn't admit to myself.
I wanted to be God for the wrong reasons.
But now I know why I need to be God.
For Dan's sake.
What do you mean?
Uh, please. Sit down, please.
[clears throat]
[Chloe clears throat]
So, Dan's...
Dan's death... [exhales]
Everything that's happened
is all Michael's fault.
He's been assembling
the Flaming Sword to win the war.
So that's why they killed Dan,
to keep us from finding that out?
No.
Michael killed Dan...
so that you would feel guilty.
So that when you die,
you'll go down to Hell.
A twisted bribe to get me
to go back like a good little Devil.
I don't even know...
I don't know what to do with that!
You must refuse to give in.
It's all a manipulation.
Detective, you mustn't feel guilty.
Right. Yeah, okay. [sniffles]
I'll just snap my fingers
and not feel guilty.
- I'm serious, Detective.
- I'm serious too.
That is not how emotions work, Lucifer.
Prove me wrong. Go ahead!
Go on! Just...
[inhales]...feel worthy!
[gasping]
Or you know what?
No, this is better. This is better.
Make yourself vulnerable.
- [Lucifer sighs]
- [chuckles]
- It's easier said than done, isn't it?
- This isn't the same.
[inhales] We can't let Michael win,
and you can't end up like Dan.
What are you talking about,
end up like Dan? Dan's in Heaven.
Lucif...
Where is Dan right now?
Where is he?
Don't make me say it, please.
- Where is he?
- [wings flap]
Who's there?
Michael?
Remiel.
- Lucifer.
- Remi!
[gasping]
She's dead.
Oh, my God.
Michael must have
found out she was our spy
and killed her with the Flaming Sword.
Wait, are there
actual flames on the sword?
Detective, this is hardly the time to
start questioning the rules of celestials,
but, yes, the sword has flames on it.
It makes sense. Don't overthink it.
No, I'm only asking because, look,
there's no burn marks around the wound,
so whatever Michael killed her with,
it couldn't have been flaming.
So he must have just used Azrael's blade.
But when I saw Michael,
he said he had the sword.
If he did, the little show-off would have
used it, which means he's bluffing.
He hasn't found the piece yet.
We don't know where it is.
Michael has an army of angels
to search for him.
Maybe Remiel found out
where the piece was.
You think she was coming to tell us that?
I don't know.
[sniffs]
I don't know. This... [sniffs]
...this could be a clue.
Look, I know it's asking a lot,
but I need the detective one last time.
I need your help.
Of course.
Maybe I can't control my guilt,
but I sure as hell can channel my anger.
Let's take that bastard down.
[huffs, shudders]
Hey, big guy.
You took one of the good ones.
And I'm...
I'm glad he's
with you and everything, but...
I just miss him.
I miss him a lot.
And I know you got
a lot on your plate, and...
[sighs] I know. I know.
Darkness makes the light
shine brighter and everything, but...
it's extra dark right now...
and I'm having a really hard time seeing.
It almost feels like...
you're not even up there anymore.
But... [sighs]
I know
that's totally impossible. [sniffles]
So...
I would really appreciate it...
[inhales]
...if you could just show me the way.
Or at least just... just, you know,
nudge me in the right direction.
Or just...
Okay, what I'm trying to say is just...
just give me some sort of sign,
just let me know that
I'm where I'm supposed to be,
where I need to be. [sniffles]
- [Chloe] Hey.
- Yeah.
[sighs] Thank God you're here.
We're gonna need your help.
- We'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Thanks.
Hmm. Maybe I should run
another sample through mass spec.
- [Chloe] Why?
- Because this doesn't make any sense.
The report says that it's yeast.
Well, Remiel did love a hot tub.
Yeast, that is weird.
You know what? Give me a second.
Okay.
I know you said to just examine
what's on the feather, but...
I can't help but do the math and...
I think I know
what this is about, Lucifer.
You... you... you do?
Come on.
Ginormous mystery feather?
On the down-low investigation?
Lucifer, you have to know
that you can trust me by now.
So tell me the truth.
You hit an emu with your car, didn't you?
- [Chloe] I think I got it.
- I can't believe it.
They're six-feet tall
and indigenous to Australia. He hit an...
Oh, I'll give you guys a second alone.
Yes, thank you, Miss Lopez.
[Ella and Lucifer sigh]
Okay. Remember TJ Ross,
the fence who had Amenadiel's necklace?
The twerp who launched me across the room
like an Angry Bird? How can I forget?
When I was working
the dead med tech case,
I looked into
the locations he operated out of,
and one of them
was an abandoned beer factory.
A yeasty venue indeed.
What if Remiel was trying
to tell us before Michael got there?
And he got to her first?
Maybe we can still get
to TJ before Michael does.
It's been hours.
We have to go see. We have to try.
What if your siblings
are there waiting for us?
[sighs]
Miss Lopez.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Miss Lopez,
might I trouble you for one last favor?
One hundred percent.
What do you need?
- ["Sabotage" by Emma Kern playing]
- [vocalizes]
♪ Take another hit
But I'm already high ♪
♪ Told myself I wouldn't
Why do I even try? ♪
♪ Here I go again... up my head ♪
♪ Staying home
And getting stoned instead ♪
♪ I know that I shouldn't
I can't prioritize... ♪
[Mazikeen clears throat]
Hi.
Um...
I'm just waiting for somebody.
[clears throat] Yeah, I know.
You're waiting for me. I'm Steve.
Okay.
That explains
why he wanted to meet at Lux.
And why I liked
his wicked sense of humor.
So you're dating already? Cool.
Seriously?
You broke up with me, Maze.
Besides, you're Steve. So...
Yeah, but you didn't know that.
- I...
- Okay, whatever. Point is...
[sighs] Um...
I've been thinking,
and I've decided.
I don't care if you die.
That's the sweetest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
- [laughs] Wait, wait.
- [gasps]
I'm just double-checking here.
That means you want to be with me, right?
Till the years are showing on your face...
and my strongest days are gone.
- Yes.
- [laughs]
[grunting]
[shouting]
Well, well, well, TJ,
you're quite the feisty human, aren't you?
Finally! Help us, brother.
This little cockroach won't let go!
[Michael] TJ.
If you know what's good for you,
you will let go of the necklace.
- Over my dead body!
- [grunting]
You know, the human makes a good point.
[chuckles] Father isn't here anymore,
which means the rules about
not killing humans vanished with him.
If you wipe this one worthless soul
out of existence...
I'll have everything I want.
[exhales]
[grunts]
- [groans]
- [TJ snarls]
Michael.
[sighs] Sorry, but I can't do that.
[sighs] As good
at cosplay as Miss Lopez is,
I never was as adept
at subterfuge as my twin.
Lucifer!
Let's do this, shall we?
- [wings flap]
- [both grunt]
[exhales]
Well... [clears throat]
That was gross... [groans]
but I guess you need a strong stomach
if you're gonna be God. [chuckles]
Is this the God you want?
A God who slaughters the innocent
for his own selfish gain?
[chuckles] Humans are the selfish ones!
They're animals!
They don't matter.
What about Remiel? What about our sister?
Does it matter to you
that Michael murdered her?
That can't be true.
Michael?
I did what I had to.
Sometimes sacrifices
have to be made for the greater good.
Heavy is the head
that wears the crown and all that.
- [gunshot]
- [shouts]
[panting]
Well, hello, Chloe.
You do know bullets can't hurt me, right?
Wasn't supposed to hurt you.
[wings flap]
- It was supposed to distract you.
- [Raziel gasps]
[exhales]
[Linda] Okay. All right. Watch this.
Ready?
Okay.
- [Charlie babbles]
- [Linda] Did you see that?
- [hesitates]
I mean...
He falls all the time, Amenadiel.
Twice as much as
the other kids in the baby group.
Okay. Okay, so,
this occupational therapist/mom/influencer
that I follow on Instagram
who sponsors a blog, says that we...
- Maybe what we should do, Linda,
- [gasps]
is just let Charlie
figure it out for himself. Yeah?
You mean,
we should just let him hurt himself?
I don't think I can do that.
How could... How could you do that?
[chuckles] We're not signing him up
for cage fighting, Linda.
Falling is how humans learn.
It's how I learned.
Look, I... I lost my wings, my powers.
I fell again and again.
You know?
And getting back up...
[sighs]
...well, that was the most
empowering experience of my life.
Yeah. I'll make a chart.
I'm gonna log every time you fall,
Charlie, and see if there's a pattern.
Then I can slide into the mom-fluencer's
DMs and see if she has any ideas.
- [cell phone vibrates]
- Yeah. [chuckles] Hello.
[chuckles]
What?
No.
[hesitates]
[Linda] Amenadiel, what happened?
[sighs]
[Lucifer sighs]
I can't believe Remi is gone.
She...
She died like she would have wanted.
She died a warrior.
It doesn't matter how she died.
She's still dead!
Dad and his mysterious ways.
If he'd just chosen a successor,
we wouldn't be here.
Remiel would still be alive,
Dan wouldn't be in Hell.
Father didn't give us the answers, Lucy,
because he wanted us to find our own way.
- Oh, even if it means dying?
- Yes!
Yes, Lucy.
You have to risk falling if you wanna fly.
Dad had faith in us.
- That's why he gave us choice.
- [Lucifer] Well, he shouldn't have.
I had the choice to save everything
and everyone I care about, but I didn't.
I chose wrong.
Michael is going to be God
because I didn't have the balls
to kill a two-bit fence
who wound up dying anyway.
And now, who knows how many other people
are gonna die because of my...
cowardice?
It's not cowardly to save a life.
It's not cowardly
to fight for a single soul.
We owe it to Remiel. We owe it to Dan.
We are the ones still standing.
We are the ones that have to fight.
[scoffs] Metaphorically
for you, of course,
because our siblings are invulnerable.
- You'd be powerless against them.
- [Mazikeen] She won't be powerless.
Here.
You can have Stabby.
Thank you, Maze. [sighs]
I'm just not sure I know how to use this.
It's okay. I figured a way around that.
You're not fighting!
Dan died because of me, Lucifer.
I am fighting.
You are not fight...
I am fighting!
Fine.
Fine. Well, even if we had
a dozen demon blades,
it's still the four of us
against a literal army of angels.
I think I might have an idea
how we can get our own army.
You don't mean...
They're the best chance we've got.
What do you think, Maze?
[Mazikeen] Hey, I'm all in.
Let's kill a bunch of angels.
[Amenadiel] No, Mazikeen!
Now, if we're gonna do this,
there will be no killing.
They're our family.
You wanna tie
another hand behind our backs?
Fight a war like a bunch of wussies?
It's not cowardly...
to save a single life.
["New Blood" by Zayde Wølf playing]
Fine. Whatever.
At least we'll all die together.
Well, off that optimism,
Dad gave us the power of choice.
What say we make
one last spectacularly bad one?
♪ I'm looking for new blood ♪
- ["Dark Things" by Adona playing]
- ♪ I've done dark things ♪
♪ In these shadows ♪
♪ All that I crave... ♪
[Chloe] Huh. So, this is where
he wants to hold the vote.
It's, uh, quaint.
For what it's worth,
there's no one else
I'd rather do this with.
[wings flap]
Where's Maze?
And our reinforcements?
Well, it's taking
a little bit longer than expected.
[sighs]
Right. Well, we'll just have to stall.
This really is a family affair, isn't it?
You actually showed up. Look at that.
You ready to bend the knee, brother?
Yes, Michael, we...
[sighs] Listen,
we accept you as our new God.
[Michael] Do you?
[chuckles] I wanna hear from him.
The one who doesn't lie.
Of course, brother.
You are...
God...
[sighs]
...awful!
[chuckles] I mean,
what on Earth are you wearing?
Is winter coming or something?
Very funny, Lucifer.
Very, very funny. [laughs]
Why do you have to fight the inevitable?
It's the only way I know how to fight.
I demand a vote!
[laughs] Seriously?
All right, fine.
Fine! Who here is not voting for me?
I said, is anyone here not voting for me?
[sighs]
Well, that's it.
That's your speech, is it?
I think I've said all I need to.
[scoffs] Typical Michael.
All fear and no substance.
- [huffs]
- [Lucifer] Brothers and sisters,
I know what you all desire.
And I know it's not me as God.
But I also know you don't want him either.
So you have a difficult decision to make.
Everyone knows
what Michael's all about. Fear.
He's using it now
by threatening you with the Flaming Sword.
But me...
I'm gonna try
and convince you with the truth.
I'm gonna tell you
the real reason I want to be God.
[Zadkiel] I know why
Lucifer wants the throne.
He told me.
And it's for love,
of all things. [chuckling]
- [sighs]
- [all laughing]
[laughing continues]
I never thought I'd hear it. Love.
The best reason one could have.
Lucifer has my support.
He is worthy.
Who's with me?
Thank you.
Oh, I really thought
that was gonna be a whole thing.
[sighs] "A" for effort though, Zadkiel.
Well, looks like we have the numbers.
Consider the vote complete and me...
God!
[bird tweets]
Oh, come on!
I thought there'd be a little some-some,
a flash of lightning, maybe, unless...
I... I thought Dad said we were choosing.
Maybe it has to be unanimous.
Right. Right. [chuckles]
Well, if it has to be unanimous,
there's only one way to make that happen.
Get rid of all the opposing votes.
[Lucifer] Wait.
- Mom never liked you.
- Thank you.
[huffs] Where is Maze?
Any minute now, Lucy. I'm sure of it.
[Chloe] What are we gonna do?
Can you hear that?
[humming] Can't touch this.
Can't touch what?
- ♪ Can't touch this ♪
- [all humming]
- [humming continues]
♪ My, my, my, my ♪
♪ Music hits me so hard ♪
♪ Gets me saying, "Oh, my Lord!" ♪
♪ Thank you for blessing me ♪
♪ With a mind to rhyme and two fly feet ♪
♪ It feels good
When you know you're down ♪
♪ A super-fly homeboy
From the Oak town ♪
♪ And I'm known as such ♪
♪ And this is a beat
That you can't touch ♪
[humming]
That's gotta be Dad, right?
[Lucifer] Yeah, yeah, no, no, she's right!
God must be here making us sing!
Dad has returned!
- [Gabriel chuckles]
- All right. All right, stop!
♪ Hammer time! Oh-oh-oh! ♪
No, no, I mean stop this... this nonsense!
You're obviously just stalling.
- [sighs]
- [Mazikeen] Lucifer!
Finally!
[in Lilim]
At my command, brothers and sisters!
[in English] That is so sexy.
Not now.
Right. Of course.
[clears throat] But definitely later.
[singer vocalizing]
♪ She is fire, she is fire ♪
[Michael] Very cute. A little demon army.
But you still don't stand a chance.
[inhales] You might
wanna ask your girlfriend to leave,
or she's gonna get hurt.
I was just gonna say
the same thing to you.
[laughs] Chloe, how many times
do we have to go through this?
Your bullets can't hurt me.
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
Turns out melting down one demon blade
makes a lot of bullets.
[kisses]
[Lucifer] So you see, dear brother,
we're more evenly matched
than you anticipated.
Now, I know you want to avoid bloodshed
amongst our siblings, as do I.
So... why don't we just, uh...
you know, shed each other's?
Mano a mano?
Or ala a ala?
Which means wing to wing in Latin...
Got it, yes, thank you.
And precisely.
I win, Godhood is mine.
You win, you have my full support,
and I'll crawl back to Hell
like a good little Devil.
When I win,
you won't be crawling anywhere.
This is to the death.
So be it.
- [all gasping]
- [Michael] Ahh!
I have the Flaming Sword.
- You don't stand a...
- [grunting]
- Lucifer's losing.
- Zadkiel, he has to do this on his own.
- [Michael chuckles]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
Brother, can I borrow
your staff for a moment?
Lucifer!
- [grunts]
- [cackles]
Oh, ho-ho-ho-ho! My brother
has a stick, whatever shall I do?
[both grunt]
That staff is
all that remains of the Tree of Life.
I know.
And I can't think of a better use for it.
Than for a lost cause?
No, we have Michael
right where we want him.
[grunting]
- Ha!
- [grunts]
[Lucifer shouts]
[snarls]
[grunting]
[Michael shouting]
[wings flap]
[grunts, panting]
Goodbye, brother. [yells]
[grunting]
Oh, ho-ho-ho! You're never
gonna take this sword from me, brother.
[laughs] Dear brother,
that was never part of the plan.
- Plan?
- Now!
- No, no, no!
- Get the blade, Lucifer!
[Michael shouts]
- [laughs]
- [wings flap]
Azrael.
With the Angel of Death
at our side, I can't lose.
I'm sorry, Lu.
No... [gasps]
[panting] I got it!
- Chloe!
- [Chloe screams]
Chloe!
[Chloe groaning, gasps]
- [sighs]
- [Mazikeen sobbing]
[Amenadiel] Maze, hold.
Okay, hold. The plan!
The plan has gone to shit.
No! No, no, no! No! No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[sobbing] No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
This is all my fault.
This is all my fault. I'm so sorry.
[sobbing] It's not your fault.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[Chloe panting] No, stop. Lucifer.
Lucifer...
we make our own choices.
- I chose to be here. And Dan...
- [whimpers]
[shuddering] What happened
to Dan is... is not my fault.
And this is not your fault.
It's not your fault.
I love you.
- [Lucifer] No.
- I love you.
[sobbing] No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
[continues sobbing]
I told you she should leave.
And good news is sounds like
she made peace with her guilt.
I bet she made it to Heaven.
I guess that means
you'll never see her again.
I mean,
you really should have taken my offer.
[panting]
This isn't... this isn't right.
This isn't right. It's not her time.
Wh... what are you babbling about?
I'm gonna get her back!
[chuckles] Lucifer, come on!
Your banishment.
You'll die if you try to go to Heaven.
So be it.
Maze. Hold!
[panting]
[in Lilim] Fight!
[all yelling]
[in English] Let's go.
♪ What will it be? ♪
[birds chirping]
Mmm!
Just as good as I remember it.
Egg sandwiches. A Decker family tradition.
[Chloe] So good.
[sighs]
Dad, this is so nice.
Yeah, monkey.
- [loud whooshing]
- It sure...
...is.
[Chloe] Is that normal?
[dad] Not as far as I know.
I'm sure it's fine.
It's Heaven.
- [explosion]
- [rocks shatter]
[gasping, panting]
[coughs]
[grunting]
[panting]
- [Lee] Man, you don't look so good.
- [continues panting]
Mr. Said Out Bitch?
That's impossible.
Says the dude
that just fell out of the sky.
[Lucifer gasps]
Why am I not burning to a crisp?
[exhales] I should be ashes by now.
I'll be damned. The ring.
Lilith's immortality has protected me.
[shudders]
Though not for long, it seems.
Okay, I don't know
what the fork any of that means,
but you look like you could use a hand.
[Lucifer grunting]
- [panting]
- [grunts]
[Lucifer coughs]
The last time I saw you,
you were... you were in Hell.
Did I fly in the wrong bloody direction?
Nope, you're in the right place.
This is Heaven.
Or at least, one of its many rooms.
I'm still trying to get
the lay of the land.
I hear they have a room
made entirely out of cotton candy.
No, no, no, that's impossible.
No soul has ever
made it up here from there.
I don't know about that,
but I know I took your advice.
I faced my family. My guilt.
You went through the door.
Yep, finally.
And boom, Heaven!
- [both laugh]
- Heaven.
[inhales] Heaven!
[exhales] The detective.
Hey, don't worry, she's here. Come on.
What... what are you doing?
- Hey, you helped me.
- [gulps]
Let me help you.
There we go.
- Wait, come on, Dad! Come on. Tell me!
- [laughing]
I'm serious.
Your mother's face was completely purple.
She forgot she had
the Althea makeup on.
And no one in the PTA
was brave enough to tell her...
[Lucifer] Detective! Detective!
Thank you. Thank you.
Lucifer.
Lucifer!
What...
Lucifer.
What are you doing here?
[panting] I've come to get you.
It's not your time. You need to come back.
Oh, that's right. The...
- The... the war, and...
- Yes.
...and I left Trixie...
- and my friends and...
- Yeah.
...I left you.
- Yes.
- But... but...
my Dad's here,
and I can't... I can't lose him again.
It's okay. I'm not going anywhere.
But it sounds like some people
could use your help, Detective Decker.
- Thanks, Dad.
- [breathing shakily]
- Okay. Wait! How do we get back?
- [gasps]
[Lucifer] I'm not sure we can.
I'm afraid there's
not enough power left for the both of us.
No, I'm not going without you.
What are you talking about?
[Lucifer] You have to.
You have to.
The world still needs you, Chloe Decker.
- No, you don't have to do that!
- [grunts, pants]
I know. I know I don't have to.
I choose to.
What?
I choose you, Chloe.
Because... [shouts]
- [gasping]
- [fire crackling]
I choose you because...
I love you.
[Chloe] Lucifer. Lucifer!
[heartbeat thumping]
[gasps]
[panting]
[groans]
- [shouts]
- [slashes]
[groans]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
- [gunshot]
Whoo!
[angels grunt]
[groaning]
[coughs]
Huh. [gasps]
[scoffs]
[Michael huffs] No way.
He did it.
He actually brought you back. [chuckles]
- Just so I could kill you again.
- [whimpers]
[grunting]
[chuckles]
Goodbye, Detective.
Oh!
- [shouts]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
[Chloe grunts]
[both grunting]
[Chloe shouts]
[shouts] You took the man I love from me!
[panting]
Do it. Do it!
[Lucifer] Detective!
[shuddering]
[gasping]
This isn't you, Chloe.
[grunts]
- [gasps, sighs]
- [Michael gasping]
- [coughs]
- [gasps]
Bend the knee, brother.
To the death, right?
[screams]
No more killing.
[Michael gasping]
In my time here on Earth, I've learned
everyone deserves a second chance.
Even me.
Even you, Michael.
Lucifer, how?
I don't know. I...
["And So It Begins" by Klergy playing]
♪ You ♪
♪ Knew this day would come ♪
♪ And you aren't the only one ♪
♪ And so it begins ♪
♪ And so it, and so it begins ♪
Oh, my me!