[airlock door opens]
[air hisses]
[airlock seals]
["Atomise" by Temples plays]
♪ And what's that listening
to our brain ♪
♪ Hear it rearrange ♪
[airlock hisses]
♪ See the atoms synchronize ♪
♪ Right before your eyes ♪
♪ Let us atomize ♪
♪ Disassemble
Pull apart ♪
[lock disengages]
♪ Take it from the start ♪
♪ Let us atomize ♪
[gurgles]
[woman in bed grunts]
- Looking for something?
- Oh! Hi.
Huh? Oh, just Lucifer.
[Chloe grunts]
Aw, sweetie, it's come to this?
Full-on delusions.
We are gonna get through this.
- Oh...
- I promise.
It... It's fine. It's fine.
- He... He really is back. I...
- Mm-hmm.
I... I saw him yesterday,
and there's a new case, so...
Wait, wait, wait. Lucifer's back?
Like, seriously back?
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- Huh. Yeah.
Full bars, battery's charged,
but no texts or messages.
Awesome.
Not surprised, though.
He didn't tell me when he left.
Why would he tell me when he's back?
Ella, I know you're bummed at him,
and you have reason,
but he also had a really good reason
for leaving so suddenly.
And while he's been gone,
he's sort of been through...
Hell.
So, you know, if you could
just cut him a little bit of slack.
I guess it would be nice to have
good ol' Lucifer around again.
I mean, I missed him, you know.
I don't miss him like you miss him,
'cause I don't find him attractive.
- He's like my brother. [chuckles]
- Yeah.
Anyway...
[Lucifer] Hello.
Hello there, I'm Lucifer.
Lucifer Morningstar.
Morningstar.
[chuckles lightly]
I am the Devil.
I am a devil of my word.
Devil.
[chuckles]
[breathes deeply]
[inhales deeply]
Hello there.
I'm Lucifer, Lucifer Morningstar.
Hello, Detective.
I would never lie.
Not to you, Detective.
Detective.
[chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
- So, Judy Mason?
- [Ella] Oh.
Yeah. Poor Judy.
She was a biochemist and
a commander of the Red 2 Mars Project,
a simulation, engineered by
the fine folks at Brody Aerospace.
Uh... as in "Anders Brody"?
The tech billionaire?
We talked to him last year on a case.
- The guy had a boat.
- Yeah. Guy has a spaceship, too.
He rich!
And so is the entire crew
on this project, actually.
Judy was the only scientist.
The other five were just civilians
who paid buttloads
for a spot on the Red Planet.
I mean, Brody himself is going
to take them to be the first Mars colony.
I mean, that is
if tests go according to plan.
This doesn't look like part of the plan.
Nope, Judy was stabbed in the neck.
- There's an apple...
- Mm-hmm.
...and this hair, which was stuck
in that bloody footprint.
I checked everyone's suits
but couldn't find any blood.
The killer must have cleaned it,
because, since no one's allowed
in or out of the dome,
it had to be one of those five.
So we got ourselves a locked-door mystery,
mi amiga.
Huh. All right.
And the cameras,
did they capture anything?
Yeah, but most of the footage
has already been wiped.
Okay.
Well, I got to talk to the crew,
and I'm gonna head back to the precinct.
Hello, Detective.
Lucifer.
Hi, I... I was looking everywhere for you.
Well, here I am,
and there's nowhere I'd rather be, so...
I can't believe you left
and didn't even say goodbye!
- Bloody hell.
- You just ran off to Florida
and forgot about us.
Florida? I...
Oh, yes. Yes, I was in Florida.
My mother was terribly ill.
You said you had to take over
the family business.
Indeed. My mother was ill, which is why
I had to take over the business.
But Florida is wretched.
Far too many creepy-crawlies,
and no Miss Lopez.
Oh, I can't stay mad at you!
- [Lucifer chuckles]
- Aw! But, hey...
No más of that mierda, okay?
No más.
[Lucifer chuckles]
[chuckles]
Detective, what's wrong?
Can I...
Yeah.
You just lied to her.
Uh, no. You did.
I just kept up the ruse.
You never lie.
Remember, Detective,
for you, I was only gone for two months.
But for me, I was in Hell
for thousands of years.
A few things might have changed,
maybe even improved.
After all, a little white lie
could be quite beneficial.
[Dan] Oh.
- Hey.
- You're back.
Great.
For example...
Daniel... [clears throat]
It's really, really good to see you,
and you're looking exceptional,
by the way.
[chuckles]
Oh, I love your bracelet.
Did you make that?
Uh, no.
No, it's amethyst.
Cleansing my chakra.
Well, good luck with that.
Thanks, man.
See? Lucifer 2.0.
Lucifer's back? What?
Yes! Yes, it's... it's amazing.
I... I am...
I am happy. [forced laugh]
I'm ecstatic. [chuckles]
And we're sitting.
What's wrong?
Uh...
Well, it's... it's probably nothing,
but Lucifer's acting...
um, different.
Different how?
I don't know.
I'm sure it has nothing to do
with the fact that I told him I loved him
right before he left,
and he didn't exactly say it back.
But he did say...
[sighs]
"It was you, Chloe.
It was always you,"
which is kind of a big deal
because he used my name,
which is something he never does.
So I'm pretty sure he's not acting weird
because I freaked him out or anything.
Well... I think
if Lucifer's been acting unusually,
it's probably because he's been in,
well, you know...
Hell.
- Yeah.
- Although it may have been
a couple of months for us...
he's told me that
time's not the same there,
so it might have been
thousands of years for him.
Yes. He, um... He told me that, too.
Um...
Unless he's lying.
Yeah, right.
At least we know that
that's something he never does, right?
[chuckles]
Uh...
Right?
Well, actually, this morning, um,
I found out that Lucifer has
reconsidered his position on honesty.
[chuckles]
Oh.
Interesting.
Well, I'm sure whatever
Lucifer is going through,
it has nothing to do with you
or his feelings for you.
He probably just needs time
to reacclimate.
You know, remember...
what his life is like here.
Right.
Yes. Yeah. Yes, that...
You're so right, that's it.
I just have to, to remind him
of who he was when he was on Earth,
and then give him a little jump start.
That's exactly it. Thank you, Linda.
You're a genius.
You two are perfect for each other.
[chuckles]
Maybe.
So there's five
Red 2 Mars Project members.
We just have to figure out
which one had motive to kill Judy.
Yes, interrogation. I remember it well.
Crucial to the crime-solving process.
Well, and it can be boring,
but you'll make it fun.
You always do. That's who you are.
Right, let's get down to serious business,
shall we?
You, uh...
You hated Judy, didn't you?
Well, I didn't exactly love the woman.
Fact is, Judy was a piggy little thief,
always stealing our food rations.
Well... [chuckles]
...the stomach wants
what the stomach wants, am I right?
I mean, we all have desires, right?
I wonder what... what she desires.
Well, probably just to eat her own food.
She just said it.
Did Judy do anything else
that you found aggravating?
Yeah, actually.
She totally bugged out
when I microdosed this one day.
I mean, I'm going to want to trip
when I take my trip, right?
That reminds me.
You left this at my desk.
- Detective!
- [mouthing] You want?
It's not even noon.
Yes, I can see how that behavior
might grate on one's nerves.
Oh, I don't know.
She never really bothered me.
She was a bit loud
on the sat phone sometimes.
Other than that, nice lady.
You're lying!
Mm. No,
I'm not.
[whispering]
I'm sorry, did you want to do that?
No.
There must be something
you're not telling us.
[woman] Not to speak ill of the dead,
but Judy was a bit of a party pooper.
We had about five books
the entire time we were in there,
and she managed to spoil
the endings to all of them.
Yeah? What'd you do,
bite the head off a bat?
Stab her in her sorry space ass?
Huh, Sharon?
Actually, that was my husband
that bit the head of a bat.
Oh, come on! You're lying.
I apologize for my partner.
That was very unprofessional.
It's quite all right.
By the way, I never managed to thank you
for all the things you did for Ozzy.
From one Prince of Darkness
to another, right? [laughs]
Yes. Well done.
So other than the books, you liked Judy?
Yeah. Totally.
Everybody did, especially the guys.
- Oh.
- Mm.
I mean, she was so hot,
and smart, of course.
But she's not the only one
who knew about science.
Did you know that I engineered
five of my fragrances myself?
The fruit scents
are slightly controversial,
but everyone loved my melons. [laughs]
[Chloe] Mm-hmm.
[laughs]
Oh... Really?
Nothing?
At least hit on her.
Why would I do that?
- She might be a murderer.
- Wait. I didn't kill Judy.
I'd never hurt Judy.
- I am certainly not a murderer.
- Dude, I didn't kill her.
Is this cinnamon?
No, I did not stab her
in her "sorry space ass."
[groans] Dearie me!
That got us nowhere.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Hey, what's going on with you?
Are you okay?
Of course. Everything's fine.
Don't you want to do something impulsive,
inappropriate, sinful, you know?
Like... What... [grunts]
Here, eat this.
Well, I'm not really hungry.
That's not why you eat it.
- Looks like...
- Hey.
Hi.
Hey, is that my pudding?
Yes! Yes, here you go, Daniel. Yummy.
Okay.
[sniffs] What's your game?
Nothing, just thought
you looked a bit peckish.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Did you spit in it?
He spit in it.
Got something, kids.
That hair I found
in the bloody boot print,
it's sheep hair.
Now, unless someone
was into some freaky stuff...
Don't even say it.
I won't.
It means that someone tracked that hair in
from outside the dome.
Oh, well, that is exciting!
Well done, Miss Lopez.
Right, I'd say it's time to go and talk
to the people running the program.
Genius!
Oh, God, it's so great to have Lucifer
back again, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
[Lucifer] So we understand
no one was allowed
in or out of the facility,
but people must have come to the dome
to drop off supplies, yes?
Uh, no, actually.
The whole point is
to simulate a real trip to Mars,
so no one's going to swing by when you're
just, you know, 33 million miles away.
And what about repairs?
Again, all maintenance has to be done
on site, although that's minimal, too.
We've made a lot of improvements
from the first project to Red 2.
We're less concerned
about equipment failure
than we are of people breaking down.
And what does that mean?
One of the main reasons
why we're running these simulations
is to test the psychological strength
of our travelers.
It's difficult to be isolated
with strangers for so long,
away from your family, friends,
everyone you love.
Yeah. I participated
in the Red 1 Mars Project.
I can tell you firsthand,
the experience really...
changes a person.
But once you were back for a while,
did you start to feel
more like yourself, or...
To tell you the truth, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if I'll ever be the same.
Well, it must have been particularly hard
on your relationships.
Detective,
didn't one of the crew members mention
that Judy was loud on the phone?
Perhaps she was arguing with someone
back home.
[woman] Doubtful.
The sat phones are just used
for project communications.
They're only connected to the system here.
Well, did anyone here
have issues with Judy, then?
[sighs] What about Donovan?
- Who?
- An aerospace engineer
who used to work here.
But when Judy got promoted
to project commander of Red 2 over him,
he got pissed.
He went to Brody, he threw a fit,
so Brody fired him.
Donovan was kind of...
- emotional when he left.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, was he?
- [Chloe] Huh.
Okay.
[Lucifer sighs]
Detective, I...
I could tell the questions you were asking
certainly weren't just about the case.
You're concerned that I have changed.
Well, the truth is...
I have.
But I need you to know
that my feelings for you...
haven't.
[Chloe sighs]
You've already been so patient.
I just ask that you give me
a little more time.
Of course.
Whatever you need.
[sighs] Thank you.
[elevator dings]
[distorted chiming]
[Lucifer grunting]
[choking]
How could you?
After everything
we've been through, Lucifer,
how could you go home without me?
[in American accent]
I'm not Lucifer! I'm not Lucifer!
I'm not Lucifer! [grunting]
[gasping]
[panting]
Lucifer told me he had a twin brother.
And you are Mazikeen.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Michael.
"Michael," huh?
How do I know you're not Lucifer
saying you're Michael
just so I won't kick your ass?
Lucifer doesn't lie, remember?
[chuckles]
Do these look like Lucifer's wings to you?
Fine. What the hell are you doing here?
To right a very serious wrong.
See, there I am in the Silver City,
doing my thing,
when Gabriel strolls in and says,
"Lucifer went back to Hell,
voluntarily."
Well, I just crack up,
as you can imagine, but...
then Raphael starts going off
about how Lucifer's grown,
and then Remy says,
"Yeah, what a sacrifice,"
and then pretty soon all I hear is,
"Lucifer, Lucifer, Lucifer!"
So you're jealous?
No.
I'm pissed.
Lucifer finally does
what he's supposed to do
without whining about it,
and he gets praised?
He rebelled against Dad.
Almighty God, for God's sake.
Since when do we congratulate a convict
for serving a sentence?
And if I know my eternally
selfish brother, and I do,
all this sacrifice and responsibility
bullshit, it's just smoke and mirrors.
I don't know who he's trying to fool,
but I do know...
that as soon as he hears someone is
up here playing with his toys...
maybe even breaking a few,
then he will come flying right back up
to reveal his true colors.
So...
[sighs deeply]
[in English accent] Hello, Los Angeles.
Seems to me you're the only one
trying to fool people.
Good luck with that.
Humans are smart.
Especially Chloe Decker.
[in American accent]
I admit, she was getting
a little suspicious, but...
I'll just up my Lucifer game
until she's properly hooked,
and then I will achy-break
her little heart.
Do you even know how to be Lucifer?
Know anything about Earth? Humans?
I pay attention, Miss Mazikeen.
I know a lot of things.
And what makes you think I will let you
get away with any of this?
Well, why wouldn't you?
Why wouldn't you even help me?
Hmm?
I told you, I know things,
and I know that you're pissed
at my brother.
Join me.
Lure him back up here, and then
you can kick the real Lucifer's ass.
Or you could just keep beating up pianos.
It's your choice.
[sighs]
[electronic dance music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
- [in English accent] Hello, brother.
- Hey, Lucy.
Lucy!
You're here!
[laughs]
Wait.
You're here.
Yes. Yes, I got a bit bored,
so I thought I'd pop back up.
Anyway, I'll see you later.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
I'm going to need just a little bit more
information than that, brother.
Like, for instance, who's watching Hell?
No one, but don't worry.
They've promised to be
good little demons.
I left them a cheese plate
and put on some cartoons.
You're being awfully glib.
I'm always glib, brother.
Look, I know what this is about.
You're afraid for baby Charlie, right?
Yes, Lucy, of course I am.
What's to stop more demons from coming up
and taking my son again?
I went back to Hell for a reason.
I was concerned, too, but I'm not anymore.
Everyone's in line, trust me.
All right, so, DMV lists this
as Donovan Glover's most recent address.
If he goes to Mars,
they're never going to find Waldo.
[both laughing]
You know, you seem more like
your regular self tonight.
- Do I?
- Mm-hmm.
Donovan Glover?
[Chloe] LAPD!
Oh. [grunts]
I don't believe he heard you.
[tires squealing]
He's headed for the bridge.
- But if you head west...
- We can cut him off.
You read my mind.
[tires squealing]
Well done, Detective.
[Michael laughing]
[brakes squeal]
Oh!
Come on.
Oh! [grunts]
LAPD! Get out of the car!
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
- [gun firing]
- [Donovan grunts]
[gasps]
Well!
That was fun. [chuckles]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[Donovan] I thought you were repo men.
And woman.
Sorry I freaked.
It's just, that car is all I got left.
Well, perhaps you shouldn't have
freaked on your boss Brody
and gotten yourself fired.
Oh, you know about that?
Well, he kind of deserved it.
He gave a promotion to someone
way less qualified than me.
You're referring to poor Judy.
[Chloe] The woman you stabbed in the neck.
Wait, are you saying Judy's dead?
Very.
And you think I did it?
No. No way.
First of all, I've been in Texas
all week, interviewing.
Just got back last night.
Second, I never touched that woman.
Bad enough Brody blacklisted me.
Who knows what he'd do
if anyone hurt his Judy?
"His" Judy?
Yeah.
They were having an affair.
Why do you think she got the job over me?
Boss can't even follow his own
"No fraternizing at work" rule.
Brody's married.
Perhaps Judy got tired
of being the mistress.
Explains the angry phone calls.
Brody got scared his wife would find out.
Yeah, made sure she wouldn't.
He has access to Mission Control.
And the ability to delete
the surveillance footage.
Yes. We have to go talk to Brody.
Yes, we do.
Thank you.
And, uh, you're never gonna be
Ryan Gosling, by the way.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm literally doing nothing.
You never do nothing.
Something is definitely up.
Hi. So I figured out
why we can't get a hold of Brody.
He's dead?
- Not Heaven. Space.
- Ah.
Turns out he's on a suborbital
shuttle test until tomorrow morning.
So, you know...
That means that you and I...
have the rest of the evening free.
Right.
Right, well, I suppose I'll go home
and get some dinner, then.
All on my lonesome.
I'll see you later, Detective.
Ah.
Um... was that an invitation?
Don't ask me.
The guy's a freaking enigma.
Mm.
[elevator dings]
Lucifer.
I brought our favorite.
Burgers and fries.
Detective.
Detective! Wait!
Detective, please.
Detective...
Please! Please.
- Let me explain.
- Maze?
Maze?
You are acting so different.
I am trying to be patient, Lucifer.
- Understanding, but no...
- Detective...
No. Leave me alone. I...
I don't even know who you are anymore.
You're right.
Honestly, I'm not even sure
who I am anymore.
I mean, I was down there for so long,
I got lost,
lost in who I used to be.
And I have been trying so hard
to get back to the Lucifer I was,
the Lucifer that you know,
but...
When I saw Maze,
Hell just came rushing back.
Chloe,
it meant nothing.
You are the only thing that matters to me.
[scoffs]
Oh, yeah?
How do I know that you're not lying?
'Cause you do that now, yeah? You lie.
Not to you.
You're different.
I would never lie to you.
[elevator dings]
Yeah, well, I need to go.
I need... I need to think.
Wha... Detective!
[man] Nothing inspires
like a suborbital view.
Except, of course,
maybe one from the Red Planet.
And let me tell you something.
Jeff Bezos can Bezos our butt!
[crowd laughing]
But this mission,
it brings us one step closer...
- Detective, about last night...
- I don't want to talk about it.
...to making that dream come true.
- Excuse me.
[man] I couldn't be prouder.
And let me tell you...
- Mr. Brody, do you have a minute to talk?
- I'm sorry,
if you guys wouldn't mind just
hanging back with the rest of the press.
Wait a sec.
I know you.
Yeah.
You're that guy who helped me
find forgiveness.
Yes, I am.
How are you?
- Thanks again, man.
- Heh.
Oh, it was very cool of you.
Thanks again, man.
That was really great of you...
Ooh.
I'm devastated over Judy's death.
Just sick.
No one expects to lose an employee
like that.
We know you were sleeping with her.
An accomplished woman,
maybe she didn't want to be
the side piece,
maybe she didn't like sharing you.
Yes, perhaps she threatened
to tell your wife, or the public.
Uh... do I need a lawyer?
No one had more access to the dome,
to the cameras.
Right now,
no one has more motive than you.
You know, I'd say
I definitely need a lawyer.
[whispering] So right now might be
a good time to do your thing.
My what?
The mojo, with the eyes.
Oh! Right, yes, that.
Mr. Brody. Sorry, one last question.
Get the car running.
Tell me...
What is it that you
truly fear?
I...
I'm afraid...
that...
people will find out.
That you killed Judy?
No.
That I hate space.
[Brody sighs]
This astronaut crap
scares the hell out of me!
I just started the Mars Project
to compete with Bezos and Musk.
It was a goddamn publicity stunt.
So you don't want to go to Mars?
That's why you're a sweaty little Betty?
- I get carsick, for God's sake.
- Aww.
I almost passed out in the simulation.
How am I supposed to rocket my ass
to fricking Mars?
Did Judy know it was all a sham?
Not at first. She found out
when she was in the dome, actually.
Called me, pissed,
threatening to tell everyone, the press.
Well, even more reason for you
to want her dead.
No, no, no.
I talked her down,
told her I had no choice now
but to go through with the trip.
So, we made up.
I'm telling you,
I had nothing to do with her death.
Do you have an alibi for three nights ago?
I was home all night,
vomiting my guts out,
'cause the following morning,
I had to get in that stupid tin can.
Well, can anyone corroborate?
[sighs]
I guess not.
Yeah, I... I'm not saying anything else
without my lawyer.
[Brody sighs]
[Chloe sighs]
I thought we were friends.
Dan, hi.
So Brody's lawyered up.
We can't do anything
without more evidence, all right?
Yeah, I'm headed back now.
I, uh...
I upset you even more back there,
didn't I?
When I asked him what he truly feared.
Uh...
Actually, Lucifer, uh...
just the opposite.
I think it helped me understand.
I've never been to Hell,
and I hope I never will,
but from what you've told me...
it's a truly terrible place,
and if it really was
thousands of years for you,
no wonder dishonesty and fear
followed you back.
I mean, yes, you've changed,
but it would be so strange if you hadn't.
I think it's time that I accept that.
[exhales]
See you at the precinct?
Right.
Okay.
[sighs]
I told you.
- Tequila upsets his stomach.
- [laughs]
- Hey, Linda.
- Hi.
- Is it noon already?
- [chuckles] Yeah.
You know, I meant to call you, uh...
Just wondering if it might be okay
if I kept little Charlie here
for one more night.
Aren't you working?
Yeah, but there's no better place
for this little angel
than right here, strapped to me.
Amenadiel,
when's the last time you put Charlie down?
It's not that long, 15, 16 hours, maybe?
Okay, Amenadiel, give me the baby.
Okay...
What's wrong?
[Charlie coos]
Okay, listen.
I don't want to worry you,
all right? But, um...
Lucifer's back.
Okay, yeah, Chloe told me. So?
"So?"
So he's not in Hell.
He's not watching the demons.
But Lucifer wouldn't come back
unless everything was okay, right?
I suppose. He said as much.
And it's Lucifer, he doesn't lie.
What is it?
Uh... no, it's just that Chloe told me
that apparently, since he's been back...
Lucifer has started lying.
What?
Surely he wouldn't lie
about something like this.
Yeah.
Right.
No, of course, you're right...
We shouldn't let our fears
get the best of us.
Okay. Come here, baby.
[Charlie coos]
[Maze] Decker.
Hey.
So, uh...
You freaking out?
I mean, seeing me and Lucifer together...
Maze, I know what you're trying to do.
- You do?
- Yeah, and you suck at it.
- I do?
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You're trying to apologize
in your very awkward, demon way.
I am? [chuckles]
Look... [sighs]
...I was pissed.
It was devastating walking in on you
and Lucifer like that.
It was.
But I know that you're...
[sighs deeply]
You know, you're in a vulnerable place
right now.
You're lonely.
You're missing Eve.
And it helped me to understand
that Lucifer is also hurting, too.
He's desperate for love and affection,
deeply desperate.
I mean, obviously, if he was gonna
reach out to you.
It also made me realize that
I want to be the one who is there for him.
In every way.
In fact, I think it's time for us to take
our relationship to the next level.
Are you saying you're gonna bone him?
I mean...
Hopefully it's, like,
a little more romantic than that.
But yeah, um...
I think we've waited long enough.
[snoring]
Aragorn, that's not your sword.
I'm... I'm totally awake. I'm awake.
I think it's time
to go get some coffee, Lucifer.
[both chuckle]
That's good.
Mm.
You know, I am hungry.
Do you want anything
from the vending machine?
Oh, shoot.
I, um, forgot my money.
- Do you mind if...
- [quivering breaths]
- [trembling breaths]
- [Chloe sighs]
[chuckling exhale]
[Chloe exhales deeply]
- [exhales sharply]
- So, um... what do you think?
You want your favorite? The, uh...
The ranch puffs, or...
- Uh...
- ...maybe something different?
You know, I've been thinking.
You are different,
but sometimes change is a good thing.
You know, I...
I think I like this new Lucifer.
You've grown.
I've been stuck in
an old version of us, and, uh...
maybe it's time for me
to move forward, or...
for us to move forward together.
[Michael gulps]
How about after we solve this case, I...
I come over to your place?
Okay.
Oh, look at us.
Yes.
It's rather lovely, isn't it?
[gasps]
Maybe there's a reflection.
Excuse me.
Reflection...
Lucifer.
Lucifer?
Oh, Dr. Linda Martin! Hello.
So it's true.
Here you are. [chuckles]
- Yes.
- That's great.
You must be so happy.
Everyone must be so...
Who's watching Hell?
What? Oh, don't worry about that.
It's fine.
Uh, yeah, because the last time
Hell was left unattended,
demons came and grabbed my baby,
so I'm going to need a little more than
"It's fine."
Yes, I understand,
you're afraid for your child.
Yeah, I'm not afraid he's gonna
fall off the swings, Lucifer.
Do you not remember what happened?
They took Charlie.
They tried to take him to Hell.
That's a big deal.
So of course I'm going to be afraid
for my child.
I need to keep this baby safe.
Yes, I understand.
You're afraid for your baby, but...
it's more than that, isn't it?
You're afraid of being a bad mother,
aren't you?
And why do I get the feeling...
you have a good reason for that?
But don't worry.
Hell's being looked after, I promise you.
And the more I think about it,
the more it might just stay that way.
[Chloe sighs]
Can you go to the moment
right before the cameras shut off?
Mm-hmm.
Mm.Nada.
Oh.
Fast-forward a bit.
Keep going, keep going.
More... There. Freeze.
Oh, my gosh.
You're right. There's a reflection.
Whoever killed Judy
only wiped the camera footage
from the time they stepped into frame.
They didn't even think
about their reflection.
Ack. I can't see their face, though.
Is there a way to tell whose suit it is?
[Ella] It's none of them. Look. I mean,
that one has an external oxygen tube,
but the ones from the Red 2 Mars Project,
look, nada.
Those must be built into the suit.
Do you think the change
would be considered an improvement?
Definitely, yeah.
Okay. I might have an idea
of where the old suit came from.
- Lucifer?
- Mm.
Let's go.
- Right. Right.
- Yeah.
Well, it's late. We should probably
just come back tomorrow morning.
[lock breaks]
Lucifer, we don't even have a warrant.
Huh.
[Chloe sighs]
Lucifer.
Where are you?
[sighs] Nothing.
Well, let's go.
[gun cocks]
[gun fires]
Sam Chavez!
LAPD! Hold your fire!
LAPD?
Oh, my God. Thank God.
- [Chloe] Drop the gun.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Judy Mason.
Wait a minute, what?
No, no. I didn't kill Judy.
Anders Brody did.
That's who I thought you were.
That's why I shot at you.
And you know Brody killed Judy how?
Judy found out the Mars Project
was just a, a publicity stunt.
She told me. We started working together
to find proof to bring it to the press,
but she was just too emotionally invested
with the project and with Brody, and...
You know, I warned her.
I warned her not to confront him, but...
[sighs] she got impatient, and...
now she's dead.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Do you know Anders Brody?
His reputation means everything to him.
I thought he'd come after me next.
It's a clever ruse, but it won't work.
All the evidence points to you.
What evidence? What are you talking about?
[Chloe] You're the only person with access
to Mission Control,
video surveillance.
You owned a space suit
for the Red 1 Mars Project.
The cameras captured
a reflection of your suit
heading towards the dome just seconds
before the cameras were wiped.
And if I hazard a guess,
this tacky rug is sheepskin
and matches a hair
found at the crime scene.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
You're right, I'll go with you.
Sam's lying.
He didn't do it.
I killed Judy.
[Chloe] Drop the knife, Mandy.
No, I don't want to hurt anyone else,
it's just...
I brought it as proof
it's the murder weapon.
Oh, it looks like Brody and Judy
weren't the only ones
breaking the "No fraternizing
at work" rule.
[Sam] I don't understand.
You took my suit and you killed Judy?
- Why?
- I thought you were in love with her.
I mean, you were sneaking around,
and, and...
[sighs] hiding things.
and then I caught you
on the phone with her, whispering.
No, I was working with her
to expose Brody.
The whole Mars Project is fake.
What?
Why didn't you say anything?
'Cause I was trying to keep you safe.
You know, when you went away
on that first project, I waited for you.
You were gone for so long.
And when you came back,
you were so different.
I thought you didn't love me anymore.
It doesn't matter where I am.
Here, the moon, Mars...
It does not matter. There is nothing...
that will change the way
that I feel about you.
Even if I'm in prison?
Nothing.
[sobs]
[handcuffs rattling]
[elevator dings]
Detective!
No. It's just me.
I know what you're about to do
and I won't let you.
I have my... issues with Lucifer,
and yeah, I am kind of pissed at Chloe.
But this? No.
Kissing me was one thing.
Chloe is a good person.
She doesn't deserve this.
[in American accent] You're right.
You are right. Chloe is special.
Which is why I've changed my mind...
and... [chuckles]
...I'm pretty sure
Chloe has, too, actually.
It seems that, uh,
she likes this new Lucifer
even better than the old.
You told her who you really are?
No.
No, but I will, in time.
See, I've decided
I'm not going to break Lucifer's life.
[chuckles]
I'm gonna take it.
So, if you'll excuse me.
Yeah, that's not...
[choking]
[grunting]
I have a date to keep.
[grunts]
[elevator dings]
Lucifer?
I'll be there in a moment, Detective.
Okay.
[sighs]
Good evening.
Hi.
Do you remember the last time
we were here?
Of course.
We told each other how we felt.
I just hope you know that
I meant every word I said.
I...
I love you, Lucifer.
And I still do.
And I meant it, too.
I love you, Chloe.
[sighs]
Oh...
I've waited such a long time for this.
Me, too.
[both chuckling]
- [Michael] Oh!
- Hmm.
[Michael sighs deeply]
See?
Still have it on.
I can see that. [chuckles]
- You know...
- Mm?
- ...once we do this...
- Yeah.
...things are never going to be the same.
I believe you're right.
- [gun fires]
- [Michael screams]
[groans]
[panting]
Once I shot Lucifer
to prove he was the Devil,
and now I'm shooting you
to prove you're not.
That's what I thought.
[breaths heavily]
[in American accent]
How long have you known?
I knew something was off
the first time I kissed you.
But you always had such good explanations,
such good lies.
I wanted to believe you.
But then I saw you with Maze.
That's when I knew.
Lucifer would never...
do that to me.
So...
Who are you?
I'm Lucifer's brother.
Michael.
It's nice to meet...
Ow!
You know that won't kill me.
- [grunts]
- Yeah, but it makes me feel better.
Okay, okay, okay. I get it.
[chuckles]
[panting] I get it.
So what?
I guess this means you never
really liked the new Lucifer.
You're not the only one who can lie,
and you are no Lucifer.
I don't know why you're here
and I don't care,
but I do know that I am glad,
because you made me realize
that all my fears that Lucifer had changed
were just that.
They were fears.
What Lucifer and I have is special.
It's real, and it doesn't matter
how many lies you tell me.
I will never lose faith...
in me and him.
Oh, really?
No more lies, huh?
Well, how about a truth, then?
You...
are a gift from God, Chloe Decker.
What does that mean?
It means that you were
never supposed to exist.
Father made you for Lucifer.
You were put here on Earth only for him,
to be his little plaything.
Now, isn't that special?
[scoffs]
I don't believe you.
[chuckles]
It's time for you to go.
Get out!
[gasping]
[exhales deeply]
You're up late...
Michael.
Congratulations, bro.
Used to take you forever
to figure out I was playing you.
You shouldn't have used fear
to get inside my head.
You shouldn't have done that.
It was way too obvious.
Does Father know you're here?
Oh, please. I do what I want.
Go home, Michael.
You don't belong here.
Well, I could.
And when I get there, I could also
tell Remy it's time to come back,
'cause you know who else
doesn't belong here?
That's right. Your son, Chucky.
I'm not afraid of you, Michael.
Now go home.
Lucifer's life sucks anyway.
The only thing worse is the traffic.
Oh, I think thou doth protest too much.
You see, you pride yourself
on exploiting everyone's fears,
but we've always known yours.
You're terrified that
Lucifer is better than you.
That he'll always be
better than you.
Please.
Our brother?
The Devil?
The, the, the guy that was cast
out of Heaven for all eternity?
Exactly, Michael,
because despite even that, you know,
deep down...
he'll always end up winning.
We'll see.
♪ Fight for yourself ♪
♪ You must fight for your soul ♪
♪ No one is safe here ♪
♪ Will you cross over ♪
♪ To the dark side? ♪
♪ One little lie ♪
♪ Or ten little lies? ♪
♪ Won't keep you up at night ♪
♪ Will you cross over ♪
♪ To the dark side? ♪
[in English accent] Brother!
What are you doing here?
It's time, Lucy.
You need to come back.
Why?
What's happened?
♪ Will you cross over ♪
♪ To the dark side? ♪