[buoy clanging]
[seagulls squawking]
[sighs deeply]
[boat horn honks]
[upbeat dance music plays]
[partygoers laughing and cheering]
Oh! All right.
I got that bubbly!
You want to join us?
Hell to the yeah!
Just let me slip into something
a little more comfortable.
Ooh!
[man] Hello.
[gasps]
I heard you were here,
so I thought I'd pay you a visit.
No, no, no way, man! You got to go!
Well, frankly, I was expecting
a tad warmer reception,
- Mr. Said Out Bitch.
- Don't get me wrong.
I am grateful for all the money
and the gold you gave me last time.
But I'm gonna have to catch you
on the flip side,
because for once,
things are going really well for me.
And every time I run into you,
bad things happen.
Right. Well, this is gonna
get awkward, then.
Why?
Something bad is about to happen,
but I assure you,
it has nothing to do with me.
What are you talking about?
Someone is about to walk
through that door and murder you.
Huh?
[snickers]
[chuckles]
You kill me! [laughs]
There ain't no way that's gonna happen.
Oh, I assure you,
it most certainly will happen.
In fact, it's happened
over 200 times already,
and it will happen again in five,
four, three,
two...
[grunts]
[gasping]
What the hell?
Precisely.
Victim is Lee Garner, 53, career criminal.
Armed robbery, burglary,
but mostly small-time stuff.
Although he might not be
so small-time anymore,
'cause this Foshizzle is all his.
This what?
The Foshizzle.
Name of the boat, Foshizzle.
- Oh. Cause of death?
- [police radios squawking]
Gunshot wound to the chest.
Oh, and if that wasn't messed up enough,
the killer also did this.
Clean cut at the wrist, post-mortem.
We're still looking for the hand.
What do you think?
Mm.
I think I boned him.
Maze, just because
you happened to have slept
with that one murder victim
a few weeks ago
doesn't mean that you slept with them all.
How am I supposed to keep up, Chloe?
With the murder victims
or the people you've slept with?
- Either.
- [Ella] Wow.
Maze is really settling into her role
as your new Lucifer.
Well, in her capacity as a bounty hunter
for the LAPD,
she has graciously been helping me
- with my cases.
- Yeah. It's like Lucifer never left.
But he did leave.
I mean, at least you guys
got to say goodbye.
Me? Ghosted completely.
And it's been what,
like, two months since he moved to Florida
- to help with his family's business?
- Mm-hmm. Florida, yes.
That's where he is.
[Ella] He hasn't responded to a single one
of my texts or DMs.
Not even that video I sent him
of the parakeet dancing to techno.
You guys, it, like, opens up its wings,
and it's like...
[grunts repeatedly]
[giggling] And he goes, like, side to side
and it's frigging hilarious, but...
As far as I'm concerned,
Lucifer can, well...
He can go to Hell.
You guys don't think
he's having work done, do you?
Hey, Ellen.
Read the room.
Chloe, I am so sorry.
I didn't mean to bring up the "L" word.
It's just...
It's just that I miss that crazy dude,
you know?
It's... It's okay.
I completely understand.
And to be honest,
I have been working so much...
We... We've been working so much,
I haven't even had a chance
to stop and think about it... really.
You know, I haven't even...
Haven't even thought about it.
Anyhow, speaking of work... Uh, any leads?
None yet, but I'll have more when
I get everything back to the lab.
Okay, great. Call me if anything comes up.
You got it.
Okay. Cool.
Until then, Maze, I do believe
we have other work to do.
♪ You should leave tonight with me ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Leave tonight ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
[upbeat music keeps playing]
[man] You ladies wanna dance?
'Cause on a scale from one to ten,
you two are nines,
and, uh, we're the ones you need.
- Nah, we're good.
- We're good.
So you guys are back, again.
Amenadiel!
[Maze] What's up?
Yeah, we just can't help it.
Ever since you took over Lux,
it's just been so much fun.
I'm starting to see why Lucifer enjoyed
spending so much time here.
Yeah. [forced chuckle]
Excuse me, ladies.
Oh!
Did I just witness a drug deal?
No, man. Of course not.
Look, I'm gonna bail, so...
Look.
Lux is under new management,
which means new rules.
No one sells drugs in my place...
without me getting a piece of the action.
[bartender] There you go.
Let the good times roll.
Amen.
So, I didn't just die?
Well, as I was trying to tell you
before we were so rudely interrupted,
you are now in your very own Hell loop.
So, welcome to Hell.
I'm in Hell?
I... I don't understand.
Eternal damnation? Infinite suffering?
It's a pretty straightforward concept.
No, I mean, like...
"Hell" Hell?
The one and only.
Then get me the hell out of here!
It's not up to me, I'm afraid.
In Hell, you are your own jailer.
You brought yourself here.
Then I'mma take myself
on up outta here, then.
[door slams]
How in the hell?
Same response every time,
and it's not that simple.
But why am I here?
Well, that's between you
and your own guilt.
It's what brought you here,
and it's what will torture you now
through the end of time.
And now we're crossing into the country
of Boring, so time for me to self-deport.
Please.
Enjoy your eternity of suffering.
Wait, man.
You can't go.
You can't just leave me here alone.
No, you won't be alone.
My demons will always be on hand,
torturing you and such, so chin up, mate.
At least tell me who killed me.
Not my job anymore.
I'm sorry, but this really is
about you and your eternal pain,
okay?
But I had everything.
I mean, this beautiful boat
in Marina del Rey,
women, money...
I had it all.
Marina del Rey?
Los Angeles.
[sighs]
You know...
there's a good chance
I know who's on your case.
We were quite a team, once upon a time.
I mean...
to them, it's only been a few months,
a blink of an eye,
but down here, it's been...
much, much longer.
This is your lucky day.
It doesn't really seem like it.
I'm gonna do something
I haven't done in ages,
for old times' sake.
I am going to solve your murder.
So how is this gonna work?
Is the killer gonna come through that door
and shoot me again? 'Cause that hurt.
Usually, yes, but me being
the Lord of Hell does have its perks.
Oh, sh...
You see, everyone in your Hell loop
is played by a demon.
I have control over them.
Give us a wave, Belios.
What's up?
So,
if you can freeze them,
then it should be easy to figure out
who the killer is, right?
I mean, I can just lift this up and...
Oh, shit!
Again, not that simple.
See, your Hell loop is made up
entirely of your own memories.
You never saw your killer's face,
hence a big nothing.
No offense, Belios.
And take the rest of the day off.
You've certainly earned it.
So, how are we gonna find my killer, then?
With good old-fashioned detective work,
mon frère.
And lucky for you,
I learned from the best.
So, step one.
Who wanted you dead? [chuckles]
[woman] Lee owed a lot of people money.
My brother always ran
with a sketchy crowd.
He'd spend money he didn't have,
get into debt, steal to pay it back.
[scoffs]
[Chloe] Mm.
Is it too bright in here for you,
Detective?
Oh. No.
No, I just have, like,
a light, um, sensitivity thing.
Um, so...
Uh, when they found your brother,
he was on a very expensive yacht
that he owned.
Maybe he turned his life around.
Yeah.
That'd be a first.
My brother was a magnet
for bad people, bad things.
He was forever stuck
in this vicious cycle.
He was probably just riding a high.
[sighs] He was bound to come down
sooner or later.
Do you have any idea why someone
would want to cut off his hand?
They cut off his hand?
My God, why?
It's what we're trying to figure out.
You don't recognize that
as any kind of message?
I haven't seen Lee in years.
I can't even say
I really knew the man anymore.
If that's a message...
it's not one that I know how to read.
[man grunts loudly]
Decker, got a lead.
[sighs]
Sit.
Tell her what you told me.
Ow! Okay.
[sighs deeply]
Word on the street is that Lee guy
got whacked by Dirty Doug.
Who the hell's Dirty Doug?
Doug Sargisian? Guy runs a mob-backed
high-stakes poker game at the H Club?
I heard from my boy K-Swiss,
who heard it from his boy 8-Ball,
that Lee owed him a bunch of money.
So Doug did him in,
and then cut off his hand
to send a message.
Um...
What's the message?
"If you don't pay up,
then you're, like, stealing"?
Kind of on the nose, if you ask me,
but hey, message received,
'cause I owe Dirty Doug
a ton of cash that I don't have.
All right? That's why I was bailing,
until Angry Bird here ended those plans.
[both sigh]
Looks like we're gonna need
to pay Doug a visit.
- A guy like Doug's gonna...
- Lawyer up?
First sign of police.
- We need...
- Leverage.
- I know what you're thinking.
- Might be the only way.
- [Maze] What about...
- It's dangerous.
- Then, what if we...
- He'll see it coming.
Huh.
I have an idea.
Absolutely not, Maze.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Fine! Fine!
- We'll do it your way.
- Good.
So we agree to the plan?
Yeah.
We'll pose as high-end poker players,
get into the game,
get Doug to slip up, lean on him,
get him to confess.
[laughs]
Something funny?
Don't get me wrong.
You two snacks are welcome
at my card table anytime, hmm?
But Dirty Doug's game defines "exclusive."
All right? Invite-only, and...
y'all ain't getting invites.
I know someone
who could have gotten us an invite.
You don't need Lucifer,
and I don't need...
[groans]
I will get us an invite.
Right.
- Hey! Ella!
- Hi! How are you?
Thanks so much for coming.
Well, thanks so much for inviting me.
Yeah, I brought all the stuff
you requested,
but your message didn't say
why you needed it.
Well, it's for Charlie, of course.
Yeah, I was hoping that
you could teach him some science.
Yeah, I'm a firm believer
in a strong STEM foundation.
Oh, yeah. Science, technology,
engineering, math.
Super important.
[Charlie coos]
Isn't Charlie, like, two months old?
Oh, I know what you're thinking.
But Charlie is a special child.
Yeah. Every child is special
in their mom's eyes, huh?
Yeah, no, but Charlie's actually special.
- Yeah.
- That's why the classical music,
the science lessons, baby Pilates...
It's all to harness his full potential,
which is...
Which is something
the world has never seen.
Yeah.
Well, here. I'll show you.
Okay, Charlie.
Charlie, where's boron?
[chortles]
See? Yes! That's...
Yes, babasquat, that's it! That's it!
- Yes.
- Oh!
See, that's boron.
Wow! Yeah, that was... amazing.
Yeah! Having children is such a gift.
Have you ever thought about having kids?
Um...
Sure, yeah, I guess, I mean,
but, uh, you know...
kind of missing the dude part
of the equation at the moment,
and, huh, this chica has
terrible taste in men.
Drawn to the bad boys for some reason.
[Charlie chortles]
But you know, for once I'm thinking...
I deserve a good guy, you know?
So, science lessons.
Wednesdays at 11:00 a.m.?
I checked your schedule,
and that's your day off.
Sure, yeah. Wednesdays are great.
What is that smell?
Success.
Essential oils, man.
What you're smelling is called Success.
I'm all out of Strength,
but if you want...
I can hook you up with some Hope.
It does wonders.
No, I'm good.
You sure? Come on,
everybody needs a little bit of Hope.
- I'm good.
- No? Okay.
All right, all right, all right.
So I see you're really diving into this,
uh, whole self-improvement thing.
Oh, yeah, man. Yeah, I was in a bad place.
Dealing with a bunch of guilt and stuff.
But you know what?
I started to work on myself,
and it was such an awakening.
We've never even scratched the surface
of our true human potential.
- You ever CrossFit?
- No.
Aw, come on! No!
But, listen, I want you to know,
Dan, that I think
all of this personal reflection is a...
It's a really good thing.
Well, thank you, man. Thank you.
What's up? Why'd you stop by?
To report a crime.
Amenadiel, you got to stop
playing vigilante.
You can't make citizen's arrests
on jaywalkers and littering.
There was a sign.
It was clearly forbidden.
The kid was three years old.
Well, this is totally different, Dan.
Now, I have been deep,
deep undercover at Lux,
Lucifer's den of sin,
and I have finally gained the trust
of a real, big-time drug dealer.
- You need to give up on this, man.
- Dan, I want to help.
I need to help.
All right? I...
I need to help make the world
a safer place.
Now, I may have gone about it
the wrong way at first, but...
this is a good case, Dan.
It's a good case against
a legit drug dealer.
Be the change, right?
Told you I'd get us an invite
to Dirty Doug's poker game.
I never doubted you, partner.
Maze, is that blood?
Don't worry about it.
[sighs]
That's what you were wearing?
Hey, man, I love this suit.
And yes, I clearly remember
I had this bad boy on
when I got so badly in debt with that guy.
And how much did you owe?
Like, $700,000, give or take a few.
For that much, I'd have killed you myself.
[elevator bell dings]
After you.
["No Limits" by Royale Deluxe plays]
Exquisite Hell loop.
♪ No limits, no ceiling, no crown ♪
♪ No pressure gonna hold me down ♪
♪ No stopping 'til I break every rule ♪
♪ No limits to what I can do ♪
♪ Nowhere is too far away ♪
♪ No border gonna stand in my way ♪
♪ No wall that I can't break through... ♪
City of Angels, I've missed you.
Hey.
He's the guy I owe.
Dirty Doug.
[man] Evening, ladies.
Hi.
Evening.
We are here to play poker.
This shouldn't be too hard.
Just need to lose, rack up a huge debt.
Dirty Doug will approach us.
- Got it.
- Okay, good.
[Chloe grunts]
[Maze chuckles]
Excuse us.
What are you doing sitting in my seat?
You are supposed to be the arm candy.
Like hell! Look at you.
Your dress couldn't be any sluttier.
- I'm in the sensible pants suit.
- When did you last play poker?
Exactly. The point is to lose.
Fine.
- Thank you.
- You should play, darling. [chuckles]
Oh, my goodness. [chuckles]
Oh, my goodness.
Texas hold 'em. [laughs]
Oh, so exciting.
[Lucifer] So, what can you tell me
about ol' Dougie-Doug here?
[Lee] Not much,
just that he seems like
a really scary, powerful guy.
Obviously.
He's got a skinhead and neck tats.
[sighs deeply]
What would she do?
Oh, yes!
Give me all the usual background info.
What about his priors?
Any speeding tickets,
overdue library books?
How the hell am I supposed to know
any of that?
[mystical whooshing]
Is there anything you can tell me?
Not really.
I mean, I'm pretty sure he killed me.
There's that.
But we weren't exactly buddies.
Man, I don't know what else
you want from me.
[mystical whooshing]
[chuckles] Thank you.
Decker, what are you doing?
I'm winning, can you believe it?
Yeah, but you're supposed to be losing.
I know, but I never win.
[Maze chuckles ironically]
Ah! [gasps]
Okay, fine.
[croupier] All in.
This was the beginning of the end for me.
Oh, good, good.
Finally we're getting somewhere.
So, what happens next?
Now Doug offers me a marker,
which, unfortunately, I take.
Wow, you were really killing it there
for a while.
Yeah. I was.
Well, you know, if you want
to keep the party going, keep playing,
I could offer you a marker.
Um...
One question about that.
What happens if I can't pay you back?
Yeah. We heard stories.
About people getting dead.
You're referring,
hypothetically, of course,
to a certain gentleman in Marina del Rey.
Look, I'm a reasonable man,
as long as you're working to pay me back.
Or you can buy a boat instead,
and end up with a bullet in your head.
Ooh.
Sounds like a confession to me.
Maze, not exactly.
Remember, Lee was shot in the chest.
[Lucifer] That's it?
That's the marker?
He just gives you a gold coin?
No contingencies?
No stipulations or threats?
That's it.
Well, there's got to be something more
to indicate Doug's actually your murderer.
Some hidden clue.
A sign.
Well, you've got to give me
more than this.
Something, anything, Detective.
Who?
[panting]
You are useless.
This whole investigation's
a complete waste of time. I mean...
this isn't even Los Angeles.
And you...
You're not her.
Wait a second.
How do you guys know how Lee died?
Are you cops?
Correct, my dirty friend,
and why don't you come with us
and tell us why you're taking credit
for Lee's murder?
Looks like we got a runner.
Stay put.
[both grunting]
[pedestrian grunts]
[man on scooter grunts]
- [car horn blares]
- [man grunts]
[grunts]
[brakes squeal]
[Ella]
Well, no ID on your street kebab yet,
but I found this on him, a .45.
- Same as the one that killed Lee.
- Yep.
And my Spidey-senses tell me
this is our murder weapon,
but I'll know more
when I get back to the lab.
Okay, great. Good.
You, uh...
want to climb that tree, Ellen?
[nervous chuckle]
What are you talking about?
I saw that.
Maybe you can get him against the wall
and...
spread 'em.
Oh, my God.
Maze, that...
That is crazy talk, okay? I...
I'm done with the bad boys.
- Okay?
- Sure.
Whatever you say.
[scoffs]
[woman] Lord Morningstar?
There's someone you should meet.
Where am I?
[gags, coughs]
[groans]
Oh, man. I'm so sorry. That's gross.
Hey, are you the detective?
I'm a demon, and Lord Lucifer sent me
to give you a message about the case.
Lucifer.
How is he?
He's the King of Hell, so he's great.
He wanted me to tell you...
uh, it's safe where you stored it.
What? What's safe?
The thing that you stored?
"Stored"?
- [groans]
- Where?
I don't know,
you're the one that stored it.
Wait, I stored it?
Yeah, it's safe where you stored it...
Oh, crap.
This body's too jacked up to keep working.
- But you got this...
- [gasps]
Hey, is that Mazikeen?
Wait, wait!
[Ella] Decker...
What the hell? Did you move the body?
[sighs]
[Lucifer] So, that's that.
Gromos assures me
the message was delivered.
So your demon just jumped
into that dead guy's body?
And told the detective
what she needs to know
in order to arrest whoever was
behind your murder.
No need to thank me.
So, back to your torture.
And me to mine.
Hey, man. Um...
you keep talking about a detective.
Who is she?
Someone I left behind...
a very long time ago.
Seems like somebody pretty important.
More than you could ever know.
Hell, I get it.
I left people behind, too.
People I care about, like...
my sister, Meg.
You know, she meant the world to me,
and I let her go.
Now it's too late.
What's your detective's name?
Well...
I just used to call her "Detective,"
but...
her name...
Clever, manipulative bastard.
Well played.
Petty distraction
to gain the Devil's sympathy,
hoping I'll let you off the hook
from your endless torment, huh?
- Ah, man, it ain't like that!
- [Lucifer scoffs]
You just seem like a really sad devil guy.
I mean, okay,
you know, maybe a small part of me
was hoping that you'd help me out.
How many times do I have to tell you
before it penetrates
that minuscule mind of yours?
This whole thing is your own fault!
You know what, man? Screw you!
I mean, you would help me out
if you wanted to.
Thought you were supposed to be
the man down here.
Ain't you the "King of Hell"?
You really want to know why you're here?
Do you?
Well, let me show you.
- Ta-da! We made it.
- Oh! Shh!
Uh, Charlie's just in the middle
of his Japanese lesson.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Sorry. We'll be extra quiet.
[Japanese language on speaker]
Listen, thank you so much for watching
Trixie. It's just for a little bit.
And I've been dying to see the baby.
- [Dan chuckles]
- Yeah, no, of course.
You know,
Charlie's just so good with children.
Also, I've been meaning
to return these to you.
Oh, okay.
Thank you for letting me borrow them.
- Wow, so you read all of them?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Powered through them
pretty quick, actually.
So insightful.
I'm really enjoying learning
to live my own truth.
Do you have any more?
Well, this is all the self-help books
I have.
Maybe let these, you know,
simmer for a bit first.
Maybe.
[Japanese dialogue on speaker]
[inhales sharply]
Japanese, huh?
Yeah, well, Charlie got
a little tuckered out from yoga,
so we had to reschedule
Art Appreciation at MOCA
for some low-impact language immersion.
Wow, that is some schedule.
I know, I know. It's a lot of work,
but it's all about raising
the best child possible.
He's special.
Yeah. [chuckles]
We all think our own kid
can walk on water, right?
I hadn't thought of that.
Cancel swimming lessons.
[chuckles]
You know, one of the things
that I've learned from all this work
that I've been doing,
and being a dad...
- Yeah.
- ...is that the best part of life,
being a parent,
is that you get to slow down and enjoy it.
Linda, make sure to be present
in the moment.
Oh, I am.
- Totally present.
- [Charlie laughs]
Wait, what's that sound?
[Trixie giggles]
[Charlie laughing]
That's the first time he's laughed.
Two months.
That is pretty advanced.
It's easy. He just likes silly faces.
[Dan chuckles]
Prints off our squashed possum
came back to Vernon Gill, 37,
known hit man, working contracts
for small-time criminal organizations,
and my hunch was on point.
Striations from the gun I found on him
match the bullet that killed Lee Garner.
And I also found 20 grand in cash
in the trunk of that guy's car.
That's the going rate for a contract hit.
So Gill pulled the trigger,
but then who paid him to kill Lee?
- Maybe Dirty Doug hired him?
- [Maze] Doubtful.
I spoke to Ellen's boyfriend.
- He's not...
- He came in last night,
and Gill said he threatened him
for taking credit for Lee's murder.
Said it was "bad for business."
Then he joined a poker game.
Someone else hired Gill.
Huh. Okay. Um, well, I...
may have a lead.
You found a lead without me? Where?
Um, I can't exactly say.
[Ella] Oh!
Confidential informant. [clicks tongue]
Right.
- Sure.
- You got to protect your peeps.
- Ride or die, man. Respect.
- Yes.
So about this lead.
[Chloe] Yes. It...
"It's safe where you stored it."
Where I stored what?
Wait, did you store it
or did she store it?
"You stored it, and it's safe."
- What did I store, though?
- No, not you.
Who stored what? I'm so confused.
I'm confused, too.
That's why I'm sharing this.
"You stored it."
"You stored it," "You stored it..."
Yes! I knew that sounded familiar.
"You stored..."
Lee's credit card statements.
He was making regular payments
to a storage facility in Pacoima called...
You Stored It!
Amazing. Good.
All right, let's go check it out.
So what CI gave you this lead?
[clears throat]
Something very weird happened
with Gill's corpse.
[Lee] Hmm.
I used to have a car just like this.
Ah...
This is my car.
Where are we?
The root of your Hell loop.
Oh, no, not here.
[partygoers laughing]
So why didn't you tell me about the demon?
Maimed bodies, demons from Hell...
It's kind of my jam, Chloe.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
It just happened really fast,
and it caught me off guard
hearing from Lucifer like that.
It's open.
- [Chloe gasps]
- [Maze grunts]
[Maze yells]
[woman yelps]
- [Chloe] Meg?
- [Meg panting]
[dance music plays]
[Amenadiel] All right, Kyle.
If you're gonna keep selling
in my place, man,
why don't we lay down some ground rules?
I prefer the way
the old management did things.
[Amenadiel] Hm.
It was more of a hands-off policy.
The past is the past, Kyle.
I'm here to talk about the future, bro.
So I suggest you evolve.
So how is this supposed to work, then?
Going forward, I'm gonna take
20% off the top of everything you sell.
That's the deal.
That's the only deal.
Whatever.
This place is bumping so hard,
we're both gonna make a killing.
Not so fast, little man.
If you're going to be selling drugs
in my place,
see, I need to know
that it's top-shelf product, you feel me?
I feel you.
All right, let's see it.
There's more where that came from.
Looks like good drugs.
Police! Show me your hands.
Show me your hands!
Don't move.
What the hell?
Who's your supplier?
Kyle? Tell me!
There...
is none.
Where'd you get the drugs from?
My mom.
She just had back surgery.
There's nothing here.
Just the one baggie.
You just said there was more, so where?
I was maybe gonna hit up my grandpa.
[sighs]
He's getting his gallbladder removed.
Dan, I was just trying
to make the world...
a safer place for...
For Charlie.
Yeah.
It's a crazy thing, being a parent.
When Trixie was born...
I tried to be Supercop...
and round up all the criminals I could.
Then I realized...
removing all the danger in the world
is like trying to bottle up the ocean.
You want to keep Charlie safe?
Just be there for him.
Be a good dad.
How could you bring me here?
So you recognize it?
Of course you do, it's your memories.
This is my parents' house.
The house I grew up in.
I haven't been here in 15 years.
[sighs]
Meg...
She just had a baby, my niece.
This was her baby shower.
I mean, this was the last time
my whole family got together.
My mom, she got sick right after it.
She died.
My dad followed right after.
This was my last chance,
and I didn't go inside.
[Meg] I found this place
and these credit card receipts.
I kept wondering
why they would take his hand.
Then I saw the biometric safe.
They used his hand to open it.
Must have been where he kept
all his money.
[exhales] The safe at You Stored It.
That's what Lucifer was trying to tell me.
It's all about the safe.
Who else knew about it?
I don't know. Um...
His old crew, maybe?
He was pretty tight with them.
Someone must have hired Gill to kill Lee
and use his hand to get the money.
And what were you gonna do with that gun?
I heard you guys coming. I freaked.
I grabbed Lee's gun to defend myself.
I thought it might have been...
[sighs] I don't know,
his killer coming back?
Honestly, I don't know what I would've
done if it had been Lee's killer.
I was just so angry.
It's a lot of legwork to do for a brother
that you've already written off.
[Meg] Yeah.
I kept telling myself it didn't matter,
I didn't care that he was gone, but, uh...
his death's drugged up a lot of emotions.
- The truth is...
- That you still miss him?
I spent every day expecting him
to walk through the door.
Guess now I finally have to accept
he's never coming home.
All right. I'll take you home.
I'd like to grab some of Lee's things,
if that's okay.
Yeah, go ahead.
[Maze] So what's next?
We gonna crack some skulls,
track down Lee's old crew?
Uh, Maze, actually, I think
I want to, um...
just take a beat to process some things.
What's wrong?
Well, I-I think that I've been avoiding
dealing with the fact that
Lucifer isn't coming back.
Or...
you figured out that you don't need him.
We don't need him,
or anyone.
Chloe, you and I...
We're good.
Maze...
[chuckles nervously]
The thing is, I'm... I'm not good.
And I don't think you're good, either.
I-I don't know exactly what happened
with you and Eve...
This isn't about Eve.
But...
Okay, this is...
This isn't about Eve, this is about
what's right in front of us.
Right here, right now, you and me.
Maze, I know what it feels like
to be abandoned.
You know, I mean, I've been
throwing myself into work, and...
going out with you so that...
I don't have to face it and...
I just think maybe you and I are using
this partnership to fill a void
that someone else has left behind.
So...
I-I think that it's best
if we step back...
from working together.
Yeah.
Good idea.
[Lucifer] Ah, the wonders of Hell.
So, your sister's baby shower, huh?
What a joyous occasion,
full of warmth and happiness.
Truly a celebration of life.
So go on, then. Go inside.
I-I can't.
Of course you can. It'd be so simple.
Just open the door and walk in.
- They don't want me in there.
- But they invited you, didn't they?
Well, they didn't mean it.
Oh, come on. Excuses!
They're like arseholes,
everybody's got one,
but nobody wants to hear it.
- I'm not making excuses for anything.
- No?
Well, your whole family is in there,
yet you're here.
Why?
Is it because you're afraid?
Afraid?
Why would I be afraid
to see my own family?
'Cause you know
if you go through that door,
it's only a matter of time
before you screw up again, isn't it?
Might take two days, two months,
two years, but it's gonna happen.
You're gonna rob a bank or steal a car,
pawn a family heirloom.
It is inevitable.
Sooner or later,
you are going to disappoint them
all over again!
And so you'd rather stay away
for all eternity.
You're right.
It's true, all of it.
It is.
Hey, this isn't just about me, is it?
Whose Hell is this anyway?
And then Lee took me to see Saw.
It was our first R-rated movie.
I was...
[shotgun cocks]
You, put your gun on the counter.
[Chloe] All right.
Do it now.
Let's just all stay calm.
You're Rod.
You used to room with Lee.
Did you kill him?
That loser brother of yours
gave us no choice.
He still owes us our cut
from our last job.
Now, where's the money from the safe?
You don't have it?
The safe was empty when we got there.
[laughs]
What the hell's so funny?
I mean, of course it's gone.
You knew my brother.
He probably thought
he could double it at a casino, or,
I don't know,
spend it on that stupid boat.
Quit stalling and give us the money.
I've got the money.
It's right here.
It's in the bag.
[grunts]
[handgun clicks]
Get down!
Are you sure this is my Hell?
- Well, who else's would it be?
- I don't know,
but I'm thinking you're just here
torturing yourself.
[chuckles] Preposterous.
Have you forgotten this is your Hell loop?
How does this have anything to do with me?
I'm just saying.
You could have chose any moment
to torture me, but you chose this one.
But that's because this is obviously
the most painful moment for you.
Right, and for sure this doesn't
resonate with you at all.
This has nothing to do with me.
I am here because I'm the King of Hell.
This is my job. This is my duty.
Now who's making excuses?
But I should know, right?
I mean, I spent my whole life making them,
and a million bullshit reasons why I went
15 years without talking to my family.
I mean, the truth is I should have just
got out of the damn car
and walked through that door.
I missed my chance.
What about you?
[scoffs]
The self-centered simplicity of you humans
never ceases to amaze me.
How can you presume
to compare yourself to me?
I am here out of responsibility.
Demons were in full revolt.
I had to protect humanity!
- I had to protect her!
- [man] Lord Morningstar.
What!
He's got news about that detective.
[rapid gunfire]
[grunts]
Come here.
They're gonna stop shooting
and they're gonna have to reload.
That's when you're gonna run.
I'll draw their fire. You ready?
No, no, no, I can't.
No, I can't!
Meg, listen to me.
You can do this.
We're not gonna die here. Get ready.
[man whistling]
[Rod] What the hell?
Hello, bad guys.
[Rod] Who's this crazy fool?
[Lucifer]
I hope I'm not late to the party.
[grunts]
[shotgun cocks]
Thought you could use a hand, but...
looks like someone beat me to it.
[exhales deeply]
Lucifer, is everything okay?
You seem different.
Well, for you,
it's only been a couple of months,
but down there, time is different.
For me it's been thousands of years.
But the only thing that kept me going...
was thinking of you.
["Happy Together" plays]
♪ Imagine me and you
I do ♪
♪ I think about you day and night
It's only right ♪
♪ To think about the girl you love
and hold her tight ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ If I should call you up
Invest a dime ♪
♪ And you say you belong to me
And ease my mind ♪
♪ Imagine how the world could be
So very fine ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ I can't see me lovin' nobody but you ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ When you're with me
Baby the skies'll be blue ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ Me and you, and you and me ♪
♪ No matter how they toss the dice
It had to be ♪
♪ The only one for me is you
And you for me ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ I can't see me lovin' nobody but you ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ When you're with me
Baby the skies'll be blue ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ Me and you, and you and me ♪
♪ No matter how they toss the dice
It had to be... ♪
So you're not going to go up there
and help out your lady friend?
I have every faith in the detective.
She's...
quite capable of taking care of herself.
I...
am exactly where I belong.
All right, man.
You do you.
[Lucifer] She'll be just fine without me.