There it is.
By the way,
don't you think there's something
going on between Na-bi and Jae-eon?
Hey. Honestly, how could Na-bi date
a guy like Jae-eon?
Why? Na-bi's pretty.
That's not what I mean.
Jae-eon is the problem.
He's not sincere toward anyone.
That's why I ended things
after a few dates.
Really? You're the one who rejected him?
Yes. I got away from him,
but Na-bi didn't.
There are rumors about her.
What a way to end her school life.
I know, right?
-Did you get everything?
-Yes. Let's go.
Are you working?
I'm arriving at school soon.
Is there someone else you're seeing?
No.
Really?
Excuse me.
Are you Park Jae-eon, by any chance?
Yes.
So it's you.
You bastard!
Sir! What are you doing?
-Move!
-Why are you doing this?
To be honest,
I don't get why you're so upset.
You didn't need to ghost me like that.
I…
Get out of the way!
What was that?
Na-bi!
Get up, you jerk!
Stop, Jae-eon!
-You asshole. Move!
-Sir, wait!
-Move!
-Sir!
-Why did you do it?
-What are you doing?
Why did you do it?
Why? Why did you do it?
-Why did you do it?
-Police?
I'm at Hongseo University and a man is…
-Sol, stop him.
-Why did you do it?
-Come quickly!
-Are you okay?
Why?
Stop it, Jae-eon.
EPISODE 5: I KNOW NOTHING WILL CHANGE.
NEVERTHELESS,
We'll be off now.
What? I'm curious…
I mean, I'm worried about them.
Call me if anything happens.
Okay. You should go.
Bye.
-Be careful. Bye.
-Make sure to call if anything happens.
HONGSEO POLICE STATION
How dare you touch someone
who's already taken?
If you ever come near my sister again,
I'm going to kill you. You scumbag.
Miss.
Let me give you some advice.
You should meet a decent guy.
You'll ruin your life
if you date an asshole like him.
You had something to say.
-What is it?
-Let's talk later.
I'm going home.
Didn't you get hurt?
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm fine. Just worry about yourself.
I wonder what they're talking about now.
I bet they're totally fighting.
I think I just made things worse
by reporting it.
No, you did the right thing.
And it's fine now.
Na-bi could have gotten hurt.
Right?
But Na-bi was trying to stop that man
from hitting Jae-eon.
It was so cool.
-She would have been so scared.
-Right.
Na-bi should have been angry at him,
but she took his side.
I guess it's because she likes him a lot.
I should go.
See you tomorrow.
I'll take you home.
You're acting a bit strange today.
Do you have something to say?
We didn't get to finish
what we were talking about.
It's fine.
This is how we always make up.
As if nothing happened.
I feel like
we shouldn't do that this time.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about leaving
as an exchange student.
I was more upset by how you said
that was the extent of our relationship.
Hey! You're the one who--
All right. I'm sorry about that too.
I'm sorry about
how I acted at the flea market too.
But why aren't you sorry for
not telling me about him?
Hey, that's unfair.
Ju-hyeok and I aren't dating.
Then what's your relationship with him?
Put this on your lip.
Thanks.
I didn't want you to see me like this.
You nursed me when I was sick.
So let's call it even now. I'm going home.
You're not going to see me anymore?
I want to stay friends with you.
"Friends"?
What do friends even mean to you?
-What do you mean?
-Why did you lie to me?
You said you weren't seeing anyone else.
-Is that so important?
-Hey.
What do you want from me?
Right.
You just want someone who's stupid
so you can--
-What's with you?
-What?
You always draw the line like this.
You just want to see me when you want,
but you're scared I'll get clingy?
Don't worry.
That's not going to happen.
It's not like that!
Then what are we?
Weren't you okay
with everything until now?
-Why are you suddenly--
-Right.
Sorry for acting so cool about it
until now.
Honestly, I haven't heard anything good
since I started seeing you.
I pretended not to notice even
when I knew you weren't sincere,
because…
Because…
I like you.
But I can't stand this anymore.
Let's end this.
What?
It's funny, right?
There's nothing to end anyway.
Yu Na-bi.
Thanks for giving me a reason
to decide to end things.
All right. Let's end this.
You're the one who gets to decide.
Gosh. You're really…
You're really a jerk until the end.
Jae-eon and Na-bi were having an affair,
and that woman caught them!
-No way! They got caught in the act?
-Yes.
So Jae-eon actually got hit by that woman?
That's what happened to his face?
-Yes.
-I heard it was a guy, though.
-Is Jae-eon…
-No way.
Are you sure about that?
I heard it was Na-bi who hit Jae-eon.
Someone saw them fighting at night.
Why would Na-bi hit him?
-Because she found out he was cheating!
-That's ridiculous.
Se-yeong. If Na-bi really hit Jae-eon
that hard, she should join the UFC.
Na-bi should have been happy
after leaving me.
-Jeez.
-You're so ridiculous.
What's that reaction?
It's just a hair dye.
-You're unbelievable.
-It's so pretty.
What should we do with you?
She's a total attention-seeker.
Why? Looks good.
Is it that bad? Everyone at the hair shop
said I looked good.
It's pretty, but it's a shocking look.
The color's really pretty.
Did you bleach it first?
Yes. I almost lost all my hair.
By the way, Bit-na.
Did you hear anything
about Na-bi and Jae-eon?
Hey, be quiet. Na-bi's coming.
-Sol's coming too.
-Hey!
You both aren't coming to the workshop?
Bit-na, you changed your hair.
It looks nice.
Thanks, but don't change the subject.
How can both of you not come?
I feel so betrayed right now!
You should come.
The professors aren't coming.
We can just hang out by ourselves.
-I'm not sure.
-You should both come.
Can't you ask Jae-eon to come, too?
Everyone will come if he comes.
Ask him yourself.
Don't ask her to do that.
But they're close…
But what happened to Jae-eon's face?
What do you mean?
You know, right?
Who did he have a fight with?
Can you please stop asking me
about Jae-eon now?
I don't know much about him, either.
-Hey.
-Jeez, what are you doing?
Come on. Start working.
Hi.
I'm so sorry.
He must have seen something
and misunderstood.
He suddenly went all crazy.
You must be really upset.
Tell your girlfriend I'm sorry too.
-My girlfriend?
-I heard you were with someone.
Wasn't she your girlfriend?
If anything happens, call me.
Even if it's nothing special.
That won't happen.
It'll be the best for both of us.
Right.
Gyu-hyun?
Thank you.
How is it?
He's actually eating mint chocolate?
PINT SIZE
CHOOSE 3 FLAVORS
Chocolate and cashew nuts.
-Hi!
-Hi.
Hey, we're ordering ice cream.
Choose a flavor.
-I want…
-Sorry, you can't choose anymore.
I'm going to order mint chocolate
for the third one.
What? You both don't like mint chocolate?
-I hate it.
-Why would you eat toothpaste?
I know, right?
It's good.
This isn't that simple, you know.
Art isn't easy.
Making something doesn't mean
it will become an art piece.
Haven't I told you several times?
I've never seen his face like that.
Did he feel hurt by my words?
-And most of all, your inspiration…
-No, there's no way.
Na-bi. Are you listening to me?
What?
This is bad.
Will you even
be able to finish this on time?
Sorry, Professor.
That traitor.
I was wondering why you were
in the studio for a change.
Did you get rejected, too?
Of course not, Professor.
I'm the one who rejects guys.
I'd never get rejected.
And I work at the studio often too.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Then when can I see your work?
I promise to show mine to you
next time, Professor.
Sol.
Yun Sol.
You're losing focus these days too.
Did you decide to give up everything
since you're not leaving?
No. I'm sorry, Professor.
Sol didn't tell me again.
Everything's a mess.
What has gotten into you all?
You should be putting everything
into your work right now.
I told you to get inspiration,
not be reckless!
"She's at it again."
That's what you're thinking, right?
I'm just barking like a dog, aren't I?
My goodness. Maybe I was
a dog in my previous life.
No, Professor.
-No, Professor.
-Sorry, Professor.
-Yun Sol. Here.
-What? Thanks.
Don't take it too personally.
I loved your piece.
Right. Thanks.
By the way, did you really decide
not to leave as an exchange student?
Yes.
Why? Did something happen?
Just because.
I didn't want to leave.
SPICY STIR-FRIED PORK TRIPE
You said your tongue gets numb.
But I can't stand this anymore.
Let's end this.
All right. Let's end this.
You're the one who gets to decide.
Move!
Na-bi!
PARK JAE-EON
The number you have dialed is not
in the directory.
Please check the number and call again.
ALARM
I miss him.
Na-bi's lost it after ending things
with Jae-eon.
She totally got busted by the professor.
She does seem strange these days.
She's working late,
but there's no progress.
I know, right? Why did she have
to get in a relationship?
Things would have been better
if it was an actual relationship.
That's the same thing.
Why would you do that to yourself?
One is bound to end up like that
when it's over.
You should be careful too.
Gosh.
We're totally fine.
There's another victim of love over there.
Nam Gyu-hyun?
Did something happen?
I set him up on a blind date, remember?
I thought it was going well,
but my friend rejected him!
Look at him. I feel so sorry.
So you're saying he's like that
because he got rejected by her?
Yes.
Hey!
Is your friend that attractive?
To be honest, she didn't look that pretty…
What? Have you seen her?
No. I'm just saying…
Gyu-hyun's pretty good-looking, you know.
That's right.
But I shouldn't set up
any more blind dates.
Darn it.
Why don't you leave your hair down?
Just for me.
I was thinking of returning
the necklace to you.
Just throw it away, then.
You say that so easily.
SEOL-A
Hey, Seol-a.
What?
I'll be there right away.
The fee should be about 50,000 won each,
so let's go with the place we changed to.
Are you writing this down?
Yes. He's done.
Okay, that's it for today.
What should we get?
-Vodka?
-Yes!
Should we go for drinks?
-Let's go!
-Yes!
Should we call the others?
Who? Remember last time
when you called so many people?
Gyu-hyun, aren't you coming?
No.
Oh, no. He must have really liked her.
Maybe I should talk to my friend.
VISITORS RESTRICTED
IN EMERGENCY ROOM
How do you feel? Are you okay?
Yes. Thanks.
How much was it?
It's fine.
You have severe anemia.
Make sure to take your meds.
-It's so bothersome.
-You could faint on the streets.
You put your hair down. It suits you.
Really?
I should keep it down, then.
Is something going on?
You changed your number
and your hairstyle.
What's going on?
Just because.
I got sick of things.
What do you mean?
I'm sick of myself.
It will be a narrow but firm base.
Right.
Hey.
Is it really okay for you to be here?
Sure, just for a little while.
Is that what you're presenting tomorrow?
Well, yes.
Can I see? I'm curious.
Sure.
It's nothing special.
I'm just going to explain
what kind of piece I'm making.
But honestly, I don't know
if I can really make it like that.
-Gosh. This is so cool.
-This is so good.
How do you come up with this?
You're awesome.
It's really nothing special.
There are so many people better than me.
Is there a good or bad for art, too?
Of course.
It's similar to cooking skills.
You can have different tastes,
but there's a clear line between
good food and bad food.
I don't know much about art,
but I like yours.
I have a good feeling about it.
Really?
This is so good.
Can you explain how it tastes
in more detail?
The noodles taste similar
to what your grandpa made,
but the soup
is a bit more savory and light.
Anyway, I like this one more.
That's a relief.
I want to brag about this to my grandpa.
You shouldn't brag yet, though.
Oh, right.
Here.
I just picked it up, thinking of you.
Good luck with your presentation.
What's this?
Is it lipstick?
A gift for me?
Yes.
How does it look?
It looks good on you.
Thanks.
I'll do my best on my presentation.
Do-hyeok.
Right. Enjoy your food.
We're here again.
-Welcome.
Yes?
You're all smiles.
Do you like her that much?
What?
Is it that obvious?
Yes. Totally.
She's going to find out soon.
Here.
On the house.
-You shouldn't have.
-Go on, give it to her.
But this heart's a bit…
Should I make a circle, then? Just go.
-Gosh…
-Come on. Don't be so shy.
It's no problem.
YU SE-HUN
Hey, Gyu-hyun.
You know where Bit-na lives, right?
Text me her address.
Why?
She's totally wasted.
I'm going to send her home in a taxi.
-On the count of three.
-What?
You can come pick her up
if you have a problem with that.
So what will it be?
-Hey!
-Where are you? I'll be there.
What? Really? Didn't you say
you weren't feeling well?
I'm fine. Send me your location.
What's happening?
Who are you?
Who is that?
Darn it.
Oh, my gosh.
Gosh, you startled me!
Let's go for another round.
-Yes!
After we send her home.
No, we have to take her with us.
Bit-na, let's go.
-Send her home.
-Bit-na, what's with you?
-Get up.
-Where should we go?
What? He took a taxi?
-Did you come like that?
-This far?
-Hey.
-It must have been expensive.
Go on. I'll take Bit-na home.
No! I can't let Bit-na go alone.
I'll come with you.
Where are you going?
You're coming with me.
-Hey!
-Right. I should go with you.
-What are you looking at?
-Just go.
Hey, thanks for this.
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
Take her back safely,
and send us a picture when you arrive.
Go on.
Stop that.
Hey, Bit-na.
Get up.
Who are you?
It's me.
Get on my back.
What? Are you crying?
How can you do this to me, you jerk?
Get lost! I don't want to touch
a traitor like you!
What is it this time?
What's the point of talking
to a drunk girl?
Come on, get on my back.
-You jerk.
-Hey! Have you lost it?
You said you hated mint chocolate!
You hate mint chocolate.
-Did you like her that much?
-What?
You jerk.
You said you wanted to date me
only a while ago.
Too bad you got rejected when
you even ate mint chocolate for her.
It must be so agonizing.
Who says I got rejected?
Get lost. I'm not going to talk
to a guy who eats mint chocolate.
What about you? You were
being so friendly with Mr. An.
What? No way.
Then why did you ignore me
at the bar last time?
This is ridiculous. You were with
another guy back then too.
Whatever.
Stop crying.
I didn't eat it because she asked to.
I tried it because I heard
it's good for stress and insomnia.
But it wasn't effective at all.
I can't even sleep these days
because of you.
That's nonsense!
Why would that be my fault?
Well…
I think of you every night.
What?
Why are you hitting on me now?
Come here.
Stop crying.
Let's go. It's late.
Let's go.
Come on.
There you go.
Get on my back.
Hey. Stop seeing other girls
and just go out with me.
That's a lame line.
Give me a break.
I've never asked someone out before.
You better not go back
on your word tomorrow.
I can't be sure.
And why did you dye your hair like that?
You're already so pretty.
And stop drinking so much.
You know how dangerous it is
to get wasted like that at night?
-Jeez! Hey!
-What?
Everything you say is so boring.
But why are you such a good kisser?
Right, I'm a good kisser.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I think it's too much to the left.
Move it more to the right.
-All right!
-Okay.
Just a little more.
What? What is it?
It's unbelievable.
How could you have been living there?
Hey!
Is there something wrong?
No, it's okay. It's perfect now.
I'm only sleeping there until tonight.
So keep it a secret.
What about after that?
Just mind your own business.
You know--
No! I don't want to ask
my parents for help.
You can stay at my house.
My roommate went to the military
a while ago.
What are you on about?
Are you asking me to live with you?
You and me? That's total nonsense.
Why? What about it?
Lots of people do that in other countries.
Well, that's true, but…
Just think about it.
Just pay the rent
you paid for your old house.
Hey, raise the right side. The right side.
My gosh.
He's just too nice.
Are you nervous?
Yes, more than I thought.
Look at me.
Do I look better with my hair up?
-There isn't much difference.
-Right?
They're both pretty.
Right. Did you get an assistant?
The others seemed to be talking
about who they'll have as an assistant.
Not yet.
I should've done that too.
What if nobody volunteers?
I'm sure there will be volunteers.
Oh, right. Sol was looking for you.
Did you talk to her?
No. I don't want to talk to her.
What is it? Did something happen?
You knew, right?
You knew she decided not to leave
as an exchange student, right?
I didn't.
I didn't know. Did she say she's staying?
You're so obvious.
I'm trying to hold back until her
presentation's over, so I'm ignoring her.
But this is driving me crazy.
Good thinking. Just yell at her
once her presentation's over.
She's so annoying!
If she's treating me like this,
she shouldn't call me her bestie!
She's making me feel
like I'm obsessing over her.
I'm going.
Good luck.
Thanks.
-You're the best, Na-bi.
-Thanks.
I have to do my best on the presentation
and get an assistant.
I'm sure you'll do well,
but if you can't find one, I'll help you.
I'm good at taking orders.
Really? You promise, right?
You can't go back on your words.
But what do I do if no one volunteers?
I'm so worried.
Oh, my gosh.
Sorry, Do-hyeok. My friend is here.
I'll call you again later.
What was that for?
-I was jealous.
-What?
You look better with your hair up.
How long are you going to avoid me?
When did I avoid you?
You're the one who ignored me
when we ran into each other.
At the stairs?
Did that bother you?
I guess it worked.
What are you on about?
Good luck on your presentation.
We will now begin the presentations
for the 12th Hongseo Gallery Exhibition.
A round of applause, please.
There are nine presenters today.
We will select the assistants
for each piece
after their presentations are over.
The assistants will help the presenters
with their pieces.
They will be helping them through
the entire process, starting from
making the piece
up to preparing for the exhibition.
It differs by each piece,
but we recommend having
around one to three assistants.
There is a limit to the number
of volunteers,
so even if there are many for your piece,
it's best not to use them all.
The theme of my piece
is "observation of objects."
What I want to express through my piece
is human desire.
Hello, I'm Yun Sol from
the Department of Sculpture.
12TH HONGSEO GALLERY EXHIBITION
PRESENTATION BY YUN SOL
The main theme of my piece is "union."
The main material I used
is railway sleepers.
The rigidity and the traces of endurance
on abandoned sleepers
seemed very attractive.
So I focused on emphasizing
the basic attributions of the material,
such as the oil stains made over time.
I wanted to make the materials
seem attractive.
Thank you.
You're the best, Yun Sol!
What?
Good job.
Next, Yu Na-bi from
the Department of Sculpture.
Hello, I'm Yu Na-bi
from the Department of Sculpture.
The theme of my piece is…
Well…
The theme of my piece is "yeoji."
The Chinese characters
mean "left over" and "land."
Thus, an empty area of land.
It means a possibility or hope
of something happening.
Cho Seong-sik from Sculpture
with the piece titled "coexistence."
Raise your hand if you want to be
an assistant.
-I want to do it.
-Me too.
Me too.
Cho Seong-sik?
Do you accept them as your assistants?
-Yes.
-Come on out.
Yu Na-bi from Sculpture
with the piece titled "yeoji."
Who would like to assist Yu Na-bi?
Raise your hands.
What?
What? No way.
Na-bi. Do you accept
Jae-eon as your assistant?
Yes.
-All right. If that's everyone--
-Me!
I'll volunteer as well.
Do you accept Hwang Jin-su
as your assistant?
Yes, I do.
All right. Come up.
All right, then.
You should share your work schedules
and related materials with your assistants
before we finish up.
The report format
is uploaded on our school website.
-Make sure to check that.
-Okay.
-Good job.
-Thank you!
You tied your hair.
Yes. It was a bit hot.
Are you really going to do this?
What do you mean?
You really don't need to.
I thought it'd be fun.
I like your ideas.
And it seems interesting to work
with metal.
To be honest, I haven't worked with
metal before. So I'm not that skilled.
I'll help you.
That's what assistants are for.
You don't want to work with me?
It's not like that, but…
But?
I feel embarrassed
for not being able to believe
-that he sincerely liked my piece.
-Na-bi.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
-Thanks.
-I'm in an awesome team.
Me too.
Thanks for volunteering to assist me.
Here are the materials.
Do you both have time this evening?
Drinks to celebrate becoming a team?
I know a metalworking studio.
Want to check it out?
Yes!
All right then.
JAE-EON
Come in.
What? Why is there no one here?
The owner got off work.
I'm using his studio when it's not open.
I live upstairs.
I see.
I didn't know you worked this hard.
Aren't you overdoing it?
I have a long way to go.
I envy his passion.
I think I'll be about 30 minutes late.
Sorry.
Jin-su's going to be a bit late.
Sit down.
-Do you want a drink?
-Sure.
It's been a while since we talked.
It hasn't been that long.
What?
The day we went to the police station…
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
What's with the sudden apology?
You were right about me drawing the line.
When people cross a certain line,
they feel like it's meaningless.
But…
I want to change now.
I should stop reading too much
into his words now.
Change how?
Are you thinking of dating now?
I'm not sure.
I'm thinking of changing bit by bit.
Then who knows?
I might meet my soulmate.
I'll be rooting for you, then.
I hope you can be sincere this time.
You can adjust the fire with this.
Be careful. It's hot.
Start from the middle and go to the edge.
Start here and straighten it out
little by little.
It's not straightening out.
Hit it harder.
-It's flat, right?
-Cool.
-Yes, like that.
-It's getting flat.
Good. You're getting better.
Jin-su said he'd be 30 minutes late,
but he never came.
How was it?
It wasn't that difficult, right?
Right.
I think I can do it if I work hard.
Call me whenever you want to work.
You'll make a masterpiece.
Stop teasing me.
I'm not teasing you. I like your pieces.
Especially this one.
I'm looking forward to it.
I didn't know you liked it that much.
I'll get going.
Na-bi.
I changed my number.
Bye.
MISSED CALLS
SEOL-A
-Hey, Seol-a.
-Hey.
Were you waiting for me?
No.
I just called to say
I can't make it today.
-That's a relief.
-Were you busy?
Yes, a bit. I was working.
All right.
Go back to work, then.
I like your pieces.
Especially this one.
I'm looking forward to it.
So is this crumbling down,
or being made?
That's up to interpretation.
It's good.
Na-bi seems to have gained
her focus again.
Thank you.
It's so cool. Just a few days ago,
there was nothing.
Bit-na. When are you
going to show me your piece?
Focus on your work, okay?
Bit-na, let me see you work properly!
Where is she going?
This is great.
Doesn't Jae-eon seem a bit different?
He seems a bit purer.
Right. He seems different somehow.
I heard he doesn't hang out with girls.
What happened to him?
Is he dating someone for real now?
How would we ever understand the life
of a handsome guy?
-Good work.
-Give me one too.
-Here.
-Here you go.
-Have one.
-You try this.
-It's good.
-You want to make wings?
-Yes.
But I don't know what kind of shape
I should make it into.
I should print this one.
FOR REFERENCE
I wish I could see this in person.
-You can.
-How?
This artist's having an exhibition.
It opens next week. Do you want to go?
Sure. Let's do that.
Hey, Jin-su.
He's sleeping again.
Our relationship took a new turn,
and I found peace in my mind
within that friendly relationship.
Yes, I'm here.
Just because.
I thought I should cut my hair.
I didn't go to a hair shop in America,
so it got kind of messy.
Really? Should I cut it short, then?
I guess I'll do that. All right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll get it for you…
Thanks.
Are you Yu Na-bi, by any chance?
Do you know me?
Jae-eon said you were a friend
in the same department.
Right.
Are you here to see Jae-eon?
Yes. I just came
because I wanted to see him.
He's probably busy.
We have a lot of assignments.
Really?
He said he'd come out.
I feel kind of sorry now.
Hey, Jae-eon.
Oh, really?
It's fine. Take your time.
I don't smoke that much.
All right.
Excuse me,
but what's your relationship with Jae-eon?
We used to date.
I see.
And…
we're seeing each other again.
But are you really just friends with him?
Yes. We're just friends.
That's a relief.
I thought maybe I said something
I shouldn't have.
You should
just keep your hair that way.
What?
Jae-eon likes doing it
with your hair tied.
A distance that's close enough
yet not too close to hurt each other.
Jae-eon likes doing it
with your hair tied.
-Na-bi is coming?
-You didn't know?
She disappeared.
That's what you hate the most.
Getting clingy.
Certainty about the relationship.
How does one get that certainty?
I didn't know you'd be coming along.
I've always wanted to come here.
Cheers.
Then is it over with him now?
It must be someone you like.
No, just someone bothersome.
I know very well that a person
who doesn't know how to love someone
can never be happy.
You're coming here?
Hello. I'm Park Jae-eon.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park