[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 18]
You still blame me
for that matter.
No.
I just can't understand you.
You're my own child.
However,
you prefer trusting others
over trusting me.
When your great grandpa ascended the throne at five,
the empress dowager at that time held court.
And they ruled
in harmony.
If they could do that,
then why can't the two of us
do the same?
Over the years,
you've tried very means
to gather toy-boys in the palace,
and I just ignored it.
After Zhao Teng's plot,
I didn't want to get involved
in your private life.
However, you emptied the treasury
to fund your lavish lifestyle.
The Qi family merely sit on the fence,
while they persecute the faithful and honest.
I can't ignore it.
Hui,
without me,
you would have died.
I'm from the Qi family.
What if you give
your uncles more freedom?
I don't want to betray my people.
Well said.
Come on.
Why don't you pick up the cup?
Do you fear I'll poison you?
Drink it. There’s no poison.
I wouldn’t do that.
You're my own son.
At worst,
I'd force you to abdicate.
You should not drink it.
Why?
The imperial doctor said
you shouldn't drink these days.
I would like to abdicate.
I'm leaving.
Hui,
since you are a filial child,
you might as well
drink this cup of wine for me.
Haven't you tried this wine before?
I have.
Take this cup of wine to His Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Step back.
You deliberately
put poison into the wine.
Drink it.
His Majesty is tired
and determined to rest in my chamber.
[Xianyang Palace]
Mother.
I beg you
to show His Majesty
his child.
Your Majesty,
the child didn't survive.
Take the child away first
Yes.
Mother. Mother.
I beg you
to give me back my child.
Mother.
My child.
Your Majesty, is it a boy?
Yes, I have a grandson.
Send out the news.
His Majesty has a son.
Lift the curfew in Central State.
Keep the lights in the palace on.
Celebrate for 15 days.
As you command.
Your Majesty,
General Qin rode out of the city in force
and headed south.
I won the world,
but he escaped.
No need to harbor regrets over that short-sighted man.
What about Concubine Jiang?
She has breathed her last.
What's your name?
Your Majesty,
my name is Yuan Wuchu.
I'm the deputy commander of the Royal Guards.
You will be in charge of
the Royal Guards in the future.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Put to death all the maidservants
and the chamberlains in His Majesty's palace,
and the imperial doctors
who delivered the baby for Concubine Jiang.
If you leave one alive,
you will forfeit your own life.
Understood.
Your Majesty,
Qin Yan is a member of the Nanchen Royal Army.
What if he spreads word of
His Majesty's death?
He dares not.
He is not afraid of me,
but his old master, the Junior Prince of Nanchen.
I guess he went south
to seek shelter in Nanxiao
as Liu Changshan did.
The celebration will remain the same.
The grand ceremony of the crown prince's canonization
will be held in 15 days.
Yes.
Here is the divorce settlement I wrote.
Put it away.
Once my aunt
gets the empress dowager's permission,
you can give this divorce settlement to the princess.
In this way,
she can leave here
free of restraints.
OK.
You should protect yourself
after you go to the palace.
[Central State]
Who left the city just now?
General,
it was the prefectural governor of Taiyuan.
Tai...
Let's go back to the mansion first.
You guard the gate.
Yes.
You come with me.
Look,
does this belong to Grand Mentor Xie?
Yes, it is.
Why do you have this?
Someone threw this into the Residence of Cui
wrapped in a brocade handkerchief,
saying it belonged to Grand Mentor Xie
and that you would know it if you saw it.
The letter says
there's been an accident in the palace and you should be careful.
Just now I found
the atmosphere strange at the city gate.
The common people were celebrating,
but the guards were primed and ready,
as if on guard.
Lady Cui,
a chamberlain came here
and said he would take Her Highness and Her Ladyship into the palace
to celebrate the birth of the prince.
It's reasonable for the princess to enter the palace.
But why should Shiyi go too?
That chamberlain said that
the Prince of Guangling grew up in the palace
and there were deep feelings between His and Her Majesty.
Her Majesty has always regarded
the Prince of Guangling as her own son,
so to celebrate the birth of the prince,
she will naturally ask
the Princess of Guangling to go
and enter the palace to celebrate together.
Please prepare a generous gift for me to bring
before I enter the palace for the celebration.
This is the empress dowager's imperial edict.
No one can act against it.
Mother, don't worry.
I'll take things as they come.
[Residence of Grand Mentor]
Shiyi,
why won't you come with me?
People are celebrating
the birth of the new prince.
They have long forgotten that
Zixing is the crown prince.
Life is most unpredictable.
Shiyi,
he suffers in the palace
to win the throne and marry you.
Be nice to him.
As long as you treat him well,
I'll try my best to fight for you.
I don't think
I heard what you said.
You can't say it again in the future.
Even if you are a princess,
you can't say that.
Zixing.
Your Highness.
Shiyi, I'll take you to the palace.
Her Majesty is giving a banquet,
accompanied by the imperial concubines.
It is inconvenient for me to attend the banquet.
So I'll leave after I take you in.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Have you ever seen the little prince?
Her Majesty was very nervous
when the eldest son of His Majesty was born
and took care of him in person in her chamber.
Even the prince's biological mother never saw him,
let alone anyone else.
People have died before in every palace here.
So it's much colder
than outside the palace.
The Cui family pay attention to etiquette and law.
Are you
doing this just to me,
or are you doing this to everyone?
Let's go.
Don't keep the empress dowager waiting.
Shiyi,
the relationships
between people
are really unpredictable.
Your cousin is the prefectural governor in Taiyuan
in order to monitor my father,
but you and I drink happily at this banquet
in the palace.
So you are Honored Concubine Jin.
I’m sorry I didn’t recognize you.
I have doubts in my heart.
I want to ask you something.
Go ahead.
His Majesty sent Cui Feng
to be the prefectural governor of Taiyuan County.
Was there a verbal command
to kill my father at any time?
The prefectural governor of state and county
is not just a supervisory role.
It also has the duty of dispatching troops and horses
to suppress
rebellions by local vassals or princes.
The thirteen prefectural governors
including my cousin in thirteen counties
are the same.
I think as long as General Jin
is loyal to His Majesty,
my cousin
will never use military power without authorization.
Thank you.
Get some rest.
The honored concubine drank a lot tonight.
How can she see His Majesty?
His Majesty dotes on Concubine Jiang only
and rarely summons other concubines,
especially Honored Concubine Jin.
It is well known in the palace that
she is not at peace with His Majesty.
Since Concubine Jiang gave birth to a son,
no concubine can see His Majesty.
[Jiafu Palace]
What are you looking at? Do you not want to keep your head?
What's going on?
Something big.
His Majesty
passed away.
My son
is gone.
[Jiafu Palace]
-His Majesty.
After shaving your heads,
you can temporarily live in the palace
and chant scriptures
for His Majesty.
I don't want to shave my head.
I had already guessed that
you would be the only one in His Majesty's harem
who will disobey me.
I have also guessed that
among the imperial concubines in the harem,
you dare not touch me alone.
Among the thirteen counties in the empire,
the Western State has the most troops and horses,
followed by Taiyuan County.
My father is never at the mercy of others.
You want me to cut my hair,
so that I can be trapped justifiably
in the palace
and you can use me to threaten my father.
Of all those in the harem,
you really are the smartest.
Unfortunately,
your man, my son,
is now the late emperor.
Send the concubines to the nunnery.
I'm afraid your marriage with Zixing
will be delayed.
His Majesty passed away, and all the people are grieving.
How dare I talk about marriage again?
Then you can
stay with me in the palace for a while.
It's my honor, Your Majesty.
Not really.
You are the only daughter of Cui Wenjun,
the unmarried wife of the Prince of Guangling,
the cousin of the prefectural governor in Taiyuan County,
and the disciple of the Junior Prince of Nanchen.
That's why
I want you to stay in the palace.
I predicted it.
[Taiji Palace]
When His Majesty was six years old,
I took his hand
and walked into Taiji Palace.
Now suddenly
he passed away,
but I'm still here.
Your Majesty, if you are sad,
you might as well go back to your chamber to have a rest.
When the late emperor died,
your uncle
and three of the royal family
worked together
to help His Majesty ascend the throne overnight,
which helped determine the overall situation.
Uncle told me about it.
It was a dangerous night.
If they were careless,
they would lose everything.
Tonight, I feel a lot of peace
when there is a member of the Cui family around me.
This is the place where emperors of all dynasties
handled government affairs.
Write three letters for me.
Yes.
This letter was sent to the Junior Prince of Nanchen,
telling him that
His Majesty has passed away
and my grandson is about to succeed to the throne.
The situation in the court is complex.
Ask him if he can enter the capital alone
as he did before
and kowtow to the new emperor
in front of all the officials.
Why are you not writing it?
I can't write it.
Why can't you write it?
Please find another person to do this for you.
I must not
write this letter.
Tell me what you're afraid of.
What do you fear
from a mere letter?
Are you afraid that Zhousheng Chen
will recognize your handwriting,
and venture into the city out of concern?
Do you two
really love each other secretly
as rumored?
Master treated all the eleven disciples
like relatives.
If my elders were asked
to write this letter today,
as long as Master recognized the handwriting,
he would come to save them for sure.
But if on this day,
my elders were to be present,
then absolutely no one would
do such a thing,
that would put Master at risk.
You're not afraid to die, huh?
Leave it to Your Majesty.
You're trying
to conceal
your love for him.
The Junior Prince of Nanchen
is really untidily romantic.
Shiyi,
your uncle saved me twice,
so I won't kill you.
Come here.
If my father finds out
you treated me like this,
he’ll kill you all.
Your Highness, calm down.
Other concubines
have been sent to a nunnery
and only you're still here,
which shows Her Majesty's
special care for you.
Her Majesty's care for me?
She's just afraid of my father.
Your Highness, as you were a child,
you might not know
the Empress Gao's brother
had more troops than your father.
But what happened in the end?
He was killed
on a narrow path in the palace.
It's exactly that one you just passed by.
You're honored women.
As long as you don't hurt yourselves,
no one can do that to you.
Close the door.
How did Empress Dowager Gao's brother die
at that time back then?
After His Majesty ascended the throne,
he was tricked into the palace
by Her Majesty Empress Dowager.
On a path in the palace,
he was surrounded
and strangled by soldiers.
Does Her Majesty want
to deal with my father or your master
using this old trick?
Your Majesty.
How is the situation outside the palace?
The city people are still taking part in the grand ceremony.
It's very crowded and lively.
Hasn't Counselor-in-chief come?
He's on his way.
Close the gate.
Without my instructions,
no one enters the Central State.
Yes.
[Central State]
Move it, now.
This is His Excellency Counselor-in-chief's carriage.
You're surrounded.
Who are you?
Nanchen Royal Army.
[Xuanguang Palace]
How boring.
Your Highness,
you don't seem sad about His Majesty's death.
He didn't have me in his heart,
so I am not sad.
But you held a wedding witnessed by heaven and earth
and consummated your marriage.
Do you have no special feeling
for His Majesty?
As he was the emperor,
I married him.
We consummated our marriage
as I wanted to have a son
and be the Empress Dowager.
He has feelings
for Concubine Jiang,
but I had no feelings for him.
My father
will control the whole country
sooner or later.
By then,
he'll be close to death.
It seems
we can only
be allies tonight.
Yes.
You and I are destined to be mortal enemies later.
But before that,
we should first manage to come out of this alive.
Your Highness.
Your Excellency has a clear conscience.
Why do you kneel down?
I,
I finally got to see you, Your Highness.
We'll be saved.
Qi Zhenzhen wants
to command vassals with her grandson.
No.
In fact, the baby
wasn't His Majesty's son.
Didn't Concubine Jiang give birth to a son?
Yes, she did,
but the baby died that night.
To keep it a secret,
Her Majesty killed
29 people in Concubine Jiang's living palace,
including the imperial doctors, palace maids and chamberlains.
She even killed Concubine Jiang.
I was forced to,
so I didn't dare to resist.
Your Excellency's family is safe in your residence.
Don't say that.
No.
She...
My master doesn't want to look into it.
If you do as he says,
you'll have a chance to redeem your crime in due course.
I'd like to follow His Highness's orders.
From tonight on,
they will follow you
wherever you go.
OK, OK.
What will
she do next?
Help the new emperor ascend the throne and hold court.
Since she wants the new emperor to ascend the throne,
help her do it.
Um...
We should let
a non-existent prince ascend the throne?
Yes.
Do you still remember
how Liu Yuan was executed?
Yes, surely.
Do everything as I said.
Don't have an ulterior motive,
or you'll be the first person
who goes to accompany His Majesty.
I'll atone for my past crimes
and act at your command.
Uncle, thank you
for guarding the frontier for my father these past years.
There is a patterned sword and an axe decorated with gold for you.
In the future, report to me at any time you want.
You can go to court by sedan
and enter the hall with a sword.
I only have the wooden sword
Your Majesty gave me with me today.
As your uncle,
I think
you are more important than the throne.
Uncle.
Sorry for not
keeping you safe.
[Taiji Palace]
Your Majesty.
-Your Majesty.
Your Majesty. Why did
you die so young?
Your Majesty.
Our country can't be without an emperor.
Though His Majesty passed away,
he left
a newly-born son for us.
I think we should
help him ascend the throne
to stabilize the court and appease the people.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty Empress Dowager,
it concerns the security of our kingdom.
If the newly-born prince
ascends the throne,
I'm afraid the vassals will resist and stir up great turmoil.
Your Majesty, please think it over.
It's common for a young prince to ascend the throne in our dynasty.
Emperor Gaozu ascended the throne at 5,
and the late emperor at 6.
Both of them were assisted by the empress dowager.
Why can't it work that way now?
Not exactly.
Your Majesty,
it was a temporary expedient
for the late emperor to ascended the throne at 6.
The Gao family monopolized the court affairs back then.
If the late emperor didn't ascend the throne,
then the Central State
would be controlled by the Gao family for sure.
We're not in imminent danger.
Why don't we
choose a man of the right age
from the royal family to be the heir?
The late emperor's remains are scarcely cold yet.
His newly-born son is crying in my chamber.
But you can't wait
to support another now.
Without any selfish motives,
I just think of the interests of our country.
Don't make excuses to me.
Explain to Her Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Prepare for the enthronement.
Yes.
[Mingguang Palace]
The Cui family's opposition
upsets me a lot.
After the enthronement, everything will be settled.
It's useless
even if the Cui family opposes us
together with other prominent families.
But we
can't hide the baby's not existing
for long.
Do you still remember
the deceased Prince of Lintao
has a 5-year-old son
named Liu Zizhen?
Besides Zhousheng Chen,
he's the clansman most closely
related to the late emperor.
I'll bring him into the palace tomorrow.
Your Majesty, after this matter,
you can make an edict to the public that
you were tricked by Concubine Jiang
into believing her pregnancy
and so put
all the blame on her.
But she already died.
People outside the palace don't know it.
Then you can make an edict
sentencing Concubine Jiang to death
and letting Liu Zizhen ascend the throne.
In this way, you can convince
the officials and vassals.
A 5-year-old child
is at your mercy.
I'm afraid the old officials
wouldn’t believe such an absurdity.
I'm behind you.
Send Liu Zizhen to the palace.
Yes.
You're worried about Shiyi?
Shiyi is in the imperial palace...
Her Majesty knows
she can hold back many forces at play,
so she won't be in immediate danger.
If so, why are you
still worried?
Go to the Residence of Cui.