[English subtitles are available]
[Once and Only]
[Episode 21]
Your Highness.
You must've been worried
for the past few days.
What exactly happened?
Jin Rong attacked Henei.
My uncle led an army to suppress the rebellion.
What about my brother Cui Feng?
How is he?
According to the spies,
Governor Cui left
Taiyuan County earlier.
We still have no idea where he is now.
If he left early,
he's probably hiding somewhere,
waiting to meet up with my Master.
When my uncle returns,
he may have news about him.
If he attacked Henei,
why is the Eastern Palace locked up as well?
The Royal Guards joined the Qi family in rebellion.
After my uncle led the army out,
they took the opportunity to kidnap His Majesty
and went to Jin Rong for shelter.
His Majesty was kidnapped?
After my uncle left,
he ordered General Zhou and the Royal Guards
to protect the city together.
General Zhou...
What happened to him?
He is seriously injured
and hasn't woken up yet.
Shiyi.
He's in my uncle's chambers.
If you want to go…
Meng Luan, summon the imperial doctor.
The imperial doctor has already seen His Highness.
His Highness hasn't slept for days
and said that
he would only go to rest
after seeing you.
Let me bring you to your room.
Get some shut-eye.
Rest for a while.
Shiyi.
Don't go.
Xiao Yan.
I'm actually no different from you.
I'm not close
with my family.
Tonight,
let's guard here
and send Zizhen's soul off.
Are you feeling better?
Am I having a fever?
I'll get the imperial doctor.
I'm showing you my weakness.
Can't you see?
I'll ask Meng Luan to come.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Attendant Cui is outside the palace
waiting to see Your Highness.
Let him in.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll go back to Xuanguang Palace first.
Your Highness.
Spread the news of His Majesty's death
to the Central State in three days.
Jin Rong has shown me his sincerity
with their lives.
Attendent Cui.
How will you show your loyalty?
I...
I'll show my loyalty
with only one sentence.
Zhousheng Chen
is a great threat.
If you don't get rid of him,
it'll be hard for you to rule.
Master.
I would like to lead the scouting camp
into Taiyuan County first.
Be careful.
Yes, Master.
Cui Feng is now in the hands of Jin Rong.
Only a few generals know about this.
Don't reveal it to anyone else.
[Hall of the Heavenly Kings]
When will you take me to the Eastern Palace?
Be patient.
It's not the time yet.
I can wait.
You and her haven't even gone through the ceremony yet anyway.
Why did you make the move early?
I have no idea either.
You gave the order
to make the move early?
She's a member of the Cui family.
If the two of you got married,
who would recognize me as the Empress?
Whatever the case,
as long as you're not on the throne,
you can't marry her.
You are Liu Hui's Honored Concubine.
I must first find a good reason
to marry you,
let alone the serious task of making you the empress.
Even if you list hundreds of reasons,
you can't convince me.
Liu Zixing.
The Jin's army
is fighting for you in the frontlines.
I hope you don't let us down.
Fine.
I promise you.
[Xuanguang Palace]
Your Highness.
Have a seat, I'll ask someone to prepare tea.
No need.
I'll leave shortly after telling you something.
Have a seat.
His Majesty has passed away.
When?
Nanchen Royal Army reported it secretly today.
He was still a child.
Your uncle has submitted a letter,
wishing I'd take the throne.
Do you disapprove?
You and I are destined to be married.
You can tell me anything.
Do you wish to hear the truth, Your Highness?
The emperor's career is unpredictable and always changing.
In a short period of time,
two young masters have been replaced in the Central State.
The people's support accumulated over the years
has been depleted.
The choice of the next emperor
must be chosen with great scrutiny.
Not to mention,
Your Highness is not the Crown Prince.
I was
once considered the future emperor.
I was considered the future emperor.
I was considered the crown prince.
I don't blame you for forgetting it.
No one has ever taken it seriously
except for me.
When I was brought into the palace,
my father had no army to command and no power to win.
That was why he had no capacity to fight power for me.
What I've achieved thus far
is all my own efforts.
Perhaps in your mind,
my uncle is the best candidate.
I've never thought so.
My master has little interest in the throne…
You should call him “uncle”
as I do.
Do you know why
your maid wasn't allowed to enter the palace?
She has been with you for nearly ten years in the Western State.
Her presence
would remind you of the Western State,
thus you'd talk about it
and forget
who you belong to.
I had no selfish intent
when I said those things.
It's not appropriate to
talk about marriage for the time being.
Let's postpone our marriage
for now.
It's just a show
to appease the Jin family.
Your Highness, why are you so distressed?
My heart is tormented more than hers
when I see her suffer.
Take them all away!
Stop!
Xinghua.
They are my parents
and siblings.
Don't you know that?
The Qi family is guilty of the most heinous crimes.
Nine generations of its clan shall be executed,
including you, Princess.
You dare to hurt me?
Why don't I?
If it weren't for your high status,
I wouldn't have come to get you myself!
How dare you! Let me go!
General Li! General Li!
Hold on, General Li!
General Li!
May I have a word?
The Prince of Guangling had given orders.
Seeing how loyal the Cui family has been,
the wife of Governor Cui,
Qi Xinghua shall be pardoned.
To execute the Qi family
is the consensus of all ministers.
Do you
want to protect her?
Yes.
I want to protect her.
She is not only from the Qi family.
She's also our Cui family's daughter-in-law.
General-in-chief.
Can you let a member of the Cui family go?
Since you said so,
I'll accept this royal order.
Take them away.
Go! Go!
Let them go!
Xinghua! Xinghua!
Xinghua!
Mother!
You can't save them.
I…
I'll go beg the crown prince.
Wenjun.
Princess Xinghua…
The Residence of Cui is not seeing any guests today.
Ask this guest to leave.
Yes.
This way please.
Brother Zixing.
I beg you to giver orders
to release my parents and other families.
Why did you barge into the palace?
They wouldn't let me see you.
They said it was your order.
I did give the order.
I have my own reasons
for not seeing you.
Executing the Qi family to calm the people's anger
is already a foregone conclusion.
You should stay in the Residence of Cui
for your own sake.
You...
You want to pave your way to the throne
with the blood of the Qi family?
Qi Zhenzhen has done evil for more than ten years.
She has offended everyone.
It's not that I want them to die.
It's that no one wants them to live.
Stay at the Residence of Cui.
After things have settled,
I'll find a way out for you.
But they are my own parents,
how can I hide?
I can't just stand by and
watch them die.
Brother Zixing.
Please help me.
Can you do something?
Brother Zixing!
I can only protect you.
I'll send her back to the Residence of Cui.
Your Highness.
Did the cold wake you?
I'm feeling fine.
Come sit down.
Where's Shu?
I came here in the morning
and saw that the fire was burning weak.
Go and prepare breakfast.
Since I entered the palace,
I've never had breakfast
with Your Highness.
Go now!
[Xuanguang Palace]
Yes.
Let's go inside.
It's cold outside.
You're cold.
I was wrong, Shiyi.
I'm used to being alone in the palace,
so I don't know how to get along with people.
I mean...
Get along in a normal way.
Give way.
What's going on now?
Is the enemy already here?
Don't panic!
I bring news of victory from the Junior Prince of Nanchen.
His Highness conquered Taiyuan County
and has won every battle.
The rebels are defenselessly
and fleeing in disarray.
Junior Prince of Nanchen! Junior Prince of Nanchen!
[Central State]
If Master refuses to enter the city,
I'll have no reason to see Shiyi.
General Feng.
Are you worried about Miss Cui?
Why do you say I'm worried?
Though I can't see
the sun or the moon,
I am able to see through people's hearts.
The night before Shiyi got married,
we talked all night.
I felt upset for her.
Xie Chen.
Would you perform a divination for me?
About Shiyi's marriage.
I have done so already.
How is it?
Not very good?
It wasn't accurate.
How can you not be good at divination?
In the horoscope,
she's not destined to get married.
That does sound inaccurate.
Actually, that Liu Zixing
treats her very well.
I can tell.
What you see may not be true.
Where is the royal army now?
Just outside the Central State.
They're already back?
That's right.
They came back to recuperate for a few days before heading out again.
Why didn't they enter the city?
It's my master's habit.
They prefer to station their troops outside the city.
They did the same thing in the Western State.
What a pity.
The people were eager to see the royal army.
What else did you overhear?
They say
the Junior Prince of Nanchen wants to
completely eradicate the Jin rebels.
He has sent a royal order
to have all the county governors to send troops.
Does that mean
the Prince of Pingqin is coming too?
Help me ask around again.
I want to see if the Prince of Pingqin is coming to the capital this time.
What are you laughing at?
If you want to know these,
just ask His Highness.
They came to the capital to quell the rebellion,
yet all I think about is catching up with an old friend.
It wouldn't be appropriate.
Forget it, ignore my request.
[Central State]
Hold it!
Where are you from?
What's your intention?
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
Prince of Pingqin, don't be angry.
He's a newcomer.
He doesn't know the rules.
Come here.
Well…
What are you afraid of?
Yes, yes.
Your Highness.
How do you know me?
[Ping]
You saw the flag.
Yes.
So anyone
who has a piece of cloth and makes a flag
can pretend to be me?
What if I'm a fake?
What if you let me in the Central State
and I have all the dignitaries
beheaded?
I was wrong.
Get up.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Whose soldiers are you?
Replying to Your Highness,
I'm a member of the Royal Guards.
Who does the Royal Guards obey?
The Prince of Guangling.
The Prince of Guangling?
How old is he?
Has he ever led an army?
He dares to take over the government now?
Your Highness.
Prince of Guangling.
The Prince of Guangling is a member of the Liu clan.
Shut it!
You can tell what a general is like by observing his soldiers.
Seeing how weak you are,
I know he's never fought before.
Let's go!
[Central State]
Go, go, go!
I've been vexed all the way.
Tell me
why did you give up my sister-in-law to someone else?
We're not
in that kind of relationship.
You won't tell me the truth, huh?
Monk, you say something.
I don't know secularities.
You don't know secularities?
When you were in Nanxiao,
you had a bunch of wives and concubines.
There were girls throwing flowers at your carriage
when you went out.
You were a flirtatious prince.
You don't know secularities?
It seems that the Prince of Pingqin
knows a lot about me.
You follow my sworn brother,
shouldn't I investigate your background?
You should.
Well...
In my opinion,
since your last name isn't Liu anymore,
you're no longer in chains.
Why not…
What have they given you?
Aside for making you vow
to fight for them,
what else did they give you?
They only gave you this.
But even that you gave to me.
It's a precious thing.
Of course it's precious.
With this,
the government gave me a thousand war horses.
In Beichen,
only with war horses could I recruit soldiers.
This is how
I worked my way up.
He is my sworn brother
and more importantly, my confidant.
Most of His Highness' friends
were once helped by him.
Don't you think it's a pity?
Don't you have regrets?
How about we talk business first?
Go ahead.
Business... business...
Tomorrow, my royal army
and the reinforcements from the regional princes will go first.
I'll leave the Central State to you.
I'll guard the Central State?
Yes.
I've brought
all the best soldiers.
Those Regional Princes are all
slimy characters.
There is no way
they would give you their elite.
That's precisely why
you need to defend the city.
I don't understand.
If you were only called to the capital,
someone would surely suspect
you and I were joining forces
to take over the empire.
That's why I've summoned
reinforcements from all the Regional Princes
to make it not so suspicious.
What…
It's just an expedition…
You've really thought about everything.
Once we leave tomorrow,
the people of the capital
will go under your protection.
And her?
Well.
Before you go on your expedition,
let's go see Eleven.
It's not proper.
What's so improper about going to see your disciple?
Are you kidding?
I will take you there.
Forget it.
You're asking me for help,
and not the other way around.
You entrusted me with the Central State.
So, you have to do
whatever I want you to do.
Good timing, Feng Qiao.
Feng Qiao, go with us
to the place we're going later.
You can avoid suspicion
with a female disciple there.
Monk! Monk!
You'll come with us too.
It'll be better with the monk there too.
Let's go.
Come with me! Let's go!
Come on, come with me!
Let's go!
Eleven!
Cui Eleven!
Your sworn brother is here!
Come out!
Master.
I was wondering
who here in the palace would call me Eleven.
In my eyes, you are
always that little girl who couldn't speak
in Nanchen royal mansion.
Shu, prepare some tea.
Yes.
No, I'll do it myself.
Come in.
No one comes here normally.
So it's a bit messy.
It's hot.
Want some more?
That's enough.
When did you guys get here?
Half an hour ago.
They said it was improper to see you.
What's so improper about this?
You see?
We've come in, right?
Prince of Pingqin has great power.
Who dares to mess with you?
That's true.
When will you go on the expedition, Master?
Tomorrow.
So soon?
Yes.
What?
Do you worry about us?
When have we ever lost a battle?
For outsiders, the royal army
is invincible.
But to me,
those who fight in the battlefield
are my closest relatives.
Every time you guys go on an expedition,
I would be worried sick.
It's like that every time.
I know.
[Xuanguang Palace]
Take care.
May Master
live up to the people's expectations and be invincible.
May all the generals
live up to the royal orders and be victorious.
♫Can't bear it, my heart is burning♫
♫The dependence I feel♫
♫I'm suffering with you♫
♫Suffered so much from this sea of pain♫
♫I can leap down for you♫
♫Stain my painful love red♫
♫The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♫
♫Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♫
♫Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♫
Not looking back
means not expecting to return.
♫The snow falling, the sand flying♫
Only without worries,
would someone
♫It's hard to leave him unattached♫
become fearless
and risk their lives on the battlefield.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Please come back safely!
Your Highness!
Come back safely!
[Baima Temple]
If I pray with you,
whose relatives
do you think will win?
Why are you here?
I'm a hostage.
I've been living in the Baima Temple for a long time.
You haven't answered my question.
Which side of us will win?
Nanchen Royal Army has never been defeated.
What if they lose?
The Junior Prince of Nanchen
fought in wars ever since he was 13 years old
and he has never been defeated.
Since Jin Rong rose to power,
only news of victory
has been sent to the Central State.
Princess Consort.
Another news of victory?
General Zhou is awake.
Tianxing.
You're awake.
I'll do it.
Oh, right.
I heard that Master and his men
had marched to Taiyuan.
Yes.
They've won every battle.
What about your elder brother?
Is he safe?
I haven't heard from him.
Here.
Your Highness.
What did General Jin say?
He's begging me to save him.
He's been trapped by my uncle for 16 days.
His army has run out of food.
They'd have to eat each other if it continues.
Your father has lost the battle.
Your Highness wants to abandon us?
How can you tell?
Though Zhousheng Chen won,
it won't stop you from ascending to the throne.
You will be the emperor for sure.
That is why you
won't care about my father.
Why are you keeping quiet?
You must be thinking of how to get rid of me!
Would you hide me away quietly?
Or just kill me?
I want you to go to Taiyuan County
to persuade your father to surrender.
Impossible.
My father would rather die than surrender.
Only by persuading him to surrender
can you survive.
All of you are useless!
You can't even stop Zhousheng Chen
for half a month!
Get out!
Yuan Wuchu!
I'm here.
Go.
Bring that man here.
Yes.
Prefectural Governor Cui.
Are you still not kneeling?
I in my life
only kneel to my parents,
His Majesty
and the Junior Prince of Nanchen.
You've been in the Nanchen Royal Army for many years.
You know them best.
If you are willing to help me,
I will share half of
the realm with you.
Bring him back.
Force Zhousheng Chen to retreat.
Yes!
It's no better than
the Northwest here.
Yesterday,
the war horses were so cold
that they forgot how to eat grass.
It's already December.
It should be getting cold.
I really want to go back to the Western State
to have a bowl of lamb soup.
-That's right.
That's true.
It's been a long time since I've had
a bowl of lamb soup from my hometown.
That's right.
-Have a bowl of lamb soup.
-General.
General, they've brought a man out,
saying it's Prefectural Governor Cui.
Scouting Camp.
Follow me!
Yes.
General Cui.
Xiaoyu.
I can't believe he's still alive.
They want us to withdraw our troops and return to Pingyin
before they'll let General Cui go.
General Feng.
What do you think?
Say something!
Xiaoyu.
Do you remember our
battle in Shouyang?