[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 23]
Your Highness.
I, Yang Shao, owe you more than an apology.
Zhousheng Chen plotted to usurp the throne.
He deserves to be executed.
Counselor-in-chief Liu Wei and the noblemen from the Liu family
were all killed by him
The rebellious ministers are in power, the loyal ministers suffer.
Jin Rong!
You will be punished by the heavens!
Do you want to die?
Your Highness!
I am too incompetent!
Your Highness.
-Minister Wen!
-Minister Wen...
Who else wants to die?
Come out!
I'll let you die for your country!
We are incompetent!
Your Highness was wrongly convicted, but we can do nothing.
Your Highness, I'll go with you!
-Minster Wang!
Minster Wang...
Fellow ministers.
You don't have to die for me.
Your Highness, I'll go with you!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
I'll go with you!
-Your Highness!
-Your Highness! Your Highness!
Jin Rong, you'll get what you deserve!
Your Highness!
-Your Highness!
I'll go with you!
They have gone insane.
They've all gone insane.
Begin the execution!
-Yes!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
I'll go with you!
What's wrong?
Are you having a nightmare?
I'll get the imperial doctor.
Your Highness! Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness!
-Your Highness!
Kill them!
Kill them all!
Generals, please hold on!
Liu Zixing sent out the news that
Nanchen Royal Army has rebelled.
Now all the rebels and traitors
who have been defeated by you,
as long as they come to Pingyin to join the emperor,
will all be given the title of Vassal.
Now all your enemies are coming.
Generals!
Retreat is the best course of action!
Only by retreating,
will there be a day of revenge.
Master is still in the palace.
How can we retreat?
Advisor Xiao!
Without His Highness back,
we will never leave.
I'll bring him back.
[Jiangdu Palace]
I came here to pick up the body of our prince.
Why bother to pick up the body
of a rebel?
Not to mention that he is a sinner.
I will not let you take him away.
I am sure you know who I was
before I became a monk.
If you don't let me enter the palace
to collect the prince's body,
I will return to Nanxiao,
put on my armor, pick up the sword,
[Jiangdu Palace]
lead my great army to take over your territory.
Master!
Don't come closer!
You won't bear to see this.
This is death by dismemberment.
General Feng.
Your Ladyship.
Which palace are you from?
When did you come here?
Why have all the palace maids changed?
Shu.
Shu...
Your Ladyship.
Where is Shu?
I don't know.
Your Ladyship.
You can't go out.
There's trouble outside.
What happened?
I don't know.
Your Ladyship.
[Luanning Palace]
You really can't go out.
Your Ladyship.
Where is this place?
This is the Eastern Palace.
Why am I in the Eastern Palace?
His Highness has ordered
imperial doctors to bring you
to the Eastern Palace.
[Luanning Palace]
This is His Highness' residence.
It's heavily guarded.
Why did he send me to the Eastern Palace?
What happened?
I don't know.
I'm just following orders.
Your Ladyship.
Please return to your living palace.
Don't make things difficult for me.
♫I don't seek glory of the multitude♫
[Luanning Palace]
♫I only want to have a quiet conscience♫
♫With a pot of liquor, I travel all over the world♫
♫The horse's hooves sound on the battlefield♫
♫I am griping a great ambition in my hand♫
♫I don't fear the rain and wind and have an inflexible will♫
♫As a general, I may forget any wound on the shoulder♫
♫I am willing to stick to a ray of light for a lifetime♫
May the land
be free of war.
May the people of Beichen enjoy peace and prosperity.
May the people prosper
for evermore.
May the people of Beichen enjoy peace and prosperity.
May the people prosper
for evermore.
♫The sun and moon know my heart♫
♫Forgive me as I never retreat on the battlefield♫
♫There will be a grand scene of prosperity♫
♫I don't expect people to praise me, and I just want to have a clear conscience♫
By order of the regent,
[Chengming Gate]
until he returns,
no one is allowed near the Eastern Palace
and no one is allowed to see Miss Cui.
Why can't I see her?
She's my sworn sister.
Get out of the way.
Do you wish to die?
You think you guys
can stop me?
If I let you in,
I will also die.
I'll let you die, then.
Men inside!
Prepare the fire!
We'll die with this Eastern Palace!
What are you doing?
Your Highness!
Our lives are worthless.
If we resist, we die.
If we let you in,
we also die.
In that case,
we'll
burn down the whole Eastern Palace
to have her join us in hell!
If you dare
harm my sworn sister,
I will cut you all into little pieces!
Your Highness!
The Eastern Palace is heavily guarded.
We have no way to get in.
I knew it.
How I wish I could
tear down this palace.
Prince of Pingqin.
I'm Yang Shao.
Yang Shao?
Jin Rong's dog.
I'm not here to fight you today.
I just want to give you a piece of advice.
Even if you stay,
you'll not be able to help her.
You would only get yourself killed.
I don't need you
to teach me what to do.
I don't want to talk too much
to an ignoramus either.
I was just trying to help His Highness
keep some strength of the royal army.
This is what I owe him.
Whose side are you on?
It doesn't matter which side I'm on.
I owe Miss Cui two lives.
I owe His Highness a debt of gratitude for not killing me.
If you believe me,
go out of the city for a few days
and wait for my message.
If you don't believe me,
I'll save
Miss Cui myself.
Slow down.
It's okay. It's okay.
Good wine.
Good wine!
You know what.
There was definitely something wrong with that carriage that day.
Yang Shao is very suspicious.
I'll go to the general tomorrow.
Yang Shao, I knew it was you!
What did you say?
He let Zhou Tianxing go?
We followed him out of the city
but Yuan Wuchu ambushed us.
All the men I took died.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
Get out!
That is the person you trusted?
You loser!
He insulted me,
and I have to crown his daughter as my empress.
The territory has already belonged to Your Majesty.
One day, these people
will be eliminated one by one.
Your Majesty.
The blessed moment has arrived.
Kneel!
Hail!
Long live the emperor!
Hail once more!
Kowtow!
Greetings, Lady Cui.
I've never been friends with Jin Rong.
I wonder what the reason
for your visit is?
I've been entrusted by His Highness from the Western State,
to ask for your help, Lady Cui.
You've made up your mind?
From now on,
I'll leave Wushui to you.
After you return to Qinghe,
don't delay
and move south with them immediately.
Only the people and books matter.
As for the other things, just leave them behind.
What about you?
Shiyi is still trapped in the palace.
Back then, for the sake of the Cui family,
I gave up on her father.
This time, I can't give up my own daughter
for the Cui family again.
Go.
Xinghua.
Thank you for taking care of me these days.
I'm going back to the palace.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Xinghua.
Since you married into our family,
neither I nor Feng
have ever treated you badly.
Now that you're leaving,
I have a favor to ask of you.
As long as I can.
I will do it.
I want to see my daughter.
Is that too much to ask for?
Zixing has been keeping
a very close eye on her.
Several times I have entered the palace,
but I have not been able to see her.
I will try to persuade him
to let you see each other.
Be patient, auntie.
The time will come.
Thank you.
[Luanning Palace]
Leave.
Your Highness.
His Majesty has decreed
Miss Cui shall be conferred with the title of Honored Concubine.
The ceremony shall be held on an auspicious day.
This is His Majesty's nursemaid.
Lady Li.
She has been working
for His Majesty for many years.
She will be in charge of serving Your Highness in the future.
I'll take my leave.
Your lowly servant greets Your Highness.
You'll give her a conferring ceremony that of the empress?
I have already made you the empress.
You are honored by all the people.
And now you come to make a fuss
about the conferring ceremony of an honored concubine?
I'm not being petty.
I pity her.
Liu Zixing.
You killed her master and her senior sister.
You put her cousin under siege.
And now you're trying to use this to cover up your sins.
If I were her,
I would wish to eat your flesh
and drink your blood.
[Reporting Document]
Get out.
Get out of here!
[Reporting Document]
Meng Luan.
Yes.
Before the ceremony,
you must keep a close eye on Shiyi.
Without my permission,
no one is allowed to see her.
Yes.
[Luanning Palace]
Your Majesty.
How is my Honored Concubine these days?
She hasn't spoken much these days.
I'm afraid...
You were my nursemaid.
You should be the most honest person to me
in the whole palace.
I'm afraid that
her old illness from childhood would recur.
I've been so busy with government affairs these days
that I've neglected you.
You should be my empress.
What your uncle has always wished for
is to see you become the empress.
I remember that.
I have invited
all the famous clans to the capital city.
If you need anything, let me know.
[I want my master, senior brothers and sisters to come to the capital city.]
Uncle led the troops far away from the border.
I'm afraid he won't be back in time.
I still have to see my ministers.
You should get some rest.
The Prince of Runan, Liu Cheng.
The Prefectural governor of Beiqing State, Lu Jun.
The Prefectural governor of Yiyang County, Lu Shida.
And
all the Nanjing State
have surrendered to Nanxiao.
Our border with Nanxiao
has collapsed.
We must take things
step by step.
Have some tea first
to moisten your throat.
What about Shouyang?
Shou...Shouyang...
Previously,
it'd been guarded by Cui Feng.
But now...
I ordered you to invite the famous clans to the capital city.
Did anyone respond?
I'm incompetent.
Zixing.
The reputation of Cui Wenjun in Wushui
is not accumulated overnight.
It's been built up over time.
If you want to win over those famous clans,
you must make up with Cui Wenjun.
He can't be trusted.
Tomorrow.
You go invite Cui Wenjun to the palace.
Tell her I have a favor to ask of her.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Xiye Gate]
The Yang clan of Hongnong
is loyal and modest.
Disciples of theirs are all over the territory.
The Zhangsun clan of Jiyang
is holding the military power.
They are the only ones
who can suppress the rebels inside the Pass.
And the Yuwen clan
often lives in the northwest.
Their foundations are much deeper than the Jin clan.
These clans hold the military power.
They are the ones
Your Majesty must win over.
Can you help me
invite them to the capital city?
Candidates for all official positions in the court,
from the Counselor-in-chief to the Praetorian Guard,
can be recommended by you.
As long as you assist me,
the prestige of the Cui family
will only be better than it was before.
As for the Empress Jin,
I had no other choice.
I hope you can understand that.
In my heart,
Shiyi is my real wife
and my only empress.
Then may I ask Your Majesty,
when will I be able to see Shiyi?
Your Majesty won't let anyone near her.
I can understand that.
But I am her mother.
Is Your Majesty worried that
I would harm my own
daughter?
I don't want her to find out about what happened in Pingyin.
Nowadays, everyone knows that
the Junior Prince of Nanchen
was executed for conspiracy.
If that is true,
Shiyi
will understand your decision.
Or is Your Majesty worried
she doesn't know right from wrong?
Shiyi is sentimental.
I'm afraid she can't bear this news.
She is sentimental,
but she knows loyalty better.
If you can help me
persuade her to accept this matter,
I'll be grateful.
Meng Luan.
Yes.
Bring her to the Eastern Palace.
Lady Cui.
I treat her with sincerity.
I hope
for the sake of your daughter
you won't make her suffer too much.
When getting on the state bed, face forward,
climb from the foot of the bed into the brocade quilt.
From the empress down to the palace maids,
no one is allowed to turn their backs to His Majesty.
The same applies to getting off the state bed.
You should face His Majesty,
and slowly get off the bed from the bottom of the bed.
[Luanning Palace]
I will follow you inside.
Those are orders of His Majesty.
You think I don't want to see my own daughter
live happily?
His Highness has already passed.
What's the use for me telling her the truth?
I've seen this country change hands too many times.
I'm done caring about these things.
I just want Shiyi to live a happy life.
I'm glad
that's what you think.
[Luanning Palace]
Shiyi.
You don't want to talk?
Let me take a good look at you.
You look like how you were
before you went to the Western State.
Zhousheng Chen has rebelled.
Impossible!
That's impossible, Mother!
Calm down.
You must calm down,
if you want to hear me out.
In the Pingyin Palace,
His Highness plotted a rebellion.
Fortunately, his evil intention was noticed by the Palace Attendant Cui.
Zhousheng Chen was captured.
His Majesty ordered he was to be executed by dismemberment.
The execution lasted three hours.
Yet he didn't even utter a cry of pain
and refused to plead guilty.
Death by dismemberment.
Shiyi.
Shiyi, just cry it all out!
I know you can't take it.
I'm here.
Cry out, Shiyi.
Shiyi.
There are many rules in the palace.
It's not easy for me
to come visit you like this.
Take care of yourself.
Mother, he wouldn't rebel.
He wouldn't rebel.
Lady Cui.
It's almost time.