[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 13]
Dad, have some tea.
Stop.
This...
You did it on purpose, didn’t you?
By the way, Ning,
why haven’t you
mentioned Li Qingfeng for quite some time?
How is he now?
Didn't father ask me not to mention him?
When did I say that?
I told you not to mention him so much.
OK. Calm down.
Your shoulders always get tight when you're excited.
Relax.
Here, here, here.
By the way,
I heard
your charity chamber
is well-recieved.
People are all saying positive things about you.
I think
Li Qingfeng
must be very impressed by you.
Mr. Luo is.
Li Qingfeng just said something good about it.
In this matter,
I am also very impressed by you.
Li Qingfeng only said something good about it?
What's so great about him?
Li Qingfeng just doesn't ingratiate himself with other people.
So you mean
I ingratiate myself with others?
Father.
Why do you dislike Li Qingfeng so much?
Well.
Because he had the nerve to refuse you.
That's why I hold a grudge against him.
How did you know that?
It wasn't your seventh brother who told me.
How would I know
something so important like this?
Right, father?
Father, have some tea.
As the saying goes, no one knows a man better than his own father.
Ning,
I know your temper
and your personality.
As long as you are determined,
no matter what others say,
you would never change your mind.
But I still have to tell you
what is needed to be told.
Since Li Qingfeng has rejected you,
I think you should stop getting involved with him
so that you won't tarnish our family's reputation
and your own, understand?
Yes.
Speaking from the bottom of my heart,
as long as you're sure he's the one,
even if I have no other choice,
or even if I don't want you to be with him,
I will
never stop you.
But it doesn't mean
I will
see my precious daughter suffer.
So I suggest that
you talk it through with Li Qingfeng
as soon as possible,
and ask him to tell you what he really thinks
so that he won’t get in the way of your happiness for the rest of you life.
I have been looking for a chance to talk to him.
If he refuses me again,
then I’ll give up.
But if he doesn't,
then I’ll seize the chance
and that'll reassure you
to show you what a good daughter I am to you.
You should have done this earlier.
Serve tea.
Let me do it for you.
My daughter is serving the tea.
The tea my daughter serves
tastes great.
[Sanfu Orphanage]
Please come in.
I've been thinking about it day and night.
But I still can’t figure it out.
What is it?
When I came here, I said that
I'm good at easy work.
But since the first job,
I've been doing the hardest work.
Why?
I seriously suspect that Luo Ye
and Li Qingfeng are trying to give me a hard time.
That's ridiculous.
Just think about it.
Even that's really the case,
you have finished all of the work.
That means
you are a good general director.
That's only because you taught me well.
I didn’t teach you anything.
Look at Luo.
She’s been helping you,
but you never thanked her.
I've always been good to her.
Whenever I brought you something delicious or entertaining,
I always gave her the same.
Ask her if you don’t believe me.
You should be much nicer to her.
Much nicer?
My Lady, he's already very nice to me.
Besides,
I didn't help him that much.
Then help him more in the future.
Okay, I'll do as you say.
Much nicer.
Here are some toys for kids.
This is a...
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
Idiot, what are you laughing at?
You! Don't slack off!
Get back to work!
Okay, I will.
...the garden. This is our whole idea.
This way!
Be careful.
Is this the slide?
It looks interesting.
Of course.
You haven't seen such a beautiful slide, have you?
This is my idea.
Awesome.
This way.
This way. This way.
OK.
Are you tired?
Do you want some water?
Qingfeng, do you want some water?
No.
Thank you.
By the way,
remember to
put the swing there later.
Let me see if this slide is sturdy enough.
I don't suggest you do so.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
This is made for children.
It’s not sturdy enough for you to use it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're too big for it.
I've never seen things like this before.
It's such a novelty.
I've never seen it before.
Because you are ignorant and ill-informed.
I have seen it when I was only seven.
These are all my ideas.
You're very knowledgeable.
I admire you so very much.
By the way, Architect Li,
this morning you
moved the kids' beds out of their dorm.
Next,
do you have any renovation plan for their dorm?
The dorm doesn't need renovation.
It doesn't?
Be careful.
[Sanfu Orphanage]
Take care.
Mr. Xu, be careful.
Look at these beds.
This...
Slow down.
Put it down.
Okay! Okay!
This...
This is?
A bunk bed.
A bunk bed?
This is the solution
Li Qingfeng came up with
to solve the shortage of their beds.
Mr. Xu,
let's move the beds
into the dorm to see if they fit.
OK.
Thank you all.
Architect Li. Architect Li. Architect Li.
Thank you, everyone.
Good job.
Mr. Xu.
Take a look.
Okay.
I'll have a look.
Don't worry, Mr. Xu.
I was there for the whole working process myself.
I was the supervisor. They are absolutely safe.
I'm not worried.
We trust you.
Father.
There are two drawers here.
Are they for the kids' clothes?
Yes.
You're very thoughtful.
There are still twelve beds like before.
But they only take up the space of six.
If we have more children,
we can put the beds together.
In this way,
we can save more space.
But if you have more children,
which means more beds,
it won't be well-ventilated enough.
So if it is not necessary,
I suggest you don't put more beds.
No more. They'll be enough.
Architect Li, you're brilliant.
The design really surprised me.
I'm so impressed.
I’m flattered, Mr. Xu.
I only came up with the idea
based on practical problems.
As long as I help you fix the problems,
I'm happy.
Also,
the drawers are Miss Chen's idea.
Both of you are brilliant.
How easily you just
solved our problems!
Thank you so much.
That's great.
On behalf of all the kids here,
I want to express my gratitude to Miss Zhao and the two architects.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Xu! Mr. Xu!
Mr. Xu. You don't have to do this.
You're our senior.
Yes.
You don't have to bow so often!
Mr. Xu.
From now on, you can see us as your family.
We will often come here to visit you
and the kids.
If you keep treating us as guests,
we wouldn't dare to come again.
THat's right.
You don't have to thank us so much, Mr. Xu.
We just did what we could do.
Right?
He's right.
You've been helping the kids for all these years
without asking for anything in return.
Everyone can see what a great and kind man you are.
Our contribution is nothing
compared with yours.
I'm so flattered.
What I've been doing means a lot to me.
I ask for no credits.
Sorry, everyone.
Sorry.
I will bear in mind
your kindness.
Actually,
my father spends all his savings,
goes to great lengths
and dedicates the latter half of his life
to this orphanage,
only because he's...
atoning for his sin.
Sin?
Twelve years ago,
my parents
took my sister and me away from our hometown, Hongzhou,
and moved to Lin'an.
My father, along with my mother, sister and me,
traveled for more than half a month.
He then had no choice
but to abandon my sister
without my mother knowing
at the door of a family in a small town we passed by on the way.
My mother got sick from missing my sister.
She passed away in less than half a year
after arriving in Lin'an.
It was a turbulent time,
and my father knew
once he abandoned my sister,
we would never see her again.
If this is fate,
you can never escape.
But after my mother passed away,
he could not get over it
and was down for years
until a few years ago
when the imperial court set up the governmental orphanage department.
That's when my father seemed to have found
his calling.
Then he founded this orphanage
to adopt the abandoned babies and raise them.
My father said
this is his way to redeem him from sin.
But I know this is his way to heal himself.
Because during all these years,
I have witnessed how he has changed
by raising the kids.
I know that
he's getting rid of misery.
So no matter what,
I will stay by his side
and keep going together with him.
I didn't know that
there would be such a story behind you and your father.
Don't worry, Qi Cai.
I've established the Charity Chamber of Commerce.
From now on, I will donate to
civilian orphanages like yours on a regular basis.
You'll be our key recipient.
Just ask me if you need anything.
I will help you.
Yes. And also Wood Feather House.
All of us will come to your aid.
That's right.
Just take us as your friends and family.
Mr. Xu is atoning for his sin,
but what he does is actually a good deed.
From now on, we will stand by your side.
I will, too. At any time,
I'm the coach of the orphanage.
I will protect the kids.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
We're really lucky to meet you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Xu.
Please don't do this.
[Sanfu Orphanage]
We will visit you again.
Take care.
OK.
We're off.
Let's go.
[Sanfu Orphanage]
I really don't understand.
Why do you always like to discuss things
while I'm asleep?
What's there to discuss?
We just finished the work at the orphanage.
I wanted everyone to rest for a few more days.
But the reputation of Wood Feather House is still poor
and we can't afford to rest.
I ask you all here
to announce our next work
in Wood Feather House.
So soon?
What work?
Everyone,
this is the house we're going to renovate.
My lady.
This house is so beautiful. Does it really need renovation?
I don't know.
Councillor Zhang, this house is exquisite enough.
Even the fascia boards and the thresholds
are elaborately carved.
There's no point of renovation.
Are you sure you want to renovate it?
Councillor Zhang, what exactly do you want?
That's right.
I want to renovate this house.
Excuse me. I have to go.
Architect Li. Architect Li.
Please wait.
If you leave like this,
Boss Luo will be embarrassed.
Councillor Zhang, with all due respect,
first, this house is already well-decorated enough.
The last architect must have worked so hard on it.
Second, this is a new house.
It must have been built recently.
As an architect,
I don't have the heart to tear down
what another architect
put his heart in.
Father.
Fu.
You've got so many people here again?
You finished playing the zither?
You want to renew my house again?
Fu, it’s none of your business.
Come with me.
I'm so sorry to trouble you guys.
You can leave now. This house doesn't need renovation.
This is my daughter.
Her name is Fu.
Shaoqing,
take her to the lobby and wait for me.
Come, Fu.
Let’s go to the lobby.
No.
Father.
You've tried to renovate my house again and again.
You spent so much money and energy on it.
Why would you do so?
Fu,
He knows what he's doing.
It's just a renovation.
It's no big deal.
Maybe it's for feng shui,
or for it to look even better.
Just don’t think about it.
Brother!
Fu, don’t you trust me?
Be a good girl.
Let's go for shooting.
Let’s go. Come on.
Good girl. Let's go.
Councillor Zhang, your daughter seems a bit odd.
Meng Yuanxu, don't be rude.
Councillor Zhang,
if you have any problems,
just tell me.
That's the only way we can help you.
Am I going to die soon?
Nonsense.
If that's the case,
would I still take you to hunt?
Let me ask you.
If I'm not sick,
then why does father
repeatedly ask the doctor
to check on me?
My silly sister.
Dad is old now.
So he needs the doctor
to check on him.
That's why the doctor checked on you, too.
He checked on me as well.
The doctor said
both of us were in good health
and could live until 99.
Hysteria?
I heard of it before,
but I've never seen a patient of that.
What are the symptoms
of your daughter's hysteria?
What does it have to do with this house?
Fu is fine during the day.
But at night,
she's always crying that she wants to live in the most beautiful house in the world
instead of this one.
That's why
I have hired many architects
to renovate her house.
However,
Fu is still not happy with it.
She’d rather live
in the artificial hill every night
than step into her own room.
What about the other rooms?
Right.
Did you get her to live in another room?
I've tried all the rooms,
including the wood shed
and the inns.
But none of those worked.
Have you taken her to see a doctor?
Yes.
I've invited
every doctor in Lin'an except for the imperial doctors.
Right now,
the most important thing is not how to cure her hysteria.
In the past few months,
she has been living in the artificial hill or the pavilion.
If her hysteria breaks out and she loses her temper,
she won't let anyone approach her,
which means I can’t take care of her.
As her father,
that really breaks my heart.
So now, I just hope that
you guys can build the most beautiful house
that she's been asking for,
so that she can get some good sleep.
Why not try some sleeping drugs?
You...
Councillor Zhang,
Our chief executive is a martial artist.
Please don't blame him.
As for the renovation,
now that the house
is not the most beautiful house according to Fu,
I think
the most beautiful house
is not an extravagant one.
So we can't change it randomly.
How about I and Li...
We still need to discuss it
and think about a new idea.
How about this, Councillor Zhang,
could you please show us
all the architecture drafts before?
By the way,
could you please also tell us
how Miss Zhang reacted to every draft
briefly
so that we can make an analysis?
That makes sense, Architect Li.
We have never thought about it before.
Great!
Shaoqing and I will sort them out today
and give them to you.
OK, then I’ll leave now.
Thank you all.
There really is no shortage of weirdos in this world.
That house is even better than the one my mother lives in.
Why is the hysteria girl still not happy?
Mrs. Meng’s house is a really good one.
Luo, you have seen her house before?
No, I havn't.
I mentioned it to her before.
Anyway,
what happened today is unbelievable.
I thought
we could make a lot of money from him.
But I didn't know it would be such a tough job.
That's right.
I can’t figure out anything, either.
Li Qingfeng, where are you going to start?
We have to wait until Councillor Zhang's son
shows us the previous drafts,
so that we can decide what to do next.
This is the only way.
Let's go and have some rest.
Let's go.
Architect Chen.
What's wrong?
If Councillor Zhang's son
brings the drafts here,
could you please bring them to Wood Feather Pavilion to me
so that we can find out the materials,
structure and characteristics together?
Taking Miss Zhang's reactions into consideration,
I think we'll be able to see if we can find anything new.
You can do it on your own, and I can do it on my own.
Why do we have to do it together?
Qingfeng.
Here. Mr. Zhang.
Put it here.
Come on.
Architect Li.
All the drafts are here.
Each architect has different habits,
so they all use different kinds of paper.
The drafts in these two reels
are quite special.
You can have a look.
The others are basically similar.
There are a lot of
really exquisite drafts here.
Mr. Zhang,
you must have spent a lot of money
renovating this house, right?
Money is never a problem.
Now, as long as you can build a house
that can help Fu sleep well,
my father and I will be happy.
Boss Luo is right.
There are many creative
and excellent designs.
But they are just not the most beautiful house according Miss Zhang.
So I want to know what exactly
is the most beautiful house to her.
I'm curious about that.
So I will do my best to finish this job.
I have no idea.
I have another question.
Go ahead.
What was the cause of your sister's hysteria?
If you dare to go out of this house,
don't ever come back.
Father, please calm down.
Don’t get too angry.
Fu, you too.
Listen to father.
Let him go back.
Are you going to let him stand outside the house?
Father, can't you just meet him?
The Zhang family now has
quite some reputation in Lin'an.
Many high-ranked officials are lining up to marry you.
Many young talents are lining up to be our matrilocal son-in-law.
What does Xu Qian have?
Xu Qian has his own business.
Business?
You call selling fruits and sweetmeats on the street business?
I like him for who he is.
Besides,
weren't you also a poor guy when you were young?
Fu, you are silly.
Does a man like Xu Qian deserve you?
Does he deserve our Zhang family?
Father, I always do everything you tell me to.
Can't you just let me do it my way once?
Have I not let you do it your way?
I asked you to learn music, chess, calligraphy and painting,
but you always followed your brother to go for shooting and hunting.
What kind of a girl would do that?
But at last I did
listen to you and practice music every day,
didn't I?
That's what you're supposed to do.
I'm your father.
You are my daughter.
As long as you're in the Zhang family, you shall listen to me.
So
it was Councillor Zhang who didn't allow your sister
to be in a relationship with Xu Qian?
Not just my father. I also said no.
Couples from families of equal status make the best marriage.
Xu Qian is not qualified
to marry my sister.
Families of equal status...
I wonder how many lovers
were forced to break up because of that.
Mr. Zhang, Miss Han didn't mean that.
What happened later? Please go ahead.
Then Xu Qian elpoed with Fu.
My father was furious.
So he sent me to go after them.
Xu Qian, stop!
Fu, stop the carriage.
We need to talk.
Fu! Don’t stop!
Hurry up!
Xu Qian!
Stop the carriage.
Where are you taking Fu?
You won’t be able to escape here.
Xiao Fu won't marry you.
Come on.
Fu!
Their carriage turned over.
Xu Qian died on the spot.
Fu was unconscious.
When she woke up, she got hysteria.
She is fine during the day.
It's just that it seems
she doesn't remember Xu Qian anymore.
But at night,
she goes crazy and talks nonsense.
She doesn't listen to anyone of us
and asks for the most beautiful house in the world.
Although Xu Qian died,
I still hate him.
Without him,
Fu wouldn’t have become like this.
Is it really that important to have families of equal status?
You may not understand, Miss Chen.
My father spent his whole life
trying to make himself from poor to rich.
But in the end,
he is still a businessman
who's a second class citizen.
So he always hopes that Fu and I
can change the status of our family.
Only in this way,
Fu and I, along with our children,
will hold our heads up high
and be respected.
My father has worked so hard
and hope he can find a son-in-low who's an official.
At worst,
that guy should be from a family of businessmen.
What's wrong with that?
No.
We understand what you are trying to say.
Why don't we...
Why can't businessmen hold their heads up high?
As long as they can support themselves
and their families,
and have their own dreams and principles,
while maintaining the basic ethics and code of conduct,
they can hold their heads up high.
That's right.
There are businessmen who do good and give back to society.
And there are high-ranked officials who do evil.
It's not about what you do for a living,
but about what you are by nature.
You two are so unsophisticated
and naive.
You have no idea
how cruel the reality is.
If you are a businessman, no matter how successful you are,
no one will really look up to you.
Even among friends,
you're still the most inferior one.
My father just wants to change the status of the family.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Those who are hungry want to have food.
Those who have food want to wear pretty clothes.
Those who have pretty clothes
want more money.
Those who have money,
like your father, want to change their status
and become an official.
After being an official,
they'll want to go higher and higher.
That's not wrong.
That is human nature.
But the pursuit of desires is never-ending.
On the way to pursue desires,
if you hurt your loved ones,
you must stop and think about
what is more important,
your desires
or your loved ones?
Mr. Zhang,
don't get me wrong.
We didn't mean to dismiss you.
We just want you to
put yourself in your sister's shoes
and really think about it,
so that you can
understand your sister better.
It will also be helpful for her condition.
You are right.
Let me go back and talk to my father.
After all, my sister's illness is our priority.
Architect Li,
anything other questions?
Since I have known the whole story,
I’ll try my best
to see if I can build the most beautiful house
for your sister.
That's great.
Thank you, Architect Li.
Mr. Zhang, let me see you off.
Miss Zhao.
[Wood Feather House]
This is?
This is the employer of our next project.
Mr. Zhang.
This is Miss Zhao Yining.
She is the owner of Wood Feather House.
Zhao Yining?
Are you the daughter of Mr. Zhao Xian?
Are you doing business with my father?
Not yet.
But
your father and my father do know each other.
Mr. Luo and I
are going to talk about the project budget.
Since you’re the boss, shall we have a discussion together?
I never get involved when Mr. Luo talks business.
You go ahead.
Miss Zhao, since we are all businessmen,
could you please do me a favor?
Let's talk
and make friends.
OK.
Thank you.
Please.
Miss Zhao, please.
We're not that close, so excuse me for not drinking with you.
Mr. Zhang,
Miss Zhao is always very straightforward.
That's why she is so different
from the others.
Here, I'll have a drink with you.
Mr. Zhang,
have you saw the budget?
I've checked the final amount.
No problem.
Mr. Zhang, you're straightforward too.
You're just like Miss Zhao.
Miss Zhao,
I wonder if you will go to my house too
when your colleagues go to work there?
I’ll go if Li Qingfeng goes.
What do you mean?
Because I like him.
With all due respect,
Mr. Luo, please forgive me.
Isn't it inappropriate for Architect Li
to be with Miss Zhao?
Your families don't really match, right?
I don't care.
You have something to say to me, don't you?
No, no.
Good.
Come on. Let's drink.
We'll take the work
to renovate Miss Zhang's room.
Luo. Miss Han.
Go and find some information about Xu Qian.
See if you can find anything useful.
Do it as thorough as you can.
OK. Just leave it to us.
Sir?
Go ahead.
You won't let me
do the hard work again, right?
Go find a doctor
who knows about hysteria
and check on Miss Zhang.
Luo,
go with him.
You're more considerate.
Remember, ask the doctor
to see if you can learn more about the illness.
Okay.
It's quite easy, but it's a bit too easy.
Councillor Zhang once said that
he has gone to every famous doctor in Lin'an to no avail.
So if you want to find another doctor,
you must find someone who knows hysteria
and is good at treating hysteria. That's not easy.
How is it not easy?
I’ll just go and find...
Sir!
Why don’t we
go now?
Miss Han, let’s go, too.
Qingfeng, we're off.
What about me?
I don't have things for you to do now. Just stay here.
What are you looking at?
If you don't want to work with me,
I can do it myself.
You...
OK, then do it yourself.
Miss Zhao, I'm going to work.
I see. Focus on your work.
I won't disturb you.
Didn't you say you didn't want to work with me?
I did say that.
But I don't think you want to leave.
Right?
Or you can ask Miss Zhao
to build another Wooden Feather Pavilion for you.
She wouldn't say no.
You don't need to
get Miss Zhao involved.
You just don't want me to say bad things about her, right?
I would never do that. She's not the bad one.
Would you want me to say bad things about Mr. He?
I don't care. Just say it if you want.
If you don't know what to say,
I can kindly help look up more words for you.
Come on.
What a waste of time. Boring.
I wonder if Dr. Lin is in his mansion now.
If not,
do we have to go to the palace to invite him?
By the way, Luo,
did you bring your badge?
Yes.
I also thought of this before I left,
so I went back to take it.
I'm never obsessed with details,
while you're smart and thoughtful.
You and I are a perfect match, huh?
Sir,
don’t say that.
What's wrong?
You like my lady,
so you shouldn't say that
to another girl,
in case people misunderstand us.
But you're not just another girl.
You’re my Luo.
By the way, I have another favor to ask.
What is it?
When we pass by my family house later,
go home with me.
Go home?
Tomorrow is my mother's birthday.
I'm afraid I can't go back after we start work.
Since we have some free time today,
you can go back with me to meet my mother.
But it's your mother's birthday.
I don't think I should go.
If you don't go,
my mother will interrogate me for three days
to find out where you are.
Please, just do me a favor.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Let's go.
Watch the steps.
[Qian Fu Sugar Store]
There you go.
Three coins. Thanks.
Goodbye.
Boss.
Could you tell me
how much the sweetmeats are?
Three coins for one catty.
More expensive than before?
Sir,
our price has always been the same.
That's not true.
When Mr. Xu was here,
these only cost two coins.
Mr. Xu?
Him?
We're different.
It's always three coins when I run this store.
But if you two buy in bulk,
I can make it...
5 coins for two catties for you.
Very good.
I asked around.
They haven't seen Mr. Xu for a long time.
I'm afraid that
you may never see Mr. Xu again.
Has he left Lin'an?
Not just Lin'an.
He has left the mortal world and gone to heaven.
How could this have happened?
If I hadn't rented this store,
I wouldn't have known about this
It's the landlord who told me.
It's a secret.
Sounds interesting.
Please tell us what happened.
Didn't I just tell you
it's a secret?
I'll have 20 catties.
Here, here.
Mr. Xu
eloped with Councillor Zhang's daughter and died from falling off the carriage.
Sir, please take back your chin.
Don't let it fall and break my floor.
I know this is shocking.
When I heard about that,
I didn't believe it either.
I wonder what is so good about Xu Qian
that he could get Miss Zhang to fall in love with him.
That makes two of us.
I was wondering that
if it were me,
even if she would like me,
I wouldn't have eloped with her.
Even if I have to kneel in front of the Zhang's mansion for three years,
I would make sure that I could really marry her.
But that's just my wishful thinking.
The Zhang family
is way out of my league.
If you insist on climbing the higher tree,
when you fall, you can only blame yourself.
Very wise, boss.
You're brilliant.
Just out of curiosity,
do you know anything else about Xu Qian?
No.
No?
Goodbye.
Wait!
What about the fruits?
You're not buying them?
The story you just told me
is not worth 20 catties.
What else do you want to know?
How old was Xu Qian? Where did he live?
How tall was he?
You know none of those.
I want to know so much.
But you can't answer my questions.
I have no choice but leave.
No matter how delicious your fruits are,
I don't like them.
Please. Please don't leave.
I do know something else.
I don’t know where Xu Qian is from.
But
he is about the same age as us.
He's quite tall.
He lived...
I don't know where he lived.
But I know he rented a place to live.
Its owner
is the landlord of my store.
I heard that
that's where he
rendezvoused with Miss Zhang.
Rendezvous?
Yes.