[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 7]
Verification passed.
[Sanglan Costume]
What are you doing?
Have you brought gauze?
Yes!
What's wrong?
I...
I hurt my ankle
by accident.
Is it serious? Let me check.
No, no, no.
It doesn't matter.
Let me check it.
Is it proper to just run away
after flirting with me?
It's not like that.
I just
appreciate you a lot
for taking care of me.
It can be a little dangerous for you
to thank me in this way！
I hope that you can be responsible to me
after thanking me.
Wait!
I...
I shall tape the gauze on my ankle myself.
Thank you.
Is it proper to just run away
after flirting with me?
It can be a little dangerous for you
to thank me in this way！
I hope that you can be responsible to me
after thanking me in this way.
Su Su, how can I help?
Please help me duplicate this key.
It's the key to the door of Lu Nan's bedroom.
Yesterday, I found in his safe
a mortgage contract
he signed with Auntie Lan.
Mortgage contract?
I didn't have enough time
to see the content clearly.
I'll try to get into his room again.
I also found
a kind of dye called thorough dye
which only uses vegetable dyes.
Anything wrong with it?
Do you know
why they all want the fragrance brocade?
It requires a special kind of craftsmanship
to make the fragrance brocade.
No matter it‘s the filature, prints
or dye,
any technique used in the process
can shock the clothing industry.
And that's why both Eminence and Gu's Group
try every means to get it.
But owing to its high cost,
no one dares to rashly invest in production
as it's not profitable.
You mean
the thorough dye may be a step
of making the fragrance brocade?
I'm still not sure about it.
For no one has seen the fragrance brocade
except Auntie Lan.
So
I may need some baits
to elicit the truth.
Mr. Lu,
this is my plan
for cooperating with Sia.
As far as I know,
the Gu's Group is now
Sia's first choice for cooperating.
Luckily, their director this time
is Amy.
And I'm acquainted with her.
If my plan is okay,
then I'll visit her as soon as possible.
I want you to be fully in charge.
Be sure to make Sia cooperate with us
even if giving up some profits.
Sit down.
The cooperation with Sia
can be much more important than profits.
I think
we need to find a special way
to get Sia's favor.
We can focus on the fabric
which is always the weakness of Gu's Group.
Because we have no other strength over them.
That's true.
I also think so.
Three months ago,
I tried to cooperate with a factory
which produced brocades and silks.
But things didn't go very well.
Later the one in charge needed money urgently,
so he promised to use their core technology
as the mortgage.
But after I paid the deposit,
the one in charge had an accident,
and then the cooperation was suspended.
But you have already paid the deposit.
Even the manager had an accident,
we still have the right
to use their core technology they mortgaged.
Only the manager knows the core technology.
But she became a vegetable
and has been in a coma.
Lu Nan has paid the deposit!
But from the records of Auntie Lan's bank account,
she didn't receive the deposit at all.
What are you thinking about?
I didn't expect that
you once had a failure
in investing.
Don't worry,
I'll try my best
to make Sia cooperate with us.
Although the thorough dye is newly developed
by our research department,
it can be our selling point.
So I'll tell them to assist you
with anything you need.
Okay,
thank you Mr. Lu.
Have you found something different
on me today?
Your new tie doesn't suit your shirt.
What's this?
Data for the thorough dye.
So is it the same to the fragrance brocade?
They're very different.
That's weird!
If Lu Nan did have the fragrance brocade,
there should be no need for him to do so.
It's a total waste of time for him.
[Nanxi City Hospital]
[Outpatient Building]
Sis, go to rest for a while, I can do it myself.
Thank you for your hard work.
After I figure out the truth,
I'll come to help so that you can rest.
Don't mention it.
Master Lan is the closest person to me,
and it's my duty to look after her.
Anyway, thanks to you!
By the way, I found that
Auntie Lan signed a mortgage contract
with Eminence before.
Do you know about it?
Mortgage contract?
What did Master Lan mortgage?
She didn't tell you about it?
Maybe before she was to tell me,
the accident just happened.
You're recovering well on the whole.
The blood clot has become much more smaller
than it was when you woke up.
As for your memory,
it's just a matter of time.
After all,
as far as I'm concerned,
it's already a miracle for you
to go out of a five-year coma.
Is it that only when the clot disappear
can my memory return?
Not exactly!
It' hard to say.
Why?
Because
it's full of nerves in our brains.
If the clot
moves towards your nerves,
it'll compress
the nerves around.
As a result,
you're very likely to go blind,
or even worse
to become a vegetable again.
I get it!
About my condition,
please help me keep a secret of it.
It's my duty as a doctor
to protect every patient's privacy,
Let alone yours.
After all, I watched you grow up,
right?
Don't worry about it!
I shall go to
get your past medical records.
Okay.
[Elevator;
Gynecology; Obstetrics; Health Examination]
Su Bei,
why are you here?
I'm having insomnia lately
for feeling too stressed,
so I came to get some medicine.
Why are you also here?
I also felt stressed so came to see a doctor.
[Urology]
You make too much of it. It's not what you think.
I'm healthy.
I just came to ask the doctor
to prescribe some medicine for me.
Sure. You're still young.
It's normal to do so.
But medicine won't help all the time.
Just remember to take it easy!
I shall go.
Damn! I can't be more healthy.
By the way,
How's Yu Qinglan now?
Still being in a coma.
Do you still want to recover the debts
when she's in a coma?
I'm not that cold-blooded.
I invested so much money in the project.
There was some problems with thorough dye
and the fragrance brocade has been missing.
So I have to keep an eye on it.
Keep following up it.
By the way,
guess who I just met in the hospital
when I went to get your medical records!
Su Bei!
Your wife!
Why did she go to the hospital?
To see a doctor! Being oppressed by you,
she's suffering from a nervous breakdown.
I think I may also need
to see a psychiatrist
in case that
too much work pressure
makes me suffer from depression.
I don't want to be that tragic.
Fine,
if you don't want any stress,
then go to work
for the security tomorrow.
I have to make money to get married.
You put too much essential oil.
Why are you here?
I should be the one to ask you.
Mr. Lu,
why are you doing so?
A manufacturer sent it to me.
It can be a pity to throw it away.
Are you sure that
it's not because you care about me?
I just don't want you to get sick and delay work.
But if you care too much about me,
I'll feel stressed, Mr. Lu.
If you keep behaving recklessly like this,
I'll also feel stressed.
If there's nothing else,
please go back to your room, Mr. Lu.
I shall rest now.
This is the data
of Sia Group's Amy
that Yun Fan collected.
[THEA Brand Director Amy]
It can may be of use for you.
He even figured out the kind of fruit
and coffee that Amy likes.
Yun Fan is really careful.
It was because I was supervising him.
Then,
thank you!
You can buy anything you want.
Don't be too stressed.
I can help you if the work is too difficult.
You can have a day off tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work lately.
What are you laughing at?
Mr. Lu,
this represents my aprreciation,
not asking for money
I know.
But, this is for you
to show my appreciation.
You hands are a little bit cold.
Be sure to keep warm!
[Operation Monitoring Center]
Hello!
Are you at home?
Of course I am.
You ungraceful woman!
Not demure at all！
Verification passed.
[Contract]
Hello.
Hi, Yezi,
I've seen the contract.
Auntie Lan has mortgaged
the fragrance brocade to Lu Nan.
Help me check the record of her company.
I have to know
whether they have received the money.
Got it! I'll go check it immediately.
By the way,
it's time to deal with Sia now.
[Yonghong Grand Spa Thermal Resort]
For our Gu's Group,
I'm sure that
we make the best haute couture in China.
So if you want to enter China's market,
Gu's Group is your best choice.
I know what you mean, Mr. Gu.
I'll report what we've discussed
to Sia's headquarter.
And I'll contact with you
as soon as I get the reply.
Then you need to hurry up.
To be honest, the Gu's Group is your only choice.
But Sia is not the only one partner
that Gu's Group can choose.
Sia isn''t the only choice for the Gu's Group,
but it's the partner
the Eminence mostly wants to cooperate with.
Annie!
Amy! Haven't seen you for a long time.
I didn't expect I can meet you here.
Today,
as the representative of the Eminence
I came to talk to you
about the cooperation in clothing.
So,
let's talk inside the room.
This is our newly-developed dye this year,
the thorough dyeing.
It features the idea of
being environment-friendly and colorfast.
Moreover,
we have made great breakthrough.
According to our research,
Sia mainly targets
consumers of high-end products.
But in recent years,
consumers began to question
the quality of your products,
especially about clothes fading color.
It can be a great problem for you.
As far as I know,
you've been looking for solutions.
And the technology of my company
can help you solve the problem.
Secondly,
in terms of the profit sharing,
my company is more sincere
than the Gu's Group.
The profit sharing you offered to us
is indeed considerable.
But,
the thorough dye of your company
is still not mature enough/
The market share
and the high reputation in clothing
of the Gu's Group in China
are far better than yours.
So it has an edge over you.
I admit what you mentioned above.
But it can also be hard for the Gu's Group
to develop something new.
But for the Eminence,
it's a company with creativity and potential
which targets the young consumers.
And these ideas
can exactly match up with yours.
Let me see.
Maybe I can suspend the
contract signing with the Gu's Group,
and report what you told me to the headquarter.
But,
I can only
give you one month.
During this period,
I hope that you can achieve new breakthroughs
in the thorough dye.
Thanks a lot.
Su Bei!
You're still here!
I'm waiting for you.
I can drive you home.
Okay!
Come!
Thanks.
You can just stop here.
Thank you!
I'll treat you another day.
So are you returning me a favor?
If it is,
then there's no need for you to do so.
If it's just a meal between friends,
then it will be my pleasure.
It's both of what you mentioned.
If you don't want it,
I can save the money.
If you say so, I must let you treat me.
I can do it myself.
We can eat when you have time.
Bei Bei,
you're back!
Have you been waiting for me here?
You're a girl,
and I'm a boy.
I have to protect you.
I'm your mom.
You have a son?
You...
why are you here?
You lost it in my car.
Thank...
Thank you!
So careless of you.
So,
about today...
I have a poor memory,
so I can't remember what happened.
Thank you very much!
You're my friend,
so you don't need to thank me many times.
Please keep down!
Bei Bei,
I hope you can listen to me
patiently.
Although my dad
can be annoying,
I'm not
prepared
to have a new dad.
I think my dad deserves another chance.
Yes,
you're right.
You don't understand! All of you！
This family still needs me to protect.
So,
Mr. Su,
have you finished your homework yet?
That...
As for the homework,
I think,
we can talk about it later.
Be careful!
Are you sure that Lu Nan paid the money?
Yes, the money was indeed received,
but was soon
transferred into the account of a person
named Qiao Yufeng.
This is a 24-year-old countryman in Guang Lin.
But why didn't we have any idea
of the money before?
Someone has covered the track
in Auntie Lan's account.
But I haven't
found out where Qiao Yufeng is now.
Keep investigating in it.
We must find the manipulator of all this.
Su Bei, get out there!
-You can't come in
-You can't come in.
Long time no see.
What?
Is anything wrong?
Damn you！
Are you the one who deprived me of my endorsements,
and asked to force me out?
You don't deserve me to do so.
How could I waste my time and energy
on you?
Why do you look down upon me?
Don't you know who you really are?
You think being President's wife
and the famous Annie
can allow you to do whatever you want to do?
Yes.
You...
Fine, Su Bei,
you want to destroy me, right?
Then I'll give you a hard time.
We will see.
[The 8th Anniversary Celebration]
Manni,
Manni, don't drink too much.
You should stop now.
You can't just be angry and drink here.
I've told you
Su Bei is no longer the one she was 7 years ago.
You should listen to me
and stop competing with her.
You don't think I can defeat her, right?
That's not what I meant, Manni.
Think about it.
We're best friends.
I'm definitely on your side.
I just think that
my brother is now under her control,
so we can do nothing to her.
Who said it?
If I expose  to the public her plagiarising
seven years ago which caused one's death,
then she will be done.
You can't do that.
I mean Eminence
was also involved in it.
So you must keep the secret.
Besides,
time is different.
She's no longer a designer.
No one will care about
whether a model agent has plagiarised before.
And it was
you...
Anyway,
You can't
let her have the advantage over you anymore.
But,
if I can't do anything,
she will always
ride over me.
Or
maybe you can let her disappear.
You're right.
If only I can let her disappear.
Nan Nan!
Are you ignoring me?
Have we met before?
You...
Fine,
as a gentleman, I've forgiven you.
I came here today to tell you
you should treat your wife well.
If she got away with another man,
you can only cry.
Are you done?
Boy,
first I have to tell you
I'm not your dad.
So whether your mom is fine or not
has nothing to do with me.
Second, I'm very busy now.
I have no time with you.
So,
you should go back
to where you came from.
Or I'll find your mom
and ask her how she taught you
and why you're here alone.
Don't tell my mom!
Chris!
Why are you here?
He's the child of Ye Ting's sister.
Sorry for bothering you, Mr. Lu.
So,
I'll take him back home.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go!
He,
is so cute.
He's cute, but he lacks love.
Being abandoned by his dad since he was born,
he has never felt any love from his dad.
Do you think
whether his dad would regret abandoning him
if the dad knew
how lovely his son is.
I still have work to do. I shall go now.
What's wrong?
Did I say anything wrong?
Chris,
do you want auntie
to play toys with you?
No,
I want to wait for mom.
Mommy,
you're back.
Could you play this with me? It's hard.
Mommy will play with you later.
Chris,
mommy wants to apologize to you.
You don't need to be sorry.
Auntie has told me
it was good for me.
Chris,
mommy can't tell
daddy about you now.
You won't you blame mommy, will you?
I won't ask for dad anymore.
I only want mommy to be happy.
I won't blame you.
My son,
you're such a good boy!
Mommy's so lucky
to have you as my son.
I'm also very happy
to be mommy's son.
Sorry.
This woman is out of control.
Why are you back so late?
Where have you been?
Why aren't you asleep?
What's the matter?
You don't feel comfortable?
I'm fine.
Wait me for a while!
Brown sugar water.
Drink it.
I really...don't need to drink this.
I'm tired.
I have to rest now.
Do you know that
I'm caring about you?
Besides,
I don't like to be ignored.
Do you know?
Fine,
Got it. I'm not ignoring you.
I'm just really tired.
By the way,
how's it going
with Sia's stuff?
Did it go well
without the fragrance brocade?
You don't need to worry about it.
You should only take good care of yourself.
How can you be so tired
for the kind of trivial thing
like endorsements?
I can't stand you being so thin.
By the way,
I bought you something
when I went to the supermarket today.
[Pulse-activating decoction(codonopsis)]
[Zinc gluconate oral solution]
[Oral liquid for reinforcing qi and nourishing blood]
[Tonic fluid for soothing nerves]
The seller told me
these are beneficial to women's health.
They can be effective.
I...may not like drinking them.
It tastes good.
Drink all of them!
[Iron-zinc amino acid oral liquid]
How should I get along with you?
[Little kid]
Mean dad!
What are you doing?
Who are you, little boy!
I'm calling you.
Don't run!
Hey, boy! What are you doing?
This...
The owner will blame me for this!
[Ye Ting]
I've found Zhang Yuan.
Okay, keep an eye on him.
[Su Bei]
Don't let him run away again.
It seems that Mr. Lu
has offended lots of people.
It's me!
Have you seen the news?
It's terrible!
For these years,
[Press briefing]
[Top model of Eminence reveals
shocking inside stories to ask for help]
I've been enduring
Mr. Lu's harassment to me.
If it were not for having a contract
with the company,
I would never endure this.
I thought after my sister Su Bei
took over Eminence,
I could get relieved.
But I didn't expect that
they were all demons.
Get on the car!
[Top model of Eminence reveals
shocking inside stories to ask for help]
I really have no other choice.
So I can only tell the truth
regardless of the risk of revenge.
Please help me!
Please do help me!
The current condition is not in our favor.
Someone is hyping it up
and inciting the public on purpose.
People online
are all in Su Manni's favor.
Members of the board also knew about it.
They're asking you to explain.
Tell the PR department
not to do anything now.
And don't remove it from the trending topics.
I'll hold an emergency meeting 15 minutes later.
Okay！
Watch out!
The brake doesn't work.
Lu Nan!
Don't cry!