Youyou independent broadcast theater --YoYo Television Series Exclusive
your daughter
to marry Andy Lord that she's gone shit
I see you Shuigan Dong ball our house
my father
to fight with him I
do not beat my dad
do not hit other hit
me marry me marry me marry
me marry
me stop
you married my father put me
assure you
it Chifeng meant it
if you married into the mountains
I'll put your father
can not marry balls balls
father
promised me after the stop
I bet do not let worry
take care of myself
ball away
balls balls
balls balls dad
dad dad
walking
balls
balls balls
Wang Gongzi
father
a long time did not come to the floor
come inside, please
be wishful wishful
doing this for
you, but we Qingzhou
floor the largest restaurant in the inn
here to marry up the hill
a few good luck
Keguan
you have to eat it or housing
housing
le inside please
go
inside we
invited
you to be careful Princess Qingzhou seemed to
me to see you so happy
as you go marry Mei three young master to
Princess well you do not have to
make fun of me this watch to
see how the Qingzhou
someone else
to come pick us up Yeah Yeah
I called Salix
not go to see the courage of Mei also really big
Princess dare neglect of this
rare I do not go
out quickly master
the big day ah Master
Master Master
Master Master ah
hour to the
master said
the Princess had
to go door to Qingzhou
wedding, then it serves
wedding
family laws
no, no
family law master well
do not
worry, said slowly
Princess directly to your home but do not
live in the building wishful
What
this this this
Princess lived wishful floor will not
do it because World Youth did not go to meet
so angry
that does not make World Youth
refusing to pick up his three young master, ah
this classic
inverse World Youth like this
now, I am afraid it is not easy to pick up
this father is not the answer it
it is not I pick it
shut up
is not my Princess who do you pick
me
to go there quickly Tao Nakai
Princess gave me a come back
I
go ah
adults admitted to Princess suddenly wishful floor
time to prepare if we
have to take care of ill places
also ask you to forgive me more than
other people inside it
you will rest
assured a tenant a bath
a little later to ask her to leave
must make sure that security
is Princess have kept all ah we
export lady
suddenly admitted to this restaurant
is not substandard etiquette ah
I is the royal
etiquette I'm
pro-clan on the holy seal of
Princess'd say these three little plum
he did not come to the next of kin
is simply not looked down on us, Miss
royal plum three little thing that can not be
possible because he hurt
me just how he
in the foreground listening to a small two
to three less Mei said that the bandits suffered eye injuries
eye injuries
this plum government servant
I am afraid
to say I was
blind blind
dignified nine palace princess
to marry a blind right
now we quickly packed Luggage
must not
hurry back to the government
must not let
this marriage is coming to a decision
if you go back, then made a Qijunzhizui
everyone had dead
lady is coming to a decision and then
coming to a decision to
appease your Drink tea,
you do not say
I want a quiet person trekking trip
you go out I go
out
I go out
and think about ah
clouds clouds
stop yelling
I heard how the
housekeeper Mei House has been at the gate with
a small butler
dare to pick a princess we
see three little Mei
did not yet come
around to see
Andy go
doing it
God
how you came
to see me that I did not get married cheap
Lord your wife you are too anxious
I worry
I have to thank you ah
thank you for giving me find a
chest crushed stone hag
that bitch what name
she called the little balls
small balls
that also stunned with what
to look for her in the past
Can not you see God go
all the officers and men
to me out of
this it is still the second floor bath
bathe
her in that house which
she
says that room on the upper house of Lin
Lin
I went to see
Miss figured out from behind
that now well, we
all dress up go
Who is that
matchmaker
bandits also get married so particular about
out out
out Princess Princess
Sophie
out please Master a
good Master
said
clues found murdered his wife
Princess Thanks to the
infinite royal graciousness
I grant marriage to Mei Mei's House this is my great honor to the clan
of Mei
Wu Zi this is not the cottage you
will be kind to the next
World Youth Princess May I
serve the country when
the government also
down bounties
do I have to report
who you are ah clear that people do not have to go yet
human life I now want to escape
what happens is
my father's gambling debts owed
then I have to give him
too much debt I want to go to the cottage when Yazhaifuren
now the girls life you quickly go
hard on it
I can not escape
I escaped my father would have been dead
these people simply Yiguanqinshou
I help you give them Offenses
who are you,
Princess ran the wrong room
steward came here is the
original Manor House
which may how do how to
do, if they knew to salute a
princess when I was not
preparing for the wedding
to Princess
would not behead
Kyrgyzstan is tense moment
so just forget etiquette
Princess
prayer
two prayer Diocese
husband and wife worship
Mrs. generals in
the ceremony
into worship
it my gosh this
bridal chamber
next finished
how do you
how do
you awake Who
here this is where ah
Who are you
this is Qinglongzhai ah
I Zhaizhu South tyrant's adopted son
is three masters here
is your future Messire
Messire
Qinglongzhai
me how I
would do I just
hid in here
can drag moment is the moment
that you are what people ah
I were you I did not get married ah I xianggong
Dear husband
he is not blind yet
to come if you dare call me
come what people
think of me as
this Feiren mistake inn girl
how to do how to do
now that he got the wrong man told
me he could not
Princess would kill me
there might be up to no good ah I
do what I want
ah you do not
tell your father
bailing wondering what you have to charge me the
debt also follow people for granted
but do not worry
Bao Lord Yeah I
assure you chest crushed stone is better than a thousand times
that you know the baby Lord what I call
you you know who I do
not do it my
little meatball
martial arts you
too Playing silly
little ball
toss day deserves to be hungry.
I've got a lot of good
I love
you all doing it
froze the doing of this dish would get cold
froze the doing
it yourself over it
you say the whole Come quickly eat
a delicious
entertainer you say you are in the mountain time
never seen so many delicious things
you see it you are hungry
thin it into what
you worry
you follow me will never let you hungry
put you nourished
I'm going home I'm looking for my father
what you cry ah
ah this is not to your appetite
to eat chicken as well as the
trekking so that
you do not cry
except you
do not send you home
anything I can promise you
that you can not touch me promise promise me
you'll never touch you
okay how can I marry you why I come back
to marry you
foster parent said it is going to give me back the treasure
to stay
Bao Lord God
said let your boss see him with the bride
down the line know it
go ahead
do not lift the lid
open ah I would be dead
wrong to say that they
believe someone should believe it
if I do not how to do it
was arrested
behead how to do it
how
you doing
Princess is a slur on my blind
blind you really
do see him on that day
when the carriage had been blind
you do what
I say I told you
this was all a misunderstanding this is a mistake
I do not want to marry me
I
do not want to marry is
not forced not
me I do not know how
confusedly Mei was sent to the House that
this is coming to a decision who would escape marriage
since you do not want do not want to marry me
then we kept themselves marry
each well
are not we all be here
how good their
security, although we will never be
the name of husband and wife couple in reality
means that you will not touch me
think this is
how Princess married
no, no
I agree I agree I agree
I agree I agree with the good
never seen such a narcissistic
and so I have
to eat tomorrow effort I ran
right ah he is not blind it
can be walked and
how I
want to escape ah
eating too much
light I can go again I hear
say that again
today, but the wedding night
the bride can
wander around us
less secure plum government guard guarded
you are doing
it, etc., etc. why do you
sleep ah ah
then you sleep on the bed where I sleep ah
you want to sleep in bed my mind
I do not mind it
in this
present Princess adults both beautiful and noble
How can it be that you can take advantage of
this is that you help yourself
help yourself
out if you say
you say you a big man
you occupy a whole bed
you have the nerve to do you
this is my bed
quilt on
your bed in there
own take on
the line
ah I see you are a blind man in the negotiations
I do not care about
me and you large number of adults
in this princess can sleep at bad
foster parent
where we come
Andy Look at your point of breath
wife did not get married it
the same way you would hurry
back down her back
that I do not want to worry
I look young married woman said with a long-sawed
satisfied with it
foster parent I'm so happy with
it that's thanks to five,
full satisfaction ah
bride looked up
to see the old lady
meatball head up
to look at you
quickly sense
the foster parent
parent foster parent
Zhaizhu
really nice
girl you look good
this kid is so
scared of it not being
the back of the mountain
a little
scared that we
do not know Lianxiangxiyu ah
foster parent who
have already reconciled with the foster parent in front of
you and give me
a good save face
Andy
you're lucky ah
or foster parent to me the election was good
of you to give me up
is this woman
to be married Why is it
you do not agree with me after I
get married Why should tell you
why my father
ah you agree to let
you marry this woman is it
you better marry her you should not even think
you have anything to do with
me ah
my violent temper my
Andy
south incense you a crazy girl
you
Hurry up and get ah you dare to marry her
I try to let go of
South-release
this is why your father do
I
have any good heartless
Andy he is not
he is a good father
I am you, you
like him
or not I am a father
Andy he should get married
in the end you are not my parent father ah good good
father promise you
I will take
for you to clean up the heartless Andy
okay
not
you fix him what
he does not fix him with
you still want to get married father good
father promise you it
will give you a satisfactory reply ah
you go back, OK
I have something to discuss with Five
I'm sure
you determine
quickly how
to go back
ah Five
Zhaizhu
smoke with you this wicked stuff
even told me that what chest crushed stone is
not
how I
also like this no see you
bring me such a beautiful Yazhaifuren
Zhaizhu the first time I see
who you know looks okay
to me I said
I went to
my fans
I go
to
my death you
take it
well do not frown
South-assured
she is not malicious
like a habit after you
who have told you after
you said that eat ah
really a little tired of it
we two young married woman to
go to bed
Why did not
you talk to young married woman too
exhausted individuals this is
what you should be doing this you
take your shoes off to sleep ah ah
not
you sleep here where I sleep ah
you sleepy or drowsy left to the right
you just pick
it you you're a rogue
you get out of here right now
that I slept where I ah
you love where to sleep where to sleep
if you do not go out, then
I'll die for you
I do not
trekking
trekking trip
walk okay
I died
that night how
Bao Lord Spring night moment not to
be worth a thousand gold wedding ah ah
ah one thousand one thousand your head
Although we are not
bandits
but also have to pay attention to how can consummated marriage
ah ah
there tomorrow to give me what Qiangdian
rouge gouache ah ah know things like women
do that
with you here to see me live
to see not you are asked to take
a good living
from the open
I have to think of a way to get out as soon as
Andy Lord seems to really like me
maybe he could use to escape
Master waiting
a few days ago
I found what
appeared in the streets of a madman Qingzhou
he referred to the babble of time
to kill Helena May
I send him tied up
this man what he called
the origins of epilepsy
Qingzhou Chen Lao people
mad evil nature
disappeared a decade ago
and recently from the local
people have been living now back to Qingzhou
completely insane
weekdays with no family to rely on begging What
he also found a
mention beggars who rely Skiles
special tracing cable
I found great year he killed his wife
on the internet in Romania through the underworld killer
where he is now
said to
appear next to the Earth Temple shack
I have sent eyeing
sure to put him back alive to see me
a
good
night chivalric
spirit Xia us
together
Youyou independent broadcast theater --YoYo Television Series Exclusive