Timing and Subtitles created by
🌹 "The True Team" 💖 @ Viki.com
[Truth or Dare]
[Episode 2]
Wrong Marriages
Your daughter being able to
marry Master Xiao Bao is her dumb luck.
If any of you dare harm my Wanzi,
I'll fight them at all costs!
Father! Don't hit my father, stop hitting him!
- I'll marry, I'll marry.
- Stop!
If I marry him, will you let my father go?
Don't worry, I, Chi Feng, keep my word.
If you marry,
I'll set your father free immediately.
Wanzi! You can't marry him!
Father, promise me you won't gamble again.
Don't make me worry for you again, take care of yourself.
Wanzi.
Take her away.
Wanzi! Wanzi!
- Father!
- Let's go.
- Wanzi!
- Father!
[Ruyi Restaurant]
We haven't come in so long. This way, please.
Why are we here at Ruyi Restaurant?
Ruyi Restaurant is Qingzhou's largest tavern.
To marry up the mountain here is very lucky.
Excuse me, are you here to dine or lodge?
Lodge.
Alright, this way, please.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Be careful.
[Double Happiness]
Princess, I think we're almost at Qingzhou.
Since you're so happy,
how about if you go marry Young Master Mei Sanshao?
Princess, stop teasing me already.
It appears we're almost at Qingzhou,
why isn't there anyone coming to welcome us?
True. How about it I tell Qiu Hua to check it out?
It's fine.
This Mei Manor is so daring.
How dare they be so cold-mannered towards the Princess!
I'm not even interested in going.
Young Master, hurry and come out!
Today is the wedding, Young Master.
Young Master.
Young Master! It's time.
Young Master, Young Master!
The Lord said that the Princess has arrived in Qingzhou.
If you don't greet them,
you'll face family discipline!
Greet?
Family discipline?
Lord, bad news!
Don't rush, take your time.
The Princess didn't come to the manor straightaway,
but is staying at Ruyi Restaurant!
- What?
Th-this--
Why is the Princess staying at Ruyi Restaurant?
Might it be because Shiqing didn't greet her,
so she's mad?
Then, hurry and tell Shiqing to go and welcome her!
Third Young Master won't go no matter what.
This unfilial son.
Lord, with Shiqing's current condition,
I'm afraid it might not be best to go welcome her.
Father, this won't do anyways. If there's no choice left, I can go.
Shut up! Is the Princess someone for you to go welcome?
Juzheng, hurry and go welcome the Princess from there.
Me?
- Go!
- Yes.
[Ruyi Restaurant]
- What's going on?
- How grand!
Sir, the Princess came to stay here so suddenly, so
we didn't have enough time to prepare.
If there are any inconveniences, please forgive us.
Is there anyone else here?
Please don't worry, there is one guest left who is bathing and dressing. We'll ask them to leave soon.
We must ensure the Princess' safety.
Yes, we've already covered all exits.
[Lin Hai]
Miss, do we lack courtesy for suddenly staying in an inn?
Courtesy?
I'm a clan relative of the Royal Family,
a Princess conferred by the Emperor himself.
However, that Mei Sanshao isn't even coming to greet us.
What does he take the Royal Family for?
Miss, Mei Sanshao not being able to come
might be because he's injured.
What happened to him?
Earlier, I heard from the front desk that
in order to fight bandits, Mei Sanshao injured his eyes.
Eye injury?
The Mei Manor servants say that unfortunately,
- he's blind.
- Blind?
I, as the Princess of the Ninth Manor, have to marry a blind person?
Let's hurry and pack our bags to return to the manor.
You must not, you must not! This is a bestowed marriage,
if we return, that would be deceiving the Emperor!
- Everyone will face death!
- 'Bestowed' again!
Miss, please calm down. Here, have some more tea.
- Stop talking about it, I want to be alone for a moment.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I'll leave, I'll leave.
Think it over, okay?
Gosh.
Qiao Yun!
Stop yelling, I hear you. What's happening?
The Mei Manor Housekeeper is waiting outside.
A small housekeeper dares to come welcome our Princess?
Did you see Mei Sanshao?
Nope, I guess he didn't come.
Come on, let's go check it out.
Let's go.
- What's up?
- Wait, Master Xiao Bao.
Why are you here?
I am here to see my cheap future wife.
You're in such a rush.
I'm in a rush?
I should thank you.
Thanks for finding me a stone-breaking dragon lady.
What's the woman's name?
- Her name is Xiao Wanzi.
- Xiao Wanzi?
What are we waiting for? Let's go find her.
Wait, Master. Look, there are guards everywhere. I was chased out.
She's still bathing on the second floor.
Bathing? Then, which room is she in?
She's upstairs in the room named
'Lin Hai'.
'Lin Hai'?
I'll enter from the back to check it out.
My Lady has thought it through?
Since you're all dressed up,  let's go.
Who is this? The matchmaker?
So even bandits can be this particular about marriage.
She's here.
The Princess is here.
Please.
♫ The lonely star and moon are interlaced ♫
♫ as they drift across the milky way ♫
♫ How does one conceal the vulnerability in one's heart? ♫
♫ That fated ♫
♫ moment belongs to me ♫
Young Master, A'Rou said that she found clues about Madam's death.
Alright.
♫ Look and remember fondly the scenery as night flowly falls ♫
♫ Such an unintentional coincidence ♫
♫ A cautious touch ♫
♫ Reluctance is most  ♫
Young Master, the Princess has arrived.
♫ Fingertips brushing, you ask me, ♫
♫ "Whom does your heart cling to?" ♫
♫ The moon stains the night with spots of light ♫
♫ My heart is like fire, burning for you ♫
♫ Even my tears are hot ♫
♫ No regrets as my heart loves ♫
♫ Fingertips brushing, you ask me, ♫
♫ "Whom does your heart cling to?" ♫
♫ The moon stains the night with spots of light ♫
♫ My heart is like fire, burning for you ♫
♫ Even my tears are hot ♫
♫ No regrets as my heart loves ♫
By the Emperor's mighty grace,
a marriage is granted to the Mei Manor.
This is the utmost honor to my Mei Family.
Mei Manor? Isn't this the mountain fortress?
My son, Shiqing, will take good care of the Princess from now on.
And my entire family will serve the country
to repay the Emperor's kindness.
Could it be that I just...?
[Lin Hai]
Who are you? Hasn't everyone been escorted away?
My life is at stake. I'm running for my life right now.
What happened?
My dad owes a gambling debt, so to repay it for him
I have to go to the mountain fortress to be a bandit's wife.
Life is too difficult for girls. You should leave now.
I can't escape. If I run away, my dad will die.
These people are simply despicable! I'll help you punish them.
Who are you?
Princess, the housekeeper is here!
I ran into the wrong room.
So this is the General's manor.
What should I do?
If they find out that I'm not the Princess,  they'll kill me.
It's time. Proceed.
First, bow to the heaven and earth.
The Princess was nervous,
so she forgot the etiquette.
Princess.
Bow.
Secondly, bow to the parents.
Husband and wife bow to each other.
The General and his wife are both here.
Bow.
The ceremony has ended. Enter the bridal chamber!
Oh my god! I'm doomed!
What should I do?
You're awake?
Who are you?
Where... is this?
This is the Green Dragon Fort.
I'm the adopted son of Nan Batian, the chief of Green Dragon Fort.
I'm also the third-in-command here. Moreover, I'm your future husband.
Green Dragon Fort?
My husband?
How could this be?
Could it be that I just...?
[Lin Hai]
I'll hide here for as long as I can.
Who are you?
I... I'm your husband-to-be.
My husband? Isn't he blind?
If you dare come over, I'll call for someone! Guards!
This bandit mistook me for the girl in the restaurant.
What should I do?
Should I tell him that he has the wrong person right now, and I'm actually the Princess?
No, he might kill me.
He might even do something worse to me.
What's on your mind? Let me tell you, don't even think about running away.
You dad has already mortgaged you to me.
It is natural that he repays his debts.
But don't worry. If you stay with me, Master Bao,
I can guarantee that it will be a lot better than performing on the streets.
Right, Master Bao...
Then, do you know what my name is? Do you know who I am?
Aren't you Xiao Wanzi?
Could it be that my martial arts skills are too advanced, so I hit you too hard?
Xiao Wanzi?
You must be hungry after a long day.
I prepared a lot of delicious food. All of them are my favorites.
Woah!
What are you doing? The dishes are getting cold.
What are you being distracted for?
Then come over here yourself.
Look, they're all delicious. Come on, hurry up and eat.
You didn't see so many delicious dishes when you were performing below the mountain, right?
Look at how thin you are. You must be starving.
Don't worry. You won't ever be hungry if you stay with me.
I'll make you chubby.
I want to go home. I want to see my dad.
Why are you crying? This dish don't suit your tastes?
There's also this! Here, eat this chicken.
Alright, don't cry. Look,
besides sending you home, I'll give you anything you want.
Can you promise, then, promise that you won't touch me?
Never touch you? Impossible. Why would I bring you back here, then?
My dad told me to marry you so that you could give me babies.
Master Bao! Master Bao.
The Big Boss said to bring your bride to meet him.
Okay, I know. You can go.
[Double Happiness]
Please don't take off the veil!
If you take it off, I'm finished!
Someone will believe me if I say there's been a mistake, right?
What if they don't believe me?
What if I get captured and beheaded?
What are you doing?
What? Princess, are you looking down on a blind man like me?
He really is blind? Was he already blind when I last saw him?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I...! I'm telling you, this is a misunderstanding!
I...didn't want to marry.
You didn't want to marry?
I was forced!
No no.
I...I don't know how I was somehow delivered here.
The emperor decreed this marriage. No one can avoid it.
Since neither of us wanted to marry, then let us steer clear of each other.
We'll each stick to our own place.
No...! We've already come to this step. How will we stick to our own place?
We are married in name, but we will not consummate it.
That means you won't touch me?
What? Princess, you want to get married now?
No no no! I agree, I agree!
-I agree! I agree!
-Excellent!
I've never seen such a narcissist.
Once I'm full and energetic tomorrow, I'll run away!
That's not right.
Isn't he blind? I can run away right now!
What? You want to run away?
You ate too much. No matter how light your footsteps are, I can hear you.
Besides, today is our wedding.
It's not safe for the bride to run around everywhere.
Our security here is very tight.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Sleeping.
If you sleep in the bed, where am I sleeping?
If you want to sleep in the bed too, I don't mind.
I mind!
I...!
This princess is beautiful and esteemed!
You can't take advantage of me!
Then do as you'd like.
Do as I'd like?
Are you human?
You are a man!
How could you take over the entire bed?
This is my bed.
Your blankets are over there. Go get it yourself.
Fine.
Since you are a blind man
blind man,
I won't hold this against you!
I'm magnanimous! I can sleep anywhere!
Oh no.
Godfather! We're here!
Xiao Bao, look at you.
You carried your wife all the way here before you even got married!
I was in a rush! I wanted to see what my wife looked like!
Are you satisfied?
Godfather! I am too satisfied! This is all thanks to Master Wu.
Satisfied?
Bride.
Lift up your head, let me take a look.
Wanzi! Lift up your head! Godfather wants to see you.
Hurry up!
Godfather?
Chief?
Father?
Beautiful.
This girl is beautiful!
Lady.
This brat carried you all the way up the mountain.
Did he scare you?
I was scared.
He really doesn't know how to be tender towards women.
Godfather!
We already made up!
Who made up with you?
Give me some face in front of Godfather!
Xiao Bao.
You are so lucky!
Godfather picked a good lady for me!
Get up!
This is the girl?
If you are getting married, you have to get my permission first!
Why should I tell you? Why do I need your permission?
I-!
Father!
You are marrying this woman, right?
Don't even think of living well if you marry her!
-What does it have to do with you?
-I-!
This temper of mine!
Xiao Bao!
Hurry and go! Go!
-Go!
-Nan Xiang!
-Father!
Why are you doing this?
I-!
What is so great about Xiao Bao? He's not loyal, right?
Father, I just like him, I think he's great!
Are you my father?
Xiao Bao is going to get married, are you really my father?
I promise you!
I will definitely deal with that brat Xiao Bao for you, alright?
No!
What use is that? He's still going to get married!
-Father!
-Fine!
I promise you. I will give you a satisfactory answer, alright?
Go back first, alright? I have something to discuss with Old Wu.
-You sure?
-I'm sure. Hurry and go back.
Old Wu.
Come.
What is it, Chief?
You unreliable wicked man.
You told me she breaks slabs of rock on top of her chest! And she looks like that??
Why didn't you bring me a beautiful wife like that?
Chief!
This is my first time seeing her too! Who knew she doesn't look that bad?
You're still saying that?
Damn!
Here, have a seat.
Alright, stop with the long face already.
Don't worry.
Nan Xiang has no bad intentions, you'll get used to her in the future.
What future do I have with you?
Now that I'm full, I'm actually kind of tired.
Wife, let's go sleep. Come on.
Hold on, who are you calling wife?
I'm so tired.
What are you doing?
Taking my shoes off to go to bed.
Wait, if you're sleeping here, then where do I sleep?
Do you want to sleep on the left or right side? Your choice.
You scoundrel...get out of here immediately!
Then, where am I supposed to sleep?
You can go sleep wherever. But, if you don't get out of here,
- I'll die in front of you.
- Don't!
Fine, fine, fine! I'll leave.
- Are you satisfied if I leave?
- I'm dead.
Well, Master Bao.
How come you aren't going to the bridal chamber at night?
One hour in a spring night is worth a thousand pieces of gold.
(A romantic night is priceless.)
A thousand pieces of gold my head!
Although we are bandits,
we still have to be cultured.
How could we consummate when we're not yet married?
Also, go get me some items for women tomorrow.
Like lipstick, foundation, and blush, got it?
Then, stay here and keep watch. If you don't, then you'll be responsible.
Okay.
I have to hurry and think of a way to escape.
It seems Master Xiao Bao actually likes me.
I might possibly be able to use him to escape.
No...
Young Master, I apologize for the wait.
What have you found?
A few days ago, a lunatic appeared on the Qingzhou streets.
When he was spewing nonsense, he mentioned the murder of Madam Mei.
So, I ordered him to be tied up.
What is his background?
He is Chen Laodian from Qingzhou.
Has a crazy personality and is evil.
Ten years ago, he disappeared from here.
Recently, he's wandered back to Qingzhou.
Now, he's completely insane.
Without family or friends,
he can only survive on begging.
What else did you find out?
He also mentioned Lai Laobao from the beggar gang.
He specializes in finding people and building connections.
I found out that the year when madam was killed.
He was looking for assassins from the underworld sects.
Where is he now?
It is said he will appear at the shed next to the Earth Temple.
I've already sent someone to keep an eye out.
You must bring him back alive to me.
Yes.
I see.
Night-Spirited Hero.
We will uphold justice together.
Together.
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫
Timing and Subtitles created by
🌹 "The True Team" 💖 @ Viki.com
♫ Light is casted in my eye by chance ♫
♫ Just like how I came into your world by chance ♫
♫ If the painting is beautiful, it's because of you ♫
♫ If time turned back, would we meet again? ♫
♫ The most beautiful scenery of this life ♫
♫ is the clouds passing through the moonlight ♫
♫ Twisting and turning, I've fallen into your palm ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫
♫ The night awakens us with the silver moonlight ♫
♫ Whoever catches the firefly shall walk together with me ♫
♫ Fated chance destined it to be you ♫
♫ What a pity to not meet in all this time ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫