Timing and Subtitles created by
🌹 "The True Team" 💖 @ Viki.com
[Truth or Dare - Episode 01]
[Blind Groom]
Qingzhou, a  place seemingly peaceful
but there was a salt gang rebellion that affected the people
on this occasion the black cloak
cat-shaped face four-pronged sword
appears at night
to the people of Qingzhou he is
looked up to by everyone
The Night-Spirited Hero
who's there
tell your leader, try to inflate the price of salt again
I will take his head
outside Qingzhou
the bandits who survived from the General's Palace force,
took possession of the mountain
- and made the merchants who passed by flee.
- Stop.
And in the meantime, the one who can compete with them in terms of strength
Is the third son of the Mei army.
Mei Shiqing.
Mei Shiqing. I'd say you're just a junior general. Even if your dad is here...
He'll still have to call me uncle.
Siheng. Save the people.
Yes!
Save me, save me!
Young Master, are you alright?
I told you long ago,
you should have used my tactic long ago. What did you wait so long for?
You slimy bottom feeder! Ah!
Young Master.
Let's go.
I, He Yizhi, am back in Qingzhou city today.
Boulder-Shattering Chest
Show the Qingzhou citizens
our skills.
Boulder-Shattering Chest!
Next, I present to you
my daughter Xiao Wanzi!
- Bravo!
Kids, do you also like the Night-Spirited Hero?
Yes!
I'll let you in on a secret.
The Night-Spirited Hero is also my role model!
- Wow!
Now it is time for our most exciting event!
Breaking a big stone on the chest!
Great!
Golden Sea rock!
- 30 wen!
- Stable mountain rock!
50 wen!
Longevity rock!
Finished in one go!
- Crow mountain rock!
- 5 taels!
Today, for the benefit of the citizens of Qingzhou.
We have decided anyone who gives 10 taels,
We will break all 5 slabs at once!
- Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.
Is there any boss who will pay?
I will give 5 teals!
- Make way!
- Make way
- Master this way.
- Who is he?
- This way, prince.
Greetings, prince.
How about you give 5 taels more?
We'll break whichever of the five stones you want.
I don't want to break stones.
If you come with me,
I'll let you live it up.
Prince, we're just performers.
With our life, we cannot enjoy this type of happiness.
Don't be shameless!
What do you take our prince for?
Back off!
- What's going on?
- Who are they?
Stop watching! Stop watching!
This is? Huh?
What are they up to?
Get her! Get her!
- Get her.
- Argh!
Aah!
Sorry! I'll fix it.
Is that not it? Then, I'll put it back.
Hurry up and go!
You didn't warn me about using a hammer!
Hurry and chase them!
Chase after them!
Make way!
Chase them!
Stop right there!
Master! You be the judge!
In broad daylight,
what type of person are you to bully elderly and a woman?!
It's her! She hurt our prince.
Master! You be the judge!
Nonsense! They're spewing nonsense.
Obviously, they tried to bully an innocent girl in broad daylight.
They are the ones at fault.
Alright. Disperse! We have important matters to attend.
Siheng, it's too noisy. Return to the Mei Manor!
You all better leave!
Otherwise, we'll deal with you using military laws!
Scram!
Stop!
Are you alright?
You're blind?
Who are you? Get out!
What kind of attitude is that?
I just saved you.
Is that the kind of attitude you should have towards your savior?
Get out!
Don't you have anything grateful to say?
Young Master, are you alright?
- Wanzi.
- Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
See? This is what a person should say.
Siheng, take her away!
Young Master, are you okay?
Siheng, toss her out! Go back to the manor!
Wanzi, hurry and get down!
Hurry up.
[Green Dragon Fort]
What happened to Xiao Bao?
Godfather! Hurry up!
- He's injured that badly?
- Be careful.
- He's injured.
- Oh my.
Xiao Bao greets Godfather...
Xiao Bao, didn't Mei Sanshao hurt your chest? Why is your foot wrapped up?
Godfather, look at him!
We are brothers!
He doesn't even care about me and he is still here talking about me.
if you followed my plan we won't have failed
Godfather, it's because he messed up, that three-legged cat kung fu.
Me, a three-legged cat?
If it weren't for him,
I'd have caught all of them!
Xiao Bao! Xiao Bao.
How did you get hurt like this?
-it hurts
-it's ok, it's ok
Xiao Bao, which goddamned person did this to you? Tell me, Nan Xiang.
I'll skin them alive for sure!
Him.
Me?
I told you to go and fight enemies, not to fight your own side!
Xiao Bao hurt his right leg, right?
Today, I'll also destroy your right leg!
- No, I--
- Stop right there!
- Nan Xiang, let me explain!
- Let me through!
Stop right there!
It's fine, it's fine.
Xiao Bao...recover well.
Old Six, take care of him.
Yes, Chief. No problem.
[Mei Manor]
Those damn bandits!
I'll let them have death by a thousand cuts!
Siheng, what did the doctor say?
The doctor said...
Say it!
The doctor said...there is little hope for Young Master's eyes.
This quack!
Who diagnosed him? Bring him to me immediately!
Lord, calm down. You don't want to harm your health from anger.
Shiqing, seriously.
Your marriage is priority, so why would go around fighting bandits?
If the Princess sees your current condition, she definitely won't want to marry you!
Since I have turned out like this, I'm afraid I'm not a good match for the Princess.
I ask of you to clarify the situation to the Ninth Prince Manor and withdraw from the marriage early on.
This is a marriage conferred by the Emperor!
How could I allow you to take hundreds of Mei family lives as a joke?
I told you to go take the imperial examination, yet you took the military exam!
I told you to marry the Princess,
yet you-- you're blind.
Fine, are you trying to anger me to death?
Lord, first and foremost, Shiqing is injured.
Second of all, he never wanted to unite with the Ninth Prince Manor through marriage in the first place.
As I see it, how about...
betrothing the Princess to Shiyuan?
Yeah, dad. Betroth her to me.
Shut up!
As someone who roams bawdy houses and gambling houses all day, how shameless are you to marry the Princess?
Dad, at least I can see the Princess.
- Not like--
- This is a bestowed marriage, how could you be allowed to mess around?
If Shiming were still here,
this wouldn't be left to you two good-for-nothings!
If big brother were still here,
He'll just one of your chess pieces to be used by you.
Fine, I see you dare to lecture your father now!
Bring out the family discipline!
Lord!
Lord Shiqing didn't mean that.
- Today is madam's anniversary!
- Quiet!
The marriage is soon, what would the Princess say if Master was injured!
I will take the punishment in his place!
Mei Shiqing, this is a marriage bestowed upon by the Emperor.
Regardless of if she's a good match or not, you have to marry her anyways!
You're but a blind person. I'll see how long you can be arrogant for.
[Ninth Prince Manor]
Have a seat, father.
Okay.
- Does this feel good?
- Yes.
Daughter, take a look around your home.
It is nothing fancy.
The house is empty and all that's left is the empty title of "Imperial".
Daddy, I heard you pleaded the Emperor for the marriage.
Then, can you also ask him to cancel it?
Don't say that!
This is a marriage appointed by the Emperor.
Refusing the marriage would be refusing his order! You must marry him.
Father.
Qingzhou General Mei's Third Young Master Mei Shiqing.
He's a talented youth known far and wide.
If you marry him, it's a match made in heaven.
Daddy, Qingzhou is far and rural and the Mei family are military commanders.
Are you really just going to marry your daughter off like this?
I--
Daddy, I think their wealth
and military power has caught your eye.
Imperial sons and daughters...
have never been able to decide on who they marry.
You must be married.
Xiao yun. Attend the princess, get ready to be married.
Yes.
Daddy!
Father!
Princess, get up now.
I've already told you you've tried this too many times, it won't work.
Didn't the emperor already say?
The Mei family's Third Young Master is a talented youth known far and wide.
Perhaps, this might even be a good marriage.
What talented youth?
I've never even seen him.
What if he's really ugly?
What if he's a drooling idiot?
How about this? I'll run away from home.
At all costs, no! This is a bestowed marriage.
If you run away, this whole manor--
Will be implicated for nine generations, miss.
Miss! Miss!
We didn't make a single cent, what do we do about dinner?
Think about it this way, how energizing was it to teach those people a lesson today!
Energizing? Regardless, I'm out of energy now.
Look here, there's a baozi booth up ahead. Let's hurry a few steps
and I'll buy you two big meat buns, okay?
Sound good? Let's hurry.
One step, two steps.
- One step, two steps.
What's that smell?
- What's wrong, Wanzi?
- What's that smell?
What's that smell? It smells so good.
Wanzi, this is Qingzhou's most famous Ruyi Restaurant.
Their menu includes sweet and sour ribs,
sweet and sour fish, braised ribs...
Stop thinking about it, Wanzi. This isn't the place for poor folks like us to eat at.
Have a safe trip!
Father, so this is the legendary Ruyi Restaurant.
Wait, wait for me.
I'll just smell the fragrance.
I'll just smell the fragrance and be satisfied.
[Ruyi Restaurant]
That's enough.
Wanzi, put it down. Okay,
your father will end your meatless diet once today.
We won't eat much, just one of their dishes.
Sweet and sour ribs, okay?
Okay, let's go!
Dad, these sweet and sour pork ribs really live up to their name.
Daughter, my wine is also delicious.
Let me have a cup as well. Here, Dad.
Don't drink too much. Your face is already bright red.
This is makeup!
Lady A'Rou!
She really deserves her reputation. So beautiful...
Say, do you think that I could be like Lady A'Rou one day?
You should drink less, Daughter.
Young Master, here is your meal.
Don't disturb us if there is nothing else.
Understood.
Young Master, don't be too upset.
The General still values you a lot.
For this marriage, he put in a lot of effort.
The hidden dangers of the Green Dragon Fort have not been eliminated yet.
How could I have the time to think about these things?
Besides, my father
abandoned my mother and I for merits in the war ten years ago.
Today, even if my leg broke,
he would still force me to marry
to gain more power for him and the Mei Family.
Where is A'Rou?
She's performing downstairs. She'll come up soon.
Young Master, what happened to your eyes?
Young Master and I went to catch the bandits of the Green Dragon Fort,
but we fell into their trap, so his eyes...
Third Young Master, you brought me, a performer who was looked down on by others,
into the Ruyi Restaurant. You not only allowed me to sing and dance,
but also let me manage the Ruyi Restaurant.
I will never forget your kindness to me.
I am willing to always stay by your side and serve you.
I'm not blind. Get up.
Young Master, why do you have to pretend to be blind?
Could it be to escape from your marriage?
My actions today are a military secret.
I didn't expect the Green Dragon Fort to actually set a trap to frame me.
A mole most likely leaked the information to them.
Thus, I'm playing along
to appear weak so that I can secretly catch the mole.
The Mei Manor has always been strictly managed.
To think that such things would happen.
How is your progress on the matter I asked you to investigate?
I found a location where private salt is hidden.
Ever since Li Tianlong's group collapsed,
there hasn't been salt smuggling
in Qingzhou City for decades.
Looking at the current situation, this salt smuggling
is a sign of resurgence.
Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
What's going on?
I'll go check.
Good! Good! Good!
Amazing!
Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
If you add one more tael of silver right now,
we'll perform one more time!
Good! Good! Good!
It's fine, Young Master. It's just a little girl who drank too much. A bunch of people are watching her perform.
I didn't expect there to be a hidden talent in our Ruyi Restaurant.
We need to be careful.
Young Master is worried. I'll go with Siheng and take a look.
Where is the delicious food?
The smell of sweet and sour pork ribs?
Who is it?
So you're over here.
Who are you? Get out.
Are you blind?
You look really familiar.
Do we know each other?
But how can you eat if you're blind?
Since we know each other, I'll take care of you.
I'll feed you.
Siheng!
Open your mouth.
Don't you want to eat?
So strong!
Open your mouth.
Why is she this strong?
Why aren't you eating?
Such a strong wine smell!
Are you that...
that young General Mei?
The young General Mei?
The beggar?
You ungrateful person!
I obviously saved you, but you're still mean to me?
Fine, I don't care if you were mean,
but you also teased me!
I'll let you know
what is
Xiao Wanzi's rage!
Impudent! Pull her away!
Hurry and leave!
Roar!
Young Master, are you alright?
A'Rou, don't let this crazy women appear in Ruyi Restaurant in the future!
Understood, Young Master.
Lunatic.
Go away!
Are you okay, Wanzi?
How could you push someone?
Look, you two.
If you don't have money, don't come to Ruyi Restaurant to eat.
We aren't some charity organization.
Let's go!
So what if we come? What're you going to do?
We'll just come to your restaurant every day to smell the food!
Right? We'll just come to their restaurant every day to smell the food!
You okay, Wanzi?
Let's go!
Bye bye.
Let's go home.
Sweet and sour ribs are delicious.
Daughter, you enjoyed yourself.
Tonight, we have to sleep on the street again.
Delicious.
Night-Spirited Hero! Night-Spirited Hero!
What? What's up? Wanzi!
Wait for me! Me!
Don't move!
Night-Spirited Hero!
Teach me how to fly!
Luckily, she's not here.
It actually is you.
I really like you.
I actually... really like you.
Can you bring me with you in the future?
Let's fight evil together.
We're a match made in heaven.
Damn it.
Wanzi! Wanzi!
Dad, the Night-Spirited Hero is here.
Wanzi, where did you go?
Where's the Night-Spirited Hero?
What do you have on your mind all day?
Let's go!
Big! Big! Open!
Dad. I'm really hungry.
I want to eat west lake vinegar fish and sweet and sour ribs.
Wait a second, daughter. This round is all set for me.
Still big. Big! Big! Big!
They must have been cheating at big. Your dad is aware of it okay?
He Yizhi, you've lost everything again.
When are you going to pay back all the money you owe?
That's right! I'll go get you the money.
- Trying to run away, huh?
- No, no.
You stinky old man, you can't pay back the money.
But your daughter, looks like you. Eh?
- What are you trying to say?
- She'll sell for some money.
- No, no, no.
- Father, save me!
I, He Yizhi, will pay back the money I owe by myself.
This has nothing to do with my daughter. All right, Brother Feng?
Are you able to take the responsibility?
Just wait until I'm full and energized,
I'll beat you up!
- Wanzi!
- So noisy.
- Shut her mouth and take her away.
- Hey!
Father, save me!
Didn't capture Mei Shiqing.
It's all your fault! If it weren't for you, would I end up like this?
Would you have been able to beat Mei Shiqing if it wasn't for my powder blinding him?
- You're disgusting! You bastard!
- Move away.
Xiao Bao.
Drink the medicine.
Nan Xiang, I beg you, let me go.
Xiao Bao, this medicine has to be drunk while warm. I can carry you!
Don't run! Let me feed you you. Brother Bao!
Wait for me! Don't run!
You're the Second Master of our fortress.
We cannot let him benefit.
Nan Xiang likes him.
I have good news that I'm not sure if I should say.
What news?
Wedding?
Paradise Casino people told me that.
There's an old man. Owes lots of money.
He has a daughter who has a "Boulder-Shattering Chest".
Her figure is awesome.
Can give birth to a whole bunch of kids. I think.
She suits Xiao Bao especially well.
What do you mean a whole bunch of kids? Is she a sow?
Hey Wu. I know you like the type.
- Wishing lots of kids for you.
- I mean you.
Xiao Bao. We are talking about getting you a wife.
Your injury is almost fixed now.
Why am I marrying Godfather?
I'm still young. I'm not in a rush.
I feel Wu makes sense.
Then... Then you've got to find me a good girl.
I already mentioned. Said that "Boulder-Shattering Chest" girl...
I don't want a shrew.
You need to find someone to handle your bad temper.
Firstly...
I will help us reverse our fortunes.
Secondly, it will give you a heir.
- Godfather...
- Get out!
Are you the chief or am I the chief?
Thanks, brother.
Hey, Xiao Bao!
I know you don't like bitter things
so I prepared sweet fruits.
- Try it.
- I'm not eating. Stop bothering me.
What's wrong? Just eat one.
Eat one.
Let them feed on these.
Xiao Bao! Where are you going? Wait for me!
Looks like this daughter of mine
really likes Xiao Bao.
You say. This brat.
Keeps ignoring Nan Xiang.
Don't think my daughter is good enough?
Then I'll find him a "Boulder-Shattering Chest" girl.
Find an auspicious day. Bring her up the mountain.
I've already worked it out.
It'll be a rare super auspicious day in 3 days time.
You're really capable kid.
Then let's do it in 3 days time.
The Green Dragon Fort will have a celebration.
Master, I'll get people on it right away.
Why don't they feed us.
Might as well kill me.
What are they going to do with me?
Don't think too much.
We will work out the situation...
as it happens.
Hey. They're bringing food.
Brother Feng. Brother Feng.  Brother Feng.
- Brother Feng
- Food
How are the two of you doing these few days?
No good.
You should at least feed us and let us bathe.
That bun you gave us was so small. Left us hungry.
- Give us more food. Okay?
- You are so strong.
Won't you run away if we gave you food?
Brother Feng. We won't run.
But don't worry. In a bit, I will take you to go get a good bath.
Bath?
Great...a bath?
- Bath?
- Wait,
th-this, what does this mean?
Have you heard of Green Dragon Fort?
The chief's godson, Master Xiao Bao, is interested in daughter.
Hey Brother Feng. That's not possible.
My daughter is a maiden, how could she enter the bandit's den?
This is not up to you.
- Father!
- Wanzi!
Father!
I advise you to be smart.
Your daughter marrying Master Xiao Bao
is her dumb luck.
Moreover, no matter how strong you are.
When you get there, you will not be able to escape the mountain.
I dare you to harm my Wanzi!
I'll beat you at any cost!
Father! Stop hitting my father! Stop hitting him!
I'll marry! I'll marry!
Timing and Subtitles created by
🌹 "The True Team" 💖 @ Viki.com
♫ Light is casted in my eye by chance ♫
♫ Just like how I came into your world by chance ♫
♫ If the painting is beautiful, it's because of you ♫
♫ If time turned back, would we meet again? ♫
♫ The most beautiful scenery of this life ♫
♫ is the clouds passing through the moonlight ♫
♫ Twisting and turning, I've fallen into your palm ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫
♫ The night awakens us with the silver moonlight ♫
♫ Whoever catches the firefly shall walk together with me ♫
♫ Fated chance destined it to be you ♫
♫ What a pity to not meet in all this time ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫