- Good morning, Benjamín.
- Good morning, Your Highness. Welcome.
- If you would come with me.
- I'll see you later, okay?
ARI, SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO REACT.
SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT AT THE LAKE CLUB.
ARI IS TYPING...
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE LAKE CLUB? DEBATE?
I'D RATHER MEET OUTSIDE SCHOOL SO WE CAN
TAKE OUR TIME PREPARING OUR ARGUMENT.
A school full of girls from good families,
all waiting for my son to look at them,
and he falls for the janitor?
She wants to be a fashion designer.
She's a very bright and intelligent girl.
I know that sort of intelligence.
I've seen it in all the other
Little Miss Nobodies after him.
Cayetana will behave
and stick to the path set for her.
How do you know that?
She has shown unconditional support
for her boyfriends before.
She'll be with him no matter what.
She has everything to gain.
You'll throw a New Year's Eve party.
The media will be there,
and there'll be a photo shoot.
I want you to invite all your friends.
You can bring that girl if you want.
Cayetana.
So, Benjamín filled you in.
Do you really like her?
Very much.
Have you at least given
other girls a chance?
I don't want other girls.
I want her.
Fine, you'll introduce her formally
at the party.
That's part of your campaign
to clean up my image, right?
We're not together right now.
You mean you can't win
your peasant girl back?
Don't call her that.
Do you want her back or not?
Yes, Mom.
Well then, do what you need to do.
What's happened to you here in Madrid?
I don't recognize you anymore.
I WANT TO SEE YOU TONIGHT
WHAT TIME SHOULD WE GO TO THE HOTEL?
I'M SORRY, REBE. I CAN'T GO.
I WANT TO START THE YEAR WITH YOU.
PHILLIPE
BEFORE I GO: MOM, GUZMÁN, OMAR
Shit.