Yes, Mom.
Benjamín said he'd be here
with his three kids.
They'll be in my class.
Don't worry.
Thanks. I love you.
Let's talk tomorrow.
It's a pleasure to meet you in person.
The pleasure is mine. Welcome.
I'll introduce you to my children.
Patrick.
PEEP INTO THE CLASSROOM.
GIVE ME TEN MINUTES.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING.
REBE, SORRY TO BE A PAIN. CAN WE TALK?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HI, ARMANDO.
MAYBE WE COULD MEET ONE MORE TIME.
IF YOU WANT TO.
That's fine. Leave her.
I don't want anyone
to get expelled because of me.
No one should pay for their family's sins
because of who my family is.
It's a matter of control and security.
My family didn't ask for even half
of the measures you put in place.
Besides, I've had the chance
to meet my classmates,
and I feel welcome.
I don't see any danger in them.
Very well.
Which measures should I get rid of?
The cameras, perhaps?
No, not the cameras.
I'd prefer it if you kept them.