BELLA: I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
But dying in the place of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
(OMINOUS THEME PLAYING)
BELLA: So I can't bring myself to
regret the decision to leave home.
I would miss Phoenix.
I'd miss the heat.
I would miss my loving, erratic,
harebrained mother.
(SOFTLY) Okay.
PHIL: Renee, come on.
BELLA: And her new husband.
Guys, come on. I love you both.
We got a plane to catch.
But they want to go on the road,
so I'm gonna spend some time with my dad,
and this will be a good thing.
I think.
(SINGING) When the thorn bush turns white
That's when I'll come home
I am going out to see what I can sow
And I don't know where I'll go
And I don't know what I'll see
BELLA: In the state of Washington,
under a near constant cover
of clouds and rain,
there's a small town named Forks.
Population, 3, 120 people.
This is where I'm moving.
My dad's Charlie.
He's the chief of police.
Curse the powers that be
Cause all I want is...
Your hair's longer.
I cut it since the last time I saw you.
Guess it grew out again.
BELLA: I used to spend two weeks here
almost every summer,
but it's been years.
I've cleared some shelves off
in the bathroom.
Right. One bathroom.
It's a pretty good work lamp.
The sales lady picked out the bed stuff.
You like purple, right?
Purple's cool.
Thanks.
Okay.
BELLA: One of the best things about Charlie,
he doesn't hover.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
Heard you guys coming
all the way down the road.
Good to see you.
Bella, you remember Billy Black.
- Yeah.
Wow, you're looking good.
- Well, I'm still dancing.
I'm glad you're finally here.
Charlie here hasn't shut up about it
since you told him you were coming.
(CHUCKLES)
All right, keep exaggerating.
I'll roll you into the mud.
After I ram you in the ankles.
CHARLIE: You want to go?
- Yeah.
Bring it.
Hi, I'm Jacob.
- Hey.
We used to make mud pies
when we were little.
Right. No, I remember.
(LAUGHS)
Are they always like this?
It's getting worse with old age.
- Good.
So, what do you think?
Of what?
Your homecoming present.
- This?
Just bought it off Billy here.
- Yep.
I totally rebuilt the engine for you.
- Come on.
Oh, my gosh!
This is perfect. Are you joking me?
(JACOB GRUNTS)
Sorry.
I told you she'd love it.
I'm down with the kids.
Oh, yeah, dude. You're the bomb.
Okay.
Listen, you gotta double-pump
the clutch when you shift,
but besides that, you should be good.
That's this one?
- Yeah. Yeah, right there.
All right.
Do you want a ride to school or something?
I go to school on the reservation.
Right, right.
- Yeah.
That's too bad.
It would've been nice to know one person.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
BELLA: My first day at a new school.
It's March, middle of the semester.
(TRUCK BACKFIRES)
Great.
Nice ride.
- Thanks.
Good one.
You're Isabella Swan, the new girl.
Hi, I'm Eric, the eyes and ears of this place.
Anything you need, tour guide,
lunch date, shoulder to cry on?
I'm really kind of the more
suffer-in-silence type.
Good headline for your feature.
I'm on the paper,
and you're news, baby, front page.
No, I'm not.
(STUTTERS) You...
Please don't have any sort of...
Chillax. No feature.
Okay, thanks.
- Cool?
GIRL: All right. Okay. Yeah.
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
GIRL: Get it! Get it! Get it!
(BELLA GRUNTS)
GIRL 1: To you!
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
I told them not to let me play.
No way. No, no, no.
That's... That's... Don't...
You're Isabella, right?
Just Bella.
Yeah. Hey, I'm Mike Newton.
Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, yeah.
She's got a great spike, huh?
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah, it's...
I'm Jessica, by the way.
Hey, you're from Arizona, right?
Yeah.
Aren't people from Arizona
supposed to be, like, really tan?
Yeah.
Maybe that's why they kicked me out.
(MIKE AND JESSICA LAUGHING)
You're good.
That's so funny.
Back in, Jess.
- BOY: Down here.
ERIC: Like a masterpiece, you know,
we'll have, like,
this crazy pyramid fall from the sky,
and then you guys can...
- It's my pleasure, Madame.
You guys can give each other high fives.
- Burrito, my friend?
Hey, Mikey! You met my home girl, Bella?
- Hey.
Your home girl?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
That's...
- My girl.
Sorry I had to mess up your game, Mike!
Tyler.
(ALL LAUGHING)
TYLER: Yes!
Oh, my God.
It's like first grade all over again.
You're the shiny new toy.
Smile.
Okay.
- Sorry.
I needed a candid for the feature.
The feature's dead, Angela.
Don't bring it up again.
It's okay, I just...
I got your back, baby.
Guess we'll just run another editorial
on teen drinking.
You know,
you can always go for eating disorders.
Speedo padding on the swim team.
Actually, that's a good one.
Kirk. Right? That's exactly what I thought.
- (LAUGHS) Yeah.
ANGELA: We're talking Olympic-size.
JESSICA: There's no way. He's so skinny.
It doesn't make sense.
ANGELA: Totally.
- Yeah.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Who are they?
The Cullens.
They're Dr. and Mrs. Cullen's foster kids.
They moved down here from Alaska,
like, a few years ago.
They kind of keep to themselves.
Yeah, 'cause they're all together.
Like, together, together.
The blonde girl, that's Rosalie,
and the big dark-haired guy, Emmett,
they're, like, a thing.
I'm not even sure that's legal.
Jess, they're not actually related.
Yeah, but they live together. It's weird.
And, okay, the little dark-haired girl's Alice.
She's really weird,
and she's with Jasper, the blond one
who looks like he's in pain.
Dr. Cullen's like this foster dad/matchmaker.
Maybe he'll adopt me.
Who's he?
That's Edward Cullen.
He's totally gorgeous, obviously,
but apparently nobody here's
good enough for him.
Like I care, you know?
So, yeah.
JESSICA: Seriously, like,
don't waste your time.
I wasn't planning on it.
Mr. Molina.
- Hey, Mike.
Oh, yes. Miss Swan.
Hi. Can I have the pass? Thank you.
Welcome to the class.
Here. Here's your stuff, okay?
And I got a seat for you right here,
so come over.
The last one.
Just follow along till you catch up.
All right, guys, today we are gonna be
observing the behavior of planaria,
aka flatworms.
So what we're gonna do...
(MOLINA CONTINUES
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
...regenerate.
Zombie worms.
No cell phones. Guys, let's get to it.
Gentle, gentle, certain areas.
Please just don't cut here.
We don't cut here.
You won't believe this.
Let's try to focus
while we check those out, huh, guys?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
EDWARD: There must be something open.
Physics? Biochem?
- WOMAN: No, every class is full.
Just a minute, dear.
I'm afraid you'll have to stay in biology.
Fine. Just... I'll just have to endure it.
I just can't get over how grown up you are.
And so gorgeous.
Hey, Bella.
You remember me?
I played Santa one year.
Yeah, Waylon, she hasn't had
a Christmas here since she was four.
I bet I made an impression, though, didn't I?
You always do.
- Butt-crack Santa?
Hey, kids love those little bottles, though.
All right,
let the girl eat her garden burger, Waylon.
As soon as you're done,
I will bring you your favorite.
Berry cobbler, remember?
Your dad still has it. Every Thursday.
Thank you. That'd be great.
CHARLIE: Here.
(WHISPERS) Thanks.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
RENEE ON PHONE: Hey, baby. So, listen,
if spring training goes well,
we could be moving to Florida.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Please insert $1.25
for an additional three minutes.
Mom, where's your cell?
Okay, don't laugh.
I didn't lose my power cord. It ran away.
(LAUGHS)
Screaming. I literally repel technology now.
I miss you.
- Oh, baby, I miss you, too.
But tell me more about your school.
Now, what are the kids like?
Are there any cute guys?
Are they being nice to you?
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
Well,
they're all very welcoming.
Tell me all about it.
It doesn't even matter.
Yes, it does, honey.
I have homework to do. I'll talk to you later.
Okay. I love you.
Love you, too.
BELLA: I planned to confront him
and demand to know what his problem was.
But he never showed.
(SLOW ROCK THEME PLAYING)
Bella!
BELLA: And the next day, another no-show.
More days passed.
Things were getting a little strange.
(PANTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Ice doesn't really help the uncoordinated.
Yeah. That's why I had
some new tires put on the truck.
Old ones were getting pretty bald.
Well, probably be late for dinner.
I gotta head down to Mason County.
Security guard at the Grisham Mill
got killed by some kind of animal.
An animal?
You're not in Phoenix anymore, Bells.
Anyway, I figured I'd lend a hand.
Be careful.
- Always am.
And thanks for the tires.
- Yeah.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
ERIC: Prom Committee is a chick thing,
but I gotta cover it for the paper anyway,
and they need a guy
to help choose the music,
so I need your play list.
Hey, listen, I was wondering,
did you have a date to...
What's up, Arizona? Huh?
How you liking the rain, girl?
Better get used to it, girl.
Yeah, Mike, hey, you're real cute, man.
Oh, I know...
- That was really awesome.
ERIC: Why you shooting down my game?
Let a playa play.
MIKE: Yeah, okay.
What you playing at, T-Ball?
Hello.
I'm sorry, I didn't get a chance
to introduce myself last week.
I'm Edward Cullen.
You're Bella?
Yes.
Onion root tip cells,
that's what's on your slides right now.
Okay? So, separate and label them
into the phases of mitosis,
and the first partners that get it right
are gonna win the Golden Onion.
(STUDENTS CATCALLING)
BOY: All right, good.
Ladies first.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
You were gone.
Yeah.
I was out of town for a couple of days.
Personal reasons.
Prophase.
Do you mind if I look?
It's prophase.
Like I said.
So are you enjoying the rain?
(ANXIOUS LAUGH)
What?
You're asking me about the weather?
Yeah, I...
I guess I am.
Well, I don't really like the rain.
Any cold, wet thing, I don't really...
What?
- Nothing.
(LAUGHS)
It's anaphase.
You mind if I check?
- Sure.
Anaphase.
Like I said.
If you hate the cold and the rain so much,
why'd you move to the wettest place
in the continental US?
It's complicated.
I'm sure I can keep up.
My mom remarried, and...
So you don't like the guy, or...
No, that's not...
Phil's really nice.
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
It's metaphase. You want to check it?
I believe you.
Why didn't you move
with your mother and Phil?
Well, Phil's a minor league baseball player,
and he travels a lot,
and my mom stayed home with me,
but I knew it made her unhappy,
so I figured I'd stay with my dad for a while.
And now you're unhappy.
No.
- I'm sorry, I'm just...
I'm just trying to figure you out.
You're very difficult for me to read.
Hey, did you get contacts?
No.
Your eyes were black
the last time I saw you,
and now they're, like, golden brown.
Yeah, I know, it's the...
It's the fluorescents.
(HORN BLASTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LOUD THUDS)
(LOUD GRUNT)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
ALL: Bella!
- Bella!
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
GIRL: Dial 911!
BOY: I already called.
They're gonna send somebody over soon.
Bella, I'm so sorry. I panicked.
Bella, I've got 911 on the phone now.
Bella. You okay?
You and I are gonna talk. You all right?
I'm fine, Dad. Calm down.
I'm sorry, Bella. I tried to stop.
I know. It's okay.
No. It sure as hell is not okay.
Dad, it wasn't his fault.
You could've been killed.
You understand that?
Yes. But I wasn't, so...
You can kiss your license goodbye.
I heard the chief's daughter was here.
- CHARLIE: Dr. Cullen.
Charlie.
I've got this one, Jackie.
Isabella.
Bella.
Well, Bella, looks like you took quite a spill.
How do you feel?
Good.
Look here.
You might experience some
post-traumatic stress or disorientation,
but your vitals look good.
No signs of any head trauma.
I think you'll be just fine.
TYLER: I'm so sorry, Bella. I'm really...
You know,
it would've been a whole lot worse
if Edward wasn't there.
He knocked me out of the way.
Edward? Your boy?
Yeah, it was amazing.
I mean, he got to me so fast.
He was nowhere near me.
Sounds like you were very lucky.
Charlie.
I gotta go sign some paperwork.
You should...
You should probably call your mom.
Did you tell her?
(GROANS) She's probably just
freaking out.
ROSALIE: fifteen kids that saw
what happened.
EDWARD: What was I supposed to do, then?
Let her die?
This isn't just about you. It's about all of us.
CARLISLE: I think we should
take this in my office.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Rosalie.
What?
How did you get over to me so fast?
I was standing right next to you, Bella.
No. You were next to your car,
across the lot.
No, I wasn't.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Yes, you were.
Bella, you're... You hit your head.
I think you're confused.
I know what I saw.
And what exactly was that?
You...
You stopped the van.
You pushed it away with your hand.
Well, nobody's gonna believe you, so...
I wasn't gonna tell anybody.
I just need to know the truth.
Can't you just thank me and get over it?
Thank you.
You're not gonna let this go, are you?
- No.
Well, then I hope you enjoy disappointment.
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
BELLA: And that was the first night
I dreamt of Edward Cullen.
I need everybody's permission slips, okay?
Sammy, please collect them.
- Yeah.
Guys, let's go.
Come on, get in. In. Let's go!
Look at you, huh? You're alive.
I know, yeah. False alarm, I guess.
- Yeah.
Now, I wanted to ask you,
you know, if, you know,
it's like a month away, but...
(MIKE LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Do you wanna go to prom with me?
So, what do you think?
About what?
- Do you want to go?
To prom?
With me?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I...
Prom.
Dancing.
Not such a good idea for me.
I have something that weekend anyway.
I'm going to Jacksonville that weekend.
You can't go another weekend?
Non-refundable ticket.
You should ask Jessica.
I know she wants to go with you.
All right. All right.
MOLINA: Yo, yo, yo. Hey, guys, come on.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Green is what? Good.
Let's go. Guys, come on.
Other bus, other bus. Let's go.
MOLINA: Egg shells, carrot tops.
Compost is cool.
Now, stuff that in there, Eric.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Very good, very good.
Now, I am gonna make a steaming cup
of compost tea.
Okay.
- Give me that.
Yeah. This is recycling
in its most basic form, guys.
Don't drink it! It's for the plants.
What's in Jacksonville?
How did you know about that?
You didn't answer my question.
You don't answer any of mine, so...
I mean, you don't even say hi to me.
Hi.
Are you gonna tell me
how you stopped the van?
Yeah. I had an adrenaline rush.
It's very common. You can Google it.
Floridians.
That's what's in Jacksonville.
Can you at least watch where you walk?
Look, I'm sorry I'm being rude all the time.
I just think it's the best way.
Bella! Guess who just asked me to prom.
Who?
Yeah, I actually totally thought
that Mike was gonna ask you.
It's not gonna be weird, though, right?
- No. Zero weirdness.
You guys are great together.
- I know, right?
(GUYS HOOTING)
Tyler...
- BOY: Gross.
Bella, look. It's a worm.
(GUFFAWING) It's a worm.
Bella, we shouldn't be friends.
You really should've figured
that out a little earlier.
I mean, why didn't you just
let the van crush me
and save yourself all this regret?
What, you think I regret saving you?
I can see that you do.
I just... I don't know why.
You don't know anything.
Hi.
Are you gonna be riding with us?
No, our bus is full.
Your mom called. Again.
Well, that's your fault.
You shouldn't have told her
about the "almost" accident. You finished?
Yeah.
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
She always did know how to worry.
She seems different.
She seems happy.
Phil sounds like an all right guy.
Yeah, he is.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
All right.
ERIC: No, you need the mitts.
You need them.
No, why do you keep arguing with me?
You just need them.
ERIC: You're gonna get frostbite!
- I don't even know.
ERIC: Yeah. Hey!
La Push, baby. You in?
- Should I know what that means?
La Push Beach down at the Quileute Rez.
We're all going tomorrow.
Yeah, there's a big swell coming in.
- And I don't just surf the Internet.
Eric, you stood up once,
and it was a foam board.
But there's whale watching, too.
Come with us.
La Push, baby. It's La Push.
Okay, I'll go if you stop saying that, okay?
Seriously, dude. It's creepy, man.
What? That's what it's called.
- So...
EDWARD: Edible art?
Bella.
Thanks.
You know, your mood swings
are kind of giving me whiplash.
I only said it'd be better
if we weren't friends,
not that I didn't wanna be.
What does that mean?
It means if you were smart,
you'd stay away from me.
Okay, well, let's say for argument's sake
that I'm not smart.
Would you tell me the truth?
- No, probably not.
I'd rather hear your theories.
I have considered
radioactive spiders and Kryptonite.
That's all superhero stuff, right?
What if I'm not the hero?
What if I'm the bad guy?
You're not.
I can see what you're trying to put off,
but I can see that it's just
to keep people away from you.
It's a mask.
Why don't we just hang out?
Everybody's going to the beach.
Come.
I mean, have fun.
Which beach?
- La Push.
I don't know.
I just...
Is there something wrong with that beach?
It's just a little crowded.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
Hey, it's freezing.
- I'm paddling out, Coates.
I don't know if it's worth it anymore.
- We drove all the way out here.
JESSICA: I'm at least paddling out.
- Yeah.
She's right.
- You guys are babies.
So, I keep thinking that Eric's
gonna ask me to the prom,
and then he just doesn't.
You should ask him.
Take control.
You're a strong, independent woman.
I am?
- Yes.
Hey, will you do me up?
- Yeah.
Bella!
- Hi, Jacob.
Guys, this is Jacob.
- Hey, guys. How you doing?
Hi.
- Hi.
What are you, like, stalking me?
(SCOFFS) You're on my rez, remember?
Are you surfing?
Definitely not.
- Thanks.
You guys should keep Bella company.
Her date bailed.
What date?
She invited Edward.
To be polite, that's it.
- I think it's nice she invited him.
Nobody ever does.
- Yeah, 'cause Cullen's a freak.
You got that right.
You guys know him?
The Cullens don't come here.
What did your friends mean about,
you know, "The Cullens don't come here?"
You caught that, huh?
I'm not really supposed
to say anything about it.
Hey, I can keep a secret.
(LAUGHS)
Really, it's just like an old scary story.
Well, I want to know.
Okay, did you know Quileutes
are supposedly descended from wolves?
What? Like, wolves?
Yeah.
- Like, real wolves?
JACOB: Well, that's the legend of our tribe.
BELLA: Okay.
So what's the story about the Cullens?
Well, they're supposedly descended
from this, like, enemy clan.
JACOB: My great grandfather, the chief,
found them hunting on our land.
But they claimed to be something different,
so we made a treaty with them.
If they promised to stay off Quileute lands,
then we wouldn't expose
what they really were to the palefaces.
I thought they just moved here.
Or just moved back.
Right.
ANGELA: (SCREAMS) It touched my hand.
A snake! Stop!
Well, what are they really?
It's just a story, Bella.
Come on, let's go.
(ANGELA CONTINUES SCREAMING)
A snake! A snake!
(SINGING) My mama said I didn't know
how to make a kitty meow
(DEEP GROWL)
Hello?
Gerald?
(WHOOSHING)
Hello.
Nice jacket.
Who are you?
It's always the same inane questions.
"Who are you?"
"What do you want?"
"Why are you doing this?"
James, let's not play with our food.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(SLOW BLUESY-ROCK THEME PLAYING)
JESSICA: He's not here.
Whenever the weather's nice,
the Cullens disappear.
What, do they just ditch?
No, Dr. and Mrs. Cullen yank them out
for, like, hiking and camping and stuff.
I tried that out on my parents.
Not even close.
Guys, I'm going to the prom with Eric.
I just asked him. I took control.
- I told you that would happen.
Are you sure you have to go out of town?
Oh, yeah, it's a little family thing.
Okay, we should go shopping
in Port Angeles
before all the good dresses get cleaned out.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Port Angeles? You mind if I come?
Yeah, I need your opinion.
I like this one.
- ANGELA: That's cool.
But, like, I don't know about
the one-shoulder thing.
I like this one.
- JESSICA: Yeah, I like the beading,
and you wouldn't need jewelry.
- Jess, what do you think? Lavender?
Is that good? Is that my color?
- I like it.
I liked that dusty rose one, too.
Okay, I like this one.
It makes my boobs look good.
Hey.
- JESSICA: Right?
Nice.
ANGELA: Oh, God.
- That is uncomfortable.
That's disgusting.
Bella, what do you think?
Yes?
That looks great.
You said that about, like,
the last five dresses, though.
I thought they were all pretty good.
You're not really into this, are you?
I actually really just want
to go to this bookstore.
I'll meet you guys at the restaurant?
JESSICA: Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah. I'll see you in a minute.
Okay.
- Okay.
She's right, though. This looks awesome.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
MAN: There you go.
Have a good night.
- BELLA: Thank you.
BOY: Saw you in the dress store.
- Hey, where you running to?
BOY: There she is.
What's up?
- It's my girl.
BOY 2: How you guys doing?
- Look who we just found.
What's up, girl? Hey... Where you going?
BOY 3: Where are you going?
- Come get a drink with us.
Yeah, you should hang out with us.
- Come on.
It's fun.
What's the problem?
- She doesn't like that, man.
You're pretty.
- Don't touch me.
BOY: Cute.
- Really, no. Seriously, you should.
Don't touch me.
(BOY GROANS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GASPS)
Get in the car.
That was a very dangerous maneuver.
(DEEP GROWL)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BOYS SHOUTING)
(HORN BLARING)
I should go back there
and rip those guys' heads off.
No, you shouldn't.
You don't know the vile, repulsive things
they were thinking.
And you do?
It's not hard to guess.
Can you talk about something else?
Distract me so I won't turn around.
You should put your seatbelt on.
(LAUGHS)
I thought the salad was pretty good.
- Hey, you guys, I'm sorry. I just...
Where were you? We left you messages.
Yeah, we waited, but we were, like,
starving, so we...
I'm sorry I kept Bella from dinner.
We just sort of ran into each other
and got talking.
Yeah.
- No.
No, we totally understand.
I mean, that happens, right?
Yeah, we were...
We were, yeah, we were just leaving. So...
- Let's get this...
Bella, if you wanna...
I think I should make sure
Bella gets something to eat.
If you'd like.
I'll drive you home myself.
That's so thoughtful.
It's really thoughtful. Yeah.
Yeah. I should eat something.
Yeah.
Okay, so we'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay, yeah.
ANGELA: See ya.
- Okay.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
All right, one mushroom ravioli.
Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
So are you sure there isn't anything
I can get for you?
No. No, thank you.
Let me know.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
You're really not gonna eat?
No, I'm on a special diet.
You gotta give me some answers.
Yes, no.
To get to the other side.
1.77245...
I don't want to know
what the square root of pi is.
You knew that?
How did you know where I was?
I didn't.
All right.
- What?
Don't leave. I...
Did you follow me?
I...
I feel very protective of you.
So you followed me.
I was trying to keep a distance
unless you needed my help,
and then I heard what those low-lifes
were thinking.
Wait.
You say you heard what they were thinking?
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
So what, you...
You read minds?
I can read every mind in this room.
Apart from yours.
There's money, sex,
money,
sex,
cat.
(SIGHS)
And then you, nothing.
It's very frustrating.
Is there something wrong with me?
See, I tell you I can read minds,
and you think there's
something wrong with you.
(EXHALES)
What is it?
I don't have the strength
to stay away from you anymore.
Then don't.
Okay, I think I'm warm enough now.
(GASPS)
Your hand is so cold.
BELLA: Whoa!
What is going on?
My dad's still here.
Can you pull in?
EDWARD: That's my father's car on the end.
What is he doing here?
EDWARD: Carlisle, what's going on?
Waylon Forge was found in a boat
out near his place.
I just examined the body.
- He died?
How?
- Animal attack.
Was it the same one that
got that security guard down in Mason?
Most likely.
Well, it's getting closer to town, then.
- Bella, you should go inside.
Waylon was your father's friend.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
(MAN CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
Hey.
- Hey.
Dad, I'm really sorry.
I've known him going on 30 years.
Don't worry, we're gonna find this thing.
Meantime,
I want you to carry this with you.
I don't know if you...
- It'll give your old man some peace of mind.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Cold One.
(ECHOING BOOM)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
You're impossibly fast and strong.
Your skin is pale white and ice-cold.
Your eyes change color.
And sometimes you speak
like you're from a different time.
You never eat or drink anything.
You don't go out in the sunlight.
(BELLA GASPS QUIETLY)
How old are you?
Seventeen.
How long have you been 17?
A while.
I know what you are.
Say it.
Out loud.
Vampire.
Are you afraid?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
No.
Then ask me the most basic question.
What do we eat?
You won't hurt me.
Where are we going?
Up the mountain.
Out of the cloud bank.
You need to see what
I look like in the sunlight.
(BELLA PANTING)
This is why we don't show
ourselves in sunlight.
People would know we're different.
This is what I am.
(GASPING)
It's like diamonds.
You're beautiful.
Beautiful?
This is the skin of a killer, Bella.
I'm a killer.
I don't believe that.
That's because you believe the lie.
It's camouflage.
I'm the world's most dangerous predator.
Everything about me invites you in,
my voice, my face, even my smell.
As if I would need any of that.
(LOUD WHOOSH)
As if you could outrun me!
(WHOOSHING)
As if you could fight me off.
I'm designed to kill.
I don't care.
I've killed people before.
It does not matter.
I wanted to kill you.
I've never wanted a human's blood
so much in my life.
I trust you.
Don't.
I'm here. I trust you.
(WHOOSH)
My family,
we're different from others of our kind.
We only hunt animals.
We've learned to control our thirst.
But it's you, your scent,
it's like a drug to me.
You're like
my own personal brand of heroin.
(WHOOSH)
Why did you hate me
so much when we met?
I did.
Only for making me want you so badly.
I still don't know if I can control myself.
I know you can.
I can't read your mind.
You have to tell me what you're thinking.
Now I'm afraid.
Good.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm only afraid of losing you.
I feel like you're gonna disappear.
You don't know how long
I've waited for you.
So the lion fell in love with the lamb.
What a stupid lamb.
What a sick, masochistic lion.
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
BELLA: About three things
I was absolutely positive.
First,
Edward was a vampire.
Second,
there was a part of him,
and I didn't know
how dominant that part might be,
(HORN HONKS TWICE)
that thirsted for my blood.
And third,
I was unconditionally and irrevocably
in love with him.
JESSICA: Monte Carlo?
That's our prom theme?
Gambling, tuxedos, and Bond, James Bond.
(ENGINE PURRS)
Oh, my God.
(UP-TEMPO ROCK THEME PLAYING)
Wow.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know, everybody's staring.
Not that guy. No, he just looked.
I'm breaking all the rules now anyway.
Since I'm going to hell.
So, does a person have to be dying
to become like you?
No, that's just Carlisle.
He'd never do this to someone
who had another choice.
So, how long have you been like this?
Since 1918.
That's when Carlisle found me
dying of Spanish influenza.
BELLA: What was it like?
(YELLS)
EDWARD: The venom was excruciating.
But what Carlisle did was much harder.
Not many of us have the restraint to do that.
But didn't he just have to bite?
Not exactly.
When we taste
human blood, a sort of frenzy begins,
and it's almost impossible to stop.
BELLA: But Carlisle did.
EDWARD: First with me
and then with his wife, Esme.
So is Carlisle the real reason
that you don't kill people?
No, he's not the only reason.
I don't want to be a monster.
My family,
we think of ourselves as vegetarians, right,
'cause we only survive
on the blood of animals.
But it's...
It's like a human only living on tofu.
It keeps you strong,
but you're never fully satisfied.
It wouldn't be like drinking your blood,
for instance.
Was it other vampires that killed Waylon?
Yeah.
There are others out there,
and we run into them from time to time.
Can the rest of your family
read people's minds like you can?
No. That's just me.
But Alice can see the future.
I bet she saw me coming.
Alice's visions are subjective.
I mean, the future can always change.
(LOUD BANG)
Could you act human?
I mean, I've got neighbors.
I'm gonna take you to my place tomorrow.
Thanks.
Wait, like, with your family?
- Yeah.
What if they don't like me?
So, you're worried not because
you'll be in a house full of vampires,
but because you think
they won't approve of you?
I'm glad I amuse you.
What is it?
Complication.
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Hey. Come to visit your truck?
Looks good. Got that dent out.
Yeah.
- Actually, we came to visit your flat-screen.
First Mariners game of the season.
Plus Jacob here keeps bugging me about
seeing you again.
Great, Dad. Thanks.
Just keeping it real, son.
CHARLIE: Vitamin R.
Well done, Chief.
Harry Clearwater's homemade fish fry.
Good man.
Any luck with that Waylon case?
Well, I don't think it was an animal
that killed him.
Never thought it was.
So spread the word out at the rez, huh?
Keep the kids out of the woods.
Will do.
Don't want no one else getting hurt, do we?
(SLOW, EXOTIC THEME PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
Whoa.
This is incredible.
It's so light and open, you know?
What did you expect,
coffins and dungeons and moats?
(CHUCKLES) No, not the moats.
Not the moats.
This is the one place we don't have to hide.
(OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
I told them not to do this.
MAN ON TV: You add a little bit of olive oil
to a non-stick saut pan,
and you want to cook
with the olive oil in medium-high heat.
What I do, I cut this in strips,
and then we gonna cut this...
Is she even Italian?
- Her name is Bella.
I'm sure she'll love it, no matter what.
ROSALIE: (SIGHS) Get a whiff of that.
(SINGSONG) Here comes the human.
Bella, we're making Italiano for you.
Bella, this is Esme.
My mother for all intents and purposes.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
You've given us an excuse
to use the kitchen for the first time.
I hope you're hungry.
Yeah, absolutely.
- She already ate.
Perfect.
Yeah, it's just because
I know that you guys don't eat...
Of course. It's very considerate of you.
Just ignore Rosalie. I do.
- ROSALIE: Yeah.
Let's just keep pretending
like this isn't dangerous for all of us.
I would never tell anybody anything.
She knows that.
Yeah, well, the problem is,
you two have gone public now, so...
Emmett.
No, she should know.
The entire family
will be implicated if this ends badly.
Badly, as in...
I would become the meal.
(SNICKERING)
(LAUGHING)
Hi, Bella.
I'm Alice.
Hi.
- Hi.
You do smell good.
Alice, what are you...
It's okay.
Bella and I are gonna be great friends.
CARLISLE: Sorry,
Jasper's our newest vegetarian.
It's a little difficult for him.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's okay, Jasper. You won't hurt her.
All right, I'm gonna take you
on a tour of the rest of the house.
Okay.
- Well, I'll see you soon.
Cute!
- I know.
I think that went well.
Clean this up. Now.
Was that as weird for you as it was for me?
I don't know.
Graduation caps?
Yeah. It's a private joke.
We matriculate a lot.
That's kind of miserable.
I mean, repeating high school
over and over.
True, but the younger we start out
in a new place,
the longer we can stay there.
Come on.
Yeah, this is my room.
(BIRDS CHIRPING OUTSIDE)
No bed?
No, I don't...
I don't sleep.
Ever?
- No, not at all.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Okay.
Boy, you have so much music.
What are you listening to?
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
It's Debussy.
I don't know...
- Yeah.
Claire De Lune is great.
What?
- I can't dance.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Well, I could always make you.
I'm not scared of you.
Well, you really shouldn't have said that.
(BELLA GASPS)
You better hold on tight, spider monkey.
(BELLA GIGGLES)
Do you trust me?
In theory.
Then close your eyes.
What?
(CHUCKLES) This isn't real.
This kind of stuff just doesn't exist.
It does in my world.
(PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(SNIFFING)
MAN: Hold up.
It's human.
Arizona. Yo, what's happening?
So you and Cullen, huh?
That's... I don't like it.
I mean, I don't know,
he just looks at you
like you're something to eat.
Here's your veggie plate, Stephenie.
Hey, sorry I'm late. Biology project.
I ordered you the spinach salad.
I hope that's okay.
You should order one for yourself next time.
Cut back on the steak.
Hey, I'm as healthy as a horse.
Say, Chief, boys want to know,
did you find anything
down by Queets River today?
Yeah, we found a bare human footprint,
but it looks like whoever that is,
is headed east,
so Kitsap County sheriff is gonna take
over from here.
CORA: Okay.
- Okay?
I just hope they catch him fast.
Looks like your friends are flagging you.
It's okay if you wanna go join them.
I'm just gonna turn in early anyway.
Me, too.
Bella, it's Friday night. Go out.
Looks like the Newton boy's
got a big smile for you.
Yeah, he's a good buddy.
What about any of these
other yahoos in town?
Anybody interest you?
Dad, we gonna talk about boys?
Yeah, I guess not.
I just feel like I leave you alone too much.
You should be around people.
I don't really mind being alone.
I guess I'm kind of like my dad in that way.
So, how's all the baseball stuff going?
Phil's working so hard.
You know, spring training.
We're looking for a house to rent
in case things become more permanent.
You'd like Jacksonville, baby.
Yeah?
I'm really liking Forks.
What?
Forks is growing on me.
Could a guy have anything to do with that?
Well, yeah.
I knew it. Tell me everything.
What is he? Jock? Indie?
I bet he's smart. Is he smart?
Mom, can I talk to you later?
Come on, we gotta talk boys.
Are you being safe?
How did you get in here?
The window.
Do you do that a lot?
Well, just the past couple of months.
I like watching you sleep.
It's kind of fascinating to me.
I always want to try one thing.
Just stay very still.
Don't move.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(BOTH PANTING)
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
I'm stronger than I thought.
Yeah. I wish I could say the same.
I can't ever lose control with you.
Hey, don't go.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hey, got you another one.
- Thanks.
I have a date with Edward Cullen.
He's a little old for you, isn't he?
No.
He's a junior. I'm a junior.
I thought you liked the Cullens.
I thought you didn't like
any of the boys in town.
Edward doesn't live in town.
Technically.
He's right outside.
He is?
Yeah, he wanted to meet you, officially.
All right. Bring him in.
Could you be nice?
He's important.
Chief Swan.
I want to formally introduce myself.
I'm Edward Cullen.
Hi, Edward.
Bella won't be out too late tonight.
She's just gonna play baseball
with my family.
Baseball?
Yes, sir, that's the plan.
(CHUCKLES) Bella's gonna play baseball.
Well, good luck with that.
I'll take good care of her. I promise.
Hey.
Still got that pepper spray?
(WHISPERS) Yeah, Dad.
And since when do vampires like baseball?
Well, it's the American pastime,
and there's a thunderstorm coming.
It's the only time we can play.
You'll see why.
Hey.
Glad you're here. We need an umpire.
She thinks we cheat.
I know you cheat.
Call them as you see them, Bella.
- Okay.
(SUPERMASSIVE BLACK HOLE PLAYING)
It's time.
(THUNDER CRACKS)
Okay, now I see why you need the thunder.
That's gotta be a home run, right?
Edward's very fast.
(SINGING) Ooh, baby,
don't you know I suffer?
Ooh, baby, I'm a fool for you
Come home, Rosalie!
You're out.
- Out!
Babe, come on. It's just a game.
You set my soul alight
Nice kitty.
Ooh
You set my soul alight
What are you doing?
Super massive black hole
My monkey man.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Stop!
(OMINOUS ROCK THEME PLAYING)
They were leaving. Then they heard us.
Let's go.
- It's too late.
Get your hair down.
Like that'll help.
I can smell her from across the field.
I shouldn't have brought you here.
I'm so sorry.
What? What are you...
- Just be quiet and stand behind me.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I believe this belongs to you.
Thank you.
I am Laurent.
And this is Victoria
and James.
I'm Carlisle. This is my family.
Hello.
I'm afraid your hunting activities
have caused something of a mess for us.
Our apologies.
We didn't realize the territory
had been claimed.
Yes, well, we maintain
a permanent residence nearby.
Really?
Well, we won't be a problem anymore.
We were just passing through.
The humans were tracking us,
but we led them east.
You should be safe.
Excellent.
So,
could you use three more players?
Come on. Just one game.
Sure. Why not?
A few of us were leaving.
You could take their place.
We'll bat first.
I'm the one with the wicked curveball.
Well, I think we can handle that.
We shall see.
(OMINOUS THEME PLAYS)
(WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY)
(SNIFFING)
You brought a snack.
(SNARLING)
LAURENT: A human?
CARLISLE: The girl is with us.
I think it best if you leave.
I can see the game is over.
We'll go now.
James.
CARLISLE: Get Bella out of here.
Go.
Okay, I've got it! I've got it! I'm all right!
What, now he's coming after me?
Listen to me. James is a tracker.
The hunt is his obsession.
I read his mind.
My reaction on the field set him off.
I just made this his most exciting game ever.
He's never gonna stop.
- What should we do?
We have to kill him.
Rip him apart and burn the pieces.
Where we going?
- Away from Forks.
We'll get a ferry to Vancouver.
- I have to go home. Now.
You have to take me home.
- You can't go home.
He's just gonna trace your scent there.
It's the first place he's gonna look.
But my dad is there. We...
- It doesn't matter!
Yes, it does!
He could get killed because of us!
Just let me get you out of here first,
all right?
It's my dad! We have to go back!
We'll figure a way
to lead the tracker away somehow.
I don't know. But we have to do something.
(SPORTS PLAYING ON TV)
Edward, I said leave me alone.
- Bella, don't do this, please.
It's over! Get out!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Bella? What's going on?
I just gotta get out of here. I'm leaving now.
Hey.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
CHARLIE: Bella?
What am I gonna say to him?
I can't hurt him.
Bella, what's going on?
- You just have to.
I'll be down at the truck.
Did he hurt you?
No.
Break up with you or something?
No, I broke up with him.
I thought you liked him.
Yeah, that's why I have to leave.
I don't want this. I have to go home.
Home? Your...
CHARLIE: Your mom's not even in Phoenix.
BELLA: She'll come home.
I'll call her from the road.
You're not gonna drive home right now.
You can sleep on it.
If you still feel like going in the morning,
I'll take you to the airport.
- No. I want to drive.
It'll give me more time to think.
I mean, if I get really tired,
I'll pull into a motel. I promise.
Look, Bella, I know I'm not
that much fun to be around,
but I can change that.
We can do more stuff together.
Like what?
Like watch baseball on the flat-screen?
Eat at the diner every night?
Steak and cobbler?
Dad, that's you. That's not me.
Bella, come on, I just...
I just got you back.
Yeah, and, you know, if I don't get out now,
then I'm just gonna be stuck here like Mom.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Your father's gonna forgive you.
Why don't you let me drive?
He won't.
You should've seen his face.
I told him the same thing
that my mom told him
when she was leaving him.
It's the only way he'd let you go.
Just don't worry about him now.
He's safe. The tracker's following us.
(LOUD BANG)
(GASPS)
Oh, God.
- It's just Emmett.
Alice is in the car behind us.
(MELANCHOLY THEME PLAYING)
CARLISLE: Wait.
He came to warn us about James.
This isn't my fight,
and I've grown tired of his games,
but he's got unparalleled senses,
absolutely lethal.
I've never seen anything like him
in my 300 years.
And the woman, Victoria,
don't underestimate her.
I've had to fight our kind before.
They're not easy to kill.
- EMMETT: But not impossible.
We'll tear them apart and burn the pieces.
I don't relish the thought
of killing another creature,
even a sadistic one like James.
What if he kills one of us first?
- I'm gonna run Bella south.
Can you lead the tracker away from here?
No, Edward.
James knows you would never leave Bella.
He'll follow you.
- ALICE: I'll go with Bella.
Jasper and I will drive her south.
I'll keep her safe, Edward.
Can you keep your thoughts to yourself?
- Yes.
Rosalie, Esme,
could you put these on
so the tracker will pick up Bella's scent?
Why? What is she to me?
Rosalie, Bella is with Edward.
She's part of this family now,
and we protect our family.
Oh, God. If anything...
What if...
If anything happens, I swear to God...
Nothing's gonna happen.
There's seven of us,
and there's two of them,
and when everything's done,
I'm gonna come back and get you.
Yeah.
Bella, you are my life now.
(ENGINES STARTING)
Hey, Mom. It's me again.
You must have let your phone die
or something.
I'm not in Forks, but everything's okay,
and I'll explain it later.
EDWARD: Rosalie, mark the tree.
That's good.
(GROWLS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(GASPS)
What is it? What do you see?
(LOW RUMBLING)
(FIERCE GROWLING)
He's figured it out.
The tracker, he just changed course.
Where will it take him, Alice?
- Mirrors.
A room full of mirrors.
Edward said the visions
weren't always certain.
JASPER: She sees the course people
are on while they're on it.
If they change their minds,
the vision changes.
Okay, so the course that
the tracker's on now
is gonna lead him to a ballet studio?
You've been here?
- I took lessons as a kid.
The school I went to
had an arch just like that.
Was your school here in Phoenix?
Yeah.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Edward, are you okay?
- We've lost the tracker.
The woman's still in the area.
Rosalie and Esme are going back
to Forks to protect your father.
I'm coming to get you. Then you and I
are gonna go somewhere alone.
And the others will keep hunting.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you safe again.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hey, Mom, I'm glad you got my message.
What are you doing home?
Bella? Bella? Bella, where are you?
Calm down, everything's fine.
- Bella? Bella?
I'll explain everything later.
Mom, are you there?
JAMES: Forks High School doesn't protect
its students' privacy very well.
It was just too easy for Victoria
to find your previous address.
It's a nice house you have here.
I was prepared to wait for you,
but then Mom came home after she received
a very worried call from your dad,
and it all worked out quite well.
RENEE: Wait, wait...
Don't touch her! Don't...
You can still save her.
- BELLA: Don't!
But you're gonna have to get away
from your friends.
Can you handle that?
- Where should I meet you?
How about your old ballet studio?
And I'll know if you bring anyone along.
Poor Mommy would
pay the price for that mistake.
BELLA: I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
But dying in the place of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
I can't bring myself to regret the decisions
that brought me face-to-face with death.
They also brought me to Edward.
RENEE: Bella? Bella? Bella, where are you?
Mom?
- Bella?
- There you are.
RENEE: What are you doing in here?
YOUNG BELLA: Everyone makes fun of me.
Come on, you're a wonderful dancer.
Mom, I suck.
(JAMES LAUGHING)
You do not suck.
That's my favorite part.
You were a stubborn child, weren't you?
She's not even here.
- No.
JAMES: Sorry.
You know, but you really made it too easy.
So to make things more entertaining,
I'm gonna make a little film
of our time together.
I borrowed this from your house.
I hope you don't mind.
Good.
And
action.
That'll break Edward's little heart.
You have...
Edward has nothing to do with this!
But he does.
His rage will make for more interesting sport
than his feeble attempt to protect you.
And let's continue.
(GROWLS)
(WHOOSHING)
(BELLA YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Beautiful. Very visually dynamic.
I chose my stage well.
It's too bad he didn't have
the strength to turn you.
Instead, he kept you
this fragile little human.
It's cruel, really.
(SCREAMS)
Tell Edward how much it hurts.
Tell him to avenge you. Tell him!
No, Edward, don't!
- Tell him! Tell him!
(YELLING)
(PANTS)
(JAMES GROWLING)
You're alone
'cause you're faster than the others.
But not stronger.
I'm strong enough to kill you.
(YELLS)
I'm sorry.
(JAMES GRUNTS)
(BELLA SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(BELLA GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(BOTH GROWLING)
(YELLING)
(RAPID GASPING)
Bella, Bella, it's okay.
Son. Enough.
Remember who you are.
(BELLA YELLING)
ALICE: Bella, you're okay.
Bella needs you.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
Carlisle? Her blood.
Your brothers will take care of him.
- I got him.
ALICE: Carlisle!
- Start the fire.
EMMETT: Get the floorboards.
JASPER: Alice!
- Alice, go.
Her femoral artery's been severed.
She's losing too much blood.
No, no, my head is burning!
It's the venom.
You have to make a choice.
You could let the change happen.
No.
It's gonna happen, Edward. I've seen it.
- It doesn't have to be that way.
She's still hemorrhaging.
Alice, make me a tourniquet. Your belt.
Carlisle, what's my other option?
(GASPING)
Tie it above my hands.
Carlisle!
Go.
We could try to suck the venom out.
- You know I won't be able to stop.
Then find the will to stop.
But choose.
She only has minutes left.
I'm gonna make it go away, Bella.
(GASPING)
I'm gonna make it go away.
(PANTING)
(EDWARD GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
Edward, stop.
Her blood is clean. You're killing her.
Edward.
Stop.
(SOFTLY) Stop.
Find the will.
(BLUESY POP BALLAD PLAYING)
BELLA: Death is peaceful, easy.
Life is harder.
Bella?
Baby?
(WHISPERS) Bella.
Mom?
- Hey.
Where is he?
Where's...
Where's Edward?
He's asleep.
He never leaves.
And your dad, he's down at the cafeteria.
What happened?
Well, when you fell, you broke your leg,
and you lost a lot of blood.
You don't remember any of this, do you?
Edward came down with his dad
to try to convince you
to come back to Forks.
So you went over to their hotel,
then you tripped,
and you fell down two flights of stairs.
Went through a window.
Yeah, that sounds like me.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
It's Phil.
He's so worried about you.
You're texting.
(CHUCKLES) Finally, yeah.
I told him to stay down in Florida.
Honey, you are gonna love Jacksonville.
It's sunny every day,
and we found the cutest little house,
and you've got your own bathroom.
Mom, I still want to live in Forks.
What?
I want to live in Forks.
Well, okay, but we'll talk about it.
Do you mind getting Dad?
I have to talk to him. Apologize.
Okay, baby. I'll go get him.
And I'll go get a nurse, okay?
- Okay.
So what happened?
Where's James?
We took care of it.
And the woman, Victoria, she ran off.
I'm alive because of you.
No, you're in here because of me.
The worst part of it was that
I thought I wasn't gonna be able to stop.
You did stop.
Bella, you gotta go to Jacksonville
so I can't hurt you anymore.
What?
Are you... No!
No!
I don't even know what you're... How...
What are you talking about?
You want me to go away? I can't...
No, I can't... I can't just leave you...
I know.
We can't be apart.
You can't leave me.
I'm here.
Okay, just don't...
You just can't say stuff like that to me. Ever.
Where else am I gonna go?
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Alice lent me the dress.
The cast is...
You're perfect.
I'll take care of her, Chief Swan.
I've heard that before.
All right, Bells.
I put a new can of pepper spray in your bag.
Dad.
And...
Well, you look beautiful.
Thanks.
See you.
Hey. I'll be right back.
Bella.
- Jacob.
Hey.
Nice.
- You, too.
Are you crashing the prom or something?
Did you come with a date?
No.
My dad paid me to come talk to you.
(CHUCKLES) Twenty bucks.
Let's hear it.
JACOB: Just don't get mad, okay?
He wants you to break up
with your boyfriend.
It's just, he said, quote,
"We'll be watching you."
(LAUGHS)
Okay, well, tell him, "Thanks."
- Okay.
And to pay up.
- Okay. Let me help you.
Jacob.
I'll take it from here.
Guess I'll see you around, Bella.
All right.
I leave you alone for two minutes,
and the wolves descend.
I can't believe you're making me do this.
- Just smile.
Tonight! Lightning Strikes!
Don't go stay tonight!
Wow. You are really trying to kill me.
The prom is an important rite of passage.
I didn't want you to miss anything.
Oh.
(ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
Everyday we're going all the way
Everyday, everyday, everyday
we're going all the way
Tonight! Lightning Strikes!
Bella, hey!
Do you want to go?
- Yeah.
DJ: All right, slowing it down.
(APPLAUSE)
Shall we?
You're serious?
Why not.
(SINGING) Wide on my plastic toys
Then when the cops closed the fair
I cut my long baby hair
Stole me a dog-eared map
See, you're dancing.
At prom.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Jealous
Weeping
Edward, why did you save me?
If you just let the venom spread,
I could be like you by now.
You don't know what you're saying.
You don't want this.
- I want you.
Always.
I'm not gonna end your life for you.
I'm dying already.
Every second, I get closer.
Older.
That's the way it's supposed to be.
Alice said that she saw me like you.
I heard her.
- Her visions change.
Yeah, based on what people decide.
I've decided.
So that's what you dream about.
Becoming a monster.
I dream about being with you forever.
Forever?
And you're ready right now?
Yes.
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth
Big pill
Is it not enough
just to have a long and happy life with me?
Yeah.
For now.
BELLA: No one will surrender tonight,
but I won't give in.
I know what I want.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Grounded
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth
(SINGING) How come I end up where I started
How come I end up where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes off the ball again
You reel me out then you cut the string
How come I end up where I started
How come I end up where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes off the ball again
First you reel me out
and then you cut the string
You used to be all right
What happened?
Did the cat get your tongue
Did your string come undone
One by one
It comes to us all
It's as soft as your pillow
(SINGING) I dreamed I was missing
You were so scared
But no one would listen
'Cause no one else cared
After my dreaming
I woke with this fear
What am I leaving
When I'm done here?
So if you're asking me
I want you to know
When my time comes
Forget the wrong that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
When my time comes
Forget the wrong that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
(SINGING) How can I decide what's right
When you're clouding up my mind
I can't win your losing fight
All the time
How can I ever own what's mine
When you're always taking sides
But you won't take away my pride
No, not this time
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
But how did we get here?
I think I know
The truth is hiding in your eyes
And its hanging on your tongue
Just boiling in my blood
But you think that I can't see
What kind of man that you are
If you're a man at all
Well, I will figure this one out on my own
I'm screaming I love you so
My thoughts you can't decode
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
Yeah.
But how did we get here?
Well, I think I know how
Do you see what we've done
We're gonna make such fools of ourselves
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
Yeah, yeah, yeah
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
I think I know
There is something I see in you
It might kill me
I want it to be true