Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 23
You have to be more affectionate.
Speak clearly.
Look her in the eyes.
Okay.
General Mo has arrived.
She's here.
Didn't you say we were
competing in martial arts today?
We're doing it here?
Feng Yang.
Actually, Yun Xiu...
I'll give him a three-move advantage.
Come on.
Feng Yang.
Why are you being so cowardly?
Again.
One knee.
Feng Yang.
Will you take me as your husband?
You prepared so much to say,
why did you only say the last sentence?
I forgot everything once I saw Feng Yang.
Feng Yang.
Answer him.
This is just a proposal.
You don't have to announce it
and hold a wedding right away.
It's just a ritual to tell each other your feelings.
I
do.
♪I can hear the rain outside, where did it land♪
♪I still remember the brilliance of fireworks♪
♪We part way at dusk, leaving the pieces behind♪
To be proposed to
is what every girl fantasizes about.
I do owe Tan Er a proposal.
♪The ink dried, the crown cried♪
Love
indeed has strength.
Yun Xiu, Feng Yang.
May you
be together
forever.
♪The sand is carried away by the wind♪
♪How many years were blown away,
leaving us with grief♪
Be together
forever.
♪Memory couldn't be wiped and you kept half of it♪
Tan Er.
I'll always care for you,
love you,
and stay with you
until we're old and grey.
Cheng Cheng,
I am your love of two lifetimes.
You are my
love of three lifetimes.
♪How many years were blown away,
leaving us with grief♪
♪Memory couldn't be wiped and you kept half of it♪
♪The blossoms can't bring me out of seclusion♪
♪The petals scatter and piece
together what you love♪
♪One decision makes every difference♪
♪For you, who is willing to turn
the world upside down♪
Your Majesty.
You're going to grant Mo Feng Yang and
Yun Xiu's wishes just like that?
Aren't we letting them off too easily?
Yun Xiu
is of the Pugu clan,
which is quite prestigious in Xiyue.
Once the Mo family gains an ally like this,
they will become more arrogant.
If Mo Yuan Long makes a move,
then Xiyue
will be implicated for sure.
This move
can both lead the Mo family to become restless
and keep Xiyue in check.
How is Mo Lian Cheng doing?
Mo Lian Cheng
has recovered.
But I cannot figure out
why he has the ability to
rival the Soul-guarding Bead.
Before executing the grand scheme,
I need to know the answers to everything.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Princess's Residence
By the grace of heaven's will,
Her Majesty hereby proclaims...
Secondary Prince Consort Mo Lian Cheng
has continuously acted out of jealousy,
forced two main prince consorts out,
disregarded three cardinal guides
and five constant virtues,
and tainted the royal family's reputation.
He is ordered to the palace for morality training.
What?
Separating us again?
Yun Xiu and General Mo's feelings are mutual,
Mo Lian Cheng had nothing to do with that.
I'm merely in charge of announcing the decree.
Didn't Her Majesty agree?
Why is she making moves after the fact?
I humbly accept the decree.
I have something to say to Prince Consort.
I will wait quietly.
Cheng Cheng, what do we do?
I think
Her Majesty must be suspicious
of what happened at Altar of Souls.
Since Her Majesty already knows
that you can rival the Soul-guarding Bead,
it means she has found out
about your unusualness.
If your identity gets revealed,
then...
Don't worry,
I'll act accordingly.
I can use this opportunity
to investigate
the other requirements,
aside from the Soul-guarding Bead,
we need to meet in order to go back.
You must be careful,
especially of that Xiao Zhen.
Prince Consort,
it's time for you to leave.
Cheng Cheng.
I'm leaving.
When the heart doesn't think
about the good, evil enters into it
I've etched what I've learned today
into my memory.
The reason I am this strict with you
is that you're smart and clever,
different from the average man.
Compared to others,
I am not different.
I just put in more time and effort
into studying.
You know
that I've always thought highly of you.
I've been missing the times
you came to the palace
to recite poetry, paint,
and drink with me,
before you got married.
Do you know
why I like having you by my side?
Forgive me,
I do not.
Because you
remind me a lot of the old friend
I used to mention.
His eyes,
clear and deep.
His nose bridge,
tall and delicate.
Thin lips,
beautifully outlined,
just like
the gentle hills.
He always wore a set of white, cotton robes,
with a paper fan in his hand.
Poised,
he wandered towards me,
like the clouds floating above the mountains,
and
the flowing water during the night.
From Your Majesty's descriptions,
this gentleman
sounds extraordinary indeed.
He must be
from a family of scholars.
He is a doctor.
We met
while he was on his way to pick herbs.
Xuanling Continent
Miss. Miss.
The old friend Her Majesty speaks of
is extremely similar to Young Master Lian Cheng,
and she looks so much like Tan Er.
Could it be possible that she knows Qu Xiang Tan
or…?
I'm tired.
Leave me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
His handwriting is definitely not
as elegant as Young Master Lian Cheng's.
But he clearly thought of something just now.
Please, Your Majesty.
When the heart doesn't think about the good,
evil enters into it.
Very good.
No mistakes.
Since
you already know it so well...
Prince Consort will be sent back tomorrow.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
Official Chen has a report to make
and is waiting in Jingyi Pavillion.
You may go.
Zhang
Taiwei Wall
Tianshi Wall
Red Star of Demise.
Looks like the star image
is related to Her Majesty's conspiracy.
If so,
us going back not only requires
the Soul-guarding Bead,
we'd also have to wait for the appearance
of Red Star of Demise.
Princess's Residence
Tan,
you've walked around for the entire day
and haven't bought anything.
Let's go back to your chambers and rest.
No.
I can't stay in a room without Cheng Cheng,
not even for a second.
Tan.
What's this?
M, A, R, R
Why
can't I recognize any of it?
Y
I know this one.
"Ya"?
*"Y" looks like a character which pronounces "ya"
M, E
Mountain?
*"M" looks like the image of a mountain
Cheng Cheng.
Cheng Cheng, you're back!
Oh my gosh.
♪The night was spent in yearning♪
♪The flowers bloom in the morning♪♪
♪The reflection of beauty
makes yearning unyielding♪
♪Quiet rain on the lonely hill♪
Tan Er.
We have
already
gotten married three times,
but
I still owe you
an official proposal.
Even though we've known each other for so long,
but when I see you,
my heart still pounds in my chest,
I still feel
this overwhelming happiness,
and I still want to
marry you thousands of times over.
I do.
Thousands of times,
♪I've discarded my wariness♪
♪All I want is to quietly tell you of my affection♪
♪For you, I'm willing to let go of
all my glory and splendor♪
♪To wander the world with your hand in mine♪
♪From young and lively to old and grey,
just like the average couple♪
♪I couldn't bear to step on the fallen blossoms♪
♪Our reunion and parting will sink into the earth♪
♪Let's keep the memories of this lifetime♪
♪Your most beautiful moments
will forever remain in my heart♪
I wanted to make it up to you
with this proposal.
I don't want you to have any regrets.
As expected,
if one falls for the right person,
every day is Valentine's day.
Cheng Cheng,
I want to be with you forever.
I'm here.
Every hour, every minute.
It's always Valentine's day.
Tan Er.
Spending these few days in the palace,
I may have discovered
another requirement we need to meet
in order to go back to our original world.
Tell me.
The other day. I found an astronomy chart
of Red Star of Demise
in the royal study.
Perhaps
it has something to do with
Her Majesty's conspiracy.
Or
it has something to do with
us going back to our original world.
It looks like,
not only do we need the Soul-guarding Bead,
we also need to wait for
the Red Star of Demise.
Why didn't I think of it before?
I've lived all these lifetimes in vain.
We
need to calculate the exact date
of the Red Star of Demise.
If we miss this opportunity,
we may
never be able to return to our original world.
But
we only have
a fake Liu Qian Shui.
When you were in the palace,
did Her Majesty talk to you about the past?
No.
Every day,
I'd recite
the moral codes for men.
Look at you being all scared.
I know you're a good boy.
Should I tell Tan Er
that Her Majesty may be related to Qu Xiang Tan?
Never mind.
Before everything gets verified,
it's better not to let Tan Er misunderstand.
As expected, with my dear husband by my side,
I can sleep well.
After you recovered your memories,
you got taken away
before we got to spend time together.
We should really take a break.
Say,
should we go on a field trip?
Or
go horseback riding?
go shopping?
Didn't Tan Er say
that only children have to make choices,
adults
will do them all?
Prince Consort and Princess
are about to get up.
Why isn't
breakfast ready yet?
Wait,
why are only you three working?
They...
they're still sleeping.
Still sleeping?
Wake all of them up.
Go to the kitchens and prepare breakfast.
There is no food left in the kitchens.
The servants who are in charge of groceries
haven't gone grocery shopping in a while.
What? Seriously?
Do you have a death wish?
- Let's go take a look.
- It's not all their fault.
Aunty Zhang, the treasurer,
went back to her hometown,
so no one was there to give them money,
and of course, the shopping stopped.
How can this happen?
Princess.
Leave us.
Yes, Your Highness.
Yu Hao,
what is happening?
Before, Eldest Young Master
took care of all the housekeeping affairs.
After Young Master left,
the house was left unattended.
The servants
have become a little lazy.
When Eldest Brother was here,
it was him
who took care of all this.
What do we do now?
We can't just leave everything in a mess.
You are the head of the household,
so it should be you...
Don't look at me.
I can't do it.
Don't look at me either,
I don't...
I
don't know much about the house affairs,
so I don't think I can be in charge.
Your Highness.
I've finally found you.
Early this morning, Her Majesty sent all these
Memorial
and said that starting today,
Your Highness will start reviewing memorials
and assist Her Majesty in governmental affairs.
Memorial
Memorial?
It seems Her Majesty wants to
train you to govern the country.
As per traditions,
you're about to be made Crown Princess.
Her Majesty must have ulterior motives.
When it rains, it pours.
The affairs in our residence are a mess
and now I have to deal with this.
Looking at these
is like looking at all the college
entrance examination materials.
All my nightmares are coming back to me.
What are you laughing at?
Being happy about other people's misfortunes?
When did I laugh?
Back in the days,
wasn't I the one taking care of
all these trivial matters?
Reviewing memorials
is just a daily task, very easy.
You can take care of it easily,
but I was born dumb
and I have to worry about these trivial matters?
When did I say these are easy?
I just know how bothersome
dealing with governmental affairs is.
It's a lot of trouble, and definitely not easy.
But
seeing how smart you are,
you'll be able to get a hold of it soon enough.
That's better.
Now we can't go on a trip,
go horseback riding,
let alone go shopping.
Since
you have nothing to do,
how about you take care
of all the house affairs?
How can I?
Mo Yan Chen can take care of the affairs
and have everything running smoothly,
why can't you?
We are different people.
We have different strengths.
I can learn to deal with governmental affairs,
why can't you learn
to take care of house affairs?
When you were emperor,
you had a proper excuse not to.
Now that
you don't have to do anything,
how can you still avoid it?
I'm not doing it.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You just deal with governmental affairs,
I'll take care
of the household affairs.
That's better.
My chicken.
Young Master, are you alright?
Where is my chicken?
Where did my chicken go?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Young Master.
My bad, my bad.
Young Master, are you alright?
Young Master,
today, we have to buy
10 kilograms of radish,
25 kilograms of brown rice,
four kilograms of beef,
120 kilograms of green beans,
and...
Isn't this beef?
Slaughtered on site.
This is pork.
They're easy to differentiate.
Beef is redder in colour.
Then we'll buy pork.
I am from Yu County.
Just became
a Jinshi.
*The highest degree in the imperial examination
A spare
Xingren.
*A governmental official position
My first post
was out of the county.
I was then posted to
host the imperial examinations
in Pei Prefecture.
Having "Mercedes-Benz" for four years.
*It's "working away from home", she misunderstood
"Mercedes-Benz"?
Mercedes-Benz
Young Master,
these are the items
Ledger
we still have to buy today.
Eight more to go.
We need this many
daily necessities.
Let's keep going.
Young Master,
the money sachet is empty,
we don't have any more money.
Didn't I tell you to bring a fair amount?
How did it run out so quickly?
Young Master, I did bring enough.
I brought enough money.
But you
didn't ask for the price,
you didn't haggle either,
and you let them keep the change,
and then, that was all.
Who knew there was
so much to know about buying things?
"Working away from home for four years".
Hey.
Wake up.
I did my homework,
I really forgot to bring it this time.
You scared me.
It's you?
I had a dream about my high school math teacher.
Scared me to death.
How was it going today?
Just reviewing memorials,
easy.
I've done the majority.
"Having 'Mercedes-Benz' for four years
is not proper.
The luxurious lifestyle
of households
should not be encouraged."
What is all that?
Give it back.
I heard that you
went grocery shopping yourself.
How did it feel running the house
for the first time?
It's no big deal.
Of course it went well.
Then what is this?
I think
it was a mess,
a huge mess, wasn't it?
You...
We're not done talking about the memorial.
If you submit
these memorials to Her Majesty,
things will go wrong.
You're looking down on me.
Then you do it.
How can I...
We can give it a try.
But you have to help me
with the house affairs.
How can you negotiate with me?
Fine, house affairs.
But
there are more women than men in this residence.
If all guards have to
deal with housekeeping affairs...
Since our work has been reversed,
then according
to the superiority principles,
every man and woman in the residence
must have their work reversed.
Regarding household affairs,
you need not discuss them with me,
you can make the decisions by yourself.
Okay.
It's settled, then.
Starting today,
the Princess's Residence is about to
push a major reform.
Could it be
a residence-wide salary raise?
Some people must be getting dismissed.
Quiet.
I haven't announced anything yet,
why do you have so much to say?
You talk too much.
Starting today,
all the men and women in the residence
will have their work reversed.
The women who were in charge of keeping guard
will now
do laundry,
cook,
sew,
clean, and etc.
The men who were originally
in charge of the work mentioned
will now be
guards,
drivers, etc.,
taking over for the women.
This...
Wouldn't it be a huge mess?
We've
never worked in the kitchens before.
Exactly.
And if other people find out,
it will be so embarrassing.
Right.
Those who do not do as they're told
will lose a month's salary.
You'll be dismissed.
Make way.
So weak.
Don't add so much water.
Add more flour.
Do I look cool?
Yes.
That's enough.
I've been a guard for so many years.
I can definitely
conquer
this little dough ball.
Tan.
What happened to you?
Kneading dough made you resentful?
It's not me,
it's the female guards.
They really can't
work in the kitchens.
But I heard someone was quite into it.
Anyway,
different people have different ambitions.
I think
it's better if you let the female guards
play with swords and sabers.
And those male servants,
they keep hurting themselves
practicing swordsmanship every day.
They're a real mess.
Alright.
I got it.
Leave work for today.
Okay.
It looks like
making all the men and women switch
doesn't work.
To achieve gender equality,
one-size fits all
isn't realistic.
What should we do?
You finished this much
in one day?
This is only half.
He's in his element,
going back to what he did before.
Good work
today,
work harder tomorrow.
By the way,
how is
your reform going?
Quite effective,
of course.
Everything is in perfect order.
Princess.
Do you have a minute?
The backyard...
Wait.
Princess, do you have a minute?
Out.
So, no.
This is the "in perfect order"
you were talking about?
Weren't you in the study the entire day?
Why did you come here?
I need to understand your work.
This way, I can help you.
You're just here to laugh at me.
Letting men and women switch their job
is indeed
a groundbreaking initiative,
but we ignored
one issue.
What issue?
Is the division of labour
really based on gender?
No fundamental difference is made
just by having the men and women switch.
A meaningful reform
should be appointing people
on their merit, not gender.
This is the true meaning
of gender equality.
Her Majesty is asking Qu Tan Er to review memorials
and assist her in governmental affairs.
What from I've heard,
she's just reviewing memorials.
I don't think that Her Majesty gave her actual power.
Your Highness is
the Commander of the Capital Guards.
You needn't be scared of Qu Tan Er.
It's difficult to fathom Her Majesty's thoughts.
Her Majesty has never shown
who she favours out of the both of us.
You are Eldest Princess,
and with Princess Consort and
the Mo family as your ally,
of course you have the upper hand.
Before Crown Princess is announced,
we must not show any weakness.
If Your Highness is willing to listen,
I have a plan.
Speak.
Princess's Residence
Starting today, each person
needs to submit a report on
their skills, hobbies, and things they're good at.
After a comprehensive assessment,
you will be reassigned.
You get to take half the credit
for the residence being so orderly today.
Sure enough, someone who has been the emperor
thinks about things
critically and efficiently.
It's you
who thought of the starting point,
so the credit
is all yours.
Then,
should I help you
with the governmental affairs after I get back?
You don't have to wait till you go back,
the rest of the memorials
are all yours.
I'm talking about the kind
that involves being in a high position,
looking down on all the officials,
and commenting on state affairs.
You
don't want to help me with work at all,
you just want my power and prestige.
Now I am Princess,
do I need to take away your power and prestige?
Since
it's not proper to participate in politics,
you're allowed
to take care of our child then.
Allowed?
Didn't you tell me
that it's what I should do
as a father?
Why do you have all these ready?
Just tell me,
will you take care of him or not?
This...
Of course I will.
But
one isn't enough.
Who gave you the nerve
to write down such treacherous things?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪