Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 24
How dare you!
How dare you disrespect me with such words!
Her Majesty's Grace
My loyalty to Your Majesty and Dongyue
will never waver.
I would never write anything
to humiliate Your Majesty.
You still refuse to admit your crime.
Official Chen.
Yes.
Read it for her.
She should know what she has written.
Yes.
The people must follow and they
must stay ignorant.
The nation should be clouded by folly.
There should only be a handful
who are knowledgeable.
There is no way
Cheng Cheng would write such a thing.
Based on Her Highness's opinion,
the people must follow
whatever path the government set for them,
yet they should not know the reason.
Her Highness even hopes that
the nation is full of fools
and the scholars should dwindle in number.
Better virtues, finances, and
knowledge for the people.
Such is the motto
Her Majesty rules Dongyue with.
Her Highness
disobeyed the imperial order
and encouraged policies
that would instill folly.
That's not true.
There shouldn't be any errors or issues
with the files I marked.
Should Her Majesty ask,
follow the text and interpret it
the simplest way.
Such words
did come from me.
But Official Chen took it wrongly.
May I have the permission
to use the brush?
Official Chen.
The black dots
are where the sentences pause.
Please
read it again.
Should the people be able,
we should allow them freedom.
Should the people not be able,
we should show them guidance.
May this nation be cleansed of foolishness,
may scholars and erudite fill every household.
What I meant was,
if the people
have wisdom and knowledge,
so we should allow them freedom.
For those without such qualities,
we should guide them.
I hope that Dongyue
is a country free of foolishness.
May scholars and erudite
be a common sight.
So
this is what Her Highness meant.
The dots make things much more straightforward.
The dots I used
are called punctuation.
There are many forms
and functions.
Today,
I simply showed one of them.
When you write,
you should be cautious with wording.
Ambiguity should be avoided.
Not all people who read
are smart to interpret the meaning
as you just did.
Your Majesty is right.
Normal articles
do not have any marking to indicate the pauses.
Should the military files have any ambiguity,
the consequences can be severe.
Your Highness should employ cautions
while writing.
Yes.
I will keep Your Majesty's lesson in mind.
Your Majesty.
I am quite interested
in those markings Her Highness showed us.
If
some symbols are capable of
pointing out the correct structures
of sentences,
it would
help to prevent misinterpretations.
Its risk will be greatly reduced.
May I suggest
for Her Highness
to implement this marking system
for our civil officials?
I object.
These markings make the pages look congested.
Furthermore,
the problem with ambiguity
can be avoided by using better wording.
Ambiguity
is usually noticeable only by the readers.
The person who writes
might never notice it.
These markings are simple and clear.
Official Chen,
you should learn to accept
new things in life.
Official Sun's suggestion
seems viable.
Starting tomorrow,
Princess Tan Er
will teach all the civil officials
the usage of these symbols.
We shall observe its effectiveness
in the palace.
Whether it should be used widely in the nation,
the result of this trial will decide it.
Yes.
I accept the order.
I always write with vigilance.
This line
was clearly added by someone
who copied my handwriting.
The memorials
will be sent
to Her Majesty every morning
by someone
working for the palace.
Someone must have intercepted it.
Such scheme...
There is no doubt about it.
This must be the doing of Qu Mei Er.
Just ignore her.
You should be ready for tomorrow's work.
Jingyi Pavilion
Punctuation
is used
in writing
to indicate sentence structures
and intonations.
Normally, when we read,
we interpret the sentences
with our feelings and particles.
By that, I mean,
using "Zhi Hu Zhe Ye"
*Four grammatical particles of Classical Chinese
to break the sentences.
But doing so
often causes ambiguity.
That will lead to misinterpretation
of an article.
The exclamation mark
is often used
to indicate strong feelings.
For example,
"They are cutting my pay for the
next year as punishment!"
The sentence...
must end with
the exclamation mark.
The question mark,
as its name implies,
is used at the end of a question.
For example,
"What?"
"Why are you cutting my pay for the
next year as punishment?"
The sentence must end
with a question mark.
The ellipsis
is sometimes used to impliy
there are many examples.
Sometimes,
it's used to indicate continuous
pausing of a sentence
or to express frustrations.
For example,
"Come on..."
"They cut my pay for a whole year again..."
At the end
of these two sentences,
we must use
the ellipsis.
Is that clear now?
Well said.
Your work was too sloppy.
You ended up benefiting Qu Tan Er.
She only invented the shift work
and punctuation systems.
Official Sun used this achievement
to recommend Qu Tan Er as the heir apparent.
It was my mistake.
But there are rumors in the palace about
Her Majesty's health deteriorating.
The air
in the court is stifled with unease.
Her Majesty has been on the throne
for over a decade.
She has no spouse
or heir apparent.
However,
Her Majesty's intention isn't clear yet.
Your Highness still has a 50-50 chance of winning.
Official Chen.
You and your colleagues
are always cautious and discreet.
I'm glad to see that.
But desperate times
call for actual actions.
If Qu Tan Er became the next Crown Princess,
you would be the first to face her wrath.
Yes.
I have no intention to be the heir apparent.
I don't have any ambition.
I just want to enjoy love.
I just want to be with you every day of my life.
Of course you have your ambition.
Your achievements since you became a princess
had already outmatched mine of the same time.
I can only fool around.
If I was to be given real responsibility,
there would be no way
I could ever handle it.
Not only that.
Having more power
also means
you have more resources
to protect those you love.
Not to mention
the secret of the Soul-guarding Bead,
Soul-parting Flute,
and the Red Star of Demise
are still in the empress's hands.
We cannot give up on any opportunity
to get a step closer to them.
But
Her Majesty never made any stance.
Only my fan Official Sun
is rooting for me.
Don't forget.
I am your fan too.
Spare me your fancy words.
However,
Her Majesty was seriously ill
and used your blood
to unlock the Soul-guarding Bead's power
as a means to treat her condition.
If she falls sick again,
the disaster at the Altar of Souls
might repeat itself.
In that case,
it's likely she will appoint a crown princess.
And the perfect candidate
will be you.
But...
if we want to return to the original Dongyue,
we must get close to her.
When we get too close to her,
our lives will be in danger.
What do we do now?
This matter
is beyond our capability to change anything.
However,
whatever may come to pass,
I will keep you safe.
But...
if I became Crown Princess of Dongyue,
I would have to work overtime every day.
I wouldn't have time to spend with you.
If it's a love life you want,
you can have it now.
Right.
Go to a place with me.
Where to?
You'll know when you're there.
I will play the song.
As for the flirting,
you're the expert.
I love you.
Is there any song
that is more mesmerizing, mystical,
and entrancing?
I do know a song.
It's been a while since I last played it.
It's been so long
since we had a quiet date
without any distractions.
Then make the world
even quieter.
Pretend there are
only the two of us in this world.
What did you say?
Mo Lian Cheng knows how to play
Love's Reflection.
This is an exclusive song in the
Xuanling Continent.
It was also...
the same song he once played for me.
Where is the Soul-parting Flute?
Play it for me.
I shall address you
as Young Master Mo as I did in the past.
What do you think?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Judging by Your Majesty's words,
this man
must be extraordinary.
He must be
from a family of erudite.
He was a healer.
It is him.
It must be him.
Mo Lian Cheng...
He really is my dear Young Master Lian Cheng!
He may not recognize me,
but I am always her Xiang Tan!
Do you really not remember me?
Your Majesty.
I can only wish
to share this pain with you.
With my health going downhill,
my power and duty are only a burden to me.
Official Sun was right.
It is time for Qu Tan Er
to succeed me.
Your Majesty's rule is in its zenith.
The people of Dongyue
still need you.
All I want...
before this body perishes...
is to reunite with Lian Cheng as who I was.
Your Majesty.
I understand
your endless longing
for Master Lian Cheng.
But Mo Lian Cheng might now...
Insolence!
Are you calling me a fool?
I wouldn't dare.
I trust my feelings.
It must be him.
Qu Tan Er's investiture is tomorrow.
I lost.
Do you regret
marrying me?
There is no victor in this matter.
You gave me the only vacancy in your heart.
I will always be grateful for that.
Yan Chen.
We still have a chance.
I will send some assassins.
Before the investiture,
there is still a chance to change our fate.
You must not do so.
You couldn't watch her die.
Your Highness will surely be suspected.
Doing so
will ruin your future.
Mei Er.
Are you sure...
Her Majesty
is handing over the throne?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
As decreed by Her Majesty,
Second Princess Qu Tan Er
has displayed outstanding character
and wisdom.
Hence,
the will of Heaven must be followed
and the people must be convinced.
She will be the next Crown Princess
and granted the East Palace.
The end.
It's been yet another long day.
I'm so tired.
If you're tired,
let me help you get changed.
You should rest early.
The East Palace,
the title of Crown Princess,
I...
I couldn't even dream
that I would have these to my name.
I think
you are enjoying it.
You aren't a crown prince.
Yes.
I...
should help Crown Princess get changed
so she could rest early.
But the bed here
isn't as soft and big
as those from the Snow Court.
This is bad.
The yard
is not pleasant either.
It's so empty.
The Snow Court looked so much better.
This is bad.
Even the incense isn't as good
as those in the Snow Court.
This place doesn't feel like a home.
Everything is bad!
This place isn't
a top-of-the-line mansion.
The houses I sold in the past were much better.
This may be private property,
but its value is stale
and it doesn't provide the best experience.
But you still have me here.
Are you saying
I was better when I was in the Snow Court?
Is everything about me bad too?
Of course not.
You are the only thing
that is good in here.
So
you should stop getting upset.
As long as we are together,
any place can be our home.
I will always be with you.
Don't bring that up now!
It gets on my nerve.
Tomorrow,
I must start learning how to mark
the memorials in the royal study.
You will be teaching
the consorts of harem how to play the zither.
Think,
think about it.
They are separating us by force.
Had I known sooner,
I wouldn't come here.
Now that we are in the palace,
there must be a reason for it.
Besides,
the sooner we find out what she wants,
the sooner we can be ready.
It might be a blessing for us
to move into the palace.
It might be a great chance.
You call this a blessing?
Why did we even come here?
To return to our universe
and reunite with Yu Er.
Yes.
The Altar of Souls and Soul-guarding Bead
are both inside the palace.
Therefore,
our ticket home is also in the palace.
You have a point.
In that case,
we will make the best
of this blessing in disguise.
So...
You should go to bed now.
You don't want to get
sleepy while working tomorrow.
Aren't you going to sleep?
There are some matters to tend to.
I want to sneak out at night.
No, you don't want to!
This is our first day here.
How could you leave me here all by myself?
Don't forget.
What is the other thing
that we need in order to go home?
The Red Star of Demise?
Liu Bai Shui
once mentioned
that he is an expert in astrology.
But he is also a fraud.
Even if he was,
he must have come
into our life
for some reason.
It wouldn't hurt to ask him.
I will go with you then.
No.
You are now
inside the palace.
I can go on my own.
But if I had to take you with me,
it would be
more than challenging.
Fine.
Make sure you come back early then.
If I don't see you
when I wake up tomorrow,
I will be very upset.
Don't worry.
Make sure you come back early.
Why are you sighing, Senior?
You're the Prince Consort!
Have you come
at this hour
to acquire my help?
You once told us
you are a master of astrology.
Of course.
I may be good for nothing,
but when it comes to astrology,
I'm the right guy for you.
Let me put it this way.
I've loved astrology since I was a kid.
I observe the sky whether it's day or night.
After decades of squinting,
my eyes became smaller.
But my knowledge and skills
have become impeccable.
My prediction is more accurate
than what the Bureau of Celestial
Forecast has to show.
Just now,
you were observing the stars.
But why were you sighing?
The stars
show a bad omen.
What is it?
The Red Star of Demise
might show itself again.
When will it show up?
Where?
Prince Consort,
why you so excited?
I apologize.
This omen is important to me.
It concerns
my chances of reuniting with my family
and my odds of
making the world normal again.
Senior, I need you
to calculate
the time and location of the Red Star
of Demise's appearance.
Don't be so formal with me.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Mother! Mother!
My mother!
Did you hear that?
Someone believes me!
I finally have someone who believes me!
So
you agreed to help me.
Yes, certainly.
There is a saying,
"A true man can die for those
who know the worth of him."
Don't worry, I will do my best to help you.
Wait here, please.
Wait here.
Yes, it's in here!
All right.
Come here!
Prince Consort, over here.
Sorry.
Prince Consort.
I, Liu Bai Shui,
have many talents.
I thought my talents
would never see the light of days,
just like this thing.
But today,
someone finally has use of me.
Stars in the night sky,
thank you!
Based on
the orbits of Saturn and Mars,
the Red Star of Demise
will come to pass soon enough.
But I can't be too sure
about the timing.
It might be anywhere between
two weeks to two months.
What about the location?
Prince Consort, come with me.
Come.
Mars
invades the constellation.
The closest location to see it
would be
north of the imperial palace.
The palace?
Yes.
I can't be very precise,
but I am certain about the general direction.
What's wrong?
A star has fallen from the Dipper.
The Dipper indicates troubles in marriage
and challenges in undertakings.
But with a falling meteor,
I'm afraid
someone's life is in grave danger.
Are you still awake?
I can't fall asleep without you.
Holding your clothing didn't work.
I felt so worried and scared.
What's wrong?
Did Liu Bai Shui tell you something?
Did something bad happen?
I feel so anxious.
You...
should stop being so paranoid.
I have good news for you.
About two weeks from now,
we might...
be reunited with our son.
Really?
Are you sure you weren't fooled
by that old fraud's tricks?
No.
He really is an expert in astrology.
Before I went over there,
he had already foreseen
that the Red Star of Demise
is going to appear.
What should we do next?
Two weeks...
Two weeks from now,
we can see Yu Er again!
You sound overjoyed
when you say your son's name.
Of course.
He holds the top spot in my heart,
right above you.
Tell me.
What do we need to do now?
Calm down.
We must not alert the enemy.
We need to get our hands on
the Soul-guarding Bead
and the Soul-parting Flute
as a precaution.
One more thing.
Be wary of Her Majesty.
I have a feeling
this is too good to be a coincidence.
She has the Soul-guarding Bead,
but she also looks exactly like you.
I think...
she might be...
What about her?
It's nothing.
Go to sleep.
You need to save up your strength.
Then we can
improvise in time.
I'll do nothing
but hoping
to see our son sooner.
I miss him so much.
Prince Consort, this way, please.
I, Mo Lian Cheng,
has been ordered by Her Majesty
to give a music lesson.
Before I start,
I first need to know
your proficiency with the instrument,
so...
I know this melody.
It sounds like Love's Reflection.
The only person
who knows this song besides Tan Er
is none other than her.
It was just a few notes.
Is this a coincidence?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪