Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name is etched into my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 28
Every person...
has only one heart.
I've let you down in the end.
Tan!
You're finally back.
Did Her Majesty mistreat you?
You must be starving.
I'll get you some supper.
Never mind.
I'm exhausted.
Dismiss.
I don't need the supper either.
Tan Er!
Liu Bai Shui told me
your life could be in danger.
I'm glad you're safe.
What did he say?
Nothing in particular.
I'm glad you are all right.
Was it
Xiao Zhen who sent you back?
Tan Er.
I failed to keep you safe.
I'm sorry that you had to go through this.
Cheng Cheng.
What happened to your hand?
It's nothing.
It was an accident.
Tan Er's kiss
might be different from mine.
What is it?
Nothing.
I was mesmerized by your charm.
I've been observing.
There wouldn't be any mistake.
Are you not feeling well?
I spent days in prison.
I was in constant fear.
I need time to calm my nerves.
Feel my hand.
It's icy cold.
Is this warm enough for you?
I can barely remember
the last time I smiled with such joy.
Lian Cheng, you gave me everything.
I don't want to lose it again.
Promise me.
No matter what happens,
don't leave me.
Silly.
I promise.
Pinky swear.
This must be Qu Tan Er's childish trick.
Forever and always.
Princess's Residence
Cheng Cheng, save me!
Cheng Cheng, save me
Jing Xin!
Get rid of the mirrors!
I don't want to see any of them here!
Get it done!
What's wrong?
Why would you want the mirrors removed?
I was in prison for so long.
The moment I saw my reflection,
I realized how much I've aged.
I'll get rid of them for you.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Your Highness.
Your Highness has been summoned to the palace.
Understood.
As decreed by Her Majesty,
the ruler of the Xihe regime,
this announcement shall be made public.
Her Majesty humbly succeeded
the ancestors' legacy.
Continuous exhaustion from the state affairs
had taken a toll on Her Majesty.
Her Majesty's health was deteriorating.
However,
the nation and its people
need a ruler to lead them.
Crown Princess Qu Tan Er
is virtuous and wise.
Her Highness
will unit the people of this country.
Crown Princess will succeed the throne
as the next Empress.
The funeral shall be minimalist.
Her Majesty shall be mourned for five days.
This shall be the announcement
for all people.
I am aware
that I'm not as wise as Her Majesty.
I shall devote myself to the duties
and live up to Her Majesty's expectation.
Official Sun.
When did Her Majesty pass away?
This morning during the period
from five to seven.
Who was with Her Majesty
at that time?
Official Xiao,
Imperial Physician Li,
and several servants.
Where is Official Xiao?
The loss broke his heart and mind.
He chose to join Her Majesty in the afterlife.
Eldest Sister,
you wish to know other information, don't you?
Her Majesty's passing was too sudden.
And with only a handful of people
looking after her,
things don't add up.
Shouldn't we find out what really happened?
Her Majesty only passed away hours ago.
Yet I do not see a tint of sadness
on your expression.
But you raise one question after another.
How disrespectful!
I was merely concerned about
Her Majesty's passing.
You should be worried about yourself.
Unless you want me to rake over the ashes,
I suggest you get out now.
Princess's Residence
Cheng Cheng.
I'm going to have the throne soon.
You will soon become
the top of the harem.
I was told you behave like Her Majesty
in the main hall.
How was my acting?
Had I not done so,
Qu Mei Er would never stop bothering me.
Her Majesty passed away,
but you don't seem surprised at all.
When we visited her,
she was already ill.
We knew she was dying.
I feel sorry for her,
but I'm not surprised.
What about the five days of mourning?
Her Majesty ordered you
to mourn only for five days,
why would she
be in such a hurry to let you take over?
Perhaps Her Majesty knew
the court was in disorder
and there were other factions
brewing their plans.
You answered everything with ease.
You don't act like the silly Tan Er I knew.
I'm not silly.
If Her Majesty didn't teach me all these,
I wouldn't know at all.
Do you
still remember our promise?
If you become Empress...
I remember.
For every right that women have,
every man shall have it too.
After the reformation,
we can finally go home
when the Red Star of Demise arrives
and reunite with Yu Er.
It's been so long.
I wonder if he has grown up.
Did he just say the two of them
were going back to a different world?
Could that Yu Er be their son?
Yes.
It's been too long since I last saw him.
I miss him a lot.
That kid is nothing but a worthless child.
How is it worth it to return just for him?
I will figure something out
to make you stay in this place willingly
and start a new life with me.
She asked Jing Xin
to remove all the mirrors?
Yes.
Her Highness's condition
is getting restless.
Not only is she wary of Jing Xin,
but she also thinks someone is watching her.
Don't you think she seems
like an entirely different person sometimes?
I don't understand.
Tan Er's condition
is far worse
than the trauma from her imprisonment.
I'm afraid
there are other causes.
What do you plan to do?
To find the answers.
Stop right there!
Get out of our way.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Do you admit your crime?
I don't understand.
Was Crown Princess
released back to the Snow Court directly?
Prince Consort, please have mercy on us!
It was Official Xiao who took her.
Official Xiao?
Where did he take her?
Official Xiao told me nothing.
Do you understand your crime
will warrant a death sentence
to your entire clan
when she ascends to the throne?
All I know was
that they went to the imperial chamber.
As for the rest,
I know nothing.
Please have mercy on us!
I knew it.
They were meeting Her Majesty.
Inside the imperial chamber,
there is only one place that is suspicious.
Her Highness is about to move here.
I have been ordered to inspect the house.
Open the door.
Prince Consort.
By the law,
there must be no inspection
before the coronation.
Do you mean
that Her Highness's order
wasn't good enough as a royal decree?
Is that why you are disobeying her?
I meant no disrespect.
I'll ask this one last time.
Stand aside!
Even if Her Highness was brought here,
the traces
would have already been wiped clean.
Young Master...
This is the remnant
of the burned Glacial Soulweed.
Glacial Soulweed?
It grows in the Xuanling Continent.
It's rare anywhere else.
It has unique properties.
Well...
The most unique effect it has
is enabling the host of Soul-guarding Bead
to take over another person's body.
But the price
is human sacrifice.
Put out the candles.
Young Master.
These shimmering specks of dust
are the disintegrated flesh
of the human sacrifice used in the ritual.
I finally understand why
Xiao Zhen
passed away with Her Majesty.
Young Master.
Someone is coming.
Let's head back.
Princess's Residence
Young Master.
Our investigation last night
didn't bear any result.
Tonight, should we go...
No.
Our frequent visits to that place
will draw her suspicion.
Remember.
We must not alert her.
There is something I don't understand.
Where would the original soul go
after another soul
has taken over the body?
The original soul?
I merely
fell from the wall
by accident.
I'm fine.
Tan Er's consciousness
is still inside the same body.
However,
Her Majesty is suppressing her.
She can only take control
indirectly at times.
I understand now
why she asked Jing Xin
to remove all the mirrors.
This must be the real reason.
We have half an hour
to redecorate the living room.
Don't let anyone notice it.
Yes.
This is how it goes.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Admit it.
You're not the real Tan Er.
Indeed.
I am Qu Xiang Tan.
Qu Tan Er's body
has always been mine to use.
Your voice...
Yes. You can tell by it.
This meddlesome girl's consciousness
will soon fade into oblivion.
Cheng Cheng! Save me! Cheng Cheng!
Tan Er!
Can you hear me?
I'm right here.
Come out!
Stop yelling!
Her mind is weaker than mine.
Even with these mirrors,
she won't last for long.
Cheng Cheng! Cheng Cheng! Save me!
Cheng Cheng!
Tan Er!
You hear me, right?
Tan Er, is that you?
It's me.
Is that you, Tan Er?
Cheng Cheng!
Stop it!
No.
You can't afford to kill her.
You still need this body.
Indeed.
But I couldn't care if this body
is covered in wounds.
What about you?
I hope you always keep this in mind.
Two souls
share this body at the moment.
Behave and do as I say...
if you don't want her to suffer.
Do you really think
using her life as leverage
can make me bow to your will?
Listen closely.
You might as well end her life.
I will join her in the afterlife.
I will be with her in heaven or hell.
Play along with this act.
Outsiders
shouldn't know my true identity.
Otherwise...
the consequences will be severe.
Tan Er.
Princess's Residence
Since the date is fixed,
Official Sun will be in charge
of the preparation for my coronation.
Yes, Your Highness.
Unfortunately,
I have a relapse from a previous disease.
I'm afraid I couldn't make it to attend the ceremony.
It doesn't matter.
I will
have the proper arrangement for you.
Even if you're bedridden,
I will have the guards carry you there.
You...
Now that you are part of the court,
not only do you refuse to kneel
before Crown Princess,
you even disrespected me with your ill manner.
Do you wish
to be buried in a casket
before my coronation?
You even dare to take my life?
Of course I wouldn't.
I'm not you.
I'm not foolish enough to attempt
an assassination before my coronation.
Even if I was,
I wouldn't leave any traces
as some simpleton once did.
However,
I can't say the same for these people.
They only respect you, Eldest Sister,
and have no respect for me.
They are also corrupted to the core
by taking from the people.
I think...
it's time for them to meet their demise.
Guards.
Execute all of them.
Your Highness, have mercy on us!
Qu Tan Er!
Are you going to disobey my order
over some sinful officers?
Do not give me more reasons
to take your life.
Eldest Sister.
What more do you have to say?
I was out of line a moment ago.
I humbly ask for Your Highness's forgiveness.
On the Prayer Ritual to Heaven,
I will
send my blessing to the new Empress.
In that case,
everyone may leave
and start preparing now.
Yes.
Stay, Eldest Sister.
There is something
only you can settle.
Your Highness,
how may I be of service?
I need you to eliminate the rebel leader,
Mo Yuan Long.
You two were conspiring against the throne.
I found out about it a long time ago.
As for Mo Yuan Long's plans
and evidence of his crime,
I need you
to hand them over.
Dismiss.
Eliminating Mo Yuan Long?
Why would Tan do such a cruel thing to the Mo family?
Judging by her tone just now...
No.
Tan has been acting strange lately.
I must tell Prince Consort.
Prince Consort.
I have
something to report.
I was passing by the study.
I overheard a conversation
that the Mo family might...
Perhaps
I got it wrong.
You heard it right.
What will happen to the Mo family?
Tell me.
How can you be sure I didn't hear it wrong?
Did you expect her to do such a thing?
So she isn't the real Tan!
It's Her Majesty.
It's Her Majesty who had just passed away.
Her Majesty?
What about Tan?
Where is Tan now?
Is Tan already...
No.
I must save Princess!
Let go of me!
If we could take her life,
your blade wouldn't be needed.
Her Highness is still in there.
She is still inside that body.
We cannot harm her at the moment.
You two knew this all along?
If you knew this all along,
why didn't you tell me?
We kept you in the dark
because you are with her all the time.
If you knew,
you would draw her suspicion.
If you didn't know,
it would be for the best.
What do we do now?
How can we save Tan from her?
Be by her side.
Pretending nothing had happened.
She started to suspect me.
Yu Hao
can't approach her at all times.
You're the only one
who can stay by her side,
pretend as if nothing had happened,
find out more about her
and find her weakness.
Can you do this?
Yes.
I can do it.
But what about the Mo family?
From what I heard,
she seemed to have evidence about
the Mo family's plan for rebellion.
Fourteenth Young Master is in the residence.
And Eldest Young Master too.
Can you talk her out of this?
If I did it,
nothing would change,
and she would even be more alert.
Right now,
we must inform my father
as soon as possible,
so he can be ready.
Perhaps
we can weaken her power with this.
Then we'll have better leverage
to negotiate with her.
Okay.
I'll get to it now.
Wait.
You mustn't go.
Once you are gone,
she must notice.
Yu Hao.
You should do it.
Yes.
Jing Xin.
Tell me.
What did you overhear just now?
I need the details.
Okay.
Mo Residence
I know you hate to see me right now.
But this is urgent.
I must speak to you.
Qu Tan Er talked to me.
What have you done to her?
What have I done to her?
Forget it.
She knows your father's plan.
She questioned me.
I told her everything.
You told her my father's grand plan?
I had no choice.
The Capital Guards will no longer
cooperate with the plan.
Our only chance now
is to employ another strategy
to thwart the tyrannical Qu Tan Er now.
Only then can we survive
and keep the Mo family safe.
You plan to use the Mo family
as your scapegoat to take out Qu Tan Er!
I know you hold a grudge against me.
What will I gain now
by telling you lies?
Even if your father overthrows her,
he will disempower me when he has no use of me later.
I came here
not only out of my guilt for you,
but also out of my fear
for Qu Tan Er's cruelty now.
She means to wipe out the whole Mo family.
Is this really Tan Er's plan?
Trust me.
That person
isn't the Tan Er we knew.
She isn't the other Tan Er either.
Or maybe
she is no longer
the same person we once knew.
She acts like the late Empress
more than anything.
Even if I believe you,
that doesn't mean we will share
a relationship in the future.
After today,
we will still be strangers to each other.
I thought so as well.
I came to tell you all of this...
only to make the rest of my life
pass with less guilt.
That's all there is to it.
Take care.
If you lost your life because of this,
I would be in your debt again.
As long as we sever all ties,
we don't owe each other anything.
In this lifetime or the next,
as long as you don't ask to settle the score,
I will ask nothing of you.
We hate each other now.
Let our grudge
along with love...
be forgotten.
♪Without any turns♪
♪Closure was given♪
♪Turn your obsession into a forceful disguise♪
♪This wound burnt deeply,
now we have forgotten one another♪
I hope I never see you again.
♪How come my eyes turned red all of a sudden♪
♪This wound has made my heart strong♪
♪But it can never breakthrough the sadness♪
Qu Tan Er barely has much influence.
This is our chance to strike.
Mr. Mo, you are right.
With Eldest Princess as our informant,
we can proceed with this plan.
Father!
Who let you in?
Dismiss!
Yu Hao has important news for you.
My Lord.
Young Master has a message for you.
He said
that Her Highness might already
knew Mo family's plan of attack.
Her Highness is ready to strike at any time.
Young Master hopes
you make some changes to the plan.
Mr. Mo.
This is...
Calm down.
Your Eighth Brother and Qu Tan Er
are on the same side.
They share benefits and losses together.
His information
cannot be trusted.
Father.
Eighth Brother would never send Yu Hao to lie to you.
It's better
to be ready than to be sorry.
What do you know?
This is a critical moment.
Do not bring disorder to my troops!
Dismiss!
Father!
I talked to Eldest Princess.
She told me the Capital Guards
wouldn't cooperate with us.
We need another strategy.
It seems I have no choice
but to alter our plan.
The information from Eldest Princess
matches with Yu Hao's.
Yu Hao.
I got the information.
You may return now.
Yes.
Mr. Mo.
How should we proceed?
General Lu.
You have the yin imperial token.
I must ask you to risk your life
to prove that the late Empress was killed
and subdue the uprising.
By doing so, we'll be saved.
Are you willing to do that?
For the people of Dongyue,
I will
take this mission.
Good.
Everyone,
we shall set out now.
Inform our allies at the borders.
Order them to march to the capital now
for one last battle.
Time is not on our side.
Do it now.
Yes.
This residence is no longer safe for us.
Qu Tan Er would never hurt Lian Cheng.
But yours and Jing Xuan's safety
is still a concern for me.
Both of you
should seek shelter outside the city.
When the battle is over,
we'll make further arrangements.
Father.
In this critical moment,
I cannot leave you behind.
I'm the eldest son of the Mo family.
I shall fight by your side.
Very well.
If things go south,
meet me at the Luomei Pavilion
of the eastern suburb.
Yes.
You shall leave the city.
Father.
I'll stay too.
You will only get in the way of my plan.
Do you understand?
Fourteenth.
At least one of our Mo family must survive.
You are leaving
not for your life,
but our family's bloodline.
In that case,
I will follow your order.
Mo Residence
The men we sent out
should have reported in.
What is taking them so long?
My Lord!
Bad news!
Troops of imperial guards
are marching this way.
They are going to surround the Mo residence.
Do not tell Yan Chen
about this for now.
Order Yun Ying to take him
out of this house now!
Through the back door.
Yes!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have
to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part,
no matter what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪