Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith
that gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from
the chrysalis of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 27
Stop!
You, stop!
Over there! Someone is over there!
Keep up.
This way.
Someone is here. Go.
Eldest Brother.
This is too risky.
I worry about her no less than you.
I have something
that I need to ask her in person.
Take care.
I'll lead the guards away.
I'll meet you at the prison.
You should also take care.
I'll bribe the Lead Prison Guard,
it'll help you get into the prison
more easily.
Let's go.
Who is there? Stop!
Stop!
Here, dishes are here.
So slow.
Come, come, come.
We have alcohol and meat.
Let's enjoy ourselves to the fullest.
You, come to the toilets with me.
Continue drinking.
Slow down.
Who are you?
Official Xiao asked me to ask
Her Highness some questions.
Official Xiao?
Do you have a token?
Does Official Xiao need a token
to ask questions?
Asking questions privately is
probably Her Majesty's order.
A token is too ostentatious.
Lead Prison Guard, do you know what I mean?
I understand.
She is a major criminal. You should be quick.
Tan Er.
Cheng Cheng.
Yan Chen.
Why is it you?
Sorry, I just woke up.
How did you come in?
Are you here to rescue me?
You surely are a good bro.
I appreciate your kindness,
but you should leave.
It's the death penalty.
I've never doubted you.
I chose to forgive and understand
all your strange behaviours.
I even convinced myself
that staying by your side is enough.
However, today,
I wavered,
I was confused.
Tell me.
Are you still my Qu Tan Er?
As long as you answer me,
I'll believe whatever you say.
I...
What should I say?
No one will believe me other than Cheng Cheng.
Should I fool him with a fake story?
No, no, no.
It's too evil to lie at this moment.
The Mo Yan Chen in this world
loves Qu Tan Er deeply.
How can I tell him the truth?
I'm not Qu Tan Er,
so I've never loved you.
I'm sorry.
Stop right there.
You are not her?
Then who are you?
Where is Tan Er?
How should I tell you?
This body
belongs to Qu Tan Er.
But it's me who currently lives
in this body.
I'm
Qu Xiao Tan.
Then tell me, where is Tan Er?
She was killed by Qu Mei Er way before.
But should I tell him the truth at this moment?
Cheng Cheng.
The real Qu Tan Er died
when she fell into the water that time.
Tan is
from another world.
She makes
this body continue to be alive.
As for why Qu Tan Er fell into the water,
you should know the reason
behind it after thinking a bit.
How is this possible?
How can such an absurd incident
exist in this world?
Eldest Brother.
Even if you don't believe
the absurd incident we speak of,
you should believe
the actual Qu Tan Er
will not fail you.
Tan Er will never fail me.
I'll get her back.
Yan Chen.
Is it okay
that we told him the truth?
Although it's cruel,
it's the truth.
I missed you so much.
We need to go now.
No.
Her Majesty definitely knows that
we're meeting each other here tonight.
She permitted you to come
for some reasons.
I don't want you to suffer here.
Not even for a second.
It's okay.
Take it easy.
You?
Heart?
I know
that no matter where we are,
no matter what situation we are in,
and no matter if we are poor or rich,
you will always
be in my heart.
Take care of yourself.
Go.
Tan Er.
So,
suffering in this kind of place,
being in this kind of situation
for the one you love
can bring such happiness.
You really don't know anything
about the incident
that Second Princess fell into the water?
I don't.
I have asked Tan Er.
When she brought the wedding invitation to me,
she was pushed into the water
by Eldest Princess herself.
I saw you being nervous after that.
How do you explain that?
She is posing as Second Princess.
She is trying to sow discord
among you and Eldest Princess.
Why did you go to
Second Princess's Residence?
Why did Eldest Princess
go to Second Princess's Residence?
We...
We went there merely to visit.
When I asked Eldest Princess if she had seen
Tan Er that day,
she said she hadn't seen her.
Are you saying
that Eldest Princess was lying?
My memories fail me.
Days have passed, I...
Don't say anything more.
Now that you know the truth,
feel free to take revenge for her.
Since the first time I met you,
I knew,
in this world,
I am the only one who can see the real you
and help you make achievements with your talent.
No matter how capricious I am,
I only hope
that you can see
my sincere and fragile side.
But you wanted to kill Tan Er.
I can only see your cold and emotionless side.
I did that because I wanted to give you
the best in the world.
Only then
would you be with me willingly.
Yan Chen.
I still want to say,
no matter what you want to do,
I'll do it with you.
Even if we need to defy the world's opinion,
even if...
♪The past is in the past♪
♪Turn your obsession into a forceful disguise♪
you want to kill me.
♪This wound burnt deeply,
now we have forgotten one another♪
Somebody!
I cannot bear
your love.
I'm returning it all to you.
♪This wound has made my heart strong♪
♪But it can never break through
the sadness in my heart♪
♪This wound burnt deeply,
now we have forgotten one another♪
♪How come my eyes turned red all of a sudden♪
♪This wound has made my heart strong♪
♪But it can never break through
the sadness in my heart♪
♪It is just confusion in the mortal world♪
Mo Residence
Chen Er.
Does it still hurt?
Eldest Princess sent over some tonics,
and I've accepted on your behalf.
Chen Er.
Do you still remember
what I told you at the pavilion
the day you married Eldest Princess?
You said you would give your all
for the Mo Family.
You would bear any grievances
after
marrying Eldest Princess.
I don't know why you came back to
Mo Residence.
However, I want you to remember
what you said before.
Eldest Princess
treats you well.
You should be content.
Father, I'm sorry for letting you down.
My destiny with her has already ended.
Chen Er,
you are the only one I can count on
in this family.
How can you say such unreasonable words?
Second Princess is going to be abolished soon.
Cheng Er is handling a lot.
Xuan Er is still young.
Feng Yang is an unfilial daughter...
You shouldn't be so capricious when it comes to
the fate of the Mo Family.
Also,
what I'm planning now is meant to
fulfill your mother's last wish.
Mother's last wish?
What do you mean?
I have never told you about this before.
In fact,
our Mo Family was the feudal lord of this land
before this kingdom was established.
Her Majesty relied on our power
to unite the country
and establish Dongyue.
However, nowadays,
Her Majesty is tyrannical.
Collecting extra taxes and
not listening to the people's wills.
People are suffering.
Your mother's last wish
is to replace Her Majesty.
Our Mo Family
had such great achievements?
Chen Er.
Your mother did everything
for you.
I'm planning everything
for you too.
Don't act on emotions.
I made this medicine for you.
Rest well.
Remember what I said.
After you recover,
return as soon as possible.
Get some rest.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Your Majesty.
We can activate the magic circle today.
I don't need to
drink this medicine.
Your Majesty.
I've already
finished composing the Soul-destroying Song.
Go get everything ready.
What else?
Since Your Majesty saved me
from the wolves,
I swore to live
only for you.
Time passed rapidly.
Now you can rebuild your body.
I'm very happy for you.
Yes.
You were so little back then,
but you fought with the wolf pack all night.
I really couldn't believe it.
Your Majesty wasn't any older than
I was at the time.
Why are you so emotional today?
I'm just
missing the days
when I played instruments with Your Majesty.
After I am reborn,
you'll be
the first person to play instruments with me.
Does that sound good?
I'll
remember this.
Official Xiao?
I can leave?
I can wash up once I'm back at my residence.
You don't have to go through such trouble.
I'll feel bad.
Crown Princess,
please get yourself ready as soon as possible.
This looks so much like getting ready
for the execution.
Anyway,
I'll try to prolong the process as much as I can.
Official Xiao.
Why are you so loyal to Her Majesty?
How did you meet?
Why are you so loyal to her?
Is poker face also popular here?
According to my observations,
with this solid employer-employee
relationship between you,
you must've been tricked by Her Majesty.
Simply speaking,
you fell into
Her Majesty's setup.
If you want to win her heart,
you need to do the same to her.
Your Highness,
your words are more and more presumptuous.
I have a few tips and tricks,
do you want to know?
First,
a four-character short phrase,
and a five-step trap.
They are
triggering curiosity,
gaining attention,
building relationship,
criticizing misunderstandings
and abusing feelings.
If Your Highness keeps rinsing,
you will eventually lose your mouth.
I haven't finished.
These are only some of the setups
Her Majesty may have used,
I have more...
I know you are trying
to hold off from getting ready.
Never mind,
this is going to be the last time
we see each other.
The last time we see each other?
What does that mean?
You just asked me
how I met Her Majesty.
Her Majesty
saved my life.
Saved your life?
She appeared at my most helpless moment.
The whole world had abandoned me at that time.
She was the only one who helped me
without any hesitation.
She taught me how to read.
She is only a few years older than me,
but she always appeared to be so mature.
She made me want to take care of her.
Sadly, I was too young at the time.
I didn't understand anything.
I could only hide behind her.
You like her?
After we had grown up,
I got mad when I saw
other men being nice to her.
When I saw her being tired,
I blamed myself for not being a better man.
She always laughed at my foolishness
and childishness.
But I know,
she is the foolish one,
because she doesn't know true love.
Your Highness,
you should get changed
in the next room.
You haven't finished your story.
What happened next?
Did you tell her your feelings?
We grew up together
away from secularization.
She was born for people to look up to.
I knew she didn't like me.
That was good.
She wouldn't like others either.
I once thought we could be like this
until we grew old.
Who knew...
♪You turn around as the firework fades♪
♪Fate played a trick on me
so I pick up my flute again♪
♪The string broke and the song ended,
they went their separate ways♪
♪If it wasn't meant to be, why bother
bringing up the vows again♪
Now,
my only wish is
to see her smile when I look up.
♪Lonely music-playing looks to the waning lights♪
Her smile is like warm sunshine in the winter,
lighting up the entire world.
♪Still keeping this face in mind
for a thousand years♪
♪I shall come and go with the wind
as the blossoms fall♪
♪I will never stop waiting for your return♪
♪We shall wander the world together
like clouds touched by the winds♪
♪From breaking down the barriers
to falling helplessly in love♪
Your Highness,
let's go.
Senior.
Prince Consort.
You look
exhausted today.
Tan Er was imprisoned despite being innocent,
I really couldn't sleep.
I came to ask you
if there are any signs
of the Red Star of Demise.
Don't worry Your Highness.
Before you came,
I did the divination for you.
Let me tell you.
The "Shi Star" moved three times from the north,
*Should be "Di Star", a constellation in ancient China
the two poles are in anti-phase,
indicating a great chance.
However, the moon has grown an angular light,
indicating danger.
Senior.
Can you say everything in simpler terms?
What do you mean?
I felt good today,
and have done the divination for Your Highness.
Even if there is a great chance
to change fate today,
two stars clash,
only one of them can stay.
And there appears to be
uncertain danger.
Thank you, Senior.
I...
I haven't finished, why did you leave?
Fate has been settled,
external forces can hardly change it!
Your Majesty.
The process of body-usurping
will be tortuous.
There will be a process when
two people's consciousnesses
exist in the same body.
You should remain clear-headed
and strong the entire time.
Otherwise,
you will lose yourself
in Qu Tan Er's consciousness.
I'm telling you,
my consciousness is very strong.
I have already experienced this twice.
You are playing with fire.
Let go.
Let go of me.
Let go of me, let go of me.
Let go...
You've lost your mind.
Qu Xiang Tan.
Do you dare to play fair in a competition with me?
I must get
what I want.
Your Majesty.
I wondered why you let Cheng Cheng marry me
even though you deeply liked
Eighth Young Master of Mo family,
and even made me Crown Princess.
It turns out
that you've planned everything.
You knew you were dying,
so you planned to take over my body.
You planned to have Cheng Cheng and the country
in your hands.
How despicable.
Don't worry.
I've been waiting for this moment
for so many years.
No one's consciousness
is stronger
and more solid
than mine.
Let's begin.
I'm looking forward
to playing instruments with you.
Okay.
What is this?
Qu Xiang Tan.
Completing this altar
will sacrifice Xiao Zhen.
Do you know that?
Do you want
Xiao Zhen to sacrifice himself for you?
To die for you?
What should I do?
Bring me to Her Highness.
Crown Princess left a while ago.
Really.
Official Xiao brought Her Majesty's message,
suggesting that Crown Princess is innocent.
Her Majesty worried Crown Princess would feel
uncomfortable staying in the palace,
so she ordered Official Xiao
to send her back to her residence.
They all saw it.
Take me inside.
Okay, okay.
See?
Now,
do you believe me?
Mo Lian Cheng.
Cheng Cheng.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I hope that person
can protect you for me.
♪What is it all for♪
♪To love you like I do♪
♪Don't tell me I should learn to let go♪
♪Self-deprecation to the maximum♪
♪But love has become a double-edged sword♪
♪Knowing each other so well,
you know where it hurts the most♪
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
♪Didn't think if I can get it back♪
♪I feel even more lost afterwards♪
♪And it pains me♪
♪Why do this♪
♪Ask yourself whether you are willing♪
♪Willing or not, love has turned into hate♪
♪Who are the tears for♪
♪Who loses and who wins♪
♪Who really cares♪
♪It hurts anyway♪
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if
I have to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter
what hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have
to travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind
in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪