Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Time flies in the blink of an eye,
a moment passes, another lasts♪
♪My love has become tangled
without anyone knowing♪
♪The enchanting brocade was woven,
much like our intertwined destiny♪
♪My yearning has become my burden♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
♪I'm willing to turn into a monolith that
gazes upon the edge of the world♪
♪Your name will be etched onto my heart♪
♪Like the silk from the chrysalis
of a reborn butterfly♪
♪Our fates will forever remain entangled♪
The Eternal Love S3
Episode 25
Xuanling Continent
Miss! Miss!
The physical wounds are healing,
but the internal injuries aren't
getting any better.
It sure does seem like Yi Feng's doing.
Who exactly are you?
You know Mo Yi Feng?
A longtime friend of mine.
And Miss, you are…?
No need for you to know.
Wait till Mo Yi Feng sees your corpse,
then he will understand.
Your wounds might have healed,
but Yi Feng is a master at combat.
You can't move yet.
Be a good girl.
When I cure you,
it's not too late for you to kill me.
Come on.
May I now
know your name?
Don't get distracted.
This Love's Reflection
can help heal your wounds.
There's ample spiritual power here.
It can help your wounds
heal faster.
You must learn this song first,
so that even if I'm gone in the future,
you can treat yourself.
So can you now tell me
your name?
Qu Xiang Tan.
Young Master Lian Cheng.
Why am I reading this?
Like she's actually going to
ask me these questions?
She's just trying to separate me and Cheng Cheng.
Lower your voice.
This is the royal study.
There are guards outside.
Forget it! I'm not going to read it!
It's not like I'm actually going to
become the empress here.
If I have the free time,
I should be investigating more useful things.
The Soul-guarding Bead.
The Altar of Souls.
Red Star of Demise.
The Qu family is a royal family
and she looks exactly like me.
Who founded Dongyue?
In the original world,
Dongyue
was founded by Mo Yi Feng,
gaining independence
in the Xuanling Continent.
Then what about this Qu family?
They...
They probably are...
related to the Qu Clan from the
Xuanling Continent.
I don't even know
what you're doing,
talking to yourself all day.
It's too hardcore.
You won't understand.
I need some more time to figure it out.
It's because
I'm used to living in the Dongyue
that has both the Qu family
and the Mo family,
so I
didn't think about it in this way.
Now that I think about it,
if the empress's last name is Qu,
then she should be
the Mo Yi Feng
from the original world.
Then she's...!
Right.
Everything you say is right.
So it is indeed you.
Didn't you already know?
That's right.
But...
how could this be?
Back then,
you were murdered by your lover's sword.
It must have been painful.
All these years, I've been waiting
for you to tell me
whether it's more painful to die
by your lover's hands
or to kill your lover with your own hands.
If you insist on helping Mo Yi Feng
and stopping me from achieving my goals,
then I have no choice but to kill you.
♪To love you like I do♪
♪Don't tell me I should learn to let go♪
I can't bear to watch
♪Self-deprecation to the maximum♪
my lifetime friend and my love
having a fratricidal conflict.
If killing me
can make you feel better,
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
then I'm willing to die.
You...
♪Even without knowing words can't be taken back♪
♪The more is spoken the more the heart pains♪
♪It will be even sadder♪
If you still can't let go,
♪Why do this♪
then don't hesitate
and kill me.
♪Willing or not, love has turned into hate♪
You think I can't?
Lian Cheng!
♪Who loses and who wins♪
♪Who really cares♪
♪It hurts anyway♪
Lian Cheng. Lian Cheng.
♪To love you like I do♪
♪Don't tell me I should learn to let go♪
♪Self-deprecation to the maximum♪
Leave.
♪But love has become a double-edged sword♪
What happens between you and Yi Feng
is none of my business anymore.
♪Knowing each other so well,
you know where it hurts the most♪
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
♪Even without knowing words can't be taken back♪
♪I feel even more lost afterwards♪
♪And it pains me♪
♪Why do this♪
Does it still hurt?
♪Ask yourself whether you are willing♪
♪Willing or not, love has turned into hate♪
No.
If she's Qu Xiang Tan,
then what about Tan Er?
Yi Feng wouldn't have randomly
ordered me to marry Tan Er.
♪Who really cares♪
Please behave yourself, Your Majesty.
Wasn't the truth revealed?
Why are you still calling me that?
Weren't you the one who saved me?
Weren't you the one who insisted on
teaching me how to play the zither?
Weren't you the one who asked for
my name over and over again?
Weren't you the one who made me
fall in love with you
and live with pain for the rest of my life?
♪Say everything that can hurt others♪
Since Your Majesty knows how to play the zither,
then I shall
take my leave first.
♪Even without knowing words can't be taken back♪
Lian Cheng.
♪The more is spoken the more the heart pains♪
Save me one more time.
Just like you did before, please?
♪It hurts anyway♪
What are you doing?
You're making a big mess.
Be careful not to get caught.
I can't even search some documents?
Then what documents are you looking for?
I'll help you.
I want to find out
the empress's name.
There's no need to find out the empress's name.
Calling the empress by her name is taboo.
How can it be written in any documents?
But I still need to look it up.
Even if they don't contain the empress's name,
there must be some clues.
Clues about
the secret of this world.
Official Qu.
Official Qu is
the only distant relative the empress has now.
Right!
How could I forget about him?
Jing Xin.
Go distract the guards at the door.
I need to go see him now.
Understood.
Your Highness.
Her Majesty ordered me to
bring you some desserts,
saying that you've worked hard
reviewing memorials.
Where is Her Majesty now?
Her Majesty is in the imperial gardens
learning the zither with Prince Consort.
Her Majesty?
Wasn't he teaching the consorts of the harem?
Please enjoy your meal, Your Highness.
I'll take my leave now.
If she's indeed Qu Xiang Tan,
her approaching Cheng Cheng now…
Tan!
The guards outside the doors
have been removed from their posts.
Great.
Jing Xin,
I need to go
find Cheng Cheng right now.
Didn't she say
she is going to find Official Qu?
Cheng Cheng! Cheng Cheng!
Cheng Cheng! Cheng Cheng! Cheng Cheng!
Your injuries…
Right.
I'm living with my dying breath,
waiting for you to come.
Xiang Tan, listen to me.
Tan Er! Tan Er!
It's not what you think!
Tan Er!
It's really not what you...
Go.
Tomorrow, I'll still be here
waiting for you.
You're the empress.
It wouldn't be appropriate for me
to meet you in private.
Don't you want to know my secrets?
Alright.
But only to treat you.
You've finally come face-to-face
with Young Master Lian Cheng.
Hope that
your years of perseverance won't go to waste.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Tan Er.
She's Qu Xiang Tan.
Yes, she is.
You knew already, didn't you?
It was only a guess.
I've only just found out.
Just now,
I was treating her wounds.
Cheng Cheng.
I've always thought that
we were destined to be together.
However, the ultimate origin of this destiny
has something to do with the connection
between Qu Xiang Tan and me.
But now...
Tan Er,
you are the one I love.
As for her…
I haven't figured out
what exactly is going on.
Give me some time.
Once I find out the truth,
then maybe
we can go back to our world.
Go back to our world?
I'm tired.
I want to go home.
I miss Yu Er.
What?
Not used to seeing me dressing like this?
You can ask anything you want to know.
I'll tell you everything.
Your illness…
What was the cause of it?
And why
are you here in Dongyue?
That year,
Mo Yi Feng and I fought a hard battle
with Demon Lord.
Even though we managed
to seal Demon Lord away,
we were badly injured.
After I woke up,
I realized that it was Xiao Zhen who saved me
and before I knew it, I was already in Dongyue.
If it weren't for the Soul-guarding Bead
and the Soul-parting Flute,
I probably would have died already.
I may have lived
but was gravely injured.
So I need
an altar suitable for training with
the Soul-guarding Bead.
And that's the Altar of Souls.
You ascended the throne
so you could have the money and power
to build the Altar of Souls?
I did it so I could live.
I was in unimaginable pain, but I was able to
hold out long enough for you to come.
It's quite preposterous.
My injuries
prevent me from being able to love.
The more I love someone,
the worse the injuries become.
But as long as I am alive, I will think of you.
And to be able to think of you, I must stay alive.
Here I am in this unsolvable maze,
using the pain caused by you
to remember you.
No need for you to do so.
Your illness...
I'll help you cure it.
And after it's cured?
If you leave me once I'm cured,
then I'd rather you never be able to cure me.
I still don't understand.
You were Eighth Young Master before.
How did you get yourself back?
It's true that Eighth Young Master before
was not me.
I don't know where he went either.
Perhaps he has died.
And why
am I living in his body?
To be honest,
I don't know either.
I've been thinking that
Qu Tan Er's has also changed a lot.
Then tell me.
Who is she?
Isn't she Qu Jiang Lin's daughter?
How would I know
if she has changed a lot?
But
I've been curious.
What kind of power
allowed us to meet here
once again?
Now it seems that
you not only have the Soul-guarding Bead,
but also the Soul-parting Flute.
There is nothing
you cannot do.
If I were really that capable,
would I have needed to use Eighth Young Master
as a replacement for you
and struggled until now?
It happened a long time ago.
If you are still...
It's been a long time,
yet I still want to ask you.
When we were at Xuanling Continent,
were your feelings towards me
genuine?
They were genuine feelings of
Young Master Lian Cheng.
But now,
I am Mo...
I'm heading back.
Don't forget what you promised me.
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow, I'll wait for you here
so that you can continue to treat me.
Cheng Cheng.
You're back.
Come on.
See what I've made for you.
It's your favorite
braised carp
and steamed shrimp.
What do you think?
There are more here.
Desserts I made for you myself.
I've got the bath water ready too.
Do you want to
eat first
or shower first?
What?
Don't tell me...
that you're too used to being Prince Consort
and are weak to me spoiling you?
Are you still the Tan Er I know?
Or am I dreaming?
Of course, I'm Tan Er.
Come on, sit down.
Tell me.
Did everything
go well today?
We just reminisced about the old days.
But
she was suspicious of your real identity.
Reminiscing...
That's good to hear.
It has been so long since it happened.
You do need to reminiscence about it.
That's right.
Otherwise, it'd be so awkward.
Here.
Try this dessert I made for you.
Since Tan Er is so well-behaved,
I'll tell you a bit more information.
You don't need to tell me anything
too detailed...
I just
revisited everything
that we did before.
Revisited everything?
There are some things
that we can't revisit in broad daylight.
So I'll go meet her
in her bedchamber at night.
Mo Lian Cheng!
You're going too far!
I thought that
I could be more considerate
and give you some space so that
you can deal with it yourself.
But do you think
I'm a pushover?
You were teasing me on purpose?
Calm down.
If I didn't say so,
would you be able to
release all of your anger?
So that means that
you guys didn't revisit anything?
Nothing at all.
But
I don't think she's someone
who will let things go easily.
Perhaps
my complicated relationship with her
is the key for us
to return to our world.
Since you promised her you will cure her,
then you must keep your promise.
But
it will take some time
for her injuries to be cured.
Is it difficult?
Tan Er,
the hardest step
is this last step.
The two of us need to be locked up together
for seven days and seven nights in a private room.
And we need to
have our clothes off
so that my pure chi of Yang
can mix with her.
Mo Lian Cheng, do you want to die?
Are you looking for a beating?
I...
enjoy seeing your jealous face.
Don't know if I should say you have good taste
or strange taste.
Then...
how about I go with you?
No.
Absolutely do not
act recklessly.
I can't even see for myself
how I get cheated on.
Every time I hear this song,
our past stands before me
like a dagger
and cuts wounds in my mind and heart.
But if it weren't for the sound of the flute,
I would never be able to fall asleep.
Your Majesty
taught me this song.
I shouldn't have passed this
Soul-parting Flute to you,
but at that time,
you were the only one with me.
Who else could I pass it on to?
Your Majesty, you still remember.
I'm tired.
When you leave,
leave the Soul-parting Flute here.
I need to use it tomorrow.
To you, the Soul-parting Flute
represents the memories you had with him.
But to me,
it also represents the memories we had.
Your Majesty, your illness
is due to injuries to your circulatory system.
Besides taking medicine every day,
you need to use the sound of the zither
to soothe your frustration.
Why did Her Majesty call me here?
This is a booklist
Her Majesty made for you, Your Highness.
Please read it over carefully,
Crown Princess.
That's my Cheng Cheng.
Based on what I see, their distance
is the normal social distance
between a doctor and his patient.
The Soul-parting Flute.
Crown Princess,
how do you know about the Soul-parting Flute?
Father once mentioned it when I was a kid,
so I recognize it.
I'll read the books on this list carefully.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Since the string is broken,
I have no choice but come to
treat Your Majesty at another time.
I will take my leave now.
How could you speak about
the Soul-parting Flute out loud?
Good lord.
I somehow managed to gloss it over.
Is my explanation just now
alright?
Deceive him?
He's a very paranoid person.
He will never believe your explanation
and will definitely make some preparations.
But after this,
I'm suddenly enlightened.
Suddenly enlightened?
Yes.
The only person that knows how to play
the Soul-parting Flute is the chief
of the Qu Clan in Xuanling Continent.
Liu Qian Shui gave you the sheet music
and you were able to teach yourself.
That is precisely because
you are the descendant
of the chief of the Qu Clan from that world.
And she
is the Qu Xiang Tan from a parallel universe.
The Young Master Lian Cheng
that fell in love with her is also the
Lian Cheng of that parallel universe.
It was not me.
Then that means
there's nothing
between you and the empress.
Theoretically,
that is so.
But it is no lie that I've played
the song, Love's Reflection, before.
What the Young Master Lian Cheng
from the parallel universe did,
I also did.
So even if I'm from
another parallel universe,
I can't pretend that she is
a complete stranger to me.
After all this talking,
you're saying you still have to face it.
Hope that it wasn't because of
this star-crossed fate
that the Soul-guarding Bead brought us here.
Qu Tan Er...
How could she recognize the Soul-parting Flute?
Your Majesty.
Have you really mentioned it to Qu Jiang Lin?
Qu Jiang Lin
does not even know of the existence
of the Soul-parting Flute.
Your Majesty.
As I expected,
this Qu Tan Er
has a mysterious background.
Find out who she is
as soon as possible.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪This longing, this pining♪
♪In this lonely city♪
♪Oh, to live a life unrestrained♪
♪Someone sighs as they look back to the past♪
♪A flower shower enchants the four seasons♪
♪As the seasons pass by, I am reminded of♪
♪The love that once occupied my heart♪
♪Who had loved and who had fallen♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪
♪If you were to join me in this play♪
♪From now to the unknown future♪
♪We shall not part, no matter what
hardships we must face♪
♪To love only you so deeply that I forget myself♪
♪To wish only for you never to leave my side♪
♪I will find you even if I have to
travel across the sea of time♪
♪We leave our steps behind in the trail of time♪
♪Forever and ever, never to part♪