♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 31=
(We'll be a happily married couple
to enjoy the jolly good time)
Maoya.
This time, are you going to regret this?
No.
All right.
As long as you're happy,
I'm at ease.
The curtains rise along
with the crescent moon.
The best fragrance and finest
stallion arrives at the doorstep.
Thank you for the hard work.
A day of celebration and joy.
Everlasting health and happiness.
Thank you for the hard work.
These are bonuses for you.
Please carry the carriage well.
My wife.
This way, please.
♪Approach you slowly
and accompany you silently♪
♪We look at the stars together♪
♪Your shadow
under the moonlight♪
♪The unforgettable gentleness♪
♪As detailed as the poem♪
♪The word spoken softly♪
♪In my ears like wind♪
Lift the carriage.
♪You fill up all my view♪
♪Waiting for the birds to come home♪
♪They are all coming for you♪
♪To listen to you♪
♪Your beautiful voice♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪You dance like the cloud♪
Maoya!
Take care of yourself.
♪Hide you in my heart secretly♪
♪Even though you're childish♪
♪Telling you softly that
you're the most beautiful anticipation♪
♪Seek no more as it'll always be you♪
♪Can't stop loving you♪
♪I'd only tell you my feelings♪
♪Waiting for the birds to come home♪
♪They are all coming for you♪
♪To listen to you♪
♪Your beautiful voice♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪You dance like the cloud♪
♪We grow old together slowly♪
♪Waiting for the birds to come home♪
♪They are all coming for you♪
♪To listen to you♪
♪Your beautiful voice♪
Congwen.
♪You dance like the cloud♪
Someone would like to meet you.
♪We grow old together slowly♪
Take care.
Goodbye.
Don't worry about it.
Congratulations.
Take care.
Lady Xie is married to
His Highness again.
Is this considered
their second marriage?
Who allowed her to drink so much?
That's ridiculous.
Don't worry about it.
Let her be.
I find her
really adorable.
That's enough.
Hurry up and help her to the backyard.
She can't get drunk here.
This...
This is ridiculous.
Hurry up.
Take care.
The long day is finally over.
Hanchen's residence is spacious.
I ran back and forth dozens of times.
My legs
are exhausted.
Boyang.
It's time for you to work out.
Your stamina is poor.
That won't do in the future.
Xingzhou.
You've gotten pretty cheeky.
I guess it confirms the saying that
goes, one who lies down with dogs
will get up with fleas.
Are you calling Hanchen a dog?
That's true.
On Hanchen's wedding night,
he drank three whole jugs of wine.
He'd go wild.
I was referring to you.
Me?
All right.
Fine.
It doesn't matter.
As long as the three
of us remain together.
everything will be fine.
You're right.
Sirs.
Please keep it down.
It's getting late.
We shouldn't interrupt
His Highness' wedding night.
All right.
Let's drink up somewhere else.
Let's go.
(Sleeping Room)
Zhao Xiaoqian.
If you do not come right now,
you will never come near me for good.
You...
What's wrong?
Are you not going to
sleep with me?
I'm exhausted.
Let's just go to bed.
How would you like to sleep?
Like this?
Keep this in mind.
Since you're married to me,
you have nothing to fear.
Do you understand?
Zhao Xiaoqian.
I have something on.
Go to bed first.
Keep this in mind.
Now that you're married to me,
you may do whatever you want.
Mr. Liangji.
What's wrong with His Highness?
It's his wedding night.
He came out to take a cold bath.
Congratulations, Lord Zhao,
for your promotion
as the Imperial Grand Governor.
In the future,
you're going to attain great success.
Thank you, Chancellor Xu.
As the Imperial Grand Governor,
I'm afraid I'm going
to need your guidance
for the connections
and ways around the capital.
For the sake of a common lady,
you forgo the marriage with Shen Family.
For what?
If I'm not wrong,
perhaps you weren't after
the throne in the first place.
The 200,000 piculs
of provisions at Baichuankou.
Li Guangwen's bank.
The accounts of Jingdong
and Jingxi Roads.
My intentions
lie in these three cases.
Aren't you afraid of uncovering
the things you aren't supposed to?
Regardless who is involved,
I'll investigate no matter what.
What I seek is
for you to head to hell
and pay respects to
the 10,000 late brothers of mine.
All right.
How impressive,
Commandery Prince of Julu.
You managed to deceive me.
You're quite the man, Zhao Xiaoqian.
I said this many times.
Do not only cram.
Tell me.
What should you do
if a flood breaks out?
I...
In my opinion,
in order to curb a flood,
civilians should be moved
far from the waters.
Once the people are away from the flood,
and have settled down,
they'd be grateful towards
Your Majesty's grace.
Move the civilians
away from the waters?
This is a huge task.
Do you know
how much it is going to cost?
By then,
we wouldn't know how much money
would disappear again.
Your Majesty,
why did you bring
this up suddenly?
Regarding the case of Baichuankou
and Jingdong and Jingxi Roads,
do you think I know nothing?
Pardon my ignorance.
I don't know
what Your Majesty meant.
You
may mess with me.
He is the Crown Prince.
Are you going to allow him
to mess with the entire nation
in the future?
Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince and I
have never betrayed you.
Please prove our innocence.
I'm not in the mood to blame you.
Get up.
Crown Prince,
Hanchen joined the army in his teens.
He suffered hardships
for three years,
and eventually he attained
the victory at Baichuankou.
The war was quelled.
Peace was returned to the people.
He won the praises
and hearts of the people.
Look at you.
All you do is remain
taken care of at the palace.
You've not experienced
any adversity.
You're given the best tutors
and guidance.
If you continue on with your ignorance,
you should give up your position
as the Crown Prince.
Your Majesty.
All you care about is Zhao Xiaoqian.
You insolent brat!
Your Majesty.
Is this the great son you raised?
I failed to teach him well.
I'm willing to be punished
on Xiaoze's behalf.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Xiaoze is still young.
He's young?
He may be young, but he got nerves.
At this young age, he has learned to
create factions for personal gain.
He allowed the corrupted
to eat the nation up.
If he's any older,
my nation
would be destroyed by him!
He's your biological son.
Zhao Xiaoqian has achieved
meritorious deeds,
but what else did he achieve?
In the past, he and Zhao Xiaojie
constantly caused troubles at the palace.
In terms of obedience,
he cannot be compared
to the Crown Prince.
Enough!
Your Majesty.
Do not think that
I had no idea how Xiaojie died.
Do not touch me.
Summon the imperial physician.
Your Majesty.
Are you all right?
Father.
Your Majesty.
Father!
Do not move!
Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Inform Chancellor Xu.
Something happened.
Yes, Your Highness.
His Majesty
fell unconscious?
Yes.
According to the imperial physicians,
His Majesty may not wake up soon.
His Majesty is currently
recuperating at the Kunning Palace.
Her Highness is worried that
the state affairs would be disrupted,
so she sent me over
to deliver the message.
What else did Her Highness say?
Her Highness said,
His Majesty brought up
Commandery Prince of Julu.
If the Crown Prince does not buck up,
his position as the Crown Prince
will be lost to others.
Her Highness is greatly
concerned about the Crown Prince.
She sought for you to
figure something out.
Eliminate Zhao Xiaoqian,
and the Crown Prince's
position will be secured.
The thorn must be removed.
Disloyal subjects must be executed.
I'm not sure if Her Highness
is bold enough to do so.
Chancellor,
please be careful with what you say.
Chancellor.
His Majesty is still alive and well.
If we execute His Majesty's officials,
we might be in trouble in the future.
Do you know
what aggravated His Majesty?
Commandery Prince of Julu
is now the Imperial Grand Governor.
What intention is he harboring?
Isn't he coveting the throne?
The throne?
If he's after the throne,
there's no need
for me to take his life.
Commandery Prince of Julu
is using the authority of
the Imperial Grand Governor
to investigate the accounts of
the Jingdong and Jingxi Roads
and the provisions of Baichuankou.
He's aware of
the Crown Prince's involvement.
In the past, when the Crown Prince
stirred up trouble,
His Majesty would play ignorant
and let it slide.
However, right now,
what happens if someone
forces His Majesty to face the problem?
Well...
If His Majesty regains consciousness
and decides to investigate the matter,
how do we save ourselves?
That's why we have
to rely on Her Highness
to resolve the matters of the palace.
The Emperor will abdicate.
The Crown Prince
ascends the throne.
You and I
shall emerge as the Imperial Regents.
(Studio of Artlessness)
What's the matter?
I brought you chicken soup.
My husband,
let's play a game.
I have a lot of documents to go through.
Stop playing around.
You shall play the scholar
while I play the fox spirit.
Let's play a love story between
a man and a fox spirit.
You perverted scholar.
How dare you?
In the middle of the night,
you intruded the chamber of a woman.
I'm going to punish you.
Wick taught me all these.
Get back to work.
I'll get going then.
(Studio of Artlessness)
Hanchen.
We've found Li Guangwen.
Li Su has invited him over personally.
He'll arrive at the capital
in two days.
However, Xu Huan is
monitoring him closely.
He's a criminal as well.
He can only sneak into the capital.
All right.
With the evidences against Jingdong
and Jingxi Roads and Baichuankou,
the presence of Li Guangwen
would greatly benefit us.
Don't worry.
I will receive him personally.
Along with the testimony
of Li Guangwen,
even if His Majesty
refuses to touch Xu Huan,
with the presence of
the evidences and the witness,
there's nothing His Majesty can do.
What's on your face?
How embarrassing.
Something's wrong, Lady Xie.
What do you mean?
According to Shi Deng'er,
the officials love this the most.
Which official is he referring to?
Officials from the brothels.
Look at what you've done.
We have been delivering chicken soup
to His Highness for half a month.
What are we doing exactly?
His Highness must be
attending to something major.
He's treating me this way
because he doesn't want to implicate me.
I'm married to him as his wife.
I can't allow him to
treat me like a child.
Lady Xie.
(Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Take a bite.
I woke up early in the morning
to make you breakfast.
You wouldn't even take a bite.
I can't maintain my status here
at the mansion.
I didn't marry you
to make you my chef.
I'm not a chef.
I'm only cooking for my husband alone.
Aren't you the fox spirit?
What did you make?
Human meatballs?
How annoying.
All right. I'll take a bite.
Your Highness.
Mr. Shen is here
for an urgent matter.
It's delicious.
Mr. Liangji.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Have a seat.
Does anyone know
you're here?
No.
Hanchen.
Something happened in the palace.
His Majesty fainted at
the imperial palace yesterday.
This morning,
the eunuch released the Empress' edict.
The Crown Prince is appointed
regent with the aid of Chancellor Xu.
The court meeting today was cancelled.
All the four city gates
are locked down under
Chancellor Xu's orders.
In a few days,
the edict of the Crown Prince's
governance will be released.
His Majesty fell unconscious?
When did this happen?
Last evening.
Wang Xian came over last night
and informed Chancellor Xu.
Are they already aware
about your investigation?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Internally, they intend to
force the abdication of throne.
Externally, they shall get rid of
the officials disloyal to them.
Abdication of throne?
Execute disloyal officials?
They can't possibly do that.
In three days,
with the excuse of eliminating
the disloyal officials, Chancellor Xu
dispatched the royal army
to be placed at Donghua Date
and Xihua Gate.
Gongchen Gate at the north
and Xuande Gate at the south
are heavily guarded as well.
Once you enter the palace,
you shall be trapped.
His Majesty fell unconscious
all of a sudden.
My father is willing to lend us a hand
under the condition of
protecting himself.
Currently, the most difficult matter is
Xu Huan has gained control
of the inner court.
Our men
will not be able to enter immediately.
The only solution to this problem
is to disguise ourselves
as the royal army
on the day of the execution.
Enter the palace from
the furthest entrance, Wende Gate.
However, it will take
at least 15 minutes
to get to Zichen Palace.
What do you plan to do?
I'll destroy everything that comes at me
to attain victory in danger.
Where is Li Guangwen right now?
He will arrive
at the capital tomorrow.
Where's His Majesty?
He's being confined in
the Kunning Palace by Empress Cao.
This is quite the hassle.
Kunning Palace is in the harem.
Regular people are not allowed to enter.
If we fight against
Xu Huan at the main court,
prioritizing you and
then the Emperor's safety,
it will take at least an hour.
Head to Kunning Palace first.
What if you're in danger?
I'll be fine.
Support within the palace
would arrange an audience with
the Emperor with Li Guangwen.
With the presence
of the witness and evidences,
no matter how tyrannous
Xu Huan may be,
he'd still remain cautious.
Remember.
If you're in trouble,
our men would tie a yellow scarf
on their left arm.
Soldiers without the scarf
are Chancellor Xu's men.
Respond swiftly.
It's a battle of life and death.
Are you ready?
I fought alongside
with you for three years.
You're still long-winded.
I'll see you off.
Xingzhou.
I'm taking Xiaoman back to Xie Family.
Head outside the city
and rendezvous with
Li Guangwen tomorrow.
After that,
leave with Su Family and Xie Family.
I've prepared a house for you
outside of the city.
If I do not return after three days,
do no wait for me.
Return to Wujiang Prefecture
immediately.
Hanchen.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is a military order.
Do you remember what I said to you?
To repay your appreciation for talents,
I'll wave my sword
and fight to death for my country.
Zhong Ziyan
is willing to die for you, general.
Xingzhou.
After receiving Li Guangwen,
I'll enter the palace with Shen Yan.
If you're reluctant,
I have no choice but to
go against your orders.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Father.
Why are we asked to leave?
I don't want to go.
I'm afraid.
Don't worry.
We're all here.
Your mother and I are here.
Don't be afraid.
That's right.
Your Highness,
why are you asking us
to leave the city out of the blue?
We did nothing wrong.
Hanchen.
Share your problems with us.
Do not make us worry.
Members of royalty are
always involved in strife.
We come from a small place.
We do not have relatives around here.
What do we do if something goes wrong?
That's enough.
Have a seat.
Mother.
(Title deeds)
I've resolved the matter
with Su Tingshan.
Su Chang Ji of Wujiang Prefecture
has returned to its rightful owner.
Mother.
After leaving the city tomorrow,
if I do not show up in three days,
head back to Wujiang Prefecture.
As for the rest,
Bureaucrat Yan will keep you safe.
Hanchen.
Tell me your troubles.
I may not be able to fight in a war,
but I'll be able to stay by your side
through life and death.
Forget it. You're not
capable of fighting battles.
You hold the most important role.
Take care of my family.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Come with me.
Can you
tell me what you're going through?
Are you mad at me
for keeping it from you?
Although we won the battle
at Baichuankou,
we suffered from heavy casualties,
and you know that.
The true reason behind this
was the lack of
provisions.
Back at the capital,
Grand Secretariat Qin
has been looking into
this matter for me.
Chancellor Xu is the perpetrator.
He's corrupted to the core.
Not only him,
even the Crown Prince was involved.
I came back
to overthrow Chancellor Xu
and avenge the brothers
who died at Baichuankou.
Is this the reason why
you're doing all these?
You're afraid that I'd get hurt,
so you're pushing me away.
I'm sorry.
What do you take me as
after marrying me?
My wife.
You must know,
based on the current situation,
the battle tomorrow will be fierce.
I may not be able to return alive.
I know you're a man of righteousness.
As your wife,
I'm not leaving tomorrow.
No.
I do not care.
You must leave.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're not going anywhere
tonight either.
At this moment,
you shouldn't be thinking
about other things.
I know you want me to
be able to remarry
as a virgin,
but I do not care.
If I were to remarry,
I would reincarnate as
a wooden fish in my next life.
Xiaoman.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
I'm spending the night
back at the city.
No matter what happens tomorrow,
if I don't return
at dawn,
return to Wujiang Prefecture.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
You're not a man if you do not return!
I'll be gentle.
Lord Li,
once we arrive at the city,
I'll place you somewhere safe.
I understand.
(Li Guangwen, Li Su's father)
Thank you, Mr. Zhong.
Since the Commandery Prince
wants me to testify,
I...
I'll definitely do my best.
Hold it right there!
Halt!
Lord Li.
At the junction up ahead,
you should get off.
I'll distract them with the carriage.
Remember.
Be very careful.
Look at the time.
Why hasn't His Majesty arrived yet?
The Crown Prince is here.
The imperial edict shall be announced.
I'm gravely ill
and recuperating in the palace.
During this period of time,
the Crown Prince shall act as regent
with the aid of Grand Chancellor Xu.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness,
what's the illness His Majesty
is suffering from?
We're all deeply concerned.
Long live the Crown Prince.
You may all rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Chancellor Xu,
what do you mean by this?
Don't be impatient,
Grand Secretariat Qin.
If you'd like to meet His Majesty,
let's talk after dealing with
Commandery Prince of Julu.
You...
Commandery Prince of Julu is here.
In the War of Baichuankou,
I received new information
about the case.
The Commander of Xiongjie Army,
Zhao Xiaoqian,
do you confess your crimes?
Chancellor, that's a severe accusation.
This is quite an exaggeration
just to give a mere commander
like me some trouble.
As a commander,
you colluded with the enemy
and killed over 10,000 of our soldiers.
Commandery Prince,
do you think who is exaggerating,
you or me?
Your Highness,
I have an appeal.
Go ahead, Chancellor Xu.
Zhao Xiaoqian colluded with the enemy,
disrupted the imperial court,
and harbored vile intentions.
He intended to seize
the position of the Crown Prince.
I
deployed soldiers to protect
the Crown Prince overnight.
However, this is only
a temporary measure.
In order to secure peace
within the palace,
this traitor, Zhao Xiaoqian,
cannot be spared.
I beg for Your Highness
to execute this traitor.
Please execute this traitor,
Your Highness!
Chancellor Xu, you...
Please execute this traitor,
Your Highness!
I'm no longer vigorous.
By respects to the forefathers,
by honour to the deities,
peace ruled the state.
I've governed the state for years.
The Empress is greatly concerned.
I fell ill due to
the overwhelming state affairs.
The Crown Prince, Xiaoze,
is brilliant and intelligent.
His proficiency in
matters of the state
is known to all.
I can leave the state to him
to place the people and
the ministers of court at ease.
(Edict)
You're forcing me to
abdicate the throne.
My Empress,
you surely
gave me a great gift.
Your Majesty, you're not feeling well.
State affairs are never ending.
In order to protect the nation,
I made the decision on
Your Majesty's behalf
to abdicate the throne
to the Crown Prince.
I beg for Your Majesty's approval.
What if
I refuse?
Your Majesty, if you refuse,
I
will give you a hand.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪