♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 32=
(Life is like a dream. Nothing
can be compared to being carefree.)
Zhao Xiaoqian,
are you coveting the throne?
Your Highness, do you
believe such an accusation?
Such insolence.
Such atrocity.
If he is spared,
it will only invite greater troubles.
Your Highness, I beg you
to issue the order.
I beg Your Highness
to execute this traitor.
Your Highness,
you mustn't hesitate.
Look at the state.
Your Highness mustn't allow it
to fall into the hands of a traitor
who colluded with the enemy.
Chancellor Xu.
Your Highness.
I beg Your Highness
to execute this traitor.
- Please execute this traitor.
- Brother.
Don't be afraid, Your Highness.
It will be fine.
Please issue the order, Your Highness.
Arrest this traitor immediately.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince cannot fall.
I've raised the Crown Prince
for many years.
He might not be my biological son,
but
didn't I raise him
like my own?
Back then,
I lost my own child.
Today,
if Zhao Xiaoqian ascends to the throne,
Xiaoze will not be spared.
I have come this far.
Please do not blame me
for being ruthless.
Chancellor Xu, you,
and the Crown Prince
colluded for personal gains
and you colluded to commit malfeasance.
Did you really think that
I had no idea what you did
or I was unperturbed?
Is that so?
I just considered the fact that
you two are my wife and my son,
and the other one is
the pillar of the imperial court.
I wanted to secure your dignity.
What's the matter?
I can tolerate it all.
Can't you be a little more patient?
Zhao Xiaoqian is coveting after
the position of the Crown Prince.
I'm left with no choice.
Qiongniang.
You and I are joined in matrimony.
Did you think that
I would abandon you?
You're the Empress,
the mother of the nation.
You could've sustained your position
for the rest of your life,
earned a great reputation,
and been praised by
the generations to come.
Isn't that great?
Why did you get yourself involved
in the crimes of treason and corruption?
Yes.
I may be the Empress,
the mother of the nation,
but do you have any idea
how much suffering and anguish
come with that glory?
I lost my own child back then.
Zhao Xiaoqian
was the cause of my miscarriage,
and yet you forced me
to treat him as my own son.
I came to this point
all because of you.
You may loathe me or
condemn me all you want.
I'll accept it all.
The Crown Prince
is my only hope.
Back then,
he wasn't the one responsible
for the loss of your child.
You're lying to me again!
Back then,
the imperial physician claimed
that your pregnancy
was unstable since the beginning.
The child passed away
before parturition.
You refused to believe it.
You harmed Xiaojie because of this.
Right now,
you're here to harm me.
Qiongniang.
I've always treated you
with care and tolerance.
Did you know that
I've never intended to
renounce the Crown Prince?
No matter how impressive
Zhao Xiaoqian is,
he's not of my own flesh!
General,
the harem is a forbidden ground!
Get out of the way!
Do not move!
Hurry up!
Arrest this traitor immediately
and execute him on the spot!
Chancellor Xu, are you issuing
an edict on His Majesty's behalf?
Your Highness.
I have an appeal to make.
I request for the impeachment
of the Grand Chancellor, Xu Huan.
He embezzled the military funds,
colluded with others for personal gains.
and accused faithful officers.
He's a pest of the country!
All counts of allegations
are listed in the appeal.
The relevant evidences
are accounted for in the appeal as well.
Chancellor Xu, if you do not believe me,
should I recite the following counts
to the entire court
of your exploitation and corruption
in Jingdong and Jingxi Roads,
how you accused and
framed the fellow officials,
and also,
how you embezzled
the military funds of Baichuankou?
You traitor!
What a load of nonsense!
Whether they are utter nonsense,
you may not believe my claims,
but you should believe
your old associate,
Li Guangwen.
Don't you think so?
Li Guangwen, your sinful servant,
is here to greet Your Highness.
Long live the Crown Prince.
You...
I tried to rush over,
but I couldn't catch up.
I fought the war alongside you
for years.
Put the blame on me.
In the past, you entered
the Prince's Mansion
and the imperial palace with me.
We've been married for decades.
We've been through thick and thin.
At our old age,
you're forcing me to abdicate my throne.
Did I allow you to adopt Xiaoze
and make him the Crown Prince
only to
bring such woe upon myself?
Tell me.
Why did I crown you Empress?
Why did I make Xiaoze Crown Prince?
I did all those to grant
you honour and authority,
and for you to share my burdens
and govern the harem.
For the past bond and our affection,
I cosseted you.
I can't believe I've allowed you
to come to this point.
It seems like
everything I did for you was a mistake.
Your Majesty.
For me to come this far,
it's all your fault.
It's all your fault.
It's all your fault!
How dare you point a dagger at me?
Come on.
Go ahead and stab me.
Stab me.
Stab me
and you'll be able to obtain
everything you wanted!
Stab me!
I'm fine!
Guards!
Your Majesty.
Watch over her.
Help me get changed.
I'm attending the court meeting.
Such disrespect before the Crown Prince.
You accused the grand chancellor
of the nation,
and connived with a criminal openly.
You've committed treason and heresy.
Zhao Xiaoqian.
For each claim you made,
your execution
is a show of mercy.
Drag Li Guangwen away.
Do not move an inch!
Commandery Prince,
if you refuse to abide,
I'm afraid this scholar
will be executed first.
Three years ago,
we went to Baichuankou
and joined the army under General Xu Zi.
Back then, I told you that
I, Zhong Ziyan, am willing
to die for your sake.
Listen up, Zhao Xiaoqian!
It's the same today!
The War of Baichuankou
lasted for three years.
We were almost killed for many times.
Numerous brothers
were starved to death
on the battlefield due to
the lack of provisions.
Li Guangwen.
I'm going to ask you again.
Do you
concede or not?
Back then, you said that
you'll have justice served
for the brothers
who died at Baichuankou.
Hanchen,
today is the day.
Do not stop!
Send him away!
Hold on!
Commandery Prince,
you want to challenge me?
You have a long way to go.
However, I'm afraid
you ran out of time.
Guards,
behead this traitor at once!
Hanchen!
Ziyan!
Ziyan.
You'll be fine.
You're going to be all right.
Don't worry.
Your Highness, you asked me
why I am so obsessed about
undertaking the imperial examinations?
Stop talking. Do not say a word.
Send for the imperial physician!
It's because injustice
exists everywhere.
I'm
going to reclaim justice.
Today...
If I died here today,
I would be
considered a martyr,
isn't that right?
Hanchen.
Stop talking.
You're going to be fine.
I'm taking you to the Spring Exam.
I'm going to attend
your Qionglin Banquet.
It's going to be all right.
Everything will be all right.
I'm not going.
I'm going to join our fellow brothers.
I recall
how cold the winter was
back at Baichuankou.
You told me
to put on two layers of Armour.
The state must be prioritized.
Baichuankou must be prioritized.
Zhong Ziyan...
Ziyan.
Ziyan!
Stop standing around.
Hurry up and execute the traitor.
You...
Why are all of you
arresting me instead?
Archer of fifth camp, Qiu Da'er,
was enlisted for eight years.
He was shot to death by arrows
in the fight at Gu City.
Deputy General Wang Zhi,
canon fighter of third camp,
was enlisted for three years.
He died of illness.
Ruan Xiaoyi,
military officer of eighth camp,
was enlisted for a year.
He died when guarding the city.
Qin Wei, foot solider of fourth camp,
was enlisted for 20 years.
In the fight at Cliff Liang,
he resisted the enemy.
He was killed after being
encircled by the army.
Huang Liu, scout of second camp,
safeguarded the escort
of the last batch of provisions,
and he was shot dead by a fire arrow
in his chest.
Military strategist of third camp,
Zhong Ziyan,
was killed in the palace
for eliminating
the evil grand chancellor.
Do these names
ring a bell to you, Chancellor Xu?
Because of your greed
for military funds and provisions,
all of them died in vain at Baichuankou!
When you fall asleep at night,
do they haunt you in your dream?
For the 10,000 lives lost,
today,
your debt will be paid!
I urge Your Highness
to investigate Xu Huan!
His Majesty has arrived!
Long live the Emperor!
Do I still exist as the Emperor?
Before the court,
things are getting out of hand.
You may all rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Li Guangwen, your sinful servant,
the previous secretariat,
is here to greet Your Majesty.
Long live the Emperor.
Your Majesty,
I offer my life to
impeach Chancellor Xu.
This confession has
recorded the evidences
of Chancellor Xu's
attempts to control the court
and embezzle the state fund
over the years.
Chancellor Xu is corrupted.
He colluded with others
for personal gains.
He embezzled the military funds
and seized the state's possessions.
He's guilty of accusing the innocent.
Such allegations add up
to a total of 146 crimes.
I seek Your Majesty to
attend to this matter.
Slander!
Accusation!
Your Majesty.
(Appeal)
Xu Huan
has served the court as
an official for over thirty years.
As the grand chancellor,
what have you been doing over the years?
Did you really take me for a fool?
With respect to your position
as an official of the court,
I chose to be lenient.
As a result, you committed such
vile and unforgivable crimes.
Even only one of these claims
is enough to annihilate
your entire clan!
Your Majesty.
I...
I confess to my crimes,
Your Majesty.
I deserve death.
I beg for Your Majesty's mercy
for the sake of my past contribution.
Arrest him.
Seal his property for investigation.
As for the associates involved,
none will be spared.
Grand Secretariat Qin,
you shall be in charge.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Take him away.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Arrest the criminals,
executed those who deserve death,
and do
everything that should be done.
My heart aches, my Empress.
I'm aggrieved because
my family twisted the truth
and lost moral sense.
My family colluded with others
to bring me harm.
Should I place you under investigation
or let you go?
It's all my fault.
I was blinded by lust and greed.
I went astray.
However, Xiaoze is innocent.
He's still young.
He had no idea what's going on.
He was being used by me.
I'm willing to bear the consequences
for all the crimes.
Your Highness.
I'm not your biological mother.
I adopted you in the first place.
Today,
there's no need to put up
an act of benevolence.
I'm accountable for my own actions.
I'll not implicate anyone.
Mother!
Shut up!
I'm not your mother!
Qiongniang,
we're husband and wife.
I'll not harm you.
You shall leave the imperial palace
for cultivation at the temple
and reflect sincerely
on your wrongdoings.
In this life,
we shall never meet again.
I
thank Your Majesty for your grace.
Mother.
Get up.
I dare not.
Let me ask you.
During the day at Zichen Palace,
why didn't you issue the order
to execute Zhao Xiaoqian?
He's my elder brother.
You knew that the Empress would
be executed for her crimes.
Why did you address her
as your mother?
Her Highness is my mother!
My son.
Remember the decision you made today.
This
is known as benevolence.
Although you're weak,
I still value
the kindness and benevolence
in your heart.
You must work harder
in order to
govern the people
with kindness and benevolence
in the future.
(Shenwu Gate)
You won.
You've finally avenged your brother.
Are you satisfied?
Did you think that I returned
to avenge my brother?
Isn't that so?
Everything I did today
was for the Crown Prince's sake.
I did this to make sure I'm assisting
a wise successor of the throne.
Even my brother
wouldn't want me
to return for revenge.
I returned
so that the people I love
may live in peace and prosperity.
Brother Hanchen,
do you see me as your rival
as everyone else are saying?
Do you seek to replace me
by killing me?
You're my little brother.
Under no circumstances
would I ever harm you.
How should I treat you then?
That's your decision to make.
You may view me as your subject,
your elder brother,
or an enemy.
Regardless what you think of me,
make sure it's the right decision.
What's the right decision?
One made without
the influence of others.
Discern right from wrong for yourself.
Protect the righteous.
Punish the unruly and the evil.
That's the right decision.
I bid you farewell, Your Highness!
Long live the Crown Prince!
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I've completed the task
Your Majesty entrusted to me.
Chancellor Xu will be executed.
The Ministry of Justice
has begun the investigation.
The associates involved
in the imperial court
were all arrested.
Property of the remaining members will
be confiscated for investigation.
You've finally achieved
what you wanted.
This isn't just what I wanted.
It's also what Your Majesty wanted.
A clean imperial court
where the corrupted are eliminated.
The people of the nation
will eulogize Your Majesty's brilliance
and thank Your Majesty
for the immense grace.
Spare the flattery.
Do you know that, by doing this,
we have lost the grand chancellor.
More than half of the officials
are involved.
The imperial court is finally clean,
but the talents within the court
have withered as well.
Your Majesty may launch the imperial
examinations to recruit talents.
With a clean imperial court,
talents will not go undiscovered.
What about you?
What do you seek?
I'd like to guard the borders
at Baichuankou.
Don't you want the position of
the Crown Prince?
A future without Chancellor Xu
implies the imperial court is safe
from the corrupted.
I have faith that one day,
Xiaoze will be able to
govern the nation on his own.
You're flattering
the Crown Prince as well.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Look at you.
I've never seen you concede,
brat.
You should stay.
Help me look after Xiaoze.
I'm not meant to be an official.
I'm used to brawls and fights.
I wouldn't be comfortable
if I stayed anyway.
I'll head to Baichuankou
to defend the borders for you and Xiaoze
and secure peace for you.
However, before I leave,
I have two favors to ask.
I seek Your Majesty's approval.
Speak.
I'd like to request for
a title granted to
military strategist of third camp,
Zhong Ziyan.
I request for a title
to be given to his mother.
Granted.
What's the other request?
I have a concubine named Xie Xiaoman.
She's from Yuyangli Village,
Wujiang Prefecture.
Her family is upright and kind.
After all that I've done,
I hope Your Majesty will no longer
betroth anyone else to me.
I request for an imperial edict
to make Xie Xiaoman
Commandery Princess Consort,
and allow her to return
to Baichuankou with me
for the rest of our lives.
I'll be eternally grateful
for your grace.
Your concubine, Xie Xiaoman?
Yes.
All right.
Granted.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
My son.
Have you
blamed me, your father, for all these?
I'm a subject
of yours.
I'm Your Majesty's servant.
I'll always be
the Crown Prince's servant as well.
If that's the case,
from now on,
you'll no longer
call me father.
I, your servant,
shall excuse myself.
All shall heed.
My nephew,
Commandery Prince of Julu,
Grand Commandant,
Imperial Grand Governor, Zhao Xiaoqian,
is kind and just.
He's proficient in both literature
and martial arts.
His filial piety and respect
reach the heaven.
His undivided loyalty for the nation
exceeds the sun and the moon.
Besides being the Commander
of the imperial court,
he shall be promoted as Grand Commandant
of all four borders of Guanxi.
He shall be dispatched to the borders.
He shall depart tomorrow.
By exception, the degree holder
of Jinshi, Zhong Ziyan,
showed great respect
and great loyalty.
His loyalty has touched the nation.
He shall be promoted as
Prefect of Administration.
He shall be buried as
a noble official of the court.
Daughter of Xie Family
of Wujiang Prefecture
shall be promoted as Duchess of Wuguo,
and granted the title,
Commandery Princess Consort of Julu.
The end.
Hanchen.
What are you doing here?
Are you missing Brother Xiaojie?
I'm missing you.
There is plenty of time
for you to miss me.
Don't be impatient.
Do you regret
becoming my learning partner?
I'd never regret it.
Why?
Because you're Zhao Xiaoqian
and I'm Zhong Ziyan.
I, Zhong Ziyan, am willing
to die for your sake.
You should hurry home.
Xiaoman is waiting for you.
In time to come,
I'll not be able to walk with you.
Till here.
My husband.
Let's go home.
(The grave of Prefect of Administration
of Song, Zhong Ziyan)
Xingzhou,
we're leaving the capital.
Will you blame us?
Don't worry.
Xingzhou isn't a petty person.
Goodbye,
Xingzhou.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
(Qingtai Gate)
(One year later, Wujiang Prefecture)
Watch out.
I said that you're not allowed out here.
You're not allowed out here.
What are you talking about?
You insisted on coming outside.
What should we do
if you tire my eldest son out?
How annoying.
Watch your step.
Father. Mother.
Is there
anything that I could help?
Oh mine.
Forget it.
Take care of my grandchild.
That would be the greatest help.
That's right, Minggu.
We don't need your help.
Get some rest.
Watch her well.
Yes.
I asked her to stay in the room,
but she wouldn't listen.
She insisted on coming here to work.
Whose fault is it?
It's all your fault.
I can barely straighten my back
or bend forward.
It's all your fault.
How is it my fault?
It's all
because of that brat inside of you.
Isn't that right?
I'll get him to apologize
after he's delivered.
Yan Boyang, what are you talking about?
Okay, my fault.
I need to nourish my body.
Where's Hanchen?
Is he absent today?
He sprained his waist
from excessive training
a few days ago.
He's recuperating in the barrack.
You're running late.
General Xu is going to reprimand you.
Of course.
A few days ago, General Xu said,
as the commander,
all I do is stay with you.
You should hurry up then.
I asked Shi Deng'er to
apply leave for me.
I've trained them consecutively for
seven to eight days.
Even a machine
needs to get some rest with his wife.
Sleep with me for a while.
I don't want to sleep with you.
Who's going to sleep with me
if you're not going to?
Go ahead and run.
Listen to me.
Do not even think of leaving
without sleeping with me.
Stop running.
Come here.
What's going on with your lady?
Whenever His Highness sees her,
he always is captivated.
What's going on with
your Commandery Prince?
Whenever he sees my lady,
he wouldn't be able to walk.
Commandery Princess Consort
sure is lucky.
In the next life,
if I was able to meet a man
like His Highness,
I'll marry him at all cost.
Get over here!
Stand here.
(The end)
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪