♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪Just in a second♪
♪Wild flame♪
♪Is about to blow up my sweet dream♪
♪It speeds up my heartbeat♪
♪I rush in♪
♪My body becomes the iron wall♪
♪I am willing♪
♪To light up hopes with my intentions♪
♪I want to♪
♪Change their times with my life♪
♪I will♪
♪Return to your side♪
♪Woah♪
♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪The alarm rings♪
♪I travel across the burning waves♪
♪We spread our wings of the guardian♪
♪On our journey to the other end♪
♪We live up to our courage♪
♪We carve our burning medals♪
♪Oh♪
♪Our youths bloom♪
♪We are not living in vain♪
♪We wear our burning medals♪
[The Flaming Heart]
[Episode 2]
(Is this 119?)
(There's a fire in Fujia.)
[Nanjing Fire and Rescue Team - Command Center]
We received a report
of a fire in Fujia.
[Jiangsu Nanjing Fire and Rescue Team]
Please move out of the way!
Find our rescue plan
for this neighborhood.
Yes.
Quickly assess the fire situation.
How is it?
Luo Jie.
Hurry and release two deck guns
to control the fire.
Understood.
Chief Chen.
The origin should be near Unit 410.
Ask Luo Jie to check
if the fire is in the room before
or behind Unit 410.
I will take a team to search the fifth floor.
Okay.
Stay safe.
Chief Chen. I'll be the safety officer again.
You go help Huo Yan with the search and rescue.
Put your walkie-talkie on channel one.
Jiang Tong!
You'll be the safety officer this time.
Luo Jie.
What's the situation?
Chief Chen, I'm almost on the fourth floor.
One, two, three!
Chief Chen, we're on the fourth floor.
Preparing to put out the fire.
Luo Jie, Luo Jie. What's the situation?
Chief Chen.
No open fires in the hallway.
The rescue team can come in now.
Copy that.
Be careful.
(Don't worry!)
Huo Yan.
You can start the search and rescue.
Copy that.
(Be careful.)
Everyone be careful.
The temperature of the door has gone down.
Prepare to break in.
Prepare the water gun!
Follow closely!
The hallway on the fourth floor is clear.
Follow me.
[Nanjing Emergency Center]
Wang Da Yin, I'm going this way.
Lift the gun higher!
Chief Chen, we found the origin of the fire
on the bottom of the fourth floor.
Be careful.
Jiang Tong!
Yes!
Make sure to comfort the crowd!
Yes, sir!
Someone told us that
there are still people trapped upstairs!
The injured person coming down,
prepare to receive!
Hurry.
Careful.
Slowly.
Take this off.
I'll leave him with you!
Okay.
His breathing is off and needs oxygen.
Go to the hospital first.
Be careful, the gas tank is coming down.
Be careful!
Away from the crowd!
Wake up.
Ack!
The fire is burning again!
Hurry! Aim the deck gun higher!
There is a perfume factory nearby.
It's a safety hazard!
Jiang Tong, go take a look!
Doctor Yan!
Run!
Here!
Hurry, give me the child!
Hurry, come over, Doctor Yan!
Hurry, Doctor Yan!
Doctor Yan! Doctor Yan!
Take the child away!
Doctor Yan!
Hurry! Someone's inside!
Chief Chen, the fire flared up again,
but we've put it out.
We're coming down now.
Alright, copy that.
Luo Jie!
Alright.
Chief!
Please help Doctor Yan!
She's still inside
and trapped by the fire!
What?
Who?
Yan Lan, Doctor Yan.
Please save her!
Chief Luo!
Little Mole! Little Mole!
What are you doing?
Chief Luo!
Get out of my way!
You don't even know the situation.
What can you do?
Do you know why I came to the fire and rescue team?
What are you doing?
Don't forget you have to
obey commands!
Huo Yan, Huo Yan.
The side of the building is on fire.
There is medical personnel inside.
Can you see what's going on inside?
Copy that.
(Chief Chen.)
(This is Huo Yan.)
The fire started on the first floor
(and is spreading rapidly.)
(Don't let our people go in from the ground floor.)
(Lower the temperature on the outside first.)
(Chief Chen.)
(The east window on the fourth floor is open.)
(It's the best rescue point.)
(Prepare the aerial ladder truck.)
Go up the ladder!
Yes!
You said fourth floor, right?
I'll go to the fourth floor now.
Are you the person that's trapped?
Listen to my command from now on.
(The first floor is going to heat up very quickly.)
(You need to get away from the origin of the fire.)
(Be careful of spreading flames,)
(and follow the stairs up.)
Little Mole!
Use your clothes to cover your nose and mouth.
Stay low
(and close the windows along the way)
(to stop the smoke from spreading back.)
Okay.
Don't rush. Take it slow.
We will definitely get you out.
Little Mole!
Is that you?
(I trust you.)
Nice to work with you again.
(Listen to me carefully.)
(Follow the stairs and go up.)
(I will be with you.)
There's an open door here.
(Don't rush. Close the door first
and look for a towel.)
(Or you can wet your clothes and
stuff them into the door gap)
(to block the smoke.)
Ack!
I can't.
The window is sundries.
There should be a door next to you,
leading to the bedroom.
(Open it.)
(We will get you out from the bedroom window.)
There's a door here.
I can't. This door is locked.
(Break it open.)
(I know you can do it!)
(I believe in you!)
Okay.
I'll try.
Thank you.
Little Mole!
What's your name?
Luo Jie!
I'm here!
Fourth floor, get closer.
Hurry!
Are you alright? Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Stay there. I'm coming over.
Okay.
Hurry!
Ack.
Don't rush. Stand still.
Be careful.
It's alright. You stay still and don't move.
Pull the rope around you.
Don't worry.
You be careful.
Come here.
Okay.
Here, hold onto me.
Hold on.
Where's the little girl?
Don't worry.
She's safe.
Okay.
Little Mole.
Little Mole!
Don't be scared.
I'm here.
Take her!
Yes.
Careful.
Slowly.
You hold onto her.
Okay.
Let's go.
That thrilling?
As long as you're alright.
Are you sure you're not hurt?
I'm really fine.
Then I won't worry about you.
Go back first.
Okay, I'm going first.
Be careful.
Be careful on your way back.
Okay.
Little Mole.
Yeah?
You're awake?
Yeah.
Still dizzy?
I'm fine.
Thanks for coming to save me.
You're a true friend.
Psh.
It's part of my job.
Your face really looks like a mole.
Is it really dirty?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Be careful from now on.
Hmm.
Don't always charge in first.
Got it.
You're alright?
Of course.
I have a few more things to do.
Can I borrow a hose?
Yeah.
[Fire and Rescue]
The team up front is sending a hose over.
Roger that.
(Roger that.)
(It's him.)
Please bring this hose to them.
Okay.
Sure.
[Aerial Ladder Truck - Jiangsu Fire and Rescue]
Who are you looking at?
The guy in the walkie-talkie.
Him?
So he's the person
who helped you before?
Watch me. I'll get his WeChat for you.
Wait here.
No, Bai!
Wait for me.
Hi!
Hi, I'm Bai Xiao Lin.
I'm going first, Luo Jie.
Here's the thing. Our Yan Lan...
Our Yan Lan was complimenting you
and keep saying how great you were.
She also said...
Anyway, she kept complimenting you.
Oh.
Our Yan Lan
is a doctor at Dongnan Hospital.
She's beautiful and kind.
Her admirers are in line all the way to France.
Wow.
A hero
really comes through in the time of need.
She's right.
At our hospital, Yan Lan
is truly exceptional.
She matches very well with you.
What are you doing?
Hurry and add him on WeChat
so that they can get in touch.
Mate, don't pass up an opportunity like this.
I almost forgot.
Got it? Hurry and ask her out.
Can I add you on WeChat?
Here, I'll scan your code.
Here, give me your phone.
I'll scan your code.
Oh.
You get two days off on the weekend, right?
Yeah.
Two days off?
You can accept now.
Okay.
Then I'll message you on WeChat?
I'm leaving, bye-bye!
Oh.
What are you looking at?
Isn't he the handsome guy who comes
to the hospital every day?
Why is he a firefighter?
He's not just a firefighter.
He's also a chief.
Chief Luo?
I'm leaving.
Lamb, beef,
tripe, enoki mushrooms
are all my favorite.
You guys are nice, aren't you?
I'm having a clear soup hot pot,
but you're all enjoying the spicy broth.
That's harsh.
If you can't eat it, smelling it is good too.
You shouldn't eat spicy after getting hurt.
We're doing this for your own good.
I just want one bite.
No!
My gosh, did you guys all learn martial arts?
Drop it.
I have an actual question.
Do you know who Professor Li chose
to help with his research?
I heard about it,
but they haven't decided yet, right?
Right.
Did you not apply for it?
I did.
But they haven't decided yet.
That's good.
You're all here?
Do you want to eat hotpot with us?
No, I'm fine.
I just chatted with Professor Li.
What do you have to discuss with him?
I need to work hard and learn from him
so that I can contribute to his research.
What?
You got picked?
It's a party here.
Professor Ye.
Why aren't you home yet?
Wait.
Professor, you should join us too.
I'll get chopsticks for you.
Right!
It's alright.
I have something to tell you.
Yes?
I have a new study.
It's a study by our hospital and Dongshan Station
on the best practices for cooperation
between medical and firefighting teams.
This study is very important
to see how we can improve
in this area.
You go with me.
Alright.
You're being picky?
I'm looking forward to working together
and presenting a viable plan
in the next few months.
Yes.
Alright, you guys enjoy it.
I'm leaving.
Professor Ye. Will you often
stay in Dongshan Station for this study?
Yes, the Dongshan Station we're working with.
Alright, bye.
Goodbye, Professor.
Bye-bye.
Director Li,
you must understand.
The car accident in the tunnel
affected Han's Pharmaceuticals greatly.
The samples of our monoclonal
antibodies were destroyed.
But please give us the test results
according to our asks first.
This is a hard thing for me too.
We can only give you the results
for the new samples after clinical trials.
Director Li.
Don't worry about things
you shouldn't worry about.
I will give you the new samples soon. Rest assured.
Darling.
Check the group message
[Work hard today too]
and reply.
Mmm.
Why are you mmm-ing?
Check the group message.
Hurry.
Okay.
Look at how great of a friend I am.
How about it?
He's a gentle and comforting long-legged uncle.
Long-legged uncle?
But Luo Jie was right.
This person talks in a strange way.
You just remembered Luo Jie?
I'm telling you.
Even though Wu isn't as handsome as Luo Jie,
he wins by looking more loyal.
I'm telling you, he definitely knows
how to spoil others.
I know you the best.
I know you're not shallow like that.
But you're wrong.
I really am shallow.
I like people who are handsome.
If you like the handsome type,
why aren't you dating Luo Jie?
You... you asked him to have dinner with me?
Right.
I just wanted to thank him.
You're making it into a blind date.
I'm not going.
Or else, you go with me.
Why would I go?
Then I'm not going.
It's not that I can't go.
How about this?
Sunday night,
EN SPACE Restaurant
at the Porcelain Tower of Nanjing.
I already made a reservation for you.
Let me have some of your good luck in love.
What good luck in love?
I got lucky because of my job.
The doctor noticed me.
Doctor?
I mean... we all went on the rescue mission
and wore the same uniform.
Why were you the only lucky one?
You have to be more confident.
I saw it.
He was chatting with her on WeChat
talking about dinner.
Wait, I have to rub his head too.
Alright.
Let me ask you two.
What?
Is it good
for the girl to pay for the dinner?
You really asked her out?
Wait, you really did?
Yeah.
I mean, Wu.
If the girl says she'll treat,
then she's just being polite.
Don't fall into the trap.
Pay attention closely.
I don't think so.
Based on my dating experience,
those who like
people in uniform like us
might be
a rich heiress
or a daughter of a fund.
Just let her pay if she wants to.
Stop kidding around.
Which drama are you watching now?
Please come back to reality.
Comrade Da Yin.
You don't have much dating experience,
so I won't blame you for not understanding.
Wu, it's not embarrassing to marry
into the girl's family.
Stop arguing.
You guys arguing makes me nervous
and anxious.
Don't be nervous or anxious.
Go shower with me.
Wait, Wu.
You can't shower with him.
Why not?
It's not safe.
Li Yan Liang!
You just have to bring that up, right?
No.
Right?
No, no.
Why are you so mean?
I'm going on my own.
I need a minute to cool down.
I'm very angry right now!
I'm sorry, sorry.
Da Yin.
Hello?
[Nurse's Station]
I just came out of Yan's room.
You're not at the hospital?
I bought brown sugar milk tea for you.
It's on your desk.
You just recovered.
Make sure you're getting rest.
Take care of yourself when I'm not around.
Alright, you go then.
I'm hanging up.
Chief Luo.
Me?
Of course you.
Is there another Chief Luo here?
Do we know each other?
Don't you come to our hospital often?
You're also the chief of
our partner organization,
Dongshan Station.
I'm deputy chief.
That's not important.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
That way if something comes up at work,
we can discuss it together.
Or we can also discuss things
that are not about work too.
Come on.
How about this?
You can also ask me about Yan Lan
and what she's up to.
Okay, thank you.
I'll scan your code.
I added you.
Okay.
Let's grab dinner later, Chief Luo.
[Be loyal to the party, be disciplined.]
Reply 1988,
episode 8, scene 26.
You're here?
Right!
Just like that!
Are you feeling numb?
Like your whole body is going soft, right?
This is called
the head pat.
During the first date,
you have to listen more and talk less.
Don't expose your shortcomings to the girl.
What's the most important thing
when having your first date?
It's to show
how different you're treating her from others.
Don't ever treat her differently.
You want the girl to feel
[Must be polite ]
that we're polite and well-educated
[Gentlemen]
like a gentleman.
You need to
keep your distance and be polite
to others.
Towards her?
Be gentle, caring, enthusiastic,
and take initiative.
If you can use actions, then don't use words.
If you can stay silent, then don't use actions.
Just act like this.
Wu, look at me.
Yes.
Yes?
Yes what?
The biggest pet peeve on a date
is only answering with sounds.
She'll feel like you're just skimping.
Chief Huo. Chief Huo.
Wu.
Chief Huo.
I already told you.
I feel like
Da Yin and Yan Liang aren't reliable.
Wu.
I'm not very good at this either.
Chief Huo, don't be so humble.
No matter what, you're more
dependable than those two.
Right?
How about this?
Pretend that you're on a date with me.
Oh.
Let's have a chat.
Hello, Wu Zheng.
Nice to meet you.
What are we eating?
I'm asking you, what are we eating?
Any... anything's fine.
Anything.
Wait, Chief Huo.
I... I'm really nervous.
As soon as you got me into the mood,
I got really nervous.
I... I don't know how to chat.
Do you know what I mean?
Hello?
Chief Chen?
Yes, I'm with Huo Yan.
Chief Chen said
he called you and you didn't pick up.
Oh.
There's a research study he wants
to discuss with you.
Oh, oh.
You can come to the squadron to find me.
I mean, to find him.
Okay.
Bye.
I got it.
Here.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
When the girl talks,
tilt to your side.
The sound will be clearer.
When you answer her questions,
don't rush.
Say what I say.
Got it?
Got it.
You got this.
You got this!
Why isn't he here yet?
Hello, Bai?
Where are you?
Yan Lan.
Something urgent came up.
I can't make it today.
I'm so sorry.
You and him...
Have fun!
Alright, I'm hanging up.
What a true friend.
Brother Wu.
I'm so sorry.
I'm late.
Sorry, I'm late.
No worries, I just got here.
Very nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
Brother Wu, you don't need to do that.
I'm very happy to have met you
through the rescue mission.
We were fated to meet.
But the fire was really scary.
Hello, are you ready to order?
(Just a glass of sparkling water.)
Brother Wu?
Just a glass of sparkling water.
Brother Wu, do you want to order?
That line wasn't for you.
You said
you would tell me more
about Yan Lan at the hospital, okay?
No problem.
[EN SPACE]
This is the place.
I brought my coworkers here before too.
I promise you'll like it.
Does Yan Lan really like this place too?
I don't know.
But...
Chief Luo, what kind of girls do you like?
Do you need to ask?
Besides her, I've never liked anyone else.
Then if the girl you like
is with someone other guys,
will you give up on her?
Impossible!
Besides, giving up is up to me.
It has nothing to do with what she does.
You say that now,
but your actions might speak for themselves.
Let's go.
We'd like to order.
What can I get you?
Brother Wu, what would you like?
The ribeye.
The ribeye. Make it medium, please.
Okay.
I want that too.
We'll have two then.
Alright.
Wait a second.
We'd like to have two too.
Oh, alright.
Please wait.
Little Mole?
Luo Jie?
Chief Luo?
Wu?
Yeah.
You... you are...
Since we all know each other,
let's sit together.
Alright, together.
Here, together.
I'll sit here.
Relax, it's alright. Don't say anything.
You know each other?
-Yeah.
We just met.
Brother Wu saved me last time.
I'm here to thank him.
Doctor Yan, don't be shy.
If this isn't a date,
would Brother Wu dress like this?
But someone experienced like Brother Wu
is a good choice.
I don't think Brother Wu is experienced.
He's capable.
Don't joke around.
Being experienced isn't a bad thing.
Little Mole.
Yes?
If you want to thank Wu,
you should have told me.
Wu and I are very close.
I could have thanked him for you.
I can thank him on my own.
(It's fine.)
Oh right. You two are here...
On a date.
To eat.
Isn't that the same thing?
It's not.
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
It's rare
that we're all here today.
It's on me.
This steak is pretty hot.
I'll help you cut it.
It's fine, I can do it.
I got it.
Brother Wu, do you need help?
I can help you.
No need, no need.
That's sweet.
It's done.
Thank you.
Wu, I'll help you cut it.
Luo Jie.
I want mine cut too.
A girl should learn how to take care of herself.
Then what about her?
She's an animal.
Oh right, Brother Wu.
I asked you to have dinner tonight
to express my gratitude to you.
You risked your life to save me.
Well not just me,
but lots of other people.
This is our duty.
As a firefighter...
Rescuing and protecting the safety
of the people and their possessions
is every firefighter's
responsibility and duty.
I should thank you instead.
As a doctor, you're on the front lines...
Rescuing people.
Only by us working together,
can we help save
and protect the public.
Doctor Yan.
Yeah?
Don't forget to thank yourself.
Wu.
Why do you sound like a veteran today?
Ahh.
Brother Wu,
you're making me feel embarrassed.
Wu.
Yeah?
You're trying very hard.
Okay, eat your steak.
It's getting cold.
Brother Wu.
Do you remember when we rescued
the pregnant lady in the tunnel?
I was totally flustered.
Thankfully you were there.
Do you remember?
Ahh...
The tunnel...
Yeah.
I remember at the time...
At the time, he showed the abilities
of a very skilled firefighter.
Back then, Brother Wu also...
He was also very brave,
so we should focus
and finish this dinner with him.
You mean the tunnel?
Right!
Actually, at the time...
Actually...
You didn't think that much.
That's what you should have done.
Luo Jie, stop interrupting.
Yan Lan wants to listen.
Brother Wu, tell us
about how brave you were.
That event
had... had nothing to do with me.
Actually...
The tunnel rescue
was mostly done
by Chief Luo and Deputy Chief Huo.
At the time, Deputy Chief Huo
suggested the plan.
That's why we could save all those people.
The steak is getting cold.
Brother Wu.
I know the chiefs contributed a lot.
But to me,
you helped me twice.
During the tunnel rescue,
I was at a complete loss.
You helped me calm down.
And during the fire,
when I almost gave up all hope,
your voice in the walkie-talkie
gave me hope.
The steak is getting cold!
No.
That... that really wasn't me.
That was the person I mentioned earlier,
Huo Yan, Deputy Chief Huo.
He did all that.
♪I am used to the dark night♪
♪I dare not expect for tomorrow♪
♪I am tired of being strong♪
♪Do I deserve to cry?♪
Was it you?
♪I need time to smile♪
♪Seems like his sight is kissing me♪
♪The moment you come♪
♪My world is lightened up♪
♪Oh baby, you're the only love♪
♪And I just want you by my side♪
♪So fate has made me♪
♪Wait for♪
♪Your appearance♪
♪Oh baby, just take my hand♪
♪And I will never let you go♪
♪Fate will not close our doors♪
♪You're worth waiting♪
♪My love♪
[Tips for Fire Safety]
We always want everything to be convenient.
But putting sundries anywhere
and riding an electric motorcycle
to your doorstep
could be dangerous.
A hallway leads to fire escapes.
If you charge your electric motorcycle
in the hallway,
it'll be like putting
an untimely bomb at your doorstep.
Remember! Leave your motorcycle unattended
and you'll regret being too careless
when there is a fire.
[Fire Safety is Everyone's Responsibility]
♪The wind is full of sweetness when you smile♪
♪I am indulged in you♪
♪Everything about you♪
♪Piles up on a rainy night♪
♪I hand over my heart♪
♪To the rising sun before the dawn♪
♪When you cry, even the stars sigh♪
♪I want to hug you and
shield you from the noises♪
♪The clouds spread when I meet you♪
♪The moon whispers a secret♪
♪The answer to this secret♪
♪Is our promise of love♪
♪I penetrate through your heart♪
♪And hold onto your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪You would know if you were here♪
♪Open your hands and wait for me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I really want to hold your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪