♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪Just in a second♪
♪Wild flame♪
♪Is about to blow up my sweet dream♪
♪It speeds up my heartbeat♪
♪I rush in♪
♪My body becomes the iron wall♪
♪I am willing♪
♪To light up hopes with my intentions♪
♪I want to♪
♪Change their times with my life♪
♪I will♪
♪Return to your side♪
♪Woah♪
♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪The alarm rings♪
♪I travel across the burning waves♪
♪We spread our wings of the guardian♪
♪On our journey to the other end♪
♪We live up to our courage♪
♪We carve our burning medals♪
♪Oh♪
♪Our youths bloom♪
♪We are not living in vain♪
♪We wear our burning medals♪
[The Flaming Heart]
[Episode 4]
Hey, Bai.
Yes?
Is Father Ye's cough getting worse recently?
I think it's lung heat.
Oh, right!
There's wild rock honey here.
I've even seen beekeepers on my way here.
It can treat lung heat.
Help me hold this for a while.
Huh?
What do you want to do?
I'm going to buy some honey.
Don't! It's so dangerous!
I'll be quick.
Just say that I went to the toilet.
Hey, wait a minute!
Take the food with you.
Be careful!
Here, take a bowl.
Yes.
Thanks.
Chief Luo.
Oh.
Thanks.
If I were a girl,
I would propose to him now.
Wu is nice.
He's all good.
Just a bit old.
Do you know how to speak?
If you don't, then don't talk.
That's right.
Excuse me.
Do you sell rock honey here?
Oh.
Yes, come in!
Oh, okay.
You haven't had lunch?
How about you eat first?
I'm waiting for my husband to come back
and eat together.
You have some too?
Thanks, I'm fine. Not hungry.
Then... you go there and choose.
Alright.
This man did not come back all night.
These bees keep buzzing.
My brain hurts from the buzzing!
Sorry.
You said that your husband
did not come back all night.
Has he ever done this before?
He has.
In the past, he'll be back the next morning.
If he doesn't come back in the morning,
I'll go into the mountains to find him.
Which direction did he go?
He went in the direction of Butterfly Valley.
We've checked the weather forecast.
There might be a storm later.
The mountain road will be very dangerous.
I'll help you find him.
I'll come with you!
No need.
I came with the rescue team.
You wait for him at home.
Thank you, Miss!
Be careful!
Don't worry.
I'll be back for the rock honey.
Then stay safe!
Okay!
I'll give you when you return!
[China Fire and Rescue]
Other girls are made of water.
What?
You're made of metal?
Mind your own business. Eat your rice.
It's nothing.
Isn't it just returning after getting injured?
People are iron, rice is steel.
You'll be hungry if you don't eat.
Eat something.
Why can't you stop talking
even when you're eating?
Can you eat properly and leave me alone?
I'm annoyed when I see you!
Hmm.
I'm full!
Such a pity.
There's one more.
Aiyo!
(The beekeeper)
(hasn't returned home for such a long time.)
(He must be in danger.)
(I must find him.)
(I've gone quite far.)
(Still no trace of him.)
I hope he's fine.
Have you all packed up?
-Yes.
Prepare to go!
Yes!
This way!
Eh?
[Jiangsu Fire and Rescue]
Bai.
Yes?
Where's Yan Lan?
She... went to the toilet.
Oh.
Wu!
Give way to us for a bit!
Okay!
Ma, watch your step!
I got it!
Bai!
Huh?
Where's Little Mole?
She...
She went to the toilet!
Right, she went to the toilet.
Chief Luo, you slow down!
You hurry up!
Chief Huo,
let's line up.
Or we'll be the second!
What's the hurry?
Haste makes waste.
Let's get some rest, bros.
Rest.
(According to the GPS,)
(Butterfly Valley should not be far away.)
Li Yan Liang!
Yes!
Do a headcount.
Prepare to go.
Yes!
Hey, Chief Huo!
Yan Lan went to buy rock honey and is not back yet.
Didn't you just say that she went to the toilet?
I...
She... she's afraid that you'll worry.
Where and when did she go?
That way, it's been half an hour.
Chief Chen, Chief Chen!
Bros,
take care of the medical team.
Okay?
[Nanjing Fire and Rescue Command]
That's it.
Yan Lan, I got it.
Don't panic.
I'll send the nearest team to do the rescue.
The drone will soon be at the target location
to locate the direction of the missing person.
Most importantly, don't act without permission.
Do you understand?
I got it.
Yan Lan,
safety first.
Safety first.
Don't worry, Father Ye.
I'll take care of my safety.
Attention, everyone!
Stop training immediately!
It's a state of emergency.
(Comrades,)
(we've received an alarm message
from Doctor Yan Lan.)
(A nearby villager)
(entered the mountains last night
and hasn't returned.)
We will conduct search and rescue
in the mountains right now.
(Huo Yan's team)
(is closest to the incident site.)
Contact Doctor Yan Lan immediately.
(Rush to the site to conduct search and rescue!)
Roger that.
Chief Chen, we can also do it.
Luo Jie's team,
seize the time now.
Lead the team back to the base camp
as fast as possible
(to prepare for the reception.)
(110 and 120 are on the way.)
(Get moving, everybody!)
Chief Chen, roger.
Return to base camp!
Hey!
Can you move?
I'll help you turn over.
Here, careful.
Be careful.
Here.
Lie flat.
Save me!
Let me take a check.
You have a femur fracture.
I have to fix it in place.
Help me.
Okay!
Sir.
You'll be alright. Just bear with it for a while.
(Yan Lan, Yan Lan! I'm Huo Yan.)
(Do you copy?)
I am!
I am Yan Lan.
I've found the person.
I'm fixing his wound now.
(I need a stretcher and first aid supplies.)
The sooner the better.
We're on our way to your location.
(Stay put and wait for us.)
Don't be afraid.
Okay!
Li Yan Liang!
Present!
Check the equipment. Set off!
Yes!
I'll fix your wound in place now.
Sir, don't fall asleep.
I'm done.
Don't worry.
The rescuers are on their way.
Hold on a little longer.
Save me.
We'll save you. Don't worry.
Faster!
[Fire and Medical Joint Training]
Liang,
hit the anchor point. I'll go down.
Yes!
Call for Blue Eagle! Call for Blue Eagle!
(Blue Eagle rogers!)
Request for backup. Request for backup.
(Roger!)
Chief Chen, we've arrived
at the designated location
and found the trapped person.
♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪Just in a second wild flame♪
♪Is about to blow up my sweet dream♪
Slowly.
♪It speeds up my heartbeat I rush in♪
♪My body becomes the iron wall♪
♪I am willing to light up hopes
with my intentions♪
♪I want to change their times with my life♪
♪I will return to your side♪
♪Woah oh oh♪
Hello?
Anyone roger?
Hello? Does anyone copy?
Yan Lan!
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪The alarm rings and I travel
across the burning waves♪
♪We spread our wings of the guardian♪
♪On our journey to the other end,
we live up to our courage♪
♪We carve our burning medals♪
♪Woah oh oh♪
♪The alarm rings and I travel
across the burning waves♪
♪We spread our wings of the guardian♪
♪Our youths bloom we are not living in vain♪
♪We wear our burning medals♪
What happened?
The patient developed traumatic
pneumothorax symptoms.
Immediate intubation is required.
He needs surgery.
His chest is moving up and down.
The patient is breathing.
Fixing is completed.
According to the procedure,
he should be moved to a safe place
as soon as possible
to await the rescue from
professional medical staff.
I am a professional medical staff.
He has a punctured lung,
causing air to enter the pleural membrane
around the lungs.
The high intrathoracic pressure
causes the veins to dilate.
The chest is going up and down.
The left side is weaker than the right.
He is at risk of suffocation
and sudden death at any time.
The storm is coming soon.
If we don't move to a safe place as soon as possible,
we'll all be in danger.
I can feel obvious soft bulges under
the skin and there's crepitus.
It's a typical traumatic pneumothorax.
There may also be blood accumulation
in the chest.
Trust me.
He can't wait for the ambulance to come.
We have to artificially
lower the air buildup in his lungs.
Chief Huo!
There's no time.
The trapped person developed
traumatic pneumothorax.
There's a risk of suffocation
and sudden death at any time.
The on-site medical staff needs to
take emergency measures.
What measures?
It's urgent!
Intrathoracic pressure keeps increasing.
We can't wait for the paramedics!
Huo Yan,
you've learned to beat around the bush, huh?
The patient needs surgery!
(Huo Yan,)
(the most important thing you should do now)
(is to evacuate the wounded)
(from the dangerous place)
and wait for the professionals to do the rescue,
not to perform surgery.
Evacuate immediately!
(Yan Lan, Yan Lan!)
(Little Mole, Little Mole!)
(Are you going to operate on someone
in the wilderness?)
Listen to me.
Evacuate to a safe place first.
(Leave it to Huo Yan.)
(He'll handle it well.)
(Get the wounded out first)
before we talk about the rescue, okay?
The patient needs me.
I won't leave.
The mountain is not equipped for surgery!
(You will ruin your future by doing this!)
Yan Lan!
Yan Lan.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
(Huo Yan.)
(Do you copy?)
Huo Yan rogers.
Transport the wounded up at once.
Stop the surgery!
Chief Chen, trust me.
The patient needs the surgery now.
(I trust you,)
(but people out there only
believe in the results!)
You will only harm yourself and Yan Lan
by doing this!
(You listen to me now.)
(Do what you're supposed to do)
(according to the procedure.)
Yan Lan,
are you confident about this?
Doctors aren't gods.
I don't know if I can save him,
but if you move him now, he'll die.
Do you know
the consequences if the surgery fails?
I know.
Do you know that
if you move him to a safe place now,
you won't need to bear the risk?
I know this too.
Then you still decided to do so?
I must do it
because he's still alive.
I can't leave him to die.
Chief Chen,
this is my decision.
I'll bear all the consequences.
Calm down.
Maybe the situation is not as bad as you think.
Yan Lan is exactly the same as you
when you were young.
And Huo Yan...
is just like how his father was when he was young.
Help me lift up his clothes.
Help me hold this tube.
Okay.
[Alcohol disinfectant]
He's breathing.
The condition of the abdominal
cavity is unknown.
We have to take him to the hospital to check now.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Chief Chen, Chief Chen, Huo Yan speaking.
Speak!
The patient is temporarily out of danger.
How long will it take for Huo Yan and
Doctor Yan Lan to come up?
At least 30 minutes for two trips
of the stretcher.
Okay, I got it.
Come on, be careful!
Yan Lan!
Make way.
(Li Yan Liang!)
Present!
Keep speeding up!
Use the shortest possible time
to pull up the wounded!
Yes!
Be careful.
Stay safe!
Support him.
One, two, three!
Stay safe!
Alright!
Someone's coming out.
Ma Qian Li!
Yes!
Fly lower.
Chief Luo,
it's raining soon over there.
It can't fly any lower.
It's raining soon means that it hasn't rained.
Okay.
Zhi Cheng!
Transport quickly!
Roger!
It still has to be Blue Eagle.
Where's Yan Lan?
Qian Li!
Yes!
Fly lower!
What's going on?
-I'll do it.
-Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Don't worry.
I grew up playing this thing.
No, no. Let me do it, Chief Luo.
Rest for a while.
Okay.
(Huo Yan,)
(move in the northeast direction.)
(Later, I'll update the assembly area)
(to your coordinate system.)
Roger.
Let's go.
Can you still walk?
I feel a bit tired.
[China Fire and Rescue]
[Nanjing Emergency Medical Center]
Chief Luo, are you saving people,
or are you eating melon?
(*being an onlooker)
And it's bitter melon.
You, you!
Why do you faint every time you see me?
No one fainted when they see you.
I'm being relaxed after saving the person!
What's wrong?
Put me down!
I have legs. I can walk on my own!
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
Come on!
Hey!
Since you're so capable
and there's going to be a storm soon,
why don't you think of a way?
I have a way.
♪Every little bit about you♪
How did you find this place?
I just passed by
and saw this little tent.
♪Follow my breath♪
♪Convergence of heartbeat tracks♪
♪Where should I start♪
♪Step by step into you♪
♪Clarity under the eyes♪
♪Warming courage in the palms♪
The weather forecast
is not accurate at all.
♪Will love be in time♪
I have a nickname.
♪There are ripples in my eyes♪
They all call me Little Sun.
Little Sun?
Yeah.
I don't know about Little Sun,
but I know
you're called Big Head.
Big Head, Big Head, no worries about the rain!
Right!
♪Let me shield you from the wind and rain♪
Hey!
What?
Look!
A live one!
What's so strange about a live frog?
That's not a frog.
That's a toad!
♪See where time will accompany the future to♪
♪Every little bit about you♪
Yes.
If you like it, then it's a prince.
If you don't like it,
then it's a toad.
♪Convergence of heartbeat tracks♪
♪Where should I start♪
♪Step by step into you♪
Eh?
Yan Lan!
♪Clarity under the eyes♪
♪Warming courage in the palms♪
♪Love is always in time♪
It seems that Chief Huo is not
good at picking up girls either.
Of course he's not good at it.
He's far worse than me, okay?
About the limited edition mystery box...
are you not angry at me anymore?
It was my fault that day in the first place.
But the thing about you acting as
the domineering president...
I was not being domineering.
You were the domineering one.
Shouldn't you thank me?
I should.
That day...
I ran into your ex-boyfriend.
♪There are ripples in my eyes♪
That's also... That's also what I'm supposed to do.
♪I don't want to see you go♪
Just ignore people like him.
He just wants to rubberneck.
♪Can I still hug you tightly♪
But that day...
you acted quite well.
♪Let me shield you from the wind and rain♪
Then...
I'm irreplaceable?
♪See where time will accompany the future to♪
Kind of.
But there are many irreplaceable people.
Like my dad and mom,
Professor Ye, Bai,
-and...
-Hey, hey!
Enough, enough.
♪The sky will finally be clear♪
I will show up in time from now on.
Okay.
You have to keep your word.
♪I only care about you♪
♪Hugs are just for you♪
♪A little more courage♪
♪I only care about you♪
♪I'm waiting for you behind♪
♪Waiting for your next return♪
I blow you to death! I blow you to death!
♪I only care about you♪
♪I'm waiting for you behind♪
Do an autonomous return.
Qian Li! Keep the drone!
Okay!
♪Waiting for your next return♪
Come on.
We have the same misfortune.
Cheers.
Who has a misfortune?
Hey, look! It's a rainbow!
Hey!
A rainbow!
It's a rainbow!
Huh?
A rainbow!
This rainbow is too ugly.
How is it ugly?
How beautiful and romantic!
Being able to see the rainbow
with someone you like
is also a kind of bliss.
It seems that I'm more blissful than you.
Aiya, Chief Luo!
It's not a big deal and you're already like this.
Isn't it just that the person you like
doesn't like you back?
There are so many people in this world.
The probability of successful matches is so low.
If everyone is like you, not accepting
anyone else but her,
how can people live?
You don't understand.
I've liked her for ten years.
[Jiangsu Fire and Rescue]
[Nanjing Team]
You
grew up too smoothly.
A little setback makes you depressed.
There are so many roads in life.
You can switch to another road
if the road you're on is blocked.
If your love doesn't work out,
you can focus on your career.
If your career doesn't work out,
you can focus on your family.
There's always a way.
It seems that I have been overtaken
on my road of love and career.
It's not the end yet.
You have to catch up quickly.
That means...
I still have a chance, right?
If I say yes,
I'll be lying to you.
But if I say no,
then I'll be lying to myself.
Well...
then it's a yes.
Cheers.
[Rescue]
[Fire and Medical Joint Training]
[China Fire and Rescue]
Aiya!
I'm sorry.
If so many ugly photos are spread,
in the future you can't...
can't get married.
What are these?
Wang Da Yin.
You!
Hey, hey!
Give me the drone.
Delete them! Delete all of them!
I've deleted them!
I've deleted all of them!
This is the only set.
Do you think I'll trust you?
What else can you do if you don't trust me?
Come.
You can get up and catch me!
Hey, no, no.
Sit, sit. You take a break.
I'll get it for you.
Okay?
Do it!
Okay.
Such a mess.
Three, two, one!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Wu, it's your birthday!
Okay, Car King, make a wish!
Hey, bro!
Can you share me a wish?
I wish to become rich!
I want too! I want too!
That... I...
I wish to become a muscular man.
I'll say one too!
I want to marry a rich girl!
I want to open a milk tea shop!
Can non-firefighters make a wish?
I wish to become a Spiderman
and travel between tall buildings...
Enough, enough.
There are only three wishes.
You don't have any more chances.
Quickly do it.
Okay.
My first wish.
I hope everyone gets what they want.
Good!
My second wish.
I hope everyone
is healthy.
-Good!
Good!
Hey,
Wu.
You can't say your third wish out loud.
It won't work if you say it.
Come on!
Cut the cake!
I have to say it.
If I don't,
there'll be no chance anymore.
I've got my paperwork done.
I'm about to leave the fire brigade.
I've even told Chief Chen a few days ago
that we have to say goodbye sooner or later.
But now that I'm leaving,
I feel very sad.
In the past,
I'm very annoyed with Wang Da Yin.
Once I leave,
I don't know who is going to talk so much to me.
And Yan Liang.
I can't see your muscles anymore.
Qian Li
is just like my own younger brother.
Chief Luo,
you always treat me to a meal for no reason.
Chief Huo.
Yes.
I know that you're under a lot of pressure
after you came.
Don't think too much.
I'll support you forever.
My last wish.
I hope that you guys
can return safely
after every patrol!
Brother Wu,
after you leave,
who's going to drive us to patrol?
Qian Li,
don't they still have you?
Brother Wu!
Chief Luo.
Ever since I became the deputy chief,
you never called me Luo again.
Always calling me Chief Luo.
I'm still used to you calling me Luo.
I, the deputy chief, wasn't able to help much either.
I have to let you go in the end.
I don't blame you.
I want to go back to my hometown to take a look too.
My mother's health is also not good.
You can come back any time
when your mother gets better.
Come back to visit us frequently.
I will.
Wu,
Dongshan Station
will always have a place for you.
In our hearts,
there will also always be a place for you.
If you miss home,
just remember to come back to see us.
Okay.
People always tell me that
those of us that used to be firefighters
are brothers-in-arms
and comrades that you can trust.
No one should be left behind.
But in the end,
we still leave this brigade
one after another.
Everyday,
we have to face the separation of life and death.
But we have to be braver day by day
and be even braver to face
the separation of life and death.
Because this is our duty as firefighters.
Today is Car King's birthday.
Don't hold up our rest at night.
Come on!
Cut it!
♪When you cry, even the stars sigh♪
♪I want to hug you and
shield you from the noises♪
♪The clouds spread when I meet you♪
♪The moon whispers a secret♪
♪The answer to this secret♪
♪Is our promise of love♪
♪I penetrate through your heart♪
♪And hold onto your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪You would know if you were here♪
♪Open your hands and wait for me♪
That's about it.
You don't move. Don't move!
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
Don't move.
Pout your lips.
Right.
Okay.
Don't move!
That's about it!
When you look for a husband,
are you willing to find one with
disheveled hair and a dirty face?
A peacock has to spread its feathers
to seek a mate.
On today's occasion,
the whole fire brigade has to come.
It's your first time to appear as
their sister-in-law.
Even if you don't mind losing face,
Huo Yan still wants his face.
What sister-in-law?
It doesn't sound nice.
-Aiyo!
-Sister-in-law?
I haven't done it yet.
Wait... wait a minute.
I ate a bit too much in the morning.
Now I have diarrhea.
I'll do it later.
Your arm, your arm.
Thanks.
Next!
Yan Lan.
What?
Seeing you and Chief Luo are doing well,
as your colleague,
I'm really happy for you.
It's weird that you're talking like that.
Talk properly.
You don't like Luo Jie, right?
I'll be straightforward.
I like Luo Jie.
I want you to help me.
Why should I help you?
Yan Lan,
will you help me?
It's a win-win situation.
The fire brigade is coming
for a medical checkup today.
Luo Jie and Huo Yan will also be here.
If the three of you appear at the same time,
what will happen with Luo Jie
being the King of Jealousy,
you don't need me to tell you, right?
Why don't we work together?
This way, you and your Chief Huo
can have a wonderful time together,
while my Luo Jie and I
can also have
time to get along nicely.
Yan Lan,
I don't get along with you
because our auras don't match and
our Eight Characters aren't compatible.
But this doesn't mean that I'm not sincere
in my relationships.
I'm 100% sincere
in my love for Luo Jie.
If you help me,
I'll definitely not treat you badly.
There are no permanent enemies.
We are friends if we can cooperate.
Let's have good cooperation,
okay?
If you really like Luo Jie,
go for him yourself.
Doctor,
am I doing the ECG here?
Yes.
Come in.
Okay.
Pull
your socks down.
Your name is Ma Qian Li?
Correct.
Lie down and take off your clothes.
We don't have any male doctors?
You are so young,
but you have a quite feudal way of thinking.
Rest assured.
Doctors see no distinction
between men and women.
It will be a little cold.
I'll be done soon.
Don't shake! Don't shake! Don't shake!
Hold on for a while. It'll be over soon.
Don't move. Don't move!
Don't move.
It will be done soon.
It's the last one. Last one.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
What?
I can't touch you?
Don't move when I tell you not to move.
Lie properly.
Please come in.
Doctor Liu,
where's Little Mole?
Yan Lan... went to the toilet!
She'll be back soon.
Chief... Chief Luo, have a seat.
Okay, I'll wait for her here.
Hey!
Eh?
What a coincidence!
I was just thinking about you.
I mean I was just thinking about looking for you.
Right.
It's okay to think about me.
I was thinking about you too.
I'm saying that
I want to see
the results of your physical training.
How did your medical checkup go?
Let me see.
Give it to me!
Why didn't you get your blood drawn?
Draw blood?
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Firefighting is is a job that requires
some special expertise.
Firefighters' weapons to extinguish fires
are not just deck guns and hoses.
In a fire and rescue team,
high-tech equipment such as fire-fighting
and smoke-evacuation robots
and fire-fighting drones have
been popularly used.
When putting out fires in high-rise buildings,
firefighters can also use
drones to break the windows
to facilitate the discharge of smoke and
the spraying of the fire-extinguishing agent.
What other high-tech
fire-fighting and rescue equipment do you know?
[Fire Safety is Everyone's Responsibility]
♪The wind is full of sweetness when you smile♪
♪I am indulged in you♪
♪Everything about you♪
♪Piles up on a rainy night♪
♪I hand over my heart♪
♪To the rising sun before the dawn♪
♪When you cry, even the stars sigh♪
♪I want to hug you and
shield you from the noises♪
♪The clouds spread when I meet you♪
♪The moon whispers a secret♪
♪The answer to this secret♪
♪Is our promise of love♪
♪I penetrate through your heart♪
♪And hold onto your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪You would know if you were here♪
♪Open your hands and wait for me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I really want to hold your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪