♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪Just in a second♪
♪Wild flame♪
♪Is about to blow up my sweet dream♪
♪It speeds up my heartbeat♪
♪I rush in♪
♪My body becomes the iron wall♪
♪I am willing♪
♪To light up hopes with my intentions♪
♪I want to♪
♪Change their times with my life♪
♪I will♪
♪Return to your side♪
♪Woah♪
♪Our battlefield is where the flame lit♪
♪My armor is my blue glory♪
♪The alarm rings♪
♪I travel across the burning waves♪
♪We spread our wings of the guardian♪
♪On our journey to the other end♪
♪We live up to our courage♪
♪We carve our burning medals♪
♪Oh♪
♪Our youths bloom♪
♪We are not living in vain♪
♪We wear our burning medals♪
[The Flaming Heart]
[Episode 3]
[Basic Information]
Hello, Chief Chen?
(Huo Yan.)
(Have you received the files of
Fire and Medical Joint Training?)
Yes,
I have. I am reading it now.
[Dongnan Hospital's F&M Joint Training Plan]
(Luo Jie was supposed to be in charge of this.)
(But he's out for duty now.)
(So you will be in charge.)
(Doctors from the hospital)
(will arrive soon.)
(Are you okay with that?)
Yes.
(Good, I'm hanging up.)
Bye.
Chief Huo,
the doctor for the F&M Joint
Training just arrived.
She is waiting for you downstairs.
Oh.
I won't go.
You will go for me.
If she has any requirements,
just do as you can.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
[Fire Station Affairs Department]
Wait...
Yes?
Nothing.
Just go.
OK.
Wu came to us asking for tips
before he asked you out.
Turns out it was only a mistake.
Here.
[Office]
So much stuff here.
What are they for?
This has always been a storage place before.
Don't worry.
We will tidy things up for you in a couple of days.
Chief Huo's order.
Chief Huo?
What else did he say?
He said...
(Li Yan Liang, Li Yan Liang,)
(there is a visitor for you at the gate.)
OK, roger.
Don't worry, do what you need to do.
OK, just take a trip.
Sure.
I will come to you later.
OK.
[Fight with loyalty! Shine like a sun!]
(Welcome.)
[China Fire and Rescue]
You are here for me?
Yeah.
Do you remember me?
You were the one who rescued me from fire.
You are...
I remember you.
Guan, right?
Yes, yes, that's me!
I am here to thank you today.
Can I add you on WeChat?
OK, OK...
sure.
I...
oh,
we are not allowed to carry
our phones during training.
That's not a problem. I will add you.
What's your WeChat ID?
OK, OK.
It's my name.
Li Yan Liang.
OK.
I sent the friend request.
Be sure to accept it.
I will, definitely.
Whenever you want to have some cake,
just tell me on WeChat.
Birthday cake,
ceremony cake, we take all kinds of order.
And we also do deliveries.
Twenty percent off for all orders
from your station.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Goodbye.
What are you looking at?
What can we say?
Good-looking guys
are killing it.
Hello?
[Nanjing Fire and Rescue Team Command Center]
Hello, this is 119 emergency service.
How can I help you?
(We have people stuck.)
(Location: Dongshan Station Storage.)
Wait,
that's right here.
Hello?
Anybody there?
Help me!
Be quick.
Coming.
Oh, good.
Please get me out.
What...
Is it that funny?
Help me out!
How...
how did you get yourself stuck like this?
I will do it myself.
Stop laughing.
Don't move.
Let me handle it.
♪I am tired of being strong♪
♪Do I deserve to cry?♪
♪I need a smile sometimes♪
♪Seems like his sight is kissing me♪
♪The moment you come♪
♪My world is lightened up♪
♪Oh baby, you're the only love♪
♪And I just want you by my side♪
♪So fate has made me♪
♪Wait for♪
♪Your appearance♪
♪Oh baby, just take my hand♪
♪And I will never let you go♪
♪Fate will not close our doors♪
♪You're worth waiting♪
Are you alright?
♪My love♪
Yes.
♪There is a person in this world♪
You are so bad at balancing.
We have professional physical training here.
You can
join us then.
No need.
Wait, wait.
♪The wound heals♪
♪I can't lose sight of your figure♪
No need to tidy up yourself.
We will help you with it
when we have breaks in the evening.
♪Sometimes I really need your hug♪
Thanks.
♪Seems like the moonlight is warming me♪
You're welcome.
I just don't want you to
get your head stuck again
and waste our time.
♪The world is lit up again♪
Don't worry.
If I ever get stuck here again,
I would rather die than call you.
♪And I will never let you go♪
OK.
♪Fate will not close our doors♪
Good luck then.
♪You're worth waiting♪
Big Head.
♪My love♪
Big Head?
♪There is a person in this world♪
Later we should organize
those dummies
for this afternoon's training.
OK.
Oh, Yan Liang,
carry some more.
Wow,
Yin,
university students today are impressive.
So good at this high-tech stuff.
[Focus on practice, train the best]
Your left wing is a bit lower.
Adjust it.
Sure.
Watch for wind direction.
That's useful.
Thanks.
Ma.
Leveled yourself up, didn't you?
Got familiar with our newbie firefighters
in such a short amount of time.
I... I was just looking around.
What's so special
about that little plane?
You have to get yourself involved?
You know how to do it.
Look at them.
Not training when they should.
Right?
Come on,
stand still.
Let me show you what a squad leader should be like.
Check it out, this is what a squad
leader should be like.
You,
newbie firefighters,
gather now.
Come on.
Move faster.
OK.
Where are you standing?
Stand where I am.
Did you save that space for me?
Do you all think
you are already well-trained
and no need to train more?
Yeah?
Let me tell you.
Those small inventions of yours,
we also made them when we were young.
These are just fancy things.
Nothing important.
For a firefighter,
the most important thing is to go inside the fire
and save lives.
Will this toy of yours do that?
What's wrong with you?
Did you request for moving?
I request.
Let's go.
I know
some of you have opinions for me.
"You are just a high school graduate.
What makes you think you can teach us?"
Because I am the squad leader.
You might think you are here
just for an experience,
to elevate yourself.
But to me,
you are no different from normal firefighters.
I treat you all the same.
So
save that irrogance of yours
in front of me.
Arrogance.
What?
Did you request to talk?
I request, it's "arrogance", not "irrogance"!
Right.
They're indeed university students.
Have such literacy.
Well,
you don't agree with what I said?
If so, let's have a match.
We shall see if your toy is more useful
than my years of training.
You dare to challenge me?
What happens to the one that loses?
The lost one will take the punishment,
which will be decided
by the one who wins.
No problem.
In position.
Ready?
Go!
This one is faster.
Good job.
Here comes the squad leader.
Squad Leader,
you lost.
I want you to go to the broadcast station,
get a speaker,
and apologize to us university students.
I lost?
Apologize?
You cheated.
You were playing with a small plane
and you switched to a huge one.
The wind was so strong that I could barely stand.
How can you break your own words?
You are a coward.
Who are you calling a coward?
You. You are a coward!
Do you dare to follow me to the tobacco barn?
Of course!
Good.
Get your protective clothing, let's go.
Sure.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Use this walkie-talkie to contact me
when you are in need.
Don't call 119 anymore, please.
Do you know how to use it?
Smart.
Try it.
Huo Yan, Huo Yan,
do you copy?
This is Huo Yan, copy.
Good.
Then...
let me show you around the station.
Get yourself familiar with the place
that you will be working at.
OK.
Right.
That
is our reception hall.
And that...
Chief Huo.
Chief Huo, Chief Huo, Chief Huo.
Chief Huo!
Calm down, what's going on?
Wang Da Yin and Jiang Tong...
Just say it out.
Wang Da Yin and Jiang Tong are having conflicts.
They are doing some "firefighting matches".
Come check it out.
I have something to do now.
Take a trip yourself.
OK.
Use that walkie-talkie if you are in need.
Got it.
Why did you stop?
Go on.
Tell me.
What the heck is going on?
Chief Huo,
we were just messing around.
Nothing to worry about.
Ma Qian Li has told me.
I am really curious.
Why do you fight every day?
He is looking down at firefighters who
graduated from universities.
He always picks on us.
We will never fight again!
I promise not to bother our leader again.
Whenever we are experimenting
with our new equipment,
he would laugh at us.
He did so today too.
He doesn't even admit that he's lost.
Chief Huo.
The drone...
Stand there.
Putting out fire with a drone.
What do you think?
A fire-fighting drone
is specially invented for putting out a fire
at a high altitude.
What a useless thing!
We have heavy rescue trucks,
ladder trucks, and water cannon fire trucks.
And our firefighters can climb the stairs too.
What's the point of using that?
There are time and height restrictions
to a ladder truck and a water cannon.
I am sure you know how many high-rise buildings
there are in Nanjing.
Time is the key to firefighting, okay?
Firefighters used to carry two pails
of water up the buildings.
Why can't we do that?
That's the past!
We are talking about the present now!
We can do that now too!
So what? Did I say we can't?
Are you looking down at our drone?
(Chief Huo! Chief Huo! There is a mission for you.)
(You need to bring Doctor Yan out
for an operation.)
Did I say I'm looking down on you?
Got it. I'll be right there.
Are you looking down on our training?
Did I say I am looking down on our training?
If I am looking down on our training,
what's the point of me being here?
Huo... Chief Huo has left!
So what?
Are you still going to argue with me?
Come on!
-Come on!
I'm not arguing with you!
I don't even want to argue with you.
[Jiangsu Fire and Rescue]
[Nanjing Team]
[Luo Jie]
Luo Jie. What's wrong?
My meeting just ended.
What are you doing?
I am applying my mask.
Is everything okay after joining our team?
Not bad.
No one angered you, right?
Tell me if someone makes you unhappy.
I'll make them apologize to you one by one.
In that case, I really want him to apologize to me.
Who?
Who bullied you?
(No.)
I was kidding. It's fine.
I shall end our call here.
I need to wash my face.
See you...
Tomorrow.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
You're so pretty today.
You look younger.
Did Auntie buy this for you?
My mother forced me to wear this.
You look good on it.
Don't you tell anyone else.
Hey! Stop drinking.
You have high blood pressure recently.
What are you doing?
Let me take a picture.
No way!
Just one picture.
Quite strong.
Hey!
Brother.
Move aside.
I want to sit with Sister Yan Lan.
Okay.
You shall sit here.
My little sister wants to sit in the middle.
She wants to sit with you.
Yes. She wants to sit with her sister.
Luo Jie is so much older than her,
but he always takes care of her.
Yes.
My son only looks cold outside.
He's very caring inside.
His occupation is the only thing
that I am worried about.
Look! His father's having some health issues.
It's hard to maintain his business.
He doesn't even offer to come back
and help his father.
Oh, right!
Lan!
Why don't you help me to talk to him?
Jie listens to you since young.
Mom.
Look how suitable Luo Xiao Yan is
to be the heir of our family business!
Look!
She is so smart and willing to
take over our dad's position.
You should train her instead.
You lost the older one.
So don't you lose the younger one too!
What are you saying?
Auntie.
I think firefighters are very good.
They are heroes who risk themselves.
Many people admire firefighters.
You should be proud of him instead.
Come on!
Having one of you
as a hero who rescues people is enough.
When you get married,
one of you needs to take care of your family.
Yes.
Hey! Lan.
My son isn't smarter than you
since he was young.
He shall take care
of the family instead.
Mom.
Auntie. I'm just...
We haven't planned so far ahead yet.
Mainly, Yan Lan...
She isn't ready to date yet.
You're making us awkward.
Look at you, Luo Jie.
Both of you grew up together.
You are childhood sweethearts.
Moreover...
Our families... Four of us are good friends.
We are so close.
What a destiny.
Yes!
Yes.
Lan.
I have pre-approved you
as my daughter-in-law.
Yes.
I have pre-approved you as my son-in-law too.
Au... Auntie.
Luo Jie and I are good friends.
We are best friends. Am I right?
Yes. Forever.
Lan.
-Come on!
-Let's eat!
Cheers!
Come on! Cheers!
Come on!
Since you are firefighters who just
graduated from universities...
Since you know nothing...
Sir!
I shall explain it to you one last time.
I wasn't scared.
I just didn't want to
fool around with you, immature people!
You never do a proper job!
But you always fool around!
Who taught you this posture?
Why isn't learning to fly a drone a proper job?
Squad Leader!
You should be more open-minded.
Who said that learning to fly a drone
isn't a proper job?
You can learn to fly a drone privately.
Why do you have to do it publicly?
You distracted our usual training.
You can't do that!
Aren't they the same thing?
In this new generation,
learning to use new firefighting
and rescue technologies
should be part of our training in the first place.
Am I right?
Yes.
Who allowed you to talk?
Did you make a request?
I request!
Can't I correct you?
You always talk back.
Are we chattering here?
Jiang Tong!
Come out!
Get ready for push-ups!
What are you looking for?
How boring are push-ups!
Let's do that instead!
What? Which one?
This one.
That one?
Stop joking around, okay?
When that is spun around,
you need to support yourself solely
by your arms.
If you fail to support yourself and fall,
your dream to be a firefighter will be doomed...
Make a request before you speak next time!
Yes!
The passing mark for a gyroscope at Nanjing
is 20 rounds in two minutes.
If I am able to complete that,
please take back
your words about us fooling around.
Learning new technologies isn't a foolish thing.
Stop having prejudice.
You should be more open to new things.
You're still so stubborn.
Alright.
Alright!
I shall fulfill your dream.
Come on!
Are you sure? Don't overexert yourself.
Stop your nonsense.
Why are you rushing?
I'm not done yet.
It's not too late to regret now.
I am not regretting it.
Start!
Are you stupid?
One!
You can't spin it like this!
Are you treating it as a dryer?
I'll do it.
Continue!
Two!
Three! Faster!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
It's enough, okay?
Ten!
Stop!
Enough!
Come... Come down.
Time's not up yet.
Before time's up,
you will be killed instead.
Come...
I don't need you to tell me these.
-Impressive, university graduates.
-Continue!
Continue!
Hold tighter.
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Move aside!
Can't you be quick-witted?
Useless men! What did you learn?
Yes!
Didn't you say...
Here!
Xiao Lin.
Boss!
You always take care of my business.
Here are some ice jellies for free.
Thank you!
I'll do it.
Okay. Give it to her first.
Thank you.
Thank you, Boss.
Enjoy!
Are you giving us a discount?
Of course!
Senior.
Aren't you staying in the fire station?
Did you sneak out today?
What's wrong?
Can't I do that?
Hey!
Eat first.
I need to go to the washroom.
Save some for me.
Humph!
Miss.
Are you calling me?
This doll is so pretty.
Where did you buy it?
Huh?
You're saying that this doll is pretty, right?
Yes.
I... I didn't buy this.
My son gave it to me.
Oh!
Your son is so nice.
Miss, my...
friends are waiting for me.
I shall leave first.
Not bad.
You saved some for me.
This ice jelly is really good.
Try it.
Okay.
Wow!
Yes! It's nice!
Yan Lan?
Long time no see.
Hey!
What a coincidence.
Who is he?
Her ex-boyfriend.
This is the case.
I am getting married next week.
I will send you an invitation.
You will come, right?
I am quite busy in the hospital recently.
I can't promise.
Are you too busy to date?
If it weren't for Luo Jie,
maybe you would be my bride.
Do you have anything else to say?
When are you getting married to Luo Jie?
A qualified ex
should act like a dead man.
This is a basic manner of a man.
Do you know?
Wait. Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
He is Yan Lan's boyfriend.
Oh, right!
Thanks for your invitation.
We will attend it.
Anything else?
Enjoy your meal then.
Aww!
I am sorry.
Join us for this meal!
Let's eat together!
No thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
My mom is in there.
Ask your mom to join us then.
-Let's eat together!
-No thanks.
Aww!
I... I am really...
I...
I saw a girl
in the bathroom earlier.
She is really cute and likable.
You...
Go out and check
which table she's at
and who she's eating with.
Okay?
The way she looked at me...
Listen to me.
She seemed very friendly.
Her gaze was very kind.
She had a ponytail
and was wearing a blue dress
with flowers on it.
She had big eyes and pale skin.
The moment you saw her,
she stood out.
Stop.
Are you starting again?
Let's eat.
Director Li.
Let's meet another day.
Okay.
Mr. Han.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mr. Luo.
Director Li
from the drug testing center just called.
He was asking
when we will send the next batch of medicine
for clinical trials.
After all these years of running
a business in Nanjing,
these sources all trust us very much.
See?
As soon as news of the next batch came out,
my phone hasn't stopped ringing.
Director Li and I
are also very close.
He was asking
about the PD-1 monoclonal antibody
just a few days ago.
It must be tough for him.
But compared to the normal medicine
out on the market already,
my clinical trials are harder to conduct.
The market needs
safe and effective patents.
Especially for a new type
of DNA-based medicine like mine.
Am I right, Mr. Luo?
Yes.
But creating medicine
isn't easy.
You need a lot of...
What's most important
are large, organized factories
like yours
to ensure the consistency
and stability of the product.
This is also
why I came here today.
I think
that if we can work together,
then it would be the joining
of two strong teams.
You really are young and promising.
Younger people like you have the
creativity to create new medicine.
But you can't do production and sales
without tens of years
of experience.
Of course.
Look.
The Luo brand
was built on 20 years of my effort.
There are many companies
that want to work with us
and use our name.
But our standards are very high.
You need to be both genuine
and talented.
Mr. Luo.
After hearing you say that,
I feel even better.
Don't just think about how young I am.
I'm not exaggerating,
but I am fully confident
in my skills and my product.
That's why in the past,
I've never bothered with companies
that don't have standards.
What is a corporation?
I think it's all about
using our strengths to win together.
Look.
Your medicine factory is an
established corporation.
Your strength
is your production experience
after all these years,
as well as your sales avenues.
As for my strengths,
it's new product development
and creativity.
Those who match well
will take what we each need
to be successful together.
That's the most important.
A successful partnership
is built on winning together.
Mr. Han.
I heard that your father used to
work in chemical engineering.
Right.
Then are you able to get
certain lead compounds?
That's easy.
Just let me know.
That makes things easy.
Here.
Today,
Dongshan Station and Dongnan Hospital
will train in the field together
to increase the efficiency of our
firefighting and hospital teams.
Attention!
Count off!
One, two, three...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen,
fourteen, fifteen.
[Firefighting and Medical Field Training]
Chief.
The training team has assembled.
Please give orders.
Back in line.
Yes, sir.
Ye.
Today is our hospital and
Dongshan Station's Blue Eagle Rope Rescue Team's
first time training in the field together.
I hope that my colleagues
and our firefighters
will successfully complete
this mission together.
Thank you!
Sweat more on the daily,
bleed less during battle.
I hope that
[Firefighting and Medical Field Training]
everyone participating
[China Fire and Rescue]
will become one with their team
so that our teams
can become a solid foundation for the people.
Huo Yan, Luo Jie.
Here!
Split into a red and a blue team.
Begin.
Red team, count off.
Chief Huo, we need to go faster.
They're already leaving.
Preparation doesn't delay your task.
Everyone, carefully check your gear.
Don't forget anything.
The route isn't easy.
Firefighters, make sure
to take care of the medical team.
I'll give everyone one minute
to organize your gear.
Brother Wu, you lead the team today.
Hey.
Car King is leading?
Oh, man.
How are we going to win now?
Get ready to cook.
Chief Huo.
Why are you so unlucky?
The other team has all the aces.
Our Wu is a Car King while driving
and a wolf on the ground.
Alright, stop kidding around.
Red Team, get ready to leave.
Yes!
Wu, good luck.
Don't let us catch up with you.
Be careful.
Ji Yuan.
You go first.
I'll catch up.
Little Mole.
I'll carry your bag.
It's fine, I can do it.
Chief Luo.
We're not on the same team right now.
Who knows who will win?
If we're not on the same team,
we need to be aligned together.
Besides,
your team might not be able to protect you.
Brothers in my team,
take care of the girls on our team.
We don't need others to get involved.
Chief Huo, don't get too excited.
I used to let you off easy.
Be careful not to lose too badly.
Good luck.
How about this?
What?
I switched it to channel three.
Our walkie-talkies
also have GPS signals.
Contact me if anything happens.
Take it.
I'm leaving now. Good luck!
Chief Huo.
These two routes are equally difficult,
but this one is longer.
Choose the shorter one.
Look carefully.
Both of these routes go through the valley.
They chose the shorter one.
The contour lines are dense.
It'll get steep.
Instead of being forced to change routes,
we might as well get a head start.
Hurry and check your gear.
Prepare to leave.
Let's go!
Be careful, Darling.
Be careful.
Everyone stop.
Chief Luo.
This obstacle is to test
our ability to rescue by rope.
But the valley is too deep.
I think it'll be very difficult.
If we use a line thrower to deploy
a line and grapple across...
There's someone over there, right?
If the line can't get across,
he will raise his flag.
Let's do it your way.
You're in command today.
Chief Luo.
You should guide us on the side.
What if something goes wrong?
What could go wrong?
I trust you, Brother Wu.
Okay.
Ma, let's go.
Don't rush. Take it slow.
Chief Luo.
The distance is too far.
Our rope lines aren't long enough.
Wu, do you have any other ideas?
Chief Luo.
What about we let Ma try with a drone?
Let him check if there's a better place
to shoot the line.
Good idea, let's do it.
Okay.
Ma!
Yeah?
Try with the drone.
Okay.
Chief Luo, we found it.
But Chief Huo and his team found it first.
Look.
Is this the closest distance?
Yes.
Lead the team over, go.
Chief Luo, we're leaving first!
Be careful.
Alright.
Here.
Come here.
Don't get too cocky.
You won't reach the end relying on luck.
Chief Luo.
We'll take our luck
and Little Mole and go first.
You can have the line.
Take care of Yan Lan!
I'll kill you if something happens.
Let's go!
Goodbye.
Keep showing off.
Be careful, Doctor Yan.
Don't worry.
Careful.
Let's go.
What?
Go.
Weren't you acting brave earlier?
You were even taking care of the girl.
Here.
I'll give you a chance
to ask the most handsome firefighter
in all of Jiangsu to hold your bag.
What a bad temper.
Ah, don't touch me!
[Fire and Rescue - Jiangsu Nanjing]
Careful.
Brother Liang.
Yeah?
Pull me up.
Here.
Give me a hand.
She won't let me help.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Wang Da Yin, are you okay?
My back!
Why are you so heavy?
My face!
Wait, wait.
I think I twisted my ankle.
What?
Look.
Where?
My right ankle.
Ankle? Which one?
The right one.
Right ankle.
Right?
Your ankle or knee?
My foot.
Liang! Liang!
Come here!
Hurry!
Where?
Mostly my ankle.
Your ankle, right? Not your knee?
It hurts!
Liang.
I'm here.
Hurry!
Don't move.
It hurts.
Here?
That hurts!
Hurry and tell Chief Chen.
Chief Chen.
Jiang Tong hurt her foot.
Okay, I got it.
[Nanjing Fire and Rescue Command Center]
You two
go and help Jiang Tong.
She injured her foot.
Yes, sir.
Is it serious?
It's fine.
One sprained her ankle,
the other scratched some skin.
Speaking of which, Ye,
you can't keep coughing like that.
I'm fine. It's just lung heat.
I know what it is.
A doctor shouldn't treat himself.
Do it yourself.
Qian Li.
I'll teach you how to recoil the rope
after climbing.
First, find a comfortable
length, about the length of your arm.
Then take half of that
and coil it like this.
Right.
Let's take a 30-minute break.
Eat some snacks to replenish energy.
We're going the right way.
Continue forward as normal.
Be careful.
Wait,
Bai.
Is Father Ye's coughing getting worse?
I think it's lung heat.
Lung heat?
Yeah.
Oh, right.
There's wild rock honey here.
I've even seen beekeepers on my way here.
It can treat lung heat.
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Having children is always worrisome
and they might get stuck at any moment.
Children are constantly exploring their world.
They're curious and nimble.
Even the smallest crack
might trap them.
Parents should always keep an eye on them
so that they can stay away from danger
and learn to spot dangers.
[Fire Safety is Everyone's Responsibility]
♪The wind is full of sweetness when you smile♪
♪I am indulged in you♪
♪Everything about you♪
♪Piles up on a rainy night♪
♪I hand over my heart♪
♪To the rising sun before the dawn♪
♪When you cry, even the stars sigh♪
♪I want to hug you and
shield you from the noises♪
♪The clouds spread when I meet you♪
♪The moon whispers a secret♪
♪The answer to this secret♪
♪Is our promise of love♪
♪I penetrate through your heart♪
♪And hold onto your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪You would know if you were here♪
♪Open your hands and wait for me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I really want to hold your hand♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪
♪I only know light wouldn't leave♪
♪After traveling past countless nights♪
♪I would know if you were here♪
♪That you are waiting to embrace me♪
♪I just want to grow old with you♪
♪Slowly♪