(LOGAN COUGHING)
VICTOR: You're always sick.
LOGAN: You were sick
when you were my age.
Evening, sir.
Evening, Victor.
I didn't realize
you were still here.
I was just keeping James company,
sir, if that's all right.
Very kind of you.
Any better, Son?
Still cold, Father.
JOHN: Just a mild fever.
You'll be all right
in the morning.
You always say that.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) And you
always pull through, don't you?
Yeah.
Now, you taking
your medicine?
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
THOMAS: Elizabeth! Elizabeth!
Your father's drunk again.
THOMAS: Elizabeth!
You should help
him home, Victor.
It's not my name
he's calling, sir.
Father!
Stay where you are, James.
ELIZABETH: Get off me!
Father!
THOMAS: Now!
You never loved him!
JOHN: I told you never
to come back here.
(GUN FIRES)
(ELIZABETH SHRIEKING)
THOMAS: Get out!
(BARELY AUDIBLE) James?
No.
THOMAS: James?
There are things you
don't understand. Don't.
I need him to know!
ELIZABETH: Please don't.
THOMAS: No more lies.
ELIZABETH: James...
(SCREAMING)
(GUN FIRES)
No!
ELIZABETH: James!
He... He wasn't your father,
Son.
What are you?
I didn't mean it! I didn't mean it!
Yes, you did!
He deserved it,
and you gave it to him.
We're brothers, Jimmy.
You realize that?
And brothers protect
each other.
You have to be hard now, hard
so nothing can ever touch us.
I want to go home.
We can't.
We stick together,
no matter what,
and take care of anyone
who gets in our way.
(DOGS BARKING)
Can you do that,
little brother?
MAN: I'm going
down to the river.
VICTOR: They're coming.
MAN: Head over the hill.
Hurry!
VICTOR: Can you run?
Keep on running
and don't look back.
LOGAN: Okay.
(LOGAN YELLING)
LOGAN: Back to back!
(GUN COCKING)
(MACHINE GUNS FIRING)
That's enough!
Enough!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
No! No!
Stand down, soldier!
Victor!
Stand down! Stand down!
Stand down!
No!
Ready, aim...
Wake me when it's over.
...fire!
GUARD: Freaks!
You're animals! Freaks!
My name is Major
William Stryker.
You've been charged with
killing a senior officer.
Is that correct?
Apparently, we have some
issues with authority...
Just keep a lid on it.
...sir.
The warden tells me
that your sentence
was carried out
by a firing squad
at 1000 hours.
How'd that go?
It tickled.
You boys tired of running?
Tired of denying
your true nature?
What do you care?
Oh, I care.
I care because I know
how special you are.
How valuable.
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
Look, you can stay here locked
up like freaks of nature,
or you can join me.
I'm putting together a special
team with special privileges.
Now, tell me, how would you like
to really serve your country?
(BLADE CLINKING)
You know,
I love this weapon
more than any other thing
in the whole wide world.
Do you wanna know why?
No.
It's memorable.
Sure, it's a little bulky,
tough to get on a plane.
You whip out
a couple of swords
at your
ex-girlfriend's wedding,
they will never,
ever forget it.
That's funny, Wade.
I think you confuse me with
someone who gives a shit.
(SCOFFS) Right, it's probably not
as intimidating as having a gun
or bone claws or the
fingernails of a bag lady.
Manicure?
Victor. Easy.
Fred got a new tattoo.
I'm concerned.
Oh, Jesus, Fred,
you just met her last night.
I love her. You love
her after one night?
She's a gymnast.
Bradley, take her down.
Oh, God.
Are you gonna puke?
If we were meant to fly,
we'd grow wings.
Aw, don't worry, Nancy.
More people die
driving than flying.
How about from impaling?
Hey, be nice, or be your
approximation of nice.
Would you like a bucket?
No.
STRYKER: Gentlemen,
wheels down in Lagos in five.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
Why are we here?
All in good time. Zero?
MAN 1: Intruder!
Perimeter breach!
MAN 2: Man the weapon!
(GUNS COCKING)
MAN 1: Intruder, stop!
Put your hands
behind your head!
Having fun yet?
Fred?
The tank?
The tank.
Yeah, I got that.
(CHUCKLING)
(MUZAK PLAYING)
Great. Stuck in an elevator with
five guys on a high-protein diet.
STRYKER: Wade.
Dreams really do come true.
Just shut it!
You're up next. Thank you, sir.
You look really nice today.
It's the green.
It brings out the
seriousness in your eyes.
Oh, my God.
Do you ever shut up, pal?
No. Not when I'm awake.
Bradley?
Top floor, please.
Cover the elevator!
The elevator!
(GUNS COCKING)
Time to go to work.
Okay. People are dead.
If you didn't have
that mouth on you, Wade,
you'd be the perfect soldier.
I wouldn't do that
if I was you, brother.
Take the diamonds.
They're yours.
I don't want
your diamonds.
I want this.
But that is nothing.
A souvenir.
Where did you find it?
I want the source.
A small village, far inland,
three days from here.
Tell him this rock is more
valuable to me than his life.
Ask him where
he found it.
(SPEAKING LOCAL LANGUAGE)
(MAN SPEAKING LOCAL LANGUAGE)
Okay.
He says it came
from the sky.
He's telling the truth.
You don't know
the language, Logan.
It's a meteor fragment.
STRYKER: I know what it is.
I'm asking him
where he found it.
Sir, base wants to
know our location.
Shut them down.
Yes.
Tell him everyone
here will die
unless he tells me
where he found the rock.
(WADE SPEAKING LOCAL LANGUAGE)
(MAN SPEAKING LOCAL LANGUAGE)
(SIGHING)
WADE:
He says that it's sacred.
Okay, fine.
Victor.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(GUN FIRES)
Victor!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
Don't even think about it.
We didn't sign up
for this.
Put him down!
(PANTING)
What are you doing?
We finally got
a good thing going here.
Don't you screw this up.
Enough. That's enough.
We've done enough.
Who do you
think you are?
This is what we do.
Maybe you'd rather be
rotting in a hole somewhere
till they figure out a way to do it to us.
Is that it? Huh?
I'm done.
You coming?
Jimmy!
We can't just
let you walk away.
Jimmy!
Why are you up
so early?
Come here.
See you, baby.
Hey.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Oh, that's nice.
Yes. Take your time.
You're wrapped, man.
(FAIR MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE WHOOPING)
GIRL: Okay,
I'm totally gonna get this.
Nope. Come on.
Oh, wow! Let's go on
the Ferris wheel.
GIRL: How does he do it?
BOY: Come on.
MAN 1:
...amazing lady in a box!
MAN 2: Swing the hammer,
ring the bell!
Hey, what do you do?
Oh. If you turn off the
light, you win a prize.
Three tries for a buck.
Come on, I wanna do it.
There you go. Okay?
No, that's obvious.
That's two.
(SIZZLING SOFTLY)
Well, that's
a stupid trick.
It's not a trick, man.
Come on. Freak.
Bye.
(BEEPING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Show's over!
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
I said show's over!
The show's never
over for us, Bradley.
Victor.
Aren't you gonna
invite me in?
Yeah. Come on in.
You know,
I've never said anything
to anyone about
what happened.
I'm living a totally
different life now, Victor.
No need to
bring up the past.
You know,
I always thought it would be Wade
to come knocking at my door.
Well... Well,
Wade's gone.
I'm not afraid
of you, Victor.
I'm not afraid of dying.
How do you know?
You've never
tried it before.
(BRADLEY SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
KAYLA: Was it the wars?
Which one?
All of them.
Tell me.
Hey.
It's just a scratch.
Looks like we're gonna need
new sheets again, baby.
Yeah.
PHELAN:
Who the hell is this?
Smells like government.
My God.
Haven't aged a day!
Clean living.
You remember Agent Zero?
Still shooting first,
asking questions later?
You still chewing
on cheap cigars?
STRYKER: Boys, please.
I have a job for you.
I already have a job.
Lumberjack?
18 grand a year?
18.5. Plus I haven't had
to kill anyone in a while.
Starting to miss it?
Right about now I am.
Yeah?
Zero, back to the car.
Atta boy.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You know, I'm not proud about the
way things ended between us.
Conversation's over.
Playing Little House on the
Prairie with a schoolteacher,
I mean, that just
isn't you, Logan.
And you would know, huh?
I would.
What do you want,
Stryker?
Bradley was killed
three days ago.
Wade before that.
I believe that someone is
hunting down our old team.
Anyone else?
As far as I know,
Victor is safe.
But whoever it is
has names, addresses.
I can take care of myself.
This is not
about you, Logan.
Your country needs you.
I'm Canadian.
I know you, Logan!
I know who you are!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Miss Kayla, Miss Kayla,
look what I did.
What did you do?
GIRL:
Bye, Miss Silverfox! Bye!
KAYLA: What's wrong?
Stryker came by today.
Don't worry. I said no.
Why is he bothering you
after all these years?
Because I'm the best
there is at what I do,
but what I do best
isn't very nice.
You're not an animal, Logan.
What you have is a gift.
A gift.
You can return a gift.
Come on, fellas.
(HONKING HORN)
All right.
Stay in the car.
I'm just gonna ask nicely.
You mind letting us go by?
You in some kind of a hurry there, pal'?
Hey, hey, hey.
Are you?
Just move your truck
so we can go by.
We're trying to have a
conversation there, all right?
You start something, you'd
better be ready to finish it.
Listen...
KAYLA: Hey, guys,
take it easy! Calm down.
Your boyfriend's
got a big mouth.
KAYLA: I know.
Big temper, too.
So please let us pass.
Thank you.
MAN: Come on, man, let's go.
How'd you do that?
Female powers of persuasion.
It's a gift.
Oh, I see.
Do you have those
powers over me?
Well, you didn't stay
in the car, did you?
(HOWLING)
KAYLA: Why is the
moon so lonely?
Why?
Because she used to have a lover.
Oh.
No. You tell this to the kids?
(LOGAN LAUGHS)
His name was Kuekuatsheu and they
lived in the Spirit World together.
Oh, this is a true story?
All right. Mmm-hmm.
And every night they would
wander the skies together...
Oh.
...but one of the other
spirits was jealous.
Trickster wanted
the moon for himself,
so he told Kuekuatsheu that the
moon had asked for flowers.
He told him to come to our world
and pick her some wild roses,
but Kuekuatsheu didn't know that
once you leave the Spirit World,
you can never go back.
And every night
he looks up in the sky
and sees the moon
and howls her name.
But
he can never
touch her again.
Wow.
Koo-koo-ka-choo
got screwed.
"Kuekuatsheu."
(LAUGHING)
it means "the Wolverine".
(SNIFFS)
What you doing, Logan?
Kayla.
(PANTING)
Oh, God.
Kayla!
(SCREAMING)
You're not from
around here, are you?
(LAUGHING)
What gave me away?
LOGAN: Victor!
You got insurance
on this place?
Insurance? No.
Too bad.
LOGAN: Victor!
MAN: What have
we got here?
Well, well, well.
Look what the cat
dragged in.
Guys, whatever this is,
take it outside.
Why?
(LAUGHING)
You don't call.
You don't write.
How else am I supposed
to get your attention?
(LOGAN GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
(LOGAN GROANING)
I hate to say it, Jimmy, but,
frankly, I'm a little disappointed.
Stay down.
Tell me something, Jimmy.
Was she worth it?
(TRUCK APPROACHING)
When are you gonna
figure it out?
We're not like them.
I am nothing like you.
Sure, you are.
You just don't know it yet.
(SCREAMING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
DOCTOR: What do we got? Bar fight.
Multiple knife wounds.
What is this, a joke?
Guy's fine.
Where is he?
Hey, hey, don't...
I said, where is he?
I don't know who he is.
STRYKER: I can help you.
Six years I've been here.
No one knew me, and then you show
up, and the next day she's dead!
I tried to warn you.
Why didn't you
tell me it was Victor?
I didn't know!
Bullshit!
Why?
I swear on my son's
life, I didn't!
Victor's appetites
were becoming too public.
I had to lock him up.
He felt I betrayed him.
Went AWOL.
He said he was coming
after all of us.
You didn't come to warn me,
you came to
save your own ass.
So what's your plan,
Captain?
You can't beat him, Logan,
you know you can't!
I'm gonna find him
and kill him.
I can give you
the tools to defeat him.
And we can still
save the others.
You mean
save yourself, right?
I promise you two things.
You will suffer more pain
than any other man can endure,
but you will have
your revenge.
I come with you,
I'm coming for blood.
No law.
No code of conduct.
You point me in
the right direction,
you get the hell
out of my way.
When it starts, whatever the
reason is that you're doing this,
focus on that.
Maybe it will help.
Trust me,
I've been through worse.
No, you haven't.
We're ready.
We're gonna make
you indestructible,
but first we're gonna
have to destroy you.
You remember what we
were looking for in Africa?
I remember.
Well, I found it.
It helped us create
a metal compound so strong
that you will be able to
withstand virtually anything.
It's called Adamantium.
I can't put Victor
down myself, Logan.
To kill him, you're gonna have
to embrace the other side.
Become the animal.
Let's do this.
I almost forgot.
I want new ones.
What do you
want them to say?
Wolverine.
(AIR HISSING)
STRYKER: Generals, welcome.
General Munson.
Today we're gonna witness
medical history.
Today we're gonna
create Weapon X.
X?
Roman numeral 10.
We are about to begin bonding
Adamantium to Weapon X's skeleton.
Let's begin.
(ECG BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
We're brothers, Jimmy.
VICTOR: Logan!
Body temperature,
108 and rising.
Why is he thrashing
like that?
Why isn't he sedated?
He feels pain just
like the rest of us,
but anesthesia
won't work on him.
That's why he had
to volunteer.
Heart rate, 190. 195.
MUNSON: Will he survive this?
STRYKER: I don't know.
ZOO.
Son.
(ECG BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Heart rate well
beyond maximum.
Blood pressure? CORNELIUS:
260 over 180 and rising.
He can make it.
Victor!
(VICTOR SCREAMING)
KAYLA: I love you.
You're not an animal.
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
(HEART BEAT SLOWS)
it means "the Wolverine".
(ECG FLATLINING)
ZERO: Well,
I guess he can die.
(WHISPERING) Come on, old friend.
Come back.
Heart rate rising.
Adamantium reservoir
is depleted.
No rejection.
Procedure completed.
We did it.
Yeah! Yes.
Are we taking him
to the island?
The island? No.
The bonding works.
We'll use his DNA
for the XI.
Erase his memory.
I think he heard you.
(ROARING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Lock down!
(PANTING)
(GUN COCKING)
Hunt him down.
Take his head off.
HEATHER: Travis.
I think there's a naked
man in the barn.
Yep.
(LOGAN PANTING)
Son?
What in hell you doing?
It's cold.
Cold.
You got no clothes on.
Yeah.
You're not on
the drugs, are you?
No.
No, just had a rough night.
Yeah, you could say that.
Come on up to the house.
Some of my son's old clothes
will probably fit you.
Here. Cover it up
with that, huh?
I don't want you giving
the old lady a heart attack.
(BLADES CLINKING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(EXCLAIMING)
(HISSING)
You all right in there?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine!
Supper's on the table.
Uh, yeah,
I'll be there in a minute.
Oh.
I swear,
I'm gonna pay for it.
Set it down over there.
Right.
Come and sit down, son.
I can't thank you
both enough for everything.
It wouldn't have been decent to
leave you out there to freeze.
"Decent."
What?
Nothing. I'm just not
really used to that word.
That's a nice chopper
you've got out there.
You know motorcycles?
Oh! Lord, here we go.
My favorite's
a '48 Panhead.
Boughtone
new off the line.
I think you're a little
young for that, son.
You must be exhausted.
You get a good night's sleep.
In the barn.
Nothing you can
break out there.
(LOGAN CHUCKLES)
KAYLA: Why is the
moon so lonely?
LOGAN: Why?
KAYLA: Because she used
to have a lover.
He can never
touch her again.
You sleep okay?
Uh, yeah.
You look like a man
fixing to do a bad thing.
You know what happens to men
who go looking for blood?
What?
They find it.
We all got a choice, son.
Yeah, well, mine got taken.
Bullshit.
This was my son's jacket.
Try it on.
Thank you.
Yep.
You want to take
my bike for a spin?
Test the suspension?
'64, huh?
(CREAKS LOUDLY)
Man, you're heavy.
Yeah, I put on
a little weight recently.
HEATHER: Good morning!
LOGAN: Good morning.
Oh. it fits you beautifully.
I brought you some...
Weapon X is in the barn.
He's just murdered
two civilians.
STRYKER: Blow him to bits. Let's
see if he can survive that.
Come get me.
Blow his brains
all over the road!
Damn it!
Alpha one, do not lose him!
Alpha two!
Target coming to you!
Pull up!
(HELICOPTER ALARM
BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Pull back! Pull back!
STRYKER ON RADIO: Zero?
Zero, come in.
Zero?
Zero, is Logan dead?
ZERO: I don't know.
I'm down.
Zero, is he dead?
Is Logan dead?
Zero, come in.
LOGAN: You tried to kill me.
Logan?
Where's Victor?
Come back to base.
I'll explain everything. We'll
take Victor down together.
Wrong answer. After I kill
Victor, I'm coming for you.
Logan, listen to me.
If you go down this road, you're
not gonna like what you find.
You wanted the animal,
Colonel.
You got it.
Those were good people back there.
innocent people.
(LAUGHING)
It's funny how good, innocent
people tend to die around you.
CORNELIUS:
Zero never stood a chance.
The only thing that'll take him
down is an Adamantium bullet.
This facility's compromised.
Prep transport.
Colonel, this is turning
into a disaster.
Don't worry.
We'll stop him.
Really?
You just spent half a billion
dollars making him indestructible.
(DOOR OPENING)
AIDE: Sir?
Yes?
The young mutant
you've been looking for.
We've found him.
General, Logan isn't the
only piece of this puzzle.
I need to evacuate
this facility.
Please go back
to Washington.
We've got work to do.
Yo hablo, I talk.
Tu hablas, you talk.
El habla. ..
Somebody translate.
Summers!
Sit up and take off
those glasses.
I have a headache.
Then you can wear them
in detention after school
while you write out
this conjugation 100 times.
Somebody else?
BOY: He talks.
TEACHER: Thank you.
He talks. El habla.
You sure it was Victor?
Yeah.
Damn. I'm sorry, man.
What the hell happened
to him after I left?
He got worse. He felt
like you abandoned him.
Hell, We all did.
But Victor, he had to prove
he was better than you.
Hunting and killing
everything he was pointed at.
Quit a few months
later myself.
Couldn't take
rounding them up.
Rounding who up?
Leave it alone.
Rounding who up, John?
Hey! Damn it, John!
We hunted our
own kind, Logan.
There's a special place in
hell for the things we did.
Mutants? Why?
Stryker said we'd be
making a difference,
protecting people
from the bad ones.
How are you gonna take
Victor down, Logan?
Remember that
stuff in Africa?
Yeah, I remember Africa.
What about it?
Damn.
What'd they do
to you, man?
Don't ask.
Listen, Zero said something
about an island.
Does that mean
anything to you?
Nope.
But maybe Dukes knows.
Him and Zero
were real tight.
Fred Dukes?
Where is he?
He's here.
Well, let's go talk to him.
Hold on. He don't get
in till around 4:00.
But I got to warn you, he developed
a bit of an eating disorder.
We all got our
coping mechanisms.
I'm trying to whup him
back into shape.
Whatever you do,
don't mention his weight.
Come on, Fred, if you wanna get
in shape, you got to move, man.
I told him he got to move.
He's got to move! What?
LOGAN: Fred Dukes? That looks like
the creature that ate Fred Dukes.
WRAITH: Hey, be nice, man.
Hey, fat... Fred.
I seem to remember that girl when
she was about 85 pounds, huh?
Oh, that's funny.
You're still so funny, Logan.
You know where Victor is?
Noidea.
What's the island, slim?
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out, Logan.
Listen, I ain't leaving here till
you tell me where Victor is.
So come on, bub,
for old times' sake, huh?
Did you just
call me Blob?
No, but...
(ROARING)
I told you not to
mention his weight.
Why'd you call him Blob?
I didn't call him Blob.
I said "bub".
God damn it.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, Logan.
I got an idea.
This is your idea
of an idea?
I'm trying to
help you out, Logan.
Dukes don't like you that
much and you know it.
Yeah,
the feeling's mutual.
Well, use them gloves, man.
Dance with him a little bit.
Allow him to let
his anger out on you.
Figure if you do that, he'll probably
tell you everything you want to know.
Come on, man,
look at him.
Got a big old ass coming out
the front of his shirt.
Jesus. He's gonna have a
coronary, for Christ's sake.
Is there even a stretcher big enough
to take this guy out of here?
It ain't him I'm worried about
getting out of here on a stretcher.
You're an asshole.
DUKES: Come on, Logan.
(BELL RINGS)
Whup his ass!
You want it?
WRAITH: Dance with him, Fred!
Just like I taught you.
You want to dance with me?
WRAITH: Come on, Fred!
Oh! Oh, that feels good.
Hey! Guess what?
See, he gonna talk now.
You got him right
where you want him.
Whose side are
you on, anyway?
DUKES: Come on!
Come on, now,
lamb chop!
Damn!
(SCREAMING)
Now, where's Victor?
(GRUNTING)
Little dark for sunglasses,
don't you think?
Please, don't! Please, don't!
Victor!
Hey, hey! Where's Victor?
Yeah. Victor's with
Stryker on the island.
(STAMMERING)
They run it together.
What? They what?
Victor will be
with Stryker?
Yeah.
You didn't know that?
(SHUDDERING)
(SCOTT GRUNTING)
(ZAPPING)
All that's left
now is Logan.
I trust you
can handle that.
I did before, didn't I?
Oh, yes. You did that.
Our deal.
It still applies, right?
Of course.
Now bag him
and tag him, Captain.
What's the island?
(STAMMERING) It's where
Stryker takes them
after Victor's caught them.
Wait, hang on a minute.
Takes who?
Mutants.
Rumor is that Stryker's doing
experiments on them there.
I mean, you never wondered
what happened to them?
I tried not to.
They killed her so I'd let
them put Adamantium in me.
They killed her for
a goddamn experiment.
Where is it? Where is it?
Logan, Stryker kept it
real secret.
But a prisoner
escaped there once.
Who? His name was Remy LeBeau.
He was a street hustler
from New Orleans.
The guards at the prison
called him Gambit
because he kept taking
all their money at poker.
That's all I know.
What's Stryker up to, Fred?
What's the endgame?
He's taking their powers.
Trying to combine
them somehow.
That's all I know, Logan.
That's all I know.
If I have to come back here,
I'm gonna take your head off.
I'm coming
with you, Logan.
There's no redemption
where I'm going.
I ain't asking.
(BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
(GIRLS CHEERING)
There's our dude.
That's cool.
I'm gonna go cover the back
in case he rabbits.
- I'm not gonna fight with him.
- Yeah, right.
What? I get in fights
with everybody?
Don't dogs kill cats?
Just go cover the back,
will you?
MAN 1: Give me 500.
MAN 2: I'm in.
Are you Remy LeBeau?
Do I owe you money?
No.
Then Remy LeBeau I am.
(BOTTLE CLATTERING)
Large blind's 100.
Small blind's 50.
May I deal you in?
What can I get for 17 bucks?
$17?
A cab ride home,
perhaps?
You my brother's
new babysitter, John?
I ain't Bradley, Victor.
And your creepy black coat
don't scare me.
Really?
Worked on Dukes.
You shouldn't have done that,
'cause now I'm gonna kill you
before Logan even
gets a chance.
So what brings you
to our fair city, sir?
Victor Creed.
And who's that?
The man I'm gonna kill.
(VICTOR LAUGHING)
He works with a man named
Stryker on an island.
Just need to know
where it is.
And why would you
think I know that?
Well, 'cause I know
who you are, Gambit.
You're the guy who escaped and you're
the guy who's gonna take me back there.
You know, John, there's something
I always wanted to tell you.
(GASPING)
You're predictable.
Ooh!
I can feel your spine,
Johnny Boy.
That's funny.
Never knew you had one.
Those are mighty nice tags
you have on there, sir.
The men who took me
wore tags just like them.
Hey, now, bub,
you listen to me.
Damn it. That little...
Two years I rotted
in that hellhole
and I ain't never
going back.
On! Shiny.
Tell me something, Jimmy.
Do you even know
how to kill me?
I'm gonna cut your
goddamned head off.
See if that works.
(LAUGHING)
You're getting slow,
old man.
(SCREAMING)
You son of a bitch.
You're gonna die for
what you did to her.
Victor!
Well, that's a nice stick.
Okay, shithead,
here's the deal.
See, you're gonna
take me to this island,
where I can
kill Creed, Stryker
and pretty much everyone you hate
in this world. Do you understand?
You're really
gonna kill them?
As long as you stay
out of my way, yeah.
MUNSON: Colonel?
General?
Is this Weapon XI?
All their strengths
and none of their weaknesses.
You really hate them,
don't you?
No, I don't hate them.
After 2O years of working with
mutants, I just know what they can do.
We can win this war
before it starts
and save countless
lives in the process.
Pre-emptive action is the
only action here, General.
The days of our country sitting
on the sidelines are over.
We need to take
the fight to the enemy
before they take
the fight to us.
I admire your passion,
I do.
Thank you.
But this is as
far as it goes.
Weapon X was a hiccup.
We know about
your son, Bill.
We know he's a mutant, and
we know he killed your wife.
You shouldn't have
kept that from us.
That...
That has nothing to do
with my work, General.
Bullshit.
You're too close to this.
I'm shutting you down.
Okay. You're right.
I won't lie to you.
My son did bring
the problem home for me,
but I took an oath
to protect
the American people
from every threat,
both foreign
(GROANING)
and domestic.
You don't like flying, huh?
I'm fine.
Just concentrate on what you're doing.
You sure?
You got a bit of sweat
on your brow there.
Very funny. Just keep
your eyes on the...
On the what? The clouds?
Keep my eyes on the clouds?
You're up and down
like a freaking yo-yo here!
Where'd you get
this thing, anyway?
Oh, this is my baby.
I won her in a game.
Jacks over fives.
Great.
REMY: Relax.
We're almost there.
There it is. The island.
Three Mile Island.
Hiding in plain sight.
No one's gonna snoop
around a nuclear reactor.
They think it's gonna turn
them into freaks.
Like you?
Right.
All right. You ready?
Because it's now or never.
Let's go.
About time.
Hey, if it makes you feel any
better, this is really gonna hurt.
Well, yeah, it kind
of does, actually.
Good luck.
Likewise.
Oh, shit.
How you doing?
Everything all right?
Is he ready yet?
A few more hours.
And he will respond
to my commands?
Absolutely.
Logan.
Welcome back to the war.
Before I gut you,
I want to know why.
I needed your powers
for the Pool.
For the what?
The mutant killer.
Deadpool.
Years of searching
and refining,
finding the right powers
that can coexist in one body
without ripping it apart.
My son was the first
piece of the puzzle.
Logan, you were the last.
You made Weapon XI possible.
I asked you to help, but you
said you wanted the quiet life.
Well,
I've learned that
nothing motivates
the men in your
family like revenge.
Who are you?
Oh, she's real, old friend.
(GROANING)
Did you really think we'd
just let you walk away?
You're a dangerous man.
We like to keep an eye
on dangerous men.
Tell him about
the day you died.
They gave me a shot
of hydrochlorothiazide.
It reduces the heart rate so
low it appears you flatlined.
(SCREAMING)
Don't be angry
with her.
She's a real credit
to your species.
Did you know that her sister
has diamond-hard skin?
Kayla's mutation
is tactohypnosis.
She can influence people
as long as she touches them.
Quite a useful tool
in a seduction.
It was never real,
my friend.
It was real for me.
I told you if you
came down this road,
you wouldn't like
what you found.
That story you told me about a man
who gets flowers for the moon,
I had it backwards.
I thought you were the moon
and I was your Wolverine.
But you're the trickster,
aren't you?
I'm just the fool
who got played.
The worst part of it is,
I should have known.
But I ignored my instincts.
I ignored what I really am.
But that won't
ever happen again.
Colonel?
Not now, Kayla.
I've done everything
you've asked.
My sister.
You said if I helped you,
you'd let her go.
Kayla, it's not
as simple as that.
Her mutation is unique.
Quite beautiful.
We just need a little more time
to analyze it, that's all.
VICTOR: You let him go?
Victor, please.
You can't let him go.
You can't beat him, Victor.
Then give me the Adamantium!
Your tests came back.
We had a deal!
You would never
survive the operation.
I can take
anything he can.
No, you can't.
You're my favorite
soldier, Victor.
Be patient.
Your time will come.
He's using us.
(SCREAMING)
How about this time
you die for real?
Let me go.
Your little mind games
don't work on me.
LOGAN: Victor!
(GROANS)
(LAUGHING)
Feels good, doesn't it?
All that rage.
Do it.
KAYLA: Logan!
You're not an animal.
Oh, yes, you are.
Do it.
Finish it.
KAYLA: Logan?
My sister.
They have my sister.
Please. I didn't trick
you into loving me.
It was real for me, too.
Please, I'm so sorry.
They have my sister.
Where is she?
Activate Weapon XI!
The bonding process
isn't complete.
Just do it! Now!
(DOORS OPENING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on. Come on!
(DOORS OPENING)
Okay.
Perfect.
Kayla, get these kids out of here.
Logan“.
Find another way out.
MALE MUTANT:
Okay. Let's go.
Wade, is that you?
Guess Stryker finally figured
out how to shut you up.
STRYKER: Now...
Wade?
You don't have to do this.
All right, maybe you do.
You're shitting me.
STRYKER: Shoot on sight!
I can help!
Point me at them!
Go.
Go! Now!
(SCOTT SCREAMING)
Did I get them?
Yeah.
Let's go.
I can't go.
Kayla, come on!
I have to stay here.
You take them.
Go! Go!
XAVIER: (TELEPATHICALLY)
Go left.
Left.
What?
We go left.
You can't see.
Trust me.
Let's see you dance up here.
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Nobody kills you but me.
Back to back!
I got him!
Oh, no, you don't.
(YELLS)
Stop!
This can't be the way.
This is the way.
How do you know?
I just know. Come on.
STRYKER: Adamantium bullets.
Let's see him heal with a few of
these through his thick skull.
You can't stop him,
even with that.
He'll heal.
His brain may heal,
(GUN COCKING)
but his memories
won't grow back.
(CRUMBLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
This doesn't change anything
between us, Victor.
We're done.
We can never
be done, Jimmy.
We're brothers, and brothers
look out for each other.
You miss me?
Ah, Jesus.
You know, when you said
you were gonna kill everyone,
I thought you may just
have been exaggerating.
Yeah.
Do I look like a man
who exaggerates?
You're welcome.
KAYLA: (SOFTLY) Logan?
Logan.
There's kids trying to get off the island.
Split up. Go!
I'm on it.
(KAYLA BREATHING LABOREDLY)
Kayla! Kayla!
Hey.
I love you.
Hey...
I'm so cold.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna get
you out of here.
Understand?
Just go easy. Nice and easy.
That's it. That's it.
Okay. I'm gonna
get you help.
(KAYLA SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(ROARING)
KAYLA: Logan!
I should make you
pull the trigger.
But that would make us
no better than you.
Throw the gun away.
Turn around.
Walk until your feet bleed.
And then keep walking.
XAVIER: (TELEPATHICALLY)
It will be all right, Scott.
My name is Charles Xavier.
I'm a mutant like you.
SCOTT: (TELEPATHICALLY)
I can hear your thoughts.
XAVIER: Yes,
and I can hear yours.
You're safe now.
Come. We have to go.
SCOTT: Come on, let's go.
REMY: The kids are safe.
Damn.
Who are you?
What do you mean, who am I?
I'm the guy who
brought you here.
Now, we got to go.
Where the hell am I?
Listen to me. I'm a friend.
I'm a friend.
Yeah? What's my name?
What's my name?
Your name is Logan.
You need to trust me.
We have to go.
Follow me.
Now!
Do you know her?
No.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
Hey, these boys aren't gonna like
what you've done to this place.
We really need to go.
I'll find my own way.
Good luck.
(SIREN BLARES)
Colonel Stryker?
Colonel William Stryker?
Yes.
You're wanted for questioning
in connection with the death
of General Munson, sir.
(CRUMBLING)
(SHUSHING)