[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 1]
Don't come closer!
Don't come any closer! No!
Auntie Lan!
[Lu Nan, the mysterious CEO of Eminence made his debut
Nouveau riche from overseas ventures into the domestic market]
[Failing to commercialise traditional craft CEO fell into coma overnight]
Lu Nan, the CEO of Eminence made his debut.
Eminence will be listed in only a few months,
[Eminence's CEO will marry the top model Su Manni]
and has once again come to the fore.
Lu Nan and Su Manni, a model of his company
were spotted entering a hotel
together late at night.
They looked very close.Tying the knot is on the way.
These are documents
I've found about
Auntie Lan's orders.
Are you really going to
take their offer?
Grudges old and new.
Our seven years of marriage feud
must be settled now.
[Divorce Agreement]
That's Mr. Zhang!
Mr. Zhang! Mr. Zhang! Mr. Zhang!
What are you doing?
- Mr. Zhang!
-Mr. Zhang!
Come down! Mr. Zhang!
Mr. Zhang! Come down now!
It's dangerous there!
Where's Lu Nan?
Why didn't he come?
Send Lu Nan over here!
Otherwise,
[Software Park]
I'll jump down from here!
Don't jump!
I want everyone to know that
it's him
who drove the senior manager to death!
[Software Park]
Mr. Zhang, come down!
Come down and talk!
That's right, Mr. Zhang. Don't do anything stupid.
Mr. Lu. Mr. Lu. Mr. Lu.
Lu...
Lu Nan, you're finally here!
If I don't get my shares today,
I'll jump down from here!
You want shares?
[Share Transfer Contract]
Then get them yourself.
If you lie to me,
I'll...
I'll jump!
You either come down
Or jump now.
Three.
Two.
One.
Lu Nan, you tricked me!
Screw you!
Mr. Zhang!
I've already reported to the group
about Yu Qinglan.
You didn't do anything about it at the time.
Why should I take the blame
when things go wrong?
It's just losing a little money.
Why do you have to do this to me?
Nan!
- Mr. Zhang!.
- Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu, I'm sorry.
- Mr. Lu.
- Mr. Zhang.
When did you ever see
Mr. Lu giving anyone a second chance?
I'm sorry.
Tell it to the police.
Don't!
Don't! Don't!
Let's go, Mr. Zhang.
Forgive me!
IN fashion banquet is about to start.
[IN Fashion Banquet]
Manni!
[Su Manni]
Don't go!
[Best Ever]
[IN Fashion Banquet]
Manni,
you're a super model now.
Do you have any
plans for your future career?
We've heard that
you'll attend the red carpet tonight
with Mr. Lu
Why isn't Mr. Lu here?
Are you having relationship problems?
Manni,
one more thing.
After your contract expires,
will you renew your contract
with Eminence Fashion?
Well.
Today, we're here
for the IN fashion banquet.
These questions make us look like
we're trying to steal the show here.
Hello, sis.
It's been a long time.
What are you doing here?
Same as you.
I'm here to see the person I want to see.
But
you want to see your brother-in-law
and I want to see my husband.
You...
There are so many reporters here today.
You'd better behave yourself.
Come closer and make a pose!
Smile. Good!
Okay, look over here.
Manni,
who's this lady?
Why are you wearing the same dress?
What is your relationship?
Tell us about it.
Manni.
Tell us about it!
Su Bei!
Who told you to come back?
I'm back
because my husband said so.
I don't have to inform you, do I?
Mr. Lu?
No way!
How could he ask you to come back? He...
We're husband and wife.
We can't be separated forever.
I came back
this time
because he insisted.
Sis,
I know that
it wasn't easy for you to work for him.
But fortunately I'm back now.
From now on,
you don't have to work so hard.
Shame on you.
Have you forgotten how you got Eminence into trouble
and embarrassed Lu Nan?
He said he didn't hold the grudges anymore.
So I think
he wants me back
because he'd like to get back together with me.
After all, we're getting old.
Grandma would love to have some grandchildren.
Dream on!
Dear sis,
I'm not only going to ruin your reputation
but also take everything from you,
including your husband,
Lu Nan.
Do you think
I'm still the same person from seven years ago?
It's time for you
to give back what was taken from me.
Now that I'm back,
I'll make sure you pay the price.
Su Bei,
You should have died out there.
Why did you come back?
Manni,
Mr. Lu will be here soon.
Su Bei.
Seven years ago, you couldn't defeat me.
You won't defeat me now.
Mr. Zhang.
I'm here.
Hello!
Excuse me.
How do I get to the washroom?
Go out of the lobby,
and then go straight ahead and turn left.
It's Mr. Lu's car!
Mr. Lu is here!
Mr. Lu!
[Best Ever Awesome CEO Lu Nan Super Hot]
Lu Nan! Lu Nan!
Nan Nan!
Lu Nan?
When did he come back?
I thought he had been abroad to expand the market.
You're too lagged behind.
He came back a year ago to take over Eminence.
Otherwise, how could Eminence
turn the tide from
a downward spiral
to preparing for being listed?
Mr. Lu!
No wonder he's the top elite in Nanxi.
Mr. Lu, we've met before.
Do you still remember me?
I'll find an opportunity
to have a few drinks with Mr. Lu.
Why don't you come with me?
Alright.
- Mr. Lu.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Mr. Lu is young and successful.
The top one in Nanxi!
So nice to meet you.
All is well here.
Once the cameras are installed,
you only have three minutes
to test if they work.
Got it.
Room service.
Manni!
I love you!
Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu, help me!
Mr. Lu!
Help!
Manni!
What are you doing?
I love you, Manni!
Don't come any closer!
Security!
Manni!
What are you doing?
I love you, Manni!
I'll have someone take you to your room.
No!
Mr. Lu,
I got hurt just now.
Can you take me to my room?
Where's your assistant?
I don't know.
Mr. Lu,
I'm really scared.
Mr. Lu.
[Use mobile phone camera to capture
and provide live audio video streaming service]
[Loading]
They're going up.
Hurry up.
Try to stall them.
[Capturing now Time left]
Stall them for another two minutes.
Alright.
Which floor?
Eight.
Mr. Lu.
I'm really sorry
for the inconvenience.
I'll only give you five minutes.
They're on the last floor. Hurry up!
Hello.
Wait.
Close the door when you leave.
Okay
No need.
Leave it open.
Mr. Lu.
Why don't you stay here
and we can talk about renewing the contract?
One minute and thirty-four seconds left.
Are you sure you can be on time?
Mr. Lu.
That crazy guy just harassed me
and hurt my leg.
Would you please go to the bathroom
and bring a towel for me?
I want to put it on my leg.
[Operations Control Centre Mobile]
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu.
Have some water.
You've drugged the water,
right?
Mr...
Mr. Lu.
I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you know
how many women in Nanxi want to marry me?
Well, to be precise.
They want to sleep with me.
They try to drug my water
at least once or twice a month.
Your trick
doesn't work on me.
Mr. Lu.
I really don't know what you're talking about.
I didn't drug it.
Yeah?
Then drink it
and I'll believe you.
Ye Ting.
Plan B.
Drink  it.
Mr. Lu,
I like you very much.
Do you like me
or do you like the title as Mrs. Eminence CEO?
I like everything
about you.
If you still want to stay at Eminence,
then stop pulling off your tricks.
Mr. Lu!
If you don't want to be a model,
you can ask the company to make a major insurance payouts for you,
so that you can compensate us
for our investment.
Mr. Lu.
I won't risk my career for this.
I'm serious about you, Mr. Lu.
Are you ignoring my warning?
Mr. Lu!
Sis.
What a surprise gift!
This is a bit too much!
It seems that
you're putting on a big show for me.
Mr. Lu, I...
Get up and talk.
Don't get us wrong, sister.
Mr. Lu and I
were talking about work.
Manni,
I didn't get you wrong.
It's just that
if someone tries to make a big deal of
out of this,
I'm afraid no one would believe
what I said about it.
I know you're so desperate to get ahead,
but you can't do this to your brother-in-law!
I didn't!
Brother-in-law?
What's this about?
Am I also going to
play a loving couple with you?
Lu Nan,
I know you blame me.
But you can't pretend you don't know me.
Miss,
you're overdoing it.
Where is Su Manni's room?
This way I think.
Manni,
I know you like Lu Nan.
It's okay if you steal him away from me.
But you're bringing in the press as well.
If words spread out,
it will be a humiliation for Lu Nan!
No, Mr. Lu.
I didn't.
It's not me.
It was you!
You must have set me up!
I don't care
what you're up to.
But I hope you know
what to say and what not to say.
Look!
This is her room.
Come on!
Mr. Lu.
Did you stay in the room
with Su Manni?
Does it mean that
you and Su Manni are a couple?
Right, Mr. Lu.
Is it true? Tell us.
You know what?
If I slap you now
and tell everybody that you seduced your brother-in-law,
what would the paparazzi react?
You were alone in a room together.
Does that mean
you're about to get married?
Right, Mr. Lu.
Alone in a room together?
You can see for yourselves.
Hurry up!
Sorry guys.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Mr. Lu and I
are just friends.
A crazy fan of mine
harassed me
and I hurt my leg by accident.
So Mr. Lu
was very nice to bring me back.
This lady
is my elder sister.
She heard that I was injured
and came to see me.
So you're biological sisters?
Really?
Yes.
We're sisters of the same father.
Take a picture!
Take more pictures!
A few more from this angle.
We have a situation here.
I'll see you later.
Are you really going to
take their offer?
You know what Auntie Lan meant to me.
Only when I get close to Lu Nan
can I find the fragrance brocade.
But the information and evidence we have
is not enough to prove that
Lu Nan took the brocade.
But he's the most likely.
Auntie Lan called me
before the accident.
She said that Lu Nan came to her several times
and offered a high price to buy the brocade.
But she refused.
According to our investigation,
Zhang Yuan came
soon after that.
Then on the night before the delivery,
the factory caught on fire.
Don't you think
it's all too much of a coincidence?
Now I see.
You're right.
But Su Su,
Lu Nan went to great lengths to get you into Eminence,
because he didn't know that
you're actually the famous model agent Annie.
You and him...
are a married couple who has been separated for seven years.
Married couple...
Don't you remember that
you signed a divorce agreement
that you wouldn't be able to get anything if you divorce.
So...
What are you going to do about it?
Since I didn't get a divorce then,
I'm not going to
let him go now.
Grudges old and new.
Our seven years of marriage feud
must be settled now.
Even if we get a divorce,
you better stay abroad
and not come back
without my consent.
I'm leaving.
I won't bother you.
You're just as ruthless as before.
I'll hit back,
twice as hard!
So
is she really my wife?
If her name is Su Bei,
then yes.
I'm married?
You'd better tell me what happened,
or I'll send you to Africa for business.
I...
I promised your grandma
I wouldn't tell you about
your marriage with Su Bei seven years ago.
So you do as she says?
Who's your boss
and who pays your salary?
Right.
Yes, you're my boss,
and you pay my salary,
but you have to listen to your grandma too.
Why did she keep it a secret from me?
She...
She doesn't want to make you upset.
After all,
we called Su Bei many times
during the five years when you were in a coma
after the car accident,
but she never came back.
Anyway,
when your grandma returns,
you can ask her yourself.
But
Su Bei went abroad.
I tried so hard but didn't find her.
Why is she suddenly back now?
That's weird.
Have someone investigate
what she did abroad over the past few years
and why she came back.
[Nanxi City Hospital]
Auntie Lan,
I'm back.
You were the one she thought of the most
before the accident.
She'd be so happy to know
you're back.
Jiajia,
thank you so much
for what you've done.
Sorry.
After the accident,
everyone at the factory left.
It's all my fault.
No. You've done a good job.
She has dedicated herself to the company.
But now there's nothing left.
No.
I came back
to find out the truth
about who tried to kill her.
How's
the investigation going about the factory?
On the day of the fire,
the factory's camera circuit was broken.
So,
there was no evidence left.
I asked Yu Jia about Zhang Yuan.
She said she didn't know either.
She only knew that Zhang Yuan contacted Auntie Lan on his own initiative.
By the way,
Zhang Yuan was sent to the detention center by Lu Nan today.
He probably won't be out for a dozen of days.
I'll go see him then.
There are so many coincidences.
It's unlikely that
they're all isolated incidents.
Go ahead with the investigation.
It's a pity that we didn't seize
the great opportunity today.
Su Manni is lame.
Actually,
it's not a complete waste.
The super model seduced her brother-in-law.
If this video is made public,
it'll make next week's headlines, right?
But...
Was Lu Nan
really pretending that he didn't know you?
Whether he's pretending
or not,
I'm looking forward to
what he'll do next.
[Eminence Group]
[Eminence Group Co. Ltd]
Sor...sorry...
We've met again.
That's destiny.
It's just you and me now.
Stop faking it.
After all, we've been married for seven years.
You talk so harsh.
It's heartbreaking!
Watch your language.
We've been separated
for seven years,
so our relationship is virtually over.
That's what you really think of me?
Stop it.
Charm offense doesn't work on me.
I almost hit your car
and gave you a fright.
So take the money
as my apology.
I don't like to owe people anything,
especially you.
What do you mean?
[Eminence Group]
Hello, Annie.
I'm Tang Xin, Eminence's administrative director.
Welcome on board!
I've completed
all the paperwork for you.
Mr. Lu is still in a meeting,
so I'll show you around first.
This way, please.
I've sent you the file.
OK.
Find the information.
The whole building is owned by Eminence.
The top floor is the headquarters.
We're on the sixth floor,
where you'll be in charge of
the Eminence Starlight Agency.
Our models are all very excited
that you're coming.
They've been waiting for you early on.
All of them?
Except for those who're at work,
the rest are all here.
I'll take you to meet them.
It's over there.
I'm sorry. I have to take a call.
No worries. I'll go myself.
Alright. The model training room is right over there.
OK.
Hello?
Did you hear that
Annie is really of something?
I heard that when Juli first started with Annie,
she was still nobody.
Then Juli made it to the Big Four
in less than four years.
She was endorsed by top brands thanks to Annie.
Really?
Yes!
Every little connection and resource
that Annie has
is world class!
With her credentials,
she can help you rise to international fame
even though you're a loser.
Exactly.
You're new here, aren't you?
It's my first day here.
But
I read online that
Annie is extremely strict.
It's a living hell
to work with her.
I heard she's really crazy.
Could she be a harsh and callous woman?
I think so.
If not,
then how come she never
takes interviews and does publicity?
Right.
You know what?
I think she must be
an old, ugly witch.
Stop it.
Annie is coming soon.
Who do you think you are?
A rookie who's never walked on runway.
Who are you
to tell us what to do?
Sister Manni. Sister Manni. Sister Manni.
Here you are.
Sister Manni. Sister Manni.
You look gorgeous!
I love your lipstick color!
Right!
Hey you, rookie!
Sister Manni is here.
Come and say hi.
She's the chief here.
Do you want to say hi?