(- So...)
- Look at Tae-Gyeong's face.
(- what's...)
- Are you okay?
(- going on here is...)
- This is too much.
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
Gosh, you surprised me.
Woo Tae-Gyeong.
I have something serious to ask you.
What is it?
You have to answer honestly.
Okay. What is it?
So...
what...
do you want to eat today?
Why are you asking me
that all of a sudden?
Gosh. Don't ask me that.
Do you want pizza?
Or... There's pizza,
and there's pizza.
Then pizza.
Okay. Pizza.
What? Potato pizza? My favorite?
Okay.
What is this?
Da-On.
Tae-Gyeong. I have something to ask you.
What is it?
What...
is your favorite cake?
What?
A place with great cakes
just opened up in front of my house,
so I was going to get you
and the others some.
What's your favorite?
I like cake with whipped cream.
Is that so? Okay. I'll see you later.
What's going on?
No way.
What is it?
What?
Oh, right.
Aren't you going to ask me something?
Da-On and Namgung keep asking me
strange questions.
Right. So...
Is there a color...
that you don't like for a party hat?
- What?
- You don't, right?
Come to the student council room
at 6pm tonight.
If they make it so obvious,
how am I supposed to react?
6pm.
Even if it's lame,
I have to act surprised.
What? What's going on?
Is there nobody in here?
Woo Tae-Gyeong, congratulations...
On becoming the newest member
of the student council!
(Congratulations on joining
the student council!)
(Tae-Gyeong joined the student council!)
Surprise! Were you surprised?
I was very surprised.
Da-On, our surprise was a success.
Here you go.
Be honest. It was obvious, right?
We tried to do it secretly,
but none of us have done this before.
To be honest, I figured it out,
but I didn't think you'd prepare it
like this.
Thank you, guys.
There's no need.
After you joined, the atmosphere
of the student council got a lot better.
Of course. We have to have
Tae-Gyeong in the student council now.
Don't you agree?
You can't leave even if you want to now.
Saying that there's too much work
or it's exhausting won't work.
I know that. It was hard for me to join.
I'm never leaving.
Then shall we cut the cake?
We can't let his face be clean
on a day like this.
Hurry up.
Hey. Just stay quiet.
It's the unspoken rule to smash cake
onto the newest member's face.
Woo Tae-Gyeong will like it too.
You didn't do that to me
during my welcoming party.
I couldn't even sleep that night.
I was very upset.
Is that so? Then just a little.
Okay.
Gosh, Shin-Woo. You're so hilarious.
Tae-Gyeong, are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- Cheers!
(Congratulations on joining
the student council!)
It's not over yet, is it?
Welcome, So-Hee.
Lee So-Hee? What are you doing here?
Right. She wanted to congratulate
Tae-Gyeong, so I told her to come.
Congratulations, Tae-Gyeong.
Thank you, So-Hee.
We'll see each other more often now.
Right. I guess so.
Okay.
It's time for Namgung's second surprise.
I will present him with a gift.
Give me a round of applause!
Ta-da.
What is it?
Gosh, you shouldn't ask that.
Unwrap it.
(Saebit Boys High School
Student Council's Ultimate Cutie)
Wow.
Designed by Namgung. What do you think?
Do you like it?
Right. Of course you like it.
There's only one in the entire world.
It's a custom design.
I did everything by hand...
That's enough already.
Stop bragging about it.
- Namgung. Thank you.
- Yes?
The more I look at it,
the better it looks.
Let's take a photograph.
We have to leave a record.
Okay. The photo zone...
will be right here.
Gather around, everyone.
Hey. Smile.
(Gyeong)
I said, smile.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Da-On. Nice.
(Gyeong)
There you go.
There we go. Let's take a photo now.
Da-On. Just be good at one thing.
Why are you so perfect? Right?
I agree.
Da-On, you're very cool.
Goodness.
What a nice image.
You must feel jealous.
- Aren't you going to take a photo?
- Right. We need to take a photo.
Okay. Gather around everyone.
How should we pose?
Should we make hearts?
Hearts? I think it's a great idea.
Like this?
Like this. A heart.
Okay. I'll take the photo now.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, my. I was just kidding.
Hold on. What should we do?
Smile. Hey, can you smile?
I'm going to take the photo again.
1, 2, 3.
Gosh. Look at this.
Look.
You came out nice in that.
Gosh.
The photo doesn't do me justice.
I agree. The camera doesn't
fully capture your handsomeness.
Are we out of drinks? I'll get some more
at the vending machine.
Let's go together...
Da-On. Let's go together.
I want something to drink too.
Tae-Gyeong, stay here.
I'll go with So-Hee.
It's already been a month since
Tae-Gyeong joined the student council.
Time flies.
- But Tae-Gyeong...
- Sin Da-On.
Do you...
like Woo Tae-Gyeong?
What?
No, I mean, you're always together,
and the way you look at each other
is no joke.
People would think you're dating.
We're just good friends.
People don't see it like that.
They'd all think it's strange.
To be honest, I was a bit surprised too.
Is that really it?
Yes. That's it.
Don't lie to me no matter what.
Okay?
Okay. I won't lie.
But then again, it doesn't make sense
for Sin Da-On would like Woo Tae-Gyeong.
Let's go.
The guys are probably waiting for us.
Okay.
Woo Tae-Gyeong.
What are you doing?
Well...
Your shoelaces were untied.
You're clumsy, so you trip often.
People like you must tie them well.
Thank you.
But why is Noh Shin-Woo
being so nice to me?
How strange.
What?
Noh Shin-Woo.
Do you...
feel bad for smashing cake in my face?
Yes. You hit the nail on the head.
Noh Shin-Woo is nice to me
when he feels bad.
Okay.
I get it.
What do you get?
(Saebit Boys High School
Student Council's Ultimate Cutie)
Here. Try some of this.
It's really good.
Hey. What are you doing?
We're all family here.
How are we family?
What do you mean?
Da-On's the firstborn, I'm second,
you're the troublemaking younger sister.
Don't you agree, Da-On?
Da-On. Am I really
the troublemaking younger sister?
No. So-Hee's the cute younger sister.
I need to answer this call.
Eat this and cheer up,
our cute younger sister.
- Get that out of my face.
- Okay. That works for me.
Do you want to go to karaoke after?
Does anyone object?
Nobody? Then let's all together.
What is this?
- What is it?
- Didn't you get a message?
Oh, right. Your phone.
Something came up,
so Da-On's going home first.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
Isn't that Da-On's bag?
- I'll bring it to him.
- No.
I'll bring it to him.
His place is on my way home,
and I wanted to go home early...
because I'm tired.
Hey.
I said I'll bring it to him.
Woo Tae-Gyeong can bring it to him.
It's late, so it's dangerous too.
More than that,
you have to go to karaoke with me.
Why would I go to karaoke with you?
You can't even sing.
I can't sing?
Hey. I'm better than you are.
My gosh.
I'll get going first.
Thank you guys for today.
Have fun, and I'll see you on Monday.
Don't go.
Let's go...
to karaoke together.
I'm really sorry.
Next time.
Gosh, I should've gotten it fixed.
Da-On!
Tae-Gyeong. What are you doing here?
Thank you.
I was in such a hurry that I forgot
I left my bag.
Why did you leave in such a hurry?
Well... It might sound strange to you,
but it's been a while
since my mother called me,
so I was excited. I thought
she wanted to have dinner together.
I guess that wasn't the case.
Right.
As usual, she just asked me for a favor
and hung up.
She has a lot of things...
that are more important than me.
I thought I was used to
her indifference towards me,
but I guess I'm not.
Nothing...
belongs to me at home.
Then why do you work so hard?
I don't want to disappoint my parents.
Plus, I hate disappointing people.
I feel a lot better after I told you.
For some strange reason,
I can tell you these things easily.
It's my first time talking about this.
You can be honest with me.
You're...
allowed to.
(Do you...)
(like Woo Tae-Gyeong?)
(Light on Me)
(Good morning, guys.)
(What is it? Did you do something
wrong?)
(- Can I sit here?
- Of course.)
When did you guys get so close?
Da-On isn't an object
that belongs to you.
(Don't think that
you're special to him.)
(The only person that's special
to Sin Da-On...)
is me.
(Light on Me)