I'm pretty sure he saw me.
This is driving me crazy.
Noh Shin-Woo.
Why are you avoiding me?
You even ignored me.
When did I do that?
I didn't see you.
Was I mistaken?
I thought you were avoiding me.
Why didn't you come to
the student council room today?
I didn't see you all day.
I was just busy.
Okay. If you're busy, you should go.
Okay.
Did I do something wrong?
No. I didn't do anything.
Then why does it seem like
he's avoiding me?
I knew you'd be in here.
I can do this alone.
If we do it together,
you can finish sooner.
Plus, didn't I tell you to call me
when you do this?
Okay. Thank you.
Oh, right. How are things with Shin-Woo?
It seems like you've gotten closer.
I thought we got closer,
but Shin-Woo
is suddenly avoiding me again.
Shin-Woo is?
Yes. It's very difficult.
I didn't do anything.
Maybe he's just a bit shy.
Shin-Woo is?
Shin-Woo gets shy really easily.
His ears are always red.
Then should I avoid him...
until he isn't shy anymore?
Better yet,
why don't you approach him
more aggressively?
"Let's hang out."
"Let's grab some food."
Like this.
Okay. I'll try that.
I knew it.
Whenever you say, "I'll try that",
I feel refreshed.
I like that.
Oh, right.
Did you show your parents your grades?
Weren't they really happy?
No. They didn't have much of a reaction.
They didn't have much of a reaction?
They're not the type of people
to express themselves.
I'm used to that too.
To be honest,
I've never been complimented.
I had no idea.
Of course you didn't know.
It won't leave a scar.
(Administration)
Am I the only who sees
that Shin-Woo isn't here?
He'd always hide out here
because his classmates are noisy.
Did he make a new friend?
He must be busy these days.
The vice president has a lot to do.
Oh, right.
You still haven't gotten that fixed?
Can you even see what's on the screen?
I don't really look at my phone.
Plus, I can focus on my studies more,
so it's nice.
Imagine if my mom heard that.
I know. It's admirable.
What's wrong?
It's the first time...
someone touched my cheek
since I was a kid.
Gosh. You have really nice skin.
Of course, it's not as nice as mine.
- Wow.
- Stop looking at me.
Why? You didn't say anything
when Da-On touched you,
so why are you only saying
something to me?
Gosh. Namgung, are you jealous?
Hey. We were just talking about you.
From now on, if I want to see you,
I should talk about you.
You're here.
Yes.
Noh Shin-Woo. Good morning.
Oh, it's not good morning.
It's good afternoon.
Although it's not lunchtime yet.
The weather is quite nice.
There's no fine dust,
and there's a light breeze.
It's...
the perfect spring day.
Yes. You're right.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to study.
Yes. Tae-Gyeong's right.
Gosh, the weather is really nice today.
Do you guys want to go on a walk
after lunch?
- What do you think, Namgung?
- What?
Okay.
It's a bit tiresome,
but I feel like I should agree.
Okay. Let's go on a walk later.
A walk.
Okay. Let's go after lunch.
Sounds good.
Gosh.
Is something wrong?
I keep getting the wrong answer.
Let me see.
You can't put this equation in the back.
Bring it to the front
and transpose it with x.
Oh, is this how it's done?
Yes. This is a bit hard.
That's why there's a formula
to solve this.
Can I write on here?
Yes.
I'm just teaching this to you.
This isn't a cafe.
Aren't you being too noisy
in a space we all share?
What?
Shin-Woo. I was a bit loud, right?
I just need to teach him this.
I'll be done soon. Will that be okay?
Why are you starting a fight?
Since when the student council room
become a studying room?
The sounds from my game are louder.
No.
I was being loud. I'm sorry, Shin-Woo.
Yes, sir.
No. Do you need me to do something?
Yes. The library got new books,
and they asked for some help
organizing them.
They need two people.
Then I'll some people who are free
to the library.
Yes, sir. Okay.
Tae-Gyeong and Shin-Woo.
Can you guys help?
So what did you do wrong?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Wait. That's my favorite bread.
I knew it. Da-On got it for me...
Things were hectic that day,
so I forgot that I agreed to meet you.
The battery in my cell phone died,
so I couldn't call.
Gosh, is that what happened?
You're such a bad guy.
So-Hee. Don't forgive him.
Should I throw all of this out?
I'll go throw it out.
Be quiet.
Da-On.
I'm sorry, So-Hee. Don't be mad.
Don't do that again.
Okay. I won't.
Did you wait long that day?
No. I didn't wait.
I couldn't get in contact with you,
so I met up with my friends.
What? I saw you waiting for Da-On...
in the student council room...
Oh, yes. Nice.
This is my favorite.
This is a wise saying from
Mr. Namgung Si-Un.
"Knowledge is power."
Don't bring him with you next time.
Tae-Gyeong and Shin-Woo
are in the library to clean up.
He said he was bored,
so he came with me.
What kind of kid is Woo Tae-Gyeong?
He seems like he's close
with the guys...
and you.
He's really cute.
He has a unique charm.
Why would a guy say that another guy
is charming?
Why not?
You saw him that day.
He's really honest.
He has a refreshing charm.
I've never seen you say
that someone is charming.
Is that so?
So-Hee, if you want to get close with
Tae-Gyeong too, I'll help.
Okay. I got it.
Okay.
Right. I have to help out
with serving lunch, so I should go.
Are you serving lunch today?
Can you give me a lot later?
Okay. I'll see you later, So-Hee.
Okay. Message me.
Are you curious about Woo Tae-Gyeong?
What are you talking about? I'm not.
I think you are.
I told you I wasn't.
What's wrong with you?
You can eat all of this.
Hey, Lee So-Hee.
I'm sure you're aware of this too,
but Da-On takes good care of people.
I don't think Tae-Gyeong has ever met
anyone like him before.
That's why he listens
to what Da-On says.
Da-On also thinks he's cute.
That's as far as I know.
Why are you telling me this?
I need to repay you for the snacks.
I like that.
"I like that"?
I'm at a loss for words.
Did something happen today?
Did something upset you?
No.
Then did I do something wrong?
No, you didn't.
Then why are you acting like this?
What do you mean?
It's like we're back at square one.
Didn't we become a bit closer?
Am I the only one who thought that?
Lunchtime is almost over.
What?
Let's back at to work. We need to eat.
Okay.
Woo Tae-Gyeong.
There's nothing that you don't do.
Of course.
The school can't run without me.
Did you organize the library well?
Yes. Sure.
Did you make up with Shin-Woo?
No.
It's okay.
Here. Eat up and cheer up.
You want me to eat all of this?
Yes. Make sure to finish it.
Eat up, Tae-Gyeong.
Shin-Woo, you get this much too.
Do things in moderation.
What if there's nothing left?
You have to eat too.
Gosh. Okay. You nag so much, Shin-Woo.
You could be nicer.
You're always complaining.
What?
Guys! Over here.
So tell me.
Did you organize the library well?
Tae-Gyeong?
- No.
- No?
Let's say that you did.
Okay. What's your review
of today's lunch, Shin-Woo?
It's not that good.
Okay. Let's say that it's not that good.
You guys are going
to go on a walk later, right?
Do you want to get ice cream
before we go?
- No.
I'm sorry,
but what's wrong with you guys?
You guys were okay up until
a few days ago.
It's confusing because
you keep going back and forth.
What are you talking?
You're not done yet, right?
Gosh. I almost got indigestion.
You're just in time.
I'm so glad to see you today.
This looks good. Thank you for the food.
Right. Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy your meal.
You too, Shin-Woo.
Hey, Tae-Gyeong. Give me your hand.
My hand?
Open up your hand.
What? Hold on.
What is this?
Are you giving Woo Tae-Gyeong
your yogurt?
You always gave me your yogurt,
a benefit of serving lunch,
but you gave it to Tae-Gyeong today?
I always gave it to you in the past.
Let's let Tae-Gyeong have it today.
Our kind Namgung should share.
I'm sharing just this once.
But keep in mind...
that I'm really hurt.
Okay. I get it. I'll be sure
to give it to you next time.
Right. Tae-Gyeong.
Do you want to get tutored in math?
Do you know someone?
I do. He's the first in the school.
His name is Shin Da-On.
What?
I'll tutor you.
You will?
Yes. It was fun when I was helping you.
I get to review it too.
I would love that, but you're busy.
Gosh, it's fine.
Do you have time today? Do you want
to have a trial lesson after school?
Okay.
Are you done already?
Yes. I'll get going first.
Hey. Wait for us.
Aren't you going to
the student council room?
We agreed to go on a walk after lunch.
Right. We need to have ice cream too.
Forget it. Leave me out.
Shin-Woo. Hold on.
- Did he really hit him?
- What happened?
- That was harsh.
- What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I must've pulled on your arm too hard.
Are you okay? Did you get burnt?
Da-On. That's not the problem right now.
Are you okay? Isn't it hot?
I'm fine.
Did you have to push him away like that?
He could've gotten seriously hurt.
Also,
aren't you going to apologize?
You idiot.
Noh Shin-Woo.
If you have a problem with me,
say it to my face.
Don't let it out on the wrong person.
Let go.
What are you doing right now?
I tried to understand you until now.
But I can't hold back anymore.
I get that you hate me.
If you hate me, try to like me.
I'll do the same with you.
(Light on Me)
I have to deal with something
that's harder than math.
Over there. Isn't that Da-On?
Why are you so nice to him?
He's not really in the student council.
I can carry them too.
You're so greedy
when you can't even do it right.
I'll pretend I didn't see anything.
I think that's only right.
(Light on Me)