♪ I got bills ♪
♪ I gotta pay ♪
♪ So I'm gon' work, work, work
Every day ♪
♪ I got mouths I gotta feed ♪
♪ So I'm gon' make sure
Everybody eats ♪
- I don't like you doing this here.
- Where should we do it, then, Samu?
I don't know,
but what if the cops catch us?
Why would the cops show up here?
We're three innocent schoolkids.
- Your mother's in jail for this.
- Wrong.
She's in jail
because some son of a bitch ratted us out.
But this is different.
We're like family here.
Fine, but we have to keep it quiet.
Not a word to anyone.
Okay? Anyone.
Relax, we know what we're doing.
♪ I got mouths I gotta feed ♪
♪ So I'm gon' make sure everybody eats ♪
♪ I got bills ♪
♪ Woke up and I bumped my head
Stubbed my toe on the edge of the bed ♪
♪ Opened the fridge
And the food all gone ♪
♪ Neighbor damn dog
Done crapped on my lawn ♪
♪ Hopped in the car
And the car won't start ♪
♪ It's too damn hot
But I still gotta walk ♪
♪ Behind an old lady in the grocery line
Praying that my card don't get declined ♪
♪ Ah damn, ah damn, ah damn, ah damn! ♪
♪ Oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man! ♪
♪ Ah damn, oh man, ah damn, oh man! ♪
♪ I got bills ♪
♪ Bringing everybody trouble ♪
♪ And my shoes ♪
♪ My shoes ♪
♪ I said, my shoes ♪
♪ Ain't got no soul ♪
♪ I got bills I gotta pay ♪
- Keep it up, Valerio.
- I can't believe it!
Good. You finally learned how to cheat.
I don't cheat, sweetheart.
The thing is, I am... oof, one of a kind.
And I have great study buddies.
We go at it hard every afternoon.
And every night.
- You're kidding, right?
- Mm. Hmm. No, I don't think so.
This is serious. Very serious.
♪ I got bills ♪
♪ Yo mama got bills
Yo daddy got bills ♪
♪ Yo sister got bills ♪
- ♪ Yo auntie got bills ♪
- ♪ I got bills ♪
♪ Yo uncle got bills ♪
♪ Everybody got bills
Everybody got bills ♪
- Shh! No, it's his turn.
- Stop! Stop!
- Quiet. Which one was it?
- It tickles!
Ah, okay. Potassium nitrate.
What?
- Take off a piece of clothing.
- What do you mean?
- He got it right, didn't he?
- Yes, but he's wearing too much clothing.
This girl learns fast.
- Not as fast as you.
- Oh, really? Not as fast as me? Ah!
Show me some respect.
I'm the teacher here.
I never thought studying
could be so much fun.
Do you realize
you could even graduate if you want to?
You could even go to college.
- For real.
- I don't know.
I never put any thought into my future.
In fact, it never occurred to me
I could have one. Pfft.
Well, you could.
- You guys are going to London, right?
- Mm-hmm. King's College.
- Why don't you join us?
- No way.
I don't have the grades or the money
to get into a place like that.
Neither do I, but his mothers will...
- We got in thanks to our connections.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Because my mothers are friends
with the dean.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't suppose they could...?
Well... my mothers are vouching
for Cayetana because...
well, b-because she's my girlfriend.
I'm not saying
that you and I aren't a couple,
but they know her well.
They've known her longer.
They don't know you yet.
Mm-hmm.
- So, I'm nobody, right?
- I didn't say that.
- No.
- That's not it.
- It's okay.
- I didn't mean that.
There is a word
for you two being together, but...
there's no word for this.
Don't worry.
You've already done enough for me.
Hey, it's fine.
♪ Got me thinkin' about
Peaches and scream ♪
♪ Peaches and scream, peaches and scream ♪
♪ Peaches and scream
Peaches and scream... ♪
Gin and tonic, please.
♪ Who am I anymore... ♪
What's this blackout thing about?
A blackout. It's just that.
This Friday at midnight,
it'll be lights out at the club.
- And that's it?
- People dig the dark.
They can do what they want
without being seen.
You could bang three guys
in front of Nadia without her finding out.
I'd be happy if you didn't say anything.
It's better for her.
Oh? It's better for her to live a lie?
If she finds out,
she might end things with me
and forget all about New York.
Why risk it?
That's what I was thinking.
Why did you take that risk?
- Why did you kiss me?
- Why do you think I did it?
I'm with someone too.
But unlike your relationship, mine's real.
♪ Wild child ♪
Are you happy?
- ♪ Wild child... ♪
- Yes.
Sure.
I see Nadia
isn't the only one living a lie.
It's on the house.
Your hands are freezing.
It's okay. It's no big deal.
You didn't see your face.
Ander...
Please don't say it's no big deal.
It is.
Chemo is killing me,
and I'm scared shitless.
And so are you.
Maybe we should stop acting
like it's no big deal.
Lucrecia, do you have a minute?
It's about Columbia.
♪ Let's get together ♪
- ♪ Let's make some noise... ♪
- Take a seat.
I wanted to tell you
that you were both ranked highest,
so we have to ask you
to make one last effort
so the panel can make a decision.
Next Wednesday,
you'll need to do an oral presentation
that goes into more detail
on the last topic you addressed.
- So? Nice, huh? Whoo!
- Oh!
- Hey! Wow!
- Ouch.
It's because of chemo. I have cancer.
I'm sure you have lots of questions,
but you have Wikipedia for that.
I get tired easily.
I hated him.
I blamed him for my illness.
The champagne bottle broke.
The neck fell by the restroom,
and I went to pick it up to throw it out.
Polo was there.
What are you talking about?
I lost control.
I stabbed him in the heart
with the glass.
- You're nuts. Why would you confess?
- What does it matter?
I'm as good as dead.
I won't let you sacrifice yourself
to protect someone, okay?
- How long has he been sick?
- For months.
- I only recently found out myself.
- What do the doctors say?
Not much.
He's about to finish chemo,
and we'll see after that.
But he'll make it, right?
Of course he will.
It's Ander.
He doesn't deserve this.
Not everyone gets what they deserve.
You knew, right?
Do you think I didn't want to tell you?
- That I wanted to deal with it on my own?
- Why didn't you tell me?
Because Ander asked me
to keep it a secret.
And because I thought,
what did I have to gain from telling you?
Would you have cured him? Besides...
sometimes, the truth is...
useless.
I'm sorry.
And thanks... for everything.
You're the best thing I've got, Samu.
And the only...
- Don't talk nonsense.
- No, I really mean it.
We've turned your house into a drug lab,
and you just grin and bear it.
As soon as the last batch is finished,
I promise you, it will be over.
We'll shut down the business.
And then you and I
will have a very boring life.
I'd really like that.
We just found out.
It sucks.
He's tired of hiding it.
It's taking longer than we expected.
And how are you holding up?
Never mind me. What matters now is him.
I try to get him to go out, have fun,
and forget everything, but...
He's very lucky to have you by his side,
you know?
If you only knew.
I know.
A word of advice.
If you want to keep your fling a secret,
you should be more discreet.
But relax, I won't say a word.
There's no secret fling, damn it.
He's my sister's boyfriend.
Yeah. Crazy, huh?
Look, being cheated on
makes us... stronger.
Try to see it that way.
I know because my boyfriend
cheated on me with your sister.
- When are you going to tell her?
- Never.
Nadia can't leave Malick now.
- Why?
- She needs him to go to New York.
He'll also be there next year.
That's why my dad let her apply
for the scholarship.
If she found out
he's using her as a beard,
she'd scrap the whole idea. I know her.
- The contract has arrived.
- Has it?
- Mm-hmm.
- When will it be signed?
It's with the lawyers now.
It will take a few days.
The only thing is...
there's a clause
that allows Yeray to withdraw the funding
- at any time during the first five years.
- What?
He'll be pulling our strings
all that time.
- Five years?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm going to tell that bastard off.
- No.
You won't say anything.
Especially not now.
WE HAVE SOMETHING TO CELEBRATE TONIGHT,
RIGHT?
Have fun.
Hi. I'm looking for...
Ah.
...this book.
Sorry, I've got it.
Nadia, you know it's essential
for the presentation,
and it's not online.
Well, I've got it.
I need to ask you a question.
If you knew someone was being cheated on,
would you tell them?
I'm sorry.
I never apologized to you
for what happened.
Why now?
Because... you never know
how much time we have left in this world.
And now that I'm starting
something serious with someone,
I understand you better than ever.
I always thought
you were cold and heartless...
until I helped break your heart
into pieces.
I'm really sorry, Lu.
I'm done with the book.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
Is that what you wanted to talk about?
Or is someone else cheating?
No, no one.
Forget about it.
How are you?
Fine.
So...
are you training hard?
With the punching bag?
Do we have to speak in Morse code?
- Come on, you have to be fucking kidding.
- You need to be careful here, baby.
You should have taken
your own advice, hon.
I trust no one.
What a depressing life.
I don't want that for myself.
- Well, it's the life you're leading now.
- Yeah.
Until I get the money I need
to pay off the school.
- Then to hell with it.
- You'll always need more.
Or do you think
that once you've tasted real seafood,
you can go back to eating canned sardines?
See if you can get it
through that thick skull of yours:
I'll pay for every shrimp I eat
with my own work.
No hustling and no scumbags.
This conversation is over.
You can see the scumbags
coming a mile away.
It's the good guys,
the ones who look like angels,
who are the ones you have to look out for.
What the hell are you saying?
I'm saying...
that our living room was bugged.
And all the "scumbags"
were either taken down to the station
or are in jail.
All but one.
The little angel.
No. Samu would never do that to me.
- How do you know that?
- Because he loves me.
Do you know what that means?
What if there was a way to make sure?
Samu, I need to find out
who it was that stabbed us in the back.
You can't imagine how badly.
Didn't we want a boring life
with no trouble?
Are you with me or not?
The snitch
must be on the security footage.
We had cameras everywhere,
but the police confiscated them.
But if we're lucky, the security company
will have a copy of everything.
But my mom doesn't know
which company we had,
and the police seized all the contracts,
invoices, and everything.
A couple of months ago,
one of the cameras broke, and I kept it.
It should have a sticker
with the company's details on it.
Why would they give you
a copy of the tape?
Because everyone has a price, Samu.
- Look over there.
- ♪ Now I'm back ♪
♪ More venomous lyrics
To claim a victim ♪
♪ I get a lot of love
From kids with backpacks ♪
It's here.
Shit, there's nothing on it.
You could try calling
all the security companies in the country
and see if you were clients.
Although I think
that'd be confidential information.
I don't know. It's your call.
Wait a minute, wait a minute...
Maybe there's no need for that.
Why are you here?
I came to...
to see if I can do anything for you.
If you need money,
I could get you the best doctors.
What country do you think we live in,
Polo?
I already have the best doctors...
and I don't need to be rich
or be a charity case to get them.
Money's your answer to everything, huh?
I just want to help.
But I don't know how.
Do you have plans right now?
I'm bored out of my mind.
How many more chemo sessions
do you have left?
I don't know.
The last session is next week.
Then I'll get the results,
and they'll tell me if I'm done.
Right.
Does it really fuck you up afterwards?
Omar says I look like the girl
from The Exorcist.
How are things going with him?
This whole thing's a bummer.
Awful timing.
Well...
bad times are great for finding out
who will stay by your side.
Do you mean Cayetana?
And Valerio.
- You're cheating on her with Valerio?
- No, I'm not cheating. I swear.
But...
well, we're together. The three of us.
Fuck.
You're getting laid more than anyone.
But it's not just about getting laid.
There's more to it than that.
And I think it's going well.
I guess it's not exactly normal,
but... who cares about being normal...
if you can be happy?
Shit, you've gone all Zen,
and you're not even high.
- Let me try that.
- Just a little.
How does this go?
Badly. At first, it's always bad.
- Holy shit.
- It's strong stuff.
Do you like sushi?
I'm not hungry.
No.
Uh, I was thinking
we could go on vacation to Japan.
Well, a lot could happen
between now and then.
Are you upset
over that kid in your class?
Mm-hmm.
I see.
I bought you something.
Stay the night.
Tonight... and as many nights as you want.
Just look at his eyes...
Ah.
I love you so much, guys.
I really do. I love you a lot.
Aww, so let's see...
You told Ander that we're together,
the three of us?
- Correct.
- Right.
And what if he tells someone?
What do we do?
It's no big deal.
We've all been called worse.
It felt good to say it out loud.
That the three of us are together.
Why do we have to stop being three
when we've only just started?
Why don't you come to London?
Huh, cute curls?
My mothers will be asking
for a couple of favors already,
but they can ask for three.
One, two...
- and three.
- But how will you convince them?
I don't know.
Right.
I know a girl who is very good
at making up crazy stories.
Well, to be honest,
it's kind of my superpower.
- Is it?
- It is, right?
What if you show me more
of that superpower?
Yeah?
Mm, I just can't resist...
♪ And my heart is not gonna rage... ♪
Mm!
Let's go in the pool, the three of us.
What's he doing?
- Yeah, let's go in.
- Okay.
- Let's go in the water!
- Let's go!
We can do it inside, right?
- Let's go.
- Wow!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Stop! Stop!
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, there's a full moon!
What's all this?
- Huh?
- What on earth are you doing?
Hello, Moms!
You're back already?
What's wrong?
- How are you? I think we know each other.
- Too well.
I've seen far too much of you.
This is not what it looks like.
We were studying outside,
and we just felt like...
- Shut up.
- Well, I'm leaving.
It's not that big of a deal.
- What, having an orgy at home?
- There are only three of us.
- Technically, it's not an orgy.
- Mom...
- it's not just about sex.
- What?
We're dating.
The three of us.
How can you be with two people
at the same time? That makes no sense!
- Why not?
- What do you mean, why not?
Have you ever seen a thing like that?
Do you think this is normal?
Isn't that what your parents said
when you said you liked girls?
That's enough, Polo!
It's always a struggle with you.
Don't we have enough problems already?
And now this?
- Hey.
- Hi.
It suits you.
Listen, if you need anything,
anything at all...
I mean, I'm not going to shave my hair off
for moral support,
- but if you need anything else...
- Thanks.
I'm fed up with all the sad looks.
I don't know what's worse, chemo or pity.
Pity, for sure.
But it's not all shitty.
Cancer also has an upside.
Really? Like what?
Well... I don't know. I used to stress
about what to do with my life.
My future, my parents
constantly breathing down my neck...
We spend so much time thinking
about the future
that we forget the present.
I only do what I want now, and I like it.
Oh, sorry.
Another side effect
is that I talk like a Buddhist master.
It's like I have a master's in philosophy
instead of a tumor.
I don't know about the master's,
but you're right.
SORRY ABOUT THE OTHER NIGHT.
CAN WE MEET?
Good morning.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah. Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Just a bit nervous about the exams.
Hey, do you want to study with me tonight?
I made plans to go to the club.
- Who with?
- Some friends.
From class.
And... and how are you today?
- Fine.
- Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
See you.
See? I told you, kid.
Everyone has a price.
Some of us are cheaper than others.
It's all set.
I'll get the hard drive tonight.
But you don't even know that guy.
Of course, genius.
That's why I'm meeting him at the club.
It's the blackout party,
and you can do anything in the dark.
Anything?
- Except crochet.
- I'm going with you, just in case.
Okay, Dad.
Rebe, what would you do
if you knew Samu was cheating on you?
- What?
- Why are you asking?
I don't know. Intuition.
The only way to be sure
is by catching him red-handed.
Are you nuts?
What's wrong?
- Are you upset about last night?
- No.
Well... maybe they're right, you know?
I've been a problem my whole life.
That's my superpower.
Let's see. Let's see.
Polo's mothers might be lesbians,
but they're older.
Okay? They don't get it.
I don't get it either, to be honest.
I'm not going to pretend
I'm super progressive, but...
it's because girls don't dream of having
a white wedding with two grooms, you know?
It's not what we were taught.
I used to think...
that people were like halves
trying to make a whole.
Or like nuts and bolts.
All you had to do was find
the one who fit you perfectly.
But Polo and I didn't fit together before.
But you showed up...
and now we do fit together.
Hey, you're our missing piece.
And, fuck...
when you find love,
having to let it slip away sucks.
Guzmán, are you going to the party?
Omar wants me to go
so that I'm not alone all day.
Why don't you go with Polo?
I saw you two last night at your house.
You were having a blast.
So that's it, huh?
We forget and just carry on
like nothing ever happened?
Maybe that's the problem.
I forgave you too soon.
The champagne bottle broke.
The neck fell by the restroom,
and I went to pick it up.
And then?
Someone beat me to it.
Who?
Guzmán. He bent down,
picked it up, and entered the restroom.
You saw him with your own eyes?
You saw Guzmán?
Is that Yeray?
- Yes.
- Aren't you going to pick up?
No. I'm going to break up with him
as soon as I finish my dinner.
- What happened?
- Carla.
What happened?
Do you want to know what happened?
What we've been hiding from you
for weeks?
Dad has practically been pimping me
so that Yeray will save the winery.
It's the only reason I'm with him!
I don't love him,
and I never fucking will!
You knew?
And agreed to it?
Don't make
the same mistake that I made, Carla.
I also had a Yeray,
but I chose someone I loved over him.
Hm. And look at us now.
People who are not of our standing,
they think we didn't make
any sacrifices to get here.
But they don't know
we're capable of doing anything
to avoid losing our status.
Anything.
Learning to love that boy is easier
than learning to live with nothing.
Think about your future, honey.
About our future.
You're crazy, Valerio.
We can't deal at the club!
Remember when my mom
expanded outside of her territory?
Know what the problem is?
What we make at school isn't enough.
Not enough for what?
Life doesn't end when we graduate.
That's when it starts.
What the hell do you need that money for?
I need thousands of euros within a month,
before the enrollment deadline
for the good universities is up.
And so do you, right?
Or will you be going back
to public education?
- Are you guys ready?
- Of course.
Do you see him?
No.
But there's still time
before the blackout.
Why don't I talk to him?
I don't trust him.
Relax, Mike Tyson.
I'm the one who taught you how to box.
I'll be right back.
Your water, sir.
Eh, easy. It's a bit strong.
- What the hell am I doing here?
- Having a good time, like everyone else.
Come on, loosen up.
Guzmán.
Are you not coming
to the hospital on Monday either?
I'm sure you have
another friend to go with you.
Resentment is a luxury I can't afford.
Because I don't know
how much longer I'll be here.
If I have only months left,
would you rather not see me again?
If you'd known how long Marina had left,
wouldn't you have liked
to have forgotten all the problems
and been by her side?
They say the key to success
is to turn your hobby into your job,
- so congratulations.
- It's a job, and it's also a secret.
Can you not say anything about it?
I can make it up to you.
You've got the wrong person.
That's not my thing.
Yeah? And what is your thing?
What do you need?
I just need to fall in love.
Boom! I have just the thing for that.
This is... happiness...
and love.
Good.
Mm.
How are you?
It's fine. Go home. Don't stay for me.
Will you be up when I get home?
I can't dance, let alone fuck.
That's not what I meant, but it's okay.
It's not okay. We should admit that.
And, listen.
- I don't care if you see other people.
- Why are you saying that?
I know it's not conventional,
but I want you to be happy.
Right now you're bitter because of me.
Do you think I like that?
No... I don't understand, Ander.
I don't get it.
Fine, forget it.
Watch this for me.
I'm going to the restroom.
Omar, throw this in the trash
without being seen.
- What?
- Trust me.
- Just do it!
- Okay.
What is this about?
I just...
I just remembered
that I lost your toothbrush.
- Can you buy me a new one?
- Sure.
No. Buy me thousands.
Millions of toothbrushes.
Sorry, babe. The ladies' restroom
was as crowded as the Tokyo subway.
- Mm. Want another drink?
- Sure.
Shit.
- What's wrong?
- Where's my bag?
- Shit...
- Fuck me!
- Shit, I'm sorry, Rebe.
- You had just one fucking job to do.
♪ Pictures like ♪
♪ She gon' post old pictures like ♪
♪ She gon' post old pictures like... ♪
Take over for me.
- Do you want me?
- What?
Want to fuck?
What about Ander?
Ander isn't here.
♪ Like ♪
♪ Pictures like ♪
♪ Post old pictures like ♪
♪ Pictures like, pictures like
Pictures like, pictures like... ♪
Fuck.
Perfect timing, as always.
Nadia!
Hey! Over here!
♪ Pictures like, pictures like
Pictures like, pictures like... ♪
What are you doing here? Great hair!
Uh, shouldn't you be preparing
for your presentation?
I should, but I couldn't concentrate.
What about you?
- Want a sip?
- Uh, no.
Me? Same as always.
I just needed to relax.
- You do seem a little tense.
- No!
Have you seen Malick?
Yeah, he's downstairs.
With the crowd. On the dance floor.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
I don't know.
I guess if he has to go, but...
Hey, so nice to see you!
I thought you'd miss the blackout!
- How come you look so happy?
- Well...
I'm about to have enough cash
to apply to a university in London!
What?
It's amazing what my family can do
to send me as far away as possible.
- You're coming with us? Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Really? Awesome!
- That's great!
I couldn't let you get away.
Where were you?
I was looking for you!
Here.
Weren't you staying in?
Malick, is there anything I should know?
- Is there another girl?
- What? No! What's this about?
- Are we okay?
- Of course.
I was gonna tell you tomorrow,
but my parents are here next week.
They want to meet you.
- Why don't we go home?
- No, wait.
- It's time for the blackout.
- So what?
...nine,
- eight, seven...
- ...nine, eight, seven...
Samu, do you love me?
What?
- ...four, three, two...
- Do you love me?
- Of course I do.
♪ Bounce ♪
I love you!
I love you too!
I had to make sure.
♪ Bounce ♪
What's this?
- It's called fluorescent paint.
- ♪ Right... ♪
My bag was soaked in it.
♪ Here we go ♪
What is that?
♪ Ladies and gentlemen ♪
♪ You ready? ♪
Nadia. Nadia!
The security cameras didn't work.
That kid wasn't a security guard,
and the hard drive was empty.
- Rebeca, listen to me, please.
- No, you listen to me, Samuel!
Just tell me one thing.
Was that the only reason
you got close to me?
No.
- Was it all a lie?
- ♪ You ready? ♪
♪ Bounce ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ You ready? ♪
♪ One, two, one ♪
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You knew. Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to give you a dumb excuse
to drop out of the competition,
especially when I'm about to beat you.
Do you seriously think I'd go to New York
with him?
Listen... with a bit of luck,
many men will come and go in your life,
but an opportunity like this
only comes around once.
Anyway, he used you.
He deserves to be used by you as well.
But what he did hurt me a lot.
Yes, I know.
You thought
you were starting something great
with this person,
and that you'd live happily ever after,
but it didn't work out.
And we both know that he's not the guy
you're really in love with, right?
♪ Don't want to be too morbid ♪
♪ Don't wanna bring you down ♪
♪ Like a child, I say things ♪
- ♪ Out of place... ♪
- Nadia.
Speak of the devil.
♪ Don't notice ♪
♪ Please don't notice... ♪
I will meet your parents,
but I don't know
if I'll be as good as you are at lying,
cheating, and pretending
that I have feelings for someone.
That's my bitch.
♪ Is it selfish to wonder? ♪
♪ Move on quickly ♪
♪ Don't answer ♪
♪ Please don't answer ♪
Let's see if we can go in.
What did you say?
♪ Just limits to feel... ♪
You did the right thing.
- Hey. You did what you had to do.
- ♪ My lungs, they tell me ♪
♪ To breathe ♪
♪ The light of my love ♪
♪ Eclipses my ♪
♪ Practice of ♪
♪ Strength ♪
♪ Heaven's nudged ♪
♪ Me toward ♪
♪ What I shun ♪
♪ I slip ♪
♪ Into the sun ♪
♪ Feeling for ♪
♪ The fear I flee from ♪
♪ Too late ♪
♪ To shut my ears ♪
♪ I'm in a world ♪
♪ That's called me near ♪
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro