♪ I'd never ask you to forgive me ♪
♪ And you will never see my side ♪
♪ And I will always think I'm right ♪
♪ But I always regret the night ♪
♪ I told you
I would hate you till forever ♪
♪ Forever, forever, forever ♪
♪ Forever, forever, forever, forever ♪
♪ I told you
I would hate you till forever ♪
- ♪ Forever, forever, forever, forever ♪
- ♪ Oh... ♪
I need the trophy.
What?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
- ♪ I told you I would hate you ♪
- Polo, come on...
♪ Till forever... ♪
Where is it?
In a safe place
where nobody can find it, okay?
Well, I want them to know I did it
so all this will be over.
- No.
- No one will find out you had it.
- I don't want you to suffer.
You don't want me to suffer?
I've been suffering by your side
for months,
supporting you.
You want to throw it all away,
and you're asking me to help you?
Cayetana, it's my decision. It's my life.
- I'm tired of everyone deciding for me.
- When have I ever done that? Huh?
Did you contact the British school
so they wouldn't accept me?
What?
What is he talking about, Cayetana?
- No...
- Of course.
It had to have been you.
I did it
because I didn't want to lose you.
Because I love you. All right?
You want me by your side,
knowing my life here is hell.
- That isn't love.
- Hi!
Why are you here? What's going on?
Everything okay?
- Lu, stay out of this.
- What a threesome you've got yourself.
Yesterday, I still thought this
was like a horror movie.
Two monsters fighting
over a damsel in distress.
Now she's in tears
over two monsters who aren't worth it.
And a son of a bitch who came
to fuck up our lives. Right, Polo?
Maybe the monster
isn't who you think, right?
- Valerio...
- Oh, please!
Lu, Lu, Lu! Can we talk for a moment?
Sure,
but you'll need to get cleaned up first.
What... what the hell, Lu?
Fuck.
- You fucking ruined my life, asshole.
- Lu...
Lu, I-I just want to...
- ...talk about your scholarship.
- ♪ Forever, forever ♪
- Just ignore him, please.
- I'll be right back.
- ♪ Forever, forever, forever, forever ♪
♪ Forever, forever, forever... ♪
- Would you like a sip, Marchioness?
- No, thanks.
♪ Forever, forever, forever... ♪
No wonder you don't want anything from me
after the other day.
Well, it wasn't just your fault.
Carla, I wanted to apologize.
I sold you the Molly
because I was jealous.
I did it knowing that you weren't okay
and could've been hurt.
And what was it all for? For a guy.
It's not your fault he's crazy about you.
And then I say I'm a feminist.
- Fucking patriarchy.
- Well...
don't beat yourself up over it.
I was jealous too.
You? Why?
He was with me,
but all he did was think of you.
Yeah. And I was with someone else,
but all I did was think about him.
We really hurt each other. I'm sorry.
Don't get too carried away, blondie.
It takes a bigger blow than that
to bring me down.
I'm worried about Samu.
Why?
Haven't you realized it yet?
That kid worships the ground you walk on.
He'd go to hell just to warm up
a damn pizza if you asked him to.
You have him in the palm of your hand.
But if you clench your fist...
Can I have a napkin?
I can't believe
you had the balls to show up here.
I just want to dry off, Omar.
And I just want you to leave.
I'm saying this for your own good.
Omar, give me a napkin, please.
Omar, go get more bottles.
- Where are you going?
- Let go!
- What are you going to do?
- Are you protecting him?
No, you idiot. I'm protecting you.
Say you stab him in the chest, then what?
You'll end up in jail,
your mom will be devastated,
and Polo's moms will want revenge.
When will this whole nightmare end?
♪ Mesmerizing ♪
♪ Mesmerizing... ♪
Valerio, please.
Let's... let's forget about Polo.
- It's over now.
- A bottle of champagne, please.
- Are you going to let him come between us?
- Get away from me, okay?
Here you are, guys.
Polo was right, all this was insane.
You convinced us it was possible.
Yeah, because it was possible.
It didn't end
because there are three of us.
It ended because of who we are.
We need glasses!
Thanks! Cheers.
♪ Hey... ♪
Son of a bitch.
Lu, forget about him.
Nadia, don't play innocent.
You want to smash this bottle
over his head as much as I do.
Admit it.
♪ But, hey ♪
♪ I really know you wanted me to stay ♪
♪ But now I need to go and be away ♪
- ♪ From everything in my head... ♪
- Is it true that your mother is out?
It's true.
And she's eager to get back to business.
I need her to send someone to scare Polo.
- Excuse me?
- To scare the shit out of him.
To scare him to death, literally.
What are you talking about?
How much have you had to drink?
♪ I just can't take it no more ♪
♪ I just can't take it no more
I just can't take it no more ♪
♪ No more ♪
♪ I’m done ♪
♪ I really wanted you
To smile again today ♪
♪ But you don't know
Am I ever gonna stay? ♪
♪ It's really hard to stay... ♪
I just stopped someone
who was coming straight for you,
but I won't be able to stop everyone
who wants to slit your throat
in this club.
Thank you.
- I didn't do it for you.
- ♪ This time, I'm going my way... ♪
- Why the hell did you come here?
- I'm going to turn myself in, Guzmán.
What?
Tomorrow.
♪ I just can't take it no more
I just can't take it no more ♪
- Tonight.
- ♪ No more... ♪
I know I'll never be able
to make up for all I've done.
To you...
to Samuel...
But at least my moms will pay
for Nadia and Lu's program.
♪ But, hey... ♪
That's why I came. To tell them in person.
To tell you I'm sorry...
...and to tell you it's over.
♪ I just can't take it no more
I just can't take it no more ♪
♪ I just can't take it no more ♪
- Fine.
- ♪ I just can't take it no more, no more ♪
Get out of here.
♪ I'm done ♪
♪ I really wanted you
To smile again today ♪
♪ But you don't know ♪
♪ Am I ever gonna stay... ♪
When I get out of prison...
one day...
will you be able to forgive me?
Never.
- Uh, I'm gonna get another one.
- No, no.
- You said this was the first and last one.
- Just one more!
Shit! Careful, guys! Guzmán!
Help me pick this up
before someone else gets hurt.
- Where's the neck of the bottle?
- I don't know. Haven't seen it.
Rebeca!
I said no.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
I'd never in my fucking life
order anyone to scare Polo.
But your mom took care of that kid.
I'm not like my mother.
Get that
through your thick fucking skull, idiot!
Really?
Isn't anyone going to make him leave?
I'd do it myself if I could.
Watch out for the broken glass!
Let me do it. It's my job.
What else now?
You have to be kidding me.
Shit, Polo...
Can't you wait one night for him
to be gone?
Are you still defending him?
Clean this up, talk later. Come on!
Look for the neck of the bottle.
Get out of here, Polo.
You think I don't realize I'm not welcome?
Do you think I need you
to tell me that every day?
Anyway,
what the fuck did I ever do to you, Lu?
Huh?
Nothing.
What about to Carla?
And Ander?
Guzmán...
You don't know
how much you're hurting him.
You have no fucking clue
how much it tortures him
that you're still alive.
That you're breathing the same air as us.
Mark my words, Polo,
I'll always protect the people I love.
Guzmán...
doesn't love you...
Lu.
Stop groveling for once
in your fucking life.
But you're an expert at groveling,
aren't you?
You are.
Until they leave you
for someone better, right?
At least Carla loved me at one point.
But has anyone ever loved you, Lu?
Did you think that by being
the most stylish,
the richest, and at the top of the class,
everyone would love you?
- Shut up.
- But nobody loves you.
- They envy you...
- Shut up.
...fear you, despise you...
That's why they don't love you.
And that's why you're alone.
Shut up.
Polo?
No, I didn't...
Polo, I didn't mean to...
I know.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- I know.
Forgive me.
Polo...
♪ Lips ♪
♪ And the shadow electrocution ♪
- Lu?
- ♪ And now I'm ready to be strong ♪
- What happened?
- ♪ Then come ♪
♪ Play ♪
♪ Everyone just goes to dust... ♪
Polo!
Polo.
Call an ambulance, please!
Call an ambulance!
Polo.
I forgive you.
Don't worry.
Careful!
- Move aside.
- Stay away.
- Come on.
- Polo! Polo!
- Please!
- The police are on their way!
Calm down.
I-I didn't mean to. I didn't.
It was an accident, Lu.
- It was my fault.
- No.
- We'll tell them it was an accident.
- Nobody will believe that.
Everyone saw her throw a drink
in his face.
- But it's true.
- The cops don't want the truth.
They want to close the case
as soon as possible,
find someone to blame,
and lock them up for 20 or 30 years.
We have no choice.
Yes, we do.
We can put an end to this nightmare
once and for all.
We've all suffered enough.
Too many lives have been destroyed.
We will walk out of here,
together and free.
And we'll leave this shit behind forever.
Her fingerprints are on the bottle.
We could break it.
Not here. The noise would give us away.
Are you serious?
What if there are other fingerprints
on it?
What if they found
all of our fingerprints on it?
It would be the same as not finding any.
Polo did something horrible,
but he wasn't a murderer.
And neither are you, Lu.
He wouldn't want you to waste your life
paying for one mistake.
Nadia.
You're risking the scholarship
in New York.
What?
Before coming,
Polo convinced his moms not to cancel it.
Fuck.
If we're going to New York...
we're going together.
Have we all touched it?
All but one of us. The most important one.
We can try to make it look like a suicide.
How will we do that?
Where are you going?
Stay away from him, come on.
Hey, she's his widow, damn it.
Won't you let his girlfriend say goodbye
before they wrap him up like a sausage?
Shit, have a little decency.
Go on, then.
Come on.
Hey, thanks a lot. Okay?
I really loved you.
So much.
If only I could have loved you better.
I'm sorry.
Cayetana.
Cayetana!
For fuck's sake, Cayetana.
Come on, Cayetana.
Cayetana, that's enough. That's enough.
Let go of the bottle. Let's go. Let's go.
Don't let anyone touch the body!
My God.
It's done.
- What will they do now?
- Question all of us, one by one...
which isn't a problem,
because no one saw anything.
Agreed?
Someone saw me.
What?
Yeah, when I went to pick up
the neck of the bottle...
I bumped into a group of...
girls, I think.
Shit, no fucking...
Did anyone see you go into the restroom
with the neck of the bottle?
Yes.
Shh. It's okay. It's okay. Hey.
I need you to remember
who they were, okay?
It's important we talk to them.
Who are they?
- I can't remember, Valerio.
- Shit.
- What if those girls talk?
- Do you have a better idea?
I hated him.
I blamed him for my illness.
I lost control. I stabbed him in the heart
with the broken glass.
- You're nuts. Why would you confess?
- What does it matter?
I'm as good as dead.
What difference is it to me if I die
in the hospital or in jail?
No fucking way.
I won't let you sacrifice yourself
to protect someone, okay?
Who's sacrificing himself?
We need a decoy
to throw the cops off track.
Not just one.
We need a lot of decoys.
It's important that you tell us
everything you've seen,
anything you think might be useful.
Everything. Any detail could be key.
Guzmán.
Wait, so are you saying
we should all accuse each other?
That's right.
If witnesses saw Lu go into the restroom
with the bottle, it's over.
But if they also have witnesses
who saw me, Samuel, or Valerio go in...
- Those statements will be worthless.
- Exactly.
Now, the question is...
who will accuse who?
It was Samu.
I saw him go into the restroom
with a broken bottle.
I didn't do it.
But if I knew who did,
I wouldn't tell you.
- That means you know who did it.
- That means I'd never tell you.
Although, maybe...
I saw Valerio going in just after Polo.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Cayetana was jealous of my relationship
with Polo.
As soon as I saw her follow him,
I knew what would happen.
What time was that?
At 12:30.
A quarter to one, yeah.
I know because that's the time
I take my allergy tablet.
I was going to the restroom,
but I saw Polo.
I thought I'd better not go in...
because I didn't want to bump into him.
And that's when I saw someone
go into the restroom right after him,
carrying a glass object.
Who did you see?
I just feel so bad because...
- And with all that's going on with him...
- Cayetana, who did you see?
Ander.
Guzmán.
He bent down,
picked up the neck of the bottle,
and entered the restroom.
You saw him?
With your own eyes? You saw Guzmán?
Omar.
Nadia. That's all I know. Can I go?
- Carla.
- Rebeca.
I didn't see anything at all.
Hey. You did the right thing.
Hey.
You did what you had to do.
Nothing will happen to Guzmán.
Or to any of us.
Omar, Polo's dead.
I've been talking about death for months.
The more I talked about it,
the less I feared it.
But now that I've seen it...
I'm scared shitless.
What can I do for you?
What do you want? What do you need?
I need you.
What about the guy you were with?
That was nothing.
What do you mean?
I made it all up.
I did it to push you away. I'm sorry.
If you wanted to get rid of me,
congratulations.
You did it.
Omar...
Lucrecia, your turn.
Your turn.
I can't do it, Nadia.
You have to lie.
Tell them you saw someone else go in.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Do you remember when Dad asked you
who had messed up the car,
who stained the carpet,
or who dyed the dog pink?
I need you to make up one more story.
Lu, I need you to lie.
But this time, it's not for me.
It's for you.
Please.
Several witnesses have told us
they saw you arguing with Polo.
Did you throw a drink in his face?
Yes.
And at least two people saw you
go into the restroom
with the neck of the bottle in your hand.
Was it you?
Did you kill him?
No.
We know each other better
than either of us would like to, Lucrecia.
And I think you're lying to me.
Tell me the truth.
Why are you so shaken up? What's wrong?
I'm shaken up because I saw who did it.
Who?
I don't know. I-I don't...
What happened tonight?
I've never seen you like this before.
And I don't believe
you're this upset over Polo's death.
You weren't even really friends.
What do you know?
Polo was my friend.
Despite everything...
...we are all friends.
More like a family.
We might not say
we love each other every day...
but you have no fucking clue
what I've been through with these people.
Year after year...
...and we have a lot of years
in front of us!
I'm shaken up...
because it hurts my soul...
...that the best people
I've ever known...
have to go through this shit again...
like with Marina.
They don't deserve it.
So...
If I'm crying,
if my voice breaks...
and I don't know what to do,
it's because...
...I have feelings, bitch.
But I didn't do it.
- ♪ It's the last goodbye, I swear ♪
- Thanks, Valerio.
♪ I can't rely on a dime-a-day love ♪
♪ That don't go anywhere ♪
♪ I learn to cry for someone else ♪
♪ I can't get by
On an odds-and-ends love ♪
♪ That don't ever match up ♪
♪ I heard all you said ♪
♪ And I took it to heart ♪
Carla.
♪ I won't forget ♪
- ♪ I swear ♪
- What did you want to tell me?
♪ I have no regrets... ♪
I'm leaving...
to study abroad.
Alone?
That's the idea.
Can people come visit?
That depends.
Will you bring macaroni?
♪ Can't quite see the end ♪
♪ How can I rely on my heart ♪
♪ If I break it ♪
♪ With my own two hands? ♪
♪ I heard all you said ♪
- ♪ And I love you to death ♪
- Come here, you.
♪ I heard all you said ♪
♪ Don't say anything ♪
♪ It's the last goodbye ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ I can't survive... ♪
It's a pleasure
doing business with you again.
You know I've been away for a while,
but I'm back now.
Good morning.
How are you, baby?
I'm tired.
What is it? Too much partying, huh?
Go on, go to bed and get some rest.
No, Mom. No.
I'm tired of dead bodies...
police, and threats...
I can't do this anymore.
All I'm asking for is a boring life.
Come on, babe.
And all I'm asking you
is to quit this shit.
Please.
Tell them to leave.
Because if you don't,
I'll be the one who ends up leaving.
Inspector.
An anonymous call
warned us of the presence
of a suspicious box in a park,
about 100 meters away from the station.
I called you down here because if we find
Polo's prints on the trophy,
we'll have to reopen the investigation.
I know this must be a difficult time
for you.
He did it.
He confessed to us
just before he...
...that night.
Your brother is free.
He can come back anytime.
He's not coming back.
He doesn't trust you.
And neither do I.
I don't believe
you've been honest with me either.
What happened that night at the club,
Samuel?
What wouldn't have happened
if you'd done your job.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Samuel.
Would you like a beer?
Yes.
Did the police really buy
the suicide story?
At least the guilty party
can't contest it.
Carla.
Can we talk for a moment?
- Sure, I'll leave you to it.
- No. With you, Cayetana.
Sure.
You can go to Oxford, Columbia, Harvard...
whichever university you want.
We'll pay for it.
- And for your housing too.
- No, but... seriously...
It's what Polo would have wanted.
You were the only one
who always stood by him.
We didn't know how to do that.
You deserve it.
No. I don't deserve it.
Anyway, public universities are great.
Seriously. And I think...
...it's time I accept
that my resources are limited,
that I come from
the kind of family I come from,
and that my last name is what it is.
Still, I can achieve
whatever I put my mind to, right?
Of course you can.
Carla, I suppose you know
that you can't leave to study abroad.
You're responsible for the wineries.
I'll have a trusted contact here
who will report to me.
You'll be working closely together.
Who?
Valerio.
I don't know if you know Valerio.
This is my dad.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, your reputation precedes you.
I assure you, the reality's much worse
than whatever you've heard.
I heard you didn't even graduate.
And yet, I ran my own
highly successful business.
Yes, an illegal business.
Since when are you scared
of breaking the law, Teodoro?
Relax, I'll mostly be taking care of PR.
I'm the best at getting people to party.
Do you think
this is what the wineries need?
Valerio is a good person.
And we really need that.
- Carla, I hope this is all a joke...
- Let me tell you about my plan.
I think social media
will be crucial for marketing.
If we want to sell,
this is going to be key...
Nadia, hurry up!
Do you have the passports
and tickets?
- Yes.
- Aren't you going to check that bag?
- No, I'll take it on the plane with me.
- Are you bringing winter clothes?
Yes.
- It's cold there.
- I know, Dad.
Don't worry. I'll call when we get there.
Good.
Omar...
...I'm sorry about that boy.
What boy, Dad?
Your friend. Your boyfriend.
I'm really sorry.
Guzmán won't make it on time.
Why not?
He's with Ander.
He's getting the results
of the latest round of chemo.
We'll hear how it went
when we get off the plane.
Your parents aren't coming?
No. They're on a business trip, as always.
No, that's not true.
My parents say they no longer have
a daughter.
You'll always have a family here.
Of course you will.
Thank you.
Look after our little girl, please.
Like she looked after me.
Hi, Nadia.
First, an apology.
This is going to be
the corniest message ever.
But I wanted to say that...
if you ever decide to come back...
I'll be here...
waiting for you.
We have to go.
Yes.
You look familiar.
Andrés, right?
Román.
I don't care
how much you push me away.
I'm a fucking boomerang.
And whatever the diagnosis is,
I will be by your side, you hear?
- Omar...
- Even if the chemo takes 100 years.
I'll be at your side in this hospital
for 100 years,
- repeating the same grade.
- Listen.
So what if I graduate when people retire?
I don't give a shit.
But I won't leave you,
because I love you, dickhead.
I haven't stopped loving you
even for one day.
You won't have to.
It's in remission. They just told me.
But that was a beautiful speech.
Hi, Guzmán.
You know I'm a bit competitive,
so here's a warning.
This is going to be
the corniest message ever.
I promise I'll come back for you.
I MISS YOU ALREADY
♪ Do you wanna play... ♪
TWO MONTHS LATER
♪ In my twisted games ♪
♪ My twisted games? ♪
Hi.
- Hi.
- ♪ I like to scream in my nightmares ♪
♪ It pumps adrenaline in my veins ♪
- ♪ Bloodstreams in the cold air... ♪
- Hey, man!
- I never thought I'd be glad to see you.
- Same here.
I don't know anyone, man.
What do you mean?
Is anyone going to tell me
how good I look?
You look divine, darling.
One rich kid, two, three...
Everyone is rich around here.
Las Encinas is fucking awesome.
♪ Do you wanna come play ♪
♪ In my twisted games
My twisted games? ♪
- Come on, let's go in.
- Yeah.
Let's see what surprises await us
in class.
♪ My twisted games? ♪
♪ I lost my mind
But I'm doing just fine ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm doing just fine
I don't need my mind ♪
♪ Lost my mind
But I'm doing just fine, yeah I'm ♪
♪ Doing just fine, I don't ♪
♪ Need my mind ♪
♪ Twisted, twisted ♪
- ♪ Doing just fine, I don't ♪
- ♪ Need my mind ♪
♪ Twisted ♪
- ♪ Doing just fine, I don't ♪
- ♪ Need my mind ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I like to burn all my flowers ♪
♪ And dance around
As they go up in flames ♪
♪ As all the voices get louder ♪
♪ I start to think they're my friends ♪
♪ But I forget their names ♪
♪ Do you wanna play
Do you wanna come play ♪
♪ In my twisted games
My twisted games? ♪
♪ Do you wanna play
Do you wanna come play ♪
- ♪ In my twisted games ♪
- ♪ My twisted games? ♪
♪ Twisted, twisted ♪
- ♪ Doing just fine, I don't ♪
- ♪ Need my mind ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Do you wanna play
Do you wanna come play? ♪
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro