- Still in bed? Are you okay?
- Yes.
My head hurts a little,
but I'm starting to feel better.
- Your room looks like a pigsty.
- I'll clean it.
No, no, come and have breakfast.
I'll have Mirella do it.
- Everything okay?
- Of course.
If you're not even gonna try to hide it,
at least tell me the truth.
I'm just wonderful, Samuel.
Is that better?
Is there anyone sitting here? No?
Well, there is now. Me.
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
I hope you've given it your all
for these finals.
It's important
you tell us everything you have seen.
Anything that you think could be useful.
Everything. Any detail could be key.
What the fuck?
I don't know any of this shit.
Wake up.
What do you want?
I don't like you out of your seats.
I have a question.
There's an issue with one of the problems.
Look. You can't do the ionic bonding
between sodium and chlorine
because sodium's atomic number
is incorrect.
Hey.
You owe me an A.
I don't expect a standing ovation,
but a thank-you would be nice.
"Thank you," bitch?
Thank you...
but you shouldn't have risked it.
You didn't need to.
You're not okay.
I have an MA in interpreting
passive-aggressive behavior.
Let's see.
You're crying out for help.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Guess who finally got themselves
a big house...
fit for a party
to celebrate the end of finals? Who?
Who cares?
It'll be your project, baby.
Why me?
The house is for the two of us
to enjoy this summer.
The sooner you make it feel like your own,
the better.
Lucky me.
- Are you being sarcastic?
- She's being herself, darling.
Meet the worst version of Carla.
You should accept her
and love her so much.
Good luck.
Call me.
I don't know.
Any girl would kill to have...
everything I'm offering you,
and you don't seem very excited.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
I didn't sleep well last night.
- I see.
- But everything's fine, okay?
You worry too much.
What is it?
Look, I'm not trying to avoid
taking the blame for this.
As if you could do that.
Look, Malick liking guys
and cheating on me...
is something I can't control.
But the fact that he cheated with you...
Did you ever stop to think about me?
Do you have so little respect for me?
I clearly wasn't thinking about you
when I did it.
Or about Ander or anybody else.
I needed to do it, and I did it, period.
Great.
- Fantastic.
- Yes, Nadia.
I make mistakes, I trip up,
I lie, and I disappoint people.
Like everyone else.
- Even you.
- What?
You haven't told Mom and Dad
that Malick likes guys, have you?
Ah.
So you haven't thought about them.
Only about yourself and New York.
There you go. We all have our faults.
Gay,
a cheater,
and involved with my brother.
What a catch!
God, I can't wait for this year to be over
so I can get away from Las Encinas.
You can achieve
anything you put your mind to.
You will get out of here, for sure.
And I will miss you so much.
- Don't go near her again.
- Why?
'Cause she's not okay! Can't you tell?
Easy. I'm taking care of her happiness.
And I'm giving her a good price.
- Let go.
- You got Rebeca into this.
- I won't let you do it to Carla too.
- Did they ask for your help?
As far as I know, those two girls
want you to stay away from them.
I want you out of my house this afternoon.
COLUMBIA PROGRAM GRANT RECIPIENT
SOON
YOU ARE INVITED TO OUR POOL PARTY!
Oh, please.
Hello.
Happy?
Out of everyone who didn't deserve
to win the scholarship, it's only you...
who I'm not ashamed to lose to.
Well played. Congratulations.
Nadia!
It'll be fine. You'll see.
- Shouldn't I be giving you moral support?
- You had nightmares all night.
Don't say it'll be fine.
It's bad luck.
I'll shut up.
My therapist used to say
it's best to always imagine the worst.
That way, you can see
that the worst isn't that bad.
That was back when the worst
wasn't croaking.
Yeah...
when I used to get anxious over grades.
Oh, my God.
What's the worst
that could happen in there?
If the doctor looks at your file
and says, "Oh... almost."
"How wonderful, Ander.
You'll make all those families waiting
for an organ donor so happy."
Pfft. "You're cured, Ramón.
Oh, sorry, this isn't your file.
This one's yours."
Okay, that's enough.
Ander, the doctor will see you now.
It'll be okay.
Fuck you.
I don't have good news.
The results of your bone marrow biopsy
and the CT scan...
are not what we were expecting.
The ratio of lymphoblasts
is still much higher than 30%.
What does that mean?
For the time being,
we will have to continue with chemotherapy
and increase the intensity.
- For how long?
- As long as we need to.
Until we get results.
What if we don't get results?
Let's not imagine the worst, hm?
So, you decide to destroy school property
on the last day of finals?
- Well done.
- What can they do?
Expel you when graduation
is just three days away, loser.
I don't give a shit!
What?
Just what you need. A good party.
Among other things,
but we'll start with that.
- I'm not going.
- What do you mean?
- Aren't you going to tell me why?
- I don't need to.
I don't owe you shit.
You and I are not friends.
- What are we, then?
- We were accomplices.
Shitty ones at that.
We wanted to make his life hell,
and that asshole's as happy as can be.
I mean, he can't kick you out
just because he feels like it.
- You could sue him. It's illegal.
- I could if I had a contract.
- Why did he do it?
- I told you, roommate issues.
He saw us together.
- When?
- The blackout party.
He knows I care about you.
- That's why he wants to hurt you.
- I don't want to live with him either.
Yeah, okay. Where will you live, then?
I don't know. I'll think of something.
It's not my first rodeo.
Amazing.
We turn his living room into a drug depot,
and he doesn't say a thing.
But if you sell to the chick he likes,
he blows a fuse.
I'm going to stop.
Stop what?
- I don't want to do this anymore.
- No way.
You didn't see him.
Samuel could rat me out.
He'd ruin my school year,
just when I'm doing well
for the first time ever!
- He won't tell.
- I hate it. I want to go to London.
I have some really good things going on.
What is it that everyone sees
in Little Miss Marchioness?
She's a viper.
If she bit her own tongue, she'd die.
Fuck!
But somehow, she has everyone
eating out of her fucking hand.
But losers like me...
all we get is a slap in the face.
We're not doing this.
We're not closing the business.
We're going all out.
More than ever.
We'll make a killing
at Yeray's pool party.
I'll pass.
Don't you need money to go to London?
Leave me alone.
What happened isn't Valerio's fault.
He shouldn't have to pay for what I did.
Let him stay at your house,
at least until he finds someplace else.
And why would I do that?
Because I could tell Azucena
you almost punched a student.
You'll get expelled,
and you'll have to repeat the grade.
Is that what you want?
Then I'll tell her
why I almost smashed his face in.
Because he's a fucking drug pusher
who's dealing here at school.
He'll probably get expelled too,
but he'll repeat the grade
in fucking prison.
That's not true.
So, you didn't know
he was dealing to Carla either?
I guess you haven't noticed
she's been acting like a zombie for weeks.
I suppose she needs that shit
to get through the day.
- What the hell are you saying?
- But I don't.
I get by on my hatred for you.
I hate you for so many reasons.
One of them is you'll be leaving
without giving a fuck about all the pain
that you're leaving behind.
Get out of here.
I'm off.
I'm meeting up with Yeray.
Mwah!
- Is everything all right?
- Everything's perfect.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
And I'm very proud of you.
Of how your attitude's improved,
of how you're listening to us,
and of how you've grown up.
- Aw.
- You're a woman now.
No, a lady.
A marchioness.
Gorgeous.
Have fun.
Fuck, you're so annoying.
Drop it already, please!
Just say...
"Mom, I haven't left the business
because I like living the good life,
and I shouldn't have trusted Samuel."
Say it, and I'll shut up.
See how easy it is? That's more like it.
Anyway, so tell me,
what did you do with him?
What else could I do? I got rid of him.
What?
I mean, I broke up with him.
I'm not like you, Mom.
Okay, baby. With that attitude of yours
and your willingness
to take over the business...
you're actually becoming a bit like me.
Hm?
You were right after all.
I'm becoming her.
I need her to send someone to scare Polo.
- Excuse me?
- To scare the shit out of him.
To scare him to death.
- Rebeca!
- I said no.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
I'm never going to send anyone
- to go scare Polo.
- Sure, but your mom took care of that kid.
I'm not like my mother.
See if you can get that
through your thick skull, idiot.
Hey, honey, we're back!
Come in, you've already been here.
Let's see which room we put you in.
There are so many...
If you show me the way to your room,
I'll leave a trail of breadcrumbs
so I can find my way there and...
have some fun.
Hey, handsome.
Did you talk to your moms?
- Did they say no?
- I wanted to talk to Valerio first.
How did you get the money
to pay for college?
- I told you.
- I know what you told us,
but now I'd like to hear the truth.
It's no big deal.
Is that why you didn't tell us?
- What? Tell us what?
- He's a fucking drug dealer.
It's a temporary thing.
But, yes, that's how I'm making a living.
- Dealing drugs?
- Yes.
And you're selling to Carla?
Her money's as good as anyone else's.
Why's she any different?
She's not just anyone!
She's Carla, dammit!
She's never used drugs.
She's afraid of getting hooked.
She's like that.
She gets hooked to a perfume,
a purse, or a boy, and she can't let go.
People change, Polo.
It's been a long time
since you were with Carla.
- You have no idea what she's like.
- Guys, stop, please.
You don't know your buyers...
or if they can handle the shit you sell,
because you don't care.
You can save
your moral superiority speech.
You think you're better than me?
You're right.
I'm no better than you. I'm worse.
I'm probably worse.
The fraudster,
the murderer, and the dealer.
It sounds like a joke,
but it's not fucking funny!
- What’s wrong?
- What's wrong?
I just woke up, Cayetana,
and I don't like
what I see one fucking bit!
Get out.
Both of you. Out.
- Leave me alone.
- Shh, hush.
HOW DID IT GO?
I have to go to work.
♪ In Fantasia ♪
♪ The mirrors lie... ♪
There.
They said something about a rust effect
or something like that.
They charged me a premium
like they would Cristiano Ronaldo.
The house looks great, right?
Oh, God.
♪ Fading sunsets... ♪
Does this mean you like it?
It means that I want to get
in the pool with you, right now.
Get in.
Now?
Mm-hmm.
Take your clothes off,
or I'll pull you in fully clothed.
♪ Darkened bridges... ♪
The water's great.
Well, it's a saltwater pool,
but I don't think it's really all that.
- Don't you like that I'm enjoying it?
- Oh, yeah.
I love it.
♪ Of atrophy ♪
♪ When the winters ♪
♪ Help the golden autumns... ♪
We'll throw a party they'll never forget.
♪ Opens passages ♪
♪ For vampires ♪
♪ To suck and feed ♪
♪ Waking insights ♪
♪ Born of jealousy ♪
♪ And faithlessness ♪
It's like being in jail,
about to finish serving your sentence,
and when the day comes...
boom.
They tell you no.
That you'll be locked up,
maybe for another month, a year,
for ten years... or forever.
- But you aren't in prison.
- What?
You can leave whenever you want.
- What are you talking about?
- You can leave him, Omar.
That's exactly what I can't do.
- You can't or you wouldn't dare to?
- Are you lecturing me about bravery?
QUR'AN
- Thank you.
- In the name of Allah.
One of my daughters
going to college, in America...
Mm.
What's going on?
- Malick and I thought...
- You and Malick...?
Hear him out.
Malick and I think
it would be best if you went to America...
engaged to be married.
Did you know
what these two were planning?
You want that, right?
Just a second. Come.
- Was this your idea?
- No.
It was your father's suggestion,
and it'd be good for us.
Your family will leave you alone.
And I'll give my family what they expect,
at least on the surface.
If I get married now,
I'm guaranteed my freedom forever.
- It's a mere formality.
- No, it isn't.
You've seen what my parents are like.
For us, it's a serious,
lifelong commitment.
- Do you really not care about anything?
- No, it's not that.
I just put my happiness first.
And you should do the same.
Do you think your parents arranged
this marriage with your happiness in mind?
They're thinking about their happiness,
their honor, what people will say.
Wake up.
Either we keep up the charade...
or you can say goodbye to New York.
I don't need a pep talk to cheer me up
about the scholarship.
I didn't call you down here
to cheer you up. Nadia just quit.
She says she won't change her mind.
And since you came in second...
Nadia.
You're nuts if you think
I'll settle for your scraps.
I don't want to live a lie, Lu.
So you don't want to live a lie?
Well, grow some fucking ovaries
and tell your father you're going
to accept the scholarship and go alone.
Because you don't need a man
or anyone else, Nadia.
Be the woman who managed to beat me!
The one I admire, dammit!
The one I can't stand.
I meant to say, "the one I can't stand."
Because I can't stand you.
Okay?
People are staring.
Hey, guys, gals, and everyone!
Our suffering is over!
Finals are over!
No more uniforms!
Let's party!
♪ Don't call me no names ♪
♪ Talking this talk
And then it's all for the fame ♪
♪ What's the noise in your mouth?
Don't call me no names ♪
♪ Names, names, names ♪
♪ Names ♪
♪ What's the noise in your mouth?
Don't call me no names ♪
♪ Talking this talk
And then it's all for the fame ♪
♪ What's the noise in your mouth? ♪
♪ Don't call me no names ♪
♪ Names, names, names ♪
- ♪ Names... ♪
- Fuck.
People are going wild.
Really? That's great!
- Are you coming?
- In a minute.
♪ Names, names ♪
Hold on. Let me help you.
- There's no need.
- Grab that end.
You'll be more comfortable downstairs.
Omar and I will take turns sleeping
with you in case you need anything.
COMING TO THE PARTY? I WANT TO SEE YOU.
IT'LL BE NICE TO GET OUT OF PRISON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO BACK, OMAR.
YOU CAN LEAVE HIM.
- What do you want?
- To drag you to that party.
Fuck. I have nothing to celebrate.
Of course you do.
The end of the exams and the fact
that we're alive. Is that not enough?
Ander is sick. Really sick.
Chemo could kill him before cancer.
- You forgave Polo because of Ander?
- I didn't forgive him.
- You've moved on.
- I never will.
Have fun at the party with him.
I'm not going.
Listen, Samu.
I used to think about him day and night.
And you know what I realized?
If I can't put him behind bars,
I don't want him in my fucking head.
He doesn't deserve to be that important.
Think about it.
What's wrong, honey?
Malick and I aren't together.
What?
But we weren't together...
the last two years either,
and, as you know, I passed...
with the best grades.
I didn't need him...
or anyone else.
Just me and my own hard work.
I want to go to New York.
No, sorry...
I am going to New York.
- No.
- Dad!
Listen to me.
Just this once.
Please.
I'm no longer the girl
you want me to be.
I haven't been for a long time.
I wish I were...
because everything would be easier...
and I would still believe that...
everything you do is for my protection...
not because you're afraid to lose me...
like you lost Omar...
and May.
I swear to you...
if I go to New York,
I will always come back.
You will always have me.
But... if you stand in my way...
Thank God you're here.
- I ran out.
- Of what?
I didn't bring any with me.
Okay, fine.
You're here to make a killing.
Do you think I'm dumb?
- Drink champagne, it's better for you.
- No, thanks.
- Okay.
- Wait.
What do you want? More money?
How much?
I know those cravings well.
I'm sorry, but I won't sell to you.
In fact, I never should have sold to you.
Carla. Carla, darling.
Today is your lucky day.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Two grams for 90 bucks. Just for you.
Right in your pocket,
where you've got everyone.
- The offer ends in ten, nine, eight...
- I thought you didn't deal.
Don't think so much, honey.
There you go. Enjoy.
Carla, what are you doing?
What's that?
Mm...
Molly. Want some?
- Now you're taking Molly?
- Didn't you want to live large?
This is the full experience.
Full experience?
Don't treat me like an idiot.
I know how that makes you feel.
It's great until you get the comedown.
It makes you depressed.
It takes you ages to be yourself again.
Dude, you sound
like a Health Department PSA.
I get enough lectures from my father.
You should listen to me.
- Come on, you'll get totally loved up.
- What? Loved...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't ruin my party, please.
I was just trying to be
the coolest girlfriend.
Isn't that what you wanted?
So, Lu, how is your first day
as a loser going?
Fucking awesome. I'm actually doing great.
I don't need that scholarship.
I mean, I only applied for it out of...
Well, for the competition. You know me.
And my résumé.
I can go to any university I want.
And my father will pay for it.
Thanks, I'll order another one soon.
Why is that your fifth gin and tonic?
Are you trying to forget
how little you care about losing?
Cheers, then.
Sure, cheers.
Hi.
- Nadia!
- Hi.
You take the concept of the burkini
to a new level.
I'm in a hurry, Lu.
I need you to sign this so I can take it
to the school office before it closes.
What is it?
Azucena will let us share the scholarship.
But the budget remains the same.
So we will each have to get by
with half the money
for food, accommodation...
I'm used to scraping by, but you...
Do you think
I'm going to let you laugh in my face?
Come on, stop being so you and sign it.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Oh!
People are staring.
♪ Just to me, babe ♪
- ♪ That's why I leave you there... ♪
- Nadia.
♪ Ah, ah, ah! ♪
I dreamt so many times
about running away with you.
And now you're going
with some other guy... and with Lu.
I'm not going with Malick.
- Seriously?
- Mm-hmm.
You're not together anymore?
Where does that leave us?
You'll be here, and I'm leaving.
Can I give you a hug?
Sure.
♪ We don't want no fun ♪
♪ Sad girls, we don't want no fun... ♪
- You're late.
- Are you leaving already?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
You look like you could use a drink.
A drink and a buddy.
Yeah.
Come on.
♪ Got no longing ♪
♪ For the stars ♪
♪ We're not coming out to play ♪
♪ Flush our dollies ♪
♪ Down the drain... ♪
Tell me you're not angry.
Tell me you're as happy as I am.
Holy shit, Yeray. Seriously,
I wish you could feel
what I'm feeling right now.
It's as if electricity was flowing
through every pore in my body.
Let's take a selfie. You like that.
♪ Let it hit the spot ♪
- ♪ It's the sad girls club ♪
- Fuck.
- ♪ For the mentally fucked up... ♪
- What a long face. One more. Smile.
I don't need chemicals to be happy.
You're all I need.
Shame you can't say the same.
Come on, it doesn't matter.
Some of us need a bit of help
to let our hair down.
What's wrong with that?
Your life is perfect.
I don't get why you need to take anything.
Oh, darling...
you're kind of a pain in the ass,
you know?
Maybe I need to get high
just to put up with you.
With me?
Yes, you, your prescheduled life,
the fact I'm sentenced to five years
with you
because you're signing that contract
with my father.
But I accept that you're locking me up
in this palace with a pool, honey.
That contract is just business.
It has nothing to do with us.
Each plan you make with me
feels like another nail in my coffin.
♪ Help a sister out ♪
♪ Sad girls, we don't want no fun ♪
♪ Let the liquor drop ♪
♪ Let it hit the spot ♪
♪ Join the sad girls club
If the world has fucked you up ♪
♪ We just wanna cry ♪
♪ 'Cause the world's so mean ♪
♪ We just wanna die ♪
♪ 'Cause they killed our dream... ♪
Malick.
We need to talk.
Okay. Let me dry off a little.
No, it has to be now.
Do you love him?
How many times have you fucked?
Once.
Three... or four.
It depends on what counts as fucking.
Was it just sex?
No, it wasn’t just sex.
Are you in love with him?
I don't know.
- You are or you aren't.
- I don't know what being in love is.
I just know I'm crazy about him.
And how does he feel about you?
The same way, I guess.
Because being at your place, by your side,
it's hard on him.
Don't tell him about this, okay?
The only bathing suit I have
with no holes in it is here.
Sure.
You forgot how to sew?
Don't do this, Polo.
Don't do this.
This is the start of something good.
Something worthwhile.
Are we really going
to just throw all that away?
Just like that?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have taken it out on you.
- My problem is with Valerio.
- What he did was wrong, okay?
Whatever happened to
"everyone deserves a second chance"?
Where the hell were you?
You could at least answer
one fucking message, right?
We need to talk.
So?
I've been with Alexis.
I'm with Alexis. I have been for a while.
What?
I should have told you weeks ago.
But with the tests and all that...
Now it doesn't matter.
Omar, I don't have time to waste.
I want to end this.
Are you kidding me?
He gets me.
We speak the same language.
The language of cancer.
You don't.
No. It's not true. No way.
Why do you think I told you
to hook up with other guys?
I felt guilty about cheating on you.
So, do you fuck him?
Cheating isn't just about fucking.
It's about wanting to be with him,
talk to him...
I'm sorry.
What do I do now?
I don't know.
I'm not going to lie to you.
The sooner you go, the better.
Samuel will let you stay
at his place, right?
We can talk about it tomorrow. I'm tired.
And that's it?
You son of a bitch.
- Hey, have you seen Valerio?
- I haven't seen him for a while.
♪ Body ♪
Shit.
Help!
Help! Help! Grab her, please!
Grab her. Pull her out!
Carla! Carla!
Carla!
Hey, Carla!
Carla, hey! Call a fucking ambulance!
Hey! Call an ambulance!
Carla! Carla!
Hello... Hello.
W-We need an amb...
Rebeca, wake up!
Law? Really?
I want to be a lawyer.
Make sure no more assholes
get off the hook.
Become a judge,
and you'll make damn sure.
- What about you?
- Business.
But putting assholes in jail
sounds pretty good too.
- Maybe I'll do a dual degree.
- It'd be cool to have a friend in class.
I'm not going to a public university.
- A few bar nights, and I'll convince you.
- No fucking way.
Good morning, narco queen.
Here's what's left. I'm out, okay?
I'm out too.
Flush it down the toilet.
I want nothing to do with this shit.
- What's wrong?
- What did you give Carla, huh?
- Huh? What the fuck did you give her?
- Let go of him! He didn't do it!
- Okay? No!
- Samu!
Stop! Calm down!
Samu, stop!
- Samu!
- Samuel, stop!
Samu! Guzmán, grab him!
Fuck.
I know you hated Polo.
Yes, ma'am.
And I suppose you also know
I wasn't the only one who did.
But I can tell you that...
I saw who went in the restroom
after he did.
It was Samu.