[English subtitles are available]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 6]
Faster.
[Bootlegger: Bai Lang]
Quick!
These wooden houses are newly built.
Someone is still patrolling.
Those inside, be quick!
Be quick.
Quick!
Tie them as tightly as you can.
There must be something fishy here.
It looks normal.
Are you thinking too much?
It's fishy. It's fishy.
Why are you here?
You are here too. Why can't I?
Gao Bingzhu.
Who is this beautiful lady?
Bai Lang, right?
Yes, I am Bai…
How do you know?
What are they moving?
They are from Chuiliu Corporation.
Those in the crate should be
the replica of Lianshan copper.
So you said something's wrong with copper,
this is what you mean?
Yes.
Faster!
Hurry up!
Quick. Come out.
One. Two. More force!
It's all tied.
Carry the crates.
This batch of copper is all here?
A total of 20 crates.
It's all moved out.
[Member of Chunqiu Divine: Tiangou]
Isn't it too little?
Forget it.
Carry the copper up the carriage.
You must depart before midnight.
Yes sir.
Hurry up and move.
Hurry up and load the carriage.
Tie them all!
They're going to redirect the copper.
It's too late.
You go back to the inner guard's office quickly.
Get some back up.
I'll keep watch here.
You want me away.
There are so many of them.
We are outnumbered.
Bai Lang.
Go south along the official way for 500 meters.
There is a wine shop.
Look for Tihu.
Me?
Gao Bingzhu.
It's good.
No.
What do I call you?
Who am I passing on the message for?
Inner guard. Yuehua.
Seriously?
She…
Yes madam.
Please be careful.
We're close. No more wine.
Come tomorrow.
Tihu. I'm looking for Tihu.
What's the matter?
Inner guard Yuehua is facing danger in Longmen.
Immediate back up needed.
[Joint Corps: A message from Tihu]
Have you heard it all?
I'm not done.
Impressive.
A message from Tihu.
Tell the inner guard's office to send some back up.
Yes sir.
Hold on.
Inform the Ministry of War as well.
Yes sir.
One, two.
Go!
Hurry up.
Quick!
What to do with these workers?
Burn them. Quickly.
Yes.
Do it.
Go in.
What do you want to do?
They want to kill them all.
Go in.
Go in. Go in.
Go!
It'll be too late if we don't save them now.
Gao Bingzhu, we can't wait anymore.
Don't move.
Be quick.
Mount the horse.
Let's go.
Quick.
What do you want to do?
Let us out! Don't leave us!
Open it!
Let us out!
You don't want to stop them.
You just want to follow their lead
to get what you want.
Yes.
Open it!
Let us out!
Open the door.
Open!
How dare you!
You shouldn't be
here tonight.
You shouldn't block my way.
Even if we want to find out the truth,
we don't have to sacrifice them.
I only care about where the copper goes.
If you go out now,
you will ruin my plan.
Open the door.
Let us out!
Let me go.
Gao Bingzhu!
Are you going to
watch them getting burnt alive?
I've been waiting for five years.
This is a golden opportunity.
Let us out!
I can't care that much.
Let go.
Gao Bingzhu.
Yuehua!
Yuehua.
Five years.
This is the closest clue
I've ever gotten.
You saved them.
You are the one who saved them.
Nothing to do with me.
But you saved me.
[Minister of Ministry of War: Song Liang]
Yuehua!
Master Song.
This man...
He's wanted for murdering Minister Baili.
Gao Bingzhu.
Guards.
Capture him.
Master Song.
Master Song, be wise.
Something's fishy about
Master Baili's case.
Gao Bingzhu is not a murderer.
You don't have to explain for him.
This is the Empress' Behest
[Behest]
given by the empress.
On behalf of this,
I guarantee his innocence.
[Behest]
Yuehua!
Guards.
Escort Yuehua into the camp.
Yes sir.
Quick!
We've gone to two houses.
All had personal matters
hence be absent at the wedding.
Why are you still here?
I saw the house was messy.
So I tried to tidy things up.
How's your case?
Anything?
I don't understand some family matters.
I want to discuss it with you.
Shen Fei.
Why did you call him?
He will call in Uncle Wu
to discuss family matters with you.
You've been on the case for so long.
You must be hungry.
There's fresh bass today.
I'll have the chef
cook fish soup for you.
Bass is best for its fillet.
Making it soup is not good.
Then I'll have the kitchen make bass fillet.
Eating bass fillet at night will cause upset stomach.
If you have nothing else,
go back and rest first.
One.
[Jingji's Camp]
Two.
One.
Gao Bingzhu.
Where are you going?
You don't have to know.
Last night,
it was just to save you.
You don't have to explain.
A book written by Zhang Zhongjing
of the Eastern Han Dynasty,
in the chapter of "Essential Medical Treasures of the Golden Chamber",
such resuscitation method is recorded.
Last night,
in order to save me,
you almost died.
Next time,
don't take such risky move
anymore.
Don't follow me anymore.
Gao…
[Baili's mansion]
Open the door.
What are you doing?
Let us in.
Baili Erlang.
Your father is dead.
All the properties and treasures
should be distributed.
Yes. They should be distributed.
Let's distributed.
[Baili's mansion]
That's right.
Baili Hongyi.
Your father is dead.
The head of this family
should be re-elected.
-Re-election!
No need to re-elect.
If you want to be the head, so be it.
As to how you want to distribute the property,
you discuss among yourselves.
I have something to do.
Excuse me.
This…
Go!
Let's go in!
Done checking.
A total of twelve murderers caught.
We seized about ten stones of copper
and ten horses.
The head of the gang is still off the hook.
There are dense forests around this area,
and the roads are uneven.
We have locked down
this place.
I believe we will catch him soon.
This is the only water source here.
He will definitely come.
[A noble man has a greater commitment]
A country needs its king.
A family needs its pillar.
How can a family be without a leader?
That's true.
Right?
Let's elect
a family leader.
Who is the head of the Baili Family?
What's your order, master?
Baili Yan robbed the copper quarry.
There's solid proof.
The empress ordered Court of Judicial Review
is here to investigate.
Who is the head of family?
Come receive your command quick.
Why?
Such a big family,
yet nobody
dares to speak?
I will receive the command.
I am from the Liu Family.
I will receive on behalf of my husband, Baili Hongyi.
Your Majesty.
As it's related to Master Baili's murder,
The Court of Judicial Review has been investigating non-stop.
We found Lianshan quarry's
recipients' record.
Besides the ones about the waterway,
there's also reports on
[Chief Justice of the Court of Judicial Review: Gao Sheng]
Baili Yan's subordinates.
The lack of materials for the Heaven Project
has always been an issue.
Looks like Baili Yan's corruption...
may have been going on for a long time.
What a joke!
Baili Yan is the capital's
number one purest man.
He's bribing?
If not for the solid evidence,
I will never dare to
accuse anyone.
[Supervisor of the Ministry of Works: Huang's Spirit Tablet]
My condolences.
When did Huang An die?
Three days ago.
A day before father died.
Are two of you his friends?
I don't know him.
But he's related to
the case I'm working on.
I need to do an autopsy.
What did you say?
Autopsy?
Why don't you open your father's casket
and do an autopsy?
I did.
Chase this crazy man out!
Huang An's death is fishy.
You as his close relatives,
don't you want to know the truth?
He's already gone.
He died because he was drunk
and spilled the oil lamp.
He was burnt alive.
Drunk?
Does he drink usually?
There's a rule in the department.
Those who drink cannot be accepted.
Right. He doesn't drink.
He doesn't drink at all.
If you want the truth,
do an autopsy to find out.
[Supervisor of the Ministry of Works: Huang's Spirit Tablet]
If Baili Yan is corrupted,
is there anyone around me
who can be trusted?
We are at fault.
If the accusation is true,
where is the copper that he stole?
Your Majesty.
Lianshan's copper has been
confiscated by Song Liang from the Ministry of War.
It's all in his camp.
Does the informer have anything to do with this?
There's no evidence about that yet.
I'm still investigating.
Lianshan's copper...
is being swapped
right under my nose.
The joint corps didn't even notice.
Get Master Chu
to report to me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
My husband…
He's not burnt alive.
But...
But it was me
who received the corpse.
If a man is burnt alive, there will be signs of struggle.
The corpse will be twisted.
From Huang An's corpse, it looks like
he was killed before.
Burning the body
is just to cover up the truth.
Sister-in-law!
My brother's death
is really not an accident?
I beg you to find out the truth.
I'll try my best.
I'll talk.
This is disrespectful
towards our dead brother.
That's right.
Let him do his job.
I'm just doing based on the signals given.
Where the signal is,
I'll deliver the copper there.
[Chicken Perch]
Then what about this token?
This is given by my boss
for the purpose of trading.
[A cosmetic shop from South City: Tulip oil from Persia]
What trading?
I haven't been informed.
What are you doing?
How dare you!
You are being disrespectful!
The casket is still here.
How can you do that?
My brother's soul will be
watching you from above.
You're insulting my brother.
What hair oil do you use?
This is a clue.
A cosmetic shop from South City.
Tulip oil from Persia.
Who is it for?
Lady Zhai
used to love these things.
My husband bought it for her.
Huang An has a concubine?
Where is she?
A few months ago,
my husband chased her away.
Why?
She was stealing something to eat,
and accidentally spilled a soup.
[Huang's mansion]
The tulip oil from Persia costs a fortune.
If Huang An is willing
to buy it for her,
why would he chase her out
just because of a bowl of soup?
What you're saying is
there must be something fishy here.
Did I say that?
Then what you said just now
means...
I need to check out the cosmetic shop.
Erlang...
It is getting dark.
By the time we get to South City,
it will be totally dark.
Then we will depart tomorrow morning.
[Inner Guards' Office]
Imperial Attendant.
Call me brother.
Brother.
I'm wrong.
You don't have to rush to apologize.
If not for the joint corps
calling out to Master Song who's nearby
and got there on time,
I won't be able to see you again.
It was an emergency.
I didn't have time to return and report.
Brother.
What happened to the workers last night?
Master Song has sent them
to the inner guards.
Did they find anything?
Go back quick.
Get changed and rest.
-Don't meddle in this matter anymore.
-Brother.
They're all people
from Chuiliu Corporation.
Under Baili Yan's command,
they have been swapping the copper for years.
This case is defined as Baili Yan's corruption.
Case closed.
Brother.
Baili Yan is dead.
Why the corruption?
This matter is not that easy.
This has been decided.
Case closed.
I would like to ask you.
Who allowed you
to use the Empress' Behest as collateral
to guarantee Gao Bingzhu's innocence?
Brother.
Gao Bingzhu is innocent.
If he's dead,
the leads that I have
will be losing one.
He killed Lu Zhi and the other two inner guards.
Just because of this,
he's definitely not innocent.
Master Baili's case
involved Chunqiu Divine.
He's just like me.
He simply wants to find out who's behind all this.
If this case is closed simply,
I'm afraid...
Wu Siyue.
Mind your words.
Chunqiu Divine.
It's the empress' big taboo.
It's fine that you're mentioning it
here at my place.
If this news is spread,
it will be a huge issue.
If I can find the truth,
protect the capital,
so what if it becomes a huge issue?
Who is this
Gao Bingzhu?
What drug did he give you?
From now on,
don't ever cross paths
with this man.
If I find out,
don't blame for being heartless.
Have you heard about the things in the palace?
Master.
Wu Youjue is trying to calm things down.
This case has been declared as
Baili Yan's corruption.
With such declaration,
the joint corps is innocently involved.
Not exactly innocently.
We did have our faults.
The empress holding us responsible is sensible.
It's just that…
I'm still worrying about that matter.
Whether it's the informer and his daughter being killed,
or the copper being swapped,
those people have a way
to avoid the joint corps' watching eyes.
What you mean is…
The joint corps
does have a spy.
I'm just doing based on the signals given.
Then what about this token?
This is given by my boss
for the purpose of trading.
Gao Bingzhu?
You're not dead?
I thought that night…
I've been looking for you.
Do you know?
You've been looking for me,
or you've been out scamming?
You heartless man.
I was even looking for you.
Fine. As long as you're not dead.
What are you doing with this wooden talisman?
You recognize this talisman?
Isn't this the talisman for trading
at the black market?
The black market?
Right. This is the one.
The black market
has a variety of expensive goods,
so their trade is done cautiously.
This wooden talisman is small and unique.
Even if it's found,
you can say it's an accessory.
The patterns on the talisman
looks like it's from the Chuiliu Corporation.
Chuiliu Corporation again.
Looks like I have to go there again.
You are a wanted man.
Don't wander around, can you?
When you go alone,
please be careful.
Your beautiful long hair
is more vibrant than a young lady's.
Such beauty...
makes people jealous.
The way I see it,
your face looks prettier than before.
Words from your mouth
have always been music to my ears.
Your Majesty.
This is from Master Xunshan.
A copper mirror from Persia.
It's made of pure copper.
[Xianju Hall]
It's clear as day.
Master Xunshan usually
saves all the good things to himself.
At such moment,
he's finally willing to take it out.
[Xianju Hall]
Master Xunshan,
His Majesty does not want to see you.
Please go back.
[Chuiliu Corporation]
The kind will be bullied.
Anyone there?
Hello?
Anyone
there?
Where is it?
There's nobody here.
Why aren't there anyone here?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
No...
Is this a place you should be?
Go out. Go out.
Go. Go out.
Go.
I will go get
the one in charge.
Where are you going?
You dare to run away
from me, Bai Lang?
Spill.
I'll speak. I'll speak.
The talisman in your hand
is our person-in-charge's
Canglang Talisman.
All they do
is assassination or illegal trades.
I run because
I'm worried that I'll be involved.
What kind of man is your person-in-charge?
Erlang.
What hair oil do you use?
Osmanthus oil.
Every year during Osmanthus season,
I'll buy some.
Erlang.
Do you like this smell?
Then have you heard of
tulip oil?
Why are you asking about this?
I'm looking for a person
who uses this type of oil.
I know this tulip oil.
But this oil is very costly,
so usually the shops won't have them.
Normally the buyers will make their order
and it will be sent to them when the stock arrives.
Do you know
where the girl lives?
Come with me.
You better wear it.
This is a public place.
You are a wanted man.
Don't involve me.
Quick, say.
There is something wrong with Chuiliu Corporation.
Their cashier said
their person-in-charge is called Zhang Silang.
They do trades on assassinations.
Where is that Zhang Silang now?
I know you well.
Lately,
Chuiliu Corporation caused some trouble.
Their business was affected.
Zhang Silang
felt down
and did not return home.
He stays in his private mansion outside the city,
seeking sexual pleasures.
Private mansion?
Where is it?
My lady.
Isn't this a bit inappropriate?
Don't worry, shop owner.
We're not going to look
at your accounts.
We just want to find a buyer's address.
Doing us a favour.
This account book
is the vitals of this shop.
Please do not leak the information.
If you still don't trust us,
I'll buy all the goods
in your shop, alright?
Please don't joke with me.
If I run out of stock,
my shop may not be able to
survive in South City anymore.
I found it.
Buyers for Persia's tulip oil
are all loaded families.
Only this is sent to a brothel.
I believe it's Lady Zhai.
Let's go together then.
Miss Liu.
Where are you going?
Didn't you say to go to the brothel?
Let's go together.
Miss Liu.
This kind of place
is not suitable for you.
Why not?
[South City: Hongxiao Lane]
Come in, mister.
Safe journey.
Alright.
Mister. Come in, mister.
Come in and play.
Where are you going?
Stay here and accompany us.
Come in, mister.
Mister.
Go away.
You look so handsome.
I'm here today only for Lady Zhai.
Lady Zhai is out accompanying a guest today.
Why don't you
see if I'm alright?
Shen Fei.
Let's go. We'll go out first.
Don't go.
Mister.
-Mister, don't go.
-Ladies...
-Play with us for a while.
Ladies...
Erlang.
Have you found the person you want?
Miss Liu.
Did Erlang
do anything inside?
No.
Did he get to ask
what he wanted to ask?
Not yet.
Wait for a while.
There'll surely be results.
Let me tell you.
People in this kind of place
are only looking for benefits.
If they can't talk by asking,
maybe they can by bribing.