[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 33]
[Hanjia Granary]
Go.
Hurry up, guys.
Hurry up
and unload the stuff.
Okay.
Go.
Li Beiqi!
Why are you here?
What's going on with these grains?
What's going on with the Thunder delivered
to the Hanjia Granary?
Tell me!
They thought you betrayed us.
I hope they were wrong.
Siyue,
stop asking me.
Tell me what happened!
Let's talk over there.
[Map of Luoyang]
[Hanyuan Palace]
[Heavenly Temple]
It was shifted by 10.8 meters?
My lord,
Gao Bingzhu is back.
[Qingye, disciple of Four Season Clan]
Who is she?
She is Qingye,
a disciple of Four Season Clan.
The Clan?
The clock is ticking.
She can help us.
It was she that led me to Four Season Palace.
What have you found?
Look,
[Heavenly Temple]
the Heavenly Temple
was here before it was on fire.
The new Temple is now over here.
The new one was shifted
around 10 meters to the southeast.
What do you mean?
The Temple was reconstructed
on the original site.
The location should be the same,
and I didn't know
it was shifted.
[Hanyuan Palace]
Could it be shifted on purpose?
It's very likely.
There is a huge
groundwater network in Luoyang.
Geology is a key factor
in selecting a location for a building.
Also, there is mainly ooze below the surface in Luoyang.
Only the Heavenly Temple
was built on top of granite.
The shift in its location
means it is now
built on top of ooze.
It will easily collapse
if it is attacked.
The Thunder.
Her Majesty will kick off the Ceremony
outside the Heavenly Temple
at noon tomorrow.
The Clan will place the Thunder
around the Temple beforehand
and blow it up at the Ceremony.
In this way,
they can easily kill Her Majesty.
I've asked interior guards
to search the nearby areas several times.
They found nothing.
This is what concerns me the most.
The rhyme indicates
the geographical features of Luoyang.
It could be relevant
to the Clan's conspiracy.
It's called the Lianshan Rhyme.
Over the years, all of the Clan's plans
are based on this rhyme.
It's time to tell me
about the Lianshan Rhyme.
[Lianshan Rhyme]
Dragons and snakes slither around.
Mountains overlook the crowd.
These words are on the parchment scroll.
It's the Lianshan Rhyme.
I found it in a secret drawer
at Lady of Autumn's room.
I see.
It indicates the geographical
features of Luoyang.
It must include
the weak points of Luoyang's geology.
If the Clan detonates the Thunder
at those spots，
subsidence will occur around the Temple,
and the Clan can easily
achieve what they want.
What Lin Zhong wanted to report
can actually make or break Luoyang.
[Lianshan Rhyme]
[Heavenly Temple]
The Temple was built
on the chosen site
to avoid groundwater
so that its foundation
can remain solid.
The shift of the Temple's location
contradicts the essence of the Rhyme.
[Lianshan Rhyme, Hanjia Granary]
Every line in the Rhyme
seems to indicate the geographical
features of Luoyang,
but after I checked it word by word,
I found that it didn't exactly match
the geography of Luoyang.
You've got all the 72 characters
of the Rhyme.
It's your problem
if you can't work it out.
Lianshan Rhyme.
Lianshan Hall.
Your ancestors specialized
in waterways in the Lianshan Hall, right?
You should be so knowledgeable
about the waterways in Luoyang.
Years ago,
Yuwen Kai, the Head of Architecture,
drew a waterway map
based on his inspection.
The map illustrates
how rivers flowed in Luoyang
during the Three-River period.
Lianshan Hall.
The Lianshan Rhyme must
be related to the Lianshan Hall.
Bai Lang's ancestors specialized
in waterways in the Lianshan Hall.
He told me that
the Lianshan Hall
was established by Yuwen Kai of the Sui dynasty.
When was your map drawn?
10 years ago.
Yuwen Kai was from hundreds of years ago.
If the Lianshan Rhyme
was created by him
when Luoyang
was coming into shape,
we can work out
the Rhyme
by referring to a map at that time.
I'll go find a map.
Agent Gao!
Siyue,
You're up.
Untie me.
Have some food.
Untie me!
Li Beiqi,
why did you do this?
I don't believe
you colluded with the Clan
even if all the evidence
has pointed to you.
The Li Beiqi I know
would never do that!
Why?
Were you forced to do so?
You can tell me.
We can find a way out.
Let's go back and tell Sir Wu.
-My brother...
-Shut up!
Don't keep going down the wrong track!
Shut up!
You will get the answers
you want after the Ceremony is done.
Li Beiqi.
Are you alright?
Did you find Four Season Palace?
I saw that you came back
with Qingye.
Did she do anything to you?
Did you find Siyue?
Long story.
You gave me a signal
on the edge of the cliff.
I got it immediately
and rushed to the Interior Guard Services.
You know what?
They didn't know me
and I was nearly beaten up.
I guessed you must be here.
Madam Wu wasn't there.
I've heard that interior guards
will escort Her Majesty
before the Ceremony tomorrow.
I guess she is on call
at the Imperial Palace now.
Is the ceremonial dress ready?
It is, madam.
Put it aside.
Yes, madam.
We should have an early night
and get ready early tomorrow.
We can't make any mistakes.
By the way,
do we still
have the cleansing mud
given by Her Majesty?
We do.
You will certainly look stunning
at the Ceremony tomorrow
after you use it tonight.
It takes half a year
to make just one bottle.
It's surely good.
[Waterway map]
We need to hurry up.
The sun is rising.
Amazing!
Brilliant.
Where is Siyue?
Sir,
we haven't seen her
since last night.
Send some people to look for her.
Yes, sir.
[Waterway map in Luoyang]
Got it.
Where?
[East of the Imperial Palace]
No surprise. The Heavenly Temple.
Lijing Gate, Shang Shan Fang,
and Li De Fang.
These three places are connected
with the Temple by groundwater.
Once the Thunder explodes
at one of these places,
groundwater will flow back to the Temple,
damage its foundation
and destroy the entire building.
The three spots you circled
are all large areas.
How can we find the Thunder?
The Thunder should explode
10.8 meters below the surface
to cause groundwater to flow backward.
The Ceremony of Light is taking place today.
Our job is to protect Her Majesty.
Everyone should be extra alert.
Don't let anyone
interrupt the Ceremony
and Her Majesty.
Yes, sir.
Keep order for Her Majesty.
Protect Luoyang.
[Palace of Immortality]
May Your Majesty
blessed with longevity.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
the interior guards and the Palace Guards
are on standby.
Everything is ready for the Ceremony,
Your Majesty.
Why isn't Siyue here?
How could she be absent
at such an important event?
She is too carefree.
Tell her to settle down
after the Ceremony.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let's go.
Her Majesty is departing.
[Palace of Immortality]
You mean the Temple will collapse
if the Thunder explodes
at one of the three places.
Exactly.
Her Majesty already
left the Imperial Palace.
What we can do now
is to destroy the Thunder
at the three places
before the Ceremony starts.
Wait.
Baitan,
assist Gao Bingzhu.
Yes, my lord.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
May you bless Luoyang.
I need all the information
about the three places,
especially the information
about the geology 10.8 meters below them.
Don't miss any wells
and vegetable cellars.
Bingzhu.
This is Madam An from my Services.
You need to assist her.
You go with me.
Let's go.
Greetings,
Your Majesty.
May you bless Luoyang.
Have some food.
Siyue,
I know you hate me.
I also understand
that we can't be together.
You're Sir Wu's sister.
I'm just an orphan
he adopted on the street.
We live in different worlds,
but I get to protect you
and look after you
by your side.
That's enough for me.
However, you changed
after you met
Gao Bingzhu.
Do you remember that we used to talk freely
when we were working together?
We drank together to celebrate
you joining the Services.
You saved me
when I was injured.
After you met Gao Bingzhu,
did you ever think
of me or care about me?
Do you remember
when was the last time
we chatted?
The only person
you care about now
is Gao Bingzhu.
I don't get it.
Why is Gao Bingzhu
attractive to you?
Why?
Look,
he is a jinx.
He brings trouble
to people around him.
You will always
be in danger if you're with him.
It could even be life-threatening.
I'll kill him
when I have a chance.
[Chunrong Bar, Lijing Gate]
Dear guests,
I am sorry.
As you can see,
no tables are available now.
Please try another place.
We aren't here to drink.
My master will
celebrate his birthday soon.
We came over because we have
heard that you serve good wine.
Such a shame.
Our stock was cleared
the other day.
There is no wine now.
I can't help you.
No wine?
Do you dare show us your wine cellar?
You must be joking.
We're running a small business.
How can we owe a cellar?
Then how can you store
10 carriages of wine
imported from the West
every month?
Yeah, there must be a cellar.
Is it over there?
I've told you.
We don't have a cellar.
[The Deserted Chen Mansion, Li De Fang]
Are you alright?
Hongyi,
are you worried
about Gao Bingzhu?
I'm wondering
if they are doing alright.
They will be fine.
Don't worry.
Dragons and snakes slither around.
Mountains overlook the crowd.
They are on the parchment scroll,
aren't they?
[Lianshan Rhyme]
I see. You guys have been
trying to work out this rhyme all night
til this morning.
Liu Ran,
what's the time?
I looked at the sun.
It should be after 9 am.
9 am.
The sun.
Is it Chao Ye, meaning the crowd?
Or Zhao Ye?
Dragons and snakes slither around.
Mountains overlook the crowd.
[Mountains overlook the crowd]
Zhao means morning.
That character has two pronunciations,
Zhao and Chao.
Chao and Ye
mean the authorities and the public.
We tend to take them
as a fixed word.
But the Rhyme should be
worked out by understanding each character.
Chao Ye has nothing to do
with the crowd.
We should focus
on the east of sunrise.
What's wrong, Hongyi?
Groundwater is connected
to the east of the Imperial Palace.
[Waterway map in Luoyang]
The sun rises,
[Longguang Gate]
connecting a mountain.
The third place isn't
Shang Shan Fang.
It's Longguang Gate.
[Longguang Gate]
Shen Fei.
Should we notify Gao Bingzhu?
We don't have time.
Shen Fei.
Where is the Thunder?
It is
all over the place.
Thank god.
Let's go to Shang Shan Fang.
Let's go.
Go.
Near groundwater.
10.8 meters below the surface.
Where is it?
[Jingnian Bookstore, Longguang Gate]
Let's check inside.
[Jingnian Bookstore]
You are...
You can't get in.
Sir.
What are you doing?
Buying some books.
You can't come in.
It's fine.
What books are you looking for?
We just want to buy some books.
My master likes reading a lot.
You can't go there.
He has been
writing a book.
We need to find a book.
We'll leave
after we find it.
We don't have it.
We'll leave
after we're done.
Leave now.
Sir, listen to me.
We don't sell books.
Shen Fei.
Bingzhu.
How's Lijing Gate?
It's clear.
Only Shang Shan Fang is left now.
Let's split up.
Sure.
Gao Bingzhu,
the third place isn't Shang Shan Fang.
It's Longguang Gate.
Hongyi and Shen Fei are there.
My lord.
Shen Fei.
The Ceremony was completed.
My wish came true.
Your Majesty assigned Sir Wu
to ensure the security of the Ceremony.
It took place safely
because you put
the right person in the right position.
Besides, Sir Wu lived up to your expectations.
Sister.
Good for you!
I didn't expect you to find this place.
Do you really think you can stop us
from achieving the greater good
by stopping the Thunder
from exploding at one place?
It's about time.
The Clan has been planing for 5 years.
We are almost there.
Don't worry.
Someone will come to your rescue soon.
Bai Lang,
take Hongyi back.
Sure.
Careful.
I'll go after them.
Who are they?
I have no idea.
They're probably from the academy.
It's too late.
I'll take you there tomorrow morning.
I'll be upfront, though.
I won't go inside.
Follow me.
If you trust me,
come with me.
Where is Lady of Autumn?
She went to Luoyang
with people from the Clan.
The Clan has been making plans
based on the Rhyme these years.
Take me to Luoyang,
or I'll burn it.
What's with the boom?
Why were they all gone?
They held us back on purpose.
We were probably fooled.
It's part
of their plan.
Go check what the explosion was about.
Got it.
This isn't as simple as we thought.
The Clan must have
something to do with the explosion.
One thing is strange as well.
Somehow,
the killer I brought back
from the Clan has been helping me
look for the Thunder
around the Heavenly Temple.
Is it possible that
the Ceremony is just a guise?
They might have planned a bigger conspiracy.
My lord.
Hanjia Granary was blown up.
What?