Why on earth is Yao Ziliao
Su Yuehua
You can't afford to lose, can you deliberately provoke
Ziping, tell me why you won
You speak
People should be willing to gamble and admit defeat
Purple Azolla
You mustn't talk
At that time, the empress was clear
There must be something wrong with this
You tell me
What the hell did you do
Wang Mocha loves to attend Zen and worship Buddha
But the real Wangchuan map
There are boat tourists
Only there are no monks
Monk
The old monk under the tree
Emperor Taizu once entered Huangjue Temple as a monk
I hate people the most in my life
Hang bald monks on your lips
If anyone in the Forbidden City dares to say a word,
The consequences are unimaginable
But now times have changed
Few people in the palace remember this taboo
But the empress knows it well
How can I let you win
It turns out that you are deliberately misleading me
Su Yuehua
People catch rats in their own homes
Who let you keep good people wrong
You have to get in at one end
Purple Azolla
It's just a small skill to carve insects
Today's competition
I am the one
I won
Moon flower
What do you think is the hardest part of the real Wangchuan map
Is it really to reproduce the artistic conception in the painting
Isn't it
Wang Chuan map sample
It is indeed the most exquisite fancy cold dish in the world
It's a pity to meet the cold season
Be blown by a cold wind
All the ingredients will become more and more cold and hard
The function of viewing is far greater than eating
I had already thought about it
Use the method of carving and preserving flowers in Jingzhou, Huguang
Make all the ingredients into candied fruit in advance
For noble people to taste
What a pity
You stole the painting
Everything I can think of
You will not think of it in advance
Because you put all your thoughts
It's all on showing off skills
I forgot that the ingredients will eventually be imported
The picture of Wangchuan has been beautifully restored
If you use this talent in the side door,
Then you are on the road of cooking
It really stops there
Zouziliao
Ignore her
I can't see it
That's awesome
Lord You
Believe whatever I draw
You can't really be so naive, can you
Let's go
That's boring
You can't afford to lose
All right
The person sent for the painting did not look closely at the painting
I told her to make a trap
But it's interesting for you to come and go
Just lost once
Why do you look so ugly
She has never been so serious
What the hell happened
The high-rise buildings on the city are cut too clearly
Late coming overlooking Enigmatic
Xishan is green and connected with the East China Sea
Nanji Zhouche Club Beijing
Red brocade gardens should shine at night
Huang Yun sees Qiu Cheng in Longmu
The sky is vast and clear
Watching Feihong Wanli Levy
How
Good poetry, good poetry
Your Highness
Climbing the stairs and overlooking last night
Is there a beauty on the boat
What kind of eyes
Where does the beauty come from in the dead of night
It's more like having a female ghost
It looks more and more like a person
Full of nonsense
But where is it like when you believe in a pen
It's not like
Handmaiden's eyesight
Wrong, wrong
Damn handmaiden damn handmaiden damn
Damn handmaiden
Your Highness
Hu Shangshi was my carelessness
Please forgive me
Just now, a will came from Kunning Palace
From now on
You are no longer the standard meal of the Shang Food Bureau
Hu Shang Shi
Please allow me to have a second chance to compete
You have already lost the first game
I dare to talk big
Don't go out yet
If you lose again in the second game
What to do
Just me
Can beat Yao Ziliao
What kind of person is she
It's not worth mentioning at all
If it were me
I can give you one last chance
But if you lose again this time
He left the Shang Food Bureau forever
Yes
The Knife Skill of Su Dian Food
It's really a little superb
You see
The mountains and the waters
It's really a bit of the artistic conception of the original painting
Descendants of famous chef Su
Nature is extraordinary
What a pity
The Queen intended to help Hu Shanwei
Nature will not judge fairly
The old monk who participated in Zen meditation
Can predict the Queen's mind so accurately
You still have Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon in the Food Bureau
The tricks of young people can't hide from the eyes of empress
Wang Mocha's Wangchuan Map and the Old Monk Participating in Zen
It also brings out the best in each other
It's just a competition in the second game
It is not up to the empresses of the harem to decide
What the imperial concubine means is
The East Palace will invite the important ministers in the DPRK on behalf of the emperor
Youtai liquid pool
What about the competition in the second game
It was set in Xiyuan
Your Highness
Golden Jade Soup Just Delivered
I know you don't like it too sweet
They were specially ordered to release little honey
Only seasoned with sweet-scented osmanthus
You try it
Your Highness
Recently, it is either writing or drawing
Don't you have to deal with government affairs
I seldom have time to spend more time with you
Isn't it good
Once upon a time, when the first emperor was there,
Not to take you north to hunt
Is to force you to assist in government affairs
You can't finish reading the throne
Even I can't see you
Now your highness has free time
I am naturally glad
It's just that my father didn't ascend to the throne long ago
There are many government affairs
Your Highness, as a country, Chu Jun
It should be shared for him more
If he is willing to let me help him share it, then
Your Highness, it's time to get cold
I'm tired
Crown Princess
Your Highness, he
It seems that everything in the past
Your Highness has never forgotten for a moment
Temple
There is no burning of felt
What kind of Lei Gong chestnut to simmer
Start, start, start, start
Come on with pleasure today
Be sure to enjoy yourself and return home
Your Highness, look
Your Highness
The emperor has come up
Big Brother Big Brother
Your Highness, isn't the emperor ill
Here comes the Holy Drive
Notify the kitchen
Prepare meals
Yes
Father
See Your Majesty
Avoid
Thank Your Majesty
Quick, quick, quick
Quickly
Put this over there
Come here, this way
Gently, gently
Don't disturb the Holy driving
Father-in-law Zhao
Noble people don't have ears
How can you hear it at such a distance
Your boy is too long, isn't he
Do what you should do
Father-in-law Zhao
Just let them do these little things
Why bother you to order yourself
Last time Your Majesty came to Xiyuan
Eat something cold
The cold wind blew again
As a result, I went back to a serious illness
So the Queen asked me to come this time
Is to charge you
These wild birds bear fruit
Be sure to be extra careful
Please rest assured that Father Zhao will understand
Those two are busy first
It's a good sword
The sovereign listened to your words
The first one is advised in the above table
Sure enough, he won the favor of the emperor
You don't have to send anything to me in the future
I don't lack anything
Sovereign charge
Be careful in everything
This is the wind and cold
The prince will entertain you on my behalf
Then the King of Zhao came
Our brothers have been for a long time
There is no swimming in Xiyuan together
So today, everyone is together
As soon as your majesty ascended the throne,
It increased the age of my brother
Imperial grace is so mighty
My brother is grateful
Naturally, I want to go to the palace to give thanks
We're brothers
Don't be polite
Come and sit down
Brother Xie Huang
Ayan
Come here
When you finish the copybook I sent you,
I'll take you to release the eagle, okay
Really
Wei Wang grew up
I am very close to His Royal Highness the Prince
My favorite person in the world is Big Brother
Brother Emperor
Although the prince is young,
But quite prestigious
And won the hearts of the people
Even King Wei admired him so much
No wonder my father used to tell us when he was around
This one day Taiping Son of Heaven also
What I care most about on weekdays
Is the sufferings of the people
Object discussion between the government and the public
You all serve the first emperor
A loyal minister for more than 20 years
It is the pillar of the country
If there are any omissions in my future administration,
I hope you guys
Take out this seal for correcting mistakes
Dense and sparse to smell
I
Be sure to consider it
I give you this seal
I just want to get along honestly between the monarch and his subjects
The last thing I like is flattery
What I love most is the truth
From the heart
I wait for a decree to thank you
Ai Qing
What advice do you have
Your Majesty's administration is clear and there is no deficiency in political affairs
How dare I speak nonsense
Zhong Ai Qing
It is a good thing that my father can ask for words in coachable
But it's hard to relax in the garden today
Why don't you leave government affairs for the time being
Wait for them to consider it carefully
It's not too late to give advice to my father
His Royal Highness is right
Your Majesty, please let me wait and think about it
As soon as I ascended the throne, I gave an order of admonition
But today
There is no admonition of loving Qing
Good
Just
Everybody up, please
Thank Your Majesty
The fish tuna is really delicious this season
Father
Fish tuna is delicious
But it's a fishy thing after all
Extremely cold in the stomach
Fear of hurting dragon body
Get out of here
Eat less oil and don't eat too much
In case you get sick
How can you accompany me to release the eagle
Isn't Big Brother delicious
Big Brother, this is crisp and delicious
Mingming tastes best
Excuse me, is Yao Zhang's meal there
I am
Meng Shangshi has orders
Please come with me, girl
Is this cold
Sure enough
Melt at the entrance
This chicken piece is still very white and delicious
Cook chicken in light vinegar in advance
To be so fragrant and tender
What's the use of this copper coin
Miaomiaomiao
Antler vegetables with porridge have excellent flavor
Please taste it, Your Majesty
Common practices of mandarin fish porridge are not common
Brother, this is really interesting
It's just a round monk porridge in Yi Jianzhi
Read a few idle books
Dare to show off before the command
That's interesting
If you love reading, you are an elegant chef
Brother, you are so strange today
See nothing pleasing to the eye
How on earth did this kitchen offend you
Do I have
You're wrong
What did Hu Shangshi tell you to do
What are you talking about
Meng Shangshi didn't tell me to lead you there
Meng Shang Shi
Serving the emperor for dinner
Those who come to send messages must be the command's people
You see
Your boots are covered with mud
It is also worthy to serve in front of the emperor
Somebody come
Somebody, there's an assassin
Somebody, please
There is another person
There are moles under the eyebrows
Short in stature
It's going that way
Don't chase it yet
Yes
What did I say
How can you back down
People still can't tolerate you
Don't you come now
Thank you, Lord You
How
Blood
The more you rub, how can you meet people
And now
Can you still see it
Don't you go soon
What's the matter, Xiao Shi
Let me check
And move me to see
What's going on
Xiao Shi
Ayan
Don't come over. Get out of the way
Xiao Shi
You get up
Your Highness
A-a-a-a-a
Ah, ah
Ayan
Go to Xuan Tai Yi quickly
Yes
Ayan
Blockade Xiyuan and prohibit anyone from entering or leaving
Yes
Is there anything unusual before King Wei goes out
No, no, no
Your Highness was just fine
What's wrong with this
It's antler
Your Majesty, it must be the antler
Who allows you to talk nonsense
Antler grows in Shan Ye
It is inevitable to be contaminated with snake venom
Mung bean soup must be scalded before eating
Now His Royal Highness King Wei is poisoned
I'm afraid they have neglected this
Your Majesty is careful in cooking
There would never be such a big mistake
Or please ask the Imperial Doctor to treat His Royal Highness Wei Wang quickly
All the kitchens involved will be won
Who cooked the antler today
They
What happened
Take away
Why are you arresting people for no reason
What are you doing
Go, go, go
What did I do
Let go
Let go of me
Cut the crap
What the hell have we done
Let go of me
What's going on here
Quickly
Sister
You can't go. You can't go
What the hell happened
Hu Shang Shi
Events of the Day
Fresh antler from here
They were all scalded with mung bean soup
Meng Shangshi and Ziping were wronged
I have narrowly escaped death
There is still time to care about other people's lives and deaths
You are really an extraordinary person
The feud between you and me
After all, it has nothing to do with business
Meng Shangshi and others were imprisoned
The Food Bureau must have lost its reputation
The errand of entering imperial food
It must be taken by the food supervisor
Then what good will it do to you
Meng Shang has no way to eat
This makes a big mistake
When I officially take over in the future,
Will regain the right to eat
You don't need a little palm meal
Royal Guards
Not from the rest of the antler
Find out any problems
How can you be so sure
Snakes and insects crawl through venom residues
Who can guarantee the dish that King Wei took
No problem
Moon flower
You've been in the kitchen the whole time
You should see it with your own eyes
All the antler vegetables
They are all cleared with mung bean water
I didn't see anything
Moon flower
On the menu of that dish
Only Yin Ziping and Fang Hanying
Let you get away with it
But don't forget
There will be no Meng Shang to protect you in the future
If you come to provoke regardless of honor or inferiority,
Hugh blames me for being ruthless
Moon flower
I can win by strength
Why bother to make trouble
You don't think
Am I the one who tampered with the antler
It was their own negligence
I ran into the emperor's favorite youngest son
It's a day to die of her
If the doctor diagnosed
Is it true that King Wei's illness has nothing to do with them
Wei Wang suddenly fell into a coma after eating
How did they get away with it
Yuehua, you should know
This matter is not man-made
Everything is God's will
What we've done
It's nothing more than standing by and watching
Do you understand
Yes
Imperial concubine empress
Wei Wang's disease
Wearing a court sentence
Everyone in the palace knows it
My son was in good health before he went to the garden
He ate poisonous antler
Empress, this minister also dare not make an assertion
This is not the time to investigate the cause
The most important thing is
Is to cure Wei Wang's illness
Sister Yao
Evergreen
I've asked someone I know
Wei Wang is seriously ill with high fever
His Majesty himself prayed for him
Waiting all night again
It's just that the doctor can't find out the cause
Meng Shang's food is afraid of being in danger
Don't wait
I want to see the Imperial Concubine
I really have something to say
Now Wei Wang is seriously ill
The imperial concubine is angry with Meng Shangshi
Don't say you can't see it
Even if you saw it,
I'm afraid I have to fold myself in
Evergreen
Then you tell me
What kind of symptoms do Wei Wang have
How could I know that
Let's go
It's not just Meng Shang who eats them
There is also Guanglu Temple in Shanglinyuan
Anyone involved in this matter will be implicated
I can't take care of it
You have been waiting here for two hours
You have done your utmost
Go home
Let's go
Evergreen
Your Majesty
Although your highness has taken the poison-clearing decoction,
But he is too young
Now the head and face are swollen
Pulse floating number
I'm afraid I can't stand it
Your Majesty
Coco, on his back
Toxic backlog in lungs
There is redness, swelling and heat pain
Your Majesty Ayan is the most like you
Usually sickly
How do you think he can stand the pain
I want to spend it safely this time
I really can only ask God for mercy
Your Majesty, Your Royal Highness, is worried about King Wei's illness
Please see again and again
See, see, let him go back
Yes
Your Majesty, you said Ayan is good
How can you suddenly be poisoned
Someone must have a grudge against male and female servants and concubines
Deliberately wanted Ayan's life
His Royal Highness the Prince
Your Majesty said please ask your Royal Highness to go back first
When Wei Wang's illness has improved,
Again
Let's go, Chen Wu
Prince Boxing Heart
Please transmit it to your majesty
Quickly
Go to report Hu Shangshi
Yes
Empress Empress
There is still a grievance in the Food Bureau
To play in person
How dare you
How dare you stop the Queen's ceremonial ceremony
Don't retreat yet
Empress still has grievances in the Food Bureau
Please ask the Empress to redress her grievances
Somebody drag her down
Empress
Emperor Taizu set up drums outside the Wumen Gate
Allow the wrongdoers in the world to complain to the holy man
Empress Xiaoci and Empress Renxiao followed the example of the imperial court
Open up a wide range of ways to rehabilitate grievances in the harem
But now the grievance is in front of the empress
How can the empress sit idly by
Don't stop her mouth yet
Empress Empress
Wait a minute
Handmaidservant. See Synonyms at Empress
Monteggia made a big mistake by omission
You're still here to redress her grievances
Take away
Hu Shang Shi
Can you assert in front of the empress
There is really no grievance
Why can't I argue
Don't take it away yet
Hu Shang Shi
Empress Empress
Don't listen to this woman's gossip to confuse people
She is a Monteggia henchman
Will do everything possible to excuse her
The handmaiden will send her to Miyagi
Make an example of others
She mentioned Queen Filial Piety just now
Empress Ren Xiao
If you don't listen to her redress
But I am heartless and unkind
Emperor Taizu, the empress, has long said clearly
Only those who have great grievances and confidential feelings can shout grievances
There are still people in the harem who deliberately falsely accuse
Involve innocent people
How can her words be accepted
Besides, this person shouted in front of the temple and collided with the phoenix driver
Violate palace rules
Collision Phoenix Drive
Handmaiden is willing to receive punishment
Just ask the Empress to redress her grievances
You have to think it over
If you go back on your word when you are punished
It will be punished as causing trouble for no reason
By that time
I will send you to Gongzhengsi for a higher punishment
Ask the Empress to fulfill it
Empress
Good
I help you