August of the 22nd year of Yongle
Zhu Gaochi, Prince of Daming, ascended the throne as Emperor
Make Crown Princess Zhang Queen
And canonized Guo as the imperial concubine
Zhu Zhanji, the great grandson of the emperor, is the crown prince
Hu is the crown princess
Zi Jin
The Crown Princess's Palace sent people
Previous days of crying sacrifice
Crown princess is weak due to qi deficiency
Have a cough
Hu Shang's index finger name asked you to make a medicated diet and send it
Yes
The civil and military ministers advised him to enter five times
Your Majesty has just promised to ascend to the throne
According to etiquette
It has been more than 27 days in mourning
Officials who are in a hurry to change clothes
But I miscalculated
After all, father and son are United
So is the prince
I heard you coughed badly yesterday
Don't hold on
Or please ask the medicine manager to come and have a look
I was too tired a few days ago
Blood stasis and heat are in it
I caught a cold again last night
Just rest for a few days
Don't make a fuss
Or is your health important
Handmaiden, I'll make you a cup.
Ganfengling developed by Tai Hospital
You drink first
Good
Then it's good to feel the wind these days
Or are you the most considerate
It's very hot
I'm feeling chest tightness and polydipsia
The Crown Princess has been coughing for a long time
Lotus leaf porridge clears heat and moistens lung
Please have a try
Inside are sweet-scented osmanthus and taro puree
Yes
Cinnamon is fragrant and refreshing
Taro benefits stomach and spleen
But the Crown Princess is weak and has spleen deficiency
Taro is prone to abdominal distension
Not multi-purpose
This lotus leaf porridge is very good for me
Today's meal is light and delicious
Give it to the Crown Prince as it is
Yes
Crown Princess
Be careful to lead the wolf into the house
Exemption from Yongle's 22-year hukou salt grain
Horse grass, firewood and charcoal are in arrears everywhere
Since December of Yongle 20 years ago,
Do your best to avoid
Add another one
Escape to people everywhere
Be forgiven for one's sins
Send back to the place of origin to resume business
Avoid the difference for two years
Taxes and grain owed by their households
Do your best to avoid
Father
I'm just going to buy everywhere
Is that why you're here
Father stopped in Xishima and Yunnan
Acquisition of cross toes
It's all a matter of caring for the people
My son has no objection
Only the return of Nanjing
I also ask my father to think twice
Who said it was all returned
You know before I say it
Are you sending someone now
Peep at my every move
Father calms his anger
I just heard that my father ordered people to go south
When repairing Nanjing Imperial City, I dared to speculate
After the great funeral of Grandpa Huang,
Father may intend to return it all
If my son guessed wrong
I also ask my father to forgive me
Since moving the capital
South-to-North Grain Transfer
Wasting people and money
Arutai is constantly disturbing and causing trouble
Nanjing
It is the capital set by Taizu
Return to Nanjing
That is to follow the old system of our ancestors
Father
Beijing is the land of Longxing
Natural barrier and geographical advantage
Grandpa Huang moved the capital here
It is to respect the son of heaven
Guard the gate of Daming
System 4 razes the world and achieves the foundation of the world
It's easy to return it in a hurry
Grandpa Huang's painstaking efforts will be destroyed
Father
The man that Grandpa Huang wants to kill
Regardless of the severity of the crime
You will be forgiven
The national policy he set
It is also a change of course one by one
Run in the opposite direction everywhere
Why on earth
Prince
Don't rely on the favor of the first emperor
You can be so presumptuous to me
Grandfather loves me
Just because the people in the world who can understand him
Just me
Grandfather's ambition father doesn't understand
I'll never understand
You just want to be a king of benevolence and righteousness
But now the country's biggest future trouble is not removed
Rely solely on benevolence and righteousness
Unable to govern the world
Then you tell me
What is the future trouble
A captaincy
What I do
You don't have to worry about it
Get the hell out of here
Get out of here
My son retires
Continue
Yes
At that time, the Royal Guards were ordered by the Imperial Examination
Supervise the East Palace
Where is the volume
When Grandpa Huang wins, he will return to the DPRK
We went hunting together
Your Excellency
We have been ordered to monitor the East Palace
Now the new emperor has succeeded to the throne
Will you settle accounts after autumn
Kneel down
Hu Shang Shi
What does this mean
Crown Princess
Handmaiden specially came to plead guilty today
Handmaiden is lax in royal control
Let Yao Ziliao commit the great crime of privately longitudinal Zhuang Fei
Private longitudinal Zhuang Fei
Before Zhuang Fei was buried
Yao Ziliao took advantage of the meal delivery machine
Privately vertical Zhuang Fei out of the palace
This matter is proved by Ajin, a maid of Yongning Palace
Now the harem is initially decided
Empress Empress is busy with everything
Handmaiden dare not disturb
Specially came to ask the Crown Princess to decide
Hu Shang Shi
Do you know what a sin it is to falsely accuse
Even if you were my elder sister
I won't be light either
Ah Kin
How dare you hide it in front of the Crown Princess
Is it desperate
Crown Princess
It was Miss Yao who gave her master a jade pendant
Just walked out of Bei'an Gate safely
What jade pendant
A phoenix that only a queen can have
The Bei'anmen guard is an old man in the palace
Once you see this pendant,
Panic is still less than enough
How dare you stop it
General Chen Lao promised to keep his mouth shut
On returning to the palace
But you need to leave Pei as evidence
Yao Ziliao
Where did you get it
It is said that this Feng Pei was carved by the first emperor himself
Empress Renxiao carries it with her day and night
Seeing Pei in the palace is like seeing the Lord
You can't obey orders
Empress Renxiao personally raised the prince
Grandparents and grandchildren have deep feelings
After she died
Leave Yu Pei to the First Emperor
Indicate that you should leave it to your future grandson-in-law
You said
This jade pendant
Why is it in the hands of a female official
Yao Ziliao
Who the hell are you
Your Highness
Tell her to come
I want to see her
Yes
What is it
Your Highness
General Chen Lao, the guard of Bei'an Gate
Know that your highness is waiting for the catalpa palace day and night
Never dared to disturb
Heard about your highness's return
There is one thing to offer
Why don't you answer
Yao Ziliao
She was the first emperor of that year
The princess set for the prince
Mrs. Peng Chengbo
Crown Princess
Sun Shi is ten years old
She was introduced to the palace by Mrs. Peng Chengbo
Raised by Queen Zhang today
Six months later
Sun Shi came out of the palace with illness
Stay in Yongcheng for illness
You can only get married when you grow up
Who knows that the first emperor complied with the destiny
Change you to be your princess
Sun Shi is narrow-minded
A serious illness
After the first emperor learned about it,
Be greatly unhappy
No one has dared to mention her since then
Crown Princess
I told you that you are kind and righteous
See it now
You have been blinded by this snake and scorpion woman
She concealed her identity and entered the palace
Lurking by your side
What exactly is the purpose
It speaks for itself
Hu Shang Shi
You and I get along for a long time
Have I ever done a bad thing
Killed a man
Don't you dare say
You concealed your identity and entered the palace
It's not for another purpose
Crown Princess
This woman stays in trouble
Can't be tolerated
I know you can't be ruthless
I'll do it for you
Bearer
Are you really going to kill me
Hu Shang Shi
Palm meal Yao Ziliao
With intent to murder the Crown Princess
Not allowed to be interrogated by Gong Zhengsi
Has committed suicide by taking poison
Crown Princess
The evidence is here
Previous
You want to take my identity
Now we have to fabricate lies
Take my life
I always thought you were a good person
But when it comes to yourself,
You have to turn around Gan Kun
Are you ignoring right and wrong
Can't
Elder sister
She must die, Crown Princess
She must be killed
Elder sister
After entering the palace
I lost a sister
When I saw you,
I have a feeling of being lost and recovered
Just before yesterday
I'm still thinking
You are so intelligent
You can't live up to it
Future
I should leave the mantle to you
But
You threatened the Hu family
Threatened the Crown Princess
I can't help it
I will be a cow and a horse in the afterlife
Pay for my sins today
Elder sister
You're confused
All women in the world can enter the palace
Sun Shi alone can't do it
I did all this for you
Even if you don't do it for yourself
Think about your loved ones, too
What are you doing
Zi Jin Lai
Are you all right
Zi Jin
Your Highness
Take people away
Zi Jin
If I hadn't sent someone to keep an eye on Qingning Palace,
Are you going to hide it from me all your life
Your Highness, please rest assured
Miss Yao is just too frightened
The body is fine
Allen Su will come over soon
Go down
Yes
I retire
There is not a word of explanation
This is going to go
Yao Ziliao
No
I forgot your last name is not Yao
Is even the name a fake
Your Highness is really a noble man who forgets things
When I saw you,
You're only ten years old
Yes
Into the palace for the first time
Still young
How many years have passed
Don't say your highness
Who else in this palace remembers who I am
It was your grandmother who entered the palace for you
Isn't it
Is your highness going to pursue the crime of taking the slave's name
I told you
Don't call yourself a handmaiden
I'm not a handmaiden now
And who is that
You ventured into the palace
Approaching me on purpose
What exactly do you want
Your Highness
That year
I went to worship Buddha with my mother
I accidentally met Mrs. Peng Chengbo
Since then
My wife often goes in and out of Sun's house
And what my mother taught me
It is also becoming more and more strict
And then I found out
In order to consolidate the power of the Zhang family, my wife
I've been looking for a girl with early wisdom
Carefully teach
In case of Tai Sun Fei's choice
Ultimately
She picked me out
Your Highness doesn't like playing chess with me very much
Do you listen to me play the piano
In addition to chess, calligraphy and painting,
Pipa string
Female red cooking
Even Cuju riding and shooting is a cinch
What does your highness like
I will learn to be proficient
Not so
I'll be beaten
Serve Your Highness
Live for you
Seems to be the only meaning in my life
I don't know any of this
Yeah
Such a trifle
How can you defile your highness's ear
Your Highness will never know
Before I entered the palace to meet the emperor,
What happened to the Sun family
Since I was the master who taught you since I was a child,
You have become the right election for Taisunfei
This is a good thing
Then why did she
She's not my master
She's my real mother
I know when I pee
She is my mother
But I never called her once
Because of her humble status
Because she will defile the lintel of Sun Shi
So we get along day and night
She held hands
Teach me to read and write
Play the piano
But don't let me call her mother
How many times do I have to blurt out
In the end, I didn't dare
She's dead
Die for me
A man who is a great grandson's wife
How can anyone know
Her mother was born in music
What a proud person she is
She never accepted her fate
But she accepted it
For my future
In order to let me have a background that is not criticized,
She hanged herself
Your Highness
As far as you are concerned
It's nothing more than changing a candidate
As far as I'm concerned
It means my biological mother died in vain
It means her death is meaningless
I don't want it
I don't want to be a great grandson
I just want her to come back to life
I was wrong
One of the things I regret most
Was when she was alive
I didn't call her mother
I'm sorry
Zi Jin
Your Highness didn't ask me
Why did you enter the palace
Although Xu is not my biological mother,
But she sympathizes with my mother
Treat me like my own
She is seriously ill
Still holding a breath
Want to see me get married in style
But in the end
In the end, I waited for such news
Your Highness
Just because of this marriage
I lost the most important person in the world
So I have to go to the palace
I must see it with my own eyes
The woman who replaced me. How good is she
I want to ask your highness myself
Where on earth did I go wrong
You're not wrong
Everything is not your fault
I promise
From now on
No one will dare to hurt you again
I promise
Crown Princess
Your Highness, he
Please rest assured that the Crown Princess
Your Highness would have severely punished Hu Shangshi
But Miss Yao said
After all, get to know each other
Ask your highness for mercy
Your Highness has ordered Hu Shangshi to go back to meditate on his past
But if you do it again
Next time
Crown Princess
Your Highness ordered the handmaiden to send you back to the palace
Go out and watch
Yes
Elder sister is careless in words and deeds
Infuriate your highness
Now you're satisfied
I've never nurtured a man so carefully
Now I will kill her with my heart
And for whom
You still don't know how to repent
Even though she was engaged to your highness
But now times have changed
Am I so narrow-minded
There is room for many beauties in the harem
Can't she be alone
What are you laughing at
I'm asking you a question
Why not answer
Emperor Taizu ruled in order to avoid the harem
Exclusive power of consorts
There are already ancestral precepts
After every son of heaven and prince,
Imperial concubines
Carefully select folk women with good families
These women who were elected to the palace
There is no family to rely on
The only thing you can rely on
Is the affection with the emperor
Taizu Xiaoci Queen Ma
Emperor Renxiao, Queen Xu
All of them accompanied their husbands to fight
Has made indelible contributions
In the heart of the emperor
Even if the world is stunning
It's not as good as having a wife
Emotions of mutual affection
Crown Princess
Now let me ask you something
What is your affection with the prince
The prince is surrounded by beauty
But I never despised my wife
He is not such a person
Wife
Don't forget
You are immersed in your own grief
Almost injured the prince by mistake
What kind of love is there between husband and wife
Think about it
Know Sun Shi's misfortune and dedication
The prince will give birth to infinite guilt and pity
The only thing you should be thankful for is taking the lead
Early determination of birthright
Otherwise, Sun Shi will appear
Where can you stand?
Stop talking about it
This harem is changing rapidly
Even if there are merits, it may not be safe
Queen Zhang today
Stay with your husband all the way
From the prince's son to the throne as emperor
Saved him in danger many times
But now in this harem,
There is one more Guo
Founding hero family
Young, beautiful and sacred
He also gave birth to three princes
Your Majesty became the imperial concubine as soon as he ascended the throne
What kind of person is Queen Zhang
Isn't it forbearance and concession everywhere
How are you better than Queen Zhang
It's time for the Crown Princess to wake up
You have been ordered to monitor the East Palace
But only record my good deeds
Aren't you afraid of the first emperor blaming you
I fear
When Your Majesty was in the East Palace,
Someone who has something to do says
Your Highness knows how to slander people
Your Majesty's Cloud
I don't know
Knowing as a child ear
Knowing that there are often people behind them telling slanderers to the first emperor
Alienate the royal family between father and son
Your Majesty is tolerant and generous
Only the filial duty of being a son
Minister
Naturally, I only do my duty as a courtier
So you are
Is it loyal to the first emperor
Or loyal to me
Your Majesty
Five Northern Expeditions by the First Emperor
Entrust the country as much as possible
You are sympathetic to the people, the country and the benevolence
Who doesn't admire the civil and military affairs of the Manchu Dynasty
How can I allow villains to frame up
As a result, the national foundation collapsed
As a royal guard
Fulfill the duty of supervision
Record and hear
Hear and hear
If a word is not true
I am willing to be punished
Almost wronged loyal ministers
Get up
Yes
Wang Jie resigned due to illness
I order you
Lead the Royal Guards Command
Don't betray my trust in you
The minister was ordered
Chen Ding Liver and Brain Tu Di
Live up to the grace
Your Majesty
It's time to eat
Go ahead
Yes
Miss Yao refused to accept it
She said
This Feng Pei doesn't belong to her
From now on
Meals in the East Palace
It's up to you to take care of it
Hu Shang Shi
The meals of the prince and princess
They used to name each other
Zi Jin
The company begged me for a long time
I promised to let you through
You have to do a good job
Don't ruin my reputation
Yes
The company is usually in charge of some
Small things about firewood and charcoal
Why do you want to tune the past
Who is going to transfer to the company
Holy Oracle
From now on
Meng Shangshi returned to Shangshi Bureau
Still in the official position
Master Jing
In this way
Shang Shi Bureau
There are two adults who are still eating
Shang Food Bureau's Division of Food
Division IV, Department of Yun, Department of Pharmacy
Heavy responsibility
Since Emperor Taizu's time,
I set up two people who still eat
Now
It's just following the old rules
Is there anything wrong with it
Congratulations to Meng Shangshi
He Xi Meng Shang Shi
Master Jing
I appreciate Yao Ziliao's cooking skills very much
Want to keep her in the catering department
What do you think
Meng Shangshi is both
Still in charge of the Food Bureau
All the staff are under your control
All right
Let's go your separate ways
Yes
That's great
Zi Jin
Meng Shangshi sits in the town
We can feel much more at ease in the future
Master Jing
At the beginning, you were
Promised me personally
Let me take charge of the food bureau
Monteggia's bullying
I don't even pay attention to me in the past
How can I help her
This holy oracle
I'm just following the orders.
People who even hate empresses
How can I see your majesty
Is it Guo Guifei
This official doesn't know
Master Jing
You want to stay out of it
I'm afraid it's not that easy
Since I took charge of the Food Bureau,
Handle a large number of current accounts
If Monteggia returns to power,
Once it is checked,
It is inevitable that adults will be involved
You threatened me
Dare not
Take care of yourself
I told you before
Jing Quan is insatiable
You shouldn't get too close to him
At the beginning, I was only in charge of the Shang Food Bureau
If you don't give him some benefits,
How can you
Be promoted to Shangshi so quickly
Meals should enter the population
Don't let any mistakes be made
As a kitchen
For one's own sake
Crime of indulging others
What other qualifications do you have for cooking
A Wai
You weren't like this before
I thought you said
Can be contended for or won
But you won't forget
The bottom line of being a man
You now
Remember before you
Have you said anything
Bottom line
People only need to take the first step
Crossing the bottom line
That's a matter of time
But you can rest assured
If something really happens,
I'm the only one to bear it
It won't involve you
This is the period of filial piety
A rudimentary diet
Please forgive your highness
Grandpa Huang has always been
To red tape
Sneer at one's nose
But
If he knew
Father now has green vegetables and tofu all day long
I'm afraid I'm too happy
And don't talk
Seems
You really hate me
If there were people in the world
Master my destiny
Causing me a lifetime of pain
I will kill it
Your Highness speaks heavily
Handmaiden dare not
I dare not
Still don't hate
Even if you have the power to reach heaven,
There's no way to get your mother
Bring the dead back to life
Then
Is there anything else I can do for you
Your Highness
Time has changed
I have no regrets
I think
A woman who has been hired by the royal family
It is impossible to marry again
Become a monk
Or die
I have no complaints
I'm telling you
It is impossible
I won't let you go
I don't care if you are Yao Ziliao
What kind of Sun Shi is it
I will never let you go again
Yuan Qi
Your Highness
Take the inkstone away
Yes
Don't put it on
I won't eat
You keep saying you can't
Don't complain
It's all excuses
How
You become so timid now
Don't even dare to say a word of truth
Yes
What
It's all lies
I abhor Your Highness, I abhor the Imperial Palace
Hate what brings me bad luck
All people
Your Highness
I hate you
If your highness doesn't decapitate his head
The handmaiden stepped down
Inkstone
I'm sorry
I scared you
Eat more
I'm really angry
All right, all right
What a coincidence, Miss Yao
We meet again
It is still in filial piety
Your Majesty is vegetarian
You beast will be punished, too
This is the prince's inkstone
How can adults punish at will
The emperors are keeping filial piety
How can the prince be an exception
Give it to me
Lord You
Birds fly in the sky and fish swim in the shallow bottom
These are common sense in the world
Why don't you go to Shanglin Garden
Forcing tigers and leopards to eat fast
Help Zhuang Fei achieve her wish
And borrow the hand of the crown prince
Tide over the difficulties smoothly
That's a good way
Just deliberate
Seek the heart of the East Palace
But at the time of a great victory,
Do not hesitate to admit everything
Self-destruct the Great Wall
Do you know that you're doing this
Equal to the prince
Pushed back to Hu's side
Your Excellency has to monitor the East Palace
Who gave the courage
Emperor
I'm not spying
I want a promotion
It is natural to please the prince
How can you do it without knowing him
It turns out that adults' secrets
More than me
So two people full of secrets
Can you cooperate
My Lord is joking
The work of Royal Guards
I can't do it
Your enemies are difficult to deal with
I'm afraid you haven't gained a firm foothold yet
He lost his life first
Think it over
I'm waiting for your answer
Laugh when you want to cry
It's really stupid