Father
Out
Dad
What are you laughing at
Grandpa Huang doesn't have to waste time
You asked Lord Xia to accompany me to visit the countryside
Understand the sufferings of the people
Lord Xia always forced me to eat with millet
I have a grudge in my heart for a long time
So I sent someone to visit secretly
Trying to find evidence of his guilt
But the people I sent came back and told me
There are only cloth and earthen wares in Lord Xia's house
Nothing else
In fact, it is only a trivial matter for Xia Yuanji to kill or
That
What is a big deal
Grandpa Emperor
You have been ill twice
Long live your grandchildren
Your grandson will go for you on this northern expedition
Good or not
Life is 100 years old
There are many things in the world
But they are all gone
There is no smell
Yan Hui-san
Fame has been passed down for generations
I want to create meritorious service for all ages
Why a centenarian
But you can't go
Grandpa Emperor
I can rest assured that the North Expedition
Because you stayed in Beijing
I can't risk Daming's future
Arutai
Invade every year
People are suffering
I often think about it
The cone center is piercing
They scolded me for being overjoyed
By him
Scold me for being militaristic
Also by him
I
Even if there is a eternal stigma behind him,
Never allow an inch of Daming land to be trampled on
Not to mention the displacement of Daming people
Children
Your father has read a lot of books of sages
Be fooled by a bunch of book beetles
Since you think
That old thing in the household department is still useful
I'll leave it to you
Grandpa Emperor
You have been on the throne for more than 20 years
All nations come to Korea
Try to ask the past dynasties
With the respect of the son of heaven
Personal expedition to the desert
How many people are there
Your mind and vision
Is it known to the finches under the porch
There are few eagles in the world
How many short-sighted finches are there
Wear thousands of clothes
Is not to wear flattery
What other nice words are there
You
Have you finished what I asked you to do
Don't do it yet
Go ahead
Zhan Ji
When Grandpa Huang wins, he will return to the DPRK
We went hunting together
Yes
Retirement of grandchildren
April of the 22nd year of Yongle
Zhu Di led hundreds of thousands of troops
The fifth personal expedition to Mobei
Order the Crown Prince to supervise the country
June
Daming Army Arrives at Dalan Namur River
Arutai fled when he heard the wind
The Ming army searched the valley for 300 miles and got nothing
The army is short of food and grass
Zhu Di ordered the squad
July
Holy driving to Yumuchuan
Zhu Zhanji returned to Beijing by secret order to raise grain and grass
Soon
A piece of news that can shake the world
Follow
Yao palm meal
Don't you have anything to say to me
Handmaiden fear
You don't have the slightest look of fear on your face
I return to Beijing in March
I met Grandpa Huang and left in a hurry
I returned to Beijing in May and stayed for three days
I deliberately didn't summon you
I just wanted to see if you'd come to me
I haven't seen you for so long
There is nothing to say
Your Highness
This braised rabbit meat
It was specially cooked for your highness by the Shang Food Bureau
Hu Shangshi made it by himself
I can't believe you put me
The rabbit I brought back to you all the way
Be cooked
Your Highness, this
I'll write to you
You didn't reply to me until a month late
Let someone bring you a gift
How dare you make it braised in soy sauce
With a dedicated female official like you
It's really moving
What are you laughing at
Your Highness
This is the other one
The one my highness gave me has long since run away
How can you stay until now
I haven't been back to Beijing for so long
You don't miss me at all
Your Highness
I
Say
Your Highness
Stay in Shangshi Bureau
Don't go anywhere
Your Highness, Father
You left too suddenly
My son is heartbroken
Your Highness, don't do this
Great grief hurts my body
You should take good care of yourself
Your Highness
Father
Where's the emperor and grandson
Back to the words of the Crown Princess
Yang Rong and Hai Shou's Secret Report to Beijing
As soon as Emperor Taisun learned the news,
I reported it to His Royal Highness the Prince
I immediately left Beijing to welcome the funeral
Once the ruling and opposition parties hear about it,
Everyone will be afraid
Send my orders
Blocking messages
Waiting for the emperor's grandson to return to Beijing in Fengzi Palace
Go to mourning again
Yes
Emperor
August of the 22nd year of Yongle
The Crown Prince sent Taisun Yingzi Palace to Kaiping
Military mourning
Be careful
Why don't you come down first? Come down
Hurry up
Grandpa Emperor
Clearly agreed to return from the expedition
You, my grandparents and grandchildren will go hunting in Nanhaizi
Now the old bow is still there
But where did your old man go
You have made a promise in your life
Never break a promise to others
But why only this time
And you lied to me
Why
Your Majesty's Register
Your Majesty
What
Taizu collapsed and died
Forty concubines in the harem
All body martyrdom and burial
According to the ancestral system set by Taizu
All the concubines in the harem
All must be buried underground
How many people
Sixteen people
All must be buried
Your Majesty
Wait a minute
Please tell the empress
Families of concubines who are buried
Give preferential treatment according to the old rules
Father and brother hereditary Royal Guards
Princess Zhuang has served the first emperor for a long time
It's better to send her on the road
Go ahead
Yes
You can't go in there
The queen has a life
Be especially kind to Empress Zhuang Fei
Besides
The concubines must eat enough before going on the road
Why bother Princess Zhuang, you two
Empress Zhuang Fei
This is the walnut cheese you mentioned many times before
You try it
Is it the same taste as before
Not the same
Walnut cheese made with my mother
Help me
I beg you to help me again
Empress Zhuang Fei
You get up quickly
You have touched us many times before and remembered it in our hearts
But we are just small palace maidservants of the Food Bureau
Martyrdom is an ancestral system
How can we help
Deadline for human burial
It was after sunset today
You help me get out of the palace
Help me out of the palace
Empress Zhuang Fei
You
The Queen won't see us
I can't plead with her
I'm not I'm not running away
I just want to meet my mother
She has no son
No one to rely on
I don't ask for anything else
I just need to see her once
Even if it is said that
Say the last farewell words
I'll just say goodbye and come back
I'm begging you to help me
Please, please
I'll just say one word and I'll be back
I
I just want to see my mother one last time
Even with such a little request,
Can't satisfy me
You want to leave the palace
Empress Zhuang Fei
There are only three people now
If you don't come back before sunset
The three of us will lose our lives
You have a way to get me out of the palace
That's great
I swear
I will definitely come back
I swear I'll be back
Well, before sunset
Yao Ziliao
Know I'm going to die
Use this kind of thing to perfunctory me
Fuck off
Get out of here, all of them
Get out of here
Fuck off
Empress
Everybody out
What are you doing, Empress
Empress calms one's anger
Handmaiden will redo it and send it
It's Thursday today
There was supposed to be an inner city outside Xuanwu Gate
You can go out with a waist tag
But there has been a strike during the funeral
Entry and exit
Most of them are people who go to various prisons and bureaus to do business
Go all the way through the long street
Encounter patrol guards
Show them the waist tag
Just say
The number of sauces sent by the wine and vinegar noodle bureau is wrong
Hu Shangshi sent you to ask
Next
Waist tag
What are you doing
It's in line
It's clear that I came first
What's wrong with me standing in front
You are unreasonable.
Do you know what this place is
Wanton noise
Get out of here
Take away
Let's go
Go
It wasn't her first
Out of Xuanwu Gate
The really sad one is at Bei'an Gate
How kind of a girl you are
A dying man
I really redone it and sent it
Is the dying man
Why bother with her
Be full
It's better to hit the road later
Go inside
Why
Yeah
It used to be profitable for me to help her
But now she is going to be buried soon
Is a useless person
Why are you
To take such a big risk to help her
What are you looking at me for
Am I wrong
Clearly follow the steps said by Empress Zhuang Fei
To make walnut cheese
Why does it taste different
People are going to die
What to eat is different
Good
Even if you say so
She went out of Xuanwu Gate smoothly
But how can she get out of Bei'an Gate
I heard that the eighteen red shops there
Hundreds of guards
You can't escape with your wings
Zi Jin
We're going to get people back now
You can also atone for your merits
How is it
Zi Jin
Is it these walnuts that are the problem
Yao Ziliao
And only you would believe her
If it were me,
Have a chance to escape
Why don't I run away at once
The empress will come back
She never broke her promise
In the face of the threat of death
Anyone will become selfish and cowardly
There is no exception
Clearly you don't have to come in to deliver food
Then why did you come
Not afraid of death
You will be afraid by yourself
Purple Azolla
Will come back
I knew it
Who will take the initiative to come back and die
Liar
Yao Ziliao
You fool
Go
Go quickly
Hurry up
There is also Zhuang Fei, the master of Yongning Palace
Go quickly
Miss Yao
Palm lamp
They'll be here soon
Quickly
It's right ahead
Don't delay the time.
Yes
You go
You go now
Purple Azolla
You don't have to worry about implicating other people in Yongning Palace
I stay
Why do you say that
I should have been a dead man
I will pay you my life this time
You and I will not owe each other in the future
What does this mean
The night our whole family died
I was the only one who escaped from life
You think
The man who opened the cricket can in those days
Is it really my brother
People who know you are kind now
What kind of monster is it?
You go quickly
I'm not leaving
You go
Purple Azolla
Open the door
Yes
Why is it plugged in
Knock
Yes
Open the door. Open the door
Open the door quickly
Open the door
Crash open
Yes
I will serve your majesty
Dress up yourself
Who allowed you to be so presumptuous
No rules
Empress Zhuang Fei
Please
I thought Princess Zhuang was gone forever
But
How on earth did she get out of Bei'an Gate
Zi Jin
What's the matter
Don't you like hemp fiber cake best
So delicious hemp fiber cake
Eat it at ordinary times
I can't help swallowing the hemp fiber cake with my tongue
I don't know why
It doesn't taste good at all now
This is when I made walnut cheese for Zhuang Fei
The rest of the ingredients
What's the matter
Where do these come from
Liaoxian Mianwalnut and Lingbao red jujube
They are all excellent tributes
Here it is
This is the ingredients sent by the pharmacy department to make medicated diet
Although the nuts are big,
But it is far less sweet and crisp than cotton walnuts
It's still a little astringent
What is this for
It's not too late to make walnut cheese now
It's for Princess Zhuang
The number of ingredients sent recently has become more perfunctory
Fragrant rice and dried fruit antlers
There are problems with the number of seafood in the East China Sea
Wang Sishan resolutely refused to accept it
If it weren't for the handmaiden perfunctory
I am afraid I have already asked Guanglu Temple
I see
I'm afraid Wang Sishan is opinionated
In case she knows
I'll take care of it
Yes
Where did Zi Jin go today
You check it out
I'll go by myself
Empress
Zi Jin
Don't be rude
Empress Zhuang Fei
The handmaiden made you walnut cheese
You try it
Wang Si's meal
I just want to do my last thing
Zi Jin
Purple Azolla
Quickly
Right
When I was a child in Jiangnan
This is the taste of walnut cheese made by my mother
Empress
No matter how excellent the ingredients are,
The most beautiful taste in the world
It is the memory of my hometown
I'm sorry
I lied to you
I walked out of the Forbidden City
I didn't want to come back
But the bearers scared away
I can only carry my mother behind my back
Knocking on the door from house to house
Can cling to our relatives in the past
No one dares to resist the decree
But my feet
It's not far away
Even if I give birth to wings,
I can't fly out of here
Empress should hit the road
My last moments in this world
It's warm
Empress
The Emperor arrives
Your Majesty is here
Did Your Majesty come specially to see him off
I am willing to die today
I implore Your Majesty to remember your promise
Take care of my mother for me
Don't let her be displaced
No branches to follow
Your Majesty
Ancestral system can not be violated
Zi Jin
Mother
I went
Empress
Empress, are you all right
Down
Now
Do you understand everything
Presumptuous
Concubines can only be buried without children
After the courtiers, they were saved from death according to the law
What's more
Your Majesty is now in good health
I just
I just can't bear it
I was born for Emperor Taizu in those days
There are also concubines who have given birth to children
Why don't you think about it
Who will decide your destiny in the end
You
Empress
Your hands are shaking all the time
Send you back to the palace, handmaiden
Purple Azolla
Yin Ziping
Zi Jin
Quick, quick, quick
You come back
What are you doing
Don't you know how to get out of Bei'an Gate
Nowadays, the whole country holds mourning and crying sacrifices
We still have a chance
Go, go, go
You come here
You tell me
Why did you leave
Sacrificial burial
Only concubines were buried
We are the palace maidservants of the Shang Food Bureau
Then you promise me
Don't care about the emperor and grandson anymore
Let's not be concubines anymore
Be a good female official
Good or not
Purple Azolla
Ronghua Fugui Fresh Clothes and Gourmet Food
No matter how precious everything is,
They are insignificant in front of life
Look at today's situation
I'm afraid you will follow in the footsteps of Zhuang Fei
Rest assured
I won't
Become a concubine
If there are no children
Possible martyrdom
Become a female official
Row difference and step wrong
Worry about one's life
Walk out of the palace gate today
There is no way to lead
The whole city is under martial law
How to get out of Beijing
Unaccompanied woman
How to make a living
Even if you set up a career,
How to preserve
Zi Jin
What can we do
Is it the king's land under the whole world
Don't Princess Zhuang want to escape
She wants to
But where did you escape in the end
Even if you really escaped,
That is also Zhulianjiu clan
Flee
You can never escape
Since you can't escape,
Then stay
Purple Azolla
It's the wrong burial
Is the world wrong
Mistakes must be corrected
But it's an ancestral system
Even today's prince can't openly
I'm not afraid
Purple Azolla
Don't be afraid, either
Whenever you remember four words
Man-made things
You think about it
Whether you are a female official,
Or be a concubine
Even the most ordinary people
Who has no dilemma
There will always be a way out
Wherever you go
How far do you go
As long as someone is with you
Not alone
Have this belief
It can support me for a long time
End
Maybe it's the way out
Hu Si Shan
This is the medicated diet spectrum I wrote
Take time to look at it for me
She gave Princess Zhuang a jade pendant
Just walked out of Bei'an Gate safely
What kind of jade pendant