Pickled preserved vegetables
Yes
Pickled radish relieves summer heat and stimulates appetite
Wrapped in golden eggs
With wild millet onions
It will be more sweet and fragrant
Rice crust
Yes
Use pine as firewood
Absorb rice fragrance and woody fragrance
Plus crispy crispy crispy rice crust
Salty soaked rice is exceptionally sweet
It's a pity that such an ordinary firewood meal
The people in Beijing can't share it
Why
Handmaiden gaffes
I will allow you to speak out
Handmaiden daring
Your Majesty
Tianshou Mountain where Changling is located
And the Western Hills
A place where firewood is forbidden
If the people of Beijing want to get firewood,
Often taken from hundreds of miles away
Ancient mountain forest Chuanze
Share it with the people
Not unique to the royal family
Pass a decree
Juyongguan goes east
Connect with Tianshou Mountain
All mountain forests are forbidden to firewood
So as not to disturb ancestors and ancestors
All other mountain forests will be banned
Yes
Get up
Thank Your Majesty
No wonder Guo Guifei often praises you
Say you are sympathetic to the hardships of people's livelihood
Stay with me in the future
Remind more
Handmaiden fear
Don't be too modest
Is there anything else to say
Your Majesty is sympathetic to the hardships of the people
It is a blessing to all people
Some people deceive the superior and deceive the inferior
Contrary to Your Majesty's original intention
Handmaiden didn't dare to disturb rashly
It's just, Your Majesty, that you asked
Handmaiden can't help but answer
Speak
Guang Luqing Jing Quan wants to follow the old rules
Picking jade-faced raccoons in Nanjing
Take it all away
Yes
Why do you suddenly come to audit the accounts
Will the Food Bureau be implicated
What's going on
Guang Luqing followed the old example
Picking jade-faced raccoons in Nanjing
This is to please your majesty
Who knows, Your Majesty
It's just a matter of urgency
How can it be because of the desire of the appetite
Disturb the people
It's just now. The officials in Jing Quan don't say it
Also ordered a strict investigation
Who knows, check it out
Unexpectedly, it was found that Jing Quan stole the legal objects of the inner government
Enrich one's own pockets
There is something wrong with purchasing
Naturally, there is someone to help the food bureau
I also want to transfer you to the company
This is my own trouble
Here comes the door
Don't go to work yet
Yes
A Wai
Master
Moon flower
Master can teach you
I've already taught you
Remember
Be sure to practice more frequently in the future
Don't live up to Master's expectations for you
Master
Master, where are you going
Meng Shang Shi
Gong Zhengsi found out the account books of Shangshi Bureau
I already know about it
Do you know that
Just now, Wang Si was in Gongzhengsi
Claim all the charges
Unexpectedly, people like Hu's
I can't believe someone would be so loyal to her
Master has never only known how to cook food
Regardless of entering or leaving the account book
Guang Luqing's mistakes must have nothing to do with her
I believe her innocence
Then you should find out
The culprit behind it
I know you reported it to your majesty
You must tie the bell to solve the bell
Only you can help Wang Si's meal
In order to sit firmly and still eat, Hu's family
Help Jing Quan forge account books and embezzle silver
Why should I help such a person
I beg you
Forgive her
Leave her alone
You begged me
Yes
I beg you
Moon flower
When I went to see the Crown Princess,
Make a claim
Take all the blame for you
This is because
Protect one's children
It is the nature of being a mother
But
From then on
It's all on your own
Master, master
May I have a word with her
Still rushing out of the palace
Don't miss the hour
Master
Why do you want to help others
I knew her when I entered the palace at the age of seventeen
At that time
I'm sickly and frail
Often beaten and hungry
Only she tried her best to protect me
I know that she is not a good kind
But I want to protect her
Because
She is my only friend in this palace
They said you were dismissed from your official position and repatriated to your original place
Then will I never see you again
Just returning home
It has been tolerated by the emperor
Later
Master is not with you
You should take good care of yourself
Do you understand me
It's time to start
Don't cry
Master takes the blame for you
And you dare not show up
When it's really heartless
If I show up
Is to give people a handle
Everything she gave
It's all in vain
Zi Jin
Look
How is it
This is ugly
This
I've been putting it on for a long time
Yin Ziping
You can't do your best
Why don't you do it
No
You always do this
If you can't, just come over and over again
Seeking perfection is also a disease
You
Start over
Swing the plate like painting
Know how to leave blank
Not the fuller the better
Come again
Purple Azolla
Above
Learning art is like sailing against the current
If you don't advance, you will retreat
What are you doing standing there
Haven't practiced yet
Yes
Meng Shang Shi
The rest can be sent to the Department of Medicine to make Chrysanthemum Powder
Don't waste
Yes
I'm not good at medicated diet
The road ahead depends on yourself
It's not a big deal
What about the Food Bureau
Every year, you have to enter thirty palace maidservants
There are only one or two things that can really master the temperature
Master shows you the way
How far can this road go
Depend on one's own ability
I understand Meng Shangshi
Don't waste your time
How to set the plate and match the color in cooking
This is all exquisite
Meals can't be empty and tasty
Let people have the desire to taste
Even though the color, flavor and taste are delicious,
You have to have character
It must be known that the product of poetry lies in conception
The product of painting lies in spirituality
The taste of delicacy lies in style
When others taste dishes
Don't ask who the kitchen is
You are a teacher
This is the beginning
Then what is the highest realm
It's not your turn to ask
Continue
Disciples visit Master
Now it's up to you
Organize the famous scores of past dynasties
You should learn to learn from the past and the present
Mastery through a comprehensive study
So can't stand the blow
What other climate can it become
Hu Shang Shi
Before she left
The most worrying thing is you
I heard that
You are already restoring Tang's burning tail food list
There is no one to teach now
Is it stagnant
Ambition is good
But strength must match ambition
Otherwise, it will become wishful thinking
There's still a long way to go
Yes
Empress
Empress gets dizzy in the morning
Palpitation and abdominal pain
What is the reason for this
How long has it been
Previously, the palace was busy
There is another great funeral behind it
Empress doesn't want to disturb others
This is just hard to hold
The illness has been more than three months
There was blood again last night
One more thing
Monthly events
It's a slippery vein
Pan Siyao
What are you talking about
Have you made a clear diagnosis
The pulse in the ruler is endless
It's just that the empress is weak and her pulse is not obvious
It is accompanied by palpitation and spontaneous sweating
Congratulations to the Empress
Empress Hershey
Empress rest assured
Emperor Taizu has long said clearly
There are endless changes in human feelings
And courtesy is suitable for change
If parents are newly bereaved,
Wailing at dusk
Another three years of silence
Do not have children in the ban, etc.
In fact, the ancients were unkind
It's been three months since the empress was pregnant
It is not a case of in-service pregnancy
If it is a happy pulse, it is correct
Just use Hegan Yangrong Decoction to warm the meridians and stop bleeding
It will heal in less than half a month
It's obviously a disease
Can diagnose the happy pulse
Tai Hospital
What kind of mediocrity have you raised
Empress
Pan Siyao
Empress Empress's pulse seems to be difficult
How can you assert in one bite
Is the slippery pulse
You have only been promoted to medicine department for half a year
My diagnosis
When will it be your turn to decide
Pan Siyao's remarks are bad
What disease is it? What disease is it
This is related to the qualification of being promoted to the department of medicine
What's the point
Dai Yuan's judgment said it was a happy pulse
What do you have to argue about
Now Lord Hu says so
You don't have a problem with it, do you
The Department of Pharmacy is under the Food and Drug Administration
I'm just a six-product female official
Dare not openly disobey adults
But as a female doctor,
There is the heart of a healer
It has not been diagnosed as a happy pulse
Even if the holy man comes in person
You can't make me change my mouth
You
Please forgive Hu Shangshi
Just
Guo Guifei didn't ask the emperor
Send a woman doctor
Go to recuperate for his grandmother Yan's health
I think Jiang Siyao is just right
Yes
Empress's meal in the future
Please bother Hu Shang to eat a lot
Hu Shang Shi
Why is Jiang Siyao so unruly
Western Han Dynasty
Women's national medicine, the righteousness of hanging pots to help the world, goes down in history
Ever since her
It has become a common practice for the Imperial Medical Department to set up female doctors
Nowadays, the female doctor in the medicine department
Not a famous doctor who should be recommended everywhere
Is born in Xinglin family
Everyone has unique skills
Far from being comparable to ordinary doctors and women
But
No matter how skilled a doctor is,
You may not be able to see the things in this palace clearly
Salty or not
Just
Yao Ziliao
Empress meets happiness
Tai Hospital opened Hegan Yangrong Decoction
Warm up for the empress
Need to be conditioned slowly with medicated diet
From today
It's up to you to help Su Yuehua
Complete the meal of Kunning Palace together
Hu Shang Shi
Why don't you let me help Yuehua
You have been in the Shang Food Bureau for so long
Do you remember the first volume of the meal
Can you distinguish Radix Angelicae Pubescentis and Radix
Can Perilla seed and Cuscuta chinensis be distinguished clearly
With you
I also want to intervene in the Queen's meal
If you think you have a long life,
Hang him with a rope
Don't bring trouble to the food bureau
Don't look at me like that
We are in the Shang Food Bureau
Everything takes cooking as the first priority
Yes
Today, the sun is really coming out in the west
First, Hu Shangshi turned his face ruthlessly
I have to transfer you to the company
Stopped by Meng Shangshi
She turned to introduce Su Yuehua to Kunning Palace
It is suppressing you in every possible way
Now the Empress is happy
It's such a great good thing
How can you share the credit
Have you finished the schoolwork assigned by Meng Shangshi
The landscape picture is in the clouds
I can't understand it at all
You go and teach me
Walk, walk
This is the prescription prescribed by Dai Yuan for Empress
Tai Hospital will also send medicated diet every day
You cook according to the recipe
You have to check it yourself
There must be no conflicting things in the medicated diet
You can rest assured
I will definitely do my best
No
Yao Ziliao is responsible for everything
You don't have to get involved
Empress Empress
Carassius auratus and ginger kernel soup and lotus seed porridge
They are all diet orders issued by Tai Hospital
It's all about having a baby and calming down
Shut up
Daughter-in-law greets her mother
Don't go out and kneel yet
Mother Queen
I heard that there is a doctor named Sheng in Tai Hospital
Cured the arthralgia syndrome of the first emperor for many years
The medical skill is very good
Why don't you ask him to show you
There are such doctors in Tai Hospital
Why didn't you come in earlier
Back to the empress's words
Dr. Sheng is proficient in arthralgia syndrome
Once upon a time, it was specially used to treat the first emperor
It has never been treated as soon as possible for the harem maid
Not as good as
Go to ask your majesty first and then ask Dr. Sheng too
Go ahead
It's really Yu Li Ren porridge
That's right
Sheng Taiyi put the original lotus seed glutinous rice porridge
Changed to Yu Liren porridge
All medicated diets for preventing miscarriage have also been replaced
What's the matter
Yu Liren can enter the spleen and lower qi
It is an agent for breaking water and blood
If the empress is really happy,
How can you prescribe a medicine to break blood and moisten dryness
Are you saying
Plum kernel is a taboo medicinal material for pregnant women
And
I saw the illness of the empress that day
And the air
It's really not like being happy
That is, Dr. Sheng found out the real cause
Dare to prescribe blood-breaking medicine
The Food Bureau doesn't care about the prescription
Don't think much about it
Just do it
Moon flower
Meng Shang Shi
Yin Ziping
Will you work for me in the future
Willing to work for adults
A little thing
Don't be nervous
Why don't you run to Yongning Palace for me
The present theme of Yongning Palace is
Guo Guifei
Yes
Your Majesty is determined to return it
Lord Yang tried his best to dissuade him
I'm afraid it won't help
Your Highness
Is your hand okay
Strange ah
How is the return of the capital going
Your Majesty
This matter is contrary to the original intention of the first emperor
I am afraid that the ministers in the DPRK will have many criticisms
Nanjing is the emperor of Ming Taizu
A set capital
In those days, Huangkao insisted on moving the capital
The three main halls were hit by skyfire
This is a warning from heaven and ancestors
So
Also all
It is I who want to restore the ancestral system
Your Majesty, Your Highness the Prince has arrived
Father
You wait
Shi Qi
Minister in
You advise Wei Zhe for me again
Household Department
May be unwilling to give up silver
I can promise
Only the main temple will be repaired
Never waste the silver of the national treasury
Again
After all,
The transfer of grain to the north can also save a lot of expenses
Father
I told you to wait
Shi Qi
What was I going to say just now
Caoliang transfer to the north
Grain
Two million stone grain
People are overwhelmed
Again
Once the northern prisoners invaded Datong,
Isn't the capital dangerous
So say
Also all
It is a big game that I have thought carefully
Emperor
After the Caohe River was dredged,
Solved the transportation of grain
Prosperous state capitals on both sides of the strait
Daming's porcelain and silk
Tea wood
North-South exchanges are unimpeded
As for the Northern Lu
The Son of Heaven hunts himself
It is they who guard against it
Father can't just look at the gains and losses of one place at a time
Have to plan for future generations
What exactly are you going to say today
My son came today to tell my father
I went out of the palace twice
It is to find the ink that Grandpa Huang wants
Not to win over courtiers from all over the world
Oppose the father's move to the capital
Please don't send Royal Guards again
Follow my son
You guard against your son like this
My son is not used to it
Not happy either
I asked the Royal Guards to follow you
Not looking at you
Is to protect you
Zhu Zhanji
How dare you talk to your father like that now
Good advice is good for action
Father doesn't like to hear it
My son is helpless
If you see Royal Guards again next time,
But I won't take care of my father's face
Please think twice before you leap
My son retires
Zhu Zhanji
How dare you, you boy, be presumptuous with me like this
How dare you throw your face at me
I am today I am
I
Shi Qi
The minister is in
What I said just now
Without missing a word
Tell Vizhe
Also all
I
It must be returned
Micro-minister leads the decree
Micro-minister retires
Come out
Your Majesty
My male and female servants see you work so hard
Specially brought you ginseng soup
It's not like I'm shady
Why do you have to tell me to hide
Those ministers chant every day
Say I dote on you too much
What ignores etiquette and rules and laxes
Chanting gives me a headache
Sit down
Your Majesty
Just now, male and female servants and concubines heard it in the back
Others say you are too lenient
But the male and female servants thought
Under the sun
There is no softer heart than yours
A man with wider shoulders
Your Majesty
You will be a good emperor
I hope so
I'm not like the first emperor
What kind of meritorious service do you want to build
I just want to
Less fighting and corvee
Less greedy officials
Let my people
Live a good life in peace
Your Majesty
Tai Hospital reported it
Empress Empress took the medicine prescribed by Dr. Sheng Tai
Suddenly bleeding
Lord You, let me go
Your Majesty Your Majesty
I am wronged
Empress is not a fetal elephant
If this is the way to treat it
In a few days
Empress's life is in danger
Your Majesty Your Majesty
I am wronged, Your Majesty
Your Majesty
Keep treating like this
In a few days
Empress's life is dying soon
Hu Shang Shi
Do you still send the medicated diet
Go back and do it again according to the prescription of abortion
Yes
Mother Queen
Empress and mother
Help me up
Mother Queen
Don't move
Go to the Qing Palace
Slow down
Go and invite the crown prince quickly
Yes
What to do
This situation has been going on for several days
For seven days
Empress Empress refused to take medicated diet to prevent miscarriage
Just eat some porridge every day
There is no improvement in the condition
Empress Empress is pregnant with dragon heir
If what you just said is spread,
Be careful to get hit by the board like that Sheng Tai Yi
Clearly not happy
The whole palace is said to be happy
It is obviously seriously ill
No one in the hospital dares to prescribe a prescription
What kind of world is this
You hurry to bring food to His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
I take turns delivering meals with Fang Dianshan
Nor is it a long-term solution
What exactly is the misunderstanding between you two
No
Send it if you don't have it
Purple Azolla
Go quickly
Go, go, go, go
Purple Azolla
What do you want from Your Highness
I thought your whole life
I don't even want to come to this study again
Responsibilities
Dare not shirk
Hate me so much
Why don't you just put some arsenic in it
Silver needle can be tested
There are always things that can't be tested
I dare not let the whole family accompany me to die
You are so honest
Yao Ziliao
Your Highness
Handmaiden surname Sun
I don't know any Sun Shi
I only know Yao Ziliao
Your Highness
Why don't you pay more attention to the illness of the empress
Miss Yao
The queen is happy
Your Royal Highness can't help either
What you say makes no sense
Handmaiden gaffes
Please forgive your highness
Your Highness
The Queen has always claimed that she is ill and not pregnant
Don't you find it strange
Dai Yuan judged that
Mother is happy at this age
It is inevitable that your temperament will change greatly
Anxiety
I go to say hello twice a day
I didn't even see her
Empress has given birth to four children
How can you not know the symptoms of pregnancy and childbirth
She claims all day that she has abdominal pain
Imperial doctors are helpless
What if Dr. Sheng is right
Isn't she happy
Dai Yuan was sentenced to rotate daily with four doctors
You think a person is wrong
Are they all wrong
It is the medicine master who takes the pulse
It was Dai Yuan's judgment that cut off the diagnosis
Who dares to overturn his conclusion
What's more
The emperor decided that the empress was pregnant
Who dares to be openly disappointed
Known diagnostic errors
The consequences are unimaginable
How dare you go along with Sheng Yin
Your Highness
Dr. Sheng received thirty sticks
I would rather die than change my mind
Does he really want his life
It's not
Because in the heart of Dr. Sheng Taiyi,
Medical ethics
And the patient's life
Far better than personal life and death honor and disgrace
The same
Although I am a female officer of the Shang Food Bureau,
But the medicated diet is cooked by myself
Into the patient's mouth
I have to take responsibility
Unknown etiology
And blindly serve food
This is not a kitchen at all
It's an accomplice to murder
You say so
Is that my father did something wrong
How dare you
Humble status of handmaiden
How can you have the courage to doubt it
It's just your highness asking questions
Handmaiden dare not answer
Yao palm meal
Let her speak
Your Highness
In the Emperor's mind
Couples who have been married for more than 20 years
Far less than the dragon heir out of nothing
Place in a different place
How is the Empress Empress feeling now
Your Highness as the Son of Man
Can't you feel the same way
Your Highness
Where are you going so late
Father-in-law Yuan
Screen drawing girl
The prince can now be in the study
You see
It's so unfortunate
Prince has just left the palace
What can I do about this
What's the matter
Rest assured
Sheng Yin's
I have plans
Mother Queen
Be careful
Meet the Empress
Are you here
Quickly report
I want to see the emperor
Yes
Late at night
Come to the pharmacy to buy medicine
No
It's drug theft
Stealing drugs that are not available in the medical bureau
Chen Wu
Yes
Come out
How
Do you want me to invite you in person
A humble position. See Synonyms at Your Highness
Your Highness
Open the door
Let me see what you can do
Yes
There are only two guys in the store
I'm already asleep
Your Highness, please