I need a batch of clams from Liaodong
Specializing in treating women's disharmony of qi and blood
You find out
Arrive in Beijing in August and September
Yes
Your Highness
This medicinal material for treating disharmony between qi and blood
It was Dr. Sheng who told you
How do they know how to distinguish medicinal materials
What did I bring you here for
Don't help yet
Yes
If it arrives in Beijing in September,
Maybe it's sun-dried
Sun-drying
This
This is locked
It should be this thing
Help people over
Yes
Thank you, Your Highness
Royal Guards are really Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon
Stay another half an hour before leaving
Your Royal Highness Your Royal Highness
The humble position is wrong
I followed you to protect your highness
Take away
Your Highness
Your Highness, come back
No
Is this a save or not
What are you two looking at
Come and help me
Wait for half an hour
Sure
Queen
Male and female servants. See Synonyms at Emperor
Deeper exposure
In poor health
Why do you have to see me
Ask Your Majesty's permission
Zhunsheng Taiyi
Continue to diagnose male and female servants and concubines
He gave the Queen a prescription before
Almost lead to human life
Fortunately, Long Si is safe
I'll keep him alive
It's already mercy
How could the Queen believe him
Male and female servants believe in Sheng Taiyi
Dr. Sheng did not deceive your majesty either
Is it pregnancy or illness
Don't male and female servants understand themselves
Ask Your Majesty's permission
Dr. Sheng continued to treat me
Empress Empress
Dai Yuan sentenced him to be proficient in women's prescription
How can a mere happy pulse be consulted wrong
If you trust that quack
In case you hurt Long Si
Then who can afford to eat sin
There is no Long Si, Your Majesty
This matter is of great importance
Nature should not be neglected
Empress Empress
You go back to peace of mind first
How about Xuan Tai Yi asking for peace pulse for you again
Peace
Within three days
I will give up my breath here
Where is peace
Queen
Get up
It is a great good thing to meet happiness
How can you be full of nonsense
Father
The Empress is restless
Will say ominous words
I also ask my father to forgive me
Help your mother back to the palace
Your Majesty
I married into the royal family at the age of fifteen
Serve Your Majesty for more than 20 years
Give birth to three sons and one daughter
I don't ask for anything else
Just ask your majesty
Look at me
In order to serve you, I dedicated my life to serve you
Allow me to be willful once
Just for once
I want to see Dr. Sheng
I want to live
Ask Your Majesty for mercy
I ordered Tai Hospital to consult for you
Isn't it saving your life
Every woman in the world must have children
I've never seen you so crazy
Queen
You had a baby
Can you tolerate a quack misdiagnosis
Let's lose one
A hard-won child
All consequences
I am willing to bear it with all my strength
Ask your majesty for help
Empress is the master of the six palaces
Mother instrument world
How can you say such a bizarre thing
Give birth to children for the royal family
It is the primary responsibility of the harem concubines
If I change my body,
My body is willing to give my life to save the dragon tire
How can an empress because
Can't stand some pain, then
Your Majesty
Cold moonlit night
You can no longer tolerate the Empress
Such a gaffe
If you really hurt Long Si,
Then what should I do
Help the Queen to return to Kunning Palace
Re-pass the decree
Summon all doctors to consult
Your Majesty
Ask Your Majesty for mercy
I'm in pain
Ask Your Majesty to help me
Your Majesty
Go ahead
This hour
Go quickly
Yes
Queen
Come
Male and female servants and concubines gaffe today
Ask Your Majesty for forgiveness
Male and female servants and concubines retire
Before the Imperial Examinee
Always praise the queen for being deferential and wise
I also take her as my wife everywhere
How did the Queen become today
Like another person
So
Be so arbitrary
Irresponsible
Your Majesty
Wu Cairen
The empress has no guests today
Please go back
I'm not going in there to bother
I'll be right here
When the Empress gets better,
I'll go in and say hello again
Come on in with me
You go down first
Your Highness
What's in that sack
It still moves
Go back
Go back now
I'm not a doctor
How much it gets in the way here
Then you just let Mei Nvguan
No matter how persuaded, he refused to leave
Don't let your highness see it with his own eyes
I serve here
How can I get there
So that the Crown Princess can specialize in beauty
So now is the critical moment
You can't leave even more
In this deep palace
Pampering is indispensable, but it is also indispensable
No more, no less than me is enough
Let's go
Mother
Your Highness
Zhan Yong Zhan Zhao and Jiaxing
Crying to see you
They're worried about you
But I've had them sent back first
When you feel better,
Let them come and greet you again
Good
Mother
This time I brought Sheng Yin
Take your pulse personally
His Royal Highness the Prince
Your Majesty has made a decree
Sheng Yin is not allowed to enter the palace again
Your Highness
It's against the rules
It's the rules that matter
Or is mother's life important
Sheng Yin
Yes
I
How
Your Highness
Fortunately, you made a quick decision
If in another three days
Hua Tuo can't be cured again
Sheng Tai Yi
The empress's illness is really so serious
The empress's pulse is heavy and tight
Lackluster
Neither slippery pulse nor pregnancy
But the meridians are blocked
Poor blood gas
Dangyi Taoren Chengqi Decoction
Hedidang Decoction promotes blood circulation and removes blood stasis
However
They have been taking medicine to prevent miscarriage and nourish their spirits
Warming meridians to stop bleeding
The more nature makes up, the more serious the illness is
Amenorrhea for 4 months
And abdominal pain
It's not pregnancy. What is it
As for the slippery pulse, it is flickering
That's the empress who is weak
Happy pulse just doesn't show
Your Highness
Taoren Chengqi Decoction has peach kernel and rhubarb
There are leeches and flies in Didang soup
Both prescriptions are blood stasis-removing drugs
Pregnant women taboo
Sheng Yin
You made a name for yourself
Damage the life of dragon fetus
This is a capital crime
His Royal Highness the Prince
Never listen to what quacks say
He went down with this dose of medicine
Don't say dragon tire
Phoenix body is also at stake
Your Highness
Previous diagnosis of handmaiden
It is indeed a slippery pulse
Please think twice, Your Highness
Everyone talks about gold
Accumulation and destruction of bones
After all, there are too many mediocre people in the world
Your Highness
I don't need to say much
I hope your highness will decide
Your Highness
Imperial doctors can prescribe medicines to patients
But you can't make decisions for patients
Mother
You have told me since you were a child
Be decisive in your life
Hesitation is bad for great things
So my son's way of dealing with people
They are all like mothers
Even if you go the wrong way
Overcome difficulties and thorns
We must also go out of a bloody road
But now it's a matter of life
It is up to the mother to decide for herself
If you think Sheng Yin is right
Your son supports you
Your Highness
In case the emperor blames
My son is watching outside
No one will bother
You can rest assured
My son has always been with you
Please Sheng Yin
Intake medicine
Yes
Your Majesty
You have to make decisions
What's going on
Your Majesty
You must stop the crown prince
He insisted that Sheng Yin heal the empress
I am afraid
I'm afraid this time Long Si really can't keep it
Arrogance
Your Majesty
Qikai empress just took the medicine
Zhu Zhanji
Where is that quack
Your Majesty is here
Dr. Sheng, this is
Back to the Imperial Concubine Empress
I have made a written pledge to fulfill a military order before your highness
If you can't cure the empress,
I am willing to die
Sheng Yin you
You, you made a big mistake
Wearing a court sentence
Do you dare to follow my oath in public
You
If you can't cure the empress within ten days,
I'll take the head on your neck
Your Majesty
Two digits
Can dare
Your Majesty
Imperial doctors rely on medical skills to diagnose diseases
Not ignorance and fearlessness
Threatened with a knife and axe rashly
Imperial doctor is frightened
How to diagnose and treat with peace of mind
Sheng Yin
Don't speak wildly
If you hurt Long Si,
How can I get compensation for taking your head
Zhu Zhanji
Is this one of your tricks
Teach them
Father
Please respect the mother's decision
I don't respect your mother
If I don't respect her,
How can you call a doctor for consultation
Why did you come to visit in the middle of the night
Zhu Zhanji
Do you know that
Maybe because of one of your mistakes
It will ruin your mother's life
And the unborn child
You, you laugh
Smile, smile, smile, smile
Father
When you were the East Palace,
Do not hesitate to offend Grandpa Huang, but also stick to his heart
Brave admonition
As your wife
Mother is always by your side
Love is undiminished
Did she ever ask you about the consequences of doing so
Has she ever had a trace of fear and retreat
She never
What do you do
As long as you want to do it, she won't ask
I resolutely supported it
But if it were you
Why don't you trust her once
If you can't cure the queen
I don't want your head
I'm going to destroy your door
Your Majesty
After the empress took the medicine,
Sure enough, there were a lot of blood stasis
The spirit is also good
Purple Azolla
I'll do it
You worked here all night last night
Only when cooking
My heart is calm
Last night
Empress Empress used blood medicine
Except for the stasis
Afraid of deficiency of qi and blood
Today, it is advisable to use medicated diet for invigorating qi and benefiting blood
I want to prepare in advance
You do the work alone
All the credit was divided by others
With what
The more you practice, the better your skills
Until no one can replace it
Is unique
Losses are blessings
It's not all deceptive
Row
To please the Empress
Is to please the crown prince
Purple Azolla
There is something hidden in my heart all the time
It's about my past
I want to tell you today
Yao Ziliao
Please treat the empress to dinner
This longan medlar pigeon egg soup
Supplementing Qi, enriching blood, nourishing yin and moistening lung
It should be taken first
Are these bergamot petals on it
Back to the empress's words
This meal is called Chicken with Bergamot
There is a peculiar taste in the entrance
Like fermented bean curd
No
Lingering on the tip of the tongue
It smells like wine again
Back to the empress
This recipe contains
Tofu milk and glutinous rice wine
Glutinous rice wine warms the middle and benefits qi
It was specially selected by the handmaiden for you
You have a heart
Empress
You slow down
You are recovering from your illness
Don't eat too much
Crispy skin and juicy inside
It tastes really good
It's a pity
It has been many, many years
I don't smell this smell anymore
Queen Zhang is a native of Yongcheng
I like to use hot soup with fried dumplings for breakfast
You are proficient in famous dishes from all over the world
How can you not even know this thing
It's just some street snacks
How can you offer such crude food
There are more than 20 kinds of ingredients of Chinese herbal medicines in the soup
Adjust according to the changes of the four seasons
The Queen asked about the recipe
You are speechless
In this way
The empress knows that there is another person who makes the meal
What a waste of the opportunity I gave you
Empress
Your phoenix body is recovering
Otherwise, we'll do it after a while
Do you know the origin of this spinning wheel
Handmaiden heard
This was given to you by Queen Renxiao in those days
Yeah
When my mother gave it to me, she said
One husband does not plow
Or suffer from hunger
A woman does not knit
Or suffer from cold
Male ploughing and female weaving
The husband sings along with the woman
It is the best in the world
Yes
Empress
What a pity that the spinning wheel has been smashed
Empress sent it to Shangshi Bureau
When the firewood burns
Yes
Father
Why are you here
I heard that my father's dragon body is not safe
My son came to plead guilty
Father
Take the medicine first
Wei Chen came late
Please pardon the emperor
Guangzong County, Shunde Prefecture has a lot of rain this year
The local report is late
Life and life delayed the disaster relief
I have already made a decree
However, natural disasters
Be sure to open the warehouse for relief first
But in this way
There must be officials who are greedy for ink
Are you going to
Father
If you are worried about local officials
Take advantage of disaster relief to enrich oneself
You can send patrol according to the censor to visit
However, the empire went to check with great fanfare
As far as eyes and ears can see
It's just that others want to see it
At a young age
What do you know
Father
Now the Royal Guards are out of Beijing to get people
Arrests often occur without permission
It is conceivable
How arrogant are you on weekdays
If you order them to visit secretly again,
I'm afraid there will be more illegal things
When Grandpa Huang was here,
They will restrain themselves a little
Now
It's me
Let the Royal Guards act cheaply
Father
Out
Verbal collision between children and ministers
Please take care of the dragon body
If you mother and son hadn't joined hands to anger me
I am in good health
Why don't you go
My son retires
Inverse
I have read the paper you presented
It's fairly pertinent
But those things are worried by ministers of various ministries and hospitals
Don't worry about it
One mutilates Zhongliang
Butchers who kill countless people
I will learn from people who are full of reading to give advice to the emperor
What capital has water transportation to solve households' difficulties
Have nowhere to live
It's simply nonsense
I dare not talk loudly
People only need a few strokes
Talk to guests and friends at Lord Liu's banquet yesterday
Write it down one by one
Your head will be in danger tomorrow
Don't stain my eyes with this pickling thing
This is
Your Majesty
Recurrence of old disease
Dai Yuan ruled that the dragon body must be conditioned according to the prescription
You can't be vegetarian anymore
Help quickly
Move in
Move things in together
Come here
Come
Be careful
You bring it
This is what the Imperial Concubine of Yongning Palace wants
You can't take it
Do you have eyes
Dare to occupy the Queen's master's things
You let go
Give it to me
Don't take mine
What are you doing noisily
Sister Yu Lu
It is clearly the black wolfberry set by Kunning Palace
She insisted that the imperial concubine should use it
I have to take it all away
We made a reservation three days ago
It's just that it doesn't match for a while
There must be a first come, first served
Let go
You all took it
What am I going to tell you
Stop
Jade chowder
It doesn't matter if the little palace maidservants do something wrong and scold them
Who gave you permission to do it
Again
The imperial concubine prepared black wolfberry
It is to cure the emperor's heart disease
Who can go over the emperor
Give me Chinese wolfberry
I
Give it to me
This is decided by the Imperial Concubine
Mine
Sure
This black wolfberry was born in the mountains
Hard to come by
You dare to knock over such precious medicinal materials
Clearly you let go first
Why are you framing me? You knocked it over
You
Look at the canon meal
Parsley can make a big disaster
I
Something heartless
Dare to abuse anything
Everyone misses. Say it well
So loud and noisy
What did it look like when outsiders heard it
Pack up quickly
I have no one behind me
Naturally, I dare not be presumptuous
Which is better than the upper sister
I am rushing to settle vegetables with others
It's about to climb the high branch
You
Be cruel to others
His face has changed
This is a painful foot, isn't it
I let you fall
Xuelu, you take it
Let go
Don't take it
Can't take it
I really can't take it
Don't spoil it
You can't take it
Stop fighting
Recipe canon meal
Don't take it
You
Come here
Stay
Stop
Let you fight
Purple Azolla
Yin Ziping
Don't take it
Stop fighting
Purple Azolla
Stop
Here comes Lord Shang Shi
Don't stop it all yet
Kneel down, kneel down
Kneel for an hour
Meditate on the past
I
Kneel well
Pretend
What about you
What to fight
The emperor's golden words
Reinstated Meng's official position
I can't refute your majesty's wishes either
The Love of Man
Seek profit
If you want to be in charge of the food bureau,
Everyone must be convinced
Otherwise
Even if I do,
It's hard for you to convince the public
Empress
Handmaiden has confidence
On Qualifications
Monteggia is far above you
I want you to compete fairly
Empress Empress
Go down
Your Majesty has just issued a decree
Guo Guifei's brother Guo Ming attacked the Marquis of Wuding
Grandmother Yan surpassed the system and was named the Duchess of Yingguo
Mother Xu was named Mrs. Tai
And
The first emperor nearly served Huang Yan and had an affair with foreign ministers
After Huang Yanyan took over,
All the assets under his name also belong to Wudinghou
Everything is planned before moving
Be too impatient
Can't achieve great things
Yes
Granddaughter Guo Duansushu's grandmother's knee
Self-serving and merciful
Over summer and over autumn
Recent news of grandmother's disharmony in daily life
The special envoy will lead the imperial doctor
Go and say hello
Jade Beijing
You must send this letter
Hand it over to grandmother
And bring me a few words
Kishito Tomoki
So help the top
Courtesy, frugality and modesty
So self-control
Please ask your grandmother to give birth to brothers, sons and nephews in the discipline clan
To protect our Guo family
Long-term peace and wealth
Empress
Now your own brother has attacked the marquis
It can be seen that your majesty treats Guo's family with great favor
Even the Queen's maiden family is far less than that
You should be happy
Why are you still so worried
I'm glad
Someone will be unhappy
If you can't be prepared for danger in times of peace
Disaster
Not far away
Yes
Wait a minute
Here
It is a thousand-year-old wild ginseng and a thousand-year-old Ganoderma lucidum
This is the medicine from Tai Hospital
Old people are getting old
Weak and sick, susceptible to wind and cold
This is specially given by the imperial doctor
You take it with you
You should be careful to observe the maid around the old grandmother
In case there is poor care,
Get rid of it at once
Yes
Be careful on the road
Let's go
Your Highness is back
Why are you here
Didn't your highness love this solitude best before
Just because the strings are broken
What a pity
Now I have found it
Silk strings matching the original piano
Replaced it for your highness
You listen
The voice is as clear and mellow as before
Why don't I play a song for your highness
Relieve your highness's boredom
No need
Someone will sort it out
If your highness is bored,
Can you tell my body
Although I am stupid,
May not be able to solve your highness's worries
But if you speak your heart,
It won't be left untold
Your Highness, stay with the piano
Thank you for your trouble
If nothing else
I'll see you another day
Your Highness
What else is there
A rudimentary study
It is not a place to live for a long time
The mother is afraid that people will lose their care again
Sent me to consult with your highness
Let's go back to live
People come and go in the palace every day
It's very noisy
Compared with here
Lack of elegance
I'll live here
Where is Your Highness
Where should I be, too
Since you won't move away
Then from tomorrow
I often come to keep company
When your highness is busy
I will grind ink and pour tea
If you are free
Talk with you again to relieve boredom
How well
I told you so long ago
You don't have to serve day and night
When the former mother and queen were the Eastern Palace concubines,
Every father's diet and daily life
Will take care of it personally
This is the duty of being a wife
Once upon a time, because your highness was tolerant,
I am more slack
Now it is a serious mend
If I say no, I don't have to
Yuan Qi
Send the Crown Princess back
Yes
Crown Princess
You please
I'll come back tomorrow
You don't have to send it
Serve your highness well
Your Highness
Do you see
How do I feel
Today, this crown princess
It's different from usual
What time is it
Why hasn't the meal been delivered yet
Sent it, sent it
It was already delivered
Miss Yao has put the food box
It's out there
Weren't the Crown Princess here just now
Not even if you send it
You go tell her
I don't like today's meal
Let her do it again
Redo again
Yes