Mother, take some medicine
Go to the palace, mother
Hurry into the palace
Mother
Take back what belongs to you
Do you hear that
Go
You go
You go you go
If you can't do it, you're sorry for me
I'm sorry about your mother
You're sorry for yourself. Do you understand
Even if I die,
I die unsatisfied
Zi Jin
What are you so foolish about
Is this the plum blossom mold you are looking for
The crown prince is too difficult to serve
The plum blossoms haven't blossomed yet
The fragrance of collected plum petals has already dissipated
Isn't this meant to make things difficult
It's camellia
There is a kind of plum fragrance that seems to have nothing
Plum petals picked before
Plum fragrance has long faded
Ingredients or timely things are better
Hu Shanxiang came to the study just now
You won't go through the door
Why
Answer me
Zi Jin
Hu's family is not too big
I can't depose her
Your Highness misunderstood
I want to be a female official
Stay in Shangshi Bureau all your life
In this way
Your Highness need not have the slightest guilt
My life also has support
What are you talking about
I want to be a female official
I want to be a cook
Do you have more than half your heart for me
If I hadn't entered the palace,
Will Your Highness still remember me
Yes
I don't deny it
I don't remember what you looked like when you were ten
I even forgot you as a person
But at the beginning
Taisunfei is a gift forcibly given to me by the Zhang family
The source of all this misfortune
It is the flattery of the Zhang family
Grandpa Huang's stubbornness and suspicion
It's not fair for you to do this to me
Emperor Taisun wants to promote weaving
The officials dug three feet into the ground
How many innocent people have lost their homes
Choose a concubine in adulthood
How many women are locked in the cold palace
Stay away from one's native land and relatives
Everything they've done
It's all to please you
Your hands are clear and white
But on your knitting jar
It's covered with blood
In your eyes
Whether I know it or not, whether I like it or not
Even though no one has asked my opinion,
Just because I am the emperor's grandson
Is the culprit
So
Would you rather stay at the Shang Food Bureau
Than stay with me
If you have half an apology,
A little pity
Please forgive my disobedience
Because
I don't want to be your concubine
I don't want to live for you all my life
I don't want to be a puppet around others.
Please help your highness
Out
Miss Yao
Henceforth
I don't want to see this woman again
Son minister. See Synonyms at mother queen
You're here. Sit down
Yes
Yeah, that's it
Throw it away
Mother Queen
Aren't all these you as your father
Old sewn clothes
Sew carefully one stitch at a time
I don't know how many nights I stayed up
My eyes are boiled red
You can't lose it
He is now the emperor
You don't need these
The clothes made by the imperial grandmother in those days
Grandpa Huang has been wearing it close to his skin
Never reluctant to lose it
I think these clothes are all new
How not to use it
Father does not love
Then do it for your son
Keep your son wearing it every day
If you like it
Let the Crown Princess sew it for you one day
Crown Princess is not good at women's red
Don't say it's a sachet
I'm afraid
You haven't even received a handkerchief, have you
This is your fault
To be fair
Hu is not good at literature and ink
Do not like female red
I can't talk about poetry with you
Sentiment and interest congruence
But she has a kind heart
Be especially considerate of others
She did something wrong in the past
You shouldn't indulge blindly
If we had made it clear earlier,
It won't be alienated here
Mother Queen
Why is it always the son's fault
This folk mother-in-law
Young couples are at odds
Will protect her daughter-in-law
Only in this way can husband and wife be harmonious
Family prosperity
What's more, she is in the deep palace
If I don't protect her again
She was wronged
And to whom can I speak
Zhan Ji
She already knew she was wrong
You give her another chance
Don't be like me and your father
Come
Write me a word
Yes
Light point
Come and see
What is this
What do you mean
Ancient
What does this mean
I have no idea
How can I do this problem
This topic is too strange
Yeah
What exactly does it mean
It turns out that the Empress used Yan style
Meng Shang Shi
This first game is titled Ancient Cuisine
Su Yuehua is proficient in this way again
I'm afraid it will be
How
Are you so afraid of her
Your Excellency
I lay particular stress on simplicity in cooking
Stable pressure can smell a peach
But Su Yuehua was born into a famous chef family
He also followed Wang Sishan to study famous dishes of past dynasties
I played against her
I'm afraid there's no chance of winning
In this way
None of you have the determination to win
Meng Shang Shi
Please let me have a try
You
Yin Ziping
You're just an emissary
I have to compete with Su Dian food
Don't go down yet
I will win the first game for you
Empress Empress's title of the first game
If you lose the first game,
Hu Shang's index finger name made Su Yuehua start
Is to make sure that we have no one to fight
None of you are sure of winning
Do you want Meng Shang to eat a person's self-degrading status
Go and compete with a canon meal
Even if you win
It's also a victory, isn't it
Meng Shang Shi
Recipe canon meal
In the recent period of time,
Ziping worked hard day and night
You see
This peony flower carved with tofu
It is not comparable to ordinary carvers
Please give Ziping a chance
Trust me
Row
Let's do it like this
Yes
Thanks
I've warned you many times
Be friendly with people on weekdays
Don't make enemies everywhere
Otherwise, it is to please Meng Shang to eat one person
There was a constraint behind the competition
What should you do
A lowly birth like me
Even if you crawl on the ground,
They only think I'm dirty
Why bother to be servile and obsequious
But if you want to beat Su Yuehua,
It's really not an easy thing
Don't I have you
Your Highness
I overheard my elder sister talking about jasmine soup
I have to try it today
It's a pity that jasmine today
Can't compare with the fragrance of summer
Your Highness will like it
Your Highness
Do you have medical books here, too
If nothing else
Why don't you go back first
Yes
Master can't
Yuan Qi
Your Highness
Tidy up
Let's move back
Yes
Your Highness
How do you draw this picture
How nice
It's still early
If you and I climb high and overlook at the moment,
Observe the distant mountain shadow
Lakeside night view
There are more half-empty clouds passing in front of the curtain
Cool breeze from heaven on all sides
What a pleasure it is
Go
Don't go back to the palace
Go now
Your Highness, it's getting late at night
I don't understand poetry
I'm not good at painting
If you go, you can only spoil the fun
If your highness is happy,
Tomorrow, you can invite your courtiers to swim with your arms
Wouldn't it be better
Just
I'll just go by myself
Why don't you go back to the palace first
Your Highness
Or this temper
I thought you could sleep while sitting
Go to sleep quickly
It should be finished before dawn
Let you go to sleep
It's late at night
You adults are on duty
You shouldn't walk around either
My proposal
Have you thought it over
I refuse
Others take your status
You don't complain
Don't complain
You don't hate Hu's threat to your life
Don't hate
You think you can avoid the butcher's knife by hiding in the stove
You can't really be so naive, can you
This is my business
Don't bother adults
I don't believe it
Don't believe in what
I don't believe anyone is deprived of everything
Still calm
I don't believe you can't complain or hate when you are on the verge of despair
Why are you so calm
Even if I die,
I die unsatisfied
You and Hu are destined to live only one person
Is that why you give up
Then why do adults hate Zhu Zhanji so much
Examine suspicious people all over the world
Is the most vicious thief
Cunning and treacherous beetles
Be obedient to my hands
Was interrogated by a woman for the first time in her life
I was just ordered to monitor the East Palace
How to talk about personal grievances
I don't know what the prince and the adult have
But as the saying goes
Be close to each other
Far from near
Adults are courtiers
Ann can spy on the East Palace
Separate the love between father and son
I hope adults will think twice
You still protect him
Some people are really lucky
Urinating is the heir appointed by the first emperor
Thousands of people love each other
Even the abandoned daughter-in-law
So generous and kind
It's really rare
Rare
Good
You are your Bodhisattva
I'll be my Luo Cha
Let's go our separate ways
Just woke up
You see
You are too good, Zihao
What's the matter
What are you watching
Nothing
Is it good-looking
You can't understand it either
Indeed
What are you doing
I'm surprised
I put the picture clearly in here
It was specially locked
It's gone now
I'll look for it
You go down
You get off, you get out of the way
Where did you go
Where did you put it
Just put it there
Have you looked for it well
It can't be opened, you cabinet
What for
Look what you've turned into
It doesn't matter if you don't come looking for it
I said it wasn't there
You didn't look well, did you
Not here either
This is the Wangchuan map
Song Qing Yi Lu Zeng Yun
Tang has bhikshuni Fanzheng
Exquisite workmanship
Preserved with a lump
Gourd and Vegetable with Soy Sauce
Yellow and red variegated colors make a scene
Today
I will follow the example of Brahma
Cold dishes with colors
Reproduce the picture of Wangchuan
Are you sure
Although the selection of materials for some pictures has yet to be considered
But I have it in mind
Good
From today
You should all obey the orders of Su Dian food
Yes
What to do
Unexpected
Su Yuehua
There is no copy of Wangchuan map in the palace
Where on earth did you get this one
As far as I know,
You only know how to cook
You don't know much about painting, do you
Naturally I can't
This is just
The Imperial Palace is dedicated to the imitation of painters
I borrowed it for details
Why not
Su Dian cuisine
Are you really going to
Reproduce the picture of Wangchuan with fancy cold dishes
In addition to Yuehua, Shangshi Bureau
Who else has such ability
You
This picture is clearly painted by Zi Jin
I didn't expect lofty Su Dian food
Would do such a shameless thing
It's an eye-opener
Yin Ziping
No evidence, no evidence, no blood
Watch your tongue
Su Dian cuisine
Reproduce Wangchuan map
It's not just about similarity
It is necessary to reproduce the artistic conception in the painting with fancy cold dishes
This is by no means an easy task
I'm looking forward to your finished product
Purple Azolla
Let's go
I don't care how you win
All I care about is the final result
Yes
It is clearly a picture of Wangchuan that you imitated from memory
Why don't you let me expose her in public
Lost everything has been lost
If you just made a scene,
But there is no evidence
I'm afraid Hu Shang will eat you back
Make you disqualified from the competition
I lost my qualification for the competition
She can't get a bargain either
I thought I was the only one who would do bad things
I didn't expect this
People who are full of righteousness and morality become bad
It's a hundred times more hateful than me
Yin Ziping, you still laugh
You remember
The more people make you angry
The less you can get angry
Once you are angry,
I fell into the trap of others
I'm not angry
I'm not angry at all
But I'm just mad
Purple Azolla
Bow your head and be insulted and laugh
Forbear your grievances
The world can't fight it
Why should a moment's joy and anger be in color
Doesn't Su Yuehua boast that he knows the famous dishes of the past dynasties
The first game of restoring ancient dishes
We have to win yet
You're so confident
As long as I want to win
That will definitely win
Don't be angry
Unexpectedly
You would do the same thing
Have precious things
Just give birth to timidity
But you see
I am a man with nothing
But why are you doing this
There is one thing
Even if you lose morality and conscience,
I must finish it, too
You have excellent cooking skills
You are sure to win
Exemption from gifts
That's nice
No, no, you guys have fun
Sister
Here comes my sister
You are in good health
Everything is fine
So is my sister
Good
Sachet for the Queen
Embroidered by oneself
Not bad
How nice
Sit down. You sit down, too
Crown Princess, what are you looking at
What is this
Back to the empress's words
It was recorded in the chronicles of Ganchun in the Song Dynasty
Spring orchid and autumn chrysanthemum
There are neither orchids nor chrysanthemums
Why is it named after it
This white pomegranate and pear
Meaning Orchid
Orange meat means autumn chrysanthemum
It's a pity
Spring orchid and autumn chrysanthemum soaked in sour plum bittern for too long
Recipe canon meal
Said the Empress
Spring orchid and autumn chrysanthemum soaked in plum brine for too long
Sour
What about the fragrant cherry
The empress likes it very much
I can't cook the appetizer well
Let's throw in the towel as soon as possible
Recipe canon meal
What shall I do
It's not my first time to cook
Can't even grasp the time well
And I tried it myself before serving
Then the empress
Isn't it obvious to help them
Snow reed
You see what she carved
You see, she's a good knife worker
Really
It seems, really it seems
Clearly not fine painting
But naturally know how to put Chen Bu potential
It should not be underestimated
What are you talking about
They seem to have changed the ingredients in Stone
Is it cucumber or wax gourd
What if I
Be sure to use wax gourd
I mean, ah
A picture of Wangchuan
Draw mountains and rivers on earth
How easy is it to restore the artistic conception in the painting
Su Yuehua is on the way of cooking
It's really talented
Yao Ziliao Yin Ziping
Why don't you start
Recipe canon meal
Help me continue kneading dough
Knead dough
What the hell are you two doing
Once upon a time, I saw dragons and phoenixes climbing branches
Good-looking and auspicious
What is this
A black mess
It's the first time I've seen it
Such a strange carved cold dish
Zi Jin
It's all here according to your orders
What are they doing
With that picture of Wangchuan,
What they do is in vain
Why are you still in no hurry
Where did you win this wonton
I can't, Zihao
Your wonton is different in shape
How can this work
Zi Jin
It's over it's over it's all over
This is the scene of deer and firewood in Wangchuan map
Wang Mocha lived in seclusion in Wangchuan in his later years
I often swim in Yuan Ye with a few friends
Poetry is rewarded for pleasure
And make a souvenir of Wangchuan
Look at it
This is Hua Zigang
Ying Lake
This apricot museum
That's Xinyiwu
That's right
It is Wangchuan map
Imperial concubine empress discerning eye
Ignorant like me
How do you know what Wang Mocha's excellent works are
I've never seen such a spectacle before
Hua Zi Gang
Zhu Yiyi
Ying Lake
Just hearing these names
It makes people fascinated
I didn't recognize it
Why ingratiate yourself with this
With the most common fruits and vegetables in the world,
Carving green mountains and green waters, the boat is graceful
Every cold dish here
They all condense the painstaking efforts and ingenuity of the kitchen
It's really rare
Guo Guifei
What do you think
Wonderful workmanship
Since Guo Guifei said so,
Do you need to compete in this first game
It's just a pity
There are several ingredients that are not used well
This scenery is quite similar
It's just that
The mood of this character
Out of date
This carving process is really exquisite
Even trees are in various ways
Never repeat the same
Look here
This willow silk is as thin as spring rain
I can't see it
What ingredients are used
Crown Princess
It's better to eat a hot pot this season
When the cold wind blows, everything is chilly
I'm telling the truth
Why don't you try it, too
Meng Shang Shi
It is already ready
Withdraw
Bottle gourd and mutton stuffing
What the empress said is
Duke of Zhou distinguishes the response of twenty-four qi
In good weather
Twenty-four flower shapes are specially used today
Accompanied by vegetables unique to the twenty-four solar terms
It is wonton with twenty-four solar terms
So
All the vegetables in the twenty-four solar terms are ready
Back to the Imperial Concubine Empress
Toona sinensis, water shield and water spinach
There are also vegetables such as Artemisia selengensis
They are all made in the fire room and the fire resistance
It's shrimp and shepherd's purse
Wonton stuffed with water spinach and fish meat
Filled with clam meat and lettuce
And this butterfly shape
It tastes slightly sweet with lotus root
The vegetables for tribute are all cultivated in the fire room
It is not a thing that conforms to the season at all
This is a bad taste
How can it be compared with your reproduction of Wangchuan map
It's not just vegetables with twenty-four solar terms, is it
I think the stuffing in every wonton
There are mysteries
This taste is by no means the same as usual
Back to the Imperial Concubine Empress
Because some vegetables are not timely
So the stuffing of every wonton
You have to work hard
For example, pea seedling chicken wonton
Take fresh seedling tips and mix them with duck oil
Such as Chinese toon ham wonton
The best elite meat to choose
It must be pickled by secret recipe in advance
So complicated and trivial
Isn't it against the original intention of simplicity in cooking
Back to the words of the Crown Princess
It's just enough from the beginning
After that, you can't get tired of eating
It is said that you are not tired of detail
All because of good weather, the country is rich and the people are safe
People can enjoy natural gifts
Make the world the best
It is precisely because of pursuing the way of cooking that
There are agriculture, animal husbandry, fishing and hunting
Medical way of cooking utensils and food utensils
Even the refinement of literature and art
That recreation of Wangchuan map is the best example
The ingredients needed today
They are all common things in the kitchen
Not much cost
But it takes some thought and time
Is able to speak well
Although they use ordinary things,
But because of the stuffing,
So everything tastes good
And the taste is different
It's really wonderful
Meng Shang Shi
You are really well trained