Your Highness
Do you think my piano sound is refined
Your Highness, what are you looking at
Wu Cairen forgives sins
Handmaiden made a momentary mistake
It has stained your clothes
Might as well do something
I'll just go back and change it
You rest
I'll be back in a minute
Your Highness, the men from the food bureau are here
Is it
Your Highness, the handmaiden will invite it now
Miss Yao, let's go
Your Highness
If you are told to wait, you will wait
Can't you talk
Are you going to freeze to death
To make me feel guilty
I'm telling you
Even if you freeze to death
I won't feel bad either
Your Highness
The food is getting cold
Handmaiden takes it back and redoes it
Don't be angry
It's too cold
The food will be cold
Your Highness, calm down
Handmaiden will go back now
Yao Ziliao
Without your highness's orders
The handmaiden is really going back
OK, then I'll beg you
See if you can still act like a handmaiden
To treat the master
Your Highness
Handmaiden yesterday
Has been officially promoted to the palm meal of the Shang Food Bureau
A palm meal of low grade
Do you really want it?
Wang, the female official of that year
Famous for his moral knowledge
The holy man wants to be recruited as a concubine
Quan Fei even invited her to accompany her
So glorious
She also declined politely
Insist on going out of the palace and returning home
Far from forcing her
He also gave a lot of money on the day of returning home
Slaves dare not compare themselves to sages
But your highness has always followed the example of the Holy One
The Holy One is so broad-minded
Your Highness is also shine on you
How can you force a palace maid
You said the word "Xinyue" yourself
Have you forgotten all about it
How can I forget
How dare you forget
I only wish your heart were like mine
I will not live up to my lovesickness
But your heart
Do you really know my heart
Even though the handmaiden's status is humble,
I dare not pay my heart
You stop
Chen Wu
Send her back in person
Yes
Go and get twenty sticks
Your Highness, the handmaiden is wronged
It's really snowing so hard
How unjust the handmaiden is
Is the handmaiden to take it out on you
Forty
Show us quickly
I want to see it, too. I want to see it, too
How nice
It's awesome. Yeah
So many
See what dishes are available
Let me see
Purple Azolla
It's so cold outside
Why are they all freezing through
Didn't you bring an umbrella
I said I'd go
You're so weak
Why are you still running around
Nothing, nothing
Much better
What's the matter
Would you like to see our specialty
Just in response to his this
Yes, I'm sure I can beat them
What happened to them
I heard that at the New Year's Eve banquet every year,
The food bureau and the food supervisor have to compete
Winners
You can get the right to enter imperial food next year
But this year's other side's dishes
She actually found out all about it
Strange to say
Shangshanjian is holding back more energy than Shangshanju
How can you expose your food list
Where did she come from
I'll see what's in the back
Not that Cao Zhou is in trouble
This peony arriving in Beijing after Mid-Autumn Festival
Are they all grown in Henan
I told them
Don't send peony seeds this year
But the flower farmers heard that
The empress in the palace is for disaster relief
I even donated my own hairpin jewelry
I personally picked out the best flower seeds and sent them
The palace moved them into a warm cave
It has been raised for quite a while
How can little help be worthy of gratitude
It makes me feel very sad in my heart
When the mother was there,
In winter, I am afraid that heavy snow will crush private houses
In the heat, I was worried that the scorching sun burned the crops
I still don't feel at ease when I leave
Thinking about the wives and children of the soldiers killed in the counter-insurgency
I told my father to give them awards and pensions
This is the true virtue of women
Now we are in the harem
Can do your part
It didn't live up to her kindness
Crown Princess
You emulate Empress Ren Xiao everywhere
It's really my duty to take the mother instrument as my duty
Guo Bianfei, please be careful
If such words are spread out,
How do you call the Crown Princess to live by herself
Founding hero family
There is such a nun virtue as you
An unscrupulous woman
I am not afraid of losing the reputation of the Guo family
Tang Tang Han Wang Fu
In order to be jealous,
Make no sense of honor or inferiority
How
Do you deserve to talk about women's virtue
Empress Zhuang Fei
This Qiongyuan is windy
I felt dizzy after enjoying the flowers for a while
Forgive me for being rude
One step ahead
Sister-in-law, don't dispute with her
She is a notoriously asshole
It is important that you take good care of yourself
After all, this peony is not a festival
It can't be raised well in the warm pavilion
I think the plum blossoms in front are blooming very well
Come on, let's go and have a look
Guo Bianfei is too domineering
My father has always been humble and benevolent
How can you make her so lawless
Guo Bianfei is his father's favorite princess
They are also our elders
How can the younger generation talk about the gains and losses of the elders
Look at this little story
It's really angry. I'm also angry
Wu Cairen
This is the holy year
Specially prepared for the Empress
What about the best peony
Miao Xian
Coming, coming
Let's go
These fish you sent
Fish scales are dull
The scales have fallen off
And this shrimp
Shrimp heads and tails have fallen loose
Shrimp shell is black
And it feels slippery and sticky
It's not like you said you just died.
These ingredients
Don't you dare send it to the palace
How exactly did you check it
Serve meals to calm one's anger
Today, Your Majesty gives a banquet to his ministers
Guanglu Temple is busy up and down
Maybe it was a momentary negligence
Besides, this fish and shrimp transportation
It's a long way
Inevitable
Food is to be imported
The taste can be covered with heavy oil and heavy salt
But are the ingredients fresh
What is the appearance of the product
Can you fool yourself
With this stale ingredient
Not only will it damage the body of diners
It will even ruin the conscience of the diner
My heart has rotted
What qualifications do you have to make meals
Return all these ingredients to me
Yes
Move quickly. Move quickly
Meng Shang Shi
All the ingredients used in the palace are carefully selected
There is such a mistake today
It is nothing more than Guanglu Temple favoring Shangshan Supervisor
Deliberately let us lose
Forget all kinds of difficulties on weekdays
Now I can't even use such despicable means
Let's all move up
Your Excellency is wise
Have a long plan
These ingredients are all stored in advance by me
Check well and don't make any more mistakes
Yes
Go and bite
Bite it
Bite bite
Bite
Go on, grab its eyes
Bite it
Yes, yes, you throw yourself at it
You bite it
Bite it. Come on, you go up, go up
Bite it
Right
Come on
Bite
Bite it
Right, right, right
There it goes
Bite and bite
Bite it
Your Highness
Don't you want to see cockfighting
Up, up, up
It's all ready
One big one and one small one
Which one do you think can win
A small one
Small
Then this time
The handmaiden dared to gamble with your highness
I think the big one can win
You take your men and get twenty sticks
Your Highness
Bite it right to right
Something that doesn't live up to expectations
Just bite
Up, up, up
Come on
Good bite
I lost my money in vain
The little one wins
Miss Su
What can I do for you
Lord Siqing asked me to send a new food list
Meng Shangshi personally checked this food list
Just six more courses
I wonder what's wrong with it
No
We'll get it done
Wang Si's meal
You see
But it can be carved thinner down here
Good
Miss Su
Shang Shanjian adjusted the food list
The first one is to explode two pieces
Then we still burn sea cucumbers with onions
The last line
It's all three things of happiness and longevity
Fushou Quan's three things bring together abalone and sea cucumber
Fish lips and other ingredients
Three things about happiness and longevity with authentic taste
Soup alone has to be boiled for ten hours
People are prepared at all
I want to disgrace the food bureau
Be caught off guard
The Food Bureau is disgraced
What kind of coke do you have
Serving should also pay attention to the order
Once you have eaten all three things of longevity,
The dishes in the back are boring
The last line
It was originally Zi Jin
Don't delay the hour
Let's get started, everybody
Yes
Your Excellency
Come with me
Ganqing Palace has a good banquet on New Year's Eve tonight
The humble position is responsible for guarding the palace
Dare not go AWOL easily
The security guards of the palace will be handed over to Liu Qian for the time being
You and I have other priorities
Let's go
Let Grandpa Huang drink less wine tonight
Emperor
Your Highness, Emperor Taisun, advises you to drink less
Why don't you eat it
Recipe canon meal
That fried sea cucumber with green onion
Your Majesty only looked at it
I never touched it again
I said earlier that this year's sea cucumber looks bad
I told you to change black ginseng
You won't listen
The taste of inferior ingredients is naturally inferior
Where can black ginseng match sea cucumber
Is Meng Shangshi very angry
Explore again
Yes
Quickly
Go ahead and prepare the rest
Let's go
The delicious taste of a pot
Can you hold down all three things of happiness and longevity
Steamed sea cucumbers and fish maw are hard to hold
A thick soup that has been boiled for more than ten hours
What's more, it's too late now
That
What about mutton
Neither this nor that
Is that all
Lose the game helplessly
Let me think again
Zi Jin
What exactly are you looking for
It's interesting
Don't underestimate this dish
Just this kung fu of removing bones without hurting flesh and blood
Just get it
Grandpa Emperor
This pigeon meat is steamed to death
And the soup is very nourishing
You try
Meng Shangshi accepted it
This clear soup cabbage is not really clear soup
There should be something in it
Duck, chicken and ham
As Your Highness said
It is a meal specially cooked by Shangshi Bureau for the Prince
There is a folk saying
No ham is not beautiful, no chicken is not fresh
No duck, no fragrance, no elbow, no thick
That's right
Be an expert