Why don't you use Tibetan fragrant pigs or mullet roe
No, no, no
Some people have used it
What else can I use
I have my own way
Really
You go
You go busy
Come on, come on, come on
Go ahead
You see
Why is she cutting cucumbers
This is not giving up
Are you here yet
Coming, coming
Taisun, please sit down
Father
I heard that you are ill
Can you please have a doctor too much
What disease is it
Headache
No
It's here
A gouge out of the heart
The whole bifurcation
Just
It all hurts
Since my father is ill,
You should rest assured of illness
Have any errands
Even if you tell your son
Seriously
Good
Lord You
Don't be so serious
I'm not here to find fault today
Lord Liu entered the palace to meet him
I came to see the meal list prepared for the mission
I'm just leading the way
Meng Shang Shi
Last year, the meal list of Guanglu Temple was not suitable for taste
Almost caused trouble
This year, the prince gave orders
To personally supervise
You can't be sloppy at all
Lord You has dealt with those people a lot
That's why he was asked to take a closer look
Your Excellencies
Please come with me
Delicious meat
But it's not greasy
It's completely different from the usual pork
Tibetan fragrant pigs sent by Wusi Zangdusi
What adults say is right
This kind of pig grows in mountains and forests
Drinking natural mountain springs
Eating wild people participate in pine mushrooms
So the meat is delicate and mellow
Fresh and tender
Handmaiden wants to
Most guests come from the sea
I have never tasted the delicious food in Tibet
This is how to cook soup with the spine of Tibetan fragrant pigs
The front legs are made of lion heads
This kind of pork
No matter how it is cooked,
Are not disappointing
Well said
I am the only one in the world
Where can I find this ginseng pig again
It's so delicious
Good
With ginger pepper
Unripe fragrant floating nose
Puffer fish is poisonous
River perch is ashamed and tasteless
Swordfish is indeed the first in Jiangxian
But now the spring season has not arrived
I used dried fish to send it away
I also used gold foil
This is the commonplace color
Wrapped in silk and silk
Is a peerless beauty
Self-deception
Step down
Why add pepper to it
In my hometown
Pepper all the way from Sumatra
Shipped from Guri
Price is more precious than gold
Your Excellency
This is a tribute girl who has just arrived
Pepper is piled up in the library in China
But you judge people by their own merits
Offer such cheap things as treasures
Wouldn't it be disrespectful
Handmaiden has shallow knowledge
Please forgive me
What is the faux pas
The arrival of His Highness unknown
Please forgive me for the loss of welcome
It's a small matter to entertain guests
It's a big thing to lose the national system
I heard everything you said just now
All over the world
Murphy Wang Tu
Lead the shore of soil
Murphy Wang Chen
China began in Qin and Han Dynasties
He kept coming and going with the Gentiles
As for me, it is even more so
Grandpa Huang's thousands of orders
Where does the caravan go
Whether by sea or land
You can't bully the widow, you can't bully the weak
Some places don't know the weather
He gave the calendar
Church farming
In some places banana leaves are used as food utensils
People can only eat cold food
It is necessary to open a ceramic mutual market
Give acupuncture herbs
In some places, etiquette and customs are impassable
Fighting constantly
We will quell the war
Our fleet brought it
It's not just gorgeous silk and porcelain
But also Chinese herbal medicines
Acupuncture weaving
Architectural navigation
And a large number of Chinese classics
They all stay in overseas countries
Why are we doing this
Just because of the scourge of widowhood
Then there was chaos
Only the world is peaceful
Then the people in the world can enjoy happiness
So
She doesn't understand. You have to tell her
And treat them equally
Your Highness, please forgive me
These children are confined to the deep palace and have limited horizons
Your Highness's lesson is better than my ten years' work
Remember today's words
A person should have a broad mind and vision
It will be good for you all your life
Yes
Step down
A kind of red shrimp is mentioned in the collections of Materia Medica in Tang Dynasty
Shenglinhai Huiji
The big one is a foot long
Must can be a hairpin
Just in line with Taiping County Records
Colorful giant shrimp with abnormal burly
Exactly the same
Therefore, it is also called God Shrimp in Quanzhou Prefecture
Today, the traditional practice of local fishermen is specially adopted
Cook splendid shrimp rice
Please ask noble people to taste it
Where is the meal
Your Highness doesn't know
Rice in fishermen's mouth
Often refers to fish and shrimp
Shrimp meat dipped in sauce has unique flavor
It makes people feel like they are back in the bow
The moment when the sea breeze blows
Unspeakably relaxed and happy
Fresh and chewy
It's the smell of the sea
What do you say, Your Highness
Powder, waxy, sweet and endless aftertaste
Needless to say, betel nut and taro
Taro again
Crispy and sweet
Far better than steamed taro
Do two things with one impression
Ordinary ingredients
Make an unusual taste
This is the craft
No matter how delicious it is
It's just some cut cucumbers
Fennel broad bean
Add a taro
Not even a shredded pork
Why is it so stingy
Are you going to win by quantity
Grandpa Huang asked his father to do errands
It happened that my father fell ill
But the emperor's life is the emperor's life
He is ill
Only I can come
Your Highness
Do you still need to ask the prince for instructions when you look at the meal list
Call the cook
Why use ordinary food
Back to your highness's words
Ancient cloud
It's a pleasure to have friends from afar
Entertain guests
It really should make them feel at home
But the people of our country are the most precious people
All the products of this land
It is a gift from God to the industrious people
They are the ones who should taste it most
And
When Zhang Qian sent to the Western Regions,
Brought back the ingredients you used today
Precious seeds
Take root and sprout in the land of China
After being cultivated from generation to generation,
In order to change the ever-changing delicious food
Throw me a wooden peach
Reward it with Qiong Yao
Prepare a meal list for the mission
In addition to delicacies
Add these too
The rice I just ate
It's very soft and delicious
Jingshan Bridge Rice
Huguang suffered a natural disaster last year
If this kind of rice is supplied to the diplomatic corps,
So the wealthy businessmen in Beijing
Will compete for it
In this way
The life of the people will be much better
It's just a little chef
How to have so many thoughts
It's just a coincidence
How come he's back
Your Excellency
Please
All the way
The opal brought back from Hurumus
See if you like it or not
Thank you for your reward
Handmaiden is ashamed and afraid to accept it
Line line line
Miss Yao
Haven't you been looking for it before
Is this log book
I sent it to you
I can't use it
Bring it all over
Keep it
Thank you for your handmaiden, Emperor Taisun, for your reward
Good
You tell her
One day
Our fleet brought it back
It won't be just jewelry and spices
There will be more products that benefit the Chinese people
It's over
I forgot the most important sentence
Walk, walk, walk
Reward
That's what she said
How dare that handmaiden reply indiscriminately
That's what Miss Yao said
Hurry up, hurry up
Come on, come on, come on
Quickly
Hurry up, hurry up
Father-in-law Yuan
Thank you very much
Go in by yourself
Go on
Open
Yes
What did you do today
Back to your highness's words
In accordance with established practice
Meal list from Guanglu Temple
The food bureau cooks according to the order
Yao Ziliao
Handmaiden is guilty, please punish your highness
What are your sins
Please show your highness that handmaiden is stupid
Get out of here
Handmaiden retires
You go and persuade her to come back
Don't come back if you can't persuade you to come back
Your Highness
How can this be called persuasion
I don't like her strange appearance
Your Highness
Miss Yao has no yin and yang
This is how handmaidens serve their masters
One question and one answer
Be careful
Without the slightest trespass
What's wrong with it
I never treated her like a handmaiden
Go quickly
Go on
Your Highness
You see
Is the month
Your Highness takes tonic
You can't bait hot things
Eat early
Duck Soup with Coix Seed and Lotus Seeds
Change hibiscus meat and silver carp tofu
Apricot goose mixed with broom
Cut the roe
Go and get her back
This time
Go for me
Yes
Pinellia ternata
Three spoonfuls
Gold tooth powder
Zi Jin
Look at my craft
Is it good-looking
This is too expensive
The pattern is too dense
But it's still much better
Make persistent efforts
Meng Shang Shi
Mr. Chan
Meng Shang's food is polite
Mr. Yisheng
Shame and dare not
I vaguely remember when Han Ying entered the palace for training
You have served as a teacher
It's worthwhile to call you sir
I wonder if you are visiting today
But what do you want from the emperor and grandson
Today, Lord Yang entered the palace
Taste Miss Yao's Suzhou Pastry
Quite elegant
I want to ask your kitchen to copy it
I came here specially to ask for a prescription to go back
This is a trivial matter
I asked Zi Jin to write it and send it to me
Why do you come to the door in person
Then thank Meng Shang for eating
I'll send someone to pick it up later
Good
Mr. Chen walks slowly and doesn't send it
Please forgive me, Lord Shang Shi
I am also afraid of missing my son's good future
Serve people with color
When what a good future
It's good to be young and ignorant
Avoid a lot of sorrow
There are palace rules in the palace
Female officials have more dignity of female officials
I'm still in the food bureau for a day
He was sheltered by me for one day
There is no reason to take it away by force
Do such a senseless thing next time
I won't be lenient
Yes
It tastes wrong
Your Highness
Today's dish
It's exactly the same as yesterday
What's wrong
Try it yourself
How dare a handmaiden
Can't taste it
Your Highness, please make it clear
It's not that the dishes are wrong
It is your highness who is in a bad mood
Your Highness
The same food
Diners have different moods
The taste will be different
I think it's the cook who doesn't pay attention