Come and help me sort out my books
Your Highness
Take stock of the grain in the world's military and civilian yamen
Check the number of annual cashiers
It's really tedious
Our department is already understaffed
Sudden imperial edict
Isn't it a soup crab
Where are your hands and feet in disorder
Of course
Your Highness's orders
I must do it
It's just that the year is approaching
I also ask your highness to give you time
Rong Chen went back to draw up the articles of association
Come and report to your highness again
Your Highness
In fact, this government granary stores grain
There are reports everywhere
Just press the report for statistics
If you really want to send personnel to the field for verification,
On the selection of this personnel alone,
You need to think it over and over again
Scrutinize and scrutinize again
You must be cautious
According to my minister's opinion
Why don't you put it aside for a while
Take a long-term view
Lord Song has a point
It's a pity that I met your majesty yesterday
He said eight months is too long
Only half a year was allowed
Then
Lord Song
Have a good time
Your Excellency
Please
I retire
What are you laughing at
Are the books in order
Your Highness
Handmaiden has doubts in his heart
Dare to ask
Your Highness, what is this painting
This is the fruit of tribute from Sumatra
It's called gambling
Grandpa Huang doesn't like its fragrance
But I tasted it once
It tastes very sweet
Dare to ask your highness
Where are the overseas countries
What kind of local conditions and customs are there
This is the homework of the Food Bureau
Make meal lists for overseas messengers
Listen to what you say
Seems eager to find a boat
Escape from overseas
There is no shortage of strange people in all dynasties
Enthusiastic about seeking immortals overseas
Fairy is not found
But there are a few logbooks
If you're interested
Self-seeking
Maybe on the travel notes side
Your Highness
Tai Sun Fei has been invited again
Take it
Your Highness will not come again tonight
Yes
Father-in-law Yuan
Tai Sun Fei
Your Highness is afraid that you will be empty
The extraordinary handmaiden came to report it
So
He's not coming again
The emperor recently detained his master to talk about government affairs
So your highness, he is too busy
When your highness is idle,
Be the first to think of you
You go
Tai Sun Fei
Brocade book
It's all my fault
I broke his heart
Walk with me for a while
If there is a person who disappoints you very much
She wants to repent now
Will you forgive her
Why not answer
Your Highness
Who has no fault
You can change it after passing it
Great goodness
You are a really strange person
You've done so much
See me but don't say anything
You know I'm talking about her
And let me see her
I'll let you go
Because you want to go
Your Highness is puzzled
Can't be released for a long time
How can this be fun
It's better to be open and ask for a peace of mind
Isn't it
In the Royal Family
Don't ask for a love that depends on life and death
But ask for a respectful wife
But I sat with her
Everyone feels uncomfortable
You said that in this world
Is there such a strange couple
Your heart is so sincere
Who in the world won't cherish it
As long as your highness treats each other sincerely
There will be a day when the clouds will be seen
I went to see her
Are you really happy
Look at your worries
Think one's own worries
Your Highness shows his face
We are delighted
Your Highness is puzzled
Can't be released for a long time
How can this be fun
It's better to be open and ask for a peace of mind
Let's go to Hongqing Palace
Yes
Citizen's daughter greets His Royal Highness, Emperor Taisun
Your Highness
Taisunfei greets the Crown Princess
Will be back soon
Would your highness please sit down for a moment
This is Miss Hu Fuqi
Go to the palace to visit Tai Sun Fei
Your Highness is back
Why didn't you tell me earlier
You are talking to the Crown Princess
How dare a handmaiden disturb
Seven sisters
Why are you here
Shan Yuan greets Tai Sun Fei
No one reported it before
What's going on
Why not answer
Previously, the crown princess gave her mother
The grace of visiting the palace
Now Tai Sun Fei is ill
Mother often misses
But the legs and feet are not flexible
He sent seven younger sisters into the palace to visit the sick
I am ill
What's wrong with me
Tai Sun Fei and Huang Tai Sun have been married for a long time
But there are no children for a long time
Not only do the crown princess miss it
Parents also often worry
Elder sister
I always think of my family
No matter how much I blame you and hate you
I also regard you as the only support in the palace
You're the only one I can trust
But only because I have no children
Can't win more honor for the Hu family
You guys
One by one, you
Why do you treat me so cruelly
Why
Say something
Third sister
No wonder your highness just came over
He left without looking back
He thought I was a wife
Unexpectedly for one's own selfish desires
Dedicate your sister to your husband
So as to flatter your mother's family
Sure
Since you all don't care about face
Then I will fulfill you
Bearer
Drag this bitch down
The staff is responsible for thirty
Expulsion from the palace
Tai Sun Fei
This
Master
Tai Sun Fei
Please spare the handmaiden
Master
Miss Big Save the Handmaiden
Handmaiden also listens to your orders
Handmaiden is obedient to orders
Master Jin Shu has followed you since childhood
But your closest handmaid
Such a person is for the Hu family
You can betray the maid who deceives your master at any time
I will never keep her
You take her out of the palace at once
From today
Without my orders
No one in the Hu family is allowed to enter the palace again
You listen up
From today
I want to live according to my own wishes
Whether it's you
Or a father
If you disobey me again,
Don't blame me for being ruthless
Elder sister
Third sister
How come the third sister is like a different person
It's good to change
If she's still the one she used to be
A muddled look
You can't live in this palace
This is the case now
It's like a great grandson
Let's go
I'll walk you out of the palace
Your Highness
Tai Sun Fei is still waiting outside
There is no need to report her news in the future
Yes, I know
Wait a minute
The handmaiden will invite Tai Sun Fei now
Your Highness
I'll I'll go
Tell her
The books are messed up
Tell her to come and rearrange it
Your Highness
I see
You go and tell me again
I have something urgent to see your highness
Tai Sun Fei
You know your highness's temper
The more you clamor to see him
The more unhappy he is
How about this
You go back first
When your highness is in good spirits,
You come and make amends yourself
This thing will be over
Master
It's windy here
Let's go back
I can't find any of the books I'm looking for
How did you organize it
I'm asking you what I'm talking about
Your Highness
Asking me
Or are you asking a handmaiden
What's the difference
Your Highness is right
I am a handmaiden
What are you talking about
I persuaded the temple to go down to see Tai Sun Fei
His Highness vented his grievances on me
I think your highness should be aware
What I've done for you
Not a handmaiden will do it for his master
You
I am delighted with you
What I've done for you
It was done by a woman for a man she admired
To please your highness
I can endure loss
Even heartache
Persuade you to go to see Tai Sun Fei
But you
But I put the books I sorted out
Just give up like this
Your Highness didn't lose a book
It's my heart
You
How dare you speak to me like that
Your Highness
You treat me the way your master treats your handmaiden
Then from now on
I can use it, too
The way handmaiden treats his master treats you
It's not my job to tidy up the study
Your Highness should be dissatisfied
But punishment is
If your highness has no other orders,
The handmaiden retired
What did she just say
She
She said she liked you
She said she would use the handmaiden way
To treat her master
Tell her to roll back
Go on
Rolling rolling
Your Highness told you to get back
Tell you to roll back
You're screwed. You're screwed
Your Highness