Listen to me.
I'll be the senior prosecutor today.
It's my treat tonight.
Drink whatever you like.
(Successful career)
I don't allow anyone
to leave the karaoke room sober.
Drink.
Cheers.
Come on.
Friends,
my wife is expecting our second child.
I'll go home to keep her accompany.
You have fun.
I'll leave first.
(Happy family)
You see your wife and child every day.
But it's not easy for us
to meet as old classmates.
To be honest,
I've missed you these years.
Me, too.
(Romance continuing)
Please come now.
Don't be so slow.
Who else still hasn't set off?
Qian Wei,
what's wrong with you?
I haven't seen you the whole afternoon.
And you, Lu Xun.
It's our class reunion
seven years after graduation!
How can you still let her work overtime?
I'll compensate for your loss.
Can you let her leave?
Be quick. Come on.
(The Seventh Reunion
of Law Department 2011)
(Delete and Leave)
Hello.
One more dozen of beers.
Wei,
this is a sugar water shop.
Our main product is dessert.
But you?
You take it as a bar.
Don't influence your junior schoolmates.
My brothers and sisters,
please cherish
your college life.
You know that?
Don't end up like me.
Seven years after graduation,
I'm now a paralegal.
I once was a script editor.
I also worked in a foreign enterprise.
I even had jobs as a cook
and a driver.
I worked in many trades.
But I've never been in the court.
Things are even better now.
Seven years have passed.
My hair keeps falling out.
My boyfriend ran away with another girl.
And I don't even have a job now.
Life is so hard.
College is the best.
Do you hear me?
Goodbye.
Welcome to my shop next time.
See?
Now I can't influence them.
If sadfishing could earn me money,
I wouldn't have been rich.
Please bring me the beers.
=Episode 2=
=My Youth and Hairline Both Come Back=
=Legally Romance=
(Make Your Life Sweet)
No need for the beer.
Two double-layer milk custard, please.
It's been many year since we graduated.
You still come here for sugar water.
It's not easy for this shop
to continue to open.
Well,
every day you pop up in front of me.
Have you equipped me
with a positioning system?
Or you are Thanos?
Back in college,
every time
you lost to me in the exam,
you would come here to have water.
How did you know that?
At that time, you already thought that…
I thought
that it must be predestined
that you couldn't beat me even once.
So I'm predestined
to be your boss.
Thank you.
For eleven years,
you've never missed any chance
to laugh at me.
You are so "well-intentioned".
I do have a good intention.
So I don't want you to leave.
I remember you said
that you wanted to defeat me
and became the best lawyer.
As long as you are still
working in this profession,
you haven't lost the game.
I really hope
that you can win even once.
I also don't want to give up.
But I'm the person
who signed on the confirmation
of evidential material.
I lost their documents.
What else can I do to apologize
except for resignation?
I'm a bachelor
who fails to pass judicial exam
in seven years.
And I'm also a paralegal
who got the client's evidence lost.
No law firm will hire me now.
I will.
I'll find evidence to prove
that Lawyer Wei destroyed the exhibit
and figure out the relationship
between him and AES.
I've lost at first instance.
I'll win it back in the final judgment.
To escape
won't solve any problem
but will only make us lose more.
I'm not escaping.
Then why can't you
pass the judicial exam?
Isn't it because of your father?
(Haizhou District
for 2014 National Judicial Examination)
Qian Wei.
What are you doing?
(2014 NATIONAL JUDICIAL EXAM
ADMISSION TICKET Qian Wei)
About the exam,
I've tried very hard.
But I just can't pass it.
A talent like you
who's always the best
doesn't know how it feels like.
Actually,
there are many things I can't do.
But passion is not a choice.
It means you have no other choice.
Of course, I can be a good guy
and tell you
that you can't get it over
so you'd better stop trying.
It's simple for me to that.
It's so painful
to face up to it.
So you can turn back and leave.
But if you do that,
it will be a waste of you talent
and your capability.
Therefore,
I'd rather play a villain
to push you.
I know it will put you in great pain
to make a breakthrough.
But you still have me.
I'm by your side.
Carry all together
You are such a master
of paper folding.
Trust me, Qian Wei.
We will win.
But I think,
well,
can you let me escape it
for at least tonight?
Okay.
It's fine for me.
But…
Stop dawdling here.
Destination, Class Tree.
Get her up.
Well,
we are old classmates.
You really
don't need to do this.
Move.
Oh, my things.
My phone.
My bag.
(Class Tree
Law Department 2011)
Sir,
all students of grade 2011 have come
except for Mo Zixin,
She's in another city.
Why is that?
Have you informed her?
Yes.
This bad girl.
Lu Xun.
Distribute the shovels
and let them dig the wish bottles out.
Come on.
All boys.
Let's dig the bottles out.
Move.
Well, over ten years ago,
Mr. Zhen was still a middle-aged man
with thick hair.
Look at him now.
Only several hairs
hang on his head sparsely.
Keep your voice down.
Aren't you afraid
that Mr. Zhen will be mad at you?
Not at all.
To be frank,
the so-called class reunion
is just an occasion
to judge the people
who are not successful.
Do you understand?
Qian Wei.
Your hair
is pretty thick.
My hairstyle
is full of signs of years.
But isn't that because
I'm so worried about
all of you?
Right.
A mischievous student
can cost a hair of mine.
A disobedient one
can also cost a hair of mine.
But after meeting you, Qian Wei,
my hair never stops falling out.
I'm sorry
You've graduated for seven years.
Have you passed the judicial exam?
Back at school,
you were so indulged in love.
I heard that Li Chongwen
is now the legal director
of AES Group.
What about you two?
When will you get married?
Lu Xun,
you've become
a senior partner now.
That's a good thing.
But,
you should find time
to get yourself a girlfriend.
Back then, the relationship
between you and Mo Zixin is…
Sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
My hands are slippery.
So I didn't hold it well.
It's not your hands.
It's you that are slippery.
You did it on purpose.
Sir.
On purpose!
Have a rest.
Okay.
Just dig. Be quick.
Mr. Zhen just mentioned your love affair
and you got uncomfortable.
Move.
- I remember during freshman year,
- Come on, guys.
- you helped your brother Qian Chuan
- Be quick.
- to steal Lu Xun's girlfriend.
- Okay.
If you buy the ticket as a couple,
a decade later,
we will send half of the ticket
to both of you respectively
(Advanced Booking of Concert Tickets)
and the couples who can piece
the two half tickets together
will get a refund.
A decade?
I think within less than half a year,
half of these couples will break up.
Well,
this kind of activity
is a one-way bet for the organizers.
Only idiots will buy.
But so many people are waiting in line.
That one
He's a real idiot.
(Concert of Ten-year Appointment)
(Zixin just threw the ticket,)
(and the next minute)
(you let Qian Chuan express his love.)
(You are so skilled)
(in stealing others' girlfriend.)
Lu Xun
has stayed single for ten years.
The worst thing he has done
is picking on you at work.
It's very kind of him.
It's not like that.
Did he lose his girlfriend for my sake?
What I did then
was just a little push.
It's fated for us to be a couple
with someone.
And it's your fate to work under Lu Xun.
It's up to you today.
This is your bottle.
Here.
These two are yours.
Thank you.
Check whether this one is yours.
Let me have a look.
This is really mine.
Qian Wei,
you were in such a hurry just now
to dig the wish bottles out.
Why not open it?
Have you fulfilled your dream?
Without exception,
all wishes are still wishes.
But it's okay.
I'll put them on the door
after I go home.
They can help ward off evils.
None of them has come true?
I remember
that you used a whole page.
Even if God
wants to make life hard for you,
he should at lease
grant you one wish.
What a coincidence!
God hasn't missed any one of them.
Let me put aside big wishes
like "good health for parents"
and "success in both career and love."
Just this one.
"Keep a lovely dog."
For the time being,
I can barely afford to support myself.
It's all right.
Look at mine.
My dream
was to transfer to music department
and perform in Mercedes-Benz Arena.
Are you serious?
What.
What's wrong?
Can't I have a music dream
though I'm tone deaf?
If it's easy to realize,
why did I put it into the bottle?
Am I right?
Music?
To be honest,
that's a little crazy.
What about yours?
What are you doing?
Don't be shy.
Partner Lu,
what's your wish that hasn't come true?
You've already realized your dream.
I didn't realize it.
How's that possible?
What I wanted was
a wonderful love.
However,
that girl doesn't love me.
Qian Wei, as the forever No.2,
though you never defeat the No.1,
you've kept him single for ten years.
You win in some way.
Stop talking,
Nevertheless,
there are plenty of fish in the sea.
Right?
Well,
as a successful and hot man,
Lu Xun can get any girl he wants.
If this one doesn't work, get a new one.
That's nonsense.
I read a book by Maugham.
There is a Book Review of the book.
It says
that there's a hole
in everyone's heart
and it needs to be filled
with something
in the same shape.
Maybe this thing is not perfect.
Maybe it's even twisted.
But if it's not the right person
to get into
your heart,
this hole will never be filled up.
It wasn't filled up in the past.
You'll have the right girl
in the future.
Right?
It can be filled up now.
(Mo Zixin)
This is Zixin's.
You keep it for her.
Why should I keep it?
Qian Wei.
You are the class monitor.
Qian Chuan,
what are you doing here?
Where's Zixin?
She's on a business trip
so she didn't come.
I'm not asking you.
Who do you think you are
to tell me
where she is?
Don't be so rude.
Shut up.
You…
Don't be rude.
What's it?
Zixin's wish bottle.
What are you doing?
Zixin's wish bottle
should be given to her by Lu Xun.
Why?
I'm the class monitor.
All right.
Take it if you like.
No, no.
Trust me.
You will feel so sad
if you give it to him.
Just keep it well.
Well, what's the big deal, monitor?
I'm her ex-boyfriend.
Besides,
it's not in the law firm.
Why do you still take his side?
Give it to me.
Well,
I'm not taking his side.
No.
Don't take the bottle.
You don't need it.
Help, guys.
Take him away.
- I don't who's this boy.
- You want to get physical?
Give it to me.
Did you just hit me?
Have you eaten dynamite?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Are you going to hit the monitor
- for a bottle?
- Have a nice talk.
Article 108.
Qian Chuan enters the national team.
It's okay
that this one is not fulfilled.
Article 109.
A head of thick hair and lots of money.
Well,
to be honest,
apparently my wishes
are reasonable and legitimate.
What's so hard to realize them?
Okay.
It's okay that they can't be realized.
But why does every wish go against me?
It's not right.
Now I don't even have a job.
Seriously?
The worst part
is Lu Xun.
I hope that he can forget
our personal grievances.
Guess what?
He and Qian Chuan almost had a fight.
I don't care.
Anyway, you must
give me an explanation.
Today,
whether you…
(Qian Wei,)
(stop running!)
(We're not bad people.)
What do you want?
I can't hear you. I can't hear you.
(College-opening Exam
for Law Department 2011)
(Name: Qian Wei)
(Serious and Solemn
College-opening Exam for Law Department 2011)
What's this?
Is this a prank again?
What are we doing here?
Reality show?
Sir, she's cheating.
I'm cheating?
Are you nuts?
(Serious and Solemn
College-opening Exam for Law Department 2011)
Mr. Zhen.
Qian Wei, right?
Only ten minutes left
for the examination.
If you don't know the answers,
just hand in a blank paper.
Don't influence other students.
(Zixin)
(Liu)
(It must have cost a lot)
(to prepare the reality show.)
Well, sir.
Can I check the time?
(September 3, 2011)
It's not fake.
- It's real hair.
- You… you!
You… you… you!
This is really real hair.
Hands off me!
How could you pull my hair?
The hair is real.
Be quiet!
Qian Wei.
How dare you hit your class teacher
the first day in school?
Do you still want to study here?
I want. I really want.
This time,
I will live well.
Thank you, sir.
Sit down.
Protect your hair.
Only nine minutes left.
I won't give you
even one more minute!
It's okay. I'm good.
Other students focus on your paper.
Behave yourselves.
Keep good discipline.
(College-opening Exam
for Law Department 2011)
(Fill the blanks)
(Explanation of terms)
(Objective questions)
(Serious and Solemn
College-opening Exam for Law Department 2011)
(... civil law)
So simple.
It's really so simple
Mr. Zhen,
I'll take all the scholarships
for the next four years.
I'll bring your teaching career
to a new height.
Oh, youth.
I, Qian Wei, am back.
Failure is the mother of success.
I've been a failure for ten years.
This time,
I am the grandmother of success.
Lu Xun.
It's said you entered the law department
as No.1 in the whole city.
Uncle Lu must be very happy.
little does one think
We're classmates in junior high school.
What a coincidence
that we're still classmates in college!
How's Uncle Mo?
Is his business doing well?
Pretty good.
Hey, stop filming.
Stop, stop it.
(At that time,
(someone took photos)
(of Mo Zixin)
(Shocking! Wet show of beauty on campus!)
(and posted them on the Internet.)
(After that,)
(Mo Zixin was often gossiped)
(by some ill-intentioned students.)
(That's her.)
How's Uncle Mo?
Is his business
doing well?
Yes.
Pretty good.
Lu Xun,
are you okay?
Hello?
Is there something wrong
with your brain?
Um.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's really a misunderstanding.
I just thought
that…
You know, this faucet…
Then why did you push me to the ground?
Are you a lunatic?
You made signs to me
in the examination room.
Of course I would report you.
Did you have to retaliate
against me like this?
Well,
he's not my boss now
Why should I put up with him?
This is the year 2011.
He's still a younger brother.
Hey, you!
Don't be so narcissistic.
It's just a college-opening exam.
Did I need to cheat?
Besides,
I'm telling you.
It is a sure thing
that for this college-opening exam,
I,
will take the first place.
Do you hear me?
Who is this person?
Why is she so arrogant?
Right.
How dare she say that
in front of Lu Xun?
Well, my classmate.
What.
You don't believe it?
For the exam,
the criminal law you cited
in the last subjective question
has been amended.
The 8th amendment to Criminal Law
has come into effect
on May 1, 2011.
That means
you are wrong about that question.
Two points lost.
And, don't call me classmate.
I'm your elder sister.
I can also make a prediction.
From now on,
you will lose to me
in every examination,
every competition,
and every community activity.
This time, it's your turn
to be the forever No.2.
Say whatever you like.
Don't put your hands on me.
I don't care.
Then I'll also make a prediction.
You'll be scolded very soon.
Have a guess.
Is my prediction correct?
Not everyone is a prophet.
Qian Wei.
The disturber of examination discipline.
You want to escape?
Come to my office.
Wei.
(From Dad)
(Why did you hit the teacher)
(the first day in college?)
(Mr. Zhen called)
(and asked whether you were)
mentally deranged.)
(Apologize to the teacher now.)
(Don't get punished by the school.)
Right.
Dad is still alive.
Well, sir.
There's something urgent at home.
Can I go home first?
I'll come back to you very soon.
Is it that urgent?
Fine.
Then you don't need to come.
You'll receive
a disciplinary warning next week.
Isn't a nine o'clock curfew too early?
In the future,
this is just the beginning
of nightlife.
This door still remains unrepaired.
Tonight,
I will take Qian Yanping
to go to hospital.
I'll get him cured first.
Then I'll turn the tables.
It's so late.
Why are you going out?
You!
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
Well,
I'm not
trying to get out.
It's just that…
I… I want to…
Are you hungry?
It's okay.
I also plan to go out for some food.
Let's go together.
How about this?
You come down first.
I'll go up
and then pull you up.
Come on.
Well, it doesn't
feel right.
Actually, I…
Don't worry.
It's not like I must get out.
Don't be afraid.
I am also a student.
I'm from Grade 2010, law department.
My name is Li Chongwen.
My name is Qian Wei.
- Why are you doing this?
- Please wait.
Why do you haunt me?
Let go of me.
Go away.
You are annoying.
You…
Do you know me?
I don't
I don't want to know you
in the past, now and in the future.
Stay away from me.
You were trying
to climb the wall just now.
I just want to give you a hand.
I won't take advantage of you.
Stop it.
Stay away from me!
Give me a hand? I don't need it.
If you enjoy helping others so much,
you can be Aquaman.
Then you'd better study
in the ocean department.
Law department is not right for you.
Aqua… Aquaman?
I can't swim.
What? Who's Aquaman?
You don't need to know.
Go away.
Stay away from me.
What are you doing again?
Qian Wei.
You,
cheated in the exam,
hit your senior
and climbed the wall to get out.
What do you want?
You broke more school rules in a day
than others break in a year.
Do you have to get yourself
a disciplinary measure?
Don't give me that look.
Resentment?
Are you all right, Senior Li?
It's okay.
In the future, you will have
a tit-for-tat fight.
The scene of you two getting along
makes me feel uncomfortable.
We were studying how to climb the walls.
Somehow,
she suddenly got upset.
You got it wrong.
He didn't get it wrong.
I was hitting you.
And afterwards,
if you get close to me again,
I will…
Go to eat something.
Your stomach keeps rumbling.
I'll hit you every time I see you.
Don't laugh. I mean it.
You're threatening him,
my classmate.
In serious cases, you'll get detained.
Do you want to live here
or go to the police station
for tonight?
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
The teacher made me be acting monitor.
So many things happened
on the first day.
Where's the face
of Law Department 2011?
It's all because of you.
Acting monitor. Wow, you are so great!
Do you think you are my boss?
As for Law Department 2011,
I have plenty of time
to gain glory for it.
Don't you worry about it!
Goodbye.
Come back.
What!
Look at yourself.
You are just fooling around.
You'd spend tonight
safe and sound first.
Take it.
Why should I take it for you?
Come on.
Be a good girl. Take it.
I won't take it for you.
Take it.
Go!
Well,
I need to get out.
It's urgent.
Stop talking.
I have an emergency.
Can I…
Let me get out.
I'm come back soon.
No way.
Don't tug at my clothes.
I'm talking to you.
Are you a kangaroo?
Don't jump around.
Well, take your thing.
I'll go myself.
Take the bag yourself.
Well.
Qian Wei, wait. Stop!
Help! Don't chase me.
Qian Wei.
It's our first time to be roommates.
You don't need to be so nice.
Qian Wei,
you also don't need to be so impulsive.
Done.
I,
am very satisfied
with this hairstyle.
It does look good.
You two
are like Iron Man,
aren't you?
You equipped our dormitory
with water dispenser
and refrigerator.
To be honest,
I'm not as rich as you are,
but I have some experience.
For girls studying law like us,
baldness is a common problem.
If we directly
tie our hair up,
it's easier for us to get bald.
Therefore, this bangs
and these hair-growing products
are my best wishes
to your Lisa,
Linda and Amanda.
Lisa, Linda, Amanda?
Who are they?
Sweet,
each hair
of each bald girl
deserves a name.
You'll understand ten years later.
Come on.
Stop your bullshit.
Ten years?
I don't buy it.
You don't believe me, right?
It's time to show you
my status and superpower.
In your fridge
is all beers.
How do you know it?
At that time,
I was conquered
by Big Sister Liu
with this fridge of beers.
I have two more suggestions.
Don't hide the fridge
under the table.
Otherwise,
Aunt Ma will confiscate it
as an illegal appliance
the day after tomorrow
I know.
You'll say you can buy it again.
Am I right?
What a waste of these beers!
Isn't it?
You can't squander money like that.
One more thing,
an underwear stealer
will frequent here recently.
So you must put your underwear
and precious things
in a safe place.
Do you understand?
Okay.
You make me jumpy.
Since they'll be gone
the day after tomorrow,
let's drink them all today.
Um, drink now?
Drink.
Zixin, can you drink beers?
Of course.
A friends with status?
That's rare.
I,
decide to befriend with you.
To our pretty hair!
To our youth!
To turn the tables!
To get rich!
What do you mean by turning the tables?
It means that we can have
whatever we want and a cool life.
Turn the tables?
Right.
To turn the tables!
Come on. Cheers!
(Shopping Mall)
(In 2011,)
(there's no makeup sponge)
(or facial cleanser.)
(It depends on leaflets and phone calls)
(to order takeaway food.)
(One-year study of the Civil Code)
(goes to waste.)
(But it's all right.)
(Because of my youth)
(and hairline are back.)
(Although)
(I still met Li Chongwen,)
(this time)
(he doesn't matter anymore/)
(Tomorrow is the opening ceremony.)
(Finally,)
(I can see Father again.)
(Dad is right.)
(I really can)
(start all over again)
(without relying on others.)
(Once again, let's change the world.)
(Guanghua University)
I won't come down.
I miss you so much.
This child
(Opening Ceremony)
Wei, come down.
No, I want to hug him.
Your father
can't hold your weight.
Let me carry her for a while.
How nice it is!
Stop showing off.
It's okay, girl.
It's so nice to have a daughter.
You miss Dad, right?
Stay on my back.
No worries.
I can carry you for long.
I'm a little trembling.
But it's not my legs.
It's because of the music.
Come down.
All right. It's okay.
You are better than Qian Chuan.
That boy.
He didn't even show up to welcome me.
Are you OK?
(2011 Opening Ceremony
of Guanghua University)
Slow down.
Be careful.
Thank you
Li Peng.
Be careful.
Watch the steps.
Watch out.
Ten minutes left.
Is everyone here?
They'll come.
(2011 Opening Ceremony
of Guanghua University)
Where is Qian Wei again?
By the way,
I bought a gift
for entering college.
The tour guide
recommended this to me
when I was traveling in Tibet.
And it cost me a lot.
The guide said
that you can reverse the situation
when you're at a low point
in your life
by twisting this little wheel.
How did you know that?
That's what he said.
You were ripped off again.
And don't keep saying things
like avoiding the low point of life.
Do you know Murphy's Law?
You don't want something to happen,
but it will still happen.
Besides,
I think
my life is very good now.
There's nothing I want to change.
No, don't.
Don't throw it.
Who's Murphy?
I don't know him.
Why should I trust him?
Look,
you will know
how important this little thing is
when the time comes.
You can ask me for it
when you need it.
But for my fat thumb
which can't wear it,
I wouldn't have given it to you.
I'll keep it for now.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Qian,
there are just five minutes
before the ceremony starts.
How about
taking your seats inside first?
- Okay.
No, no, no.
We'll go to hospital first.
Go to hospital?
It's you.
Not me.
What about me?
Last night, I dreamed
that you had acute leukemia.
So now I must take you
to hospital for a checkup.
What do you mean?
What's the matter with you?
What disease do I have?
You don't believe me, right?
Let me tell you,
I also dreamed
that you hid your private money
in your long johns.
And Mom's birthday present this year
is hidden in…
No, stop.
I'll take her to hospital.
This kid is ill.
Wait.
Mr. Qian.
Only five minutes left.
It's okay to have dreams.
But could you dream after the ceremony?
No.
The ceremony is just a formality.
It's not important.
My thing is urgent.
I've promised the head teacher
to hold the ceremony well.
I must keep my promise.
My mother is a doctor.
If
you need it,
I'll let her…
It's you who promised the head teacher.
I have nothing to do with it.
Go.
Let's go.
No, no.
We should go now.
You must go to hospital now.
Hey, you!
(Welcome 2011 freshmen!)
(Outpatient Department)
See? There's no big problem.
Don't be afraid.
But this indicator is a little high.
Have some grapes.
The Greek grape growers
grow Greek grapes.
Good.
So sour.
It's not.
Your Uncle Wang from next door
said that his daughter
brought him a box of
cherries.
American cherries.
Cherries
from America.
And?
He said that it was very sweet.
I said I wanted to try one.
He refused to give me any.
What a stingy man!
But his daughter is so great!
If you want some, just say it.
No need to speak in riddles.
No, I'm not.
I'll take the grapes away.
Hello.
(Cherry)
Is this 386 yuan per kg?
Yes.
That's "cheap".
Dad doesn't want to eat this.
He can have tomatoes.
Isn't it just 200 yuan?
Why was I being such a cheapskate then?
Before his death,
Dad had never eaten cherries.
Are you okay?
I'm not.
Can you lend me 500 yuan?
What? Five hundred?
I don't have 500 yuan.
I don't have that much money.
Your mom
will come back
in a while.
You can ask her.
I can't.
If I ask her for money,
she will ask
what's the use for it.
You borrow from me
and I will also ask you about its use.
It's clearly better to borrow from you.
Can you lend me some?
Come on.
I really don't have that much money.
Stop it.
We just met a few days ago.
Do I know you well?
It's okay.
We were strangers yesterday.
We are acquaintances today.
If you lend me the money,
we'll become good friends.
No way.
I don't want a friend
like you.
I really don't have money.
Come on.
Don't be like this.
I really need the money.
- I'll use it for a good purpose.
- No.
Look,
don't put your hands on me.
This is my money.
Besides,
it's okay that your parents
see you touching me.
But if my mom sees it,
what will she think of me?
Do you really refuse to lend it to me?
Okay.
If you don't lend me the money,
I'm really not sure
what your mother
will think of you.
I don't understand
what you just said.
I don't have that much money.
All I have…
Mr. Lu Xun, lend me some money.
Please.
Thank you.
My living allowance.
500, just 500.
If we really live to that age,
how happy we'll be!
Right.
How's it going?
Wei,
guess what the doctor said?
Anything wrong?
Nothing wrong.
That's nice.
Early checkup is useful.
Dad, this is for you.
Cherries imported from America.
Oh, dear.
Eat as much as you want.
Others have it.
You can also have it.
Good.
So expensive?
(American Cherry)
Wei,
several boxes of this can cost
your monthly living allowances.
Well, money doesn't matter.
What matters is that you are happy.
Right?
Yes, right.
Dad,
one more thing.
Could you quit the job
in that parts processing factory?
That workplace is so filthy.
And it's such a closed environment.
There must be
excessive chemicals inside.
It can lead to blood disease easily.
You've already reached
the age of retirement.
Just retire early.
How can I retire?
The company needs me.
Will the factory close down
if you retire?
Wei is right.
No one is as busy as you
at this age.
I want you to retire.
All right.
You're the boss.
I'll take your mother to dinner.
Let's celebrate.
Bye, Mr. and Mrs. Qian.
Goodbye.
We can have
Bread Soaked in Fish Head Soup.
Lu Xun.
Thank you for today.
You let my father do a full examination
and lent me the money.
I'll buy you dinner
Do you like hot-spicy pot,
spicy hot pot, or what?
Both okay.
It's up to you.
I,
don't want food.
I want the money.
And,
what's the cherry that you bought?
Five hundred yuan
for just two boxes.
It's not ordinary cheery.
It's imported from America.
What's more,
don't be so narrow-mined.
It's just some money.
I'll return it to you.
I really want to get on well with you
for the next four years.
During the four years,
how much money will you owe me?
I already regret
wasting so much time
with you.
And can you stop interrupting me
when I'm not finished yet?
If you
want to be a troublesome girl,
no problem
But don't get others involved,
especially me.
Do you understand?
Yes.
No matter in 2022
or in 2011,
this person
is just equally annoying.
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪