Hold all my calls.
♪ Boss Baby ♪
♪ I'm the Boss, Boss Baby, boss, boss
Boss Baby, boss, boss ♪
♪ Watch a itty-bitty kid get large ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ Stroller rolling
Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ I run this house, I rule this crib ♪
♪ Change my diaper, son, where's my bib? ♪
♪ Don't pacify, you just got to pay me ♪
- ♪ Who's in charge? ♪
- ♪ Me, the Boss Baby ♪
I'm the new CEO!
- [laughs]
- [cheering]
I'm the new CEO!
[baby] Bonuses for everyone! Whoo-hoo!
I'm the new CEO...
What are you people doing in my office?
Frederic Estes kidnapped
Turtleneck Superstar CEO Baby.
Yes!
I mean, obviously,
I'm also worried about her safety,
but don't you see the opportunity here?
Not really.
Leadership.
Every new CEO has to make a big splash,
seize the loyalty of his team.
What better way than a high-stakes
rescue operation?
[laughs]
What's this other one?
Nothing. It's just...
"To my baby brother." In your handwriting?
A congratulations note.
Templeton, I'm blushing.
Don't read it right now. It's for...
- You're quitting?
- No!
I told you, like, 20 minutes ago.
I already forgot!
- Why?
- It's all in the letter, okay?
But forget that for now.
We have to rescue Turtleneck.
After that,
you can read what I wrote and... Hey!
Resignation not accepted.
But I double-checked my spelling
and everything.
This is it, Templeton!
We're finally in charge.
This is where the real fun starts.
Did you know this company has a fleet
of fully-loaded baby assault vehicles?
- I didn't.
- You do now!
- Staci, put in a requisition.
- On it.
- Jimbo, show me your war face.
- [shrieking]
Let's rain down baby fury.
- I'm still quitting after this.
- [chuckles] Sure you are.
Now, how do we locate
a rotten syndicate of old people?
- With an old person...
- No!
[Templeton] Gigi!
[grunts] Templeton,
I'm Baby Corp's new CEO!
I can't go running for help
to our elderly enemies!
Gigi's our grandma.
And she'll know
where we can find Frederic.
[sighs] Just get the info.
Don't tell me where it comes from.
- It will be from Gigi! Oof!
- Ga-ga, goo-goo, cannot hear you.
- [Gigi] Tim!
- She's been turned! Take her out!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't realize you were there!
[giggling]
- How did the baby...?
- Wait. You're leaving today?
It's the End O' Summer.
Heading back home
right after the festival.
- But...
- [Boss coughing, mumbling]
Speaking of talking,
do you know where Frederic Estes is,
for no reason you should ask about?
Well, sure. He's at the festival
like everyone else.
He and his senior friends
even put together their own fun house.
Ha! What a hoot!
[door opens]
That has to be where
they're holding Turtleneck.
Your mom and dad are off rehearsing
for the big festival finale,
so I thought the rest of us
could go together.
- One last...
- Going ahead.
You catch up! Love you! Bye!
[bell dinging]
[gasps] I need backup!
Whoa! [thuds]
There it is: One big fat mousetrap.
- [grunts] What?
- You're killing me, man-baby.
Don't look straight in the camera.
Why is Hendershot filming us?
Leadership, Templeton.
I clawed my way to the top.
Now I show Baby Corp
what a real CEO looks like.
[Hendershot] And... put some mustard
on it this time.
Estes' fun house.
It's one big fat mousetrap.
But Baby Corp is a tiger,
and you can't catch a tiger
in a mousetrap.
- Great line!
- Great CEO!
He says I'm a tiger! [roars]
Ow! Quit it!
- Ready to have your baby minds blown?
- [baby] Yeah!
- How come he gets to look at the camera?
- Because I'm the boss, baby.
- [baby] Whoo-hoo!
- Roll in the heavy forces!
[tires screeching]
[giggles, sighs]
[engine revs]
Aw! How cute! They have baby rides!
Go get them, Staci! Yee-haw!
I've never said "yee-haw" before.
I love the new CEO me!
[Staci cackles]
Clear the geezers! Infantry, fire!
[explosions]
- It's half-off coupons!
- For what?
It doesn't matter!
Boom, baby.
[cheering]
This is great!
[Boss] Baby steps.
And watch your diapered backsides.
Never trust any place
that mixes old people and fun.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [gasps]
What the...?
[screams] I'm an old fogey!
What have they done to my baby face?
[crying]
Hug save!
- [camera shutters clicking]
- [screams]
I'm gonna die one day,
and I've never tried Thai food!
I've got to live!
[cries]
Shield your eyes
from the sagging decrepitude!
Keep moving!
Whoa! [gasps]
You wanted to show everybody
what a great leader you are. Well...
Good call, Templeton.
CEO says you go first!
[screaming, barking]
I meant you should go.
Then what's the point of being in charge?
Ugh, fine.
Leadership pose!
Oh, fart, poop, doodie!
[all screaming]
[both] No!
It just sliced through my shoe,
you babies!
[both grunt]
[all grunting]
[grunts]
[man's voice] Get off my lawn!
How is this a fun house? Ow!
Get off my lawn! Get off my lawn!
- Get off my lawn!
- Dodge like you're being audited!
- [all gasp]
- Right behind you, boss!
[screams, grunts]
I made boom-boom.
[man's voice] Get off my lawn!
Get off my lawn!
- [baby screams]
- [both gasp]
[Boss] Keep moving!
Your new CEO has everything under control!
- Get off my lawn!
- Boss, we got two exits!
Staci, Jimbo, peel right.
Templeton, Katja, we go left.
Hendershot! How's my voice? Too yelly?
You're focused on the ears
when you should be focused on the heart.
- Get off my lawn!
- Incoming!
- [grunts]
- Get off my lawn! Get off my lawn!
[both screaming, grunting]
[laughs]
Jim Dandy! Did I just bag two CEOs
for the price of one?
And I know just the ransom.
We're not paying you one Buffalo nickel.
No, you're gonna shut down Baby Corp.
- [all gasping]
- We're taking back the world's love.
Old people are the new babies.
[cooing, babbling]
That's disgusting, and you need to fire
your marketing department.
Googah Kai!
Yah!
- Googah Kai!
I don't know any baby karate!
Then use what you do know!
[yells, grunts]
[screams, grunts]
The camera makes me feel throw-uppy,
but I think we're winning!
[both] Yay!
Jimbo, Staci! Where are you?
It's the final fight!
- Got stuck in a mirror maze, sir.
- I'll ask this baby for directions.
[screams]
It was me again!
- Save me a shin kick.
- No promises. [gasps]
Peekaboo!
Let go of my brother, bathtub hands!
[grunts]
[belches]
[coughs] Ew! Gross little kid!
- Googah Kai!
- Whoa! [grunts]
I just did what I know.
Still quitting, read the letter.
Beebs, we rescued the CEO. We won!
Gimme the hero shot!
Welcome to the future, Baby Corp.
It tastes like mashed victory. Yee-haw!
[all] Yee-haw!
[clapping]
There you have it, Baby Corp,
your new CEO,
a gigantic, ridiculous fool.
Uh...
- Wha...?
- [Estes grunts]
Ma'am, you're working with the old people?
Working with old people? No.
[gasping]
No.
- [all scream]
- I am old people.
[spits] Eh?
Ew! Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew.
This whole time you've been
Turtleneck Superstar CE-Old Lady?
And she's my old lady!
Kissy, kissy!
[kissing, moaning]
[all retching]
We've been plotting this for years,
a simple two-part plan.
One, distract from the outside,
care of my sweet snoogle-mint Frederic.
[all screaming]
Meanwhile, part two,
I sow chaos on the inside.
If you solve the formula
for Stinkless Serum,
you get the job of CEO.
- [grunts]
- [teddy bear squeaks]
[screaming]
Bravo. You only made one mistake:
I did crack the formula
for Stinkless Serum,
a super weapon to change
the balance of love forever!
[both laughing]
Honestly, I expected more cowering.
Let me try it again.
- Stinkless Serum!
- Wait.
[sniffing] I recognize that one.
That's Tsunami Inferno,
our biggest failure!
It smells awful.
No, it... [screams]
Yes, it does!
Why would you lie about...
[gasps] Oh, no.
You never wanted us to re-crack
Stinkless Serum.
You were collecting
all the rotten, stinking failures.
Good baby.
An arsenal of stink
to be unleashed on babykind.
What did you call it, Boss Baby?
A super weapon to change
the balance of love forever.
[gasps] Every baby in town
is at this festival.
All we need is the perfect patsy
to deliver the stink...
little Timmy Templeton.
What? I don't work for you.
Do you?
[screams] Ragtime brainwashing!
- [playing ragtime tune]
- [whimpers, groans]
Let's play canasta!
Enjoy your End O' Summer Fest, Baby Corp.
You'll love the grand finale.
No!
[screaming, grunting]
One more charge.
We can crush these oldies.
Get up and fight!
- You're no CEO.
- What?
You did kind of win the job
in a fake contest.
So what? I'm a born leader!
- You played right into the enemy's hands!
- So did everybody else!
Then I guess nobody's our CEO. Ugh!
Looks like it's back to underground
"got your nose" fights for me.
You are the garbage baby.
- What do I do now?
- This is terrible!
- Talk about failure in leadership!
- No! Wait! Listen to me!
- Triplets!
- I'm not a tiger! [sobs]
Jimbo! Staci!
Sorry, boss, we're still stuck!
You're gonna be okay, Jimbo.
Thanks, Jimbo.
Hendershot.
You broke my camera, Beebs...
and my heart.
[sobbing]
[sighs]
Yee-haw.
[coughing] Oh, that's deep-fried! Ech!
Okay, Templeton, I'll bite.
Why quit the best job
any of us will ever have?
[Templeton's voice] "Dear baby brother,
I'm happy you got the job you wanted,
but I'm not sure
you really even know how to be a boss."
Junk mail.
[sighs]
"I saw you step on everyone's toes
just for a dumb promotion.
Seems like in business,
when times get tough,
everyone turns against each other.
- [gasps]
- But in a family,
tough times are when we come together.
I want you to be the best boss,
like Mom and Dad
are the best mom and dad.
I'd do anything for them
because I know they'd do anything for me.
So, maybe being in charge just means
people can always trust you to help
and you trust people to help you.
Love you, bye! Your brother, Tim."
He actually wrote that part down.
Tim! Timmy!
Tim! Timothy Templeton!
[Boss's voice] Paging Mrs. Templeton!
I have news about Tim!
What did you do with my grandsons,
you monster?
Easy! I'm on your side.
The baby's fine, but Tim's been swept up
by a rogue band of elderly.
Now, I know Frederic Estes is your friend.
Estes can suck a lime
if he's got my Timmy.
- No! [screaming]
- Where's Frederic, prune mouth?
I don't know, I swear! Please!
My bones are the texture of popcorn.
Keep questioning seniors.
We have to find Estes.
Oh, I'll find someone
who knows something
if I have to pry their dentures
out with a wrench.
Goldfarb, you old gossip, get over here!
- [panting]
- [grunting]
- [grunts]
- Where's my grandson?
Uh, what's a grandson? [chuckles]
I'd hate to see this hearing aid
run out of batteries.
No! I won't be able to hear gossip.
Oh, all right.
I don't know everything, but...
whatever they're planning with your boy,
it's gonna happen at the final high note.
Final high note?
The grand finale? Of course.
Look up here, everyone.
It's TV's Marsha Krinkle!
Hi. Okay, let's kick off the entertainment
with a warm welcome for our house band,
Cracklin' Bones O'Dell
- and the Cracktones!
- [man] Whoo-hoo!
[cheering]
[joints clicking]
I can't believe
we're finally playing a gig.
And with the Cracklin' Bones O'Dell!
I'm so starstruck.
[Marsha] And on guest vocals,
here to sing the international anthem
of old people,
which is apparently a thing,
Turtleneck Superstar Old Lady!
- [applause]
- [gasps]
Now, the oldies tell me
there's a special surprise
for our town's babies at the end,
so be sure to gather up all those adorable
little bundles of... whatever.
[cooing, giggling]
No, no, no, no, no!
Mrs. Templeton, the final high note!
- I know what it means!
- [Goldfarb panting]
Talk to me.
We only have until the last note
of this song to find Tim.
What?
I need to know right now, can I trust you?
This is a grandson we're talking about.
I'd do anything for them.
- Even the baby?
- Of course.
He drives me half out of my skull
sometimes,
- and I really don't get the suit and tie.
- It's called respect for the workplace!
Sorry. Continue.
But I'm his Gigi.
Push comes to shove, I'd take a mule kick
to the butt bone for that kid.
Then get over here and help me find Tim!
[band playing ballad]
♪ Every wrinkle tells a tale
Of wisdom, love and glory ♪
♪ Here's a butterscotch, child ♪
♪ Come listen to my story ♪
♪ From the beach-lined coast
of Marseilles ♪
♪ To the plains of Saskatchewan ♪
Wait a minute, what's she gonna rhyme
with Saskatchewan?
Gah! Keep your head in the game!
♪ You can find us on your highways ♪
- ♪ Driving slowly with our blinkers on ♪
- [Boss gasps]
Stinky Serum-soaked spit wads.
- [giggling]
- [Boss gasps]
One for every baby in town!
I found him.
Where is he?
No time. They're building to the finale.
[joints clicking]
I'll get Tim.
You make sure that song doesn't end
- before I get there.
- Huh?
Wait, how am I supposed to...?
Gigi Templeton, take it to the bridge!
- ♪ We, the... ♪
- [microphone feedback]
♪ Old people
Frequently cold people ♪
Would it kill you to turn up
the thermostat?
- Give me that, you old bag!
- [microphone feedback]
[both grunting]
[band playing rock music]
[Dad] This is so rock 'n' roll! Ah.
[growls]
[panting]
Dang babies! Hope you like stinkin'!
- [both grunting]
- [microphone feedback]
Back off!
- [Turtleneck grunts]
- [screams]
- Mom!
- Oh, my!
Let's hear that last verse,
sweet schmooky!
[ballad continues]
♪ We, the very aged... ♪
Last verse. The last note! [grunts]
Whoa! Oof!
Hold for the last note.
- [grunting]
- ♪ By the TV news enraged... ♪
Hey, boss, did you miss us?
I just shoved mirror Jimbos
until one fell over.
His memory will haunt me.
Jimbo, uppies!
♪ With aching hips
And midnight bathroom trips... ♪
Are you babies ready for the big surprise?
[giggling]
All new, flame-proof Plushythingy!
- [Estes cackles]
- [babies cooing]
[Estes] Open wide!
Behold your future!
♪ It looks... ♪
[inhales]
- ♪ Old ♪
- [gulping, grunts]
[giggling, cooing]
Why aren't these babies stinking
like garbage fondue?
- What in thunderation?
- [belches]
[hacks, coughs]
What gollumpus made the turtle burp?
[hacks, gasps]
I'm an old man again?
On the last day of summer?! Dang it!
Wait, did you just swallow
all those stinky spitballs?
Babies needed me.
And from what I hear,
being in charge means
people can always trust you to help.
You read my letter.
[belches]
[all gasping, retching]
That's right! Everyone shun
the repulsive pipsqueak!
All babies smell terrible!
Give your love to old people instea...
[grunts]
Stay away from my grandkids, Estes!
The baby smells fine.
[sniffs] Cajun Christmas!
It's like he farted a mummy!
But I love him anyway.
[kisses] Ugh!
[Boss belches, sighs]
[chupie zaps]
- [Templeton] Hey.
- Templeton, what...?
Tim told Baby Corp what you did.
I don't know if the Board is gonna make
you CEO or not.
But after you took a stinking like that?
Every baby in this company
will follow you anywhere.
Give that boss man a baby salute!
[giggling, applauding]
And we went hunting
for a special thank-you gift.
Original Stinkless Serum?
But Estes stole that days ago.
How did you...?
We made a covert switcherooni.
Tomorrow, we seek our vengeance.
Tonight, let us become... stinkless!
[both retch]
That wasn't stinkless.
[belching]
To Baby Corp.
[belches]
[Staci sniffs] Ah!
- There's that new baby smell.
- See you at the office after school?
You're not resigning?
From the company with the best boss
in the business? No way.
[footsteps approaching]
[both gasp]
Can I say goodbye
to my two favorite grandsons?
I'm really gonna miss you!
So, I don't know and I don't want to know.
Know what? Why would there be
anything to know? What? [chuckles]
No. And I thought I had a big imagination.
What I do know is,
if my grandsons are ever in trouble,
you can always trust your Gigi.
That goes for you, too, boss man.
[sniffs] What is that stench?
[scooter whirring]
More velocity! Escape is a soaring falcon.
- We must become its wings...
- [officer grunts]
You two are under arrest
for stinking up the whole darn town!
- [siren wailing]
- Last hours of freedom, Templeton.
Any final requests
for reckless, devil-may-care summer fun?
[Turtleneck] Can we get separate cells?
[Estes] Oh! Like you smell daisy fresh!
- [car doors close]
- Nah. This is good.
♪ Boss Baby ♪