[grunts]
Hold all my calls.
[giggling]
♪ Boss Baby ♪
♪ I'm the Boss, Boss Baby, boss, boss
Boss Baby, boss, boss ♪
♪ Watch a itty-bitty kid get large ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ Stroller rolling
Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ I run this house, I rule this crib ♪
♪ Change my diaper, son, where's my bib? ♪
♪ Don't pacify, you just got to pay me ♪
- ♪ Who's in charge? ♪
- ♪ Me, the Boss Baby ♪
[slurps]
[burps]
What?
Forgive me for hoping that
in our time together,
a hint of my refined style
might have rubbed off on...
[belches]
That was involuntary.
[laughs]
- That was amazing.
- [Mom] Ted! Let's go!
I don't like that look Maggie from HR
gives us when we're late!
Her human resources need some work,
if you ask me.
[laughing]
Human resources.
What?
Ah... choo!
Oh, my. Are you sure you're okay
to stay with the boys?
[hacking cough]
Please. I once pulled a 12-hour shift
at the mill
with walking pneumonia
and a hoof-shaped bruise on my buttock
from an unrelated fight
with a police horse. [coughing]
Please share none of these stories
with my children.
Ted, car!
If you need a nap,
number's on the fridge for our babysitter.
Marisol.
- [romantic music playing]
- [no audible dialogue]
Marisol.
Marisol? Magnificent idea, Templeton!
I was hoping to hit the office
for that presentation
on Baby Corp hair removal cream.
We've been testing it on worker baby Chip.
Don't parents want their babies
to grow hair?
Mmm... not on their backs.
So there it is. Gigi goes down sick,
you spend the day
with your beloved Marisol,
and I attend my presentation.
Success explosion! Boom!
Look at that. Wins everywhere.
You had me at "Marisol."
How do we make this happen?
[Gigi] Ah-choo!
Ah-choo! [coughing]
Psychological warfare.
Really, it's not that bad.
[hacking]
[whoops, sneezes]
- I don't need to lie down. [coughs]
- Shh.
Relax... sideways.
Just a spoonful of castor oil and...
[snores]
Go time.
[inhales]
[whimpers]
[knuckles pop]
[groans]
- Just do it!
- [yelps]
Hi, Mrs. Marisol's mom?
This is Timothy Templeton.
Yeah, your daughter knew me as Tim,
but I go by Timothy now.
So, is Marisol free
to babysit me and my brother
today and tomorrow and forever?
Play it cool, kid. Close the deal!
She's booked today? And tomorrow?
And when you say forever,
does that mean...?
No, it's not a problem. Bye!
[panting]
Breathe, Templeton.
Tell you what, Gigi's asleep anyway.
Just come to the office with me.
You can copy your face.
Squishy-face copies!
Or any body part, dealer's choice.
Wipe it down when you're done.
What did I do wrong?
- [groans]
- [pops]
Forget it, Templeton.
Today's a hard lesson, but a good one.
Business is business.
- Don't get personal.
- [doorbell rings]
[gasps]
I knew your mom was a big fat liar!
Uh...
I brought soup?
For your grandmother.
How did you know she was sick?
[chuckles] It's from one of her adorable
friends. I'm sitting him right now.
My Gigi is friends with a baby? [gasps]
Are you sitting another big kid?
Is his name Tim?
[Marisol laughs]
Of course not!
I don't sit babies or kids anymore.
- [horn beeps]
- Enough jib-jab!
- [screams]
- Old people.
We've got 30 minutes left on the clock.
Be right there, Mr. Estes!
Senior sitting.
The elderly hire me to hang out with them.
Booked me solid for the whole summer.
Neat, huh?
Does "neat" mean crazy?
What about us kids?
Old people are, like, half the work
and pay twice as much.
A no-brainer from a business standpoint.
The more I make,
the more I can invest
and grow my business in the future.
Kids are great, but right now is all
about maximizing expansion capital.
Gotta chase that revenue stream.
[chuckles]
- I'm probably boring the heck out of you.
- Oof!
[gasps]
Business is business.
Anyway, time to scoot Mr. Estes back
to the Senior Center,
and then it's Mrs. Fardy all afternoon.
I'll probably never see you again, so...
bye, boys!
Stay in school!
[whirring]
Betrayal!
And with Estes? Oh, it burns.
Oh, I feel like my stomach
just punched me in the stomach.
Wait. Why are you so angry?
What happened to not
taking business personally?
How dare you! I would never!
This is business!
Marisol's an industry trendsetter.
If she's abandoning babies for old folks,
others will follow.
[beeping]
[Hendershot] Ooh! You called it, Beebs.
- It's bad.
- How bad?
Worst thing since that shag carpet
on Chip's back. [grunts]
Town's losing babysitters left and right.
Copies are done.
Why do you need copies of two pasty
white circles squished against the gla...
- Oh, come on, man.
- It's my butt.
[Superstar CEO] Boss Baby!
Turtleneck Superstar CEO Baby!
Uh, allow me to introduce you
to my brother.
May the light within me
see and honor the light within you.
[speaks Japanese] Who farted?
What happens to babies
when there are no sitters of babies?
- Already on this one.
- They have to go with Mommy and Daddy.
Babies at fancy restaurants.
Fussing through the opera.
At Jazzercise classes.
"Jazzercise"?
- Okay, you know jazz?
- Yes.
- And you know exercise?
♪ Ooh-ah-hh...! ♪
Public meltdowns.
Parental stress levels
at an all-time high.
Fix now!
Namaste.
- More info on Jazzercise.
- [shoes squeaking]
[Boss Baby]
Marisol's the alpha sitter in town.
Everything rests
on getting her back on our side.
- So, we head to Mrs. Fardy's house.
- [team chuckling]
- What's so funny about Mrs. Fardy?
- [laughing]
Fardy. Fardy. Fardy.
Am I mispronouncing it?
[all laughing]
Oh.
F-A-R-D-Y, people.
Get your minds out of your diapers.
Once at "Far-dee's" house,
Templeton infiltrates Marisol's business.
Lucky devil.
And I convince her that kids and babies
are where the biz is at.
My convincers are primed and ready, sir!
Always love that gung-ho,
morality-free spirit, Stace,
but Templeton and I
are handling the Marisol side.
So, what do we do?
Baby love is tanking.
Mommies and daddies need someone
to watch their wee ones.
But we don't have any babysitters.
Sure we do!
- [snoring]
- She just won't know she's babysitting.
Field team takes care of the babies.
Gigi's your cover.
Babysitting babies. On it, sir!
- Let's go get our babysitter back.
- Yes!
[cooing]
Still no sitters?
But we've got Jazzercise in ten minutes!
[phone rings]
[woman] Hello.
Hi! It's Sandy Burgess,
your very real adult neighbor.
Yeah. I dropped my child off
with the Templeton lady
on my way to the taxes doctor,
and she wanted me to spread the word
that all babies are welcome here.
Now, I understand
if this all seems unusual, but...
- Be there in five! No take-backs!
- [line clicks]
Oh! [chuckles]
Yo, Triplets, how's our fakey-sitter?
Behold our masterpiece, the Mona Sleepsa.
"I'm a responsible adult!"
"Bring me your babies!"
Cool shades!
This is gonna be a cakewalk!
I'll be in your ear the whole time.
Say exactly what I tell you.
I've got my own talking style.
And that's great, but this is business.
Marisol and I understand each other...
as professionals.
You're a baby.
She doesn't understand you at all.
I'm charming and fun to be around,
so I'm gonna work from there.
- Templeton!
- [doorbell rings]
Tim?
Stellar response time. So professional!
Oh! Business, business, business!
- What are you doing here?
- According to findings,
90% of parents are comfortable...
I like your hair today.
I'm here to be your appendix!
- Apprentice!
- Apprentice.
Last time I sat for you...
I'm a different man now.
I want to learn how to be a babysitter,
to learn from the best.
I want to be around the best,
for as long as it takes.
Every day is okay with me!
Sorry. I don't need a helper, Tim.
Tell her time management
is a huge component
- of a successful business!
- Uh...
You can take half of her busy work!
I can do the busy stuff!
Like wiping spills or making a sandwich.
Bread is my specialty.
That's double the time she'll have
to foster relationships
that lead to repeat business.
That's double the time she'll have
to foster relationships
that lead to repeat business.
You. All the "she's" are "you's."
Come on in.
Whew.
This is Tim, Mrs. Fardy.
He'll be helping me today.
Touch my good china,
and I'll gut you like a catfish!
Where's my sandwich?
Let's see how much time
you can actually save me.
- Bread!
- Bread launch!
- Mustard!
- Fire mustard cannons!
Turkey, cheese, lettuce, tomato!
Pickle bomb! [mimics explosion]
[laughs] Wow, that was fun.
And Mrs. Fardy's lunch
is ready in half the time!
Some people call it time management.
I call it "Tim management."
[Marisol] Efficient and clever.
Focus on the mission, Templeton.
- Bring Marisol back to babies.
- Uh-huh.
Sure.
- [static hisses]
- Hello. Hello!
- [doorbell rings]
- Who could that be now?
[giggles]
Tim!
Did you leave your baby brother outside?
Uh, I thought he'd be okay in the shade?
You want to learn to be a sitter?
Rule one: Babies aren't dogs.
I'm going to take Mrs. Fardy
her sandwich.
Try not to endanger your brother
while I'm gone.
What are you doing in here?
This isn't part of the plan!
Neither was ditching your earpiece!
Change of plans, divide and conquer.
How about you divide and stay out there!
We need you in good with Marisol.
Show how attentive you are
with the old raisin!
Meanwhile, I'll be extra cute
to remind Marisol
how fun it is sitting adorable,
intelligent, and powerful babies.
- Strictly for business?
- Of course. Why else?
This is a chore.
You're getting the prize
with old Fardy, believe me.
Mission, Templeton. Focus.
[triplets cooing]
Oh, she's making friends already.
And they all look so happy.
Thanks for doing such a great job, ma'am.
[Staci] Anytime. Have a great night.
Now get out. I mean, bye!
Like I said, cakewalk!
- [man on TV] Clambake!
- [audience laughs]
- Nuh-uh.
- [coins clattering]
- No.
- ♪ Solve some space crimes... ♪
No.
- [speaks Spanish]
- [remote clicks]
I'm Marsha Krinkle, and that's what passes
for news in this hick town.
She should really watch that attitude.
A positive spin
means more advertising dollars.
[giggling]
- [Marisol] I gotcha!
- [growls]
[coos]
Oh, my gosh, did your baby brother
just wave at you?
He is so cute!
Hey, Marisol, want to make
another sandwich?
Remember how fun that was?
[mimics explosion]
That was the pickle. Ow!
What... ma'am?
If you're gonna make noises,
crank up the Krinkle!
Sorry, Mrs. Fardy. Let me help with that.
[Marsha] ...the town looks forward
to its Annual End O' Summerfest...
Staci, how's your end?
Uh, getting a little full,
but we're handling it.
- [doorbell rings]
- Come in!
- Here's Scooter!
- Thanks, bye!
[giggles]
- [gasps] It's...
- Scooter Buskie!
[squeals]
Triplets! All six eyes on Buskie! Now!
[babies grunt]
- [burps, giggles]
- Good boy.
[burps] Ooh! There it is.
If you're done kissing that girl
with your eyeballs,
I think I burped out some mustard
on my upper lip.
[smacks]
You need help cleaning up, Mrs. Fardy?
No, I don't need help,
I just like getting my money's worth.
Allow me, Marisol.
Thanks, Tim.
- [burps]
- What a good burp!
It's like gas
was your tummy's competition,
but you cornered the market.
[giggles]
I know that look. That's my look!
That's a lot of gas.
Probably needs a diaper change.
- Be right back!
- What?
[grunts]
You fell in like with her!
What? Don't be absurd, man!
I saw you. You were all,
"Ooh, no one burps me like you, Marisol!"
And that hug!
Burp me again, Marisol, hug me again!"
You said business wasn't supposed
to get personal. Well, now it is!
Don't go down that road, Templeton!
You're forgetting what's at stake.
If we can't get her back,
we might lose her to old people, forever!
- [both growl]
- Mrs. Fardy wants some pudding.
Just don't give her anything else
with mustard!
I know, right? "Burp!" [laughing]
- [laughing]
- [giggling]
[Marisol] Aw!
Can you handle the pudding
while I tend to this little cutie?
Good to have you helping today, Tim.
Don't forget to peel the skin off the top
of the pudding.
- She likes the skin on the side.
- [cooing]
[growls]
[Marisol] Whoo!
The amazing Bebé Volador!
- [mimics airplane engine]
- [Boss Baby squeals]
[Marisol chuckles]
Ah-whoosh! Here comes the airplane.
[laughing]
I bet this is how the Queen of England
eats pudding!
Aw, Tim, that's so sweet!
Yep, we're just a couple of little cuties
over here.
Whoosh! Here's the airplane again!
- [cooing]
- Whoo! I'm gonna get ya!
- [Marisol] Who's gonna get that baby?
- All right!
- [giggling]
- [laughs]
[Marisol] Oh, yeah, I gotcha!
Circle the runway.
I'm still working my chew!
You're getting it everywhere,
you little booger!
- Hey, I said I'm full.
- Tim!
But we were being cute.
Knock it off. Your brother's the cute one.
[growls]
[gasps]
[panting]
Ow!
[growls]
Ha, ha!
- Secure!
- [grunts]
Hold on!
[growling]
Yow! [grunts]
[Marisol] Hey! Boys!
What are you...? Enough. Enough!
[gasps]
You bet your heinie I'm deducting
cleaning costs from your tab!
My profit margins!
You boys just cost me business.
Line crossed.
- But the baby...
- You? Fired.
You? This is why I quit sitting babies.
Tim, take your brother and just go home.
Well, this day's a real turd bouquet.
Twenty years from now,
you'll have no one to blame but yourself
when you're toting your kid to the opera
because there's no one to watch him!
Future me hates the opera!
And everything was going great
until you got jealous and barged in.
- You weren't doing the business at hand.
- You weren't doing the personal at hand.
- That's not a real thing!
- You're not a real thing!
Stop slinging nonsense insults
I can't respond to logically!
[babbling]
[growls]
Oh, yeah, the babies.
[whimpering]
- [banging]
- [Scooter squeals]
[both gasp]
- [Tim wails]
- [Scooter screams]
[Gigi snoring]
[faint crashing]
- Jimbo? Staci?
- [Jimbo] Over here, boss!
The plan went awry.
[crashing]
Gigi could wake up any second.
I can't hear you
over the sound of baby love
cratering like a rogue meteor! [groans]
I never should have let things
get personal!
Feelings are your job.
Yes, they are.
I have an idea,
one that's both personal and businessal.
Grammatically incorrect,
but I'm intrigued.
- Two brothers.
- Two superpowers!
I have a gigantic heart.
I have a brilliant business mind!
And a stunning vocabulary
and elite cosmopolitan style.
You only get one power.
[Tim] Brothers, unite!
[both] We are TempleTron!
[Tim] Whoosh!
Let's get our babysitter back!
[snoring]
♪ Still duct-taped to the wall ♪
♪ Oh, no
We're still duct-taped to the wall ♪
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
[both] ♪ Heaven help our taped souls ♪
♪ We're duct-taped to the wall ♪
[doorbell rings]
I thought I told you...
Wait! Let me say something. Please.
If you come to our house right now,
no questions asked,
you'll get four hours of pay,
times 20 babies,
for about 20 minutes of work.
- Why are there 20 babies in your house?
- I said no questions asked.
Look, I'm with Mrs. Fardy right now.
To be honest, that's where the money is,
with old people.
It's just business.
Bye, Tim.
Real quick.
How many little brothers do you have?
Six.
Six? Whoa. Well, I just have the one.
But I know no matter
how big of a pain he is,
there's nothing more fun
than making him smile.
[giggles]
Sitting babies, Marisol.
That's what you were born to do.
It's more than just business,
it's personal.
Aww!
And again, there's a butt-ton
of money in it for you.
Business: boom.
Yo, Mrs. Fardy,
I'm taking an indefinite leave of absence
to explore a career realignment!
[Mrs. Fardy] No skin off my pudding!
You're gonna need your busy bag.
I'll get it. Appendix Tim is on fire!
Yeah!
- [Scooter squealing]
- [gasps]
El niño diablo.
[squeals]
Finally, a challenge worthy of my skill.
- Ready, Tim?
- More than ever.
Combine TempleTron and MarisolBot.
- Baby carrier!
- Engage!
[growls]
[squeals]
[wailing]
Snacks! Pacifiers! Bottles!
Soothing distractions laser.
Pew-pew-pew!
- Movie?
- Launch tape and play!
[woman on TV] ♪ Good night, stars
Good... ♪
Toss me scissors.
Engage warning of scissor safety!
Oh, yeah. Duh.
[babies cooing]
[snipping]
[moaning]
[mumbles] What's with all the babies?
It's me, Mrs. Templeton.
Marisol the babysitter. Remember?
You let us into the house.
There was a fire at the place
I was sitting, so we had to come here.
- You're a hero.
- [yawns]
That's so nice, cowboy man.
Ah-choo!
[snoring]
Thanks!
We'll give you a call to sit Scooter again
real soon!
You were right, Tim.
I was born to sit babies.
Sure, they've got weird smells too,
but at least I know why.
And you have a real knack
for this business.
You better call me when you're older,
we'll join forces.
Eighty-twenty split, of course.
[giggles]
Did you hear her say I was right?
And how what I said brought her back?
How I should call her when I'm older?
Did you hear that part?
[Marisol] Wait, hang on.
I almost forgot.
If your grandma's done with that soup,
can I get the container back?
It's Mr. Estes'.
I should tell him I'm out
of the senior-sitting business anyway.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of everything.
Singing telegram from Marisol Lopez-Lugo!
What the...? Well, then, spit out
your musical tomfoolery.
♪ Sorry no more senior-sitting ♪
♪ 'Cause Marisol is quitting ♪
♪ Here's her resignation letter ♪
♪ She's gone back to something better ♪
- What?
- [squeals]
[yelling]
- [Tim] Thank you for the soup!
- [babbling]
Babies!
[theme song playing]
♪ Boss Baby ♪