Hold all my calls.
♪ Boss Baby ♪
♪ I'm the Boss, Boss Baby, boss, boss
Boss Baby, boss, boss ♪
♪ Watch a itty-bitty kid get large ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ Stroller rolling
Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ I'm the big Boss Baby in charge ♪
♪ I run this house, I rule this crib ♪
♪ Change my diaper, son, where's my bib? ♪
♪ Don't pacify, you just got to pay me ♪
- ♪ Who's in charge? ♪
- ♪ Me, the Boss Baby ♪
[Boss Baby cooing]
[grunting]
Die! Dead!
And that is the story of my career
as of 30 minutes ago,
when I allowed Frederic Estes to steal
Baby Corp's only vial of Stinkless Serum!
Poor little metaphor!
So, now we have maybe 15 minutes
to come up with a foolproof plan
to keep Turtleneck Superstar CEO Baby
from firing me.
No wrong answers. Jimbo.
Apology hugs?
Wrong answer! Staci.
I always keep a Plan "B" in my backpack.
It's spiders!
Oh, what? So you release them
into Baby Corp
and I squash them, looking like a hero?
Why would you kill my babies?
[growls] Templeton!
Sometimes when I mess up
with Mom and Dad,
I do something nice to show I'm sorry,
like extra chores or...
Brilliant, Templeton! Stop talking!
I can see the plan now!
Is that Boss Baby up there performing
unselfish service for this company?
Please, Templeton,
I don't want recognition.
Doing good is its own reward.
What a virtuous example!
Baby Corp is lucky to have him,
and should never consider firing him.
Hello, work associates.
Who would like to see my new trampoline?
- What?
- How delightful! I will be right down.
Oh, no! He's slipping
off the window washing platform!
- [babies gasping]
- [Boss] That is an accurate description
of what is happening.
- [gasping continues]
- [Jimbo] Boss Baby, no!
- [glass shatters]
- [screaming]
How could such a terrible tragedy
have occurred?
It no longer matters
what Boss Baby did wrong.
Let us mourn him
in traditional baby style.
[crying]
Wah, wah, wah.
Then I wait three weeks,
show up with a few bandages,
and everyone's so glad to see me,
all is forgiven.
Ooh! Great plan, Tim.
That was nothing like my plan.
Yeah, we plussed it in the meeting.
My career's on the line, Templeton.
You in or out?
- We're brothers. Of course I'm in.
- [Mom] Boys!
Your dad and I were wondering
if you could keep all the screaming down.
Um, no one's screaming, Mom.
Well, you're about to be, from excitement,
for end-of-summer
inside-the-house mini golf!
[screaming]
Your dad called dibs
on the front hallway for his hole.
Gigantic rapids.
Honey, do we any bigger canoes?
And I'm cooking up a par seven nightmare
in the kitchen,
so whatever hole you're designing,
challenge me!
Oh, I got your challenge: Magma Madness,
featuring vinegar
and baking soda volcanic explosions
- that will crush your golf ball!
- [clattering]
But, um, first, I'll need time
to let the baby help.
It is his first family mini golf.
We'll build Magma Madness together.
Probably take us a while,
don't check on us.
Why would you? What? Just mini golf stuff.
Aw!
What a good big brother.
Yes, I am.
Tell me this is gonna be quick.
I'm a business baby.
I'll tell you whatever you wanna hear.
Let's do this!
[Templeton] Add vinegar. Baking soda.
Mix 'em up, and I can make it
look like you were so terrified,
your brain exploded.
- [imitates explosion]
- Ooh!
You're suddenly way
too into my fake death.
Whatever gets me back to mini golf.
[elevator dings]
Brain-splosion is cooking.
Just give it two minutes
to build pressure, and...
Babies of Baby Corp!
[gasps] Too late!
She's announcing my firing!
- Templeton, abort!
- But I already did the... [whimpers]
Plan "B." Spider babies!
Crisis! Our intel indicates Frederic Estes
and the Consortium of Ancients
are plotting something big
for tomorrow's local End o' Summer Fest.
Ugh!
We're already late for family mini golf,
and now Estes
wants to ruin the town carnival!
What is happening to my end o' summer?
Inconceivable as it might seem,
we must assume our enemies have decoded
the formula for Stinkless Serum.
- Oh, no! Stinkless Serum!
- Oh, no!
- That belongs to us!
- Already?
Sir, if old people get rid
of their bad smells
and babies still stink,
we're gonna get crushed
on the love charts!
That was gonna be our secret weapon!
How did old people even get it?
Using the stolen vial
that was supposed to be guarded
by our VP of Field Operations, Boss Baby.
- He's over there. You may frown at him.
- [all growling]
Solution: If old people plan to unveil
their own Stinkless Serum tomorrow,
we must make today our tomorrow.
- [all] Huh?
- Explanation:
We are re-cracking
Stinkless Serum ourselves, today.
All of you have been transferred
to Research and Development
as of when I finish this sentence.
There. Done.
[whirring]
[flies buzzing]
Drool stains. Sweaty little baby booties.
Spit-up.
In total, eight bad baby smells.
Baby fatty roll crust?
That's a Category Five baby odor,
weapons grade.
Your assignment:
Find a formula that will unstink them all.
So we're supposed to become experts
in molecular chemistry by 5:00 p.m.?
[Turtleneck] And for those of you
worried about mastering
molecular chemistry by 5:00 p.m.,
allow me to sweeten the pot.
Forget about who you are, where you are,
or what you've done to help
or hurt Baby Corp.
If you solve the formula
for Stinkless Serum,
you get the job of CEO.
[gasps] Ah!
- I gotta crack that formula!
- CEO!
I am so gonna crack that formula!
Boss, you could do it!
5:00 p.m.? I can't take that long.
I'll miss mini golf.
Forget 5:00 p.m. With my desperation
and your chemistry skills,
we'll have the serum cracked
in an hour, tops.
What chemistry skills?
You made that vinegar-baking soda thing
that was supposed to go off in two min...
- [explosion]
- [baby screams]
Somebody's brain exploded!
- [whimpers]
- [Templeton chuckles]
Oh, yeah. I'm awesome.
Heads up: With the CEO job on the line,
this place is about to get nuts.
Backstabbing, sabotage,
alliances and betrayals.
As of right now, no one is trustworthy,
not even you two.
- What? Shame on me!
- [Staci giggles]
Yeah, I'm pretty much capable of anything.
You want me to use my dark powers
in your unholy service?
- Yes, please.
- Cool.
Hey, come on. You don't want to win dirty.
[Staci grumbling]
I thought you were in a hurry
to get back for tiny golf.
I am. But if I'm helping with this,
we do it my way.
Your way?
- Or should I say, the way of...
- [thunder crashes]
Dr. Baron Von Science Fair...
- the Third!
There's my mad chemist.
Bring me your smelliest challenge.
We will fight its bad smells
with a concoction of good smells,
and science away the stink. [cackles]
Stanky Blankie!
Ground cinnamon,
plus tropical fruit gummi ducks!
[cackles]
[sniffing]
- [retching]
- [Staci] Mm-mm.
Bring me your second smelliest challenge!
[Jimbo] Goopy chupie!
Fresh popcorn, plus those markers
that smell like hot dogs!
[giggles, cackles]
[sniffs, shudders]
It makes me want to cry and barf
and go doody all at once!
[Boss grunts]
We're getting nowhere!
Your concoctions smell like wet dogs
and Southern dumpsters!
Keep cracking, Baby Corp.
Cast out your smelly missteps
and point your noses achievement-ward!
You're right.
We'd have to be mad to continue!
[cackles]
Again!
Fresh-baked bread!
Candles from that store at the mall!
- Ginger ale burps!
- [belches]
Behold my creation: Werewolf Hot Rod!
Uh, Werewolf Hot Rod?
Every invention works better
with a cool name.
That's a mad science fact.
Now put it to the test!
[cackles]
[flies buzzing]
- [dings]
- [Boss gasps]
- Yes!
[buzzer blares]
Werewolf Hot Rod!
It destinkified drool stains and spit-up!
- That's two bad smells down!
- [monitor beeping]
- [baby 1] What? No!
- [baby 2] No!
- Boss Baby got two already!
- But...!
Nothing to see, people!
Eyes on your own work! Come on!
- Darn it!
- Why "darn it"?
You've cracked two out of eight
bad smells already.
I thought we'd be done by now.
This is gonna take forever!
You're on a roll, Dr. Baron.
- Just keep your head in the game.
- Don't say "game!"
I'm trying not to think
about the mini golf game back at home,
and now I'm thinking about
the mini golf game back at home.
Hoo-hoo! I solved spit-up smell!
Look out, CEO job, I'm coming for you!
The others are catching up.
Faster, Templeton!
Think, think! We need a hole in one.
Ugh! I can't stop thinking
about mini golf!
You gotta unleash me, sir.
I can slow down the competition
like molasses.
Sorry, I meant with molasses.
Or spider backpack.
Just so you know,
that option's still on the table.
Hey! I said we don't have to win dirty.
But I really wanna!
Jimbo can handle mixing
Tim's science junk by himself.
Don't make me!
I already got werewolf smell
all over my fingers, and it's scaring me!
Everybody calm down.
Staci, you know
I love your twisted handiwork,
but Templeton says he's got this.
Go make a supply run. Cool down.
Fine!
Jimbo, let's hose that werewolf stink
off your hands.
Yay!
[sniffs, screams]
- Templeton.
- Ten-minute golf break?
- Sure.
- Yes!
If you'll solve one more smell for me
before you go.
Deal!
[Jimbo mumbles]
[Chip] Ah, come on!
You're killing me, spit-up!
- Worker Baby Chip, right? What's wrong?
- [sniffs]
Just can't seem to un-stink
the grossed-out bib.
[yells]
My serum works on the booties,
the sour milk bottle...
You cracked sour milk bottle?
Oh, yeah, that one was tough.
But I hear you solved the drool stains.
[chuckles] Yeah. Now, that one was... Wait.
If I've got drool stain beat,
- and you've got sour milk...
- Swap formulas?
Nuh-uh!
I don't want to give your team
an advantage
when you're just a putt away
from the winning shot.
[echoing] Putt away! Winning shot!
Putt away! Winning shot!
Mini golf.
We have to swap formula secrets.
It would help both of us.
That's fair, right?
That should fix sour milk for you.
And there's your drool-proof solution.
Oh, and real quick,
can I borrow your stinkiest formula?
This one smells like asparagus farts!
Perfect! Finally, it's tee time for Tim!
What's this?
The solution for sour milk. Golf break!
Send me three beeps on the baby monitor
if you have an emergency!
- You boys good to golf? Tim?
- [toilet flushes]
- [parents groaning]
- Don't go in there!
Bad asparagus sickness.
Wait. I haven't bought any asparagus
since... [gasps] That explains so much!
Your mom and I are ready to putt
whenever you are!
- How's Magma Madness?
- Fine. Baby's sleeping.
We shouldn't talk about it anymore.
It might wake him.
Can we golf a different hole
while we're waiting?
Oh, well, sure,
if you think you're ready to face...
the Labyrinth of Red-Footed Death!
If you can sink it in the red shoe
in less than three putts,
you get double dessert for a week.
Triple desserts if I sink it in two.
[chuckles] It's on!
[clinking]
- Yes!
- One more putt to hit the red shoe.
Triple desserts on the line.
To the victor, fudgy glory.
Will Tim Templeton's parents be dealing
with bedtime hyperactivity all week?
[Tim sighs]
- [baby monitor chiming]
- [gasps]
What's that beeping?
One of my toys is out of batteries.
Don't worry about it.
- [chiming continues]
- [growls]
- Whoops!
- [clattering]
Shoot! That leads downstairs.
I'm gonna have to go find that ball
in the basement.
I might be a while, but don't come
help me. This is my responsibility! Bye!
Way to play with honor, son!
I was one putt away from triple desserts!
This better be important.
Ugh! What's that smell?
- That's the stink of betrayal!
- What?
That formula didn't solve sour milk!
Expired cottage cheese, plus clam juice?
Who thought that was gonna work?
- But I traded with...
- Chip, of all babies?
Chip who steals copy machines?
I told you we couldn't trust anyone,
but most of all, never trust a Chip!
I did it! De-stunked another one!
Sour milk, spit-up, sweaty baby booties,
and drool stains!
[monitor beeping]
- [baby 1] Drool stains?
- [baby 2] Impossible! How did he get that?
Whoa!
Four down, four to go.
Sniff my inevitable victory, loser babies!
[Turtleneck] Bravo, Chip!
[sniffing]
Do I smell a future CEO?
[chuckles]
Not yet. Keep working, babies.
We had a deal! It was fair!
Don't cry over sour milk! [chuckles]
I tried to warn you, Templeton.
You're in the corporate jungle now.
The only thing you can trust
is your own success,
and even that can stab you in the back.
Try it, Success!
[both sigh]
Don't feel too bad.
I'm sure your back wasn't the first one
stabbed today, and it won't be the last.
Chief Exec! Chief Exec! Chief... Hey!
Chip, you rot! All your work was mine!
We had an alliance, bro!
Since when are you alliance buddies
with Chip?
I thought we were working together.
Not cool, Amal!
- [Amal] See? It wasn't just me!
- [Chip] Don't blame me for everything!
[all arguing]
It has begun.
[panting]
Boss Baby! My partners all betrayed me,
but they didn't take my notes.
- Maybe you and I could form an...
- No! Scat! Get out of here, Simmons!
We're still high up on the leaderboard,
and all the corporate zombies
are gonna want a piece of our brains.
Don't let them eat my shot at being CEO.
Templeton, double time
on the stinkless chemistry.
And get me back to mini golf.
Staci, take Jimbo with you.
- The moment has come.
- [Staci cackles]
[Jimbo gasps]
Wait. What is Staci...?
Just making sure you and I
can work without interference.
Keep them fighting, keep them panicked.
Just keep them away from the Boss and Tim.
- Come on, now! We had an agreement.
- You started it!
- How could you?
- [blows raspberry]
Staci. Hey. I see Double B's
riding second right behind Chip.
I'm thinking,
if your team partnered up with me...
No! Your team and me!
[snaps fingers]
[gasping]
[gasps] Chip's stealing your work again?
What? I did not! But I totally would.
Eat chemistry, Chip!
[grunting]
- [Templeton] Yes! We got three more!
- [monitor beeping]
What? Boss Baby's team solved
Dirty Diaper and Stanky Blankie?
I am still stuck on my second stink!
I must know his secrets!
Mad Dog Phil smells an opportunity
to piggyback on others' success!
[gasps]
They're hungry for ideas,
and have none of their own!
It's a corporate zombie invasion!
[both gasp]
[all groaning, snarling]
How do we stop them?
What? All of you want me to sabotage
the hard work of Security Baby Katja?
I will teach you the price of betrayal!
[all gasping]
Uncle's breath!
[retching]
I claim all your research
as the spoils of war!
- Hey!
- No fair!
You just made the mad dog rabid!
[howls]
[screaming]
[panting] Ha!
[grunts]
- [roars] I'm angry!
- [gasps]
[grunts]
[yells]
- [yelling]
- [whimpering]
- [grunts]
- [teddy bear squeaks]
[all yelling]
Are you sure you want to win like this?
Trust me,
it'll all be worth it once I'm CEO.
It's been too long.
I need to check in at mini golf,
and you should too.
It's the final 40 minutes.
Everything's on the line.
And Mom and Dad aren't going to believe
you're napping forever.
I'm telling you, we need to do this.
Do you not even trust me anymore?
[sighs] Five minutes.
Whatever we need to do,
you get us back here, ASAP.
- [Mom] There you two are!
- [baby coos]
Did-did you not work
on your golf holes at all?
I guess we were too busy playing.
Well, Gigantic Rapids is ready to swing.
Come on, grab your club.
We'll do Magma Madness later.
Is it a long course?
[chuckles] If I know your dad,
it's gonna be brutal.
The Gator Moat of Croco-Death alone
is a solid 20 minutes.
I rented a real iguana.
Fair warning, he's a biter.
What if I only have five minutes?
[laughs]
You're a kid. You've got nothing
but free time. Let's golf!
[growls]
Mom, Dad.
- I... I don't want to play mini golf.
- [Dad] What?
I thought you loved it.
I do love spending time with you guys.
And I know you both love mini golf.
But I guess maybe I outgrew it.
Sorry, Tim. I wish you'd have told us.
Okay. No more inside-the-house mini golf.
I guess we'll find other traditions.
Thank you, Templeton.
You're the one person
I can always count on.
I told them I hated mini golf.
I love mini golf!
- Templeton, I... I didn't intend to...
- Let's go crack your stupid serum,
so I never have to think
about this day again.
[whimpering]
[babies shouting]
[timer beeping]
Pencils down. No time to test it.
What do we call this one?
Golf Slayer.
Templeton.
It's no inside-the-house family mini golf,
but it's the best I can do.
Come on, I guarantee you a hole in one.
[Boss] Boom, baby.
I hope you get the job.
This day was a rollercoaster ride,
right down to the fear, the adrenaline,
and the flying chunks of goop everywhere.
But my fears have been allayed
and my hopes rewarded.
I am over the moon with excitement,
bursting at the seams because Baby Corp
once more has its Stinkless Serum!
- No way!
- [all gasping]
[baby] Amazing!
Do you think it was us? No, probably not.
Impossible. Maybe? Gah!
Just spill it!
Congratulations to our winner,
the next CEO of Baby Corp...
Boss Baby!
Boss! You're the boss, Boss Baby!
I'm the CEO?
- I'm the CEO! [laughs]
- [cheering]
I did it!
- I'm happy you got what you wanted.
- [laughter continues]
[Turtleneck] Celebrate today, Boss Baby!
We'll make it official
with the Board of Directors tomorrow.
[cheering continues]
Sorry, buddy. You know it's my nature.
Hey, I respect the game.
- You're not partying with us?
- I had to write a letter to my brother.
- Want me to give it to him?
- Nah.
I'll just leave it
on his new CEO desk for tomorrow.
Don't want to step on his big day.
- You're a good brother, Tim.
- Thanks.
It's been fun working with you, Jimbo.
Maybe I'll see you around.
- Huh? Where are you going?
- I'm quitting the field team.
What?
Hello? Miss, um, Turtleneck Superstar CEO
Still-For-Now Baby?
I'm just leaving something for my brother
to read when he moves in.
Huh?
Intervention! [yells]
You are not quitting our field team!
We don't accept this letter!
That's not my letter.
It was already on the CEO's desk.
"Come and get her. X-O-X-O..."
[gasps] "Fred"!
I think Estes kidnapped Turtleneck!
But what does it mean?
It means war.
Yeah! [laughs]
[sings tune]
Inappropriate for the moment.
Yes, I can see that now.
♪ Boss Baby ♪