[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 19]
You are now holding
10% of Evergreen's shares.
According to the original agreement,
I completed the task.
Now I want to quit.
Quit?
Would Mr. Xue let Qin Hebo
go to Mr. Gao's office
to steal the materials?
If he intends to
destroy Evergreen's reputation,
leaking the information of VIP customers
is the best way.
Are you going to ask An An
to stay there
and catch Qin Hebo with the goods?
I will be there myself.
Zhening.
I will go with you.
In fact,
you don't want it to be Qin Hebo,
do you?
Of course not.
If it were him,
all my good impressions of him
would be shattered.
Sisters.
Today I will recommend you
a mask.
The mask.
Right.
This pre-essence mask.
It works well and is affordable.
You…
It seems that he won't come.
Okay.
The goods you most look forward to
will be available soon.
Let's count down together.
Three.
Two.
Go.
Thank you.
I asked a friend of mine before,
if a person had done something bad,
could he get better?
You gave me the answer today.
Before you gave me
a list of weddings in May.
I owe you.
Today's text message
is to pay you back.
Shuangshuang.
Don't explain to me anymore.
I don't care about your explanation.
We met here.
It would be nice
to end here.
It's a good end.
Shuangshuang.
Let go.
Let me go.
Shuangshuang.
You asked me before,
if you stopped serving the devil,
would we still have a chance?
I really want to believe you.
I want to believe that
you are telling the truth.
But ask yourself
if you can make it?
Could you give up
what you have now?
Can you let go
of who you were?
If you can't even do this,
how can you ensure that
you can get better?
Nothing like this would happen.
About this…
I don't know how to explain.
Can you give me another chance?
What else can I do for you?
Qin Hebo.
Just because I like you,
I hurt my most important friend.
Because I like you,
I went bad.
I am already a bad person.
Liking you costs too much.
I don't want to go on anymore.
I do like you.
But I hate…
I hate myself being like this.
You are back.
What happened to you?
I have a stomachache.
I just went to the pharmacy.
That's okay.
Go back early to rest.
Go back early.
Hard work for you.
[Mr. Xue]
Sorry.
Last night,
it was me who told Qin Hebo.
Actually…
I'm a spy!
I don't know that Qin Hebo at all.
I lied before.
I'm doing this
because I want to steal something
from him.
I'm also a spy, actually.
What do you mean?
My purpose
is to take over the entire Evergreen Hotel.
Forget it.
Forget what I said.
I just wanted to give him
another chance
and I believed that
he could get better.
But…
Sorry, I am the one to blame.
I am sorry for you.
It's all over.
I'm afraid you will get hurt.
Shuangshuang.
There is a saying
goes that
why people make mistakes?
Because everyone makes mistakes.
This is why
a pencil comes with an eraser.
It has already happened.
Face it bravely.
Cheer up.
Give yourself a chance
to choose and change.
Think about it.
If you want to calm down,
it's understandable.
No problem.
But you have to think about
when you will be back.
Worth Or Not needs you.
Thank you, Qian.
Never say that between us.
Nobody's inside.
That girl went back home.
Mr. Sheng.
Qin Hebo submitted a letter
of resignation to the board of directors.
This is the resignation document
that the Personnel Dept.
needs you to sign.
Emily.
After I leave,
you could no longer stay in Evergreen.
I found a job for you,
and the salary and treatment
is no worse than here.
Can I still work with you?
I want to take a rest.
Work hard.
Let me pack things up for you.
I have nothing to pack up.
Just leave me alone.
Okay.
How about it?
Is Vice General Manager Qin
satisfied?
Thank you for your consideration.
By the way, Hebo.
Join the board of directors meeting later.
In the future,
we have to fight together.
I made it myself.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Why?
You want money?
The position of
the general manager of Evergreen?
Or Evergreen's shares?
I don't get it.
How much did Mr. Xue pay you?
You even ruined Meng's wedding.
Haven't you always regarded her
as your own sister?
Did you even pretend these?
I failed to live up to you
and Meng's feelings.
Sorry.
I just want an explanation.
I could forgive your past misdeeds.
I have nothing to explain.
I don't need your forgiveness either.
Say goodbye to Meng for me
I didn't tell her
about your deeds.
I don't want her to know
your true colors.
But starting today,
we are done.
Quite fair.
Qian.
I got you a glass of juice.
Thanks.
Are you still thinking about Shuangshuang?
How do you know?
You are not at your best all day long.
And you called Ai as Shuangshuang.
Right.
It's just…
I am uncomfortable
when she is not here.
I do miss her.
I know
you are just used to
Shuangshuang always by your side.
Her sudden departure
makes you feel uncomfortable.
But don't worry.
She just got caught in her emotions
and couldn't get out for a moment.
She will come back
after a while.
Mu Xiaoyan.
What happened to you today?
You are so considerate.
I am always like that.
But you never figured it out.
You are usually like this.
And this.
Really?
Well.
We have to believe that
Shuangshuang will definitely come back.
Hebo.
Come on.
Let's talk in the car.
Not necessary.
Let's talk here.
We don't have to hide.
In fact,
I have always admired you.
I believe that
as long as we join hands,
Evergreen will soon be ours.
But I didn't expect you
to give up such a bright future
and opportunity.
You let me down.
I promised to buy Evergreen for you
in order to return your favor.
Nothing else matters.
Maybe you forgot it.
When I failed to start a business,
I went to Lihe Capital for investment.
And I was rebuffed many times.
until one day…
[Meeting room]
Sorry.
It's okay.
Young man.
Are you sure
to enter with this?
I have a suit.
If you don't mind,
I can lend it to you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks so much.
Sorry to bother you.
How was the conversation going on?
They agreed to consider my plan.
Thank you for your clothes.
In fact, I noticed you for a long time.
You have been here for a month.
Normally, one would be dispirited
after being rebuffed once or twice.
But I found that
you are very persistent.
It's so rare.
Because I thought
they would like my plan.
Why do you think
they always reject you?
Sometimes
people need packaging.
Brat.
Would you like to
work at Lihe Capital?
Are you serious?
Yes.
Later you gave me a set of clothes
and a work opportunity.
I was really grateful.
But compared to what you gave me,
I may lose more now.
I am leaving.
Shuangshuang
likes Qin Hebo so much.
That's why she informed him.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Qin Hebo left Evergreen.
Do you need me there?
It's okay. Don't worry about me.
Well.
Those with different values
cannot be forced to be friends.
Maybe his departure
is good for both of you.
Yes, I got it.
Although Qin Hebo left Evergreen,
Lihe Capital
has now penetrated into Evergreen.
I guess they will soon
send a shareholder representative
to Evergreen.
The next opponent
is coming soon.
You can just
roll with the punches.
If husband and wife work together,
there would be infinite power.
Who is your wife?
Qian.
Here comes customer analysis data
of this week.
Okay, let me check.
There is a user
called Lele's Dad.
It should be Yueyue.
The profile photo is a guitar.
The ID indicates
that's a male.
But he bought
all the shampoos,
masks and baby toys
sold during the live.
Everyone thinks that he is
a super good dad
who cares much
about his wife and kid.
[Yueyue's Keyboard]
What's in your mind?
I am thinking of my dad.
You never talked about your dad.
Because there is nothing to say.
If you don't mind,
you can talk to me.
He was a member of the band.
Although he knew he was just a foil,
he cherished
every opportunity to perform.
While there was no show,
he would be responsible
for the logistics of the band.
Zhe, Ming.
Come on.
Here you are.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's eat.
Hey.
I just asked you to buy some beer.
Where is the beer?
Sorry.
I will buy it.
And a packet of cigarettes.
Sure.
Baby.
One day
you will see Dad playing
on such a stage.
Dad is so cool!
Are you ready?
Don't open your eyes.
Now open your eyes.
Is this the piano you bought for me?
This is the keyboard I bought for you.
Do you like it?
[Yueyue's Keyboard]
Yes!
Thank you, dad.
So your nickname
is Yueyue.
I don't know if I am called Yueyue
or Lele.
My dad hopes it to be Yueyue.
He wanted me to love music
as much as him
and be a musician.
My mom hopes it to be Lele.
She wanted me to grow up happily
and never be like my dad.
What happened next?
Don't you know
our situation?
We don't even have Lele's tuition.
And you spent money
on an electric guitar?
I…
My guitar is broken.
Make a decision today.
Music or family.
Which one do you choose?
Dad.
Yueyue.
Stop crying.
I am leaving.
You should grow up happily.
Don't go, dad.
Dad!
Finally
he chose music
and left.
Has he ever contact you?
It's been 20 years.
He has never contacted us.
It's as if
he never had us.
If one day,
you meet him again,
what will you do?
I hope I never meet him again
in my life.
If I meet him, beat him up.
Hello.
I will be there soon.
Go to work.
I am also going back to the company.
Okay.
I think
it works pretty well.
So we should expand this.
A new member joins
today's general meeting.
Hello, everyone.
I am Qi Lin, the representative
of Lihe Capital.
The last thing I want to see
still happened.
I tried my best
to avoid this kind of problem.
I didn't expect that
we still need to face each other.
Lihe Capital knows your abilities well.
So
I understand
why they transferred you here.
Well, in the future…?
Business
is business.
[Worth Or Not]
Qi Lin knows you very well.
And she is very capable..
It turns tricky now.
Why are you more worried than me?
Never mind.
I can handle that.
Lihe Capital is really all-pervasive.
As you said,
I can just
roll with the punches.
No matter what happens…
Okay, I have to go.
All right, bye.
Qian, someone is looking for you.
Hello, what can I do for you?
Your dad is looking for you.
Miss Qi booked the presidential suite
of our hotel.
It seems that she would live here
for a long time.
From now on,
pay close attention to all her actions
and report to me in time.
Got it.
This way.
The lease on the house
he rented before expired
and he has no money to renew it.
So he has to make do here.
What…
What happened to him?
Your dad has a tumor in his head.
The operation is of high risk.
But he still insisted.
The operation wasn't very successful.
The tumor was removed,
but he doesn't remember anything.
Those are your dad's medical records.
He planned to go to you
after the operation.
But it ends like this.
[CT Multimedia Graphic Report]
Your dad knows that you are selling goods
in the live broadcast.
He bought every item
you recommended.
The recipients are all
Yueyue's Dad.
Your dad is a member of our band.
He is the guitarist.
But we often go to performances.
We can't always take care of him.
So I came to you
to take over.
We know you hate him.
But we have no choice.
[Our shop provides tour guide service]
[Holiday Garden of Samueli]
Good morning.
Didn't you go out?
Not yet.
Shuangshuang.
Mom.
What's up?
Look what you did.
So careless of you.
Hello.
Okay. Sure.
Hold on.
Sure.
Shuangshuang.
The guest in room 102 arrived.
Pick him up.
Come on. Hurry up.
It's going to rain.
Come on.
It hurts!
When Building No. 2 reopens
this time,
I would like to invite
the world-famous piano master Mr. Peter Bao
to play for us,
and serve as spokesman
for Building No. 2.
On the one hand,
this can demonstrate the quality
of Building No. 2.
On the other hand…
Mr. Sheng.
Sorry to interrupt.
We spent a lot of money
on the refurbishment
of Building No. 2.
Before making a profit,
another large sum of money
would be spent on publicity.
I actually agree with Mr. Sheng's plan.
Now is the information society.
It's worth
spending money on publicity.
Right, Mr. Sheng?
Why would she persuade
other shareholders
to accept our publicity plan?
Hasn't she had any contact
with other shareholders
in the past few days?
She only attends
the shareholders meeting occasionally.
She acts alone
at other times.
She jogs and swims
as if she is taking a holiday
in our hotel.
It's really abnormal.
Keep an eye on her.
[Good Luck Agricultural Products Supermarket]
Hello.
I am at that gate
of Good Luck Agricultural Products Supermarket.
The signal is bad.
Hello.
Well.
The signal is bad.
Where's the place?
Did you find it?
Good Luck.
Hello.
The signal is bad.
I found you.
You are the guest of room 102?
I really came to travel.
What a coincidence.
I didn't expect it to be you.
You came to travel?
Trust me.
If not,
there would be thunder…
God doesn't believe you.
Go back to where you belong.
You are not welcome here.
Be nice.
Wait.
Carry my luggage.
Wait!
Hello.
Ms. Chen?
Miss Xia.
I am so sorry.
There is a traffic jam.
I may be late.
How long would it take?
I have some work to do.
Well.
Please hurry up.
Sure, I'll be there as soon as possible.
Okay, thanks.
Open your mouth.
What's up?
Hello, Qian.
Why are you not here yet?
The suppliers are here.
Deal with them first.
I will go downstairs in a while.
Okay.
Who's that?
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want to distract you.
It distracts me even more
by doing this.
I will ask someone
to look after him 24 hours a day.
24 hours?
Don't be so nice to him.
He doesn't worth it.
Should we tell your mom?
No.
My mother said
she didn't want to see him all her life.
All right, let's eat.
Hello, it's me.
Everything is going well.
Why so much trouble?
At least she could hate me less.
It's better than being turned away
as soon as we meet.
Whatever.
You have to face it directly.
It is useless to escape.
Shuangshuang.
Why are you back alone?
Where's the guest?
I missed him.
Missed?
You missed him?
Why?
Didn't I give you the phone number?
No one answered.
No one answered the phone.
What?
Shuangshuang.
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no drudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪