So it seems
You two are still eating again
It's a tie-breaker
This white gourd chicken
It is a combination of wax gourd cups
Practice with watermelon child chicken
It's quite fresh
It's just
This watermelon can be greasy and fresh
Can make chicken soup
Bring a sweet taste
But this wax gourd is thick
No matter how beautifully carved it is
It can only be reduced to a container
What's the effect on this chicken soup
Your Highness is right
Every ingredient
We should make the best use of everything
What your highness said is very true
Everything is the negligence of handmaiden
What is this all about
What is this thing pasting up
I don't know that either
Recipe canon meal
Hu Shang Shi
Are you putting yellow mud on winter bamboo shoots
You come
Good
Concentrate
Don't make a fuss
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
Your Majesty
Once fish and shrimp are dehydrated,
Carry it into the palace chilled
Often lose its true taste
The best kitchen in the world
It can't make up for this regret
So do winter bamboo shoots
Dig out winter bamboo shoots in the forest
Baking in place with mud
Is the most beautiful in the world
This bamboo shoot leaves the soil
Not more than half an hour
The handmaiden is wrapped in yellow mud
Cook with slow fire
In order to retain its natural fragrance
Please taste it, Your Majesty
This
This mountain family gives a clear confession
The recorded forest freshness
It should be eaten locally
Leave the soil for a long time and then put yellow mud on it
And what is the effect
Your Highness, you will know when you taste it
Xianna
Delicious
Please have a look at it
It's salt grains
This lotus root tastes special
I can't taste it for a while
The ingredients inside
Taiping Shenghui Fangnei
There was a record
Replenishing Qi and Harmonizing Middle School
Medicated diet for promoting fluid production and moistening lung
It is this Taiping mixed lotus root
It's just lily yam
Asparagus white poria cocos
Speaking of it
There is nothing unusual about it
Then this medicated diet
Is it for your majesty
What a pity
Your Majesty must be
Delicacies have been used for a long time
The stomach is bored with panic
Will feel that
Is this spring fresher with winter bamboo shoots
Right, Crown Princess
Crown Princess
Should it be all right
I have no idea
Hu Shangshi, they are gone
Check
Hu Shang Shi
Is everything ready
Ready
Jade chowder
Be careful
Nothing
Strange
It's about time
Why don't you see Hu Shangshi for a long time
Goose meat is soft and rotten
The soup smells fragrant
Your Majesty always likes to eat geese
The way of roasting goose collected from the folk
No less than a thousand kinds
Can get your majesty's praise
It's not easy
Eat two geese in a row
I'm afraid I can't taste the delicious taste
Come
Unexpectedly better than Yunlin Goose
The taste is fragrant for three points
There are also snow vegetables hidden in the goose belly
Love Princess
Queen
Together
This goose is as colored as ivory
Soft bone fragrance
End of product
There are bloodshot bones
The taste is extremely mellow
It's memorable
Right
Hu Shang Shi
How is this goose meal cooked
Return
Your Majesty
This dish presented by Hu Shangshi
It is the legendary fire-roasted goose
Mother concubine
What is a roasted goose
His Royal Highness King Wei
That is to put geese
Imprisoned in an iron cage
Ignite charcoal fire and bake it
Goose drinks pepper slurry when heated
Shedding of goose feathers
The goose is still alive
Pepper paste penetration
Goose meat is tender
Cook a goose in this way
Goose meat is extremely tender
Bold
Too cruel
Your Majesty, pardon
Hu Shang Shi
Cooking together is taken from nature
How can you cook
Such cruel food
Somebody
Your Majesty
Your Majesty is generous and kind
There was a ban first
How dare a handmaiden disobey
It's just
How to make this goose meal
It was carefully developed by handmaiden
I also hope your majesty will be tolerant
Please have a look at it
What is this
Your Majesty, this is coarse shell ash
This goose meal is made of coarse shell ash
Made instead of open flame
Named Roast Goose Without Fire
Handmaiden is stupid and ignorant
I misunderstood Hu Shangshi
I also ask your majesty to plead guilty
Be jealous of talents and slanderers
Even if the cooking skills are higher,
But there is no room for people in my heart
How do you deserve to be in charge of a game
Your Majesty, today is the Shangyuan Festival
Don't let these little things
Bad the festive atmosphere
You guys must feel that you are still eating
Today's party is boring
So I specially set out
Make everyone happy
All right, all right, you guys go down
Prepare meals separately
Yes
Your Majesty
Is Yao Dianshan's hand all right
Yeah
It seems to be seriously injured
You said she was hurt like this
Still insisting on cooking
I can't do it anyway
I can't do this for me
Yeah
I don't know
Will it have an impact on the future
I think this injury is like this
Never rest
It will definitely fall into the root of the disease in the future
I'll take care of the rest
You're sweating in pain
I'll do the rest
You go get busy with something else
Purple Azolla
Do you know this seasoning recipe
How many times have I peeked at it
I've learned it a long time ago
You go
To do something else
If I get so badly hurt,
I can't even hold a knife
Nothing
Be careful
Zi Jin
This is my possession
It has a miraculous effect on bone and muscle pain
At least it can relieve the pain for a while