Since you left,
My father has always been thinking about it in his heart
After all, they are biological father and daughter
Don't
Can't you really let it go
Before the mother died of illness
He told me himself
If I'm not selected
Master Mu doesn't have to die
Mother doesn't have to die with hatred
He said everything, everything
It's all because of me
I want to see my mother one last time
He's the one who put me
He was taken to Pengcheng Bo Mansion
Half a year in confinement
I only hear the wind and rain on a cold night
Have you ever heard of it
A care from relatives
At that time
Where is Father
Brother
And where are you
Empress T-shirt
That's why I came to see you in the palace
Such grace
How rare it is
A-Mei
You may as well blame us
Hate us
You can't just watch
The whole family of Sun Shi suffers
It's a brother. I
Please, please
I'm begging you
You go now
I don't want to see you again
Even though all of us
I'm sorry for you
What about the mother who died of illness
She has cared for you since she was a child
Have you fulfilled her last wish
You didn't
If she had a spirit in heaven,
I have to watch helplessly
Look at your husband
And his own son died because of you
You can stand up to her
You are not afraid of the Queen's intimidation
Is worried
Your own splendor and riches
Rest assured
If you really want to decapitate your head,
Just kill me
It won't implicate you
An open man
Purple Azolla
A-mei who wants a future
Make your own money
This
Purple Azolla
A-Mei
Hold one's hopes on nepotism
Purple Azolla
Don't fight, you rat who is afraid of death
A-Mei
You get the hell out of here
Fuck off
Zi Jin
Meng Shang Shi
Originally, you chose your own ideas
Participate in Shangyuan Banquet
This time her hand was badly damaged
I'm afraid it's difficult to heal for a while
Whether or not
Shang Shi's adult
Aren't you still sick
Please allow me to participate in the Shangyuan banquet
As a kitchen
It is necessary to carve and shake the spoon
Your hand is badly hurt
In case because of the competition,
Aggravate the injury
Can you do it
Meng Shangshi chose me as his deputy
If I cherish my own hands blindly,
How to live up to it
What about the grace of adults
I've made up my mind
Please ask for permission
Good
I promise you
Hu Shang Shi
Everyone laughs
Hu Shangshi is overreaching
Open provocation
I guess
Over the years
Hu Shangshi has always hidden his strength
Stay until the big day
Show before people
This is a game
Hu Shang eats hard
I have been waiting for a competition for ten years
Prepare to spend half a lifetime of forbearance
To fight for the glory you want most
But this time
Heaven will be on my side
With this one of you
Probably never again
A hand that can't lift a knife
Yes
With this one of mine
You may leave your disabled right hand behind
I want to see you lose with my own eyes
Lose the most desired power
Leave the Forbidden City in despair
It deserves to be the person I trained
Good
I'd like to see it
How do you fulfill this oath
You're so bored, so bored, so bored
Stop following me
Your Highness just had a nightmare
Think of many old things
There are many things I don't remember
Say what you have to say
Don't hesitate
Your Highness
On the Yuan Festival
Long live Aoshan Lantern Festival
It is already under preparation
At that time, Your Majesty will invite empresses and princesses
Tongguan Aoshan
Be sure to send more people
Strict interrogation
Yes
Your Excellency
Everything is ready
If it hurts like this, give up
Meng Shang Shi
Why do you insist on participating in the competition
I can choose another deputy
Shang Shi's adult
I asked Ji Dianyao
If I rest at ease,
When will it recover
She said
Everything depends on God's will
In case
Then this is me
The last chance in life
Hand hurt
Even the most basic kung fu has been forgotten
Beat chicken chopped
Don't cut the knife too hard
Otherwise, the tendon will break in it
Start over
Yes
Since this is your request
I will be strict with you
Regardless of your hands
Will it really be scrapped
We must stick to it
Yes
Good
One more
What beautiful fireworks
Good
Your Majesty
One more
Okay, one more
Good
One more, one more, one more
One more
Go ahead
Good and wonderful
Take a good look
The lamp is going to burn
Why hasn't His Royal Highness arrived yet
Good
Purple Azolla
Why did you drag me here
It's really too late
There is still an hour left
It's about to go to dinner
What are you panicking about
Today is the Yuan Festival
Aoshan Lantern must be seen
You see
Good
Watch your skill
It's so beautiful
Good and wonderful
Take a good look
It's so beautiful
Purple Azolla
Look at it. Look at it
You
Where are you going?
Son minister see father, emperor and mother
Brother, you are so good
Your Majesty, look
The prince is all for you
I just went off to perform
Just smile
Repeat one's hand
Prince of a country
Act recklessly
What kind of system
My son just wants to
Be happy after coaxing your mother
Mother Queen
You have seen it all just now, haven't you
I saw it all
You can have this filial piety
The mother is really overjoyed
Hu Shang Shi
It's up to you to decide the question
Eight Chinese cuisines
But in general terms
There are more than ten million delicacies in various places
We're gonna fight
There is no limit to cuisine and no limit to it
How about just fighting thoroughly
How to call it a thorough fight
In accordance with previous years' practice
Good cuisine praised by Your Majesty
You can give a banquet to your ministers
You and I show our magical powers
Compare final
Delicacies on the list of official banquets
Who is the best chef in the world
It will be clear at a glance
According to what you said
If you can't support it later,
I have to be substituted
Shang Shi's adult can rest assured
Grass millet
I'll do it
What is Yao Dianshan doing
Serve
Soft chicken skin
The meat is tender
Unusual taste
Back to the emperor's words
This salt-sealed chicken
It is wrapped in yarn paper
Air-dried chicken
Salt
This is a very interesting way to do it
Your Majesty
This exquisite peony catfish
Not only beautiful in shape
It tastes more beautiful
There is also a unique smoky smell
The prince is right
Handmaiden specially used
Smoked fish meat with raw tea leaves
It will be slightly fragrant in smoke
Then take this one
I thought I said I was going to offer nine cold dishes
How can a box be sent away
Is this giving up
Self-knowledge is the most important thing in people
So good
Your Majesty
Handmaiden daring
Please uncover it yourself
You
Don't scare her
I really want to see it
In this box
What a treasure it is filled with
This is
Nine-color box
This box looks quite chic
Available with ordinary boxes
It's just an extra cold dish
I see
There is no previous intention yet
Back to His Royal Highness the Prince
The so-called nine-color saving box
Is
White Meat with Garlic
White Jade in Gold Clothes
Chicken slices with pepper and sesame seeds
Carassius auratus with bone crisp
Peach kernel in sauce
Diced rabbit with red oil
Beef with dried tangerine peel
Cowpea with ginger sauce
Sweet and sour snow rolls
Nine kinds of ingredients and nine kinds of knife skills
Nine different cooking techniques
The beauty is not in the dish itself
But according to different seasons
Dishes can be adjusted at any time
Meat and vegetable collocation is different
Small saving boxes are all-encompassing
Just follow this nine-color box
Ordered Guanglu Temple to give banquet ministers
Yes
What does the Queen laugh at
Your Majesty
You see how interesting the play is
Which play
Analgesic with acupuncture and moxibustion
It can only seal the pain for a while
If you can't support it,
Never force
Yao Ziliao
So sharp-edged
It's really rare to see
How
Your hand
Can you still support it
After you lose to me
It will be clear by itself
Duck breast has not been colored
Add fire
Yes
Meng Shang Shi
In no hurry
Recipe canon meal
Give me this
It turned out to be cooked slowly
I would like to try it
Quiet
Why are you eating today
So serious
Your Majesty congratulates you on the Yuan Festival
Shang Food Bureau carefully prepares meals
Handmaiden daring
Your Majesty, please taste it
Your Majesty
This is the Shang Food Bureau in front of the command
Compare the skills of cooking
This is more interesting than watching a hundred plays
That's true
Please wait a moment, Your Majesty
Roasted duck
This duck is tender and delicious
The skin is crisp and crisp
And this thin layer
Oil on the skin
Duck oil is too greasy
Oil is not fragrant when it is less
Good. The good thing is that it's just right
Incense
It smells beyond words
No
The roasted duck meat in Guanglu Temple is less old and oily
It can't be compared with this
Your Majesty
Original Material Selection of Jinling Roasted Duck
Wild flower duck
Now it is changed to be carefully selected
Feeding small white ducks
Ingredients are just one of them
Kung fu is the most important thing
The temperature difference is a fraction of a cent
A thousand miles away
Duck's paw is immersed in
The unique aroma of ham
There is also a faint aroma of flowers and fruits
It's honey
Handmaiden with the sweetness of honey
Neutralized salty ham
To highlight the delicious taste of the main ingredient duck's paw
This way of roasting ducks
What pays attention to is skill
And this ladder duck
The test is ingenuity
You can't tell the outcome of this game, can you
Say so
This game is a draw
Chicken is crisp and rotten
This practice is also unique
Your Highness, what's wrong with this dish
Fresh and smooth
Mellow taste
Seemingly tofu pudding
But how can there be tofu pudding
Such a delicious taste
So it seems
You two are still eating again
It's a tie-breaker
This white gourd chicken
It is a combination of wax gourd cups
Practice with watermelon child chicken
It's quite fresh
It's just
This watermelon can be greasy and fresh
Can make chicken soup
Bring a sweet taste
But this wax gourd is thick
No matter how beautifully carved it is
It can only be reduced to a container
What's the effect on this chicken soup
Your Highness is right
Every ingredient
We should make the best use of everything
What your highness said is very true
Everything is the negligence of handmaiden
What is this all about
What is this thing pasting up
I don't know that either
Recipe canon meal
Hu Shang Shi
Are you putting yellow mud on winter bamboo shoots
You come
Good
Concentrate
Don't make a fuss
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
Your Majesty
Once fish and shrimp are dehydrated,
Carry it into the palace chilled
Often lose its true taste
The best kitchen in the world
It can't make up for this regret
So do winter bamboo shoots
Dig out winter bamboo shoots in the forest
Baking in place with mud
Is the most beautiful in the world
This bamboo shoot leaves the soil
Not more than half an hour
The handmaiden is wrapped in yellow mud
Cook with slow fire
In order to retain its natural fragrance
Please taste it, Your Majesty
This
This mountain family gives a clear confession
The recorded forest freshness
It should be eaten locally
Leave the soil for a long time and then put yellow mud on it
And what is the effect
Your Highness, you will know when you taste it
Xianna
Delicious
Please have a look at it
It's salt grains
This lotus root tastes special
I can't taste it for a while
The ingredients inside
Taiping Shenghui Fangnei
There was a record
Replenishing Qi and Harmonizing Middle School
Medicated diet for promoting fluid production and moistening lung
It is this Taiping mixed lotus root
It's just lily yam
Asparagus white poria cocos
Speaking of it
There is nothing unusual about it
Then this medicated diet
Is it for your majesty
What a pity
Your Majesty must be
Delicacies have been used for a long time
The stomach is bored with panic
Will feel that
Is this spring fresher with winter bamboo shoots
Right, Crown Princess
Crown Princess
Should it be all right
I have no idea
Hu Shangshi, they are gone
Check
Hu Shang Shi
Is everything ready
Ready
Jade chowder
Be careful
Nothing
Strange
It's about time
Why don't you see Hu Shangshi for a long time
Goose meat is soft and rotten
The soup smells fragrant
Your Majesty always likes to eat geese
The way of roasting goose collected from the folk
No less than a thousand kinds
Can get your majesty's praise
It's not easy
Eat two geese in a row
I'm afraid I can't taste the delicious taste
Come
Unexpectedly better than Yunlin Goose
The taste is fragrant for three points
There are also snow vegetables hidden in the goose belly
Love Princess
Queen
Together
This goose is as colored as ivory
Soft bone fragrance
End of product
There are bloodshot bones
The taste is extremely mellow
It's memorable
Right
Hu Shang Shi
How is this goose meal cooked
Return
Your Majesty
This dish presented by Hu Shangshi
It is the legendary fire-roasted goose
Mother concubine
What is a roasted goose
His Royal Highness King Wei
That is to put geese
Imprisoned in an iron cage
Ignite charcoal fire and bake it
Goose drinks pepper slurry when heated
Shedding of goose feathers
The goose is still alive
Pepper paste penetration
Goose meat is tender
Cook a goose in this way
Goose meat is extremely tender
Bold
Too cruel
Your Majesty, pardon
Hu Shang Shi
Cooking together is taken from nature
How can you cook
Such cruel food
Somebody
Your Majesty
Your Majesty is generous and kind
There was a ban first
How dare a handmaiden disobey
It's just
How to make this goose meal
It was carefully developed by handmaiden
I also hope your majesty will be tolerant
Please have a look at it
What is this
Your Majesty, this is coarse shell ash
This goose meal is made of coarse shell ash
Made instead of open flame
Named Roast Goose Without Fire
Handmaiden is stupid and ignorant
I misunderstood Hu Shangshi
I also ask your majesty to plead guilty
Be jealous of talents and slanderers
Even if the cooking skills are higher,
But there is no room for people in my heart
How do you deserve to be in charge of a game
Your Majesty, today is the Shangyuan Festival
Don't let these little things
Bad the festive atmosphere
You guys must feel that you are still eating
Today's party is boring
So I specially set out
Make everyone happy
All right, all right, you guys go down
Prepare meals separately
Yes
Your Majesty
Is Yao Dianshan's hand all right
Yeah
It seems to be seriously injured
You said she was hurt like this
Still insisting on cooking
I can't do it anyway
I can't do this for me
Yeah
I don't know
Will it have an impact on the future
I think this injury is like this
Never rest
It will definitely fall into the root of the disease in the future
I'll take care of the rest
You're sweating in pain
I'll do the rest
You go get busy with something else
Purple Azolla
Do you know this seasoning recipe
How many times have I peeked at it
I've learned it a long time ago
You go
To do something else
If I get so badly hurt,
I can't even hold a knife
Nothing
Be careful
Zi Jin
This is my possession
It has a miraculous effect on bone and muscle pain
At least it can relieve the pain for a while