(This drama is fictional and people or stories are not tied to reality.)
Is this the line?
- You may go inside. - Thanks.
I'm Hong Cheon Gi of Baekyu Painters Society.
Hong Cheon Gi of Baekyu Painters Society.
Look who this is.
It's Painter Hong.
Darn it.
We need to square everything first.
How can you assault a lady in the middle of the day?
Where are your senses?
- What's he doing? - That's impossible.
Be quiet, all of you! What do you know anyway?
Hey, you.
Are you really a painter?
Show me your contest ID slip.
Yes, sure.
I think I left it.
But I'm with Baekyu Painters Society.
I really am a painter. Please let me in.
Goodness, how can a woman be a painter?
You'll even make dogs laugh.
You can't go inside unless you have a contest ID slip.
Next person. Finish up quickly.
- Wait, but... - Hurry.
Let's go quietly while we're nice. Don't put up a fight.
No, wait. Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Let her go immediately.
The litter?
Scholar.
I see that you two are together.
Watch your mouth! He's...
Man soo.
Yes.
She's coming with me.
Says who? Come here.
You!
Darn it, you!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Scholar Ha, you're here.
- How dare you make a scene here? - Quiet!
This is Prince Yangmyeong's Maejukheon.
Get out of here! Go!
- Cheon Gi, I'll get you! - Get out of here!
Please come inside.
This woman is also participating in the contest.
I'm going in with her.
Yes, I understand.
See? I told you so.
Now, please hurry.
Take out your ID slip in advance.
- All right. - Line up, please.
(Episode 5: Maejukheon Painting Contest, Part One)
This is so amazing.
It's crowded like the central marketplace.
Anyway, what brings you to the painting contest?
I was invited by Prince Yangmyeong.
Oh, you were invited.
Well, he may have invited you here,
but where is his courtesy?
No one is here to escort you.
Never mind, I'll be your escort.
Then please help me out.
Sure. Trust me and follow me.
This way.
Right ahead of you. Be careful.
Anyway, Sir Scholar. How are you so good at using your body?
It was as if you could see.
No, even those who can see couldn't do what you did.
Are you a military officer?
I've been training since when I was young.
Let's just say I had a great teacher.
Anyway, you were the best.
How could I ever repay you?
Don't mention it. It was something I ought to do.
But still. Those men are the minions of Wolseongdang.
I don't want you to get in trouble because of me.
People say it's best to avoid fights.
I'll avoid them as much as I can, so don't worry.
But you have to be very, very careful.
It looks like this is where the guests are to sit.
And on the other side,
I'll be drawing out in this yard.
Is that so? I look forward to it.
I've never been to such a huge place before.
I've dreamt of this moment for quite a long time.
I'm sure you could win first place.
Sorry? Goodness, no way.
However, I'll do my best.
Then do paint in dashing spirit and see great results.
(Dashing spirit: Staying strong as one advances forward)
Come this way, please.
Thank you.
You have to keep your eyes on me.
I apologize.
It's all right. I'm used to it now.
Then please excuse me.
Where did she go? Where is she?
- She's over there. Come on. - Where? Oh.
Cheon Gi. Hey.
- Hey. - My gosh!
Why do you walk so quickly?
Goodness, you fool. When did you come? We were worried.
Hey! You two came into Maejukheon by yourselves.
What? You were worried? Please.
I met Jung Seon Rye on the way and almost died.
- What? - What?
You met that guy?
How did he get released so quickly?
No idea.
So? And?
What do you mean? I ran away as best I could.
Anyway, we should stay vigilant when we walk around at night.
Man, then everything we did, we did in vain?
My gosh, I can't believe it.
He looks familiar.
Hey, forget them.
Let's grab our seats.
Okay. We can talk about this later.
You haven't found seats for us?
- We went looking for you! - We had no time to get seats.
(Master painter, Monk Manyoo)
(Touch of a deity, Kang Hee Yeon)
(Magical touch, Sim Dae Yu, also known as Sim with a bamboo hat)
There are some seats left.
It's a great spot.
Now, look.
I'll make sure I win first place here at Maejukheon.
You'll get into Gohwawon if you make it to the third screening.
Don't be such a show-off. Stay modest, and paint carefully.
Hey, that's not good enough.
Are you ready?
I'm all ready.
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
Goodness, look who this is.
It's Scholar Ha of Seomungwan.
(Seomungwan: An office in charge of astronomy, weather, and calendar)
Your looks always remind me of an entrancing painting.
Have you been well?
(Prince Joohyang, Lee Hoo, the second son of King Seongjo)
I thought he's the type who wouldn't care for paintings.
His Majesty especially adored him, so I wondered what he's like.
He's very dignified and even beautiful.
He really doesn't seem human.
Is that so?
Prince Joohyang is here.
Forgive my belated greetings, Your Highness.
I thought you'd be busy carrying out duties at Seomungwan,
so I never thought we meet in a place like this.
I looked at my fortune today through hexagrams,
and an unexpected 24th hexagram came out.
It must've meant I'll have the honor...
of sitting by your side as I watch over the contest.
- The 24th hexagram? - Are you saying it was destined?
Yes.
It's nice to have a man who's as upright as you say that.
My ears are delighted.
Do enjoy the contest.
Yes, Your Highness.
You're one mischievous man.
If I had...
just died at the cliff back then.
Step back!
Mother!
Mother...
(Investigator Kim Gong Rae, Prince Joohyang's bodyguard)
All honored guests and painters,
Maejukheon Painting Contest is about to begin.
Please take your seats.
Hey.
Draw stones to look as light as feather.
Draw trees as if they're characters.
When you draw bamboos,
you should be well-versed in penmanship.
If any of you are aware of this,
you must know calligraphy and painting are the same.
(The theory of calligraphy and painting as a single entity)
I hoped to find a talented painter as such,
and opened up the doors of Maejukheon in four years.
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm Yangmyeong, the lord of Maejukheon.
Now, let me introduce the judges who'll judge the paintings with me.
First off,
Han Geon, an expert of Gohwawon.
(Gohwawon: An office in charge of paintings)
(Han Geon, Expert of Gohwawon)
And his long-time colleague, a historic painting society,
Choi Won Ho, the master of Baekyu Painters Society,
(Number 52)
Yoo Si Saeng, the master of Jungyu Painters Society.
(Yoo Si Saeng, the master of Jungyu Painters Society)
A dear friend of mine and my brother's,
and the finest writer of Dan Dynasty, Seo Ki Jung.
(Seo Ki Jung, the erudite of Bomungwan)
Lastly, a man of profound knowledge in literature and martial arts,
who always sets an example as my older brother.
Please welcome Prince Joohyang.
This Maejukheon Painting Contest will be held over two days.
The contest will have three screenings.
You'll draw two paintings for two screenings today,
and tomorrow will be the third screening.
(Three different screenings for the contest)
First,
an honored guest of my choice will announce the theme...
for each screening.
Second,
the evaluation will be held without publicizing your ranks or statuses.
That's it!
We got this. We can do it.
Third, after the evaluation,
the judges will decide if you pass or not with the red and blue sticks.
Red stick means you pass.
Blue stick means you don't.
If the majority hold up red sticks, you pass.
If not, you do not.
However,
even if everyone does not let your painting pass,
senior judges may use their free pass stick...
and let you pass the screening once.
(Senior Judges: 5 judges who old superior authorities)
(Free Pass Stick: Given only to senior judges as a free pass)
Now,
I look forward to seeing paintings that'll become legendary.
I wlil also...
take part in the evaluation as a judge.
Painters, feel free to use papers as much as you need,
provided by Maejukheon.
If you stay seated, you will receive...
your first piece.
- Thank you. - Also, if you do not finish...
the painting within the time limit, you will be eliminated.
The time limit changes for each round.
- The stamp is so pretty. - And the theme will change too.
This is wonderful.
This is premium paper, so it even smells different.
You two sound like hillbillies.
You might end up kissing the paper.
- Hey, Young Wook. - Yes?
Who's that creepy monk?
Master painter of Jeolla Province, Monk Manyoo?
Once he drew Vimalakirti on the wall of the temple,
the painting shined the entire temple brightly.
People swarmed in to look at that painting,
and the temple brought in over a million Jeon.
He shocked the world with his masterpiece painting,
so he's called the master painter.
Hey, then who's that man in a bamboo hat?
That painter seems to be...
Sim with a bamboo hat.
The magical touch of Gyeongsang Province.
Magical touch?
Magical touch.
He must be capable of doing magic tricks as he paints.
Oh, so he could paint boldly as if a horse rides through fogs.
He can even ride on that horse and compose his painting,
the magical touch.
Goodness, you slow kids.
Calm down. I have to keep calm.
What I mean is this.
He always wears that bamboo hat,
so no one knows what he looks like or how old he is.
A goblin called Hwacha that loves paintings came every night...
to have paint-offs against him.
Then he came to an enlightenment for his magical touches.
That's why he's called the magical touch.
Do you get it now?
All great painters in the Dan Dynasty...
have gathered here.
Actually, there is someone else...
who receives the most attention in this painting contest.
Who is it?
Oh, me?
I know who that is too.
The biggest potential winner of this Maejukheon Painting Contest.
Touch of a deity, Kang Hee Yeon.
The best scholarly painter who grew up as a gifted child.
He uses composed lines for his ink-and-wash painting,
yet he brings out ardent blank spaces.
His paintings are all lively and realistic.
These judges are all scholars,
so he has the highest chance...
compared to painters like us, who do this for a living.
Are you telling me...
to accept the reality that I won't be the winner...
of this painting contest?
I mean, these men are here to paint with us.
How can we dream of competing with them?
But still, let's dream big...
here at Maejukheon today, Frown.
- And Nuisance? - Goodness.
So are you going to try to win?
She has always been too hopeful since when she was young.
- That's what I'm saying. - Just grind the ink stick.
Let me announce the first painting type and theme.
(Painting type: Landscape, animals, portrait, et cetera)
(Painting theme: The overall theme of the painting)
The first screening's painting type is plumtree and bamboo.
(Plumtree and bamboo)
The theme will be...
decided by the expert of Gohwawon, Han Geon.
What?
Hey, doesn't this mean Jung has the upper hand?
Yes, isn't he his teacher?
"When I recite poetry alone under the moonlight,"
"the smell of the plum blossom begins to seep into my clothes."
"I'm afraid butterflies will fly as a group..."
"thinking that spring has already come."
("When I recite poetry alone under the moonlight,")
("the smell of the plum blossom begins to seep into my clothes.")
Now, you get 1 sijin.
(One sijin: About 2 hours)
Two hours?
That's too tight.
I don't have enough ink yet.
Start grinding the stick first.
What do you think?
I tried changing the theme to match the eye level...
with the copycat painter.
You're an outstanding strategist, Your Highness.
His penmanship is incredible.
His writing is as great as the masters.
It's a wonder.
It is.
How can he write like that?
- Goodness. - That's amazing.
His penmanship is solid yet dignified.
Prince Yangmyeong's writings are always a masterpiece.
Even envoys from other countries covet after his writings.
We could consider his calligraphy as a national treasure.
Are you concerned about him?
Why would I be?
I'm just proud to have such a talented younger brother.
It's just calligraphy.
Keep your focus solely on the intentions of Prince Yangmyeong.
Hey, Jung.
Hey. Could you interpret the theme one more time?
"Moonlight, poetry, alone, plum blossom, seep, clothes."
"Afraid, butterflies, fly, spring, already come."
What?
What the heck is he saying?
Young Wook, you try to read that.
Okay, trust me.
Make it accurate.
"Under the moon..."
The poetry is what now?
Hey, forget it. I heard that part too.
Hey.
I'll tell you just this once, so make sure you listen well.
They're reciting poetry alone under the moonlight,
but the smell of the plum blossom is so strong, it got on their clothes.
Then butterflies fly in as a group thinking it's already spring.
That's what it means.
All right, I get it.
So...
the moonlight.
Plum blossoms.
Butterflies.
What is it?
That's an uncanny painting.
I'm not even finished yet.
This won't be good enough.
He has bold touches.
Already?
Two hours have passed already.
When you touch the paper with a brush, you create a stroke.
(A stroke brings out the actual shape)
Then you're left with empty spaces.
(Empty spaces depict the energy of the created shape)
Will you let the stroke win and bring out the shape?
Or will you let it loose and let the shape show?
Father.
No one can add 10 thousand touches with just a single stroke.
Once I gave up my greed,
I could see flowers and the Moon.
Since this is the first screening, I still see many ignoble paintings.
If they call themselves a painter, what's with that first stroke?
We should focus on the dignity of the painting.
Let's find out what the painters' focuses were.
The first painting type was plumtree and bamboo.
They'll be evaluated on their take on nature and their attitude.
Swish.
Swoosh.
Once you close your eyes,
you hear sounds.
Even if she is that girl,
our relationship was already once disconnected.
I won't let my petty feelings ruin my great plan.
That's the time for your first painting.
Make sure you write your name.
[VIU Ver] SBS E05 'Lovers of the Red Sky'
"Maejukheon Painting Contest, Part One"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Come on, get up. Let's go.
Did you all write your names?
Yes.
Prepare for the evaluation.
I see a magnanimous and brave layout,
but it doesn't portray the theme's intimacy.
- It's against the theme. - Six blue sticks!
There are 26 blue sticks...
and eight red sticks.
Fail!
This person used ink too dark...
to paint the moon.
Fail.
(Light and shade)
The plum tree must be bold and strong.
There's nothing more to see.
- Hey. - It's yours?
It's not always good to fill the paper.
The energy of the plum tree isn't enough to relieve...
the sorrow of a man reciting a poem.
(Deep sorrow)
Fail!
That was yours?
Oh, dear. You did well anyway.
- Good luck. - Thanks.
Oh, dear.
The plumtree looks empty...
as it lacks strokes here and there.
- It's a fail. - Fail!
The brush strokes are rough and the ink shows no light or shade.
- Fail. - Fail!
- Fail. - Fail.
Fail.
- Hey. - Hey.
It's Young Wook's.
My gosh.
Plum flowers bloom beautifully all over the branches.
It's a good piece that portrays the plum...
that blooms throughout hardships.
There are 31 red sticks and three blue sticks.
Number 25, pass.
Pass!
Hey.
Well done.
(Number 22)
Branches stretching out elegantly under the moonlight.
I can almost smell a cool fragrance coming from the flowers.
- Pass. - Yes.
- Hey. - You made it.
You did it.
From the rough growth of the tree,
I sense the chastity of one's spirit.
Pass.
Number 32 did very well.
It's yours.
This painting has a different character and pose.
(Character and pose)
It's a refreshing composition and style.
Pass.
The Yeon merchants would clamor to purchase...
a painting like this.
There's nothing more to say.
The flowers and moonlight are drawn almost poetically.
I like it very much.
Pass.
The energy of the painting takes flight in the breeze,
scatters in the flowers and stops at the moon.
It's truly amazing.
A great piece.
But what is this?
It's a good use of blank space,
and the strokes and contrast are truly exceptional.
Your glance is led to reach the round moon,
and on the plum flowers, a gift of heaven...
is sprinkled which almost gives me the chills.
However,
although the plum grows in the cold,
it never sells its fragrance.
I'd like the painter of this work to think of what I said.
Fail.
Six blue sticks!
Four blue sticks!
There are 33 red sticks and one blue stick.
This work is a fail.
(Fail)
Wait, Your Highness!
I wish to ask you something.
Come forward.
You crazy...
- My gosh. - Let's sit down.
Oh, dear.
What a mess.
I'm Hong Cheon Gi from Baekyu Painters Society.
You just said that...
my work is good, but you can't give it a pass.
I would like to know...
why that is.
All other painters accepted their results.
Why did you come forward to doubt the judges' opinion?
I apologize sincerely...
for disrupting the event and posing a sudden question.
But I'm not objecting to the opinions...
of learned experts.
As you said, I have already failed.
So what?
My hope...
and the reputation of my society are already damaged.
If I were to go home not knowing the reason...
why I failed, I might despair and decide never to paint again.
So I dare ask.
What ability...
do you think I lack?
Your painting has a structure that is unique...
and unlike any other.
That alone is enough to seduce and bewilder.
You have great skills.
(To infatuate someone)
However, the plumtree you drew...
have flowers facing upward,
so they look like apricot flowers.
The butterflies all took flight, despite it being nighttime.
Doesn't that show the shallowness of the painter...
who only tries to win the interest of a buyer?
That goes against fidelity and loyalty the plum represents,
and is the same as selling the tree's fragrance.
You can ask me ten times,
but I would still fail your painting.
So it was the butterfly that was the problem.
What do you mean?
Can't you tell?
The prince is being nitpicky.
There's something about it.
There's something about that butterfly painting.
It was the butterfly.
What? What about the butterfly?
It looks just fine.
It has wings and feelers.
It has...
A butterfly?
- Gosh. - You're so gutsy.
This is my mark.
(A painter's mark left behind instead of a seal.)
That painter is the woman I saw at the dye house.
The two of them...
must definitely know each other.
She knows Yul?
Your Highness.
If you say a detailed painting that is almost lifelike...
is flawed by its excessive detail...
That is what I...
What do you think?
The strokes have pent-up energy,
and the branches are so stiff they might snap.
This could mean the painter was too absorbed in her emotions...
she failed to grasp the concept.
I also think the plum flowers...
are too simple,
and they look outdated and ignorant.
Your further comments...
only proved even more...
why this painting is a fail.
Your Highness.
Are you failing my painting...
because the flowers face upward so they look like apricot flowers?
You said you'd let the painters draw freely,
so how could you say that?
Are you talking back at me?
I apologize.
Whatever you say,
to me, this painting...
looks like you tried to show off using a unique layout,
but then failed to grasp the basic concept.
He figured out she's the forger.
In my painting,
the butterfly took flight under the moon too.
So why...
Now, now. Everything in the world stems from issues of the heart.
Do not blame others.
Those who are meant to pass will pass,
and those meant to fail will fail.
I see.
I finally get what it means to host
a contest in Maejukheon.
Then it's done.
You said that...
we compete as equals, regardless of our rank or status.
That this contest is only about skill.
However...
that's all just for show.
Everything's about your taste and thoughts.
I get that now.
What a brazen thing.
We cannot let people like her paint at all.
What an insolent girl she is.
I was impudent.
I will leave now.
Wait!
Your Highness. I think...
the reason none of the flowers face downward...
is because the painter thought of...
Du Hyang's poem of the drooping plum...
that grows downward by the water.
Also, the upward flowers that you say...
make you think of apricot flowers...
is because the painter was true to what she saw...
and she painted exactly what she felt.
Why are you doing this?
Your Highness.
She's a blessed painter.
My gosh.
What?
Does her painting have some kind of power?
This is so very strange.
Do you mean that Hong Eun O's daughter could compete?
I stopped her from applying, but I'm warning you just in case.
Eun O had a daughter?
Promise me that...
you will fail her.
The blood of a blessed painter.
She must be Hong Eun O's daughter.
I will...
use my free pass stick.
You got a free pass stick.
There is no need for a reason.
Pass.
A free pass?
Some petty list of painters?
It could decide the fate of my colleagues,
the honor of Baekyu Society,
and bring hope to my life.
Pass!
You're out of your mind.
Next!
Hey.
Troublemaker. I thought you'd get into real trouble.
What were you thinking?
I don't know myself.
It's too early to celebrate. I have bad news.
What is it?
I think Prince Yangmyeong bought the fake Sochundo from Wolseongdang.
What?
Didn't you think it weird that he kept mentioning the butterfly?
That can't be.
If it weren't for that, why else would he fail you?
Come on. Even so...
What'll you do now?
No one knows who Jung Seon Rye sold it to.
Hey. Let's say Prince Yangmyeong did buy my fake painting.
Why would he have kept quiet until now?
My back aches.
If you're not careful, you might lose your hand...
and your career too.
Darn you.
Mr. Choi.
Fancy seeing you here.
Hello, Mr. Song, Mr. Jang.
I have to go to the toilet. Bye.
- Get back on time. - You're all here.
Of course we are.
It's the first contest in years.
We wouldn't miss it.
I should try even hard now that I saw you here.
Goodbye.
Don't try too hard.
See you around.
Let's go.
Isn't she the rude painter who talked back at the prince?
Yes, it's her.
She came in with Seomungwan's Scholar Ha.
Seomungwan's Scholar Ha? Are they talking about him?
He's relying on his friendship with the prince to back his lover.
She even got a free pass.
Rumors that he was cursed to become a freak...
with red eyes must be true.
Don't you think he cast a spell to make the butterflies come over?
If it wasn't that, he put honey on the paper.
I'm impressed.
Darn it.
My gosh.
What?
Do you know about Seomungwan's Scholar Ha?
Yes. The guardian spirit of the King's palace.
That's it?
He's also called the freak with red eyes.
Why?
Because his eyes are red?
Yes.
No one has said that to me before.
People see my eyes and call me a freak.
Is a Seomungwan scholar a high rank?
It is.
Why? Are you interested?
Hey. Are you interested in everything you ask about?
I just heard his eyes are red and asked you about it.
What's that about a curse or something?
You're acting really weird today.
You're even asking about a guy.
Do you know something?
Come on, tell me.
Well,
he was offered as a sacrifice at the rainmaking ritual...
and they say that's why his eyes turned red.
What?
The rainmaking ritual?
Yes. It was almost 20 years ago.
Hey.
What is it? Do you feel sick?
No. Don't mind me.
If it was 20 years ago...
No way.
The second round will start soon.
Can the painter who is called...
stand and give a speech on how they will compete?
Monk Manyoo.
A painting is...
a depiction of creations borrowing the power of paper and ink.
Through it,
you must be able to meditate and teach the people.
Save us, merciful Buddha.
Choi Jung.
You don't put anything inside a painting.
It's a battle of brushstrokes.
I don't know how to lose that battle.
I will win.
There is no winning or losing about painting.
You paint, then you walk.
Then you have fun, and that's it.
Most of the people here paint for a living.
They grew up fighting others like thugs fight in the marketplace.
I will not back down easily.
You people talk too much about boring stuff.
Fighting thugs?
I'd like to win that fight.
I'd like to make my family proud.
Hong Cheon Gi.
This contest,
to some high-up noble young man is just a game,
and to some painters...
is a fight for money or glory.
But to me,
it's a lifelong wish.
My whole life is at stake.
I will win.
With that,
I congratulate all 20 people...
who made it to the second round.
Are you all ready to begin?
Very well. I look forward to your submissions.
I will explain the new rules to the second round.
In this round, you'll paint using paper,
brushes, and ink provided by Maejukheon.
You'll each get one sheet...
of oiled bamboo pulp paper.
If you make a mistake, you will not get another sheet.
Instead, you'll be failed on the spot.
One wrong stroke and you're done.
Oiled bamboo pulp paper?
Isn't it expensive paper used for portraits at Gohwawon?
Do we have to draw someone's portrait?
What? Then Nuisance has an advantage.
You troublemakers.
Would they make us draw a portrait?
If the paper's oiled,
it depends on how we use the ink.
The brush has no core,
and you only get one thick brush with a long stem.
Those who cannot use this brush...
or those who used special tailored brushes...
Just one brush? That's unbelievable.
What are we supposed to do?
Just one long-stemmed brush?
I really want to cry now.
A long-stemmed brush with no core.
It'll be hard for most to even draw a straight line.
If we use the wrong amount of water,
we can't make any delicate touches.
The delicate touches,
you can make by using just some of the brush hairs.
(To split the hairs)
We know that much.
Split the hairs?
If we compete using the same paper, brush, and ink,
the difference in skill will be apparent.
Experienced people will realize...
how to use the brush in no time.
It will come down to skill and energy.
The painting type...
is landscape.
(Paintings of scenery such as rivers or mountains.)
And the theme...
I ask Seomungwan's Scholar Ha to provide that.
Your Highness, I do not dare.
Scholar Ha is my close friend...
and an astronomer acknowledged by the King.
His poems...
are also just as astronomical.
Step forward.
One more step.
Do your best.
Spring is everywhere on the mountain,
(Spring is everywhere on the mountain)
and I play among the peach blossoms.
(I play among the peach blossoms)
I suddenly wish for a peach,
(I suddenly wish for a peach)
so I look for it morning and night.
(I look for it morning and night)
In this round, if your painting moves us,
you'll get extra points.
Also, paintings that show courage and energy...
will gain extra points.
Are you...
really Ha Ram?
The time you get
is two hours.
Everyone's painting so smoothly as if they knew the theme.
This is really bad.
Let's paint horizontally.
Hey. I don't know what's going on, but focus.
(Number 39)
Yes. I'll ask after the contest.
You drew the fake Sochundo?
I still cannot believe it.
Is it really you?
Is it you?
There's a lot I want to ask,
but I'll save it.
The peach orchard, 19 years ago.
Do you still remember that place?
I'd like to know.
Even if I once adored you,
I am already a dead man.
You listened to me,
and you held my hand with such warmth.
I cannot forget it.
Did you look forward to it?
To the tomorrow I promised?
I want to hear...
the reason you couldn't return.
(Lovers of the Red Sky)
Why do you tell me to forget so easily?
I did not come back to see you...
because I had forgotten about you.
For how long will you keep quiet?
Is it that wrong for a painter to enter a painting contest?
Do your paintings even contain...
your energy and soul?
People are not moved by a painter's skill.
You're giving up like this?
What do you know about me for you to say that?
It wasn't your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Ha Ram.
It's you, isn't it?