The pro-treaty paddies and the king
want the same man dead.
You have been chosen, Mr Shelby.
The Epsom Derby, Pol. We'll be
drinking with the bloody king.
For the last ten years,
Sabini's made it his race.
If we're going to take him down,
might as well make it there.
~ It's good to see you, Grace.
~ Tommy, do you have someone?
Your horse will come fifth or sixth.
But I will win you.
Mr Churchill was impressed.
He has asked that the
Colonial Office grant him
an Empire export licence.
I want my son out of prison. Now.
He can be freed by tomorrow morning.
I'm talking about a simple
transaction here.
I will carry out the assassination
at a place of my choosing...
Epsom.
Derby Day.
'My name is Thomas Shelby.
'And today, I'm going to kill a man.
'Today is Derby Day...
'.. and the murder will take place
this afternoon at the Epsom races...
'It may be that I am able
to escape after the killing.
'The odds are not good.
'Which is why I'm writing
this letter.
'I have been forced by agents of the
crown to carry out this murder
'and in the event
of my own death
'I want the following
facts to be known.
'My family are innocent
of any involvement.'
Who are we?
~ Small Heath Rifles! ~ Let's go.
'And while some of them may be
guilty of other things...
'.. I have not shared details of this
mission with any of them
'and no company assets were used.
'Agents of the crown have joined
forces with the pro-treaty Fenians
'to arrange this murder.
'I believe the Government intend to
falsely blame the anti-treaty IRA.
'Therefore, the bullet
I fire this afternoon
'will be the starting gun
for Civil War in Ireland.
'The man I have been instructed
to kill is Field Marshall Russell,
'formerly a Black and Tan commander,
'who committed many atrocities
in the county of Cork.
'There is no remorse in my heart
at the prospect of his death.
'However, the conspiracy
behind the killing
'is cause for international concern.
'Such is the gravity
of my secret mission
'that after I have served my purpose,
I believe they intend to kill me.'
Do you want tea?
'I therefore want to name a
particular individual in this letter.
'The agent who has initiated
and orchestrated this crime
'is Major Chester Campbell of the
British Secret Intelligence Service.
'He chose me for this dirty business
as an act of vengeance,
'prompted by a hatred
of long standing.
'In the event of my death, it is
imperative he be brought to justice.
'If you are reading this,
then I am dead already.
'I hope that living, as you do,
in a truly free country,
'you will be able to make
the above facts known to the world.
'Yours sincerely, Thomas Shelby.'
Did you one anyway,
you ignorant git.
Ada, sit down here for a minute.
Ada, if anything happens
to me today...
.. I need you to post this letter.
The stamp's already on.
Don't ask any questions.
It's... to do with insurance.
Look, Tommy?
Whatever it is you're
involved in, just tell us.
God, you never let anybody in.
We love you, Tom.
What are you doing up at
six o'clock in the morning?
~ Ready? ~ What the bloody
hell's going on?
~ Little errand. ~ What errand?
~ He just has to stand there, Ada...
~ Stand where?
~ Let's go... Come on.
~ James, what's going on?
Don't listen to him, James,
he'll get you killed!
What errand?
For the cause, Ada.
The good old cause.
MUSIC: Arabella
by The Arctic Monkeys
♪ Arabella's got some
interstellar-gator skin boots
♪ And a helter skelter round her
little finger
♪ And I ride it endlessly... ♪
Hands off cocks, on with socks...
One at a time.
One at a time, that is all I ask.
You're getting out, Mr Shelby.
♪ My days end best
when this sunset gets itself
♪ Behind that little lady
sitting on the passenger... ♪
All ten witnesses against you
withdrew their statements.
Last night.
All at once. Nine o'clock.
Don't ask me why
because I don't know.
For the next ten minutes,
you don't do or say
anything I haven't told you.
All right?
~ All right? ~ Yeah.
Hello, Ollie.
Hang on... Just you, yeah?
He stays out here.
You stay here.
♪ The light
♪ The horizon tries
♪ But it's just not
as kind on the eyes
♪ As Arabella
♪ Just might have tapped
into your mind and soul
♪ You can't be sure
♪ That's magic in
a cheetah-print coat
♪ Just a slip underneath it, I hope
♪ Asking if I can have one of those
♪ Organic cigarettes that she smokes
♪ Wraps her lips
round the Mexican coke... ♪
Johnny fucking Dogs.
♪.. Makes you wish that
you were the bottle. ♪
How did he get me out of there?
I need to get you to a telephone.
You need to make a call.
It is all part of Tommy's plan...
Apparently.
That'll probably
be for you, won't it?
Hello?
Arthur. You're out?
Right, so that'll be your side
of the street swept up, won't it?
Where's mine?
What you got for me?
~ Signed by the Minister
of the Empire himself. ~ Yeah?
Which means that you can
put your rum in our shipments
and no-one at Poplar Docks
will lift a canvas.
You know what? I'm not even going
to have my lawyer look at that.
No. No, it is all legal.
You know what, mate?
I trust you. That is that.
Done.
So, whisky.
There is one thing, though, however,
that we do need to discuss.
~ What would that be? ~ It says here...
20% paid to me
of your export business.
As we agreed on the telephone.
No, no, no, no.
See, I had my lawyer draw this
up for us, just in case.
It says that...
here, that 100%
of your business...
.. goes to me.
~ I see. ~ Just there...
Don't worry about it, right.
Cos it is totally legal, binding.
All you have to do is
sign the document
and transfer the whole
lot over to me.
Sign just here, is it?
Yeah.
I see. That's funny, that is.
~ What? ~ No, that's funny.
I'll give you 100% of my business?
Yeah!
Why?
Ollie, no.
No. No. Ollie, no. Put that down.
He understands. He understands.
He's a big boy, he knows the road.
Now, look, it's just
non-fucking-negotiable.
That is all you need to know,
so all you have to do is sign
the fucking contract.
~ Right there. ~ Just sign here.
~ With your pen. ~ I understand.
Good. Get on with it.
I have an associate waiting
for me at the door.
I know, he looks like a choirboy
but he is actually an anarchist
~ from Kentish Town. ~ Tommy,
I am going to fucking
shoot you. Right?
Now, when I came in here,
Mr Solomons,
I stopped to tie my shoelace...
Isn't that a fact, Ollie?
I stopped to tie my shoelace.
And while I was doing it,
I laid a hand grenade under
one of your barrels.
A mark 15 with wire trip.
My friend upstairs is like one of
those anarchists
that blew up Wall Street, you know?
He's a professional.
And he's in charge of the wire.
If I don't walk out of that
door by the stroke of seven,
he's going to trigger the grenade
and your very combustible rum
will blow us all to hell.
And I don't care...
.. cos I am already dead.
He tied his lace, Alfie.
And there is a kid at the door.
From a good family, too. Ollie,
it is shocking what they become.
What were you doing
when this happened?
He tied his lace. Nothing else.
Yeah. But what were you doing?
Marking the runners in the paper.
What are you doing?
Just checking the time. Carry on.
Ollie, I want you to go outside
and shoot that boy in the face
from the good family.
Anyone walks through that door
except me, he blows the grenade.
~ He tied his fucking lace, Alfie.
~ I did tie my lace.
I bet hundred to one...
.. that you're fucking lying, mate.
~ That's my money. ~ Well, you see, you
have failed to consider the form.
I did blow up my own pub
for the insurance.
OK, right, well,
considering the form,
I would say, 65 to one.
Very good odds. And I would be
more than happy and agree
for you to sign over 65%
of your business to me.
~ Thank you. ~ 65? No deal.
Ollie, what do you say?
Jesus Christ, Alfie,
He tied his fucking lace. I saw him.
Look, he planted a grenade.
I know he did.
Alfie, it is Tommy fucking Shelby.
You are behaving
like a fucking child.
This is a man's world.
Now, get that apron off and sit
in the corner like a little boy.
Fuck off. Now!
~ Four minutes.
~ Right, four minutes.
Talk to me about hand grenades.
The chalk mark on the barrel at knee
height said, "Hamilton Christmas".
I took out the pin
and put it on the wire.
Based on this...
.. 45%.
30.
Aw, fuck off, Tommy.
That's far too little.
In France, Mr Solomons, when I was
a tunneller. A clay kicker. A 179.
I blew up Schwaben Hohe.
Same kit I'm using today.
Funny that.
I do know the 179
and I heard they all got buried.
Three of us dug ourselves out.
Like you're digging
yourself out now.
Like I'm digging now.
(Fuck me!)
Listen, I'll give you 35%.
That's your lot.
35.
~ You're late. ~ I had business.
How the fuck did you get me
out of that?
I need you today, brother.
~ And pulled some strings.
You all right? ~ I am now.
So, Arthur's back in charge now?
He's in charge of you and you're
both in charge of him.
~ Look-out duties only today.
~ Tommy, I'm getting sick of this...
Finn, you don't obey orders,
you don't come.
~ Johnny Dogs. ~ Tommy?
~ Your boys will meet us there?
~ The Lees will be there, Captain.
"Captain"?
Aye, we promoted you.
Well, the boys decided you're no
longer like a Sergeant Major.
Fucking those rich women
and using those fancy words.
I'd say you're more
like a captain these days.
Fine, well, I'll take
it as a compliment.
Just don't bloody shoot me.
Let's go to the Derby, boys.
Right then, load them up.
Hello?
No, I'm afraid Mr Shelby
is in London.
He can't be reached.
No, he won't be back today.
He's at the races.
The Epsom races. The Epsom Derby.
Can I ask who's calling?
I'm going to the station.
~ What's that? ~ That money's yours.
You take the money,
you get a train
and you start a new life
in London. I don't want to see
you here when I get back.
If I get back.
Everything's an "if"
in this Birmingham life.
You can write on Sundays.
And visit on Holy Days.
But I want you to wash this city
out your hair and your clothes.
It is what I should have
done at the start.
Now, I've got business to attend to.
I do love you, Michael.
I love you, too.
You'll miss your train.
My beloved greyhounds...
.. behold today's rabbit.
When I give you the signal, I want
you to send that man to his maker.
I decided to use you men,
because I couldn't trust the hearts
and the livers
of the English pansies and posies
they've given me as operatives.
Now...
.. this is a man of some
capability...
.. but I expect no excuses
and no failures.
The Red Right Hand of the
Ulster Volunteer Force
will not let you down, Mr Campbell.
The Red Right Hand.
Good luck, gentlemen.
♪ They're whispering his name
♪ Through this disappearing land
♪ But hidden in his coat
♪ Is a red right hand. ♪
Gentlemen, today we are not
fucking about.
I hope you've all obeyed instructions
and brought loaded firearms with you.
~ Yes.
~ Very good.
You all know that if you are lifted
on a race track these days
with a loaded weapon,
you get 20 years.
That's all right.
Today, you won't get lifted.
Because today, there'll be no
coppers around to lift you.
At exactly three o'clock,
there will be an incident
in the owner's enclosure.
And all the coppers on the track
will be diverted. All of them.
They'll be looking for someone.
~ So, you'll be free to operate at
will. ~ Looking for who?
Me. They'll be looking for me.
Now, while the coppers
are busy with me,
you will make your move on
Sabini's pitches.
You confiscate his takings,
you destroy his licences
and you do it at gunpoint.
He usually has police protection,
so they won't be armed.
We should aim to complete the take
over without a shot being fired.
Understood?
And remember, the licences are more
important than the takings.
All right. Before the fun begins, you
can all lay ten bob on Nom De Guerre.
I hear she's going to win.
Only beer beforehand, boys.
There'll be plenty of time
for rum and whisky after.
And remember, do not make a move
until three, when the coppers leave.
~ That is all. ~ Feeling lucky, John.
Incidents...
What are you going to do
that's going to make every copper
at the Derby look the other way?
Trust me, brother!
Over here. Over here.
Are you ready, boys?
Ten, please.
It's right here, mate.
She threw a shoe coming
out of the box.
She looks in fine shape.
Hello, hello, hello.
~ Should I be worried?
~ You should not.
Go and drink. Enjoy the day.
I'll come and find you
when the race is done.
That's nice, is that yours?
My mother wore it to
the Derby in 1895.
She was presented to Queen Victoria.
After the race,
I'll change in the horse box
and then come and join you up there
with the toffs. What do you say?
Hm... yeah.
You don't want me to join you.
It's fine. I'll stay
down here in the mud.
Whatever happens today,
it was good.
You mean win or lose?
Yeah. Win or lose.
You know I never watch the race.
I can't stand it.
I always like to find
somewhere dark and quiet...
Tommy?
If you can't find me up there,
I'll come and find you later.
What do you mean?
Whatever happens, May, no regrets.
No regrets.
And I will find you.
Right.
Remember that.
Bye.
MUSIC: Down By The Water
by PJ Harvey
♪ I lost my heart under the bridge
♪ To that little girl... ♪
Put this on Nom De Guerre.
~ ♪ Down by the water
~ Down by the water
~ ♪ I took her hand
~ I took her hand
~ ♪ Just like my daughter
~ Just like my daughter... ~ ♪
There he is...
Fucking meatball bollocks.
Come on. Let's go.
I have to talk to you....
~ Grace. What are you doing here?
~ I have to talk to you.
Grace... this is not a good time.
This way. Excuse us.
Whatever it is, Grace,
it'll have to wait.
It can't wait.
It wasn't me who was at fault.
I'm pregnant.
The baby's yours.
But he'll believe... Make your
husband believe that it's his.
Is that what you want me to do?
Grace, I seriously have things to do.
~ It's not even worth the toss
of a coin this time. ~ Grace.
I have things to do. When they are...
When they are done, I will decide.
~ And when will that be?
~ After the race.
After the race?
After the fucking race, Tommy?
When the race is over,
I will decide what to do.
~ What to fucking do. All right?
~ But, Tommy...
I was right not to tell him.
I could have phoned him
and lied, but I didn't.
Just tell me I was right
not to phone and lie.
Agree with that, Tommy.
Yes. Yes, Grace.
Because the thing is...
.. I love you, not him.
That is a thing.
~ A baby, Thomas. ~ Yes.
Go to your race.
~ Where will you be? ~ I'll be waiting.
I'll wait where they lay their bets.
Found a lost sheep.
Come on, Lizzie.
~ What do you think? ~ About what?
~ About the dress?
~ Undo two buttons. Come on!
~ Oh, Tommy, I never thought
I'd see the like of this. ~ Yeah.
But I do know that I'm here to work.
~ So you may have noticed
I haven't taken a drink. ~ Here.
Take this. You might need it.
What's the work you want me
to do here today, Tommy?
Taking notes on a meeting?
No, Lizzie. You're not
here to take notes.
My shorthand won't be required.
Lizzie...
.. there's a man here.
And I need him to be separated from
the crowd and taken to a quiet place.
"A quiet place"?
~ Lizzie, I know what I said.
~ Yeah, you know.
You know you told me I shouldn't
do that kind of work any more.
I just need you to
isolate him is all.
No exceptions, you said.
I have drawn a map, all right?
Of where exactly
you need to take him.
For months, I made no exceptions,
~ Because you told me not to.
~ Lizzie...
just keep him busy at the
place marked with an X
and I'll get to you before
he can start, I promise. All right?
Mustn't smudge my eyes.
He might not like that.
Lizzie, this is the only time.
And after this, never again.
All right, I'll pay you
an extra five...
DO NOT talk to me about money now.
Not right now or I swear
I'll break this glass in your eyes.
"No exceptions"
has been no hardship.
You know why?
Hmm?
Doesn't matter.
~ Who is he? ~ To your right.
Soldier.
Smoking a cigarette.
Just be alone with him at three
when the race starts.
I'll do the rest. Yeah?
~ Got a piece of chalk? ~ Chalk?
It's how the soldiers know.
It doesn't matter.
Just give me the fucking chalk!
Lizzie, it is going
to be all right, eh?
I'll get to you, I promise,
before it can start.
I will be there.
Keep them fucking guns ready.
~ Keep them guns ready.
~ He's here, boss.
The coppers aren't moving. They're
stood there like fucking gargoyles.
Keep your wits about you, boys,
all right?!
'Ladies and gentlemen,
the race will begin in four minutes.
'Please make your way track side...'
Shouldn't you be busy?
When you plan something well
there's no need to rush.
You know something?
I actually trust you to do this.
Do you think there might
be some measure of respect
developing between us?
'Ladies and gentlemen,
the runners and riders
'are coming to order.
Please take your seats...'
Old foes who have grown
to admire each other?
And see each other's
professional virtues.
Personally... I think not.
I think not.
Well, I'll drink to that.
'Ladies and gentlemen, please be
upstanding for the national anthem.'
So, is the plan that you'll stay
together for ever?
Or perhaps she'll whore for you
and take her husband's money.
Is that the plan?
How wrong I was about her?
I was wrong about her, as well.
You once said to me,
that men like us can never be loved.
But she loves me. She told me.
She loves me.
And all you got was a bullet
and a fucking wolf head cane.
Well, bully for you.
This I know...
Ahead of you is damnation.
But I have the love of God
and the certainty of salvation.
I know what you did to Polly.
I know what happened
to Michael in jail.
Today, it will be me dead or you.
But whoever it is,
they'll wake up in hell tomorrow.
'Ladies and gentlemen,
'the runners and riders
are under starter's orders.'
'And they're off!'
Come on, girl. Come on.
At least make a showing.
Come on, Tommy.
What a pretty dress.
Take it off.
Shall we take this off first,
shall we?
~ Lift up your dress and show me
that you're clean. ~ Oh!
Do as you're told!
We should take it slow.
We've got all the time.
This area is closed off.
~ What? ~ The king will be coming this
way after the race.
This area is secured.
You'll have to go round.
Get the fuck off! Fuck off.
Get the fuck off me!
Oi!
RUSSELL!
Fuck!
Lizzie?
Where were you?
Where the fuck were you?
Give me the gun, Lizzie.
Lizzie. I'm sorry.
Fuck off! Fuck off!
Lizzie, just go. Go on. GO!
Officers...
Officers, I was taking a shit
and I heard voices, Irish voices.
Then I heard a shot.
I swear to God, there's
a soldier lying dead in there.
Get every man in uniform
around the king!
Every man in uniform
Right now.
The IRA are on the course.
Everyone to the king!
The Royal Enclosure now!
All right, make ready, boys,
this is it.
Right, you four get round the back.
You take three of your boys...
Scudboat, come on... Show them guns.
Right, you come with us
and you stay back.
Let's go!
Put your hands in the air.
Turn around!
Is there a problem?
There are Fenians on the course.
A soldier's been shot.
Someone said there was
an Irishman in here.
That was correct.
Very sorry, sir.
Shadow Security to His Majesty.
I will now take
command of the situation.
MUSIC: Come On Over by Royal Blood
Mr Sabini, you're late.
Have a seat.
What happened to your nose?
You want to have that
brother of yours put down.
I tried that. He bit the vet.
I told the coppers that
you're a fucking Gypsy racketeer
Peaky Blinder and they're coming,
they are going to throw you
out before the king comes up here.
Well, from what I saw,
the police are a bit busy right now.
Did you win any money today,
Mr Sabini?
Where are our coppers?
I said to that sergeant one minute,
he said two,
and it's fucking ten.
Like I told you, they're a bit busy.
Same as my boys.
~ What the fuck does that mean?
~ What does that mean?
Well, my boys are on the track
having a little bonfire.
Gaming licences, you know.
Fuck...
You placed too much reliance
on the police
for your security, Mr Sabini.
That was a mistake.
No, no. Think about who you are.
Think about where you are.
You pull a weapon,
you are the king's assassin.
Sit down and stay calm.
Good.
Now, your next mistake, Mr Sabini,
was breaking your promise
with Alfie Solomons.
You promised Alfie that his bookies
could come to Epsom.
He was very hurt when you said no.
He was very hurt.
And that is why me
and Alfie are back in business.
Police! All right!
It's all right, officers,
he's just a bad loser.
You fucking lose, you fucking
Gypsy bastard!! You lose!
What the fuck are you looking at?!
Step back! Move!
You are now a prisoner of
the Red Right Hand.
Now, take his hat and gun.
Get him up.
Easy...
Take a seat.
Now, you make
yourself nice and comfortable.
We're just going for a wee
drive, Mr Shelby.
Let's go.
I guessed
and then John confirmed it.
Guessed what? Who are you?
I'm May Carleton.
I trained Tommy Shelby's horse.
And you're the woman who
he said was going to sail away.
I see he didn't tell you about me.
He did tell me about you.
I wonder if that's significant.
Tell me what about you?
You have any idea where he is?
I'm waiting for him here.
There's been trouble on the track.
All the bookies
have had their licences burned.
Shouldn't you be down with
the horses...
Which means they will have to
re-apply for their legal pitches.
It's all part of Tommy's
plan for the future.
What do you know about Tommy's
future?
The applications will be
denied, of course.
And all the pitches will be
allocated instead to Tommy's
bookies.
I know because I'll make sure of it.
I have influence with the board.
There's business and there's love.
Is there?
With Thomas Shelby?
What do you want from him?
The same as you.
I want to feel alive.
Did he tell you my name?
My name is Grace.
In your statement to the House, sir,
I believe that you should say
that witnesses heard the killers
say that they were
members of the IRA
and that the killing
was in retribution for actions of
the Field Marshal in County Cork.
Oh... Our friend from Birmingham?
He has been taken care of.
Oh... A very good day, sir.
Thank...
Oh... Sorry, I must go. Goodbye.
Polly.
Tommy told me you'd be here.
And I told Tommy it should be me
who finishes you.
Small and weak.
That's how you like it, isn't it?
Well, this time small
and weak has got a gun.
You wouldn't do that here.
No?
Do you see any coppers? I don't.
They're all around
your precious king.
Polly. Polly...
~ Some part of you...
~ I have no parts.
Some part of you wanted me, as well.
I know that.
I felt it.
And sure as hell some part of me
wants you still.
Not just that part.
Some part of my soul.
Curious how that is to me...
And curious that it should be you.
Opposites, perhaps.
Opposites. And that... that thing
sticking in my heart you own.
You own part of that heart.
You do. You do, Polly.
You do.
Don't fuck with the Peaky Blinders.
MUSIC: River Styx
by Black Rebel Motorcycle Club
♪ Will you lay me down?
♪ Will you lay me
down inside heaven's walls
♪ Where every soul is
a setting sun? ♪
Let's get you home. Come on.
Look at this place! We own it!
Put your money away before
I take it off you.
Fucking clear off!
Get up!
Lizzie. What the fuck
are you doing here?
Working for Tommy.
Same as all of us.
You work for the Blinders?
What happened to you?
Fell over.
Don't fucking give me that.
Lizzie... Come here, come on,
come here.
Come here... Were you working?
Yeah? Thought you'd earn yourself
a few bob at the races, eh?
This has got to stop, Lizzie.
It's got to stop.
Tommy has already told you.
The toffs at the races
are the worst. You know that.
Come here, come here.
Look at me...
Cheer up. We won.
We fucking took Epsom!
We kicked the Cockneys'
fucking arses.
Congratu-fucking-lations.
We fucking beat them, all right.
John didn't even shoot his gun.
We're kings.
Kings of the fucking world!
John?
I don't see the same thing
in your eyes that I see in Tommy's.
You should get out.
Where is Tommy anyway?
Were any of you boys in France?
Allow a man a cigarette?
The Somme. Black Woods.
The Somme. The Bulge.
Smoke.
So fucking close.
Oh... And there's a woman.
Yeah.
A woman...
.. I love.
And I got close.
I nearly got FUCKING EVERYTHING!
Ah, what the fuck.
Get it done, boys.
Comrade, we have our orders.
You know how it is.
I know how it is.
In the bleak mid winter.
At some point in the near future,
Mr Churchill will want to
speak to you in person, Mr Shelby.
He has a job for you.
We will be in touch.
Get out of the grave, tinker!
Be on your fucking way!
MUSIC: All My Tears
by Ane Brun
♪ When I go. don't cry for me
♪ In my father's arms I'll be
♪ The wounds this world
left on my soul
♪ Will all be healed
and I'll be whole
♪ Sun and moon will be replaced
with the light of Jesus' face
♪ And I will not be ashamed
for my saviour knows my name... ♪
FUCK!
♪ It don't matter where you bury me
♪ I'll be home and I'll be free
♪ It don't matter anywhere I lay
♪ All my tears be washed away
♪ All my tears be washed away. ♪
Right...
Ladies and gentlemen,
I would like to raise a toast!
To the Small Heath Rifles!
The Small Heath Rifles!
The Lee Boys...
And to the Peaky fucking Blinders!
Who's going to stop us, eh?
Nobody.
Polly and I had a bet.
One of us
bet you'd take the money and go.
And one of us
bet you'd still be here.
She wants me to stay.
You know something, Michael?
What Polly wants... will always
a mystery to me.
I decided.
I want to make real money.
With you.
I've got some ideas, Michael,
for the future of the company.
And also...
.. I'm planning on getting married.
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
with a red right hand. ♪