[English subtitles are available]
Wait, beautiful.
Our shop is having a promotion.
You'll get hairstyling service for
free. Would you be interested?
-I have no money.
-It's free.
Join swimming club with gym
now to enjoy promotion.
I don't have time.
Don't find excuses for
your laziness, little sister.
Hi, want to know more?
Hi, want to know more about
swimming club with gym?
-I...
-Excuse me...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry. I was playing game.
-It's fine.
-No, I take this road everyday,
and I'm asked countless times a day
to do hairstyles or join membership.
I'm tired of it.
Can you all remember my face
and stop asking in future?
I'll remember.
Stop following me.
I'm getting late. Sorry.
I just want to ask directions.
It's OK. I'll ask someone else.
Where do you want to go?
Donghu University.
Do this.
First, walk straight.
After this junction,
turn left at the next junction.
Then, you'll see a bell tower.
Next, turn left again, and walk for 500
metres before you make a right turn.
And you'll arrive at Donghu University.
First, you walk straight.
Next...
Walk straight, and after this junction,
turn left at the next junction.
You can use your GPS. Are you an alien?
I'm not an alien.
I'm from another country.
I don't know why, but my Map won't launch.
Your Mandarin is so fluent. Are
you a returned overseas Chinese?
I'm a Malaysian Chinese.
I've spoken Mandarin since young.
OK. Follow me. We're headed
to the same direction anyway.
Sure. Thank you so much.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 3]
Sister,
are you a student at Donghu University?
No.
So, you're
a professor?
No.
Then, what is your occupation?
Are all foreigners so curious?
I just think when two
persons walk together,
it'll be a little odd if
I don't say something.
Department of medicine building
is right in front. Go ahead.
I'm leaving.
Sister.
I remember your face now.
Thank you.
My dear Xiao Chu Chu.
Aunt, when are you going to change
that habit of touching
people when you speak?
What's wrong? My nephew's a grown-up
now. Am I not allowed to touch him?
No, but we're in the university.
The students are watching.
It's not a good idea.
Anyway, you're right.
Beautiful and
young looking lady like myself
should keep a certain distance with Mr. Ai
so the females won't
misunderstand that you're taken.
Don't talk nonsense.
This is an university.
There're only students here.
Students will eventually graduate one day.
Besides, there're professors and staff
who you could consider as well.
Of course, I'm not giving you pressure.
Your grandfather said,
if Xiao Chu doesn't want
to find a girlfriend,
we can't force him to either.
It's just Ai family's
lineage will end here.
It isn't a serious issue.
You came here today just to tell me this?
Didn't you say you had
something to discuss with me?
Oh, right. Let me introduce you.
Greetings, Aunt Ai. Greetings, Mr. Ai.
His name is Liu Yu Cheng.
He's the son of my friend from Malaysia.
He happens to attend your
university's medical department.
I'll leave him to your care.
Look after him well.
OK.
Oh, right. What's your major?
Are you a postgraduate student?
Chinese Medicine. I'm a freshman.
It's my first day of school.
Is freshman orientation this late?
Actually, I'm 21 years old.
I studied engineering back in Malaysia
and I just graduated last month.
That's why, I could only start midterm.
Since I don't have any
basic medical knowledge,
so I couldn't enrol in
postgraduate studies directly.
You're going to start from
freshman year again?
You like Chinese medicine so much?
Yes, I'm really like it,
because whenever my
family members get sick,
we'd go to this Chinese
medicine practitioner.
I really admire him.
I want to be a Chinese
medicine practitioner as well.
So, I'll entrust him to you.
From now on, whether it's
studies or in general,
you can look for Mr. Ai if
you come across any problem.
-OK.
-Sure.
Give him your phone number.
Sure.
Are you all right?
You keep on laughing. All you do is laugh.
I shouldn't have come here with you.
Sister, you told me to come here,
saying to de-stress with you.
Do you think I'm able
to de-stress this way?
Look at the state I'm in.
It is for me, to see you in this state.
You'll de-stress?
Deng Hao Ran,
I want to eat ice-cream.
Approved.
You have to let me kick you once as well.
Sure.
Come on.
Defeated now, aren't you?
Hi, two ice-cream, please.
Here are your ice-cream.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You can have this.
Wait.
Kowtow first.
As if. Give me that.
Wait.
What is it this time?
The weather's fine. Let's take a photo.
Sister,
we're indoors.
I'm telling you we should take pictures.
The weather's good when
we're in a good mood.
And the photos will look nice
when the weather's nice. Come on.
One...
Smile.
One, two, three.
Ice-cream. Ice-cream.
You look so handsome.
All right, let's eat.
You can have this as well.
You're quite photogenic. Look.
Why are you so childish still?
You asked me to come here today just
to take these photos, didn't you?
You think after Zhang Teng saw it,
he'll get jealous, regretful, sad,
and even come back to you?
I'm not so childish.
I just thought
at least he'll feel bad when he sees it.
No, you're that childish.
Come on, look at this.
Your ex-girlfriend?
[Exercise to lose weight, but... Weather
is hot. I'll turn on AC. As for diet...]
Why does everyone else think the same way?
Two months ago,
he even brought me on a trip to Japan,
and took the trouble to book
the best hotel in Japan,
so that when I open the windows,
I'll see the most beautiful
coastline in Japan.
These memories are still fresh in my mind.
How did it disappear so quickly to him?
Tell me, is it because I didn't
give him space some time ago,
and after a while,
he'll come back to my side
when he feels better?
Ma Yi Yi,
men are really simple creatures.
What we feel and say always tally.
If he cares about you,
he'll never avoid you
or break up with you.
Even if you wish to leave his side,
he'll have 10,000 ways to get you to stay.
However,
if he really doesn't care,
no matter what you do or
say, he just doesn't care.
For example, the WeChat Moment
you prepared for his sake.
Even a commercial will
grab his attention more.
But I honestly feel wronged.
All the effort I put in
for such a long time,
in the end, it amounts to nothing.
Many things in life has no outcome.
At least you still remember,
when you push open the window,
the most beautiful coastline in
Japan is right in front of you.
You didn't even have to worry, right?
Screw that.
That's enough.
Breakup is nothing. Your next
boyfriend will be more mature.
Goodbye is nothing. The next
one will be even more obedient.
Goodbye.
Deng Hao Ran!
[CALORIES DON'T COUNT
ON THE WEEKEND]
[Photo]
Having a braces girl sitting by my side,
it feels like I'm a
teenager all over again.
Besides, we're dressed like so.
Don't you think,
today, we're three good
friends who got off school
and came to eat good food at a
restaurant with our pocket money?
You overthink.
You've become old the minute
you begin to like pink color.
Why?
See those two young girls?
Look at the way they dress.
What's so strange about it?
Let's go and party together.
Must be crazy, 857.
I know about 996 working hour system.
What's 857?
Should we ask him out?
-Ask him.
-OK.
Anyway, I think
Wu Yin is the youngest at our table.
At least she's not wearing
pastel-colored clothes like us.
Zip... Zip it up.
How embarrassing.
Hi, I'm going to serve the dishes.
Come on, the dishes are here.
-This is yours.
-Chicken popcorn. Chicken popcorn.
Smells so fragrant.
What's wrong?
My teeth hurt. I have no apetite.
This is how you lose weight
if you wear braces?
I'm envious. Let me touch it.
Come on, let me touch it.
-Let me touch it.
-I'll swap with you.
Eat the eel rice.
This doesn't require chewing.
Come on, this is for you,
and I'll take this.
I can't. Ai Jing Chu said,
I'm not supposed to eat sticky food.
Or else, it'll be a tragedy
when I open my mouth again.
"Ai Jing Chu said",
these four words have become your mantra.
Well, he's my dentist now.
Besides, my teeth
have become the biggest obstacle
to my living a wonderful life.
So, have you added each other on WeChat?
Quick, show us what his
profile picture looks like.
I didn't add him.
It'll pop up if you search
his phone number.
Come on, search it.
-Add him.
-Search his number.
-Go ahead and search.
-OK, I will.
[Search]
Search.
[User doesn't exist]
No way.
He probably doesn't use it.
How is that possible?
In this day and age, even my
grandmother has a WeChat account.
Besides, didn't Dou Dou see his WeChat
before she found out
his chats with other females?
[Liu Yu Cheng]
-Hello.
Mr. Ai, it's me. Can you talk now?
Yes. Go ahead.
Recently, I feel like I couldn't
catch up with my studies.
It might be due to a lack of foundation.
Can you recommend me few books
on basic medical knowledge?
[The type which I can understand.]
Jot this down with a pen.
OK, wait.
Go ahead, Mr. Ai.
[These few books
are easier for beginners.]
["A Century of Chemistry"
by Ernst Bäumler.]
Ernst Bäumler.
Also "The Human Body: An Illustrated Guide
to its Structure, Function and Disorders".
And "Anatomy in Easy-to-Memorize Verses"
[If you couldn't understand study
materials on human anatomy,]
[you could start with this first.]
Mr. Ai,
how did you know I couldn't
understand human anatomy?
It's hard for Chinese students,
let alone you international students.
That's right. My head's about to
explode from trying to memorize.
Mr. Ai, the books you mentioned just now,
I'm worried I might get
the titles mixed up.
Can I add you on WeChat so
you could help me verify?
I don't use WeChat.
I'll text you later.
[-Anything else?]
-Yes, there is.
I got a mouth ulcer recently.
[And I realized an issue.]
[Western medicine thinks mouth ulcer
is caused by impaired immunity,]
so vitamin supplement and anti-
inflammatory drugs is given.
Whereas Chinese medicine think it's
vigorous fire due to yin deficiency,
so pathogenic heat factor in the
stomach needs to be eliminated.
Mr. Ai, what do you think?
I think the two explanations
don't contradict with each other.
[Photo]
It seems so appetizing.
This woman. How come she never gain
weight no matter what she eats?
If you work long hours like me everyday,
and a messed up biological
clock, you won't either.
Although she won't gain
weight, she'll age.
Yes, she will.
We're going for staff bonding
event this weekend
at Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel.
Who's going with me?
Who's going with me? Who's going?
Do I have weekends?
I don't.
Then, I'll go.
Last time I asked you to go
on a staff bonding trip,
didn't you say there're only aunts
and uncles at my workplace,
so you refused to join?
That's because I had a boyfriend.
If the aunts and uncles have
a son or grandson at home,
and they fall in love with me,
it'd be bad.
Didn't you just break up
with your boyfriend?
Can't you stop for a moment?
Life is about being in love.
Wu Yin, what do you know?
Besides, good times won't last forever.
You people who don't want
to be in a relationship,
something's wrong with your mindset.
Wait, it's not that I don't want to.
It's because there's no candidate.
Me too. It's because I don't have time.
Wu Yin, people like you
who'd just marry themselves
should stop eating.
Give it back!
This is a restaurant.
Girls.
[CALORIES DON'T COUNT
ON THE WEEKEND]
-So rude.
-Remember, we're outside.
So rude.
[Although western and Chinese medicine]
[explain illness condition
in different ways,]
[they're after the same outcome.]
[For instance,]
the cardiovascular diseases
you mentioned just now,
Western medicine's treatment
is to build a stent
[to dilate blood vessels and
promote blood circulation.]
[Whereas Chinese medicine will soothe the
yang, and promote coronary circulation.]
[They're after the same outcome.]
Mr. Ai, that's really well said.
If I come across people who disbelieve
Chinese medicine in future,
I'll tell them this.
All right. Anything else?
There is.
Mr. Ai,
I recently discovered shared
bikes are really convenient,
but not parking at designated
locations is a problem.
I signed up to a charity
club in the university
which promotes parking shared
bikes at designated spots.
Can you help me to promote it
to students in lectures?
Sure, no problem.
[I'm hanging up if there's nothing else.]
Bye, Mr. Ai.
Where are we?
Dongshan Ancient Town.
That means we should be there soon.
He's so happy to be on this trip.
Where's Ma Yi Yi?
Hello, Zeng Li.
Hello. Where are you now?
I'm stuck in the line at the toll station.
It'll probably take another
hour before I arrive.
There seems to be an accident in front.
I'll take a walk near
the ancient town while waiting.
You'd better don't.
They sell products which can be found
on Taobao at few times the price.
Don't underestimate me.
Am I that type of people to
fall into tourist traps?
All right, let's not talk anymore.
I'll wait for you here.
See you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up a friend.
So cute.
Young lady,
you look so pretty in this hat.
Promotion price at RMB180.
Why don't you buy one?
RMB180?
That's so expensive.
What about this? RMB150,
buy 1 get 1 free. How's that?
I'm just browsing, sorry.
Young lady,
you've been browsing in
my shop since just now,
and you're not buying anything.
Aren't you being such a bully?
I...
All right.
You finally picked up
your phone. Where are you?
Something happened. My father fainted.
What's wrong with uncle?
No idea. My mother called me just now,
saying he's hospitalized.
I'm just worried if it's a relapse
of his cerebral thrombosis.
In that case, you shouldn't come over.
You have to visit uncle
at the hospital quickly.
What about you?
There're many buses here which
I can take to go to the hotel.
Don't mind me. Go to the hospital quickly.
Then, let me know right away
when you reach the hotel.
I will. Don't worry.
[Ginger tea with molasses]
[It's late. I wonder if there're
buses headed to the mountaintop.]
Miss,
where are you heading?
I'm heading to the mountaintop.
Is there any buses still running?
The hotel's shuttle bus
left a long while ago.
Is there any other way to
travel up the mountain?
There's none.
Look, it's going to snow soon.
The ground will be slippery and dangerous.
[No taxi available nearby]
[Zeng Li]
[Are you at the hotel?]
[I'm trapped on the way to the
mountaintop. There's no more buses.]
[Sunset]
[Waiting for confirmation]
[Cancelled]
Miss, there's a vehicle!
Really? Is it a bus?
[Dongshan Ancient Town Interchange,
bus schedule]
It's not a bus.
Someone drove a car down
from the mountain just now.
He has to head back later.
I told him to give you a ride.
Great. Thank you.
It's a black-color vehicle,
and the last two digits of
the number plate is 78.
78. OK, I understand. Thank you.
-OK. Take care.
-I will.
Last two digits is 78.
78.
Wait!
Wait up! Wait!
No way, how could I miss that?
What luck.
[Ai Jing Chu?]
You're the one who's
headed to the mountaintop?
I was waiting for my friend to
go to Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel.
But she couldn't come
because something happened.
I didn't manage to catch
the last bus either.
I almost missed you just now.
Luckily I turned around to check.
Let's go.
[Lucky!]
[So awkward.
Should I start a conversation?]
[But what should I say?]
Mr. Ai, you're also on
a staff bonding event?
No,
I came with my family.
OK, your family.
You didn't buckle your seatbelt.
[Seatbelt.]
I'm sorry.
What's this?
[Why is there a woman's hairpin?]
[The style. Is it his girlfriend's?]
Mr. Ai, this is yours.
Give it to me will do.
[What a calm reaction.]
Does it belong to your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
[But he flirts with so many females.]
[True. He can't admit to it.]
Do you want to listen to radio?
There's a knob on the panel.
You can adjust once you press it.
[The mountain road is covered with snow.]
[Everywhere I see is a vast
expanse of whiteness.]
[The cold wind roared, such that]
[I could barely keep my eyes open.]
[At a distance,]
[within the mountain, I saw a]
[something black moving.]
[It seems to be a human.]
[I thought,]
[could it be he's the same as me?]
This story seems...
Seems to be a horror story.
[That silhouette suddenly spoke.]
[Liu Bao Chang.]
[I was shocked.]
[Isn't that my name?]
[Suddenly, that shadow
figure ran towards me.]
[He stopped in front of me in no time,]
[and strangled my neck.]
[While I stuggle,]
[I finally saw his face.]
[This woman with disheveled hair...]
Switch it off if you're scared.
[Her partner]
[is smiling at me eerily.]
[Zeng Li, you coward. How could you
mistake that for something else?]
[No need to be afraid.]
[-Believe in science.]
[-I felt I ran a long, long distance,]
[yet I'm still circling in this
woods covered with snow.]
[The surroundings is so quiet.]
[Only my footsteps can be heard.]
[But I can't help feeling a pair of eyes]
[is staring at my back.]
[When I turn around,]
[there's nothing.]
[When I turn around again,]
[that woman...]
That's my phone.
[-Hello, Dr. Ai.]
-Hi.
[Why am I listening to the radio?]
[I'm Xue Xiao Mei,
Wang Zhen Zhen's cousin.]
[We had a phone
conversation this afternoon.]
I remember.
[Can you talk now?]
[About our child,]
[my husband and Mother-in-law
would like to consult you first,]
[because it's inconvenient
for us to come to Donghu.]
Mrs. Xue, I'm really sorry.
I'll give you a call later.
[Sure, Dr. Ai. Sorry to trouble you.]
Hang on a minute.
Hello. Hi, Mrs. Xue.
[Liu Bao Chang.]
-Go ahead.
[-Liu Bao Chang.]
I've seen his X-ray,
but it's a little blurry
so I can't be sure yet.
[Did he go outside because
he didn't want to disturb me,]
[or is it to keep patient's
information confidential?]
[He returned
his patient's call so quickly.]
[Seems like he's indeed a good doctor.]
It's fine. Carry on.
[He's been standing in
the snow for so long.]
[Isn't he cold?]
[Why is he walking towards me?]
[He should get inside
the car from his side.]
That's right,
under normal circumstances,
if he has a cleft lip and palate,
within the two months since
his birth, we have to
perform pre-surgery procedures.
It usually consists of impression taking
for shaping of pressure groove
and wearing aligners after that.
After three months,
we'll perform the orthognathic surgery
and palatoplasty after six months.
Close the window quickly. It's cold.
Since the child is still
in his growing stage,
malformation might occur even
if the surgery is a success.
That's right.
If continuous variation
occur in other aspects,
he might need another surgery.
Yes.
[The child is so pitiful.]
[He has to go through so much
suffering when he's born.]
Carry on.
Go back.
I understand.
[How's Uncle?]
[Zeng Li]
[Ma Yi Yi]
[He's in the hospital next to our house.]
[We're waiting for diagnostic results.]
[It must be tough for you
to look after him alone.]
[Ask Deng Hao Ran to come and help you.]
[I just gave him a call.]
[He should be on the way here.]
[That's good.]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Is that child all right?
The child's not born yet,
but from the X-ray,
seems like he has congenital
cleft lip and palate.
So, will it be cured after he's born?
That depends how you define being cured.
For those of you who come
to straighten your teeth,
some people might have come with
80 to 90 percent expectation.
The final result which is delivered
might be 100 percent.
But vice versa,
they'll think it's imperfect.
Let's go.
-Hello.
[-Hello, Mr. Ai.]
[Am I disturbing you?]
It's fine. What is it?
[Can I ask you a question?]
Go ahead.
[I was shifting the shared bikes
parked anyhow at the school entrance]
[and injured my leg. It left a gash.]
[So, it's been bleeding for half an hour
now, and there's no sign of stopping.]
[The infirmary's now closed as well.]
[Could this be serious?]
Is the bleeding serious?
This...
How can you tell?
Check if you can see yellow
adipose tissue beneath the skin.
I can't, Mr. Ai.
There's too much blood. I'm scared.
I don't dare to look at it.
Go quickly to Donghu University
Hospital's emergency department.
The wound needs to be cleaned.
It probably needs to be stitched as well.
-It needs to be stitched?
[-Go quickly.]
If the wound gets infected and ulcerated,
you'll need amputation
instead of stitches.
OK. I understand, Mr. Ai.
Thank you, Mr. Ai. See you.
What are you staring at?
What?
Keep on staring at me.
What is it?
I'm going to chop off your head
if you keep on saying that.
This is the hospital. Go outside
if you're going to argue.
Whose head are you going
to chop off? Is it me?
Here, I'll place my head here. Let's
see if you dare to chop it off.
He stared at me first.
What? What is it?
Am I counting sheep to fall asleep?
To hear you baaing at me since just now.
Fighting at the supper stall wasn't
enough. You're going to continue here?
All of you don't have to seek treatment.
Either way, all of you'll
be killed by tetanus.
No, Sister. Of course
we'll seek treatment.
We have to.
-In that case, sit down.
-OK, OK.
Qi Qi was so brave today.
As a reward, here's a lollipop for you.
Look, isn't it cute?
See? An injection doesn't hurt, right?
-Yes.
-Say "thank you, Doctor", quick.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-You're welcome.
We'll get going, doctor.
-Say goodbye to Sister.
-Goodbye.
-Let's go.
-Take care.
OK.
Next.
Sister, it's you.
Do you remember me?
You showed me directions
at the train station.
You even led me to the university.
Donghu University. Do you remember?
What happened to you?
I got a gash on my leg from a shared bike.
Lie on the bed.
Slowly.
Lift up your legs.
Sister,
you looked so cool just now.
You must be what they call
a fierce maiden, right?
Looks like you didn't learn your Chinese
properly before coming to China.
-You remember me?
-I'm going to check your wound first.
You can't use band-aids over it.
It'll get infected.
Bear with it.
The wound is big in size,
though it isn't deep.
It's fine. It'll be OK with
some cleaning and bandage.
But,
a professor from medical department said,
I'll need stitches.
It might even get amputated.
Who told you so?
It's a dentist.
If you're gong to listen to him,
go look for him to get your leg amputated.
I'll listen to you.
It'll begin now.
Bear with me.
Carrot and strawberry,
which one do you prefer?
From what I know,
these two are from different categories.
Choose one.
Carrots.
Hold this.
Squeeze it if you feel pain later.
This is so cute.
It'll start now.
Sister,
give me the strawberry as well.
Is it that bad?
Even elementary school kids
are braver than you.
I'm just curious what it's like.
This strawberry looks nicer.
Sister,
you look beautiful when you smile.
Stay still.
The car couldn't go any further.
What should we do?
It can't be helped. I guess we could
only walk for the rest of the journey.
It's not too bad. We shouldn't
be far away from the hotel.
[Turn left to Dongshan Hot Spring Hotel]
I think we just have to walk a little.
Let's go.
Do you want to button up your coat first?
Don't you have this
bunnies' ears hat?
Why don't you wear it?
This?
Wear it. It's better
than being in the cold.
It looks cute on you.
Let's go.
[Liu Bao Chang.]
Mr. Ai, I'll walk in the front.
OK.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Keep the wound dry for three days.
Come on Thursday to change dressing.
Keep the wound dry for three days?
Does it mean I can't shower?
You can, if you can guarantee
to keep the wound dry.
How do you guarantee that?
Lift it up when I shower?
Otherwise, just don't do it.
Does it mean I can't exercise either?
You still want to exercise
with wound of this size?
What if there's an infection?
But I exercise everyday.
What happens if there's an infection?
If there's an infection,
you'll get amputated.
Sister, you're scaring me again.
Don't shower or exercise.
Symptoms of inflammation are
redness, swelling, heat, and pain.
Come to the hospital quickly
if you have these symptoms.
So, out of these four
symptoms, if I only have one,
should I come?
Yes.
You're quite afraid of dying.
I cherish my life.
Any other questions?
If not, I'm going off work.
Yes. It has nothing to do with my legs,
but it's been bothering
me for awhile. Can I ask?
Go ahead.
That is, recently, when I sleep,
if I lie on my back,
my chest would feel stuffy.
But if I turn over, it's fine.
In that case, just turn over.
Also, I bought new glasses.
I'm wearing contacts now,
but if I change to the new glasses,
I'd feel very dizzy.
In that case, don't wear it.
Another thing.
That is, last time, after you hit my head,
I felt the left side of my head
swelled this much compared to
the right side of my head.
It became this much bigger.
It swelled. It became this much bigger.
Come here. Move your head over.
What about I hit the right side
of your head so it becomes equal?
It's fine, thank you.
Anymore questions? No, right?
Sister, so, next Thursday when
I come here to change dressing,
will you be here?
I don't know.
See you.
Hang in there.
We're just few hundred metres
away from our destination.
Look.
It's so beautiful.
[I suddenly feel like trying]
[how it tastes.]
Wait.
Are you all right?
Blood.
The wire breaks easily from
sudden change in temperature.
Here, let me have a look.
What do I do now?
Give me a minute.
This way,
the wire won't scrap the
inside of your mouth.
All done.
[Why are his hands burning hot?]
Mr. Ai, did you realize your
hands are unusually warm?
Let's go.
Wait.
Mr. Ai, you have a fever.
So, you went to the town
just now, it's to buy medicine?
But I'm fine now.
Let's go.
Wait.
In fact, I have one more here.
Why don't you wear it too?
It's fine, I don't need it.
Wear it.
Insert this in.
Done.
It's better than nothing.
It looks cute on you.
Let's go.
[Many years later,]
[I could still remember this scene.]
[I thought I had to spend a
long, dark night on my own.]
[But because of him,]
[the piercing cold winds were
erased from my memories.]
[What's left was the moonlight
reflected on the ground,]
[and the silhouettes of two persons]
[wearing bunnies' ears in the snow.]
[Friend marked as favorite, Zhang Teng]
[Delete]
[How many people can remain
with each other forever?]
[Delete friend?]
[Yes.]
[In a sea of people,]
[what's the probability
for two persons to meet?]
Thursday.
It really is me.
[If we could walk to the end together,]
[it'd be such a happy feeling.]