[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 32]
Even if he did betray us,
I will arrest him by myself.
Wu Siyue.
Wu Siyue!
Brother.
Where do you want to look for him now?
What matters now is not Li Beiqi,
but the Ceremony of Light.
Noodles of Gourmets. Enjoy.
Have a try.
This is good.
Take care!
I just don't understand
why Sir Wu
asked us to listen to Baili Hongyi.
Exactly.
What the hell can this blue blood know?
He can never find the Thunder of Four Season Clan.
How come this terrible task
fell on our shoulders?
Baili Hongyi even said our Services
can't be wholly trusted,
and he'd only accept those screened by Madam Wu.
Guys,
it seems
we need to teach this Baili Hongyi a lesson.
How's it going at the ports?
Everything is normal.
[Map of Luoyang]
The boats and the nearby boatmen
have been checked these days.
How about canals
and the short-stay boatmen?
Have you checked those?
All the ports are heavily guarded.
Passing with a big amount of Thunder
is almost impossible.
[Map of Luoyang]
The Ceremony of Light is so important.
How can you settle for 'almost?'
How about the south market of Luoyang?
I closed it down two days ago.
I've checked the stores, canals, trees,
and even mortar joints.
Everything was normal.
How about the gates to the Unwelcome Well?
The Well was locked down two days ago.
During the Ceremony,
no one can go in or out.
Okay.
After the Ceremony,
lift the lockdown immediately.
Yes.
I've checked Dingding Gate.
No issue was found.
However, I'd like to know your opinion on one thing.
There are some bird nests
in the tall trees near the gate.
I wonder if we need to burn them down,
in case Four Season Clan
will do something with them.
No need.
The places I circled
need rechecks.
How many exactly?
To be on the safe side,
the more, the better, of course.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
One recheck is surely not enough.
Apart from the places you circled,
there are a few more areas nearby.
We need to recheck those as well.
Exactly.
True.
Our Services can't be wholly trusted.
Who knows if some mole
will secretly help
Four Season Clan with their plans?
-Yeah.
-Exactly.
I suggest
we shall check the areas we're in charge of,
then we can swap
and check again.
We must ensure nothing goes wrong
at the Ceremony.
Good idea.
Let's do it.
If we are quick,
half a month will be enough.
The thing is that
the Ceremony of Light
will begin in two days.
None of you can imagine
the power of Thunder, right?
The Thunder
is a very powerful explosive.
Only about 800 kg of it
can blow half of the south market into ashes.
The enemies would go to any lengths
to create chaos in Luoyang.
But you, the interior guards
who should protect the city,
think one check will be more than enough.
To you, everything will be fine
because there has been no problem before.
You don't even bother to work
or think harder.
The places I circled on the map
need rechecks.
Tell me the results by evening.
Yes, my lord.
Have a seat.
Toxins!
Bingzhu, mind the toxins!
She has dried herbs there.
My father and I picked them in the mountains.
Is this your home?
Yeah.
It's late now.
I'll take you there early in the morning.
I'll be upfront, though.
I won't go in.
I'll get you some food.
Help yourselves.
Smells good.
Miss,
do you live here alone?
It's great.
I live alone, too.
What a coincidence!
Any water?
A minute.
Here.
Thanks.
How old are you?
Eighteen.
What's the problem?
Have you always lived here?
I can't remember,
but since I could remember things,
I've been living here with my father.
Then where's he?
Picking herbs in the mountains.
He'll be back in a few days.
Are there only you and your father
in your family?
My mother died while giving birth to me.
So, do you sell herbs for a living?
There are many herbs in the mountains,
so my father and I take turns
to go downhill and sell herbs.
We get good prices at the stores.
What's wrong?
Any problem?
No.
It's just that the smell is pungent.
Yeah.
Having a place to live is good enough.
True. My house also...
Where are you going?
The woodshed.
I'm not interested in
sharing a room with two men.
We can't let the hostess sleep in the woodshed.
It's cold at night.
You're a young girl.
It would be hard to bear.
Let us sleep there.
We'll set off at dawn.
Don't be late.
How about I...
The girl is so nice.
[Qingye, Disciple of Four Season Clan]
Are you saying Gao Bingzhu blew Qingye's cover
and controlled her?
Take my order.
Ask all the archers to stand by
to kill Gao Bingzhu.
Yes, my lady.
But...
My lady,
Gao has Qingye.
Even if she died,
it'd be a sacrifice for our Clan.
It'd be worth it.
Alright. Stop.
It won't work.
Stop.
I'm so disappointed.
Such a shame. You are so young.
You can find a good husband...
You wanted to kill me from the start, right?
How did you know that?
You said you've been living here
with your father,
but when I asked you for water,
you didn't even know where the water tank was.
You are not familiar with this house.
Any water?
The herbs you're drying by the window
are called Atractylodes.
They are shade-loving plants.
A girl who picks herbs for a living
should know that for sure.
No wonder my senior, the 16th Night,
died at your hands.
You...
Tell me,
where is Four Season Palace?
Tell me where Four Season Palace is!
You'll be dead tonight.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you crazy?
Follow me.
Run.
Run! Run!
Siyue,
did you stay up all night?
Brother, I'm fine.
[With Fortitude And Loyalty]
Li Beiqi took away the deployment map.
We need rearrangement.
Too many people and things are involved
in the Ceremony.
There isn't enough time.
All we can do now
is to check if we've neglected anything
and to deploy more people.
I will not let him have any chance.
Sir Wu,
someone from the Intelligence Services
wants to see Madam Wu.
This way.
That way!
[Li Beiqi was last seen at Anyuan Freight]
Anyuan Freight?
When establishing the Intelligence Services,
Her Majesty stressed
that we can't meddle in the affairs
of the Interior Guard Services.
But Li Beiqi can be related to Four Season Clan,
and the Ceremony of Light is being threatened.
So, Lord Chu has to make a compromise.
Madam Wu, I came here to remind you
not to tell others about this.
I know.
Right. If you'll excuse me.
Bingzhu,
your wound...
Why did you save me?
You knew I won't tell you anything.
In your eyes,
I should be of no use.
A surprise, huh?
You didn't expect
they would kill you, right?
I am from the Clan.
I'll die for the Clan.
It's worth it.
Your Clan
does not tolerate those who fail.
What's more,
you are in our hands.
Once you are of no use,
you will be killed.
The same goes for everyone.
The 16th Night was your senior, right?
She told me that
lives were of no value.
To achieve her goal,
she could kill as many as she wanted.
it doesn't matter
if you're noble, poor, good, or bad.
As long as you can stay alive,
and accomplish your mission,
you can kill
all you want.
But I think
we all have parents.
We are flesh and blood
and we have dignity.
Each life is precious.
I saved you
because you are
a living human being.
I must've done evil
in my previous life.
Every time I was with you,
I was so close to death.
But I am still with you.
Why is that?
Am I bewitched?
There are roses of Sharon on both ways.
Which should we take?
Someone's here.
Follow me.
My lord, let me fill your cup.
Here.
My lord, please enjoy.
The Noodles of Gourmets
are indeed the best in Luoyang.
I'm waiting for Peipei.
Which lady are you here for?
You're waiting for Peipei?
Yes.
I made a reservation half a month ago.
You can't meet Peipei.
What are you talking about?
Peipei is not your wife.
Why can't I meet her?
Because I said so!
Get out of here!
Let go!
Get out of here! Now!
Stop it!
I'm telling you to get out!
Stop!
My lord, calm down.
The guests are all watching.
I still have a business to run.
My lord,
Lady Peipei wants to see you.
Chunhe.
You made a scene in Hong Xiao Fang,
but I didn't blame you.
Now, you've driven my guest away.
What on earth do you want, my lord?
I...
I was just trying to protect you.
Please leave then, my lord.
I'm not Chunhe anymore.
I don't need your protection.
At least you're willing to see me.
You admitted you are Chunhe.
It doesn't matter if you are Peipei or Chunhe,
in my mind,
you've never changed.
You keep talking about the past.
Men
are somewhat obsessed
with what they haven't got.
I suppose this is
how you feel about me.
I'll let you have me today.
Don't come again.
You've been away from Luoyang for years.
You probably don't know
I have known too many nobles in Luoyang.
I'm not that Chunhe
everyone could bully anymore.
You don't deserve to be my guest,
but since we have a history,
let me pay you back today.
Chunhe,
how could you be like this?
It's all my fault!
I didn't protect you.
Chunhe.
No one can protect me.
I can.
How?
The Liu family has declined.
Do you think you can
control those nobles with your background?
Can you use your title
to keep ordering people around?
Chunhe.
Leave.
Hong Xiao Fang is not somewhere you should come.
Please
take today as my reciprocation.
This is the end of us.
If you dare to disturb my guest again,
I'll get you thrown out.
Do you mean I don't deserve
to get into Hong Xiao Fang, given who I am?
Chunhe.
Just go down from here.
From here?
Do you mean
Four Season Palace is down the mountains?
Yes.
The vine ladder will give you a shortcut,
but it can only bear
one person's weight.
Bingzhu,
are we going down from here?
Think about it.
If the girl
-is up to something...
-I'll go down.
Go back.
I'm already here. Why...
I'll go down.
You...
Go back.
What if...
Go.
Okay.
Stay alive.
I know you won't believe me that easily.
If I go first,
I'll probably run away.
There can also be traps
down there waiting for you.
But if you go down first,
I will probably
cut the ladder up here.
So it's up to you
to go or not to.
Leave.
To Four Season Clan,
you're of no use.
If you go with me,
they will take your life.
If you leave now,
you can survive.
I won't survive now that I'm one of them.
No matter where I go,
they'll come after me.
I was raised by them, though.
So, my life only belongs to them.
Don't you have any families?
Actually, I know another girl
who even looked a bit like you.
But she has a different personality.
She laughed and cried a lot.
She was curious about everything.
My mother's Qiongguo candy was her favorite.
Have you tried Qiongguo candy?
I saved all the good stuff for her,
but she was too spoiled.
Once she was not satisfied,
she would cry and yell.
My mother always thought
I was bullying her.
If she is still alive,
she should be of your age.
Then where's the girl now?
She's gone missing.
I don't know where she is.
Bye.
Without me leading the way,
how are you going to get in?
I've had an idea.
Four Season Clan is making a big move
and may overlook you.
Leave now,
and you'll probably make it.
[Map of Luoyang]
Have you sealed the dry wells
in the south market?
Yes.
How about Tianjin Bridge?
Reinforced.
The Heavenly Temple...
The Heavenly Temple is the top priority.
Her Majesty will go there and light candles.
By then,
at least half of the interior guards
will guard there
to ensure nothing goes wrong.
Sir Wu.
You didn't sleep, did you?
We need to ensure
Her Majesty's safety at the Ceremony.
We can't drop our guard.
I've seen your work.
This is indeed more precise
than the previous deployment map.
It seems that
even an ant will be denied entry,
not to mention
the Clan people.
I'm still worried that I might've
overlooked something.
Even Homer sometimes nods.
I suggest you go back
and have a rest now.
I'll be here.
You've been working hard,
[Keep Order For Her Majesty]
but as the Ceremony approaches,
we, the interior guards,
must be extra diligent
and carry out the work seriously.
No negligence is allowed.
Yes, sir!
Nobles? The end of us?
The end of us!
Get me wine!
Where's wine?
My lord,
you can't go on.
I can't...
Do I not get to drink?
Don't I?
Liu Feng,
what are you doing?
Sister,
I met Chunhe.
But she... she...
she is now Peipei in Hong Xiao Fang.
She doesn't want to talk to me. She despises me.
Why is she like this now?
Sister, please help me.
I miss Chunhe.
Please help me.
She was not like that.
-Listen to me, Liu Feng.
-Sister.
Back then,
Chunhe had to leave our family.
As a girl, she had to live on her own in Luoyang.
Perhaps
she had her reasons.
What reasons?
She must've been lying to me!
Liu Feng...
You're also lying to me.
Okay.
Do you know Hong Xiao Fang?
Come on.
Liu Feng.
Hong Xiao Fang. Let's drink together.
Come on.
Join us.
Liu Feng, stop messing around.
You also know Hong Xiao Fang, right?
-Come.
-Liu Feng!
Let's drink together.
I have money.
A lot.
Uncle Baili,
take Liu Feng to bathe and get changed.
Look at yourself.
You are not yourself at all.
Let go!
Uncle Baili,
take good care of him.
Yes, my lady.
For the Thunder that is fully processed,
they'll just need to ignite it
and it will explode in a minute.
How large is the blast area?
It depends on the weight.
If it's heavy enough,
everything within 150 m
will be blown into ashes.
That is to say,
the bombers...
They'll become shattered bones.
Didn't I tell you to leave?
Why are you following me?
I don't know where to go.
You're new here,
and you saved me.
If you believe me,
follow me.
Don't worry.
There's no one else.
Come in.
[Map of Luoyang]
What is this place?
Lady of Autumn's room.
Then where is she?
She took the Clan members to Luoyang.
For what?
I don't know.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You didn't ask me.
[Map of Luoyang]
They're not going to
attack so many places, are they?
No idea.
The Patriarch?
Is this Lord Freedom?
It's strange.
Why is a portrait of the Patriarch here?
Connecting legacies from the Wei dynasty.
Stars are buried underground.
Stay back!
The rhyme is called Lianshan Rhyme.
I heard Lord of Spring and Lady of Autumn
mention it.
The plan that the Clan has worked on for years
hides in the rhyme.
Take me to Luoyang,
or I'll destroy it.
Don't!
[Anyuan Freight]
My lady,
how can I help you?
Three days ago,
this man rented a cart from you.
People rent our carts every day.
How can I remember each of them?
How about now?
I remember him.
A young lad
in his 20s.
Handsome.
Which cart did he rent?
He rented all of these.
The Thunder.
Where did he go?
We have our rules.
We can't disclose
customer information.
Where did he go?
Hanjia Granary.
[Hanjia Granary]
Hurry up.
Unload the carts.
Okay.
Li Beiqi!