Unforgettable Love
Xiaobao's parents passed away
on the way
to the hospital.
Then Xiaobao was a baby.
At that time,
no one could help me to handle this.
Then you woke up
but couldn't
recall the accident.
After that we had no clue.
Even the police's investigation stalled.
I could only tell you that
your accident happened
on the way to visit your brother.
So did it have anything to do
with Yiyue?
On that day,
Dr. Qin passed by
and saved Xiaobao.
At that time you were thrown outside the car,
so she didn't notice you.
But you,
though drowsy,
might watched her dark figure
and heard her voice.
So the reason you want to expel her
is to prevent her from
reminding me of this accident.
Qiaoyan,
this is also the reason
why I've been pestered
by Zhang Cheng in these years.
For our family
and Xiaobao,
you should calm down.
Aunt,
what if Xiaobao knows
that I have something to do
with his parents' death.
Do you really think
he can regard me as his dad?
Hi, mom.
Yiyue,
are you at home?
I'm coming to see you two with your dad.
We two?
Where are you now?
Close to your home.
He Qiaoyan's home?
Yes,
but I'd like to call it yours.
Mom, come back now.
I have something to tell you.
We are almost there. Talk about it later.
It's not my home now.
Do you mean
you plan to get married
just for Xiaobao's illness,
don't you?
Yes, but I don't know
from which moment,
we gradually fall in love with each other.
So
we decided to
start dating.
And now,
why did you break up?
What's more,
why do you want to go abroad
after breaking up with him?
Because of him?
Did he force you?
I'll stand up for you.
Calm down, dad.
It's not his fault.
It's mine.
You meet your crush?
No.
But it was I
that want to be unattached.
I hurt him.
And he was so depressed.
Please don't bother him.
What...
Alright, Lao Qin.
Girl, if you are not in the mood,
you can vent your depression.
You don't need to pretend to be fine.
It's OK to be not OK.
I'm fine, mom.
Look at me,
I'm happy.
And studying in German
is always my dream.
Take it easy.
Don't cry.
Yiyue,
we'll support your decision.
But in German,
you should take care of yourself.
If you are bullied,
remember to call us.
We'll fly to German.
Come on,
nobody can bully me.
Trust me.
Mr. Wen
please sign here.
Just put there.
By the way,
please get the market director for me.
Alright.
Something wrong with the contract?
I want him to win this market,
not to bargain with loss.
I was pleased to hear that
you've made a deal with Wenmei Group.
I used to be idle.
But now that I decide to do it,
I'll be responsible.
Anything else?
Could you please tell me
that what makes you
change so much?
So diligent.
It's surprising.
It's you.
I want you know that
I'm not so bad.
I'm a grown man.
You can trust me.
But I'm not someone.
You can be yourself.
Why do you care about what I think of you?
I do care about your thoughts.
You rubbished me.
And you accused me of
a good-for nothing.
It hurt me.
There's no bet,
no joke or performance.
I wanna take everything serious,
including you.
Do you want to
raise my salary?
No.
Well, no way.
I'm fine.
If you can't help taking pills,
you can do something
to distract attention.
It's good for you.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Visit the customers with me tonight.
You ought to be hate to
visit customers the most.
At eleven o'clock tonight.
Sorry,
I can't company you.
Why not?
Yiyue is leaving tomorrow.
I've promised to
have dinner with her.
Where is she going?
Don't you know
that Yiyue had broken up with Mr. He.
She is leaving to German tomorrow.
He said nothing.
It's too late.
I should leave now.
You said you would cook today
to surprise us.
Just take it, sir.
I'm too tired to cook.
I'm exhausted!
Washing vegetables is tiring enough.
It's called family hotpot.
Just help yourself.
Are you sure
that the ingredients are clean?
Is it safe
to add the raw and cooked together?
What's more,
after dinner,
how do we remove
the odour of the hotpot?
We can't eat spicy food today.
Put it away.
Drink more hot water.
Are you alright?
Ummm,
can we start now?
It's boiled.
Let's dig in!
Why don't you start?
Here you are.
Since you don't want to eat,
shall we have a drink
to wish my dream come true?
Come on.
Alcohol
cannot bring happiness
nor remove sufferings.
You know that
we two
are from different world.
Cheers.
Toast to our dream.
Qin Yiyue
I agree to break up.
Best wish to your dream.
Let's drink!
Ruowei
the beer is
too spicy!
It's too spicy.
Cheers.
It's done.
I'm so sorry
that I live in your house
and often bother you.
It's okay.
After all,
I live on my own.
But you,
do you wanna keep escaping from your families?
Escaping
is not a good solution.
It's my own business.
Please don't comment on it.
Sorry, I just...
You just feel that since you lend me a hand,
you can judge my life.
I'll move.
I'll pay you back.
Sorry,
I didn't mean that.
Lin Wei
Sorry,
I'm not intended.
I found it
by accident,
and I just got a glimpse.
I swear that I didn't finish it.
I only read the page
which you wrote down
your preparation to express love to Qin Yiyue.
Please trust me.
It's OK.
If my words hurt you
and made you unhappy,
I can apologize.
Just live here.
I have to go.
Good bye.
Let me see you off.
Have you told her?
Nope.
I would like to say
but Zhou Ziyang chased her first.
She was really glad that day.
She said
she had a boyfriend
and she planned to study in German.
They broke up afterwards
and she didn't go to German.
I reckoned that it was a chance,
but I failed to grasp it.
That's He Qiaoyan's style.
Once he's determined, he'll work quickly.
You who hesitates is lost.
They two
will get married soon.
No, they've broken up.
Yiyue is coming to German tomorrow.
It's so weird.
I can tell that
He Qiaoyan is so
obsessed with Qin Yiyue.
Why do they break up?
I don't know.
Since they are determined to
split with each other,
they must
have some reason.
Why don't you go to German with her?
You've missed two opportunities.
Now or never.
Good night.
Yiyue,
feel free to call me
if you meet troubles.
You can rely on us.
Can you come to German
as soon as I call you?
I would
if you need me.
Well, Ning Fang is a friend indeed.
Okay, guys,
I'm not a kid.
I can handle issues by myself.
And you must take care of yourselves.
Call me when you arrive.
Yiyue, I'll miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Seeing off Yiyue.
Call me later.
Is my cousin with you?
Why do you think he's here?
I can't find him.
You can't find him?
What do you mean?
I've called him several times,
but he didn't answer my phone.
I went to his home on this morning.
My aunt said
after last morning
he left from the Heshi Group,
he never contacted her.
He wasn't at home and didn't answer my phone.
I guess
he had some unscheduled work
or took a business trip.
Or he was not in the mood
and went to a bar.
It's usual for a grown man
to stay out all night.
Take it easy.
I'll hang up.
It's weird.
Never would he
let Xiaobao sleep at home alone.
Hello, aunt.
Wen Gu said He Qiaoyan disappeared.
What's wrong?
Did he go to visit you?
He didn't.
We just had one talk yesterday.
What did he said?
Nothing important.
What's the matter?
He got it.
Qiaoyan
Qiaoyan, it's not your fault.
There's always something wrong
with my wearable.
I've tried many methods
to repair it.
It's not the fault of software upgrade.
Maybe it doesn't work
because of the hardware conflict.
What's wrong?
My algorithm.
My algorithm is false.
Where's the fault?
It's my fault!
Qiaoyan
Listen,
every perfect product
has to go through thousands of trials
before being marketed.
There are so many products
and techniques in your company,
all can provide health service,
why do you
value the wearable so much?
It concerns me
because the wearable can
monitor people's pulse.
The pulse indicates life.
I wanna grasp the feeling of life.
Got it?
Like this?
Please go home with me.
Xiaobao need you.
So do I.
Qiaoyan
Leave me alone.
You should have been in German.
I canceled the plan.
I won't leave to German.
We've broken up.
Get off my case.
Qiaoyan
Yiyue
I'm worrying about you.
Would you please tell me
what happened?
Five years ago,
He Qiaoyan had a car crash
when taking his brother' family out.
The couple died on the spot,
while Xiaobao and He Qiaoyan survived.
Since then,
he suffered from PTSD
and forgot the crash.
Now he knew the fact.
Ning Fang
As a psychologist,
you must have met
many similar cases.
Please tell me
what should I do to help him?
Six years ago, I met a patient
in the same condition.
Even till now,
he didn't recover
and his condition is getting worse.
What I could do
was to watch him
being tortured by the terrible memories.
Qiaoyan won't lose himself.
Yiyue
You are a psychologist, too.
You know how vulnerable
a man could be.
Make it clear.
I agree with He Qiaoyan.
You should go to German.
Now that he's in trouble,
I should support him.
He needs my help.
What could you do?
I...
I'll make it.
Er...
Yiyue
It may cost
the rest of your life
to help him.
And the results can be worse.
It can ruin your life.
Stop it.
I've made up my mind.
Just for him,
you can give up
your dream.
In my heart
I'm sure that
a future without He Qiaoyan
is awful.
I've explained
to Dr. Huang.
I'll keep working
until someone
take over my role.
But I won't go to German.
Communication technique is advanced now.
Video call is as effective
as face to face talks.
Wen Gu told me
the accident of Mr. He.
It's really
a horrible experience for him.
He will make it.
I believe him.
Are you sure to be with him?
His pessimism
is like a black hole,
it will devour you
if you approach him.
It's OK.
I'm full of energy.
Devouring me
is not easy.
You can call me
if you need me.
Being with you,
he'll be OK.
I'm hungry. Can you make noodles for me?
Well, sure.
Love ya.
Mommy is back!
Good morning. I made breakfast for you.
Xiaobao
she's not you mom.
She's...
Wash up first.
Let's dig in, boy.
Xiaobao,
dad has some troubles recently.
It takes time to solve it.
Let's wait for him.
How is it going?
Today I have something
to discuss with you.
I'm listening.
I overheard
Mr. Zhang's phone.
He said he had sent 10 million yuan
to help his brother pay off debts
on August 11 five years ago.
Ten million yuan?
He's a driver.
Where did he get so much money?
What's more,
that day
happened to be
the day after their car crash.
You mean
that brake failure
was sabotage?
Are you fine?
Are you hungry?
I cooked for you.
But it's cold.
I microwave it now.
You should have some.
Your hand hurts?
I burned it when cooking.
It's OK.
I'll get you medicine.
Don't bother.
Qiaoyan
I have one thing
that want you to do.
It may be difficult for you.
I wish
you can try to
recall the accident.
I don't believe that
it's your fault.
Are you not believing the fact,
or unwilling to accept it?
You take it the wrong way.
I've said
I didn't want to see you.
If you continue to come here,
we will move.
It's late.
Come back home.
I can get him.
It's wounding for him
to recall the accident.
Yiyue
do you really reckon
that it's not his fault?
The police said the brakes went wrong
and the roads were slick with rain.
But he's a good driver.
He had never
sped before.
There must be other reasons
for that accident.
Only by finding out it
can release him for the suffering.
As years passed,
we can't find
useful information.
Now only He himself
can be his saviour.
But Mr. He
doesn't have the guts to
recall the memories of that day.
You psychologists
should have solutions
to his condition.
It's up to him.
If he doesn't wanna recall it,
we have no solution.
I've told you
that don't come here.
We'll move tomorrow.
It's me.
Dr. Ning, what are you doing here?
Yiyue is so tired
that she's resting at home.
After all,
she's not your wife.
It's not her responsibility
to help you.
What do you mean?
You said you would move.
Then do what you said.
Since you decide
to leave Yiyue,
just do it.
It's none of your business.
This afternoon,
I'll express love to Yiyue
beside the lake in our campus.
Do you think
she will accept?
Accept it or not,
it doesn't matter.
I want to express
my love to her.
I can wait she
to accept me.
If you move,
she can say goodbye to the past
and live a better life.
I'll persuade her to leave to German.
And I'll go with her.
I'll help her
to pursue her dream.
Good for you.
Wish your happiness.
Where are we going?
You'll know when you get here.
Yiyue, would you like to go with me?