What?
Jun Ye is entangled by other women\
Outdoor basketball court
Wait, I'll be right there soon
She should entangle Jun Ye
She doesn't know me, Anna
Outdoor basketball court
What's happening?
Where's the woman entangling Jun Ye
There
So fast
Please be a professional judge
Don't stay too close to the court
If it were not for me
and he made the shot
Chu Ran couldn't have defended him
Stupid Judge
You are just helping Chu Ran
Now it's Chu Ran's turn to attack
Shen
I'll modify your best move
to salute to Qingmeng which I will leave
Shen
Is this your famous move
Super far three-point shot
It is not the same
This three-point shot
has no knee bending
The most important thing of super far three-point shot is the take-off height
Using taking-off to power the shot
Jun Ye hasn't played for too long
He forgot
No matter how good your skills are, if you don't practice more
you will lag behind
I have to say that Chu Ran wins this shot
Jun Ye
Am I born to chase you
I don't know why you quit
But now
Don't you want to have a real
battle with Chu Ran
And win back the things you lost
Come back, you can do this
None of your business！
What's your problem
Think about this
Let's put this beside first
Schoolmaster
It's the decision of the council
Can't you see we are in a meeting
What's your name, what is your major
Sport Management, Su Nuanxia
Su Nuanxia, you are the daughter of Su Li
Su Li
Isn't he
Minister, you go first
I'll find you later
Schoolmaster, how about dismissing the basketball club
Let's talk later. Close the door
Me
okay
Nuanxia
I've seen you when you were a child
You've grown up so fast, have a seat
Schoolmaster
I heard that they will dismiss the basketball club
and reconstruct the stadium
I'm surprised that you know so quickly
Since last time
we lost the game to Shenhua
You father
the team dismissed
the students of Qingmeng University
have lost their passion to basketball
The basketball court has been in vain since then
but also require a significant amount of maintenance
Is there no turning around
It's the decision of the council
Can you fight for this
I want to
But Nuanxia
you have no team members
How can I convince them
That's easy
As long as we have the basketball club
we will recruit members
You know
A lot of people are passionate with basketball
What about the coach
I'll be the coach of Qingmeng Basketball Club
I will go to the end with them
Schoolmaster
I didn't do this for my father
but also for myself
If I don't try
I will regret it all my life
Qingmeng has the potential
We shouldn't give up basketball
So please give me a chance
Give me
and give Qingmeng a chance
But in order to save the basketball club
the first thing you have to do is to gather a team
That's easy
and you have to lead them to defeat Shenhua University
so that I will have the advantage
to convince the council
Thank you, schoolmaster
I'll not let you down
Let's go to every room and deliver our flyers
We can't let any masters go
Let's take them all down
You're so tough
But now we have to find another master
Go!
Hey boss, is Ling Xuan here?
What do you want for drink?
I mean, is Ling Xuan, your deliver boy, here
Two cups of latte, thanks
Here's the situation
Usually at this time,
few people order take-outs here
So Ling Xuan will come later
Okay, we'll wait here
Then bring us a tiramisu
Ok
Nuanxia, do we continue
Yes, we have to find him
Why are you still here?
I forgot to tell you
Ling Xuan just called
He said he won't come today
You...
Don't be angry
Come on
I'll give you two VIP cards
20% off next time
It's you again
I'm here to ask...
what do you think of joining the basketball club?
Hey, don't be so boring
Boring? I'm longing for talents
I say for the last time
I'm not interested in basketball, please go
What's the sound
Is another girl breaking in
Say I'm not here, please
Ye, open the door, Ye
Aunt, Jun Ye is not here
I'm here for the Wi-Fi
It can't be right
I saw a girl coming in
She must be hiding
Find with me
Aunt, aunt
What's this
This is your rematch against Chu Ran
Solid line represent you
Dotted line stands for Chu Ran
And then the triangle is a disguised breakthrough
Circle for shot
You did well
Of course, I'm professional
How is it?
Do you want to join?
It's easy
Just fill in the Application Form
Toilet contract
It will be a legend of our history
What's the sound
It must be from next door
It's okay It's okay! It's okay!
Aunt, aunt
How dangerous
If you're caught, you've had it
Don't scream, I'll get rid of it
You look afraid
How can I be afraid
Then why are you shaking?
How come? I will step on it
Coming
Where's aunt?
Lucky for you
She just left,
otherwise
you can be dispelled for ten times
It's a misunderstanding, you know
I came for basketball
Are you okay?
You get out
I don't want to repeat
I'm impressed, Nuanxia
You break into Master Ye's dorm for the second time
It's useless
He still refused
It's right
It's not that easy to convince players
See
I sacrificed a lot to convince Ling Xuan
My gosh
He worked so hard
Doesn't he have to study
According to my investigation,
as long as it's not against the law, and it can make money
he's done them all
No exaggeration to say
He earned money from everyone in Qingmeng
Have you thought of how to take him down
As the VIP of eating
I can make him suffer
form living
According to my investigation,
the cafe we went to last time
Ling Xuan is in charge of the delivery there
If we order a take-out now
He will be the one to deliver
Hello, I'd like two cups of Hong Kong-style milk tea
Hello, I'd like two cups of Tapioca milk tea
Hello, I'd like two cups of Milk green team
Hello, I'd like two cups of Kumquat lemon tea
Stop
Xiao Tutu, do you want to drink milk tea like water
I paid
Miss, this is sixth floor
Do you know how many times I've come to the sixth floor?
I'm warning you, stop
Ling Xuan, as long as you join the club,
we will let you go
You can keep this going if you are not afraid of gaining weight
I can change my job
It's alright
I have Plan B
This convenience store
is another play Ling Xuan works for
Hello, does Ling Xuan work here
Do you know when will he come
I know, let me
When does Ling Xuan
work here
Usually after 10:00 a.m.
That's right
Such abnormal work intensity
Nuanxia, do you think he skips classes
I'll eat this
Nuanxia, Ling Xuan's here
Nuanxia, are you okay?
schoolmaster
get up
Ling Xuan
schoolmaster
Doing part-tame work is a good thing
But you have to walk slowly
and be careful
Thank you schoolmaster, bye
Hold on
What's wrong, Nuanxia
Schoolmaster, I think
Ling Xuan is a computer science student
He has a lot of classes
He has no time for part-time jobs
So I don't think
this is a part-time job
He must be skipping classes
I...
Ling Xuan
If you don't attend classes often, you can't get credits
You understand this, right?
I'll have the counselor keep an eye on you
Don't schoolmaster
I'll go back for classes
Yes, Ling, it's not good to skip classes
You are something
You'll know about me when you join the basketball club
As long as you join the team,
you can have credits
and there's scholarship if we win
You will also have time for classes
You deserve that
Scholarship?
I heard that Master Ye has a girlfriend
Do you know who she is?
I saw it on the Post Bar
Is it true?
Beauty, Jun Ye has a girlfriend
Do you want to consider me
The schoolmaster has said
if we can't recruit members,
we can't establish the association
If we can't establish the association
They will reconstruct the stadium
As long as we have the club, we can save the stadium
It's not a good thing to take photos of girls in secret
If you like Coach Su
I think you'd better tell her openly
You are so gossip lately
You ordered so many food
to recruit this delivery boy
You got good taste in humans
To recruit members,
you don't even care about your figure
You really sacrificed a lot
You have to think twice
It will be troublesome
Come on, let's go find her
We will have an exam in this class
120 min for you
The score will be included in credit
How come?
So unlucky, it's dark when we finish the exam
Let's find Coach Su tomorrow
I'm not in a hurry
100 minutes left
I can't hand in a blank paper
I have to finish this, even though I don't know anything
Is that okay?
Jun Ye, you can hand in the paper
Thank you, sir
Fighting, Nuanxia
Su Nuanxia is having a PE class
How can I run into her everywhere
Enemies on a Narrow Road
How dare you smash me
You are so cheesy
Why don't you carry the bricks if you have so much strength
Yes, you can't be compared to our Anna
Do you feel shameful to entangle Jun Ye with your looks
Who are you?!
Nuanxia
is so much better than boy crazies like you
You just chase around Master Ye all day
Fangirl
What? forget it, punch her
What are you doing?
Who are you beating?
What are you doing, you fangirl
Hey, what are you doing with my hair
You fangirl
Beat her
Su Nuanxia is the heroine in the picture
hugging Master Ye
Awesome
Master Ye likes this type
You fangirl
You fangirl, fangirl
You hit me?
Take off you hands
Jun Ye, they bullied me
You said ill words first
Is that Master Ye?
Can you keep an eye on your fans
Go back first
Lu Ye is finding you, call him back
I...
Follow me
Wait for me, Jun Ye
Nuanxia, you did something big
It's real between Jun Ye and Su Nuanxia
I didn't expect that Anna is meaningless one
Xiaoqiang, lock the door
Why? Is there anything you can't say outside?
I can help you find team members
You want to join?
I won't
But in order to save the stadium
I can help you
I want you,
not your help
Except me
I can give you anything
I don't want anything besides you
It's an Internet Era
I've posted the recruiting notice on the Bar of our school a long time ago
There should be many replies
Jun Ye
is in love with Su Nuanxia
They left in public hand in hand
There's a picture, there's a truth
How's this hand in hand
It should be like this
What are you doing?
I didn't blaming you for dragging me here
If it were not for you,
how can I be in love with you
We have to make it clear
This bar has high reputation
Why doesn't anyone reply to me?
Clarify, this is Su Nuanxia
I will restate that
I have nothing to do with Jun Ye
Qingmeng Basketball Club
will start recruiting tomorrow
If you have a basketball dream,
let's hold hands
and bring Qingmeng back to the peak
You must not speak for her
You all pay attention on the entertainments on the bar
What's the problem of I looking at beautiful girls
Don't blame this all on us Mushrooms
We didn't
Little sun, big dream
What a cheesy name
Students of the Department of Physical Education work out every day
How could she watch these
Little sun, big dream
Is she a fan of Jun Ye
She should change her profile photo first
People of our Department of Physical Education
will not use such a cute picture as our profile photo
Don't clarify here randomly, just be your cute girl
This
Yun Ye's fans
What are you up to?
I'm helping you clarify
I'm Jun Ye
I had nothing with Su Nuanxia
From today on,
don't let me see these absurd things
They are really together?
Is this real?
It can't be true, my gosh
How is it possible
It's real between Jun Ye and Su Nuanxia
It can't be true
I'm so surprised today
Su Nuanxia
I didn't expect that you haven't gather a team,
but found a boyfriend for yourself
and you broadcasted officially to the whole school
He clarified that there's nothing between us
You know nothing at all
Sometime things get so messed up
Do you think Master Ye is really interested in you
How could it be?
Then why would he
clarify this
I think he did that on purpose
Wait for tomorrow
Brother, look, the Bar is messed up now
They are all gossiping
There are only about ten replies about basketball
They should talk about basketball now
Basketball club is recruiting new members
Have a look
This, thanks
Qingmeng Basketball Club is recruiting new members
Have a look
Send this to them and ask them to sign up
Do you understand?
Yes
Have a look
500 each
After signing up,
remember to send your photo to the group
Do you understand?
I got it! I know!
That's impossible
The reputation of me and Jun Ye is so high
How come no one's here to sign up
Maybe comparing to basketball,
they are more interested in gossips
And that annoying Anna
She posted a message in the bar
in the name of Head of the Arts Department
saying that she doesn't like basketball
and clubs should focus on cultivating our temperament
She's the beauty queen
She has a lot of followers
So I did this for nothing
No
You have Master Ye as your boyfriend
You...
I want to sign up
First come, first served. I came first
Hurry up
Sign up!
Don't try so hard!
We will make this Application Form
Fill in your personal infounding
Give me one
Help me pass this, thanks
Fill in these infounding
Brother, is this okay?
They can't play basketball
We have no time
We have to save the stadium
The stupid club
will sign up for the club
Yes, Anna made a statement
Who dares to sign up
The Jun Ye's fan club sent a message, see
Let me see
What are they doing?
Nuanxia
I've seen your passion,
but in order to join the basketball club,
you have to pass some tests
Tests?
Will it be difficult?
Is it so troublesome to join a club
Relax, just some small tests
Go
All right, guys, stand up
That's great
Congratulations! You three
You can take the second test
More?
Take it easy, everybody!
Just an easy test
Your activates core muscles lacks strength
Leg explosive force is not enough
Look at your shoulder
You can't stand a little bump on the court
No
Go! Go! Go!
Nuanxia. If it keeps going like this,
we can't recruit anyone
There's still people coming
I, I...
I want to sign up
Fill in these infounding
OK, ok, ok
Hey, were you here before
Yes, I remember you
You didn't pass the first round
Was I here? No, I wan't
Do you know what are they recruiting
A weird man
He gives us ￥500
as long as we sign up for the Qingmeng Basketball Club
Do you think he's stupid
Yes
Thanks!
Come on, let go!
We don't recruit girls
I can do nothing
It hurts
Who are you? Why are you messing up here?
Stop!
Couch Su, what a coincidence!
￥500 each for these people
You gathered every kind of people
But no one is suitable. What a waste of money
Su Nuanxia, my brother was trying to help you
Fewer but better
These people can't join the basketball club
What are you doing?