The most important throw of Qingmeng against Shenhua
is now in Chu Ran's hands
What a pity, it didn't score
Yeah, Coach?
Are you okay, coach
What's wrong, coach
Call an ambulance, quick to call an ambulance!
Dad
No matter how this ends,
I will lead Qingmeng to win Shenhua
at all cost
Basketball courts
It's so late, who's still playing
Not bad
There are many talents in Qingmeng
We have to enroll him in the basketball club
Delete it
You played so well
Join the basketball club
Delete it.
You mean the video, don't worry
Although I don't want to admit it
You are pretty handsome in my video
How can you take others' things randomly
Give me
Here
It's so night
you take videos secretly of others
From where this is heading
we should kiss
It doesn't matter if you want to
It's just like this abroad
Boring
Hey
You haven't tell me, what's your name?
Tutu
Wake up, wake up, wake up
You don't sleep
Did you find some thing to eat
See
There are many talents in the school
I just passed the basketball court
and saw this
A boy who's just like a professional player
Do you know who he is
I can see clearly
But he's so great
Is he an old player of Qingmeng
You ask me
Didn't you search many infounding
Wait a moment
What's up?
I was thinking today
we can post in the post bar
Will anyone see this
Just wait and see
Go
okay
Please hurry up and get ready
The game is going to start
What is she wearing
Oh my gosh, it's so weird
Why is she wearing like this
Who
She doesn't have the figure
Zhang Xiaoqiang, who is Zhang Xiaoqiang
Your take-out is here
Shut up!
This is a school selection for the Provincial Games
Zhang Xiaoqiang is getting ready for the 400-meter race
Which is him
3079, there
I tell you
He's the holder of the 400-meter race record
in our school
He's ready
to break his record
He has no time to accompany you
He didn't run yet
Ready
Zhang Xiaoqiang
Run after you take your take-out
I will lose money for exceeding the time
Ready!
Come on!
Fantastic.
The jumping ability and acceleration
He must be a good forward
Luckily, I didn't exceed the time
Congratulations, you must break the record
Remember to give me a thumbs up
Excellent
Hey, are you interested in joining the basketball club
Can I get paid?
I guess no
I'm not interested in that
Beauty, you can ask me to work for money
but I'll pass on playing the basketball
You don't have to turn me down so fast
Cat Coffee, Ling Xuan
Put the team thing aside
The most important thing now
You are right
Cleaning up here
is the first step to regather the group
Why do I have the feeling of
being tricked here to be a cleaning lady
Nonsense?
You are the team manager I chose
Like I will believe you
Come on!
As soon as I heard that you will come back
I started to find handsome guys
find the infounding
of team members
I've organized the profile
of old team players
With Chu Ran and Jun Ye
the leading players of Qingmeng
and our professional coach
we will defeat the Shenhua in no second
Chu Ran has no problem
he will join the team
After all, he's my father's student
I've never heard of this Jun Ye
How's his skills
You didn't even know Jun Ye
and you want to organize a team
Jun Ye is a low profiled
school beauty
The sole successor of Jun group
He's tall and handsome
He's not only good at studying
but also the soul of the old Qingmeng
He has many chasers in the school
and his fans are called mushrooms
I'm asking you
How's his skills of playing basketball
He once refused the invitation of the National Youth Team
His skills
are not worse than your childhood sweetie Chu Ran
They were tied in the team
I heard that
Jun Ye was hiding his skills on purpose
He was better than Chu Ran
Since he can be equal to Brother Chu Ran,
we can meet him
But
What's up?
Jun Ye is so low profiled
and he's kind of weird
Although he's famous,
he never shows
It's even hard to talk to him
He quit
before your father's matter
Quit?
Where's the former players of Qingmeng
They either graduated or went for internships
They are not in the school
It's fine
It's easy to recruit four more people
We will bring out the stand of our basketball club
basketball club tomorrow
I want to choose my players myself
As long as he can play well
No matter it's Jun Ye
what is his name,
I will take him in
This light shall witness my resolution
Why isn't room 402 turning off the light
Hurry up
Regather a basketball club
Basketball club
Have a look
Show your friends
Have a look at basketball club
Have a look
basketball club is recruiting new members
Make way
Basketball club
No
None of them are interested in basketball
Wait here, I'll go to the canteen
Have a look
Have a look at basketball club
basketball club is recruiting new members
Have a look, are you interested
I'm from the school livelihood department
Don't you know that you can't
advertise out of the canteen
Architecture from ancient Greece to ancient Rome
can be called
The most brilliant page in the history of Architecture
Today we say that
Greek column Roman arch
are all classics of that period
About the construction process and data
of these architectures
Vitruvius
recorded in detail in his books
The question is
What is the name of Vitruvius's book
Zhou Haichuan
Zhang Xiaoqiang
Jun Ye
Ten Books on Architecture
What are the three columns
Vitruvius recorded
in his books
Doric column ionic column
And Collins column
All right, guys
We should all learn from Jun Ye
He started reading the English version of Ten Books on Architecture
Good job!
Did you recruit someone?
where's the roll up banner
It's taken by the school livelihood department
Do you think they are not confident in us
because we are girls
Yes
We can't recruit
in the teaching area
Let's go to the basketball court
l'm gonna do my stuff
It sounds reasonable
Go!
Is it not the time?
It must be like this
The students just finished lunch. they don't want to exercise
Let's go there
Yes, yes!
After losing to Shenhua last time
it indeed is a challenge to the players of Qingmeng
but I believe
they will be students who wants to play basketball
We have to let them know
that we are regathering the basketball club
All right, I got it
Boys' dormitory
Have a look
What are you doing
Go out, go out
Will we be spotted
Is it too late
to ask this question
Be quiet!
So tall
Hey, have a look at basketball club
Listen
Out team is recruiting new members
Do you want to have a try
Sorry to interrupt you
This is our handbook
Have a look
If your roommate is interested
you can ask him to call the number on it
Do I have to fill in the forms?
Yes, Tutu
Shen Yingliang, 186cm
Fourth grade, Department of Medicine
Cell number 1872234876
Welcome to sign up
Do you like basketball?
You are in good physical shape
Because I study medicine
compared with other members
I may have less strength
But as to reaction and the ability to control the ball
I can handle that
You are Shen Yingliang
Nuanxia
He is Shen Yingliang, the captain of Chu Ran,
the former scoring guard of Qingmeng
Well, I will take the form
I will hand in this
with a friend next time
I didn't expect to find Shen so quickly
I thought he went for internships
and is not at school
The boy's Dormitory is really a fruitful place
Then how come you didn't know him
You gathered the infounding of the old Qingmeng, didn't you
Shen is not as good-looking as Jun Ye
so I didn't pay much attention
Alright
This is the first step of conquering the boy's Dormitory
We are lucky enough, let's go
basketball club is recruiting new members
Brother Chu Ran
Nuanxia
What are you doing here?
I'm just looking for you
Are players of Qingmeng
not interested in basketball club
No one signed up here
After Couch Su left
the team dismissed
They see basketball as an entertainment
Few are willing to put time in it
It's fine
under our joint efforts
we will regather the team
By the way, let me tell you
At the sports meeting two days ago
I spotted a good prospect
Where are you going
Nuanxia, I have something to tell you
Come on
I'm going to transfer.
Transfer
Didn't you promise that
you will regather the basketball club with me
Nuanxia, sorry
I'm really going to transfer.
Where
Shenhua University
Shen Shenhua University
I'll explain to you later
No need
I know what you are doing
You want to join their team
and play with Han Mo
Although I can't regather Qingmeng with you
but I'm always here
I will help you
You don't have to
Enjoy your time at Shenhua
Now we're over
Brother Chu Ran abandoned the team
Even if we can recruit five members
can we defeat
Shenhua?
It's Okay, we don't need him
We can still defeat Shenhua
Yes, Don't be angry, Nuanxia
At least we have Shen
Tutu, put the things away
Let's call it a day
basketball club is recruiting new members
Welcome to sign up
Basketball club is recruiting new members
Continue?
Yes, there aren't many left
You take care of the top two
I'll be in charge of this row
Hold on, fighting
Excuse me
Delete it
What
Are you interested in the basketball club?
No
You can get to know this
The trophy of the championship
None of your business
How come
You have a picture with coach Zhou Danian
So
You were in a professional team
My dad was coach Zhou's apprentice,
but I have never seen him in person
You are so clumsy
and you want to organize a team
Why is there another girl breaking into Ye's dorm
How could they get in here
Hey
I don't do that on the court
Let's have a try
I'm not interested in basketball
Bye bye
Hey
Do you know the school law
What's your major
What's your name
Aunt, I...
I'm his cousin, explain
No
She's my
elder cousin
Ye, what's going on
She's here to deliver books to me
She didn't make it clear
and went up
See, here are the books
Fine, since Ye said so
You have to go
Don't come here any more
Okay
How about this
I'll give you my contact infounding
Make sure to contact me
when we have the club
Sorry
There's no Application Form
Here
Don't move
How can this woman be so strong
If you want to join the team
do contact me
Bye
Contact me
What are you still doing here, Nuanxia
Come on. Let's go
The aunt will be here
Go!
Paging
The destiny on the basketball court
At eleven two days ago
At the outdoor basketball court
a cute guy that plays basketball so well
I'm so regretful
that I didn't screw up my courage to say hello to him
I hope he can see this
or someone knows him can see this
I'll be waiting for you at the court these days
See me right there
There are over five hundred replies
They all say that he's so handsome
No one knows him
It's alright
The thing is
Someone will definitely come to sign up today
See
Shen, you are here to sign up
Su, did you find your cute guy
You say that
Do you know him
I should
Who is he
Is he your former teammate
No need to hurry
I bring you the friend
I told you
Hey
Your basketball club is already dismissed
I'm just a amateur
Why do you want me to join the basketball club
It's you!
You can wear out iron shoes in fruitless searching,
and then by lucky chance find it without even looking.
iron shoes, who are you saying
Don't be angry, Ling Xuan
Quite good
Not quite good
It's so much better than you
What's the point of bragging
Show me
Fine, how
One on one attack and defense layup
Don't blame me for not protecting girls
No problem
But I have a condition
What?
Will you back out?
You'll have to join the basketball club if you lose
What a cliche
I will not join the association
Besides, what if you lose
I will not
What was that?
Basketball club is recruiting new members
Female coaches singled out male players
Live long to see!
What about the cute guy
Is he the man in the video
What cute guy
What male player and female coach
This kind of battle
Girls are weak in height and strength
There's no doubt
I want to see that.
Jun Ye, you come to the court as well
It's rare
Long time no see, former captain
Why are you here
Xiaoqiang, you are here as well
A girl is regathering the team
Girls
She fell for such an obvious trick
Nice. Nice. Nice
A backward jump shot
This is your best move
What's the feeling of it
being used by a girl
Amateur coach
Amateur manager
Amateur polayers
Go
Hey
It's really you
I was looking for you for quite a while
You haven't tell me, what's your name?
If you want me to join the team
Forget it
Why
I saw that night
You were so good
Master Ye
Nuanxia
The man you saw was him
He's Jun Ye
I told you before
The Master Ye that once refused the National Youth Team
Zhang Xiaoqiang, Shen
The magical players of Qingmeng
are all here
You three
used to play with my father
Your father, Couch Su
Fantastic, guys
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Su Nuanxia
I'm recruiting team members
I want to regather Qingmeng Basketball Club
Hope you can join us
I'm sure with you guys
We can defeat Shenhua
You, defeat Shenhua
Brotherï¼
I'm not interested in that
Sorry, beauty coach
Wait a second
Let go
How can this woman be so strong
Master Ye, calm down
See
With your superb skills
if you don't display them on the court
Are you worthy of the beautiful girls
who cried for you on the court
You posted the paging last night
You two are really decree by destiny.
What post
Let go
Master, please join us
It's my dream to regather the basketball club
and the team needs you
With you
We are sure to beat Shenhua
Master, please join
What are you doing, Nuanxia?
What are you doing here?
Captain
I heard basketball club is recruiting new members
So I came to see
Didn't expect you to know!
Long time no see, Jun Ye
Can you call him Jun Ye
It's Master Ye
Master Ye
It remains a sore point to me
When Coach Su was here
you quitted for no reason
many say that you should be the captain of Qingmeng
I don't have to explain to the players of Shenhua
Just meet my wish before I go
Have a battle and see who's the best of Qingmeng
It's none of my business
Jun Ye, I remember you said
you would never step onto the court of Qingmeng
Are you a man of your words
It's an outdoor court
I don't mind
I'm here to destroy your hope
One versus one
I'll be the judge
Chu Ran, Master Ye, Chu Ran, Master Ye, Chu Ran, Master Ye
Where are you going
you haven't signed up yet
I can't even beat a girl
how can I join the basketball club
I don't want to drag you behind
Nuanxia has been playing the basketball since three
Ordinary people can't beat her
It's not rare to lose to her
With your physical quality
and do well in training
you can be Hanamichi Sakuragi
I only want to become Jack Ma
I have no interest in becoming Hanamichi Sakuragi
You are a hundred million dollars away from becoming Jack Ma
Wait,
Now Master Ye is defended well
I don't think he can dribble
Not for sure
He didn't break through
It's really bad of he exceeds five seconds
No. It's ok if the ball go out
Jun Ye has the ball
Jun Ye, Jun Ye
Petty trick