Chu Ran Chu Ran Chu Ran
Principal
How did you come to such an important competition? How could I not come to such an important competition?
In warm summer, I know the special significance of this competition to your father and daughter.
I'm with you to cheer you up
Thank you, Principal
Yes
Since this game is so meaningful, I will also add a little bet.
I won this from your father last year. If Qingmeng wins today,
Hand this gold medal in my hands
Han Mo, how can you do this
Good
Night God, Night God, Night God
The pace of scoring is much faster than that of the previous matches. Have you noticed that the start is even like this?
A person who controls the rhythm of the whole stadium.
It's Chu Ran
His speed is faster than the last one. It doesn't matter.
Jun Ye and Ling Xuan Can Keep Up with
It's hard, isn't it? I've been training for so long to stop your breakthrough.
Almost today, Jun Night and Ling Xuan are in great condition.
It doesn't matter. It's just one point. The ball came back.
One-on-one
You're not qualified
Don't say it too early
What is Ling Xuan doing? Why hasn't he moved
He is waiting for Chu Ran to move this level of offensive and defensive duel ratio is a few tenths of a second of instantaneous reaction Ling Xuan's physical talent
Not losing at all to Chu Ran is better than others. I have no winning face but I have not been afraid of anyone in Ling Xuan.
Is it
That's what you're waiting for
Originally
Captain's plunder skills can not only be used in defense.
It can also be used in attack.
Your self-righteous talent is rubbish. You said what
Say it again, Ling Hyun, you don't have to do this.
Your most proud thing has been mutilated.
You don't have to play this game any more.
What should I do, Ling Xuan? It seems that he has been suspended. Didn't you say that he has no talent to lose to Chu Ran?
What do we do now? Basketball
Not only in terms of talent,
Chu Ran belongs to the kind of person who is gifted and makes a lot of efforts at the same time.
The same is true of Jun Night, am I not
Isn't it
Let you ignore my efforts
Prevent together
King's Night
Do you want to be robbed, too
Night God, Night God, Night God
This state of affairs at night
Is that what you said last time
He's using his body's instinct
To perceive basketball means that he does not think through the brain when he breaks Chu Ran.
If people like Junye join our myth, then the national champion will be in the bag.
Coach Han, let's win Qingmeng first.
Qingmeng's attack is so fierce today.
Then suppress him with a stronger attack. Okay, let's get started.
What a quick pass I can't even touch the ball.
It is good that you can see clearly the three-game phantom pass between Chu Ran and me.
Take good care of the source
Four guard one to see how you still live.
Supplementary protection
Night God
Are you really not human
Green Dream Green Dream Green Dream
Are you interested in what Basketball Club
You're clumsy
I also want to rebuild the team.
I said do you like me
You don't need so many reasons to refuse me.
Anyway, the whole school knows that you Su Nuanxia is my girlfriend at night.
You are the first person I have kissed
So wherever you go
No matter what you've been through what
No matter you make what's mistake,
I will never let you go.
Green Dream Green Dream Green Dream
You night this wave without me directly hit a small climax to suppress all the myths
Not safe
Single digit difference
Can't hold down Chu Ran
Sisters, work, come on, come on, come on
You can even jump up. I learned it once and won't do it again.
Qiang Ge Ling Xuan
Is Ling Hyun okay
How's it going? It's okay? It's okay
How is it
This will definitely not be possible.
After half a day's work, Chu Ran can't scrap you.
Your boy has ruined himself.
Even if the ball just now is 100 times, 1,000 times and 10,000 times, I will still be hard on it, otherwise it will not be my Ling Xuan's temper.
It's just a pity
I can't defeat the myth team with Chu Ran with my own hands.
Yang Kai Replaces Ling Xuan
Hold on to the first half
The Qingmeng Team was replaced by Ling Xuan, No.10, and Yang Kai, No.21.
At the end of the first half, the Qingmeng team was 29-41 behind.
Don't blame yourself
If you lose, everyone will carry it together.
Xiao Yang
No pressure
Just try your best
That's what I said, but is it meaningful for us to play in the second half?
More than two minutes
Myth has scored 17 points,
Chu Ran scored 12 points alone,
King's Night
What do you think
Hit
Let me come on as a substitute in the second half. The assistant coach took so long with his clothes.
I can't find a chance to wear it.
Let me brush a wave of presence
Save everyone
You are not a student of Qingmeng at all.
So they are not qualified to represent Qingmeng at all.
Who said he was not qualified for Luye
I can give you the green light now and make you a student of Qingmeng.
As long as you don't violate the school discipline, rules and procedures, you can wait until after the match.
Thank you, Principal
Can go one step further with Miss Anna
It's my honor
The match officially started in the second half.
On the side of Bai Yin
Lu Ye, you defected to Qingmeng. Even if you did, why did you still play so obscene?
Not bad
Bai Yin, your instinct is still very reliable.
Too much, Lu Ye. I didn't expect your ball to be so poor. I went to Qingmeng.
Just to make Anna happy. If you have a problem
Also go to Qingmeng to pick up a younger sister.
Everyone, no, everyone can be teammates again, can't we
Lu Ye, you rubbish did not expect people like you to dare to say that Chu Ran was a traitor. I didn't teach Han Mo to play basketball.
Which team do I like to go to
None of them are traitors.
But what about Chu Ran
He defected to myth
Is to forget one's roots
You don't have a chance
Gu Yuan's eagle cast imitation, we are very familiar with it.
Excuse me, this is a no-fly zone
Qingmeng Team is 37-41, four points short. Qingmeng Come on
Xiao Qiang
Han doesn't seem to look very well.
Do you want to call a pause for you
A foul won't get you in, you idiot.
You can't throw it
Ling Xuan's injury was suffered here by you.
I will call back in his way.
The mythology team requested a pause.
Green Dream Green Dream Green Dream
I have never seen Chu Ran so flustered. No, no, no, I don't think so, because only in adversity can we see the real captain Chu Ran.
Coach Han
Can you give me a minute
Coach Han has long said
We are the basketball team of Myth University.
If you don't come up with the strength to match these two words,
Everywhere you go, you will be beaten in the face.
So Coach Han asked us to win every match.
We did
What about today
Do you have the heart to win
The main road show was too demon. He broke the balance. I can only say that I try my best to win.
Have you ever thought about
Why did Coach Han let me join Myth
The purpose of my coming to myth is to lead you to become better players.
Captain
Thank you
Chu Ran, I support you
I'll support you, too
One, two, three
The Qingmeng team was ten points behind 41-51.
Just now, Mingming was only two minutes and less than three minutes away and was pulled back to ten points.
Coach Han's myth team is really a terrible opponent.
In fact, what is really terrible is Chu Ran
His spiritual attribute is the king on the court.
What he is using now is the reverse skill of plundering, giving every player who is inspired by him.
Will instantly come to the peak of spirit, will and competitive state,
Is it
Hmm
Gu Yuan's ball style is soft and his core strength is insufficient, so he is afraid of his hands, feet and injuries.
Now Chu Ran's support behind him not only improves the rebounding rate,
And gave him courage
Bai Yin Is Not Alone
Is afraid of the consequences
Chu Ran gave him
It's trust
What Ding Lei Desires Most
Is recognized
Now Chu Ran also gave him
This wave was actually brushed out by them to a small climax of 13 to 4. This Chu Ran is really a big devil king.
I can't imagine that even my father didn't master the endowment, but he used it skillfully.
With his help, every mythical team member has made progress.
How to plunder and endow
It's like playing a game
To put it bluntly, they are two kinds of psychological offensives based on super strength.
Predation is a weapon to destroy an opponent.
Endow
It is a blessing to upgrade our team.
At that time, it was still a bit like
Card game, yes
Be a coach
It's like running a real-time strategy game.
Then this level
How do you want to brush the status
Is your physical strength OK? I don't need to play today. It doesn't cost much for the whole match. Then let's get started. Come on
Attention to joint defense
Don't let Shen Yingliang and Lu Ye shoot
Ding Lei Gu Yuan Bai Yinjiang's positions in the morning all formed a counterpoint relationship with the members of the Qingmeng Team.
Also forms an included angle
Limit Shen Yingliang and Lu Ye's shooting angle. If Shen Xuechang pitches at this time, he will definitely face it.
The Double Attack of Ding Lei and Gu Yuan
It will definitely reduce the probability of scoring goals.
What about he passing it directly to Luye
The same Bai Yin and Jiang Yi Chen Yi Gao Yi quickly know the best route.
Has been sealed off by them
In this way, Lu Ye's ball will be restricted if he forcibly shoots.
Chu Ran ambushed under the basket
Already waiting for the rebound
What should I do then? It will have a chance to spread it.
The Qingmeng team was only one point behind 54-55,
It has already turned over
Youth Dream Team 67-64 Myth Team Request Suspension
Although Chu Ran's endowment is strong,
However, it offset your super-strong state at night. Although we scored a lot, we still couldn't catch up with Qingmeng.
So what should we do
Ding Lei
You are a very executive person.
I don't care what you do for the next five minutes
Scrap Junye and Luye for me
Coach Han
This is not very good, is it? You didn't understand what I meant?
Or do any of you want to disobey my orders
Coach Han
Take back your orders
This is not what our basketball team should do.
You want to disobey me too, do you? This is not basketball. I don't need you to teach me a lesson.
I'm warning you
Don't forget how Zuri died
In fact, there are some things
I have never told anyone
Before the last match between Myth University and Qingmeng University,
I met Coach Han once
Churan, I don't want to beat around the bush with you either.
If you can release water in the competition in three days
I will promise you two conditions.
First
Transfer you to Myth University
Second
Recommend you to the National Youth Team
Mr. Han Mo, is what you said true? I don't want to say it again. Think it over.
I admit it
After I received Coach Han's invitation, I did have a moment of heart attack.
But respect for basketball
Let me never let water go in the competition.
Before the end of the match, there are still ten seconds left before the end of the match. The Qingmeng team is currently one point behind but the last key goal.
But I was under too much pressure,
He made a low-level mistake, missed the goal, won the Myth University, defeated the Myth University, defeated the Youth Dream University, and won the championship of this competition. Let's coach them.
What's the matter? Is there anything wrong with what
Coach, coach, coach, what's wrong, coach, coach
Chu Ran
Coach Coach
Who knew the shooting error
However, Coach Han believed that
I agreed to his request
That's how you transferred to Myth
Coach Su passed away
Youth Dream Team Disbanded
I want to keep playing
So I have to join a new team
And myth is, of course, the strongest
If you believe in me, believe in the training time I have been spending these days together day and night,
Then come with me
Play a decent game without regrets.
Captain
I have already decided to mix with you.
Let's go, fuck them, Churan, I'll support you
I just said to support you
Three, two, one
Today's match must win, let's give it a shot. I think it doesn't matter whether you win or lose at this point. Basketball is really fun.
The house is the final outline of the rule of law. Wow,
They are listed in the battle of their armies, the grain of the victorious crown, and live in abundance.
The wind of the heart is content with life.
The whole match is over.
The Green Dream team won the match 87-71. Everyone cheered.
Zhang Xiaoqiang Zhang Xiaoqiang Zhang Xiaoqiang
Know your warmth on summer nights.
Goodbye, Jun Night Before
You have to answer me a question first.
Why on earth do you like basketball
This one
Because
Basketball carries the youth dreams of many, many people. Tell me, in your eyes, they are all like what.
Some of them are persistent in their dreams.
Some people are hopeful
Some people are always running hard, while others are glowing for him.
Some people are born bullies
Some people like to talk and laugh
Some people are growing up
Some fight for honor
Some people have distant hearts.
Some people have helped us,
But there was no time to say goodbye.
Thank you for your career.
That
What about you? Your dream is what?
Ha ha repaired you.
My Dream
It's just beginning,
Hmm
Do you think Akagi Akiko looks good or Inoue Akiko looks good
Qingzi Bar
The name is the same as the person I like.
Superficial
Then Ayako
It looks cool
And talented
In your heart
Am I not the best-looking
No, you didn't say I'm not as good as a cartoon character in your heart.
I also said what
This is too routine for you, isn't it
Clearly fill in the blanks
You pretended to be a multiple choice question to fool me.
It's you who can't stand the test. Nonsense
Then let me ask you again
Which one is good-looking, my best friend or me
Don't ask me this kind of delivery question in the future.
Of course, it's the best one in our family.
You are the most beautiful in the world.
Which best friend did I say? Are you so anxious to answer? Are you guilty?
I want to cry
Brother Chu Ran
I want to eat roast chicken, okay? Let's go
I said I want to lose weight
Why don't you stop me
It took a long time to lose two pounds. Do you want to force me to bounce back?
Do you think indulging me is good to me
That day I had an epiphany
It turns out that girls' obsession with losing weight probably
Is my obsession with basketball, then I will know what to do.
Brother Chu Ran, I really, really, really want to eat roast chicken today
You're losing weight
Let's not eat such greasy food
Are you not in love with me? You won't even let me eat a roast chicken
Reason things out
Didn't you say you want to lose weight and let me supervise you?
So
Now you think I'm fat
Brother Chu Ran, how did you think of buying me coffee
I want to interview you
Having a boyfriend who loves playing basketball is what's experience.
Ling Xuan called me to watch him play basketball if he didn't agree with him, and then
And then I was ignored
Sometimes he plays ball with me
Then all kinds of let me
In fact, he is also quite collapsed, isn't he? He actually abused you
It's too boring and naive. I seldom watch him play ball.
Because he always looks good in front of me.
Once I passed by and was seen by him. He immediately started the fork-loading mode. What plundered and gave all kinds of smelly farts. He died.
Ling Xuan, he actually has a very deep routine. Although the lock screen of his mobile phone is my photo, you will find it as soon as you unlock it.
What's skin and wallpaper are all Hanato Sakuragi's black sheep. I only have five pairs of shoes to match his luxury. I only have eight lipsticks to match his luxury. I have a pair of sneakers to accompany him to watch the ball every day. I know several stars.
But he watches me make-up every day.
Even the air cushion and foundation are still silly and can't tell the difference between Tanabata. When he said he bought me a suit of clothes.
I'm looking forward to it
As a result, he took out
He told me that he had robbed Xiangbei's No.10 jersey for a long time.
That
Air cushion
Not sneakers? Actually, Lingnan's No.7 is also good.