The little girl is very energetic.
Send it
What are you doing
Work
About the basketball team
Not enough for you
Put it down. Put it down
Don't bother me with my money
You are short of money
The basketball team has bought a new batch of equipment.
So I've been in negative equity lately
How much do you need
I give
As an independent woman of the new era, I will not ask you for money.
Why is this not what I said the day before, right? Is it true that the social atmosphere is not good and I am good at it?
Why do you let go
Put me down I won't
Hurry up
I sponsored it
All right, sponsorship
Then I can think about it
Walk, walk, walk
Easy to stop
Su Nuan Xia
Are you going to do what's strange training again? Don't worry, this is a surprise.
Turn around
Thank you, your father, for saving the Qingmeng team in the mire. Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Beautiful. What are you doing
I've thought about the money you gave me for nothing. I can't take it, but if you are a sponsor, with the strength of our dream team, it will soon increase your income.
But at our current level
I can only make a friendship advertisement for you.
Come on, put it on
Let's take a photo to commemorate our first sponsorship.
First sponsorship
Is this okay? Are you ready? Is this okay? One, two, three eggplants
See no temperament super good seems to be very tall ah legs two meters long ah
I don't know who he's waiting for
I was waiting for Anna. No wonder
Lu Ye
You didn't tell me why you suddenly came over. This chocolate tastes good. I happened to pass by your school, so I turned over by the way.
I have inquired about all the low-fat ones.
Thanks
Or
Let's have dinner tonight
Okay, let's go
The three of us have seldom got together since we grew up. Why don't you ask Jun Ye to come together?
Forget it
He practices basketball every day now
No time
Don't you know that since Jun came back to the basketball team at night, the whole people have followed the magic.
I want to meet him now and say a word is very difficult, but this is too flat, isn't it?
Please help me do something. If you go on like this, you will become a stranger to me at night.
Brother Luye, help me. I'm dying
Don't you have a Jungu fan club
Just a little upgrade
Why do you run well?
What's going on here
Green Dream Green Dream
Su Nuan Xia, we have applied for Qingmeng's cheerleading team.
How about if you train that basketball team and we're here to cheer them up
That's a great idea. Okay, okay
Anna
You're fucking what again. Why do you say that? This cheerleader is part of the basketball team.
This Anna classmate has had friction with me before.
But I believe he is really good for the team this time.
Besides,
There are so many beautiful women in Qingmeng Cheerleading Team.
How cool the competition will be then
Su Nuan Xia
I can't see. You still have some insight. That's
You can be here, but we are training now. Please go outside in an orderly way.
Good
Let's go
You'll be sorry
Our Xingmeng University basketball team is playing basketball
Here
Uh, sorry, sorry, it's time to train, it's time to train
Excuse me. Excuse me
Off-site off-site off-site
Night God, Night God, Night God
You have also seen the situation in what these days.
Can you negotiate with the cheerleaders
Don't show up when we're training
When the time comes, you can play whatever you like.
It is useless for me to say what now.
Everyone already knows that you are training here.
It was also for this reason that I joined the cheerleading team.
Good
Then we are all leaders. You know my difficulties, right
How beautiful
I think I was completely defeated by you
I worked so hard to plan such a cool confession drama.
How can you be all right
It means you're stupid
I'll go
You are like a wood. You still have the face to talk about me.
Let me ask you something
The Pit Digged by Su Nuanxia
How are you goe to solve it
You mean the cheerleaders
Isn't that good
Men and women are not tired of working together.
There are still so many beautiful women with traffic,
At least Qi Feng is very happy
With the current quality of training,
How to Fight Myth
Hello
King's Night
How about that cheerleader
It was your idea
How
You've figured it out for Anna now
This young master's thoughts will not be guessed by you.
Such as
I found you a new training ground.
I can carry my bag and check in tomorrow.
Come on, Rabbit, Rabbit
Oh, my gosh
It's so big
Jun Dashen, this resort will not be your property, will it
This is from my friend's house
The environment is good
The place is also large, which happens to be training with everyone.
The point is that there is no interference.
I can't wait to start training. Come on
King's Night
Is your friend also a basketball player
The basketball facilities here are so complete that they all look like they are specially set up for basketball training.
Do I know your friend more than that
I have fought before.
To tell you the truth, this is the training base specially built by Lu Ye for Myth Basketball Team. Lu Ye
He seems to be the captain of myth and the training base of myth.
That's the enemy camp. Now it's one of our own.
Lu Ye and I are good friends.
Since Chu Ran went to the Myth Team
He dropped out of the team
This time
Is to help us train
What about the people who beat the myth
I went shopping at the foot of the mountain.
It's expected to be there in a few minutes, waiting for what
Let's move
Wait a minute
Come on, come on
Ladies and gentlemen
Are you tired after practicing for so long
Come and have a rest
Right, right, right
You must be Lu Ye. Thank you
Thanks, handsome
This orange juice is my favorite
Thank you
King's Night
This is your girlfriend hanging on the teaching building.
Hello, my name is Su Nuanxia, and I am the coach of Qingmeng Basketball Team.
The coach is still a woman.
As soon as you listen, it looks like a follow-up. It doesn't matter to you if you have a follow-up.
Warm Summer Do you mind if I call you Warm Summer
Let's talk about it
How did you two follow up
You know too much
You didn't have time to hire the best chef for you at the time of your night's notice.
You can make do with it. No, no, no, no. Thank you, handsome boy, for the reception.
Anthomaniac, don't I have the right to admire handsome men yet?
Is it possible to just look at you, a guy who has no interest, every day?
You are not my girlfriend. I have a what interest in you.
I didn't expect you to be cold at ordinary times.
Your friend is quite hospitable, isn't he
You are too naive
Rabbit, look, that shrimp looks delicious, but we can't scare the host for the first time, can we?
You said that in warm summer, it is better to start directly.
Not good
What for
You look like you want to eat that
I haven't been to practice all day.
You didn't come to class at night. Where have they all gone
Lu Ye
Do you know where you went at night
Let me tell you something, lenient to those who confess and strict to those who refuse
Du Resort
Su Nuan Xia
Su Nuanxia actually lived under the same roof with you at night.
Hello
Get me a car right now. Come on
He said that he would train today and all of them would lie in bed with me.
Morning, warm summer
Eat breakfast early
Finish training
Good
Do you know if you have to train today
Hurry up
This early morning can't give people a good rest. Last night, you slept like a pig and had to rest.
Change clothes and go to training quickly.
All I know is that training is fast.
Get up, get up
Anna, why are you here? You didn't arrange the training yet. If I don't come to Jun Night, I will really be abducted by Su Nuanxia.
I'm just borrowing the venue. Training is their business at night. I don't care.
They have all gone to training now, and you should get up quickly. That has something to do with me, what. I am not a member of the Youth Dream Team. Of course it has something to do with it.
You have to help me arrange the logistics.
Come on, come on, come on, get up, get up
Come on, come on, come on
When I get back, I will repair them all, leaving me and Jun Night alone.
Let's have a rest. I have prepared snacks for everyone. Let's come and have something to eat.
Take a break
Thank you, Anna. Then we're welcome.
It is very expensive to eat.
Every time you eat, your most active school flower sister is really persistent in coming to the resort for you.
I will prepare afternoon tea for you all day long.
Charismatic
Junye, this is especially delicious, and I am personally responsible for it.
I thought I told you not to prepare these. That's not enough. People like Su Nuanxia and Xiao Tutu
How is it possible to take good care of you
These are the most expensive and delicious things of mine.
These have no food safety problems at all.
Why can't we take care of them
You
Be sure to eat this high-calorie food.
What's the matter? I remember someone said they would break up with milk tea.
And he must not see dessert on the training ground.
I am not an athlete. I am a coach now.
It is even more important to take the lead
Clearly, this is my highlight. Why is he the only one in your eyes at night?
But these are all I've prepared, Anna. I-I don't matter. I can eat them.
As a coach, I can't even eat, let alone you. Su Nuan Xia, don't go too far. You can't let others eat with what.
Anna
You come with me
What are they doing
In the future, when we train,
Why don't you come with me
King's Night
I really don't understand this time. I will definitely prepare low-calorie food next time. If you are here,
Some people get distracted
Then I am naturally beautiful and have my own eyes and what methods.
You night, I will be able to watch silently next to you, right?
King's Night
You said that
Is it because Su Warm Summer
You have been like this since you were a child.
As long as you get angry
To find someone else's reason
So Lu Ye still lets you
This has what relations with Lu Ye.
Think for yourself
King's Night
I like you so much
I have also done so many things for you that I would never have done before. Is it better for Su Nuanxia than for what?
Including bribery of myth reserves
You
How do you know that everything has to have a degree?
I don't want you to interfere with our training any more.
It is good to know for yourself.
Only Su Nuanxia and I know about this matter.
Su Nuan, I'm not finished with you in summer.
I heard that Anna was upset by the night god again today.
I'd better not express my opinion on this sensitive topic. This is getting darker and darker. If you really have nothing to do with the night god, will anyone come after you to declare sovereignty?
You see, you see, the battle for sovereignty is like that. He's staring at you with his nostrils now.
Nonsense
Thank you
You told Anna about what, but he has lost his temper with me for half a day.
Why did he come to you so soon to complain? It's not a complaint.
Just say that you maintain Su Nuan summer and like Su Nuan summer and so on.
No way
You really like Su Nuanxia
If I like warm summer
Wouldn't it be a good thing for you
So is that
But actually
You don't have to tell Anna. I can see that you are very different to Coach Sue.
How long has it been since you played? This time, I brought the team to training.
Absolutely for women
While eating
You brought him food. I don't believe it. I didn't see it with my own eyes.
I was just saying that if
People can change
It doesn't mean I like him
Where's Mr. Shen
He seemed to have a problem with his graduation defense and went back first.
Why is the atmosphere a bit strange?
You didn't even see Anna firing at you
Eat, eat, eat, eat, you said the person who set the dishes was really
Why do you put your favorite shrimp in warm summer so far every time so far, isn't it? Jun night
Thank you. I come by myself. Sometimes it is not convenient for girls to pick up food.
There is something what wants to eat.
Despite the opening
No more
Everybody's up
Something has happened
How did you get up
What are you doing
Don't sleep
Why did Lu Ye have to call us down in the middle of the night? It was very difficult. There was what.
Welcome show Anna's not back yet
It was already dark when he went out on this mountain road. I think he was lost.
Did you call him
He didn't even take his cell phone out. Why are you waiting? It's so dark on this day. Go out and look for it. I have prepared two cars. Jack Bauer, you drive mine.
You bring warm summer at night
This is the hell of a place in what
Why can't you go around for half a day?
Why, there's a barricade ahead
I'll go down and see if I'm with you
Anna
Stop shouting and change the way
Take another road
Why can't it be opened
The key was left in the car
What should I do then
Take another walk and see
Anna
Anna Anna Anna
Anna, where are you, Anna
King's Night
How long do you think we have to go
We drove over
Twenty minutes to walk back, at least an hour. God bless me
Let's meet Anna on our way back, and they'll all be happy.
Maybe even if we find him
I can't sit in a car.
You have to walk back on your own
Do you think they have found Anna
Don't worry, Lu Ye will find her.
You better wear it. I'm not cold
I don't want to be happy
You have a cold
It hurts. This is the hell of a place in what
Anna Anna Anna
Slow down, hurt your ankle, you'll be in trouble. Where can she go in the big night? Where can a girl go?
Anna Anna
Who, who, who, who
Anna Anna Anna
What are you doing here? Why are you bastards looking for me
All right, all right, don't cry. It's ugly. You're ugly. You stay away from me. Anna can't walk. I'll carry you. I don't need you to carry me.
Tie Hanhan
You'd better give up
Life is so real. Get out of here
Let me tell you a joke
The little fish asked the big fish
Big fish, big fish, what kind of small fish do you like to eat? Then the big fish said that I like to eat small fish that speak slowly.
Then the little fish said how about this
After laughing, do you feel warmer? I feel colder.
Then let me think again
Warm summer
Actually
On that day's confession spray painting
Brother
Anna
You're finally here. It's freezing us to death.
Coach Sue, ladies and gentlemen
To thank everyone for helping me find Anna last night
I decided to offer a free sparring service.
Help everyone to improve the quality of training. Don't you just want to play ball because your hands itch?
Ling Xuan
You have never fought with Lu Ye.
I don't know the meaning of his condescending to practice with him.
Nani
Does Lu Ye have what's stunts
To put it simply
Luye's ability is perfect simulation
Although her own style of playing is a mystery, it can perfectly duplicate anyone's unique skills.
Even shine on you is so powerful
I don't believe it
One to One
This
This what style of play
Lu Ye is now simulating
The main force of the myth team is Gu Yuan's eagle throw.
Although the name sounds very secondary,
But there is no way to prevent it.
On behalf of Anna to blow you up, that's not necessarily true.
If in the official competition, Ichichen Jiang's move must be a dunk.
Lu Ye is playing away
Enough fun
It's my turn
Do you dare to do it again
What he is simulating now is
Myth Team Point Guard Bai Yin
No way
We can't even get a copy
What about the official competition
It's time for the last player to play
What a lovely killer whale, look
Beautiful bird of paradise, like a rainbow
Beautiful corals are picturesque
I like the way you read carefully.
But you keep interrupting me
The fireworks convention in Japan is really beautiful.
I should do some what for such a beautiful fireworks conference.
What do you think I'm going to do
You are too talented, aren't you? I am more talented in my studies.
I don't want to learn
What are you doing
I am just lazy and want to see pictures to relieve my boredom.
I have always wanted to go to the fireworks conference in Japan.
Will you stay with me
I also want to see
Picturesque corals, rainbow-like birds of paradise
Lovely killer whale, then you heard all the nonsense I just said.
Not a word of what you say is useless.