Why don't you answer the phone
Hello
Do you want to reconsider your withdrawal from the team
No
That what
Why don't I just ask
I said, do you like me? Otherwise, if I date Chu Ran, why did you quit the team?
By the way
Today I have a tea date with my good friend Ann
You can go too
All right, Grandpa
Please
Mr. Jun, old hello, hello, please sit down and have a good seat.
Is this Jun's night
General an
Uncle Good hello
This is my daughter Anna, who was in France a few years ago. Hello, Grandpa Jun.
Please take care of it
Junye classmate
Good
Come on, everybody, sit down, sit down, sit down
Miss Anna used to know Jun Ye. We have been in touch from junior high school to college.
This fate is not shallow
Well, it's more important to have a good talk. Yes, yes, yes,
Junlao
My daughter's tea making skills
That's a unique skill. I boast that there is no water at all. Have a good taste.
Grandpa Jun, please have tea
King's Night
Thank you
Give up in warm summer
If you want to return to the team, Junye will not stop answering the phone.
Maybe he was busy with what just now.
Rich people are busier than we think.
I believe he will come back as long as the misunderstanding is explained clearly. Look, you are still helping him.
Is Gao Fushuai privileged? Su Nuan Xia is not what I said about you. You are just too indulging in your night.
Don't pay any attention to him in warm summer. I think you are a natural gold medal coach. Some guys who abandon themselves and hate the rich are the real losers. Who do you say? Just say you? Xiao Tutu, I've endured you for a long time. I told hello, okay, stop it, stop it.
You say it again, loser, loser, loser. Okay, I failed. I see if you can leave me or not.
Then you go, Ling-hyun
Rabbit Rabbit
I'm just quick-mouthed
Who knew he was so impulsive
Who called you
Is that the village coach again
Your grandfather and my father don't know when what will be back
We can't stay silent, can we
You said
Are you that exclusive to me
No
You pull your hair like this
Hair dandruff can easily fall into tea.
Laijun Night
Why don't you ask a waiter to get a towel?
No
After a good talk with Anna, remember to take her home. Jun and I will never go back.
Nana
Take good advantage of the opportunity
Neither your grandfather nor my father is coming back. We seldom have the chance to be alone.
After all these years, you should know that
I have always been very interested in you. I am not interested in you.
Is it true that there is no such thing
I don't believe it
Warm summer
Junye, where the hell are you now, tell me right now
Why can't you say that you still choose teahouses on the court? It's so old-fashioned.
Miss, do you have an appointment? I'm looking for Jun Night
Look at that
We are both very well matched in wealth, appearance and family affairs.
You should like people like me
You won't
Do you really like Su Nuan Xia
Miss, this is it. Thank you
You're here. Sit here
Good. I happen to be a little thirsty
Su Nuan, you are really haunted by the ghost.
You
So you didn't come, you went out with her, went out with her
You think too much. Then what are you doing here? You don't answer the phone. Can you give me a reason?
Sorry
I won't be
It happened suddenly today.
What am I doing with Junye? I have a what relationship with you.
Did I meet the plot of a rich and powerful idol drama with dog blood?
I see.
He and he
He doesn't like him, but he has a bad heart towards him.
Death, so want to use me as a shield, mercilessly cut off this woman's delusion, want me to help you ah OK,
You have to be in training on time every time, but you have no credit with me,
You have to swear that if you stand me up again
You will become bald and no girl will ever like you.
Good
What are you two doing
I just can't bear to take my eyes away from your handsome face at night.
I can't help it for a minute. No, no, no
Not even zero one
Too much
Come and eat
One for you and one for me
Isn't it delicious
You said you didn't have a girlfriend before, did you use her as a shield?
I almost forgot my business
Anna
Didn't you notice at school at ordinary times? I and Jun night? On the surface, it was a relationship between coaches and players, but in fact it was a real relationship between male and female friends.
Isn't that right? Little Jun Jun is
I don't believe it
Why don't you believe it when it's over?
It seems that we can only use our unique skills.
What is she doing
This is for the future of Qingmeng
Throw caution to the wind
Believe it
Junye, I'm really out of sight. I'll disband Jungu fans now.
It seems that my acting skill is not bad.
Look what I'm doing
Isn't it just a kiss on the face? This is a basic etiquette abroad, okay?
What's wrong with me
It must have happened suddenly
Why are you sitting here? Everyone has gone. Wait for me
Aren't you going to eat
Let me tell you, Chu Ran and I are really good friends who grew up together.
Even if you hate him and envy him
I really don't have any affair with him.
I and he are the same as you are to Anna.
Nothing. You see
You and Chu Ran have a what relationship,
I don't care
It's not a matter of emotion, it's not a matter of Chu Ran
Then why did you quit the team
Don't you want to challenge Myth's first team
The competition in two months
Is it important to you
Maybe you think I'm fanciful, after all, the reserves are playing so hard.
But
I believe we have a chance to have
And there must be
King's Night
I hope you can help me
Come back to the unit
We need you
For the sake of helping me just now
I will grudgingly promise you
Thank you, thank you, thank you
10 October 2016
The team has been injected with fresh blood again.
It's good to be young, young, vigorous and hard-edged. Of course, there are also disobedience and despise teammates.
There are more and more tricks for young people nowadays.
As a coach, we should also keep pace with the times.
If they are hard, I will be soft.
Since the teammates are not friendly, I will let you love each other and stick together every day.
What are you doing here all by yourself so late? You're a ghost
Walking without sound
Is there any ghost that I care so much about the players?
I am not afraid to play the ghost.
I just didn't think
You will care about me. You have promised to return to the team. As a coach, I must not give you the most professional guidance. Not a small tone.
Tell me about it
What's my problem
One word
Say it
Not alone but tight
You haven't attended professional training for more than a year.
So
Your body function and your muscle memory are not as good as before.
You wanted to take control of the last game
As a result, you can't help it, so you start to be nervous. The more nervous you are, the more scared you are. The more scared you are.
You are even more nervous.
I know my situation myself.
I don't believe it
You don't know how you play
That's it
Do you know what's name is bitter and bitter
I can't look so ugly. It's really like this.
The eyebrows are so wrinkled that they can kill a mosquito.
Laugh
So, as long as you follow the team and practice well,
Promise you to return to the original night god thank you
But I am still used to practicing alone.
I don't like the whole team together.
How come you're such a man
Don't mention it
If you say you're a fool three times
Then I don't mind practicing with the whole team.
If it weren't for winning the myth,
I'm a fool I'm a fool I'm a fool
Barely do it
Immature
How come you hurt your ligament
I tell you I'm quitting the team
Why, I, I hit a paranormal, paranormal
Yesterday
Sorry, I'm late today, so I'll go first.
I didn't think the basketball club was really useful at this time. The hotel was too expensive at night.
It's better to sleep here than in the open air.
Don't chase me, didn't I just eat a few more boxed meals? I have what's fault
Ghost! Help! Ghost!
I don't care. I'm quitting the team. I haven't made enough money in my life. There's no ghost in this world.
Did you get too sleepy and hallucinate yesterday? Please, I didn't believe it before.
I can see both eyes
Warm summer
It's not really a ghost, is it
Anyway, I don't believe it
If there is
It must be human
For thousands of years
Some people insist on atheism and others believe in the existence of ghosts and gods.
Junye classmate
Please combine your knowledge of the basic principles of Marxism and talk about your views on this phenomenon.
Miss Li
Ladies and Gentlemen
First of all, I am a materialist in the Marxist philosophy system
The main difference between materialism and idealism is that
Nature
Did God create it
Materialism holds that the world is knowable.
Deny
There are omniscient people in the world.
So you
Can you talk directly about the fact that in the materialist cognitive theory
There is an important rule
Is to maintain the falsification of things
For example
The concept of ghosts and gods
Unless someone can prove its exact rules and influence us all the time.
Rather than sometimes without a connection close to human imagination,
In this way, we can better prove its meaning.
Not the Kui is the person who got full marks in the exam, which teacher still has a problem.
What if a staunch materialist encounters an inexplicable phenomenon
We can use various ways and means to explore it.
However, it should never be simply discussed with the concepts of ghosts and gods and miracles if it causes social problems.
Then deal with it according to law.
The team is the safety of my family. Everyone knows that yesterday Ling Xuan fell on the basketball court and is still lying in the hospital.
As a member of the team, should we get justice for him and peace for the school?
Coach
Just waiting for you to say a word
But I heard that Ling Hyun seems to have met a ghost.
Forget about it
Did you go to the basketball court for training last night
I was there last night. What was fine
What ghost, someone must be playing tricks
Forget it
Tonight, everyone will take turns to stand guard with me. We must catch this ghost.
Every time it thunders and rains, I ask him to accompany me.
I don't care
But I haven't finished my experiment yet.
I have classes
I remember you didn't have classes
Are you and I probably mistaken
How can there be ghosts in this world
What is terrible. I thought you had a private course. Then you are not afraid to come with me.
Didn't you say there was training
Preparation myth
Now the panic team is not good. I announced it. Now the ghost catching group has been formally established. He has caught all the real ghosts and fake ghosts.
Just in case Zhang Xiaoqiang Qifeng, you two will be waiting at the gate of the basketball hall, waiting for orders at any time.
Hmm
Far away
Alas, this is good.
Hmm
It's paper. Ah
Aren't you afraid of ghosts
I'm not scared by you yet.
At a shock
More terrible than ghosts
Excuse me
It's all my fault that I substituted into this horrible atmosphere in advance.
The atmosphere is horrible
What things, what what things me
He also said that he was not afraid of ghosts.
Hurry up
I think this is the most inconspicuous place.
But, uh, we can see the whole stadium here
We'll be right here
Watch the plant and wait for the ghost
Why do I have a good night's sleep
Come here and suffer so much nonsense.
This is the bone soup that I specially cooked for you.
I have tasted it
Although the appearance is not very good, the quality is not bad.
Try it
How do I think it tastes a little strange? You won't have diarrhea after drinking. Don't worry about it.
Just drink it
Sleep after drinking
And I'm here to take care of you
Believe you for a moment
Sleep
Come on, slow down
How is it
Are you feeling better
Do you want me to call you an emergency
Little Brother
What a blessing you are
Girlfriend is still with you so late.
I just ran several wards to deliver hot water to you.
She didn't do it yet.
You come to the bed
Lest Su Nuanxia say I bully girls
Wake up, wake up
What's going on with you couple
If you hurt your girlfriend, you should also get well of your illness first.
Why did you fall asleep last night
That's not right
How can you sleep in a place like this
Is it because
She
Your sleep is too ugly, isn't it? I almost fell down.
It seems a little bit
Lumbar soreness and backache
After waiting all night, I didn't wait for the ghost.
It seems that we have to continue tonight.
Do you still come? Is this place so comfortable to sleep in
Thanks to Ling Xuan's loud voice,
The whole school knows about this haunted incident. If we don't solve it,
The basketball hall may be closed.
Think for yourself
Hard work
Drink some water
Give you another hug of love
Don't
If you don't let me hold, let me wait for half a day.
You let go of me, hug yourself with the air.
Didn't you abandon me? You let go
I had just finished playing the ball at that time.
Sweating all over
I don't dislike you
I am afraid you will dislike me
Who told you to make your own decisions
I thought you said you didn't dislike me. I was instinctive. Okay
The next time you sweat again, I will definitely not hide from you when you dump me in the face.
How can I give up
It smells good. Smell it carefully.
It's my favorite milk shower gel
Guessed right