Rich levels, spicy and bitter
You said it was as advanced as making coffee with your hands.
Innovative dishes
We made the Diablo Spicy Shrimp
You have to train early in the morning. Can you go back to rest early?
Well, in order to reassure you, I'll issue a guarantee and affix a seal.
I'm going to buy pens and paper now.
I promise you are me
The only love
Forever in love
King's Night
Seal as evidence
All right, take effect
See you tomorrow. Bye
Come out
Sneaky. Something's wrong
I want you to be the assistant coach of Qingmeng. You have more than enough for yourself. No
Otherwise, you will not lose to myth. Besides, don't you want to get along with your goddess Anna day and night?
Love is precious, loyalty is more expensive, and I am also a member of Myth University.
I will not be a traitor like Chu Ran.
I am the number one topic at Myth University.
If you don't want to gossip with me,
Call Boyfriend's Adult
But
You have to pay the price
Nothing ventured, nothing gained
Go ahead
Which car do you like
Send you
I have plenty of cars
Get tired of
Got it
You are the little prince of the nightclub. You don't know that waves are just appearances.
Anna is the only one in my heart.
I never asked you about what
For the sake of more than 20 years of friends, can't you promise me
You forced me to do the trick
This one
It's an ugly photo of you bursting fat in junior high school.
This is when you were in your first year of high school.
The semi-nude photos I took
And this one of you picking your nose
This angle is extremely ugly.
There are more ugly photos of my injuries than that. If I post them online,
If they are made into expression packs, they will be with you for the rest of your life.
Master Lu loves image so much.
There are so many fans,
Row
I promise you
The premise is that you have to delete all the photos.
There cannot be any backups
Not to stay behind
I never play dirty tricks at night.
Take office tomorrow
I don't
A gentleman's word cannot be followed by a horse. It is not applicable to a prodigal son.
Current Image Recovery Techniques
But it is very powerful.
Change your mind. Whatever you want
I don't know if I look handsome or not
Something for me
I want you to be an assistant coach in Qingmeng.
Is there nothing else
I came here for the sake of your night.
It's not easy for him to play at night. I want you to help him win.
Are you trying to grieve Lu Ye
How romantic
Later, you can consider an appointment here with Junye.
Who let you see you at night
Why don't you say anything? Do you agree or not
Where are you, you, you going
Su Nuan Xia
I've been looking for you for half a day. You don't know how rude this road is.
How can there be such a strange person? Who told you not to talk like that?
Is this OK or not? I won't give you a definite message. You said no or no, but he had to bow his head.
Gone
I'm pissed off
You mean he didn't even say anything about what
Gone
It's done
We went to myth university to find him
You think I am the air, I also want to go
What are you doing here
Is to beg me to let you return to the team
Is to inform you
I'm going to be an assistant coach in Qingmeng.
Don't be too surprised
This is also my respect for myth. Who told everyone on the day he withdrew from the team?
What I despise most is people like Chu Ran. I still despise you now. I'm not farting.
As of today
I won't play again. Never
I trust you with what
A gentleman's word cannot be followed by a horse.
Give me some energy
How do you know Lu Ye will definitely agree
What he said
Better not believe a word
A guy who acts according to his mood.
You have no idea what what is on his mind.
And basketball for Lu Ye
It is only a precious hobby.
But it is not a necessary occupation.
His life
There is something more important than basketball.
Lu Ye
It is such a person
When what appeared, I was shocked.
That doesn't sound so bad
To get to know each other again
Lu Ye, Assistant Coach of Qingmeng University Basketball Team
This Qi Feng
Qi Feng Warns for the First Time to Train Well
Warm summer, warm summer, you make way for the wild.
Isn't it just to let him replace you?
Anna, are you all right, Anna, are you hungry
Anna, shut up
Are you two so fond of following me
Anyway, I have nothing to do. I like to follow you.
All right
You fetch me water
As for your bag
Qi Feng, what do you want to do
Play ball, assistant
What's going on here
Don't you train? It looks like Qi Feng and Lu Ye are going to fight one-on-one.
Why
Does that Qi Feng like you
This is too attractive and troublesome.
Let me tell you something
Don't you think that I will like you just because you came to Qingmeng as a teaching assistant for me. I have never thought so before.
You'd better not like me because of this.
You tell me to keep your voice down
Didn't you say you liked me
Yeah
But it's because I like you
Not because you did it for me, what
I want you to like me, too
Can be because I am handsome
Not because of anything else
Smelly fart from childhood to adulthood, you smelly fart smelly fart also didn't delay you from childhood to play with me to adulthood
What about what
They're talking about what
It must be warm summer who didn't believe my coaching ability.
I have to hear it
No
I think she must be saying bad things about me, let Qi Feng give up on me, not because of me
Affect the team's training
Well-founded
Approve eavesdropping
I will not give up Anna
Not to let you give up, Anna. I think you did nothing wrong today. If you like someone, you should try your best to fight for it.
Then what are you looking for me for
I want you to pursue Anna on your way
Don't delay your career
Qi Feng
You are a very sedate person.
Although the rest of the team are also very good.
But I always think that the future big brother on this team
It must be you
Coach
Do you really think so
Everyone calls me Tie Han Han
This is your advantage. This is not silly.
Is mature and steady
A wise man looks stupid
I also think you are very gentle and not like a man's wife.
Am I a man and a woman? We'll talk about this later.
I came to tell you
As the future big brother
You must take the lead
Can't be so capricious any longer
In the future, listen carefully to Lu Ye's
Coach, I can swear to you, I promise I won't leave Qingmeng.
I will try my best to be the mainstay of the team, but I don't want to listen to Lu Ye. I only listen to the coach.
Assistant Coach Forget Qi Feng. Don't be so stubborn. Coach and assistant coach are the same.
Don't be angry with yourself and that future of the team. How can you be the same
Lu Ye is an assistant coach.
You're the coach
Very different
What if he is alone
The road also
Coach, what are you gonna do
Coach
Assumption is meaningless
It can't become a reality. What if it becomes a reality?
What does what mean
Don't mind what what mean
In a word
As long as you are still dreaming
You must put down your personal grudges.
Get it
You'll understand later
This has become Shaolin basketball. Why is nobody in charge?
Good
Mystery coach doesn't care, so don't blame me.
Give me the book.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Hmm
I'm sorry. Ah
It's okay, the next time this happens,
I can't live without you
Take care of your own affairs.
I got it. Yeah, I got it.
Ha, ha, ha
For the first time, I saw the night god so quickly and steadily.
The power of love is really great.
Is this the legendary boyfriend Li? I don't know if there will be any chance to see you again in the future. What do you mean by what what?
I said I'll have to grow snacks in the future. I can't see what I am today,
Is it
I am hungry
Eat
Go
Is
Is there something amazing about what?
I've made some progress
There has been more than progress from dogs gnawing mud to being able to walk upright on both feet. This is species evolution.
If you can really play for yourself, the success of the little person is that the night god has a crush on her. On family background, appearance and even academic performance, our sister Anna is no better than her.
Too handsome
Why didn't I feel it before? Sister Anna what changed sex when she was. The last time she knew Lu Ye was doing it for her,
After coming to Qingmeng as a teaching assistant,
Some time ago
Some players insisted on playing even though the ligament of the right ankle joint was slightly torn.
It nearly led to a catastrophe.
This player is my daughter
Warm summer has a strong desire to win and lose since childhood. It is easy to be angered by opponents and show aggressiveness in matches.
As an athlete, I can still teach control.
If one day she becomes a coach, the consequences will be unimaginable.
I heard the coach was looking for you
Have you been criticized
Why don't you borrow Brother Qiang's shoulder?
I was not criticized.
Then you're depressed, what
I'm not depressed, I'm wondering if you guys feel
Recently, the coach has been a little strange. It's a little strange.
She has never missed our training before.
That's true
I haven't seen her in late training recently.
What do you think I do? I don't even know what. It's none of my business.
It seems that something really happened.
How about what
Class dismissed
Are you ready to leave? Can I help you
Su Nuan Xia
Your boyfriend's here
What you did
I didn't make it last time
I went back and studied hard.
Come on
Taste it for me
Whether or not coach Zuri has passed on the truth,
Delicious
Just like my dad did
Why do you think I'm dirty
Hmm
Shut up, you hurry up
Did you knock your teeth
Is there something about what that you've been following me like peas and carrots lately
It's okay
Just afraid
The girlfriend she got ran away.
Do you know everything
If you don't want to tell me
I can pretend that what doesn't even know
If I told you
Will you be angry
It depends on what
I want to
I went back to Beijing to continue studying.
Why
Because
About Mr. Shen
Part of it
But not exactly
Actually
I have some things
Hide everyone
Come on, come on, win in stability, come on, come on
Warm Summer Dad Has to Play Again,
I can't go to the airport to see you off.
Send a WeChat to Dad after boarding the plane,
Dad, can't I stay and fight with you? I can be a coach. I can correct all the problems before I became a coach.
Warm Summer Dad knows that you are a good boy, but being a coach is not as easy as you think. Go out and experience for a few years.
You'll understand when you get back. Okay, dad went to the competition.
Dad, although I told my dad that I could change
But over the years I have been working hard and have not improved as what.
In my bones, I still think it's right to want to win.
Perseverance and indomitable will be my bright spot, but I have long forgotten my father's instructions.
If it weren't for Shen's injury, I wouldn't have realized my problem.
Each of us will take a detour.
Now know
It's not too late
But when I realized all these problems, I found out
I was actually hitting
In the name of my father's long-cherished wish and then do some
What he didn't want me to do at all
I can't go on like this
What Problem Appears Again in Basketball Team
I can't forgive myself. I understand
Sorry
I know we just got together
If
It doesn't matter if you can't accept our long-distance love.
That
You just told me a secret
I also have a secret to tell you.
Do you want to know
You are the first person I have kissed
So wherever you go
No matter you go through what, no matter you make what's mistake, I will never let you go.
Warm summer
Are you really leaving
We have only been together for a few short months and will be separated again.
Separation is not a problem.
I have been waiting for you for more than ten years.
Not bad for a while
Beijing is good, Beijing is so far away. We will not be able to meet all the time in the future. We will go back and forth for thousands of kilometers. I will continue to play my competition.
Before I reached the professional league,
I will fly over to see you once a week.
It is not convenient to chat with you via video with different rhythms.
Although it is impossible to lead a team every day,
When you get up every morning
I will send you the video clip of the team.
I can share my day's training with you in warm summer.
Do you think what is listening to me? Yes, I listen to every word
Then you ignore me
That's because you don't love me enough. Love me, what is not a problem.
But when she abandoned me, how did it turn out that I didn't love her?
The woman in love is really strange.
What's this about
They just stood there
What Meaning
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
What about what? Don't worry. Speak slowly
That's weird. Report to coach
We are reviewing the method of loving each other.
Ask the coach for instructions
Chu Ran, let me ask you something
If one day we break up
Do you keep our little turtle or do I keep it?
Listen to you
If you want to raise it, put it at your place. Okay, do you mean we will really break up?
After that, I began to understand that the original girl's words were all traps, seemingly asking you A, but actually her concern was B, so I won't make the same mistake again.
I asked
If we break up one day, will you give me the genuine Lingnan jersey?
This problem does not hold water
We're not gonna break up
All right, you Churan have been together for so long that you won't even give me a jersey.
After that, I finally realized that when my girlfriend broke up with you,
He's probably hoping
You bought him a genuine jersey.
I mean, if, uh, if I and your ex-girlfriend fall into a cesspit at the same time and catch it up, we need artificial respiration.
What are you going to do? Do you need to ask
Of course, I gave you artificial respiration. Okay, you chu ran. Didn't you say I was your first love?
Why did you run out of an ex-girlfriend,
I got a call from your mother while I was at the drugstore today.
She said your ex-girlfriend was in the hospital
Do you want to see her? I don't have an ex-girlfriend. Good, you're Chu Ran. You don't even care about me. You don't even ask why you went to the drugstore.