In accordance with this momentum
There seems to be some suspense
Coach Han
Why don't you call a pause and set it up
Of course, young people's competitions are conducted by young people themselves.
What do you say, Churan
Shen Xuechang
Hold on. Time is running out
Are you all right
To ensure the sight of God's three points
It takes a great deal of physical strength at the expense of
Even Shen Xuechang, who is at his peak,
It can only last for ten minutes.
He has held on for 15 minutes today.
So you didn't shoot in the first half
Is it in the energy storage tank
Sorry, my energy tank is gone.
Me
No, no, no
But now there is one less person
There's no substitute
How do I play
I'll do it
Is there any other way
Su Nuanxia is really a heroine when she goes on stage. There are also such things.
This is a long time to see you. No, the female coach has to go on her own.
The competition has reached this point.
Not so much
We won't be merciful just because we are a woman.
This little girl really looks like Coach Zuri.
Qingmeng University really has an excellent basketball team.
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, my warm summer
It's weird. Don't you hate warm summer? You know what is one yard at a time.
Come on, come on, come on
No, I, I, my affectation is dead.
I will never look down on you
Fast throw
Hmm
A good ball warms the summer.
Beautiful
Little Night God, I didn't think you were quite good
The second half was very exciting.
We underestimated the enemy
Captain
Do you still have barbecue that night
Eat what barbecue. We are all so tired.
Go back and rest
They don't eat, we eat
Coach
We all lost. There's something delicious in what.
It's my problem, not anybody's problem
Although the match was lost,
But this is the hardest and most exciting competition I have ever seen of you.
What if you lose? It's a big deal to make another appointment.
We definitely have the strength to fight the first world war,
I really envy the coach's blind confidence.
Grandpa Jun, these are all my grandpa asked me to bring to you.
Good, good
He's got a good job in Switzerland, isn't he? Great
Just a little bored and always thinking about letting you go fishing with him.
You
You tell him
As soon as your relationship with Junye is confirmed,
I'll be right there
But Grandpa
On the night of the monarch, he seems to be
Never asked me out
But this
I can't help it
You have to show your grandfather's entrepreneurial momentum.
Good
It's time to sneak out with Night God again. Do you want me to borrow your skirt? It's so hard to make an appointment for a meal?
There is no problem with eating.
But if you eat like this, you are afraid that someone will misunderstand you.
Coach, do you have other plans after dinner? You're too dirty, aren't you
No wonder take-out brother ignores you
In order to prove the purity of this coach, I will change the meal to breakfast the next day now. I am dirty. I think you are the crazy Kannika Nimtragol.
Have breakfast together
What
I just took a fancy to the newly opened breakfast shop and decided to treat the hard-working wooden face classmates. Do you take a fancy to the fact that you can eat at will?
And dress formally.
Zhang Xiaoqiang
You wait for me
You are
Didn't you say you had to change clothes
That's what I said, okay
But Night God, the way you look in a suit
How is it
Do you think I look good
King's Night
I was just going to see you. What a coincidence, isn't it?
What are you looking for me for
I heard that you joined your school basketball team. Can you show me to your stadium?
No
That
Take me to see if you can tie it
Grandpa also said before that you can spend more time with me, this classmate, why do you
Hold my classmate's hand
This is
She's my coach
Yes
Who is this woman? She dares to hold Junye's hand
I think she looks quite beautiful, too. Why haven't you seen her before in school?
Anna, do you know that girl? Her name is Yao Zhen
It's a very difficult woman to deal with. How can she pester you at night?
Don't you think
It is more difficult to deal with than Su Nuanxia. Ah, Su Nuanxia is completely incomparable with her, okay? I would rather Su Nuanxia be my opponent.
Yeah
The enemy of this enemy is a friend, especially a difficult person like Yao Zhen. I have to find a helper.
What I said is not exaggerated at all.
This Yao Zhen is definitely not a good fault.
Everyone in our circle knows
If she's after someone
You must get the hand
She will be haunting you all night
And they will do everything they can.
That won't work
This will affect your night training.
Isn't it
Affect Your Night
It will affect the team to win the championship.
You don't know
This Yao Zhen
There is a way to chase men.
First
Verbal flirtation
And then
Intimate contact is too much, right, so we must work together to drive Yao Zhen away.
You accepted it so quickly to prevent it from happening.
This is a good driving skill
Isn't it illegal to drag racing on this campus? Yes
Violation of regulations
Also, section chief
How did you get this off-campus car in without a pass, but she said
I am a family member of the monarch's family, what.
How does she have the face to say that her family members are on the night of the monarch? Yes, have you inspected them?
Let me tell you something
She, she, she's a liar
She's actually
Want to sell financial management
How many times have you been pestering me and Jun Night? You don't believe it. You don't believe it. Look at the picture. If this is Jun Night's family,
How could this be your attitude at night? She has seriously affected the training of our team members, so please detain her car immediately. Now the swindlers all drive sports cars and sell financial management.
Hmm
This, this
I got my car in that school. You're in charge of fix it for me, and you're gonna send me all the information on the youth dream team right away,
We just lost the match and you're leaving. You've changed your mind, haven't you
With so many plays, I volunteer
It will only be a few days before the city games are over.
All right
Then you must call me when you arrive. You, too. If you are bullied by these straight men, you must tell me.
What dialect clearly only coaches bully us.
Now that the rabbit has gone
In the past two days, the problem of stadium hygiene will be left to you. Forget it. Coach is inhuman. Clearly, we have already lost the match. It's miserable enough. Now it's unreasonable for us to clean up. Don't pretend.
Don't worry, someone will solve the health problem. I have already found volunteers. Who?
A senior student told me that she was short of credits and wanted to volunteer here.
I think people are quite reliable, so let her give it a try first.
Should be here in a minute
Maybe he did better than I did
Isn't it
Then I'll go to practice first.
Put that on top
Coach
Yao Zhen
Yao Zhen, why are you here again
Jun night we met again
Hello everyone, I am a new volunteer. These things are small gifts for cheerleaders and players to meet for the first time. I hope they can help everyone.
By the way, I will give everyone a gift card that can be consumed in any shopping mall of Haitai Group. Don't mention it.
Rabbit said that the volunteer was you, didn't you say senior student?
It was a 10,000-dollar card. This person won't get 100,000 yuan for 10,000 yuan. Thank you, fairy.
Why is it a fairy
With this little money, I want to buy off people's hearts.
Throw it all away
But this one was thrown away
Practice ball
Zhang Xiaoqiang, right
Hello, it's Yao Zhen
Coach
Can this beautiful woman stay a few more days
What do you say
Let's welcome volunteers to join us
Su Su Warm Summer
I will welcome you very well.
These two days may be hard for you.
The team manager of the school team may not be the same as you thought before, so let me know when today's training records are sorted out.
Then today's meal may need your help.
Coach
I think they worked so hard. I know there is a restaurant that specializes in nutritious meals for athletes. Why don't I order some over?
No
You are a volunteer. Just obey our arrangement.
A good coach
Are you calling those people who just came with you
To thank them for just carrying water, I shook hands politely and then they went to the infirmary.
I heard that Yao Zhen is an independent woman abroad.
How can this kind of thing depend on others
Where am I going to get it
Where's today's soup
Yao Zhen
This floor clean-up must be checked
We brought all these things ourselves, so aunt is not responsible and the light must be turned off.
If the security guard finds out that the lights are not turned off, it is our energy conservation problem, and then the club will be deducted points.
I don't think you have heard the legend of this basketball club yet.
This is the evening.
I-I just need to finish this. Aren't you afraid
When you go back today, you will have to document these training records and send them to me for backup. I will analyze them according to the above data.
King's Night
How can I finish so many things at night? Please help me
Didn't you say you wanted to volunteer
Me
Then please do your best
Where are you, miss? I'm sorry. We'll be right back in the infirmary.
Is it okay if we do this
Of course it's okay. We're all for the team.
Let's go first
See you tomorrow at night
What about you? It's for the team
I'm here for your night. She's here
How much it affects the progress of the team. You're right.
I'll go first. See you tomorrow
Where are you going
Hands
Some people are really popular.
Yeah
So you should cherish me
Are you hungry
Let's go for a snack
Then go to the restaurant that specializes in making nutritious meals for athletes.
How's Yao Zhen's house
You
I just want to be straightforward
Just tell her I like you. No
So what do you want
In a word
This matter
We'll talk about it when she's gone
Then keep working hard
If you don't help me do my own thing, do it yourself.
Help me
Master Jun, please, help me, help me, please
Coach Sue, is there something wrong with what
Your form is not based on individual players, which is invalid.
Let me look at yesterday's draft
This
It's not Anna. Dogs are not allowed in this stadium. How did you bring dogs? Get out of here. I have my own use.
You guys, you guys are going too far. I just want to help the players.
How can you use such despicable methods to drive me away?
If the allergy is serious, you should go to the hospital.
Yeah, coach
I didn't know she was allergic to dogs. I know
I did it on purpose, didn't I? How could Coach Sue treat her little sister like this?
That's too much, I
King's Night
Coach
Is the night god pulling the wrong person
This Yao is really difficult to deal with. He will pretend to be weak. Isn't that allergy? Do you know that it is dangerous if the allergy is serious?
Get the dog out of here
How long will you stay
Until you like me
I already have someone I like
You don't want to say it's that Su Nuan Xia, do you
Yes
What do you mean
I have suffered so much these days.
It was a joke
I thought you were going to volunteer
Why don't you have any gentlemanly manners
People as good as me like you for so long.
Don't you feel at all
No
What am I doing hiding here
There are a lot of good people like you
Am I going to like every one of them
Also
If you have such bad taste, you only like people like Su Nuanxia.
I think I'm out of sight.
Su Nuan Xia
She is much better than a self-righteous person like you.
You
They all passed the exam.
Warm Summer Rabbit Rabbit I told you that I passed all the exams and I can stay. Really? Great
When I get back, let's go out and have a big meal to celebrate. You're coming back.
Yeah, look, I'm already at the school gate
Do you miss me especially
Is it okay
You didn't know you were looking for that volunteer
King's Night
What's wrong with Junye
Is Yao Zhen coming for Night God again
Don't worry, when I get back and pick up her, it's all done.
I'll talk to you when you come back. I'll tell you, it's really a turnaround recently.
When you come back, let's go to the second canteen and invite you to have a big meal. OK
Okay, bye-bye
King's Night
We have to tell him quickly.
Is it a bit insincere to send it like this?
Red envelope
I passed the general practice
There is no need to go back to Beijing.
There are only so many WeChat wallets. In the afternoon, I would like to thank the bosses in person for saving their lives.
See you at the old place
Don't you think
I was infected by Yao Zhen.
Very surprising
The second place in the last classical music training examination was
Zhang Xiaoqiang, a sophomore from the Department of Architecture,
Mr. Zhang.
Is it what's reason to be an architecture student that you should take classical music as an elective
Do you think the art of architecture and the art of music are essentially the same? No
The main reason is that this man has a thin face and dragged me here anyway.
This is Qifeng, the first student in the exam. Let's meet everyone. Hello, Qi Feng Physics Department
Mr. Qi Feng, I heard that your electromagnetism paper has been published in British magazines and I am the main force of the school basketball team.
So I'm even more curious that it's what who let you take classical music
Isn't that the power of love
Like a beautiful little sister
Knowing that people like classical music, in order to find a common topic, this is the big move.
Brother Qiang, that's enough. Stop talking about it
All right, let's start the class now.
Mom, why are you here? Why don't you welcome me?
I made braised chicken wings
And chicken with chili pepper for you and rabbit rabbit to eat
Are you going to celebrate passing the exam? You know all about it. Look, I'm proud of you.
The tail is going to tilt to the sky.
Yes, I have already called your teacher and asked about your grades. This time you are stepping on a steel wire.
I almost fell, Mom. Then I passed the exam. Don't I have to go to Beijing?
You are just like your father
As stubborn as a donkey, there must be a first step in everything. I am really happy here. You see, I learn to play basketball at the same time.
Don't worry about it
You'd better
The child
You are so handsome at night. Is it really too handsome?
You are so handsome at night
Look at what and concentrate on your meeting.
Come here, come here
No one
Go this way
You've finally listened to me and disguised yourself
Is this necessary
How can I be so shady? You have so no confidence in your beauty?
At the beginning, I had a crush on your face.
And first-class football skills and wisdom, thanks to you, I can pass all the exams this time. Maybe I can still get a third-class scholarship.
Go ahead
How can I repay you for passing all the exams
Didn't I give you a red envelope
You want to bribe the school director with money.
Or
In a different way
Kick off
No one has made me so nervous for a long time. It is really numbing to say that victory.
Do teammates still need these
Teammates
Ridiculous fetters
Did I cut everything long ago to gain absolute power with scissors?
There is not only a technical gap between you and me, but also a far more essential difference than that.
You talk too much nonsense, Chu Ran-jun
Bet on the honor of the myth reserve team and the name of the charging beast.
If you have the courage, come and rob it.
Your consciousness is not enough
Indeed as expected is the king's name on the court, what's now it doesn't matter
I'm not standing here to play games like winning the best name with you, Coco.
I just want to check
The injury to your thigh
How's it goe