You can't beat me one on one
Why don't you hide this time
Then walking with you, I am especially like a rich woman with a little milk dog. It looks like she has special money.
Jokingly
This science building
It was donated by my grandfather in 1998.
Art
It was my fifteenth birthday
Grandpa built it for me
No.11 Teaching Building
I donated my first bucket of gold.
Well, well, you
Major catering chains surpass all walks of life.
The Junshi Group has been involved in these, all of which will be mine in the future.
And I'm yours
I don't want you just looking rich
Stay with me
All I have is yours.
With you rounded off, I held it in my hand.
Half the school
Assets, then I do have a lot of money.
How come it's you again
Shen Yingliang's hand is not wanted
Doctor
Well, I played too hard last time.
Next time I will be careful not to pay attention.
In the future, don't say you can't hold basketball with a scalpel.
What are we doing here
Inspecting my assets, of course
Is this infirmary also invested by Junshi
All Equipment
Excuse me, Mr. Shen
I promise you
Find the best doctor to see Shen Yingliang.
Do you believe me
Of course
Forget it
I don't think about what. I just want to be quiet
Who is Quiet
Shen Xuechang was given a warm summer holiday.
Quiet is the new player
Don't eat it cold if you have a bad brain.
Coach Jun bullied me at night.
On behalf of Qingmeng, I offer condolences to the basketball team.
The team has grown rapidly in such a short period of time. This time against Myth, we played with momentum and style.
Although we lose, we are still proud.
The players on the pitch are the hardest. I'm not what warm summer. You are too modest.
Not the Kui is coach Su's daughter, indeed as expected tiger father has no dog daughter
Principal, don't compare me with my father.
Of course, the younger generation will always be a pioneer.
Principal, our coach is very shy
All right, then I won't disturb everyone's training.
Take a good picture
King's Night
Warm summer now wants to be quiet, not night at night.
I think bunny bunny
I feel sick
The match should be steady and win. The health of the players is more important than winning or losing.
People are higher than basketball.
What are you doing
We have something to say today
Come on
The responsibility for losing the game cannot be borne by the coach alone.
So
We are going to hold a review conference.
Start
I have too much mood fluctuation on the court, my mentality is not stable enough, my moves are fancy, I want to be handsome in front of my sister, the purpose of playing is not pure, I am stupid, I can't overcome the shadow of dunk
I didn't take the lead as captain.
Can't limit the opponent's score, so usually ask the coach to give me more practice.
In fact, every time I train to squat in the pit for so long, it's not because I have a tummy, it's because I'm lazy.
Zhang Xiaoqiang, every time I go to deliver takeout, I say that I ask for leave. In fact, I lied to you. Ling Xuan, you and I are stupid.
Zhang Xiaoqiang Ling Xuan, you two
Give me a penalty to sweep the stadium for a month. Good, good, good
I never wash my hands when I go to the toilet. I wear a pair of underwear on the front and back four times. My avi format video has two T's. I have indexed it by different artists. I am a handsome boy.
You can only instigate so much money.
Is that a little happier
How many boxed meals can you buy with so much money, the red envelopes sent out, and the water spilled out
Your heart knows I know
Don't worry. It's okay
I don't believe it
Unless
You promised me to do a happy thing together every day.
Then I'm relieved
All right, what, is everything okay
What do you want
You'll know tomorrow
What about what
I think it's all right
But this exercise is not convenient either.
The quality is too poor. I'm sorry we didn't consider the way customers try on fashion in this way. We must pay attention next time.
Are you satisfied? Excuse me
Go
Don't buy this one
Three carat weight color cutting clarity is top grade
Excuse me
Go
This looks good
It is rare to meet what you like.
Buy
Should be able to hold basketball
It is better to put basketball in your hand.
I bought too much to wear. I came here.
How can you go home empty-handed
I'll take all of these
Hold it, please
What to do
I don't want any of these things
Why don't I take these things back
And then you drive
I'll call someone to pick it up.
Let's see
Anyway, it's close to the school.
Let's go by bus
I knew you hadn't been there
How about girlfriend, isn't she good?
Do you like taking buses very much
For two dollars, you can explore the city for free.
However, the morning and evening rush hours will not work.
Don't mention it
I can drive the car and you can also
Not the same
Wait for me in five minutes. I'll be right back
Do you like sweet cones
Mainly, the second one is half price.
A two-dollar bus will do
A small cone can also be used as a toast.
The coach is under a lot of pressure.
Let's stop pretending to be deep.
Hurry up and cheer up
A smile is worse than a cry.
Warm summer
You see
The light will come
Don't mention it
Coach Sue said before
Failure is the mother of success
Then we have too many moms
If you don't talk, no one will treat you as dumb.
I'm fine. Don't worry
Junye was right
There is no way to continue like this.
I decided to pay out of my own pocket. It's my treat.
In order to help everyone clear away the haze, it doesn't matter how much it costs. Let me do it. Let's order our Ling Xuan takeout.
Kill two birds with one stone
Gifts are not sent to people's hearts.
So
Do you like what in warm summer
That's it
Let's play a game
You answer my question, we're in a
We are all in the house
Two people
Eat for a day
Three meals
One room, two people, three meals and four seasons. I'll realize it for you.
How do you know I like it best
Because
I love you
This is what I want two people to be simple and happy together.
So as a memorial to our love
I have already put this house
Buy it
Who stipulates that a treat can only be a meal
Good quality and low price
Four dollars a two each
Ah, you
What Practice Reaction Ability
What's the order, no order, no catch? Run 20 laps tomorrow, Jun Night
Sorry, the left hand is lax in training.
Why did the coach continue to practice when he was stunned?
Good
It's all my fault that I was so radical yesterday that Shen Xuechang's injury worsened.
It's all my fault
Don't take all the blame on yourself. You said why didn't I notice
If I had found out earlier, if I hadn't been so competitive, it wasn't your fault.
You're just under a lot of pressure
Need to relax
Remember when we first ate sweet potatoes
How can I eat this kind of food? Then you won't eat it for me.
Anyway, who doesn't know this kind of thing will flatulence if you eat too much, bring it
Eat as you like
No, no, no, that day, no
It's not good at all. It's not good. You still eat it.
Su Nuan Xia
Me too
Here is the small one for you
Move, move, move
This is too happy, isn't it? I also want to have a boyfriend to practice catching dolls for me.
On average, three dollars a piece is not too cool. Yes, I'll go over there and see if there are what's fun.
Thank you
For you
This is what
These are the twenty-one stars I gave you. They form two hearts in the sky.
On behalf of my love for you
As eternal as the universe
Say what
No, take it back
Why is it that where will you go has a bad ending? The ending is not important. It is good that love is eternal.
I can't be with you today
Why
Is it
I did it wrong again, what
At fault
That's great
Today, you will accompany me to do one thing.
No problem
The goal of cooking this time is very simple.
Don't call
Take-out
Secret Recipe
This is my favorite dish from now on.
Leave it to me
I'll do it
No, no, no
It's too difficult. Why don't we change it? This is your wish.
Dried chili
You said Coach Sue was so good at cooking
Why did you give birth to a cooking idiot?
You know, what, I'm a theoretical expert. I'm a natural coach.
It's ugly
It's over, it's over. I just touched the chili
Make you laugh at me
It turns out that you will choke when cooking spicy dishes.
What's the matter
Miss Coach Sue
When he used to make spicy shrimp
It must be hard
It doesn't matter. Coach Sue is so good at cooking.
How can it be the same as the two of us
It's okay. I'm here
Rich levels, spicy and bitter
You said it was as advanced as making coffee with your hands.
Innovative Dish Diablo Spicy Shrimp
We did it
Hello, everyone, welcome to the second phase of the special project of the survival guide for straight men who know you warm on summer nights. I am your mentor Qingzi.
Today, our topic is the boyfriend's desire to survive.
Question 1 When your girlfriend asks how many ex-girlfriends you have, the correct answer is what.
Baby that doesn't exist, you are my first love. It's too fake.
The past is over. I believe you are the last one for me.
Too much wrong
To be honest with you, I have talked to nine girlfriends before.
To nine girlfriends
Respectively
Eyes like your nose, like your mouth, like your ears, like your hairstyle, like your figure, like your character, like your temperament, like your
Interests and hobbies are also like your last
I finally met a perfect you
That's awesome
Good
Question 2
When my girlfriend said the air conditioner here was too cold,
I know how to do this
Ask the waiter to turn up the air conditioner
Mistakes are too perfunctory.
That's not easy. Just drink more hot water.
Ding Lei, you've had enough, no matter when you are in what, as long as your boyfriend dares to say, drink more hot water.
Can be pulled out and shot
Like me
Must be the right answer
It's not
The best you can do is pass the exam.
Who told you to wear so little
He also showed his thigh.
Don't you know, take a coat
Chu Ran, isn't it your death to answer this way?
No wonder he talked about nine. Don't you know the weather has turned cooler recently? Do I have to wear a coat every day to come out?
Can I give it to you at any time
You just deserve it
I deserve to buy you a new dress.
Go
I'll take you to buy a coat