Why haven't they come back yet
Girls always take more time to go to the bathroom. You don't have to worry about them. They need to spend what time.
Those who don't make up and don't make up may be faster than us boys.
Eat your meal
Do you think I am Qi Feng
Chu Ran, can you please take a picture for us? We'll take it when everyone is together.
Didn't you say
You and Chu Ran are pure brother and sister
How do I think he is jealous with the night god
How should I know
I'm speechless, too. Okay
Well, you are really popular.
The two male gods are jealous of each other.
There is also an Anna eyeing up the other side.
It's none of your business
No, I can't even take my little errand brother down.
It's really heart-rending. Are you all right? You and I told you not to drink so much. You still drink
The play I chased yesterday guessed the wrong combination again. I thought it was the male owner.
I am very sad that I am a good man. Why doesn't everything come according to my guess? Why is it bad?
Why do you say what I like it
You eat more at night. I think your training usually consumes your physical strength and makes up for it.
This is the warm summer spot
Then she's not here now. Just take my seat later.
She won't be so stingy, will she
Miss Anna is a good match for you
You really think so, of course
However, if you are so handsome at night, there should be no teenage fans.
You must be very experienced in love. You are a star player in Binhai Province.
There are more fans than I do.
Isn't that more experienced in love than I am
Shen Xuechang
What's wrong with Jun Ye and Chu Ran? How do I feel strange?
I have no idea
Young People's Ideas
I can't keep up
Are you fighting for the coach
Does Chu Ran want to pry the warm summer to replace Han Mo of the myth team in the past?
Why is there no answer to the phone?
Bunny, I also called
No answer
Where did you go in the warm summer
Are you all right
Are you drunk
It's not all her fault
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. She drank too much. She drank too much. Do you know that my skirt is very expensive?
Do you think this will work
Well, I'll transfer the dry cleaning fee to you
Xiao Tu Rabbit
Is it money? I have money
I'll give you all the money. I'm sorry. You're insane. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Look at her drinking like this.
I won't wear any more clothes that I vomited. You must make it up to me in full. Five thousand pieces, not a cent less.
Xiao Rabbit, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
All right, you girl
I have to remember something for you
Avoid defaulting when you wake up
Come on, you owe me the 5,000 IOUs first. Give me her hand and stand up.
Good
Ling Xuan, please send the rabbit back to school.
Pay attention to safety in small matters
Come on, slow down, slow down
There is only one seat available in Junye's car. Let me take a taxi to take you home.
What for
Let's take a taxi
What are you doing
Brother, your car
You let go of me and I can go by myself.
You're bleeding
I'm bleeding, Ling-hyun
You quickly take me to the best hospital to have a nosebleed and go to the best hospital in what.
Do you think I have no money
I have money
Give it to you. Give it to you
I don't want your money. I have long wanted to give you money.
But I know you'll be angry
You, you said, what, did you know
In order to give you an extra floor fee,
How many takeout and milk tea have I ordered? I have gained 10 kg. I have become a little fat man. No one likes me anymore.
Did you order my delivery on purpose? The wife of shop-owner said that you had a commission on the delivery order.
I'm trying to make money for you
And you know what
The noodle shop where you work
It's awful, it's awful, it's awful
Is it that bad
Ling Xuan, I'm sponsoring you. I mean it
I don't want you to work so hard again. I don't work hard. I don't work hard.
Stop thinking about how to help me
Xiao Tu Rabbit
Why did you fall asleep
King's Night
You take her home
Brother Churan is too arrogant these days, isn't he
Coach, these days
Probably exhausted, too
That's how she is
You can sleep anywhere in what.
Warm summer
What do you want me to say to understand
You said you
Why do you do so much for me
Or tell me
I usually have such a bad attitude towards you.
Ling Xuan
I like you
Hello, please ask Coach Han for leave for me.
It's so handsome. You see, it's so handsome. Is it from our school? It's from our school.
He is the new captain of our basketball team. Don't you even know that his name is Chu Ran
Hello, aunt
Chu Ran
I heard that you have been training very hard recently.
Warm summer is not here. Please come and see me for dinner when you have time.
Auntie cooks you delicious food.
I also saw it with warm summer yesterday.
What, you don't know
I really hate English class the most. I have graduated from high school. Why can't I get rid of the ocean of knowledge?
English is difficult in other classes that are difficult in what, okay?
I am not like you. I am most afraid of taking English tests.
If I pass the English exam, what will use it. In case I fail in other classes, I will not have to pay it back.
Su Nuan Xia
Mom and Aunt
If it weren't for Chu Ran
I didn't even know you changed your report to Qingmeng without authorization.
Chu Ran told you
This is too much. I'll call him. Don't change the subject.
I didn't change the subject
Mom, I was wrong
Aren't I afraid to tell you that I'm afraid of your objection
Of course I object
Didn't you already see the result of your father's training for the basketball team?
Then I didn't want to fulfill my father's last wish, did I
My team is very good, really
I believe they will win the myth.
Just trust your lovely and beautiful daughter. Support it.
Let's see
I can also take a step back.
As long as you fulfill my request
I will allow you to stay
Thank you. Don't thank you so early. This request is not that simple.
I want you to be excellent in every subject at the end of this term.
Otherwise, you will leave Qingmeng quickly.
Let's change it
There's no way, then I can only give up my favorite thing in order to get the first place in Qingmeng.
I can only give up my favorite sleep in and get up early to study hard.
Before, the dormitory environment was too comfortable.
The efficiency of reading in the library must be high.
I don't believe I can't knock you
Isn't that the coach
Encounter a coach who fell asleep while studying in the library.
It's true that I know my daughter, but I don't know my mother. Warm summer's mother really saw her.
Warm summer went to the library to prove that I still want to work hard.
Maybe she can really fulfill her mother's request.
If she doesn't pass the exam
Is it true that we can only return to Beijing,
Of course
In case she does not pass
No
With her intelligence quotient
Certainly not
Shall we help her
I think this is a deep pit.
You'd better not jump in
The coach is stupid and has strong self-esteem.
Even if you help, she may not be able to accept your statement that what
No, no, no
I mean, I have a way
Welcome Su Nuanxia to come back from the glorious sleep in the library.
Stop it
I studied here all day and what didn't learn it.
He was also photographed in the ugly hair group.
I can take the beautiful photos.
I said you really are
How long have you been there? Sleep like a pig
You are still not a friend. You deleted you for me.
But I have a way to save you from the hot water.
Are you sure you want to do this to me? Do you have memory bread or can you pass through the future and read the test paper?
You see
How do I think Zhang Xiaoqiang's tone is not like this?
It's a little stiff. Your focus is strange. Take a closer look at it.
Night God is really a student bully.
Xueba
This is a chance for you to make up for it.
I was also reluctant to find you to make up a missed lesson. I seem to
Not begging you to give me this chance
Don't you want this beautiful, kind and lovely coach to stay and help you
You think these two idioms have something to do with you
Why do you still try to be brave when you have steps down in Su Nuan and Xia Su Nuan
But now you have something to ask for
Your major is athletic anatomy
Exercise physiology
And sports psychology
Then let me see how well you have mastered it first.
Let's just be so-so
Qi and blood barrier is what's meaning.
Don't remember
Proprioceptor; proprioceptor
What mean again
You said next, next, I will be fine. I already know how well you have mastered it.
What degree degree of slag
Mr. Shen, you must know a lot about the Myth Team
Is it okay
After all, there have been several meetings. Can you tell us about it?
I heard Ling Xuan say that you had already fought Lu Ye at the resort.
Well, you must have a full understanding of his strength, right?
Besides him, Jiang Yichen, nicknamed the Violent Killer, is the strongest center I have ever played against.
And
Gu Yuan, a shooting guard who is good at eagle shooting.
And point guard Xia Ze's forward Mirage pass
They are all top-notch players. It seems that there is also a forward named Downfold, who uses three fingers to join up.
Fly up at a high speed
Xia Ze is very strong
But I beat him up
Who do you think is the most mythical person?
Today
It used to be Luye
Now it's Chu Ran
I haven't had a fight with Chu Ran yet. Tell me how terrible it is. This has to start three years ago.
At that time, I stopped at the basketball club. Let's talk about it tomorrow. I'm in a hurry to make up a missed lesson. You all helped me.
Xue Ba Jun
Do you dare to bend the rules
These are all things I would like to eat but dare not eat at ordinary times.
You said you came to make up a missed lesson for me and bought so much delicious food.
How embarrassed I am
These are your meals for the day
Every page you memorize, Mazel
You can eat the same thing
You are too eager to pass the exam.
All right, all right, do as you say.
I have already memorized half a page.
Can I eat half a chicken wing
Not so hard
Dun
People are iron, rice is steel, and people will not be hungry for a while.
I think you have the strength to do something about it.
Then
Memorize two pages before eating one. Don't go too far. If you want to go back to Beijing,
Don't waste my time here
I mean, if you don't eat these wings
It gets cold
Continue to recite
I can fall asleep all the time
Why are you so close to me
Su Nuan Xia
If you pass the exam this time
Let's go on a date
Please, I am a computer student who can't help you with English.
Nonsense
Your JAVA C + + what is not all written in English. Besides, people's night gods are not studying sports either. He is very attentively helping warm summer tutoring.
I'm not a student bully lying to me.
I checked
Last year you won a huge scholarship. I couldn't help it.
After all, earning scholarships is more efficient than working.
Forced me to study hard and strive for high marks in the exam.
You're talking about what
Don't you feel wronged by getting a scholarship? Let's not talk about it. I don't have much time. I still have two jobs to do and three simulation questions to do.
Go on and review for yourself. I'll go first.
Xue Ba Jun
I think I have learned the key points of Mazel backwards and can go out and fight.
Talk about it
Read with me the three laws of simple materialism, water, fire, earth, metaphysics, solitary and quiet films. No to reveal things. I say materialism and you say materialism.
Are you stupid to drink Coke
You're stupid
This is the super test site I invented exclusively. Recite the pithy formula. All right, just rap and walk.
No matter how boring the content is, it becomes very simple in an instant.
Do you think the representative of simple materialism is the Five Elements Theory of Jin Mu, Water, Fire and Earth
Does metaphysics represent stillness and one-sided
Is that all right
There is no problem in making up pithy formulas.
But your painting style is not right. Isn't it going to be the general exam tomorrow?
Isn't it to improve efficiency? Now Mazel has taken care of it. There is still a lot to review.
If you don't hurry, it will be dark. I'm here.
Can't be blacked out
Not necessarily
Is it true that there is a power outage in what these days. I am so tired of power outages that I should come soon.
I don't know. Let's go check with logistics. Okay
Rabbit, Rabbit, Rabbit, Rabbit
Where are you in warm summer? Our dormitory has a power outage.
No way, the dormitory has no electricity either.
It is said that the whole failure will not be recovered until after midnight.
It's over. It's over here
Prepare for today's surprise endorsement. This is great. There is no chance.
Do I have to go back to Beijing
Come on
You ask the night god to think of some way to use the power of love to generate electricity. Don't make any noise there.
I'm not in the mood to joke with you. Hang up
Looks like we'll have to study in the moonlight tonight
The moonlight is gone
Go to my bedroom
There are separate wires
Your Aunt Suguan is too scary.
Who can see it in the dark?
Come on, let's go
You are the only one with electricity in the whole school.
This kind of sVIP treatment
Let a person envy jealousy hate
Have electricity
It was just a coincidence
I did it for the sake of safety
This has something to do with security, what
Some time ago
Someone steals high-power electrical appliances.
I am worried about the potential safety hazard.
So I went to the engineering department.
Draw a new thread
I didn't expect to use it today.
You can review in this chair
This time it is very comfortable to sit up.
Good
Read for a long time
Want soft light
This desk lamp
Good for your eyes
You said you were so thoughtful to help me review.
Thank you. Then I was here studying hard before I called tonight.
Let me analyze the exercises for you
Could you please ask the logistics department
Try to call late
It's not scientific
All right, all right
Just one exercise book
You are more than half wrong.
Did you take a good look at the key points I ticked for you? I read them and I memorized them.
The answer above
I can't understand it at all.
I don't have any pictures in my mind.
Besides, those words are almost the same. I don't know which is which and which can't remember.
That's a lot
What's Fixed Points of Muscle Follow-up
I can't remember it anyway.
Good
Take a good look
Only once
Take it
Lift dumbbells and bend your forearms for example.
What about the time like this
This piece of skin
Is the fixed point
That is, the relative motion is relatively small
It is fixed
Oh, what
Feel what you let me touch
Here
So strong
What if this is the way it moves
This
It becomes a moving point.
Move
Magic
Let me have a look at the rest
Trapezius muscle
Biceps brachii and abdominal muscles
Then the pectoralis major muscle
Why don't you talk
Me
Suddenly a little hungry
Do you have anything for what
You keep watching. I'll cook now.
Eat noodles
Yes, you
It's even better than the one in the advertisement.
Selling photos is only the foundation.
The most important thing is to eat well.
Come and try it
Am I getting up too early
Why don't I do it again
I lied to you
Very delicious
Really
If you don't believe me, try it.
How is it
Is it okay
Row
If you are so reluctant, I will take care of the rest. I'm not polite to you.
This is definitely the best noodle I have ever eaten.
I didn't think I could have such a high-level treatment on this blackout night before the examination.
So exaggerated
Actually
I am rewarded to girls who study hard.