Don't you go and open the window for some air, fool
No
It's useless for me to open it. Then open it quickly, sister.
How come it's you again
What flavor
Burning what is so choking.
Excuse me
She's here to sterilize my bedroom
Disinfect and disinfect what poison
I have a cold and fever recently and am thinking of going home to rest for a few days.
This side of the dormitory is free to do some disinfection and sterilization. I'll tell you, don't cover up her.
This girl in our school will be punished for breaking into the boys' dormitory.
She's here to sterilize
She's not from our school
Auntie, please take her away quickly.
What about my disinfectant
I'll get it for you
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Shut the water off
On Personal Technology I admit that no one can resist the current myth except Lu Ye. Chu Ran myth is a place that depends on strength to speak.
Chu Ran Becomes Captain
I have no problem
It also depends on whether Lu Ye is willing or not.
Lu Ye withdrew
He asked me to take a message to the coach that he and Night God are friends in private and can be rivals in basketball, but he will never lead the team with the defected running dog.
It doesn't matter
The reason why myth has been oppressed by green dreams for so many years is
Because there is no absolute leader, Lu Ye's family is too good.
Basketball is a game to him
It is only a matter of time before you retire from the team.
You concentrate on playing your own ball.
Don't care
Although everyone has no opinion,
Let's start training
Get up
Don't interfere with training
Captain, I want to play
Yes
I, Chu Ran, have never been uncompromising.
Either you quit the basketball team
Either from the palace
Hey, where are you? Why don't you answer the phone
I'm at home
I forgot my cell phone in the car.
Are you feeling better
Your Dark Cuisine
Pro-test is effective
I'm back to normal
Really
So when do you go back to school in what
Every time I dig a hole for you, I haven't formally apologized to you.
Apologize will be forgiven.
Come back tomorrow
Let's resume training as soon as possible.
All right, no problem
King's Night
I forgot to ask you last night how do you feel when you are tied up with Ling Xuan for a day?
It's boring
Ling Xuan said the same thing
Why don't you finish it sooner
Make fun of what
This shows that your cooperation is not enough and you should strengthen your practice.
Can't you do something reliable
Go
The first Gothic church was the Church of Saint-Dennis, which was built in Paris in 1143
Its four-point coupon skillfully solves the stress problem of rib frame vault structure.
Where's Zhang Xiaoqiang
Why didn't you come to class? I don't know
Did you go to play ball
Lack of earnestness in reading
Dare to skip classes and play basketball,
Let him get ready to retake it. No, no, no, teacher. I didn't skip class. At best, I was only a few minutes late.
The three of you are doing what tricks. They said
You did well in class
Want to drop in for class
I'll tell you Zhang Xiaoqiang, don't be glib with me.
I promise to miss your subject if I fail at the end of the term.
You're on a national scholarship
Shen Yingliang
You are Qi Feng of Baoyan
Teacher
Please support the basketball team training, teacher. You can rest assured that basketball is only a sideline. Our job is still to be a student bully.
You don't usually take part in training.
Is the loneliness master after all
Or is it an out-of-breath player
I really want to have a good look
Interesting
You'll see it soon
Are you worried that we are still at the same level as a year ago
Ding Lei
You really make me sit up and take notice. I would rather not be a man than play basketball.
All right
However, it is not your own palace to prick your thigh with scissors, Captain, please fulfill my determination.
Row
From today on, you will be a regular player.
Captain, I will use my results to prove that your choice is not wrong.
True Man
Facts have proved that my love training method is very reliable.
Although there were some stumbling blocks at first,
But with the passage of time
The tacit understanding will definitely improve. I believe everyone will see their progress through today's training.
Today's training is
All clothes exchanged
Shen Aifei and Qi Aifei
Gentlemen, take your hands and feet lightly. Don't tear my dragon robe apart.
I can't do it
Pain
You take off
You see, these two people are beginning to have a tacit understanding, right? Yes, there will be a lot of people paying attention to it when it is posted to the post bar.
I said
It seems that it is not the way to spend it like this.
So what
Or else
I'll take it off for you first and then you'll take it off for me.
Why is this painting style a bit strange
I told you
After practicing this set, they will all play it on their own.
Tell the truth
If the problem of tacit understanding is solved,
Is there any hope of winning the myth
In the morning, I like strong confrontation.
Defence is not enough
He will never dunk
Alley-oop Wins Hidden
Gu Yuan's move is to throw in the Eagle. His shooting rate is now close to the standard of professional players.
World Martial Arts
Only fast can't break
Bai Yin's Phantom Pass and Xia Ze's Ghost Hand Breakthrough are, to put it bluntly, one word.
Quick
The opposing players can't even see clearly.
How to prevent why they dare to show their strength today
That's because you're here
It has brought them a strong sense of oppression.
A good shot
Yes, I can
Welcome to this place
Xiao Tu Rabbit
This is a small gift to thank you for taking care of me in the hospital.
I hope you can take it
I am a man of atmosphere
All right, I now declare our love training method officially over.
Now that everyone has a basic degree of cooperation, we will enter formal high-intensity training.
Finally liberated
Me too
Coach, I have a suggestion. I suggest we all go swimming together today to relax.
Relaxation can
But at this time
Where is the door still open? There is a little night god's house. As long as my brother calls, there will be a swimming party with all kinds of delicious food soon.
It's great for me to go, isn't it? The life of rich people is ours with such a big swimming pool.
This is called luxury. Take it easy. Come on, don't slow down. Yes, it's time to relax.
If only Anna were here
What about Su Nuan Xia
Here we go, here we go
Warm summer
Can't you swim
Although I am the king of land sports
But this sport in the water is not my dabble.
If you can't swim, you can't swim.
The words are still so nice, then I won't be able to learn. I'll tell you, an hour later, a new swimmer came into being again.
King's Night
You don't go into the pool party.
I have never seen such a boring person as you
I'm different
Very not easy to have this free swimming pool
Ll swim a little longer
There is no sport in this world that I can't learn in Su Nuanxia.
That's stubborn
Let's leave them alone
When tired, they will come up on their own.
Swimming is very difficult for what. I have learned it now.
Help! Warm summer fell into the water! Help!
Don't sink, idiot
Are you all right
You can drown in a swimming ring.
Are you stupid
Come on, come on, brother, I have everything ready for you. This is the universe invincible romantic battle that I have carefully prepared for you.
Candlelight dinner 99 roses plus violin blessing
Proper hard core confession three-piece set, you wear more handsome
You can make your debut perfectly.
Confess
Didn't you say you missed a chance to make it clear to Coach Sue
You mean
Today is a good opportunity
Necessary
Really not, you
Don't you think this pool party tonight is a bit suspicious
It's a little suspicious. The whole atmosphere decoration is very romantic.
You see, it's not Christmas. Why is there a Christmas tree and there are so many beautiful colored lights? Even if the Night God's family is rich, it can't be so well prepared at once, can it?
Wait
There should be a good show.
Warm summer
Me
I heard that you like roses very much.
This was prepared by Zhang Xiaoqiang. I missed the last one.
Celebration dinner, congratulations again. You are one step closer to your dream.
Thank you very much. I like it very much. Just like it.
Everybody had a good time today
But I have to go back early because I have class tomorrow.
Did he just confess
I don't know, it feels more useless than me.
It was really a good show.
You are miserable in warm summer.
I think it is better for you to take the initiative.
If only Anna were here
Is it not straightforward enough
What for
What situation Shen Xuechang
I scored the ball right away. Why did I blow it off?
If the whistle had been blown hard, you would have violated the law. Are you mistaken? If you want to blow it, you should also blow Qi Feng's foul. Okay
What if the referee doesn't blow
Do we lose a chance to score? There are many uncertainties in the official match.
The best thing to do in a situation like this is to put the ball outside and then let Jack Bauer hit the scoring rate.
Everyone plays in a different style and what you are talking about is a small probability event.
It's not
The old captain was right
Why are you back
Warm summer
He went out with Junye just now. He should be back soon. Why don't you wait
Next time, I've got a team member
I have to go
Yes, I'll give you a ride
Three, two, one ready for release
Although college does not prohibit love, you express yourself in such an out-of-line way.
It is too ignorant of the school rules.
Principal
May I ask which school rule stipulates that the school building cannot be hung with spray painting, which is an advertising act for the public display of more than one square meter of spray painting.
Need to go to the school publicity office in advance for approval,
Zhang Xiaoqiang
Have you gone through the approval process
Was the one who planned the affair
If you want to criticize the dismissal,
I have nothing to do with my brother
Principal
Can't expel Zhang Xiaoqiang. Our club has no substitute. How can he play when he leaves?
Do you also like your night in warm summer? I think you are very happy. I didn't
Principal
What about this
It is true that Zhang Xiaoqiang did not handle it properly.
So
Should be dealt with seriously
Jun night, why are you doing this? I'm doing this for you
All right, all right, let's not do it again. After all, Junshi is a sponsor. Let's go back to class, all of you.
Thank you, Principal
However, this big news is estimated to have spread in the school.
Come on, left. Draw a dragon with me
Draw a rainbow on your right
Do you remember three years ago
When I first met you
The new table for the basketball club is there.
Come and see the basketball club
Well, thank you for taking a look at this
Okay, thank you
Hello, is this where the basketball club signs up
Classmate
Why do you want to join the basketball club
I want to play professional league, what, did you hear him? He said he played professional league and I want to sweep the basketball world and pick up six rings. That's funny.
What's funny
My goal is also to reach the national league.
Classmate, I know you. Are you the talented freshman who refused to join the national youth team, Sayyeh God
Please give me more advice. Sayoshi, we will be teammates in the future. I hope we can interpret our dreams together.
I still remember it so clearly after so long.
Of course
The dream is always there.
No matter how long it takes, it will not change.
So you switched to the myth team
It's also to get closer to the dream. Coach Su is gone.
Qingmeng is not far away.
Green Dream Team, listen carefully. I am Ding Lei, the beast of charge. I came here today to give you a letter of war.
In two months' time, I'm going to get you down on your field with my own hands.
I didn't think the players you brought were really in debt. I arranged the match.
I just want to tell you the fact that Qingmeng has no future.
Captain, you're going to graduate soon
There is no need to get involved in this muddy water, is there?
Everyone is young, and I'm just two years older than you
You have dreams that you can't lose, and I also have feelings that I can't give up.
Let's wait and see
When the official competition comes, you will know whether Qingmeng has a future or not.
Yes
I look forward to
That
I won't send it
King's Night
I was wrong about you. You value sex over friends.
I won't help you again next time.
Coach
You must decide for me
Then let's go back to the stadium now.
I will give you the right decision. Coach what
I, I'll go back to the stadium first, and you can talk slowly, okay
You're angry
It was really Jack Bauer who did it behind my back.
I'm a victim, too
So this
It's not what you mean
You can't say that. Then you just said you didn't know
Count me as
Do you know
Su Nuan Xia
Do you have anything what wants to say to me
Actually, I want to say to you
Starting from today, you and Zhang Xiaoqiang have packed the hygiene of the stadium.
It was really hammered late at night and Su Nuanxia were in contact, but he denied it last time.
Wait
Are you sure you won't give me a chance
If you really like me, you will go to the teaching building to draw spray painting.
Let's take a look at the camera
It is too old-fashioned for you to express yourself like this at night. This is a good way for male gods to express themselves.
It must be Su Nuan's summer is too green tea to bewitch our night gods by various means.
Yes, the night god is soft-hearted and is most easily cheated by such a woman. This woman is absolutely not allowed.
On the night of the king to do something
Good
So what happens next
If I knew what I was looking for
You're back
Let me tell you something
The glorious deeds that you expressed late at night have now spread to the circle of friends and the whole university town is eating your melons.
Do you want to come to a piece of Zhang Xiaoqiang's blind heckling in person? How do you follow the rhythm? I am the coach.
How can a coach fall in love with a player
It's not a love affair between teachers and students.
Why not
Well, if that's the case, let's report to the coach about the current crisis of the team.
What crisis
This is the latest expenditure
October 25
Two Boxes of Mineral Water
Thirteen boxes of lunch boxes at Grandma's house.
October 26
Mineral water is 156.70 yuan plus the sports equipment you bought today, which will be charged for this month.
Minus 8,736.30
We are in debt this month. Are these people pigs? How can they eat so much?
Why don't you let them start sharing others next week? I don't know, but the reason why Ling Xuan trains is
Most of the reason is that there are two free boxed meals after the training.
He'd be gone if he'd split it out. Why is this drink so expensive
This is the last time you were happy to reward them. You forgot my dead head.
This is your credit card limit, which makes it full now. I have also paid you more than 700 yuan.
The repayment date is next week.
Do you still have that much money on hand now
What should I do then
There is a kind of campus cash loan that can save the emergency.
The handling fee is very high.
You're talking about the kind of
The kind of management platform that can take nude photos for credit investigation and then be taken by the police a few days ago.
Otherwise, there is a what method.
We must persist until the day when Qingmeng triumphs over myth.
Thank you
Waiter refills
Have you finished your work yet
Why haven't you left yet
Didn't I come here to ask the working talent for advice on how to make money?
You still need to make money. Jun Yefu's second generation told you verbally.
His pocket money for a day is enough for our club to spend several years. I have explained it more than 800 times. It was Zhang Xiaoqiang who made trouble behind his back.
Hurry up
You see, for the sake of my support for your career today
Tell me quickly if there is a quick way to make money in what.
And supported my career. If it weren't for you, I would have left work
Say or not
Hurry up
You are so strong that men are not as good as you.
Why don't you move the bricks
Now the construction site can make money for tens of thousands of dollars a month, which is not a dream.
Warm summer warm summer
Wake up, warm summer is over.
Are you all right in the warm summer
You're not really going to the construction site to move bricks, are you? I'd like to go, but they don't want girls.
Then you go to work in what and don't even sleep.
Well, it's like moving bricks anyway. You can't go on like this.
Why don't you ask Jun Night for help
In the style of his giant spray painting, he may have transferred a million directly to the team's account.
It's so cold
Don't worry, I have a solution
As for you, just be responsible for increasing revenue and cutting expenditure.
I went to work
Bye-bye
The little girl is very energetic.
Su Nuan Xia
What are you doing
Work
About the basketball team
Not enough for you
Put it down first
Don't bother me with my money
You are short of money
The basketball team has bought a new batch of equipment.
So I've been in negative equity lately
How much do you need
As an independent woman in the new era,
I will not ask you for money.
Why is this not what I confessed the day before yesterday, right? The social atmosphere is not good and I have a good taste for it.
Release
What are you doing