This later period is too difficult. It is more difficult than playing basketball.
This is not the first film of Qingmeng. Why can't it be perfect and amazing?
I've already registered my microblog number. Upload the movie quickly.
But how about a what title
Highlights of Qingmeng Basketball Team's Wonderful Moments
All right, I've listened to your hard work.
From then on, Qingmeng Basketball Team will soon reach the peak of its life.
Popular All over the Network Sponsoring Man Man to Become a Star Team
Don't worry, with my editing skills, I will definitely attract many fans.
Is this a loophole
How is it that the reading volume of only 15 is not enough? Usually I send a selfie to browse with more than 1,000
I sent a photo of us.
It's not scientific
In my good looks
How can it not attract clicks
Ling Xuan, you changed the cover to my photo.
Very normal
Basketball on Weibo
It's not as good as entertainment news, and you didn't buy promotion and traffic.
Don't mention it
You know that, too
Junshi Group has Propaganda Department and Public Relations Department
However, this title is also declarative.
We're trying to help, too. It's okay. Everybody, don't be discouraged
While no one is looking at it yet
We can do it again
Send it out again
Good
Junye classmate
Hello hello hello
Introduce yourself
My name is Alex
This is my company
That's right
How about our company
Recently, I am cooperating with fashion magazine.
Is to discover new people and shoot a group of plane posters,
But the editor-in-chief was not satisfied with the alternative model until he saw your video and asked me to ask you.
Are you willing to make magazines
Don't worry, we are definitely a regular company.
How about I make you an offer of 50,000
All right
I see
Good address is up here. Find me when you get there.
Be sure to call me
50,000 yuan
Mob Advertising Media Co., Ltd.
Photographer
Is your night for sponsorship fees,
If you take a look at this name, it is unreliable. It will not be an unscrupulous company that cheats boys and girls to take nude photos.
My God, you have a fire ahead of me at night. I can't imagine it.
Isn't that awesome
No
This must not be allowed to happen
You are
I'm looking for a man named Amway,
Hmm
Whoops.
Is our momentum okay?
In the car far away
Absolutely stable
Their this
For what
Good
It's perfect
It's a natural clothes rack.
The position is a little to the left.
Who are you
Who are we? We are here to punish rape and eliminate warm summer.
Evil
What are you doing here
Is this the mob, what, mob, we're here at the Bird Union Culture Media Company
You're making a mistake. What's the matter
He also wants to come in and make trouble.
I'm sorry
How do we know someone will take the name of a ghost like the bird and the crowd?
So do you have anything to do with what now
If it's okay
I ask you to leave
Can I stay? No
Let her stay
All right
But you can only keep one person
Row
Remember not to divulge the shooting information. There are free fruit, tea and water to drink. Let the security guard get them.
What a big own goal this time
This time, Jun Ye really came down to earth and took a job for the team.
Not bad. Perfect. Come on
Take your shoulders easy. Let's have another group.
Good
Good to keep
Sell his boyfriend's body for the team,
I am also a qualified coach. Well, this is the end of today's shooting.
Next
Do you have any thoughts of moving forward in this direction
You are really in good shape.
You look awesome in a suit
Excuse me. Wait a minute
You see
How about this picture? This state
Can you send me all these photos later
All right
Let me see you
How's it goe? Luo is always perfect
This is Mr. Luo, chief editor of our company
Your outline is very stiff.
Cheeks, jaws and chin lines. You are very interesting to me.
Give me your WeChat
In the future, I will personally connect with you.
I have already added your WeChat
Since you are so proud and charming
Then will you sweep me
Isn't this the story of a rich woman keeping a little German shepherd?
Why don't you fasten this button well?
Go
Little girl, I appreciate your young people's courage to love and hate.
But I feel like you misunderstood me
I asked you for WeChat at night to sign him as an artist.
I might
Misunderstanding
Don't mention it
As long as you don't mind
I asked my assistant to draw up the commercial terms of the contract.
Guaranteed income of 800,000 yuan a year
Wait until you see the contract before you make a decision
Luo Zong
I don't have to read the contract.
My girlfriend agreed
I'll sign it
If the contract is signed, the funding gap can be closed.
But
Why do I always have the feeling of selling my husband for glory?
No, no, no, Junye, trust me so much
I certainly can't let him down.
Little girl
I'm so envious of you. How about that
Have you decided, coach? Have you decided
Decided
Not to sign
With what's own boyfriend to show it to others, right
Mr. Luo worked hard. Teacher worked hard. Let's stop the team and go.
Warm summer played a handsome role in the advertising company today, but the problem of funds and grandpa
We have to solve one
Don't worry about my grandfather's problem
It can be postponed for a while.
But I can let that man beat me again.
Redeem my watch
You
Forget it
Otherwise, I will grind my teeth and go to the construction site to take part-time jobs.
You
Forget it, or I'll grind my teeth and borrow it from Anna.
Forget it
Otherwise, I will bite my teeth and open a live broadcast to cut a wave of leeks.
There can be
No, you're serious
Oh, it's not you
It's not you, it's him
Here we go, here we go
Dear fans, I am Junye, forward of Qingmeng Basketball Team.
Answer the question, Night God. You are what Night God. How long can your eyelashes be? Do you like sweets besides playing basketball?
Do you have any other preferences of what? Besides playing basketball, you have other preferences of what.
Read a book
The most intolerable thing is what
The first thing to do when you get up in the morning
Open one's eyes
The most intolerable thing
The most intolerable thing should be to make mistakes on the court.
Night God's life is so boring, besides basketball or basketball
But even in this way, the traffic in the room is also large.
See that
More than 7,000 people poured in just one minute.
The most intolerable thing is that so many gifts are too ruthless. Is he a money printer?
Brother Qiang
Please help me to see if this reward ANNA is Anna Benna.
Do you like Japanese food? I don't like listening to what music
When light music is ready, all today's questions will be answered.
Over
Ladies and gentlemen, I am very happy to meet you here today.
So you and what can all raise the issue with me, oh
My idol has approached. Night God, dare you show me your side face again? Night God, I am your little maid, face, genius is you.
I will randomly select three questions and then answer them.
Do you like what color
Blue
I like to drink what drinks.
White Water
Like what type girls
Medium-long hair
High-nosed
Round-faced
The girl who stands up right under my chin is, yes, you are.
What for
Idol Idol is me is me
The night god's boyfriend is strong and the night god pulled me up. I want to report it. Mom, the night god is telling me
Well, in order to thank you all for your support, I'll postpone it for another five minutes.
Night God, Night God King, Night God, Night God
Slow down, slow down, slow down, don't squeeze, don't squeeze, don't squeeze, night god, night god
This is the chicken soup my mother made for you. Can you have a sip of it? Night God, Night God, this is the doll I made myself. Can you accept it?
I don't accept gifts
Night God, you take it. Night God, I already have a gift, so we won't accept it. Thank you for your support.
I hope everyone will pay more attention to our youth dream team.
Officials and micro people forward more and pay more attention to it.
It's been a hard day. Everyone, go back to rest early. Thank you
Night God, night God, she's right
Let's go back to rest early today.
So handsome
All right, let's do what we say
Today, you are also tired at night. Let's all get rid of it.
Why didn't you just let me talk to them
Now it's a rising season for the team and you have the most fans. I'm afraid I'll lose my fans after disclosing my girlfriend.
So you're willing to let me take their gifts
You won't be jealous
Is that what you want to see
Neither do I
For the team
I can't help it
Rabbit Rabbit
Why don't you think there are any fans looking for me?
They dare to find my man and I hit them in the face with gifts.
All right, all right, Queen, I was wrong
Hit him, hit him, keep up, hit him
Sister, do you have time tonight
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Who said there were no handsome men in basketball
This is what I told you about the night god. He is handsome enough to turn around.
This team is full of long legs. Tomorrow's public number finally has material.
Push it to the photographer first
Send it, send it
Excuse me, is this Qingmeng Basketball Team
Yeah
We are from Liusheng Middle School and have always admired you.
In particular, Brother Junye, can you sign your name?
Your name is what
My name is Bingbing
Thank you, Bingbing. Thank you
Ah
It's Junye. It's really Junye. He still called me by name. I'm going crazy. We haven't gone far yet.
This should be a fan of Jun Ye before
Former fans are now appearing again.
To cheat a corpse
How
You're jealous of my fans
Who hasn't got many fans yet
Brother Xiaoqiang
Can we take a picture without autographs
I-I really like you
Make it clear that you like me
We think you are very handsome.
Do you know the fast player? Are you sure you can get a good picture when you develop there?
Is it
Remember to develop the photos and ask me to sign them.
Thank you, Brother Xiaoqiang
Yes, I can
I didn't expect you to have such great charm.
How do I feel like we're surrounded by enemy troops
Night God Night God I watched the video on Weibo and especially liked you. Can you take a picture with me?
Microblog Video Xiao Rabbit
Look at Weibo
Good
Oh, my God, it's been up by 300,000 fans and over 10 million hits in the past few days.
We seem to be angry. Indeed, friends' forwarding is the most effective. It seems that it is not just classmates' forwarding.
There are also well-known bloggers who have pushed it to us.
God, I've been watching this number in high school.
Look at the comments
You see
Ah
Beard
The only grandson of the family
Even if you run away from home, you even run to be a net celebrity.
Even if you make money in this way,
He won't come back.
The merit of my whole body is this stubbornness. He learned it like a model.
I'd like to see you have what who is happy or not.
Everyone, keep order. Today is our live training show. Please don't make any noise.
Isn't it just a team? There are so many people who like it.
That's a good ball
Senior Jun Ye, you are my idol. I never thought I could train with you. There is no idol on the court.
Only opponents and teammates
Let go of the fight. Take it easy. Okay
Junye, this boy is a little interesting.
How are you, senior
Hurry up with spray and ice bags in warm summer.
It looks serious
Rabbit Rabbit
Thanks, but old wounds like this
It's no use, but simply deal with it like this.
So that it can be prevent from deteriorating
Warm summer ice bag
So many beautiful women come every day.
Hello, coach, this is the water for you. Please come to you tonight.
Good
Find a sponsor quickly. This is not a good time.
Chairman of the Board of Directors
Chairman of the Board
Junye, is this your grandfather
You must go to the hospital
I have to check it out. No, the old man may pretend to be ill. You will be caught if you go there.
What if it's true
By the way, I have a sister who is the head nurse of this hospital.
King's Night
You train well
Grandpa gave it to me
Mr. hello Jun, this is a full-time nurse in charge of physical rehabilitation.
She will be responsible for your high nerve soothing massage.
Mr. Jun, how do you do? Please take care of me
Don't rush to be cute yet
The nurse who gave me the massage, has this changed to the fifth one?
Let me click it for you first. If you don't think so, let them change it.
Just press it, just press it
Is this all right
Right here
Well, how can your massage technique be different from theirs?
Maybe it's because I've learned what a therapist does in sports medicine and rehabilitation
Okay, left, left
You said. Bai
Right, right, right
No, we have just reached 300,000 fans now.
If you take this kind of hard and wide, first, this platform has nothing to do with basketball.
Even if we do, we don't necessarily have much income.
Second, it is easy for such small companies to close down now.
What if they collect fans' money? Stop it
No, no, no
Little girl
You used to be full of energy every time you came here.
Why are you so sad today
Because
I may be lovelorn soon.
Who is so discerning
Such a beautiful girl with such a good temper is rejected by some people. The elders in my boyfriend's family don't agree with us. Why?
I don't know. Maybe it's because I'm not good enough
This is bullshit
So good-natured and so beautiful
There are also professional skills that are not good enough.
Let me tell you, you young people, you must be brave enough to stick to your own things and do it bravely. Don't listen to those old stubborn people.
Do you know
Hello
We are a well-known designer brand in China. Although we have just been established, we feel that the image and temperament of our teammates are especially in line with the live broadcast of the goods during training. We will give samples and hope to have a good reply.
In fact, this is the fastest way to make money.
However, we are adhering to the integrity of fans and have to assess the quality of products.
How can he guarantee that what he sends to us is the same as what he sends to fans?
Furthermore,
This has a great impact on the quality of our training. It's nonsense.
Do you know how I feel when I read the private letter what now, what feels, I feel that these words are like cooked ducks and all have flown away?
Brother Xiaoye
How's Grandpa
Or is it the old problem of the nerve center that can only focus on recuperation?
The doctor told him not to make him angry or
There is a risk of hemiplegia.
It's been hard for you these days.
It's okay
You know it's coming
Sorry
Grandpa, I'm late
Several bodyguards can't hold you down. I won't run again next time.
Don't worry, Grandpa, you have fans now, have you become a net sensation, and I have no choice but to do so.
For the team
You listen to me, I won't listen to you
You're just as full of that coach right now, aren't you
You called her in
I want to see her myself
Grandpa
What about the female coach
Also came
Hello, Grandpa Jun
Forget it. Forget it
I know all of you
Let me be straightforward then
Who is the female coach
Why doesn't he play according to the rules? Yes, I was a little caught off guard, too.
Far field,
Oh
Duck,
Hello, everyone, the straight men training class hosted by Qingzi will continue to teach as straight men.
Not only have to face all kinds of sharp angles,
The crisis-ridden proposition sometimes contains a huge amount of information in a casual little spit.
If you are careless, the consequences will be unimaginable. For example, when your girlfriend asks you to be with me every day,
Do you feel bored
How to answer this question is impossible
This is not scientific. How can it be
Asking this kind of question is boring in itself. I'm not aiming at anyone.
I mean, everyone in this room is rubbish. When a girlfriend asks such a question,
It shows that she is bored with your relationship and has some remorse. So at this time, the witty boy must show his respect for his girlfriend while categorically denying it.
Emotional care should never be self-righteous. The only way to talk is to take care of her feelings and apologize for not giving her enough security.
I don't know how to say it. Can you give a demonstration? First of all
We should do a good job in expression management.
Looking at her with an incomprehensible look can shake her head slightly, but with sincerity in confusion.
Why do you think so
Is it because my mind is full of games
It makes you feel too boring.
Sorry, baby
I ignored you
Well, if my girlfriend asked her if she had quarreled and ran away, would I contact her voluntarily?
How do you answer that question
It depends on whose fault it is
It must be a serial phone call. Think about how much you have to worry about your girlfriend being out alone. There is no quarrel. I will never give my girlfriend a chance to get angry.
Ding Lei, how about you
Charging beasts will never bow to girls.
Charging beast, I think the trap of this problem lies in
Why do you want to let the quarrel happen? That's right.
When you find your girlfriend angry,
Can't I give her a big red envelope? Can't I give her a big red envelope?
Why should such a good solution develop into running away from home, right?
Hmm
Ah
You sit in the morning looking at your cell phone,
While waiting for the study period,
I landed first