Give it to me
Give it to me, help me. Some people play rascal and rascal as coaches are not only owed.
This is shameless. Give it to me
Why would he help me
Why should I help her
He doesn't like me by holding me like this, does he
Su Nuan Xia
Or
Let 's tear that door down
Don't look so sad, will you? It's just a little broken lock, won't it?
When the time comes, find a hammer and give you a minute to blow it. Can't you do it?
Otherwise, this is the case
You train well. Coach Ben gave you a new lock.
Rumors that some rich kids are not very good at football have become a god.
This little beauty, are you his girlfriend? Who are you? What about what? Who is his girlfriend?
Night God is my player
It turned out to be the nearest female college coach, Coach Su, who has heard a lot
Talking to you? I'm the captain of the reserve team of Ding Lei Myth University Basketball Association.
Nicknamed the Beast of Charge
In a few days, I will lead a team to play with you. Do you dare to have an open performance match, the second team of Myth University?
All right, I'll take the game
King's Night
It's a shame for your girlfriend to follow you. I dare not accept the challenge of coming to the door in the morning. Is that so unintelligent?
You let go of Coach Su's bravery. I think you might as well be good with me.
You talk too much
Fuck off
Good
Is it okay to have a temper match? You can wash your neck and die.
I will write the venue for the competition in your school forum.
See you in three days
You must have a good training now, right? A group of substitutes are just
I can handle it all by myself
You still don't want to practice together. Don't worry about it.
I will do what I promised you
Everyone will train together.
But
After this competition
Leave me alone
You said this time, this time
Men have the first time and the second time.
The myth of Qingmeng duel can be seen.
Pay attention to the basketball confrontation is a big war, Anna. You can scan the code here and pay attention to it.
Hello students can have a look at
Sweep the Code and Pay Attention to the Public Number
Although the opponent is the reserve team,
But I have been waiting for Qingmeng to regain her strength for a long time. All the girls in our class will go to cheer up.
Something big has happened
The basketball club actually made an appointment with Myth Team 2,
Turn around, turn around, don't turn, it's not a green dreamer.
Yes, Brother Feng, I didn't expect you, Tie Hanhan, to be a milk tea drinker.
Yes, I am iron and honest
That
Can you get me in the team? That's not possible. Our company is very strict, or I'll get you a card for 10 and 2 free.
Shi what Ka, tell me about it.
Brother Feng, Brother Feng, come here, come on, come on
Please help me stop Xiao Rabbit from seeing me. I'll give you this cup of milk tea.
Wonder where the hell is it
Thanks, Brother Feng
Milk tea for you
This milk tea is really your own drink.
I don't believe it anyway
How about it? Is it still enjoyable?
Now I recognize my core position, Chu Ran
You are so much better than the last match last year. We can win last year. Are you out of the water?
Do you want to drain the water
I don't know either
Captain Chu and Coach Han asked you to come over
I heard Ding Lei say
This game was your idea. Is there a problem with what, Coach Han
This is unnecessary. I don't think so.
To be polite, the current myth team is a master who is lonely, lazy and lazy.
To put it bluntly, it is a fragmented battle.
If you want to achieve a bigger goal, you must have a training opponent. The current Qingmeng team can be a sparring partner.
Let the loose strings tighten and bring the hearts together again.
Make sense
You really have the temperament of a leader. I'm not playing house on the myth team.
What I am pursuing is the peak of basketball.
You pursue the peak of basketball and I will not hinder you.
But don't forget our agreement
Warm summer, I hope you can cherish the opportunity I have won for you.
Didn't Brother Lei go to training
How tired is it like a fur-losing dog?
How is the basketball team? Coach Han got a transfer student to be the captain.
The amount of training has increased several times.
It's like a mental derangement. Then you can still quit the team like this. I must have a big dream.
Become a player of choice
Captain Ding, hello, I am willing to give you some benefits. I hope you can put a little water in the match with Qingmeng Basketball Club.
Of course, I don't want you to put the water too obviously. Look at it.
The situation in what, ah, this is
Jun night ah, Jun night day see you so drag
I didn't expect to be able to do this again.
Let's play with him
Deal
Why is it that the warm summer event is not good? Mao Mao is impatient.
You see
Green Dream Team
We accepted the benefits. I didn't expect the Green Dream Team to be so disgusting. Oh, my God, how could our Jun Jun not beat them?
It was their coach Su Nuanxia who did it. This woman is really a good hype player.
This is our monarch night must not know
Now not only the post bar, but also the circle of friends are spreading it.
Warm summer, you spent the night studying mythology. The reserve team won't
I know, it's not you. Well, you bunny, you doubt me, don't you
I don't have plastic sister flowers. I dare not
You were the one who bribed the myth reserve
The whole green dream except you
I can't think of anyone else. Do you know this is an insult to the basketball players? I would rather lose the match.
Also don't want to take bribes to win,
I told you it wasn't me
I didn't expect a basketball match to be so exaggerated.
Su Nuan Xia We Believe
You usually only give us 18 dollars of packed lunch and 80 cents of water.
How is it possible to buy each other off
Yeah
Ling Xuan, you are really good at settling accounts.
She is the only one who has this motive. With what, I have this motive. Your family is so rich.
And the loser is you
If it were me
I will not give only this benefit.
As a college student, I have to pay back the flowers every month. Why should I bribe
Anyway, I will definitely find out this person, and then you must apologize to me in person.
Make sense
What should I do? Why are you so angry? No, I can't let him know
How did you post it online
I can send it if I want
Delete it for me as soon as possible.
I won't delete it
Be careful I sue you
You gave it to me voluntarily. I don't have any legal problems.
And
If your team is not strong, don't come out and humiliate yourself.
Do you like it here
Like
That
Shall we come here often in the future
With the people you like, no matter where you go.
I like it all very much.
Really
You laugh so obscene
It is impolite of you to shout like that.
I'm sorry, mainly because your smile is too obscene and doesn't look like you at all. That's why I'm excited. Let's not talk about those that don't exist.
Let me ask you something
Have you ever met
That kind
Unspeakable love
Normal
I used to like my cousin's girlfriend, but I couldn't say it.
That's not what I'm talking about
I'm talking about
You started from the past
I feel very disgusted with her.
But then what happened
I like it very much.
You mean Su Nuan Xia, right
Fuck off
Suddenly, a lot of whitewashing people appeared.
You stink at night and face crazy, isn't it
Ling Xuan's miser is not Shen Yingliang, unlike
Zhang Xiaoqiang and Qi Feng
Not to mention
Who the hell is it
Help
I don't believe I can't find you
The Internet address of my chat account has been found. Anna did it.
I see
Why did you stop the car? Miss Su is in front of you.
It's her
Even more so, you can't stop the car.
What a coincidence
What can I do
Didn't someone think I was the one who bribed the team before? I just came over and told him to prepare an apology.
So
You have found the real bribe, so no one has to worry about it. I just came by to inform him in advance that it would be too temporary to prepare a heartfelt apology.
Childish Zhang Xiaoqiang Drives
Here
You
In fact, Miss Su is very cute. You laugh more in front of him than before.
You've been gossiping more and more lately
Okay, I won't say it. Let's go home. Let's go home.
Warm summer
Are you all right? It's all right
I'm just a little excited
King's Night
Just wait for you to kneel down and kowtow to me and admit your mistake.
What
This classmate is not in English class now.
Excuse me, teacher
Today's students, ah, have a vast collision. All right, let's continue to study by ourselves.
We're sitting here today
Is it a little far from your night
Why are these people so boring and still leaving messages here?
Anna, the night god is here
It is better to surf the Internet less.
Did you know that at night
After all
The exam is coming soon. Okay, I, I know
Did Anna Jun care about you just now?
Yeah, the night god saw us just now
It's over
Does Junye know about what
Anna, wait for us
What's wrong with Anna today
I don't know
I said you have a really hard end. You are almost cutting the table in half.
I was too excited to see the news of Jason.
That Jason knows who replied to the post.
Not quite clear
Anna
Su Nuan
How about what
Situation in what
I don't know
This is illegal detention. I also told you that you were framing it.
I've got your Internet address. You're the one who bribed the team and the one who responded, right? I asked why you framed me. Do you know how humbled I have been these two days?
I didn't frame you. I just didn't want you to lose at night.
He had a hard time playing again.
And when I talked to them, I didn't say I was you. I didn't know they were so shameless.
I even put the chat record in the post bar, so I am also the victim.
You're crying, what. I'm supposed to be the one who's crying. Okay
If your night
Knowing that I did this
He will definitely hate me in the future.
The somebody else also didn't like you, then I can't say he will like me in the future, ok, ok, ok
Could you please
Don't tell Junye about it. If he knew, I wouldn't live.
Don't cry
This can't stand the problem of beautiful women crying. What can change it sometime.
Wipe it
My eyelashes
You just forget it. It's me
Must have made public her bribery of the team.
The school has punished her. Let's give her a chance to mend her ways.
You must have been a fairy in your last life
By the way
Didn't you still say you wanted Jun Night to apologize to you?
Yeah
My apology
Pig brains are really
The competition is coming soon.
Before, a little disturbance delayed a lot of training time.
But it doesn't matter
I'm here
I watched the video of the Myth II team and came up with a tactic against them.
Next, let's rehearse it.
It is better to break in our team.
If you don't fight, it's over.
He also engaged in what tactics.
I am not desperate or angry.
Not angry, not angry, not angry
Not very strong today
Why did he come all of a sudden
Didn't he bring his own water
You don't want to ask me if I have found anyone who bribed me, do you
Didn't you come to carry water
Thank you, coach
Thank you
Here comes the meal
Today, I eat what. Today is the Kung Pao Chicken Set Meal.
This one is full of warm summer. Thank you for giving me one.
Don't you usually eat this eight-dollar packed lunch at night,
I suddenly want to eat today.
I suddenly have no appetite. Give them food.
I can't believe the coach didn't protect his food today, right
Boss, take one
Then give me two eggs
And this tenderloin sausage will also add more spicy to me.
Haole
How much is it
Ten dollars
What's the matter with this monarch night
Hanging around in front of me all day long.
I couldn't even eat
Boss, hurry up, starve to death, now, now
Thank you
How can you come here to eat this kind of food
Can't you let me have a good taste
Hello
Why isn't someone trying to make me apologize
I'm waiting
No
Why not
I haven't found anyone, have I
If you have to apologize, I can also reluctantly accept it.
Su Nuan Xia
Are you stupid? You're stupid
I'm sorry
What are you talking about
I'm so excited to go to the scene today to see the night god.
I heard that the youth dream team
This time I spent money on our water release.
I think the standard must be very poor. Let's watch the show today. Go, go, go, go
We have seen a lot of videos of our opponents in the past two days.
I specially edited the fragments of Ding Lei to show you so clearly.
Ding Lei
Although he is a reserve member of the myth team,
I have met him several times.
Although this boy plays arrogant, he is also a mythical gold. The sixth man has a lot of chances to come on as a substitute.
Nicknamed the Beast of Charge
It means that when he plays, he is very wild. Most of the players who fight him will be injured.
Then I'll give it a try. Is he fierce or am I fierce?
Ling Xuan, you are just too reckless. You play forward in the same position as Ding Lei, but his reaction is faster and more stable than yours, so you don't need to confront him.
People like you who have no brains and only know how to rush blindly should do your pick and roll honestly and watch me play.
Who do you say has no brain Ling Xuan's team is harmonious, or do you believe it or not when I order 100 cups of milk tea after the competition?
Brother
All you have to do is score three points
I will only give you a transfer.
Zhang Xiaoqiang
The team pays attention to team spirit.
Don't bring your buddy's loyalty to the team.
Got it
Tie Han Han, I saw Anna coming just now
Let her rest assured, no, no
Don't worry, everyone
Rebounding, the warm summer I have grasped to death, you can rest assured that we will definitely beat the mythical garbage reserve team today.
Goddess, which school do you belong to? Why have we never met before?
You deserve to talk to our sister Anna. Get out of the way.
Are the banners ready? They are already ready, little sister. We don't need you to come. We do it. We do it
Hang up, classmate. Excuse me
Brothers
This game is the time for our reserve team to prove their strength.
The Green Dream Team also doesn't know what to think.
This team has only been formed for a week and dares to come here to play away games.
So
I decided to keep their goals in single digits. How many points do we have to score?
At least three times as many as theirs
Coach, good coach, good coach, good everyone's hard work, coach, why did you come in person?
With our strength to deal with this kind of team that has not even passed the break-in period, in fact, you don't have to worry at all if you lose this match.
Then you can go straight to the palace.
Is it true what coach Chu Ran said just now
You've known Captain Churan for a while
Have you ever seen him tell lies
Shen Xuechang is experienced, but he is too busy at ordinary times, which makes him not decisive enough to play the ball now, so he must take advantage of the time when no one is defending.
Pull down the open position and throw three points.
Zhang Xiaoqiang, you are so unreliable at ordinary times. This match is very important, so please attack against it. All right, coach
Don't worry
I have no characteristics, but I am reliable at critical moments.
Tell me what to do
Your goal is very simple is to use Qi Feng's height to pull out the gap.
Then he passed the ball to Shen Xuechang, a foreign media player. This is today's main tactic.
The feel of the three-point shot needs high-intensity training to be maintained all the time.
I am really holding everyone back now.
It doesn't matter. We still have the night god.
Night God
With your usual training performance, you can pass the ball and block the difference.
I don't expect you to get what points.
I hope everyone will not be influenced by this kind of amateur guidance.
Come on in a minute and listen to me
This is not the time to play with personality.
The majesty of the coach's decision
Cooperate
Cooperate with you
You beg me, I
Here we go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Why
I have no idea where to put you now.
I don't know where to put the player.
It was your failure as a coach.
It has nothing to do with me
Night God is so handsome. What should I do
Half an hour late, I wouldn't have washed my hair if I had known it.
He won't be angry, will he
Have you waited a long time? I just arrived. Not long ago
Thanks. It's still hot
Matcha with a little sugar and cream. How do you know this is my favorite flavor
I was guessing
What happened to you today
I drew the eyeliner and then wiped it off and drew it again. Have you waited for a long time again?
Delicious
It's still hot
It's so cute. I like matcha tea milk tea best.
You wait a long time every time
Don't mention it
I am strong and strong.
It's good to blow the wind. If you don't drink it, it will get cold.
I like the taste is also specially inquired about by you
I feel so sorry
How about you make it up to me
As long as you remember my preferences,
I prefer American tea without sugar rather than milk tea.
And
My favorite girl is Su Nuanxia
So no matter how late she is,
I would like to wait for her