Eat noodles
Yes, you
It's even better than the one in the advertisement.
Selling photos is only the foundation. The most important thing is to eat it.
Come and try it
Am I getting up too early
Why don't I do it again
I lied to you
Very delicious
Really
If you don't believe me, try it.
How is it
Is it okay
All right, if you're so reluctant, I'll take the rest of it. I'm not polite to you.
This is definitely the best noodle I have ever eaten.
I didn't think I could have such a high-level treatment and exaggerated treatment on this blackout night before the examination.
Actually
I'm rewarding
Hard to review
Girls
Hmm
How about what? I'm your coach
Not now
Then it's you, what
Not bad, not bad
Seeing you studying so hard,
We're relieved. What, whoa, whoa, whoa
Are you here to review, too
Why don't we all sprint together
How about that whole team pas through tomorrow
You think too much
My brother's bedroom has a good Internet speed. I'm here to play games.
There is no electricity outside. I came to see the inspirational book.
How Chases School Flower
You don't say they both
Learning is quite good, right? Small exams, small games, big exams, big games,
You think it's all like you
Temporary embrace of Buddhism
I don't like to play as much as they do.
Ling Xuan
Or are you reliable or
Let's review together. I came here purely to recharge my batteries.
If my cell phone runs out of power, I won't be able to take the order tomorrow.
How did you do in that exam
Even though the last two statements have not been finished,
How did you know I had to hand in my papers in advance
Let's sneak out on a date
Hmm
I said, you came to me every day these days to inquire about Ling Xuan and finished all the work for him.
What is the blessing of this poor boy? He is so determined to meet such a good girl as you.
Boss, for the sake of coming to work as soon as I finished my exam,
You're pathetic
All right, let me tell you something
In fact, Ling Xuan is very poor.
His father loves gambling and owes a lot of debts, and then he just ran away.
So Ling Hyun, he works hard every day.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Don't worry, I'll take another 50 cups of milk tea with me later.
Girl, you want what flavor
Zhang Xiaoqiang, come and help
Here we go
Rabbit Rabbit
Did Ling Xuan send all these milk teas? Yes, yes, he recently had a big personality explosion. He felt that he was too stingy before, but he was embarrassed to tell you, so he ordered these milk teas for you.
It's a pity that Anna is not here. Otherwise, I can give her a drink. I'll leave you a drink. Ling Xuan is a good person.
But it's kind of handout
Yeah
In fact, he still values our team's value.
I think he still values making money. Don't say that.
Ling Xuan must have some difficulties.
You know something I don't know, do you
Ling Xuan takes advantage of coach to fall in love with
Absent training
He also sneaked out to work and now bribed us with these milk tea.
Do you know what
If it weren't for the difficulties in his family, he would certainly have
Home What's wrong with his home
His father
Xiao Tu Rabbit
Speak of the evil and the evil comes
Thanks
You come with me
Hey, you hurt me. The milk tea you bought
Don't be too loud. I told them you sent it. You went to the cafe to help me work.
I used to go to the cafe
I see you haven't been in training lately. What about my dad
Don't blame the wife of shop-owner
I had to ask her
Xiao Tu Rabbit
You listen to me
I don't need you to pity me. I don't need you to work for me in the store. I don't need you to go to the team.
Send me milk tea and pretend to be a good man. My Ling Xuan has nothing to do with you.
Would you mind your own business
Ling Xuan
You love rat who will repay kindness with revenge.
I am really out of my mind to help you.
In combination with your recent training results, you can actually strengthen your 3-pointer.
How come it's just the three of you, Ling Xuan
Here we go
Then he left again.
By the way, I had a quarrel with Rabbit
The match will be held tomorrow. What kind of trouble is he making? He won't have to abstain from training for so long. How can he say what?
We have to believe Ling Xuan's character. Do you think he is that kind of person after getting along for so long?
I feel like
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Why don't you understand me? Come on, come on, let's train quickly. Come on, come on, come on, come on
Bunny may be meddling
But somebody else a girl
At least know how to fight for what you want.
Ling Xuan
It was warm summer when I took a fancy to you.
Insisting on keeping you on the team
I hope you don't let her down
And don't let us down
Brother, do you think we can win tomorrow's match?
What about what
Thinking about warm summer
It's not too late to get a coach after the match.
Warm her up
Really like Coach Sue
Yeah, sometimes I think this is Coach Zuri in front of me
I sometimes wonder
If Coach Zuri is still here
Seeing the warm summer now,
I don't know if I will be very happy.
I forgot to ask you
Did this wave of one-on-one tutoring by Xueba speed you up to win?
Xiao Qiang
You said if you were dating a girl
Should I choose what?
Oh, my God
I put up with all my hardships and you are finally beginning to understand.
Let Xiao Ye teach Zhang Xiaoqiang's exclusive love secrets and wait a minute.
What you have to say next better be practical and effective, otherwise I can't let you out of tomorrow's dormitory door.
Brother
Why don't we go home early? There's a game tomorrow
Can't sleep the night before the match the next day,
Not at all
The key is to see if you have quarreled with your favorite take-out brother.
Go, go, go
I'm serious, okay?
If you really can't sleep, I'll buy you milk tea.
Super refreshing
Come on
Everyone has been fighting together for so long.
Tomorrow's game will be over my head
If you want to say wish, I only have one
What
Is your take-out brother will be there for me on time tomorrow.
It's so exciting and you can watch the night god show again.
Last time I won the Myth Night God, but my thighs drove the whole stadium. Did you get excited? What was the last time I won was the reserve team. Today I am the main force of Myth to pay a return visit. Do they have a strong main force? Do you think the name of Myth is fake?
All right
The mythological team members are so handsome. Isn't this the legendary cosmic sky group?
Don't pull me. I have to transfer to another school.
It's almost time. Why hasn't Ling Xuan come yet?
This guy has been saying good things for him because of me.
It's like a wolf's heart and dog's lung.
Warm summer
I joined the basketball club
In fact, it is not because I like it.
You already knew that
I have many more important things than it.
So
I still have to balance the work and the team.
I, Ling Xuan, will definitely not be the one to disappoint you.
Thanks to the cheerleaders
Excellent performance. Next, please enter the stadium from both sides.
I told you
Today will win back the lost points, so come on
Gu Yuan, right
I will let you remember me
This time I won't lose to you. You said the same thing last time.
Isn't this King's Night
I didn't think of it
Back to the Green Dream Team,
Guys, let's have a barbecue after the match.
Anyway, we also know their ability to ride motorcycles.
Think of it as a warm-up, just before meals to digest
A talkative person
Usually very delicious
Don't try to pass from me
It depends on your skill
That's it again
This way, this way
Zhang Xiaoqiang
It's too fast, isn't it
I can't keep up with my eyes
This is the regular rhythm of myth
I didn't expect them to be so strong. Fortunately, we have two months of training.
Everyone's cooperation is already very tacit understanding,
And there is also senior Lu Ye.
Help us target training
Otherwise, this match cannot be imagined.
Why is there no sound from everyone?
This, this job
Just like you, I haven't reacted yet.
Don't worry
Just one goal
There must be an outbreak.
When I don't exist? It's not time to touch it.
Myth Team
2 to 0
The mythology team is very good. Who is the boy whose team just scored? I like the center uncle
Are you an anthomaniac
Cheer the myth. Which department do you belong to
Tell you not to let me see you again
Qi Feng
Defence
Passing King's Night
Point guards can't hold the ball. How did they get into the team?
Phantom pass, right
Teach me
Aren't you afraid to hurt your self-esteem
If you're not sure
Just pass the ball to me and I'll take care of it.
Chu Ran hasn't even played yet. Myth has already become so strong.
You said
Will he play as soon as we lead?
We'll have to wait until we get ahead
Mm-hmm-hmm
Hmm
Don't you guys want to join the basketball club? Shout.
Jin Meng Basketball Shines Milky Way, A Photo of Jin Meng Basketball,
Some of them are of good physical quality. When the number of injured poor people is not enough, they can also be cannon fodder what.
Look at what. Look
You think we're from what
I will want your take-out red envelopes.
Green Dream Green Dream Youth High-spirited Dream Nine Days
Night God
So gentle
Is there hope for a warm summer
Don't be so serious, will you? You're not like you, you're not like you, you're not like you, you're not like
Three-point shot
That's not how you cast it
Don't worry, there is still hope for recovery.
I'm not in a hurry. I'm fighting with myself
Han Mo
You still value it. It's a coincidence to lead the team yourself.
The beautiful headmaster is also interested in basketball.
I didn't lead the team myself.
I am checking the training results of the new captain. Good, headmaster.
It turned out to be Captain Chu Ran
Captain Chu Ran thinks who will win, Qingmeng or Myth
Today Qingmeng's performance is already very good.
It can be seen that they have done systematic training for every mythical player.
Can make such great progress in two months,
It's too rare
Chu Ran
Don't be embarrassed to say
You are now a member of the myth. Principal Ning will not criticize you.
Isn't it
Coach Han
You mean Qingmeng will fail
I didn't say that
Principal
You see, Ling Xuan will go to the top as soon as he is provoked.
This is clearly a sign of inexperience
Myth leads by at least 15 points in the next five minutes.
You're better than what
You are better than what
Xiao Qiang
Anna, thank you today. I don't want you to thank you.
I know you are good in warm summer, but will you die if you are better at the ball?
Do you know the difference between animals and human beings is what? Do you know how to write the word quality? Please go back to the stove and rebuild it.
Angry at what, the competition is not over yet.
Did you see for yourselves the problems in the first half
There is no fit at all.
The teams that have been playing all the time do not even have the basic cooperation.
Does it make sense? It's not that we don't cooperate.
Ling Xuan
Come here for a moment
These take-out cards, membership cards, scorecards
It's all done by bunny bunny in your shop.
Rabbit Rabbit said
Where is it like what Ling Xuan should do to work everywhere?
He should concentrate on doing what he likes to make himself happy.
You may not like playing basketball that much
But she must like you very much
Come on, all of them have the second half started.
Come on, continue in the second half
Get up and play
What's the matter with Jun Night? Do you want to cheer me up alone?
Just because you are not in good condition,
Are you OK
I'm fine
That's good
Although I really want to win
But if there's anything wrong with you, just tell me
Rest assured
Why don't you give me some air
Green Dream Green Dream High-spirited Youth
Did you just say I can't shoot 3-pointers well?
Yes, the elder is about to graduate, so he should find a good job.
Is there no dignity on the internship field, so I ran to the field to find a sense of presence,
If only your football skills were as good as your eloquence.
And
I was just about to enter a new battlefield when I was looked down upon by others. It seems that I can't do without fighting for breath.
Let me teach you
What is the genuine super-far god three points
Mingming, why didn't we touch the two of us when we took off together?
Wait a minute
Why can't Xia Ze prevent Shen Xuechang
You see, Shen Xuechang's knee bending range is very large. The larger the knee bending range, the longer the strength will be stored.
And the longer the high point of the ball and the longer the stagnation time,
Na Xia Ze
Isn't it also very good
Although Xia Ze saw
But when he jumped up to block, Shen Xuechang could choose the height.
And the timing of the shot made him unable to defend himself so much.
You see, Mr. Shen is quite handsome when he takes it seriously.
But I'm worried about his physical problems, but
At least he has no solution now.
What do you mean
Before the senior, he didn't throw three points at God.
It was because I was worried that my physical strength would not be satisfied with the
Ling Xuan
According to this momentum, there seems to be still suspense, Coach Han.
Why don't you call a pause and set it up
Of course, young people's competitions are conducted by young people themselves.
What do you say, Churan
Shen Xuechang, hold on
Time is running out
Are you all right
It takes a great deal of physical strength at the expense of
Even Shen Xuechang, who is at his peak,
It can only last for ten minutes.
He has held on for 15 minutes today, so you didn't shoot in the first half.
Is it in the energy storage tank? Sorry
My energy tank is gone
No, no, no, I can't even stand up now.
But now there is one less person
There's no substitute
How do I play
I'll do it
Is there any other way
Su Nuanxia went on stage, which is really a heroine and such things.
It's a long time to see you
Come on, the female coach has to go on her own.
The competition has reached this point, and there can be no more.
We won't be merciful just because it's a woman. This little girl really looks like Coach Zuri.
Congratulations, Principal Ning
Qingmeng University really has an excellent basketball team.
That's awesome
That's where we got there
Bunny, do you have a towel there? Lend me a wipe of sweat
No
Look at what's matching outfit. Please help me see which of these sets suits me.
You don't have a boyfriend to wear matching outfits with. Of course, it's me and Ling Xuan.
You and Ling Xuan wear matching clothes.
Is it too early for you to understand
Ling Xuan, this miser, wears a dress for three years.
If you tell him this is a regimental suit, he will be happy to accept it.
Then everyone will think we are lovers.
It won't become a real couple either. Always make opportunities for yourself. This is called hint.
So good
Thanks
That's wonderful
Thank you. Is someone in love
Who are you still pretending to be on our team?
When I saw it, I quickly said, "Don't be a suspense. Your towel and Night God's towel are lovers' money."
Didn't you even notice
Nice towel. Thank you
You're welcome
Did you buy it on purpose
No
Towel