Thank you for your hospitality
You are the most edible I have ever seen.
In the future, we will often come to eat. Sorry, I will not entertain you. You have been blacklisted by our store because you eat too much. You will not be sent.
Then don't do marketing with me. Come out
I'm going to photograph their store and send it to my friends to tell them not to come.
What if it rains so hard
What are you doing
The manager gave it to you
He said there were no umbrellas
You go in and borrow your umbrella and phone.
I told Jason Chung
I'm going to buy this place
Change into a public toilet
No
Is that exaggerating? Let me explain to someone
Jason Chung said
The area of this place is too large
Can't change
You want to change what
Fortunately, it can't be changed. No, no, no, no, no
I'm teasing you
Just your skin
No, we have to figure out how to get there
Think it over
Are you ready
You, you
Her Majesty
Why are you looking at me all the time
I'm proud of you
Where are you going? You haven't signed up yet.
I can't even beat a girl
Also join the what basketball team so as not to drag your feet. When you were three years old, you started to contact basketball. Ordinary people can't beat her. It's not uncommon for you to lose to her.
With your physical quality
Good training can definitely become Hanato Sakuragi. I just want to be Jack Ma.
Not interested in becoming Hanamichi Sakuragi Goodbye
People like you who have no brains and only know how to rush blindly.
It's better to do your pick-and-roll honestly and watch me play. Who do you say has no brain and team harmony?
Do you believe it or not when I order 100 cups of milk tea after the competition
Considering that Ling Xuan's foot injury has not fully recovered, our training will not be so intense for me.
Come on, come on
Now you can take the initiative to increase training.
That's because of you
I want to be a hero in your life
You have always been
Hmm
Not enough
Wait a minute, you continue
I'll watch you practice here, okay
Come on, go back to rest early. You were on the sidelines.
I'm not focused
Then I'll catch Qi Feng and Zhang Xiaoqiang to accompany you.
Why
What are you doing
I remember there was a hotel over there.
We can get a room first
Have a change
Don't catch a cold
Open a room
Go
Wait a minute
This way, this way
Brother Qiang, I was knocked down again.
Can you help you five times in one round?
This way, this way
After drinking, go back to training quickly. Now Ling Xuan is more diligent than you. Yes, or is your Ling Xuan brilliant?
Don't come to herd sheep with us.
Sister Rabbit teaches well. Drink quickly. Drink quickly. Ling Xuan is very lonely to practice alone now.
Rabbit, don't sprinkle dog food any more, will you
There is really no way to use the team's public account card.
Just explain it to the rabbit later.
There is only 1,999 yuan left for the honeymoon suite.
Is that all right
Let's do this first
Don't catch a cold
Hmm
Let's practice again.
I want to play in this year's match.
The strength of Qingmeng is indeed stronger than that of each other.
Only when you play can you ensure victory.
Especially their monarch night
He is also a player with special character.
Coach Han
Come to the point
I mean, you came from Qingmeng
You have a better understanding of their internal situation.
Do you think there is a possibility
Put a little more psychological pressure on them
I have no objection to psychological warfare
But the breakthrough is not necessarily Junye
You go first, you go first
Have caught a cold
What are you doing
Japanese Roast Rotary Sushi
Mu Si cake
Why are you looking at this
Me
If you want to eat some snacks, you can't. How can athletes eat these casually?
The competition is coming soon.
You see, your biceps are not firm at all.
Get up and train quickly
Here
Training is right. Otherwise
You have to change your clothes quickly.
Let's do a set of push-ups first.
I'll find some equipment. You give it to me. Be good. Don't be lazy.
Bunny Bunny Help King wants to open a room with me at night.
The address is sent to you. Come on
Let your girlfriend be your coach.
Probably this kind of experience
Despicable and shameless
What did you say you did to our warm summer
My brother is also a victim. Well, I also want to ask how your warm summer has done to my brother.
Night God
Teach me the secret of love. I want to go to a canteen. Anna won't go with me.
Don't blame the senior for being too busy, ah, have you taken any safety measures?
Hmm
It's a good match
Let's join you
Coach, I don't have to
I'll count it for you
You are strong enough but not flexible enough.
Xiao Rabbit, hurry
Had I known I wouldn't have come to save you
Well, in order to encourage everyone, I will join you all in the national movement.
Refueling
I think
I can have another group
Get up and train for me
Shen Xuechang, get up
Zhang Xiaoqiang
It's time for dinner
Otherwise, I will not be energetic today.
Normal period
Why didn't you say so earlier
You shouldn't have practiced with us
I don't have that kind of food
Let's go. I'll take you back to the dormitory. No, I have to train this afternoon.
Let's go and want ice cream.
After eating, I will be resurrected with blood.
I was joking
He really ignored me
Why haven't you come back yet, cheapskate
What for
Get out of the way
Don't give me too much, Junye. Don't make a fuss about it. It's training.
Training
Me
Is it delicious
Have another bite
It's disgusting. You swallow it
Give me another bite
It's my favorite taste. It's hard to buy.
No wonder you've been there for so long, and you're still angry
If I had known, I wouldn't have bought it for you.
Buy any of them when you run so far.
Today's warm summer is not feeling well.
This afternoon's training should be cancelled. You have no discussion who will allow you.
Hello
I'll fight you one-on-one at night.
No time
If I win, it proves that I am no worse than LaCrosse.
I need to adjust my tactics.
I can't do it if I'm the core.
The war is imminent, even if it needs to be changed.
We have to wait for the end of the match. We have been cooperating for so long. It's not a half-set of tactics. Maybe it's better to change it.
More powerful
Don't be funny. Three-year-olds don't do that
You have been menopausal recently. You are so angry.
You can't play a joke. Don't make any noise,
Everyone is one of their own quarrelling with what. There is no need for everyone to compare internally. They are all the same. They just perform their respective duties.
Is it really as good as before? No time for nonsense. One-on-one fight can change tactics. No
Another day
Didn't you take me back to the dormitory? Do you think I will believe that you will have a good rest when you go back to the dormitory?
I also want to go back and deepen my tactics.
What happened to you this morning was my negligence
But now the training is over
Under my control
Is it hard
Brown sugar and ginger water
Can I, can I, can't stand it? I'm going to suffer from heatstroke.
I'm telling you, there's really no what on your period.
Believe me, I'm going to perform a sit-up for you now. Look
No, you must keep warm at such times.
First, you can't drink cold water.
Second, you can't do strenuous exercise.
Otherwise, it will leave the root of the disease behind.
Who told you
Internet
Not everyone is like that. Like me, I may just eat less.
And every time I especially want to drink my mother's motherwort soup.
How do I learn
It's over. I almost forgot
My mother is coming to bring me soup tomorrow.
That's good
It's not that she didn't know we were in love and then
She said she would come and meet you
That
It's good
We can have dinner together. Dinner should not be available.
She came to see me at the airport on a business trip with her colleague.
What time should the plane be free for two or three hours in the afternoon
Isn't it
It's a little too sudden. Then I'll help you later.
No need to refuse. No problem
Really? Are you sure you're okay
Then let me take you back to the dormitory first.
I have another business matter to deal with later.
Go ahead
You can't even patronize our little shit at night.
It's about what
Explain it first
I came to see you
Never let warm summer know
That's right
Today's performance of aiming at Ka is not particularly good.
Consultation fee
As half of your fans, I can't wait to help you. Then tell me what you think, Li Tao. You can't overturn if you win.
Li Tao, I don't ask Li Tao to discuss rationally. You will win. Remember, don't KY, press the camera, press the camera, plus my assists. There is absolutely no problem.
When speaking Chinese, I always forget that you are not in the pink circle.
If you should be quiet, just be quiet and don't say anything wrong.
But in just three hours
I have to make the best impression. No problem
Isn't the shopping mall near the school under your name? Take your aunt there. No woman doesn't like shopping, but she can also show the strength of your family in an advanced way.
You see, your conditions are so good in all aspects. Don't worry, aunt is absolutely satisfied with you.
By the way, that
I should wear what's clothes. It's not easy. Just look simple, generous, low-key and stable.
How about that? Is everything goe well
It went well
You can do it tomorrow.-Oh, take it easy
In my dictionary
There is no word nervous.
I believe you, Mua Da
Pompous
Immature
Look, it makes you nervous.
See the future mother-in-law monarch night is no different from ordinary people
Your move really worked
How come she didn't buy it in what herself
I only chose a skirt for warm summer.
It is that the shopping mall is not big enough.
Or is the brand I introduced not good enough?
The shopping mall is very large, and the brands are complete and upscale.
But
I want to tell you a truth
Say
Don't guess what a woman's mind is
Is it because his mother is not satisfied with me, and if she is not satisfied with you, she will not be satisfied.
Don't worry
You are an open monarch. You must be stable at night.
It did commit suicide. As a strong bank card, it has never met such a strong opponent and been treated so cruelly.
It has lost face to the world. Rest in peace, little Kaka.
Get up
Naked abuse
Sure enough
There is no better way to know a woman than a mother.
I must strictly follow my aunt's instructions.
It's Ms. Xia's style,
You continue
Daughter
Do you think you are rubbish
Since it's not why you have to pack yourself in garbage bags every day, aunt, this poison tongue ability is simply amazing.
Admire
You tortured me for most of the day
Now you can tell me
Why? Auntie, tell me
After meeting you night, she found that her military ability was very strong.
Steady, reliable and patient, it is simply not better.
This is a good thing, but aunt is afraid that you are not worthy of being alone and dying.
He also said that it was too much for you before,
I have neglected my discipline of you.
I don't know if it's too late to make up for it, and my aunt and I are both afraid what if some coquettish bitches run out of what and rob you night.
It's not as serious as you think. Girls should be self-reliant so that they can live a wonderful life.
Also, I like Junye because I like his inner part. I believe he should think so too.
Let's go in warm summer
Afraid of being filmed again, of course I have to report to Aunt Xia.
I also want to tell her what you two think of each other.
I think you can now lead the most lovely warm summer in the world.
Auntie said
Remember to be gentle with other boys and don't bully others.
What's the matter with Ms. Xia? I am still not her own daughter.
Why not toward him or me? Did Aunt Xia say what
Is there any place in what where I can help? No, no, my task is completed. Go and play.
I will not follow you and shine. Bye
Aunt Xia bought you this little skirt
It's beautiful.
Dressed so beautifully today
Where do you want to play
Don't waste it
Do you also think
I was not good enough like that before.
How could it be
Actually
I've always wanted to give you something
In the future, I want you to wear my uniform when I play games.
No problem
You just asked me
Do you think you're not good enough
Then I want to tell you now
I don't need you to make any changes
I want you to be yourself, really
Can you find a girlfriend like a man's wife? How can you be like a man's wife?
You are cheerful
Straightforward, naive and warm
I'm also worried that I'm not romantic enough.
Not considerate enough
Not worthy of you
Are you stupid? How can you be worthy or not? Only love or not
How much do you love me
Not too much, is it
But
It will take 100 years to consume energy.
If I and your mother fall into the water at the same time, who do you save first, save my mother first, and then I will save you
I can't imagine that the senior Chu Ran, whom I have always liked, is a mother treasure man.
You can say whatever you want. This cosmic problem is wrong anyway.
Then I will change to a meaningful question.
Which is more important, me or basketball
Fortunately, I was already prepared.
To answer such questions, uh, we must have a clear-cut stand.
Of course it's you
He answered without even thinking about it. What if you have to choose one?
After all, the dimensions are different, one is sports and the other is emotion.
It should be said that you are as important as basketball. I can't imagine that my weight in your heart is just a 600-gram ball. I also said that what's love, marriage, graduation, house purchase and what's
Think about it and think it's frivolous. Let's break up.
Sister
Give me a break. I'll do whatever you want. All right
Good
Then let me ask you
Is Su warm in summer good-looking or am I good-looking? I am ready to answer this question.
It must be firmly stated that it was you who answered without even thinking about it. It must be perfunctory to me. I want to go to Qingmeng to see what she looks like.
I don't object to her. Her eyes are big.
The temperament is a little similar to yours. You actually compare your current girlfriend with your ex-girlfriend. There is no me in your heart. She is not my ex-girlfriend. Then you are what's relationship. Qingzi, don't worry.
I'll explain it to you slowly
Yes
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'll clean it up for you right away
If I do it with her
Who will you help
I'll pull you away
Can't you stand up for me, rival what's price
I can't believe you are so cool and snobbish.
Do waiters deserve to be looked down upon
I advise you to eat inside and pick outside, then I will help you beat her savagely.
If we both don't calm down, what if something happens afterwards
I called the manager
Can't you do something for yourself? I'll hold her and let you hit her. You like to touch other girls so much. I'll hold you.
Instead of being beaten and hugged by you,
Come on. What's the use of me asking you
You know to hold me at such a critical moment, Chu Ran, are you still a man?