=Ancient Love Poetry=
=Episode 30=
Come on.
As long as I want to live,
even Heaven can’t take my life.
Who says no one can survive
challenging Heaven?
I will prove to the Three Realms
that I will win.
Qingmu is Bai Jue?
It’s impossible.
Is he going to...?
He’s drawing power from thunder
to rebuild spiritual veins.
So daring!
Is Qingmu taking God’s tribulation?
Is he going to
be the fifth God of the Three Realms?
He already took
49 thunder strikes before.
That was the tribulation for a God.
Now he’s taking another 32.
In all, it’s...
Eighty-one.
Who else except a True God
can trigger eighty-one thunder strikes?
Huan,
is he truly Bai...?
Demon power!
He possesses demon power!
The prime of Demigod.
We finally got a Demigod for so long.
Were his core
and spiritual veins intact,
North Sea Lord would have
become the prime of God.
He’s fortunate to have such experience.
It won’t be long until he becomes
the fifth God of the Heavenly Realm.
Houchi.
Jingzhao.
Greetings, God Gu Jun.
Gu Jun?
Wu Huan,
if you hurt Houchi again,
I’ll tear your Heavenly Palace down.
Houchi.
Muguang,
you’re the God of Heaven.
You promised me
to keep Houchi safe.
However, Wu Huan
intended to hurt her under your nose.
Are you still a man of your word?
Gu Jun...
Ridiculous!
She is a fake,
who has no dragon core in her body.
As a senior to her,
couldn’t I ask about it?
Wouldn’t I
recognize my own daughter?
She was fragile when she was little.
Her core was broken.
So I drew her core out
and had been reinforcing it
with my blood.
As her mother,
you never cared about her.
You’re also a fake.
So, forget it.
Gu Jun,
what do you mean?
you implied publicly
that I took her
as my daughter back then.
I didn’t refuse
for the sake of our past.
Now you regret it?
Yes.
I do regret it.
What can you do?
Today,
I’ll explain everything.
Wu Huan didn’t
give birth to my daughter, Houchi.
Sixty thousand years ago,
to make sure my daughter
has a rightful place
in the Three Realms,
I chose Wu Huan.
However,
that was a mistake
which has led to such misunderstanding.
So now,
I’d like to make it clear.
Wu Huan is not Houchi’s mother.
Gu Jun,
whether I am or not her mother,
it’s all but your word.
How dare you insult me so!
My daring is not limited to this.
For what you did today,
I would have killed you a hundred times.
Yet I chose to spare you for the sake
of the love we used to share.
You should reflect on yourself.
- You...!
- Gu Jun,
you’re a God.
Mind your tongue.
Sweetie,
I’m impressed.
You almost tore
the Heavenly Palace down.
Don’t be afraid.
Father is here.
We’ll talk when we’re back home.
Wait!
You people from the Qingchi Palace
can leave.
But Qingmu has to stay.
Wu Huan,
he doesn’t want to marry your daughter.
Why do you have to kill him for that?
Because he possesses demon power.
I must take his life today.
You’re just abusing your authority.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I’m doing this
for the sake of all immortals.
This young man
survived the Heavenly Thunder.
If he were a demon,
he’d have returned to his original form,
and you wouldn’t have the chance
to accuse him.
But he does possess demon power.
Right.
A small amount.
So what?
He withstood the torch of
Three-head Fire Dragon’s breath.
It’s normal he possesses demon power.
How could you declare
him a demon for that?
By the way, I heard
this young man
saved your son days ago
from the Three-head Fire Dragon.
Is that how you immortals
from the Heavenly Palace
extend gratitude?
How shameless
and virtueless!
Gu Jun, you’re wrong.
Qingmu did save Jingyang,
which is a great favor to us.
But it’s a matter that’s concerned about
immortals and demons.
His identity is suspicious.
It’s nothing wrong to question him.
Muguang, don’t forget
that when the God Realm existed,
immortals and demons were families,
not foes.
That’s right.
God Gu Jun made a good point.
Alright,
let’s put an end to it.
The doubt is yet to be settled.
We can’t jump to conclusions.
Your Majesty,
we can’t let them go
before everything is clear.
God Gu Jun.
You don’t have to be so polite.
I, Qingmu,
would like to give my life
to Houchi and marry her.
Please give us your permission.
Young man,
why do you think
I would agree on this marriage?
Just because you survived
the thunder strikes?
My love for Houchi is as true as
the sun and the moon.
I’d like to swear in the name of Heaven
that as long as I am alive,
whoever in the Three Realms,
be it Gods
or demons,
I’ll kill them if they dare to hurt her.
If I fail,
let my heart rot and my soul vanish.
Nice try.
I’ll be in the Qingchi Palace
for the next tens of thousands of years.
If any of you run into trouble,
feel free to come to Qilian Mountains
for tea.
As for marrying my daughter,
no way!
Qingmu,
God Gu Jun is always like that.
You saw his attitude to them.
He’s already very nice to you.
Besides,
Houchi is the apple of his eye.
Your proposal was too casual.
How about this?
Give him a few more days.
Jingzhao,
as you could see,
Qingmu loves Houchi more than his life.
Stop tormenting yourself.
Listen to me.
Forget him.
I sacrificed
my spiritual root for him.
In the end,
it’s all in vain.
That’s love.
Though I had given everything for it,
I still couldn’t get it.
Jingjian,
I’m tired.
Jingzhao.
It seems I
underestimated that flood dragon.
Master,
now you’re regarded as
the God of Destruction.
Gu Jun is totally loyal to Her Grace.
I’m afraid it’s not easy for you
to take her away.
Shanggu’s future
is not in anyone else’s hand.
Wu Huan, you dared to hurt Houchi.
I guess being in power for too long
makes you forget who you were.
He’s Tianqi, the Demon God!
- Demon God?
- Your Majesty.
Hasn’t the Demon God
been killed by True God Bai Jue?
I have eternal life as Heaven does.
No one can kill me.
Muguang, it’s been sixty thousand years.
You’ve become such a foolish emperor.
The demons never offended you immortals.
Yet you sent your two sons
to the Abyssal Ridge Swamp
and stop Three-Head Fire Dragon
from ascending.
So,
the God of immortals cannot
serve your greed
and you covet the Three Realms?
Demon God,
His Majesty was chosen by Master Zhiyang
as the God of the Three Realms.
Without the demons’ rebellion,
the Three Realms would’ve been in peace.
Don’t give a false account here!
You’re but a humble phoenix.
How dare you offend me!
You...!
Demon God, what’s the purpose
of your presence?
I have returned.
You immortals will pay the price.
I have no interest
in your bit of territory,
but if you encroach on any of mine,
I’ll make sure you all
be crushed
like the Green Dragon Platform.
Is he really Demon God Tianqi, Father?
Demon God has returned.
The Three Realms are in danger.
Jingyang,
ring the Green Dragon Bell.
Summon the immortal lords
to discuss a solution.
Yes, Father.
It’s been so long.
Still no news about
Her Grace and the others.
Is anything wrong?
Jiaye.
Greetings, God Gu Jun.
You’re
finally back.
If you came back later,
the Heavenly Palace
would have trampled us underfoot.
Don’t worry.
No one will bully us ever again.
By the way,
why do immortal residences decline
so sharply on Qilian Mountains?
You were away for tens
of thousands of years.
The spiritual veins and power here
have weakened.
Some slow-progressing immortals
believed the Qingchi Palace dwindled
and moved away.
Imbeciles!
Tell those immortals
if they want to come back,
it won’t be easy.
Yes, Your Grace.
Your Majesty, do you have a counter-plan
against the Demon God’s return?
Don’t panic, my lords.
He hasn’t gained full power of True God
since he was wounded by Bai Jue.
Otherwise, he would have
brought my palace to the ground,
instead of tearing down only one hall
before he left.
Your Majesty is right.
In my opinion,
the Demon God made such a scene
in the Heavenly Palace
just to bluff.
Your Majesty,
we can’t belittle him though his power
was weakened.
He intended to kill all beings
to be the Chief God.
When he gains full power
and remembers his goal,
there’ll be another turmoil.
Lordship Donghua is right.
Jingyang, lead fifty thousand troops to
the Demon Region
and guard the barriers against demons.
If you detect a move,
report immediately.
Yes,
Father.
The Demon God’s return
is a crisis of the Three Realms.
All immortals should work
in a concerted effort.
From now on,
I urge each immortal lord to be alert
and deny every chance for the demons.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Gu Jun has returned.
So has the Demon God.
Counting in the Heavenly Palace,
we’re in another tripartite situation.
No one will yield.
If we don’t make a change,
what happened sixty thousand years ago
will repeat itself.
Your Majesty, we see demons as foes.
What should our attitude
towards the Qingchi Palace be?
Do you have any idea?
About what?
About why you hid a secret from me
for so many years?
Houchi isn’t your daughter.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I...
Over the years,
you never asked.
I thought you didn’t mind.
I don’t.
But have you been honest with me?
A mortal woman
would have told this to her husband,
instead of hiding it
like you did, which led to
the misunderstanding.
Have you ever considered my feelings?
I do care about your feelings.
We have three children.
I manage the chores in the palace
over the years as my duty.
How could you question my love
to you because of this?
All right, then tell me
what happened back then.
Back then, Gu Jun
was always away
and you often came by to visit.
So I married you.
I felt sorry for Gu Jun,
so when he came to me
with the unhatched egg,
I felt sorry for the poor child
and agreed to be her nominal mother.
I didn’t know
it’d lead to so many misunderstandings.
Huan.
Over the years,
who knows the pain in my heart?
It’s my fault.
I neglected your feelings.
The grudge with the Qingchi Palace
began with my love to you
which offended Gu Jun.
Let’s forget about
the bygones.
From now on,
leave Houchi and Qingmu
alone,
will you?
Your Grace, Jiaye has informed
all immortal establishments
that Qilian Mountains
aren’t somewhere they can come and go
at any time.
Those immortals are all snobs
who curry favor with those in power.
The Qingchi Palace has been neutral
in the Three Realms
and alienated from the Heavenly Palace.
Let’s give them a lesson this time.
Qilian Mountains will be in peace.
I think those immortals
must be regretting.
With you around,
no one would
dare to offend the Qingchi Palace.
Fengran, thank you
for keeping everything
in order in the Qingchi Palace
over the years when I was away.
You flattered me, Your Grace.
Were it not for your shelter back then,
I can’t even imagine where I’d be now.
Since I stepped into the Qingchi Palace,
it has been my home.
You and Houchi have been my family.
That’s what I should do.
It just surprised me
that Houchi isn’t the daughter
of the Queen of Heaven.
The scandal about her birth has caused
constant ridicule and grievances.
I feel sorry for her.
I had no other options back then.
I came back this time
and found that Houchi’s power
had improved a great deal than before.
I wonder
if it owes to the young man
on the Green Dragon Platform.
You noticed it?
On the Green Dragon Platform,
I had no chance to ask Houchi.
Tell me more details about him.
That immortal lord is from the North Sea
and exceptionally gifted.
He reached the top of immortal lords
within only one thousand years
which makes him famous among immortals.
The Heavenly Palace tried a few times
to draw him in.
He showed little interest,
but he’s deeply in love with Houchi.
In public, he defends for
our Qingchi Palace.
I think he and Houchi are a...
A what?
A perfect match.
Stop this nonsense!
Your Grace, as you saw
on the Green Dragon Platform,
he and Houchi have been through deaths
and have given their heart to the other.
Even if you want to stop them,
I’m afraid your effort will be futile.
And Lord Qingmu is a decent
and kind man.
He isn’t snobbish at all.
Such a virtuous man is rare
in the Three Realms.
- Why do you have to...?
- Stop.
I have to cook medicine for Houchi.
Her health matters more than anything.
Judging by His Grace’s attitude,
Houchi and Qingmu will have a hard time.
Master,
I never imagined
you’d fall in love with Houchi.
And you fell completely.
What should I do?
Father.
Sweetie,
you haven’t recovered
and shouldn’t have come out.
I’m fine.
I did transfer power to you
on the Green Dragon Platform,
but you’re still far too weak.
I picked those herbs
on the top of snow-capped mountains.
They’re the best for your health.
Ask Chang Que to boil them for you.
Sweetie,
why is your power inside so robust?
Father, it was strange
at the Heavenly Palace
that I drew in the God power
of the Pilgrimage Hall.
Now I can help you
defend the Qingchi Palace.
Pilgrimage Hall?
What?
Sweetie,
why do you take such precious medicine
to me?
What a waste.
Father, stop pretending.
I can see it.
What can you see?
You’re wounded.
It’s nothing. Don’t worry.
Nothing?
Where have you been over the years?
I collected
those medicines one by one on the top
of snow-capped mountains.
Your foundation is shaky.
These are good for your strength.
You usually sent home letters
by instruction feather.
This time you went for so long
and sent no letter at all.
I ran into a few beasts
from the Shanggu Realm.
In the engagement,
my spiritual veins were wounded.
So, I had to meditate and heal.
And I woke up to find
it’s been tens of thousands of years.
Has your wound healed?
Your father is a God.
This is just an ailment.
Come on, my sweet girl,
drink the medicine.
Father,
the medicine is a gesture of my love.
Sweetie,
let me help you.
Alright, darling,
how about this?
You and I
both take a half.
Father,
you have no idea
how much I missed you
in the years when you were away.
Sweetie,
let’s go out for a walk.
Lord Qingmu, what are you...?
I’m here to visit God Gu Jun.
Please report it.
A moment, please.
I’ll report it to His Grace.
I’m sorry for what you had to face
over the years.
Don’t be, Father.
I’m the heiress of the Qingchi Palace.
It’s my duty to defend it.
My sweet girl has grown up.
I’m so happy.
Now I’m back.
I’ll see to it
that no one dares to offend us again.
Father, did you hear anything
about Boxuan on your trip?
No.
But according to the time,
Boxuan should have gone through
tribulations and become a God.
But he hasn’t come back.
Maybe he...
He won’t.
In the last tens of thousands of years,
no immortals have ascended to God,
but I believe Boxuan
wouldn’t fail the tribulation.
As long as he’s not found,
I believe he’s still alive in the world.
I was being reckless with my words.
I also believe
Boxuan is so powerful
that he’ll be safe.
Father, there’s another thing.
The man on
the Green Dragon Platform, Qingmu,
is honest about his love for me.
My love for him is also true.
You and he...?
We’ve promised ourselves to each other.
It won’t change for eternity.
Qingmu is a decent
and righteous man.
I can’t be wrong about him.
Your Graces.
Chang Que, what’s so urgent?
Your Grace, North Sea Lord is here.
He’s waiting at the gate to meet you.
He came just in time.
Lead him to the main hall.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Greetings, God Gu Jun.
No need.
I agree to meet you
to make something clear with you.
I’m clear of your affection
for Houchi,
but you will not
have my permission.
Father.
And North Sea Lord,
please do not come again.
Excuse me.
Father!
Houchi, calm down.
Why was Father so rigid?
Try to put yourself in his shoes.
You hadn’t met for tens of thousands
of years.
Well, just after you reunited,
Qingmu came to propose to you.
No father
would agree to give her daughter away.
But Father said
he didn’t want Qingmu to come again.
He doesn’t want him to come,
but he didn’t forbid it.
I think he still has a chance.
Right, Houchi.
I still have a chance.
I shouldn’t have come so soon
and overlooked your father’s feelings.
Don’t worry.
I won’t give up.
One day, I’ll make sure he accepts me
and believes I can take care of you.
Give him a few more days.
I think His Grace
is testing his son-in-law.
Testing me?
Master,
how dramatic fate is.
If you remembered everything
and were put in this situation,
how would you feel?
Houchi and Qingmu
are deeply in love.
But I don’t want
Houchi to be sad.
Father.
The princess has just recovered.
She can’t drink.
Is that how you serve her?
Forgive us, Your Majesty.
Her Grace insisted to drink alcohol.
We couldn’t stop her.
Please spare us, Your Majesty.
Never mind.
Leave us.
How is your health?
Almost fine.
When I found you lost the dragon core,
I was so worried
and I said something harsh.
The dragon core is your root.
Without a root,
you’re nobody.
I feel so sorry for you.
I was so stupid
to have done such a foolish thing.
You and Mother must be worried.
I’m sorry.
This isn’t all your fault.
If I knew Qingmu’s heart
was with the Qingchi Palace,
I wouldn’t have granted the marriage
and all this wouldn’t have happened.
I wanted that marriage.
But what happened
enables me to see many things through.
Darling,
your life in the Heavenly Palace
has been well provided.
We’ve all spoiled you.
Thus, you became proud and headstrong.
I thought it was good for you.
But love
cannot be forced.
Make sure
you learn the lesson from the pain.
I will, Father.
From now on, I’ll love myself
and try not to be willful again.
Good.
Though you’ve regained the dragon core,
losing it had caused great damage
to your spiritual power.
Why not spend some time in a retreat?
It’s immensely helpful
in rebuilding your strength.
All right,
you can’t stand in the cold wind.
Let me walk you to your bedroom
to have some rest.
Father.
You can cry if you want to.
I’m always here with you.
The Demon God has returned.
It won’t be long until the awakening.
When he becomes a True God,
he’ll come after me for Yuemi’s sake.
I won’t be able to meet his rage.
And Muguang
isn’t reliable.
I have to improve
my own spiritual power.
The time left for me isn’t much.
This bow is made of pure evil.
It will help you
improve your spiritual power.
Pure evil?
The grievances and malice of those
who died a wrongful death.
The anger in their heart
produced immense power.
So, this bow is infinitely powerful.
It’s been sixty thousand years.
I’m no longer the maid in the past,
but the Queen of Heaven,
a powerful Goddess.
Am I still not qualified to control
the weapon I couldn’t control
in the past?
Fengnyu.
Yes, Your Highness.
Master,
the immortals attacked
with missing soldiers
as their excuse lately.
We engaged a few times.
Both sides won and lost.
But the toll is heavy.
They won sometimes?
Do we have no military talent?
Pass my order.
Send Three-Head Fire Dragon
to the Demon Region immediately.
And there’s a Demigod.
Let’s see if they can win again.
Yes, Master.
I stayed up all night
and found no solution at all.
Houchi,
does your father like anything
particularly?
Aside from his sweet daughter,
His Grace values his armory the most.
I asked Chang Que about it.
He neglected the cleaning of it
while His Grace was away.
Good, it’s a test.
I’ll start from the armory.
Are you sure you want to tidy it up?
Those who already have everything
can be touched by sincerity.
Houchi, trust me.
I’ll show him my sincerity
and win his permission for our marriage.
What’s up?
Nothing.
I should go.
Sure, go.
I’m leaving.
Go.
(Qingchi Palace)
Your Grace.
Let’s go.
♪Year after year time goes by♪
♪Don’t be afraid Fate comes back♪
♪Rain floods and memories last♪
♪I won’t stop missing you
no matter what♪
♪Years have passed and I keep staying♪
♪I experience endless sadness
but never leave♪
♪Staying away and loving you greatly♪
♪I’d wait through the lifetime♪
♪I spend years waiting
for returned birds♪
♪I never regret
and let no one replace you♪
♪Hope we’ll figure out the past
when we wake up♪
♪I’ll finally confess to you♪
♪Along the way I watch flowers
bloom and wither♪
♪Maybe we part because we’ll meet again♪
♪Tears turn into clouds and rain drops♪
♪When everything works out♪
♪I’ll enjoy a free life with you
for a thousand years♪