[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 36]
Four Season Clan
has set the fire.
They only need to fan the flames a bit
so that the civilians
can be enraged.
Don't take it away!
Yeah.
You can't take it away!
My lord!
My son and I rely on the grain
for the next three days.
Please show mercy!
Please, my lord!
Please show mercy to us.
I've just received
a report saying that
someone in the south market
colluded with Four Season Clan
to smuggle grain from Hanjia Granary.
After investigation,
it turned out to be true.
No, my lord!
I know nothing about Four Season Clan.
I dare not steal grain from our country!
My lord!
Enough with the excuses!
Slap him!
Yes!
Don't!
How dare you!
No excuses!
I know that
a lot of you
have grain stashed away.
I will give you one hour
to hand your stashes over.
Otherwise,
you'll be punished as accomplices
of Four Season Clan.
It's uncalled for!
What Clan?
You didn't catch the rebels.
We couldn't buy grain,
and they gave us grain for free.
What have we done wrong?
How could you do this?
Move!
Excuse me!
Yeah!
Lord Gao,
what are you doing?
I am searching for criminals
from Four Season Clan.
Are you going to interfere, Madam Wu?
They're innocent civilians.
Innocent? They stashed away grain
that belongs to the country!
Bring him back to the Grant Court!
-Anyone who dares disobey my order...
-My lord!
-...will be punished the same way!
-My lord.
Lord Gao!
My lord!
I am innocent!
Please, don't arrest my father!
You can't do that!
You can't take him!
-Release him!
You said the grain belongs to the country.
How can you prove it?
My lord,
where does the grain in your house come from?
Get up!
Maybe you embezzled grain
and made him your scapegoat!
I am innocent!
My lord, I am innocent!
Do you want to be taken as rebels?
Kill that bastard!
We don't want to rebel!
We just want to kill
the incompetent officials.
If you want to push us down the cliff...
Go back!
We'll drag you down with us!
Back off!
Kill that bastard!
Stop them!
Calm down, guys!
Please calm down!
Calm down!
Quiet!
I am Madam Wu of Interior Guard Services.
Luoyang is experiencing famine.
I know you're all struggling.
However, the grain you stashed away
was most likely stolen
from Hanjia Granary.
We won't ask you to return the grain
that you've already obtained.
The authorities are doing their best
to find out the truth.
Please, hang in there for a few more days.
I promise we will send grain
to all of you
so that you can have sufficient food.
Who are you?
Who are you to promise us?
Yeah.
Who knows if she and that bastard
are on the same side?
I know her.
She's Madam Wu of Interior Guard Services.
She's a good person.
Let's trust her for once.
Brother.
Are you aware of all the riots?
Although the riots
have been suppressed for now,
the Intelligence Services
sent us another message.
Have a look.
They're saying that
the famine in Luoyang was caused
by the Crown Prince, who's been hoarding grain
in order to make a fortune.
So, tomorrow,
they'll all go to the Eastern Palace
to confront the Crown Prince.
Now that the word is out,
Her Majesty must've already known about it, too.
Siyue,
go and get to the bottom of this.
We must make sure that the Crown Prince
is not wronged.
Yes.
[Kites]
[Tiao Di Rice Shop]
[Sold out]
[Tiao Di Rice Shop
Sold out]
[Tiao Di Rice Shop]
The capital is in chaos right now.
How could you, the future emperor,
commit such a shameful misdeed?
I knew nothing
about it.
The servants did it behind my back.
The servants?
It was your servant that made all those elixirs.
Now, it's also your servants
that are hoarding the grain.
Tell me!
Where did you
get all these servants?
The Crown Prince committed misdeeds.
How do you think
I should punish him?
Please don't be angry, Your Majesty.
His Highness
was deceived by evildoers.
Please, Your Majesty, spare him.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, please do not get angry!
Take him back to the Eastern Palace.
He shall never leave the Palace
without my permission!
Yes.
Your Majesty!
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Do take care of yourself.
Wu Youjue!
Your Highness.
You've taken over the Intelligence Services.
Why haven't you visited me?
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Her Majesty asked me to investigate the Clan.
I also need to
manage the two Services.
I have been too busy
to do anything else.
I heard that the Intelligence Services
holds the scandals of all officials.
Find out about them as soon as possible.
That way, you and I
will soon take control
of the Court!
Your Highness,
The future of Luoyang
is at stake right now.
We need to think of the big picture.
How dare you lecture me?
Wu Youjue,
I got you this promotion.
I can also have you demoted as I want.
I still find it suspicious.
The Crown Prince is the future emperor.
He'd never risk his future
for some money.
You're right.
Her Majesty has been
watching his behavior closely.
Besides, he had just
got punished because of Dai Zhou.
He should've laid low at the moment.
In that case,
the Crown Prince was framed
by Four Season Clan.
But why did they do that?
I don't know how Four Season Clan
got to the Crown Prince,
but the people in Luoyang
are furious with the Court.
Four Season Clan
has set the fire already.
At this rate,
the Clan will win over
all the people in Luoyang.
Then, we'll be doomed.
Sir, bad news!
There's a riot in the Unwelcome Well.
Go have a look!
I've got it covered here.
Okay.
My lord,
as you predicted,
the Crown Prince has been grounded
by the evil Empress.
The people in Luoyang
could not be more furious.
In that case,
let's make the last move.
We won't be sitting ducks!
Kill the evil Empress!
Protect the natural order!
The evil Empress is incompetent.
The Crown Prince is immoral.
The Heavenly Lord and the people are all enraged!
The fire of Hanjia Granary
was divine retribution.
The servants of the evil Empress
are all evildoers who mistreat good people.
They should be killed!
Anyone in Luoyang
who can kill a servant of the evil Empress
can join the Clan
and enjoy a lifetime of fortune.
If anyone can kill the evil Empress,
they'll become the leader of the Clan
and enjoy the service of all the others.
My lord,
don't go out!
The whole city is in chaos.
There are people all over the streets.
They're heading to the Imperial Palace.
I heard that they'll rebel against the Court.
Uncle Baili,
get a horse for me.
I want to go to the Palace and see Her Majesty.
We can't just sit here and be starved to death.
We want to stay alive!
We need food! We need to stay alive!
We need grain!
The Crown Prince is immoral!
♫My life is full of precariousness♫
♫The world is in chaos and full of danger♫
♫I leave with the wind♫
♫I know what I want, so I have no regret♫
♫My mission is not accomplished♫
♫As long as the world is unjust♫
♫I turn around and your face comes to mind♫
♫Only the wind keeps me company♫
♫Even if I have countless stratagems♫
♫What's the point if no one understands them♫
♫Whose efforts will be seen♫
♫Along the journey of life♫
♫There are all kinds of obstacles♫
♫We need to come up with new ways to overcome them♫
♫Life is full of ups and downs♫
♫Life is full of encounters and goodbyes♫
♫How can we avoid those♫
♫I can vouch for you with all my heart♫
♫You are the most intelligent♫
♫You are the one and only in this world♫
[Xuanren Gate, Eastern Luoyang]
[Xuanren Gate]
People from the Unwelcome Well
shall never enter Luoyang.
Do you want to rebel?
We've been starving for days.
No matter where we go,
we'll die anyway!
We may as well start a rebellion!
Yeah!
Back off!
We'll never get out.
We'll die either way!
Yeah!
Let's overthrow the throne!
If we stay here,
we'll be stuck and die of hunger and illness.
One step forward,
and I'll shoot!
We might live if we take a step forward!
We'll die otherwise!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let us out!
Stop!
Gao Bingzhu?
How dare you come back here, you shameless man!
Luoyang is in chaos.
You mustn't leave
the Unwelcome Well.
If you go up there, you'll be killed!
You do think of yourself
as a minion of the Court
now that you've put on the uniform!
If we don't go up there,
we'll be starved to death
in the Well.
Yeah!
Let us out!
Hear me out!
We will find
the grain stolen from Hanjia Granary.
Nobody will be starved to death.
Cut the crap!
The Clan said that
as long as we join them,
we'll have all the grain we want.
Yeah!
Gao Bingzhu!
Let us out!
Shoot!
Wait!
We want grain!
Hear me out!
I, Gao Bingzhu,
am a sinner of the Unwelcome Well.
You all know that
it was because of me
that seven of my friends died.
It was also because of me that my family was ruined.
I've lived in guilt and agony
every day for the past five years.
I did think about
ending my own life,
but now that I've decided to stay alive,
I want nothing more than
to get you out of the Well
and avenge the death of my friends.
I can tell all of you that
it was Four Season Clan,
the almighty Clan in your eyes,
that caused all this.
Impossible!
He's lying to us.
-Don't listen to him.
-Impossible!
Let's get out of here!
Gao Bingzhu!
You're a liar!
My brother died because of you!
Gao Bingzhu!
You killed him!
Stop!
Stop it!
It's been five years.
How come you still don't understand
who on earth
killed your brother?
Five years!
For the past five years,
Gao Bingzhu has given
every one of you
money and food,
and for what?
So that you can treat him
as your enemy today?
We can't let outsiders
think of us
as a bunch of ungrateful
and foolish losers!
I once swore when I was promoted
as a Well officer
that I would get everyone out of the Well
to live a decent life in Luoyang.
However, so many years have passed,
and you're still here in the Well.
I didn't keep my promise.
I sincerely apologize to you,
but please trust me one more time.
I will definitely
get all of you
out of here one day.
But today is not the day.
Four Season Clan robbed the country of grain
and gave it to you
so that they could instigate you
to rebel against the Court.
Once you get out
of the Well now,
you'll become rebels
and face the death penalty.
If we don't go out,
we'll be starved to death.
Gao Bingzhu,
why should we believe
that you can get us out one day?
Yeah.
We'll die if we stay here.
I don't want to die.
Please, give me some more time.
I will bring the grain back
to you.
Please, trust me one more time.
Your Majesty,
do you need me to fetch the doctor?
As long as
there are riots on the streets,
even ten doctors won't be able to help me.
Leave.
Your Majesty...
What?
Baili Hongyi, the son of Baili Yan,
the late Minister of Works,
is on his knees outside.
He wants to report something important.
The younger son of Baili Yan?
Yes.
Since Baili Yan was vindicated
of corruption,
Baili Hongyi
has been working for Sir Wu.
Tell Baili Hongyi to come in.
People have been starving for over ten days.
They say that once you join the Clan,
you'll have food.
No one can resist the temptation.
I've been trying to talk sense into them for days,
but to no avail.
If you hadn't come here in time...
Who sent them
the message?
An outsider came to the Well a few days ago
and delivered the message.
Where is he now?
Why did you instigate
people of the Well to rebel?
Did Lord of Spring ask you to do this?
[Qingye, Disciple of Four Season Clan]
Would you ever have come back
if they hadn't started a riot?
Leave the Unwelcome Well alone!
Lord of Spring has sent many people
to spread the message in Luoyang.
This guy
was sent to the Well.
He beat me to it
and spread the message before I came.
All I could do
was to kill him.
So, I've now paid back
what I owed you.
What are you going to do?
Relax!
I know that you keep me alive
because I am of similar age
with that girl
you mentioned.
I remind you
of her.
She's your younger sister,
so you don't have the heart to kill me.
Am I right?
I was born an orphan.
I envy your sister when I see you
care about her so much.
To be honest,
I've always wanted
a brother like you.
Unfortunately,
I am not your sister.
You were asking about what I will do next.
I'll tell you now.
Why did you stop me?
Who do you think you are?
I am an orphan.
The Clan raised me.
Now that I've betrayed them,
I can never go back.
I've got no family now.
I've got no other option.
What's the point of staying alive?
What's the point?
I've paid back
what I owed you.
I can only redeem myself
for killing all those people
by ending my own life, alright?
So, you're aware
that you've killed many people
and committed unforgivable sins.
But if you do have
a shred of conscience left,
you shouldn't kill yourself.
Death is the easy way out.
It means incompetence.
It means you want to run away.
You should stay alive.
Redeem yourself for the lives you've taken
with the rest of your life.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What do you want?
I heard that
Sir Wu has been admonishing rebels
at Xuanren Gate by Your Majesty's order.
What?
Anything wrong?
Please, Your Majesty, withdraw your order.
He will likely put his life at risk by doing this.
He's an interior guard.
How could he be afraid of some rebels?
I'm afraid it's not only the rebels he's facing,
but also evildoers of Four Season Clan.
We want food!
We want to stay alive!
Back then, my brother Baili Kuanren
slandered the Court.
Your Majesty ordered to exile him,
but he then died at home.
However,
he didn't die.
Instead, he joined Four Season Clan.
So?
I know my brother well.
He's got a weakness.
If he writes an article
that he's proud of,
he'll read it in public
for compliments.
He must be
in Luoyang right now,
waiting to show off his masterpiece.
Waiting to show off
his masterpiece in public?
Do you mean that
he'll be there
and watch Sir Wu get killed?
Please, Your Majesty, withdraw your order.
You're all gathered here
for a good reason.
I, Wu Youjue,
am a high-up official in the Court,
but I did nothing
to alleviate you from starvation.
I did nothing to comfort
your babies that are crying.
I am utterly ashamed of myself.
But do you know
who is the one that got
our capital into such chaos?
The evil Empress!
The Crown Prince!
-The Empress.
-The Crown Prince.
-The Empress!
The Empress!
You're all wrong.
[Grain]
You've misunderstood the situation.
The famine occurred in Luoyang
because an organization
blew up Hanjia Granary
and destroyed the grain reserved for
over 200,000 households and millions of people.
You're all starving because of that organization!
That organization
is Four Season Clan!
[Grain]
How's that possible?
Yeah.
The Clan gave us grain.
Liar!
The Clan gave us
grain.
Yeah!
The grain Four Season Clan gave you
was stolen from Hanjia Granary.
The grain they gave you
belonged to you in the first place!
It was stolen from Hanjia Granary.
Think about this, folks!
Hanjia Granary has always been
heavily guarded all these years.
Has anything happened to it?
If it wasn't
purposeful sabotage,
how could it be blown up?
Four Season Clan
was using the grain that belonged to you
to provoke your rage.
They were using the grain that belonged to you
to create chaos.
to destroy our peaceful life!
Folks!
Open your eyes and look around!
All the grain on the carriages...
The grain on the carriages
is all that is left
in Luoyang.
I urged Her Majesty
to collect the grain
from all the officials.
We'd rather starve ourselves
than starve the people in Luoyang!
Can you understand
the goodwill of the Court?
Can you feel the grace of Her Majesty?
Is he telling the truth?
You should've all known by now
who is the real enemy of Luoyang.
It's Four Season Clan!
Baili Hongyi,
do you know
the consequences
of telling me all this?
It means I've deceived Your Majesty
and the Baili family will face the death penalty.
Aren't you afraid of death?
I am,
but I've got no other choice.
I, Wu Youjue,
hereby swear that
I will destroy Four Season Clan
and take back the grain that belonged to you.
I will make sure you can all live a peaceful life.
The officials have given their grain to us.
He has a point.
Why would they
blow up their own Granary?
There must be evildoers behind all this.
They gave us grain at such a critical moment,
maybe we should trust them for once.
We're grateful to Her Majesty!
Kuanren,
it's been so long since I last met you.
I've been planning this for so long.
I must come to appreciate it.
I don't feel resentment losing to you, though.
Baili Hongyi,
you're quite courageous.
I had already known this
before you told me.
Sir Wu
and your father
released Baili Kuanren in private.
How could they have fooled me?
It was just that
Baili Yan had always been loyal,
and I didn't have the heart
to see him lose his son.
However, Baili Kuanren
is so ungrateful!
All of this was started by my brother.
Please punish us, Your Majesty.
It's all ancient history.
I am not that petty.
Sir Wu has already reported to me
about this.
If things are going as expected,
Baili Kuanren
should have been arrested by now.
Brother,
how are you feeling?
Should I go and get the doctor?
No need, I am fine.
Baili Kuanren has been sent to the dungeon.
Do you want to interrogate him now?
It can wait.
I will know how to deal with him
after I talk to Her Majesty.
Brother, you managed to talk sense into
the civilians in Luoyang
and catch a leader of the Clan
even though you were ill.
It made me realize
the real meaning of
'Keep order for Her Majesty and protect Luoyang.'
I won't mind more compliments
like this in the future.
No problem!
Brother, I've always respected
you the most.
All jokes aside,
have you found the grain stolen
from Hanjia Granary?
I heard that it was transported
to the mountains in northern Luoyang.
Gao Bingzhu and his men are on it.
However,
I still have a disturbing feeling.
The Clan has worked on the plan for five years.
It can't be
ruined by us so easily.
You are right.
Although Lord of Spring
has been arrested,
there are still a lot of remnants
hiding in Luoyang.
We shall not let our guard down.
[Wanted]
Take a closer look! Have you seen her?
Take a closer look!
Lord Pei,
is Peipei of Hong Xiao Fang
really from Four Season Clan?
She attacked the King of East River on the street.
Of course, she's one of them!
She's so gorgeous,
and she dances and sings so well.
What on earth was she thinking?
The Interior Guard Services
caught the leader of Four Season Clan.
They're so arrogantly proud of themselves now.
If the Grant Court
failed to make a contribution soon,
we'd be despised by them.
-Alright.
Chunhe!
Chunhe, what's wrong?
Are those officers looking for me?
Chunhe,
you're safe here.
Don't worry!
I checked around when I came here.
I was not followed.
Give it to me.
It's cold on the floor. Get up.
You must be hungry, huh?
I bought a lot of
your favorite food.
Don't worry!
I've made arrangements.
Those officers won't come here.
Rest assured!
Don't you want to know
why they are after me?
I know.
You attacked the King of East River.
There are wanted posters of you
all over the place.
Aren't you scared of me?
I'm not.
I don't care if you're an assassin
or Peipei of Hong Xiao Fang,
to me, you'll always be Chunhe.
Look what it is!
I remember that
this was your favorite when you were a kid.
The city is experiencing famine now.
I walked around several streets to find this.
I remember that you'd add honey to it
when you were a kid,
otherwise, you'd find it bland.
Here, have some while it's hot.
I've got my reasons.
I am not
the Chunhe you used to know.
The officers will find me sooner or later.
You can't protect me forever.
Leave!
Or we'll all be killed!
Chunhe!
I don't want to get you implicated.
I know that you've suffered a lot all these years,
but I am here with you now.
I won't allow anyone to mistreat you.
If you don't want to stay in Luoyang,
I'll take you anywhere
in the whole wide world.
We'll never come back!
Liu Feng,
I promise you.
Let's go to a place
where no one knows us,
and we'll never come back!