A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
-[dishes rattling]
-[all chanting] Nils on the table!
Nils on the table! Nils on the table!
[whooping]
[all] Madison on the table!
Madison on the table!
[girls cheer]
Shut up!
[dishes stop rattling]
[girl] Who?
Nils… What's his name? Third year.
-[gasps]
-[boys cheering]
Madison McCoy.
[scattered cheering]
Well, let's hear it.
He…
-He put it out there.
-[girl] Ooh.
-She may have gone down…
-[cheers]
-…a little.
[laughs]
Yeah, but how was it?
It was… okay, I guess.
Nine out of ten.
[boy] Ooh. So, you going out?
No, God no. I was just bored.
[girls laugh]
Hell, yeah. It's, like, really serious.
That's enough. We've heard enough. Okay.
Yeah. "Nine out of ten."
Anyone else who
should be standing on their chair?
Huh?
Any other dick that's been sucked?
[all laugh]
No one? Jesus.
I'm sure someone has a story to tell.
Anyone?
Wille?
Wille disappeared
from the party yesterday.
-With a girl, perhaps?
-What?
-Felice?
-No. [laughs]
-If not, then who?
-No.
[all] The table! The table!
The table! The table!
-[Wilhelm] No!
-[all] Wilhelm on the table!
Wilhelm on the table!
[pounding]
Hey. Calm down, everyone.
[pounding stops]
[exhales]
["No Tomorrow" playing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪I be in the wind
Baby, I'll hit you tomorrow ♪
[girls indistinct conversation continues]
♪ You and gang-gang-gang
You ain't even real ♪
♪Gotta have a bag
I ain't no cheap thrill ♪
♪ Hopped up on the flank
Baby, I ain't had my fill ♪
♪ They know the truth
When I pull up, I'm bulletproof ♪
♪ I don't care about the rules
I be Chris Brown with the moves ♪
♪ Damn, baby, how you doing baby?
When I'm stepping in a room ♪
♪ I look at nobody's paper
They know what I do ♪
♪ When that pressure hits
Tell me your G is finna ride ♪
♪ I was made for this-- ♪
-Hi. Going to math class?
-Yeah.
Uh… don't we have math too?
Okay.
Did you have fun last Friday?
-Yeah, it was great. What about you?
-Yeah, it was nice.
Mm. Good. Great.
Uh, are you going to
horror movie night on Fri--
Yeah, it'll be great.
Well, the big question is
if I'm going, right?
So you snuggle up
in my safe arms if it gets scary.
I'll see you in math class.
Felice, when can I buy you dinner?
Where? At the pizzeria in Bjärstad?
No, I'll fly you to Verbier.
Saint-Martin-de-Belleville.
Three Michelin stars.
You'll love it, trust me.
Well, think about it. Okay?
[sighs]
-What a…
-Yeah, I know.
-I mean, oh, my God…
-I think it sounds romantic.
Romantic? Yeah, maybe if you want
to be with someone who thinks he owns you.
Okay, maybe he used to be a player,
but love can actually change you.
She's probably just jealous.
[girl] Seriously.
What's her problem? It's insane.
I don't get it.
She's making it into such a big deal.
-[girl] It's always something.
-Hi.
[chair scrapes]
[both giggling]
Everything okay, Sara?
[door shuts]
-[man] Good morning.
-Good morning, Mr. Englund.
Sit down, please.
I'm afraid the prince missed this test.
But he can take it later.
-Thank you, Mr. Englund.
-Of course.
-At your convenience.
-Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What'd you get?
B+.
[Englund] You've got to learn
to keep your nerves in check.
Most of your calculations are correct but…
many of your answers are not.
Thank you, Mr. Englund.
I used to have straight A's on every test.
Yeah, well, that school
had a lower grade average.
-Yes!
-Good, man!
Damn it, I got an A-.
Uh, they pay for
private lessons before the tests.
What?
Extra studies with Mr. Englund
at Forest Ridge House all weekend.
I study with the teachers every workie.
He's not as strict with those
who pay for private tutoring.
I see.
[Englund] Well, let's turn to page 211.
Geometry and algebra.
[Simon] Um, about private lessons…
[Englund] Yes?
What do I have to do
to get private lessons?
Come in.
So you're interested in private lessons?
Perhaps we can improve your results.
Have you talked to your parents about it?
Mm.
Okay, come and see me later on today,
we'll have a chat
and figure out your needs.
The school will send you an invoice.
How does that sound?
[horse neighs]
Come.
Come here.
[straining] That's it.
We're just going to go for a…
Come on. Come.
[sighs] Please don't. Come on.
Please, Rousseau. Can… can you…
I just don't understand his problem.
[horse snorts]
[sing-songy] Hi there. Hello.
-Hi.
-[horse nickers]
There now. There now.
-Do you want me to bring him in?
-Yes.
There. Come on.
[clicks tongue] Come.
[sniffs]
[Sara] There you go.
Good boy.
Ah. [clicks tongue]
Well, I mean…
Do you have any idea
how expensive Rousseau was?
Dad will be so disappointed
I can't handle him.
Felice, you know…
you have to stop pretending
that you're not afraid.
He can sense it
even if you try to hide your fear.
Just accept that you're afraid.
Then you can start over
and maybe then it will be fun again.
Then he will think it's fun too.
[sighs] But… how come
you know so much about horses?
[laughs]
Well, I've just always
understood horses better than people.
Maybe because of my Asperger's.
It's just, in your case
it seems like a superpower.
It feels like you don't care
what people think about you,
or if you have a lot of friends and stuff.
I would like to have friends.
Can you take a picture of us?
-Of you and Rousseau?
-Yes.
There.
Uh…
Stand a bit closer to him.
Uh… okay.
Just keep him steady. You're in charge.
-Good.
-[groans]
Uh, there. Is that…?
There. That one's really nice.
Really nice. Look.
Hey. Good boy.
Thanks.
-[August] Can you guys get the boat?
-[boy] Sure.
[August] Good. Thanks.
The other one too.
Thanks.
Looking good, Simon.
[Wilhelm] Don't worry about balance.
You'll get the hang of it.
However, you should
think about keeping your strokes
as close to the surface as possible
so as to not waste too much energy.
-But that's just…
-So you still remember then?
[exhales] Yeah.
Well… [clears throat]
Hey, socialist boy!
You could become a great coxswain.
It's well-suited for smaller people.
You know?
[chuckles]
Come on.
[in Spanish] No. No, it's okay.
[in English] Hi.
-Where have you been?
-Sorry, I had a…
I had rowing practice.
[laughs]
-Wait, what? Rowing?
-Yeah.
-What the fuck is rowing?
-It's a sport.
-Rowing isn't a sport.
-[Simon] Yes, it is.
Football is a sport.
-So what do you do?
-Well, I mean, you row.
- Like you do at camp.
-[laughs] Come on!
Well, you know.
It's something new. Something fresh.
-Seriously, who are you?
-What?
[laughs]
-I mean, seriously? Stop.
-What?
-So boring.
-[Simon] What?
You're too funny.
[Simon] I'm doing it to get better grades.
-To get extra points.
-Do you have to have good grades?
Yeah, of course you wanna have good grades
if you want to get somewhere. I think.
Like, where to?
Well, I mean, I…
I like Bjärstad,
but I don't want to live here forever.
You know?
What?
Are you playing?
Yeah.
Uh, there's pizza left if you want some.
Bon appétit.
Thanks.
[laughs] What are you doing?
Coming to see the game tomorrow?
Yeah, I'm really gonna try to make it.
Yeah, I'll be there for sure.
[dreamy electronic music playing]
[clicks tongue]
[door opens]
Oh, shit! Sorry!
I didn't see anything. I…
I just wanted to see where you were.
We have morning practice.
You can't just lie here jerking off.
I was not jerking off.
-Give it to me.
-No.
-Now get up.
-What do you want it for?
Seriously?
Just don't use the school's Wi-Fi
for porn surfing. Could be embarrassing.
[cell phone ringing]
-[Erik] Well, hello there!
-Hey, man. What's up?
-How are you?
-Well, um, I'm fine.
I'm just trying to tell your brother…
Wille here, that he might
wanna improve his strength
to make the rowing team.
-August…
-All right?
And how's that going?
To be honest, I don't think he has
the same drive that you and I have.
-He's a bit… lazy.
-Really, August? Come on.
-He was still sleeping when I walked in.
-Was he?
But we'll fix that, right?
Won't we? Hmm?
Well, I should be going.
But nice talking to you, as always.
-[Erik] See you.
-Sure.
And, hey, Wille, um…
make sure you're done jerking off
and ready to go at 0600 tomorrow. Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah?
Good.
Hi, Wilhelm.
[door shuts]
[Wilhelm sighs] Hi, Erik.
-How's it going?
-Ugh!
August is really
getting on my nerves! Seriously.
Is he always like this?
Yeah, he's always been like that.
A bit… A bit intense.
But just try to understand him.
Intense? He's fucking hysterical.
Nobody else cares about these things.
Yeah, but he's had it rough.
That school is like his entire life.
Don't you not remember
that his mom sent him there
after his dad killed himself?
What? No.
[clamoring outside]
I knew he was dead, but not that he…
killed himself.
-Maybe you were just too young.
-What do you mean "too young?"
Maybe somebody
forgot to tell me, as usual.
Can we talk later?
I have to go to practice now.
Apparently, I'm a bit too lazy, but…
I'll call you after practice. Okay?
-Of course. Bye.
-Great, bye.
Sorry.
Check you out.
Okay. Let's go.
[August]
Hold that position! You can do it!
-[boys groaning]
-[Wilhelm pants]
Asses in the air, Nisse!
[boys grunt]
Three, two, one…
and time for a break! Well done!
Hey…
Um…
The money for…
for all the booze.
Damn it. Sorry. Shit.
I completely forgot. It wasn't…
No, it's cool. I'll cover it for now.
But if you text me the amount,
I can just transfer it.
Yeah.
Good.
-Good morning.
Vincent?
-Is Vincent here?
-Uh, no.
-Vincent?
-What's up?
[August sighs]
Can you get me more?
What, already?
Seriously, how much are you taking?
Can you do it or not?
No, sorry, I can't.
I've already changed
psychiatrists several times.
I don't have any left.
So I…
I ordered…
I ordered like four weeks ago,
but it got stuck at customs.
Come on, seriously.
You know how
fucking important this year is for me.
I have to bring my A game.
Take it easy. Calm down.
Go to the counselor
and start your own assessment.
I can't keep up with this pace.
That Birkenstock socialist?
You know I don't even have ADHD.
It'll never work.
Well…
Hmm. There.
We can use that one again.
Well…
-Hmm.
-Yeah…
Uh…
Want some water?
Uh, yeah.
-Sure.
-Yes.
I think I have ADHD.
What? ADHD? Why do you think that?
I have problems concentrating. You know?
I see.
Any special reason
why you find it hard to focus?
-There you go.
-Thanks.
Well, you know,
sometimes the mind's just spinning.
-I'm sure you know how it is.
-[chuckles]
Sure, do you, uh… [groans]
Do you have trouble sleeping?
Yeah.
-Is your heart racing? Yes?
-Mmm.
-Boom, boom, boom.
-Exactly. Yeah.
And, um… are you dizzy?
-[exhales]
-Headache?
-A massive weight on your chest?
-Mmm.
Well, you see, August,
all of that,
that is just symptoms of stress.
And stress is quite common here at school.
Especially during the last year.
And as I understand it,
you are both the prefect
and the team captain as well.
-Yeah, but it's not pressure.
-Okay. So what do you think it is?
Well, it's obvious.
I can hardly sit still. Just look at me.
-Okay, okay, I can see what you mean.
-Yeah?
I need an assessment.
Oh, dear. Well, of course
we can do an assessment. No problem.
Like, now, please.
Well, you see,
an assessment takes weeks to do.
And we need to do in-depth interviews
with people who know you,
and have known you since you were a kid.
Like, for example, your paren--
Okay, yeah. You don't seem
to have grasped what I'm trying to say.
I need an assessment.
This week, at the latest.
My family
is very important for the school.
My results
are very important for the school.
If it comes out how unwilling
you have been to cooperate…
August, August, August, hold on.
I told you that I'm willing
to assess you, but it takes weeks,
you've got to understand that.
It's a long process,
there is no way around that.
Well, that's all the time we have today.
Hmm, would you believe this watch?
I've had it for over
40 years and it still works.
Hey, uh, and remember…
I'll be right here
if you need someone to talk to.
Thanks… for nothing.
["ALPHA" by Yung Titties playing]
♪ ABC I’m the alpha bitch
If you wanna know who run this shit ♪
♪ ABC I’m the alpha bitch ♪
♪ When I’m in a car, I’m driving
When I’m on a date, I’m buying ♪
♪ When I’m on a plane, I’m the pilot ♪
♪ Party in the cockpit
Bitch, I’m flying it ♪
♪ When I’m in a meeting, I’m in charge ♪
♪ Hide your wife, hide your kids
Hide your boss ♪
♪ When you busy sleeping, I work hard
24/365, I’m a star ♪
♪ Didn’t go to college, still got a PhD ♪
♪ Me and my girls
Got our knowledge from MTV ♪
♪ ABC I’m the alpha bitch
Yeah ♪
Hi.
This really is
the best thing about rowing.
It brings people together, it's really…
wonderful, isn't it?
You know, class, ethnicity,
it doesn't matter.
Everybody has the same chances.
-Am I right?
-Right.
-I'm off to the library.
-Okay, but, um…
Maybe we'll see you at practice tonight.
I can't make it tonight.
[August] You can't just skip practice
if you want to make the rowing team.
You're letting your teammates down.
I know, but I can't tonight, so…
I can't really focus here.
Uh, wait, you have to come
to the horror movie night on Friday.
At the Manor House.
Well, both of you, that is.
Okay.
"Hubba Bubba, mega long."
I think that's nice.
Taking care
of the school's freaks like that.
Fuck you, August.
Just make sure it doesn't rub off.
Sara's no freak.
Sure she has her diagnoses and that,
but she's…
she's the only authentic person around.
What kind of diagnosis?
Like, Asperger's
and, um, some kind of ADHD.
[indistinct chatter]
WILHELM: HI. WHY AREN'T YOU
COMING TO THE ROWING PRACTICE?
[clicks pen repeatedly]
[cell phone vibrates]
SIMON: A FRIEND'S GOT A GAME.
I PROMISED I'D GO.
TAG ALONG IF YOU DARE.
WILHELM: AUGUST WILL FREAK OUT IF I LEAVE.
SIMON: I GET IT, YOU'RE TOO SCARED.
Are you coming?
[sighs] Aw, fuck.
I don't think I can.
I think I don't feel so well.
Do you want me to get you something?
God, no! Thanks, but it's all right.
I'll just stay in and go to bed early.
I don't want you guys to get sick.
I've got a sore throat.
[swallows painfully]
But you do realize that I can't just
include you as a primary
if you don't, like, come to practice?
Yeah, sure. I get it.
But get some rest
and when you're feeling better,
you can get your
fighting spirit back, okay?
Super.
-I know you've got it in you!
-Yeah.
-Good.
Get some rest now.
-Okay.
-See you.
[door closes]
WILHELM: I'LL…
WILHELM: I'LL BE THERE.
-Hi.
Sorry, we don't accept card payments.
Okay, do you have a number
so I can transfer the money?
No, you need to download
the app and pay like everyone else.
Yeah. [clears throat]
-[scattered chuckles]
-[clears throat]
[bus door closes]
Hi.
-How are you?
-I'm good. How are you?
-Good.
Have you always lived here?
Yeah.
Is it nice?
[sighs] It's okay, I guess.
There isn't so much to do around here.
I mean…
Everybody does the same things
and everybody knows everybody.
-So it's… Yeah.
-Sounds a bit like my life.
-[Simon laughs] Are you kidding me?
-Hi, Prince!
Hi.
[giggling]
[whistle blows]
-What's up?
-It's all good. You?
I'm good.
-Good to see you, man
-You too.
-[whistle blows]
-Uh…
-This is… this is Wilhelm.
-Yo.
-Ayub.
-Wille. Pleasure.
Aw, shit, do you want one?
Um…
Yeah. But I can go get one myself.
II can get them! It's okay.
Ketchup and mustard?
-Uh, sure.
-Boiled or grilled?
Uh…
-Grilled.
-Uh… Okay, thanks.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Shit. The prince, man.
What's going on?
Are you into him?
What? What are you talking about?
I can see there's something going on.
-Bro, you, like, really like him.
-Shh!
No, I don't know…
"Boiled or grilled?"
"Uh, uh, uh…" And he had to
finish your sentence. What's going on?
-You like him.
-Cut it out! He's coming back!
Here you go.
They were out of grilled hot dogs.
Come on, Rosh!
-Thank you.
-No problem.
[Simon] Work it, Rosh!
[Ayub] Well played, Rosh!
[Simon] Rosh! Whoo!
Go for it, Bjärstad!
[dreamy electronic music playing]
[Ayub] Keep going, Rosh!
Come on, Bjärstad!
Keep it up, Rosh!
[both] Rosh!
Come on, Bjärstad!
-[Simon] Come on, Rosh!
-[boys cheering]
-Whoo!
-You're awesome!
[chuckles]
Keep it up, Rosh! Go for the ball!
Come on, Rosh!
[boys chanting]
Let's go, Bjärstad! Let's go!
-[whooping]
-[engines rev]
[horn honking]
[whooping]
-Come on, Ayub!
-[yells happily]
[whooping]
[Simon whooping]
Whoa!
Alexander?
Thanks.
[door creaks softly]
[August] I fold.
-[Nils] I raise you ten.
-[August] Shit.
[Nils] Okay, now you deal.
[Nils sighs] I've got a shitty hand.
[August chuckles]
Was it educational?
Hi. Sorry, I was feeling a bit better.
So I thought it was okay
that I hung out with some friends.
I asked if it was educational.
Your socialist safari.
You gotta understand
that I can't just let this slide.
You left the school's premises
without asking permission.
We all need permission.
You're replacing Alexander
at dinner duty for the rest of the week.
-Okay.
-An apology might be in order.
-Right?
-Yeah, sorry.
What'd you say?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Good.
-May I…?
-No, you know what?
You better be damn careful
what company you keep. Okay?
Especially if they
use you to get some views.
[boys cheering on phone]
[whistle blowing]
[cheering]
You know how things went last time.
Let's go, Bjärstad! Let's go!
Hmm?
[door opens]
-[Simon] Hi.
-[Sara] Hi.
You missed dinner.
Yeah. [chuckles]
I, uh… [clears throat]
I lost track of time.
You lost track of time?
How's that possible?
You can just check your watch.
[laughs]
Ah. Well…
[exhales]
I was just showing
Wilhelm around Bjärstad, that's all.
-Wilhelm?
-Mmm.
Weren't you the one who said that you, uh,
can't be friends
with anyone at the school?
Yeah, but people can change.
Isn't that the thing
about the Royal Family?
That they never change?
-Hmm.
-[cell phone vibrates]
WILHELM:
CAN YOU DELETE THE STORY SHOWING ME?
WILHELM: SORRY…
ETIQUETTE
[Madison] Is it too hot?
[Felice] No, it's not too hot.
It's okay. It just feels warm.
- I don't wanna sound like an idiot.
-[Felice yelps]
[chuckles]
All right.
It feels like August just wants to
ruin my chances to get close to Wilhelm.
Of course he does.
Just make a move on Wilhelm
and show him what you want.
Stop it.
August, can I have a word with you?
I always have time for you, Headmistress.
-Hi.
-Hello.
I just wanted
to ask you about your tuition fee.
-[scoffs nervously] I don't understand.
-Well, it hasn't been paid.
And I haven't
been able to reach your mother.
That's odd.
You know what? She's traveling.
-Yeah, of course, just as I suspected.
-That's why.
But I'll ask her to contact you.
Good. Take care now.
[dreamy electronic music playing]
-Good day, August.
-Hello, miss.
I have to…
You've got ADHD, right?
Uh… yeah.
Cool.
Actually, I've just begun my assessment.
Hmm?
Well…
So you're not on any kind
of medication or anything?
I am.
-Okay.
-[Sara] Vyvanse, 50mg.
[August] Right.
This is gonna sound really weird but…
would you be down with selling me some?
-[Sara] That's illegal.
-[August] Yeah…
[Sara] Why would I do something illegal?
-I thought that since Simon hooked us up…
-[clears throat]
We need to talk
about the rowing team. Now.
We can go outside
if you want to. If that's okay.
[August] Fine.
[Simon]
I don't want you to talking to her.
Sorry.
But, um, what about your contact?
-Can I buy some from him?
-No!
Who do you take me for?
I just want my fucking money.
How about I double what I owe you,
if you get me the pills?
Come on.
It's a great deal.
Good.
[water boiling]
Why don't you bring Sara next time?
It would be great to see you both.
Um, not sure that's a good idea.
This place looks nice.
[plays note on keyboard]
You wanna stay a while and jam?
Well, the thing is…
I can't really stay that long.
[faint yelling]
Hey, uh…
about the money…
for the booze for your friends.
Right. I'm sorry.
Damn. It's on its way.
I promise.
But still…
at least you can stay for a cup of coffee?
Yeah.
-Hey, Simon…
-Uh-huh?
We should go to a concert again sometime.
Yeah.
Like when you were a kid.
Remember when you, me and Sara went
to see the Lee "Scratch" Perry concert?
Yeah, that's right.
-Did you remember the spoons, Dad?
-Uh… yeah.
[grunting]
[blows whistle]
Rotate!
[panting]
What the fuck!
When do I get my money?
-[blows whistle]
-Gather round!
Simon, as you probably
all know, is a non-border.
A bona fide Bjärstad local.
And that's nothing to be ashamed of.
He's had to fight hard to get here.
Probably more than
any of you guys ever have had to fight.
That's quite remarkable.
We should all learn from Simon.
He has fought his way up.
Now he's here, among us.
Among the possibilities.
Simon is…
the class journey personified.
I'm proud of you.
[kisses]
[snorts]
What looking at? Huh? Get back to work!
What the hell was that?
[in Spanish]
Call me when you want to be picked up.
-Hmm?
-Mm-hmm.
-[Simon] Okay.
-Thanks, Mom.
-Bye.
-Wait, where's my phone?
[in Spanish] Here it is.
[in English] It's great that you're
getting invited to things like this.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
-Isn't it?
-Okay.
-[kisses]
-[in Spanish] See you later.
-Bye.
-Have fun.
-Thanks.
Don't you think it's weird
Felice invited us to come?
I think she likes me.
But honestly, I don't know
what I should talk to her about,
if it's not about Rousseau.
[Simon laughs]
-I'm sure it'll be fine.
-Yeah.
Cal?
Something's not right, I think
we should head back to the road.
[man on screen]
This is nuts! This is fucking nuts! Becky!
Becky!
[grass rustling]
Beck!
[man breathing heavily]
-[August] You call this a scary movie?
-[girl] Shut up.
[files buzzing loudly]
[man yells]
[August] Come on,
you can't be scared for real, it's…
Could you stop ruining the film?
Nobody asked you to come.
Feel free to leave if you want.
-Stella, stop being so uptight.
-Just be quiet!
[man] I just slipped!
[woman] Cal, are you okay? What is it?
[man panting on screen]
[man] I'm getting a little
freaked out here. What are we gonna do?
[woman] We're gonna get out of here.
We just need to keep our heads.
What about the kid?
This is about us now.
[man] Beck!
Just stay where you are, okay? Don't move.
Save your voice.
[exhales]
YOU OWN THE SCHOOL
YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS LEGACY
[breathing heavily]
Hey.
-Hi.
-[clears throat]
Are you… are you okay?
Yeah.
It got so damn hot in there,
I thought I'd get some fresh air.
Now my toe is cramping up as well.
[laughs]
How 'bout you?
I'm fine.
[students yelp]
[clears throat]
Well, I'm not…
I'm not… Stop! Wait, wait, wait!
[sighs]
[sighs] Oh, fuck.
I'm not… Sorry. I'm not…
[woman in film] Over here!
[clears throat]
[breathing shakily]