[English subtitles are available]
[Nothing But You]
[Episode 1]
Sister, sister!
Sister! Sister!
Are you alright? Sister.
[Contract]
What?
The contract.
Sister.
[Contract]
Sister, sister!
Sister.
[Ding Dong]
The extreme IP of Lemeng video.
The Journey of the Youth
[Lemeng Picture third quarter project launch]
will be in cooperation with the internationally renowned film and television company
Global Picture.
This is the first olive branch thrown by Global Picture
in the domestic film and television industry.
Next is the media question session.
Sister Xiaoran.
You are the best producer of Lemeng Video.
This time you're the Chief producer
of this extreme IP, The Journey of the Youth.
Do you have the confidence to sign a deal
with Global Picture?
There is pressure,
but more motivations.
To make a perfect work
has always been Lemeng's mission.
We'll live up to the expectations of our audience.
Sister Xiaoran.
[Lemeng Picture third quarter project launch]
Lately, there are a lot of rumors about you and Mr. Lai.
Are you getting married?
I don't respond to any questions
other than The Journey of the Youth.
[Lemeng Picture third quarter project launch]
The terms we offered this time
are in conflict with Global Picture.
They took a firm stand on this matter.
I don't know this time
if Miss Bi can get the contract with them.
There's no failure
in Bi Xiaoran's dictionary.
I hope so.
Have Global Picture's men arrived yet?
They're on the road.
They will arrive at the office in ten minutes.
Whether Lemeng can borrow a boat out to sea
[Lemeng Picture]
and surpass other domestic platforms,
is all counting on The Journey of the Youth.
[The joint investment signing ceremony of The Journey of the Youth]
This is the third time that we've been sitting here.
I hope this time we'll get a good result.
Global Picture has also been looking forward to cooperating with Lemeng.
Miss Bi is an excellent producer.
We're very satisfied with
the cooperation solution that you gave us.
Except for one thing.
The production rights of The Journey of the Youth
must be given to Global Picture.
The Journey of the Youth
is set in ancient China.
And its primary audience is Chinese.
If we gave the production rights to Global Picture,
it might be acclimatized.
The Conllision and Fusion between China and Western in Culture
might produce
a better effect.
Don't you agree with that, Miss Bi?
The market belongs to the risk-taker.
I'm not afraid to take risks.
But I have absolute confidence
in Lemeng's ability
and our country's culture.
A successful cooperation
requires mutual trust in the first place.
In order to cooperate with Lemeng,
Global Picture has backed down for many times.
But Miss Bi won't even
give up the production right.
Mr. Lai.
Is this the cooperative attitude
of Lemeng Video?
Since Xiaoran is the Chief producer
of The Journey of the Youth.
Then her attitude
represents Lemeng's attitude.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Is everything arranged?
Don't worry.
It's all set.
Boss.
[Lai Zhengyi was meeting with the boss of Sony Picture]
If you have not thought it through,
you can go back and discuss about it.
Miss Bi.
I think your company
may need to carefully think about it.
We'll also go back and talk about it.
Wait a moment.
The contract.
Right.
There was a minor error in the contract
that I need to remind you.
It's on line 9, page 8.
The per cent sign was written as the per thousand sign.
If I was doing it on purpose,
[The net profit of Global Picture will be 40 ‰ of the total net profit of the film]
Lemeng could have given up the production right.
We can get the maximum benefits
with the minimum investment.
This kind of loophole,
if it's not Lemeng but any other platform,
they probably would take advantage of it.
But Lemeng doesn't only care about the money,
but more about the work.
See you tomorrow, Miss Bi.
See you tomorrow.
This way.
Sister Xiaoran.
You nailed it! We made the deal with Global Picture.
You are the best producer.
Well done, Sister Xiaoran.
You are the lucky star of Lemeng Video.
Don't count your chickens before they hatch.
We'll officially sign the contract tomorrow.
Don't let up, everybody.
-Undertsand! -Understand!
Ugh!
Jiang Lili.
Get out!
My name is Jiang Lili.
[The 6th Mathematics contest award ceremony of Xingxin Elementary School]
-I have a twin sister, and she has facial paralysis. -The first place is Bi Xiaoran.
Her name is Bi Xiaoran.
She has our father's last name,
and I have our mother's last name.
She was born a champion.
[The math star of the 6th Mathematics Contest]
In the process of growing up,
[Certificate Bi Xiaoran]
she has always been the number one.
And I...
has always been the last one.
We look the same,
but our personalities are totally different.
[Encyclopedia of Insects]
Butterfly is so cute,
how can you stomp it to death?
[Encyclopedia of Insects]
Read this book!
After growing up,
we all entered the entertainment industry.
She's the famous producer
and her boyfriend is the
[The rich second generation is tired of plying with the pop female star]
CEO of the top company Lemeng Video,
Lai Zhengyi.
And I...
am the eyes of online spectators.
[The best actress secretly met with a guy in good shape, playing at the hotel for 27 hours]
That's right.
I am the notorious and famous
discipline committee member
of entertainment industry.
[The discipline committee member of entertainment industry]
I will reveal the truth of the entertainment industry in depth for everyone!
Boring as hell.
I don't have time to fool around with you.
Sister.
Are you going to sign the contract
with the Global Picture today?
[The joint investment contract between Lemeng Film & Media Ltd. and Global film group INC. for the TV series The Journey of the Youth]
May I take some of these pictures?
I won't get in your way.
Sister!
Give it to me!
I won't give it to you.
-Give it to me. -I won't give it to you.
Three.
Two.
One.
Alright, here you are.
Go home!
She's so grumpy!
We're not like natural sisters,
except that we look alike.
Unlike me...
Sister!
Sister, sister!
The contract.
[Contract]
[Ding Dong]
[Lemeng Pictures]
[The Signing Ceremony]
OK, understand.
There was a situation.
She can't make it now.
I have an important schedule afterwards.
If Miss Bi can't make it today,
then we'll sign the contract some other day.
Hello, Dennis.
I am the Administrative Director of Lemeng Video.
Xiaoran is not here,
but we have Sun Xi.
Sun Xi is also our company's producer.
Greetings.
In terms of seniority,
Bi Xiaoran should call him a senior.
Most importantly,
he won't drop the ball at the crucial moment.
Global Picture is willing to sign the contract with Lemeng Video for two reasons.
On the one hand,
we value the influence of Lemeng Video in China.
On the other hand,
we value Miss Bi's outstanding ability.
We choose not only the Lemeng Video,
but also Bi Xiaoran.
The Journey of the Youth
can only be in her hand,
and we'll be at ease.
You can rest assured of that.
Lemeng will abide by the contract,
giving the project to Bi Xiaoran.
We can sign the contract first,
and move the project forward as soon as possible.
Miss Bi is not available today.
Maybe we should take a rain check.
Finish it today!
Lemeng isn't the only company taking eyes on Global Picture.
Let Sun Xi replace Bi Xiaoran first.
Just get the contract now!
Miss Bi.
I thought you weren't coming today.
I apologize, it's my bad.
I was held up on my way.
It's fine.
It's about time to sign the contract.
Let's sign it.
[Contract]
-It's a pleasure to work with you. -Likewise.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
This way.
Byebye.
Lai Zheng...
Mr. Lai, I have something else to do,
I'll leave now.
Jiang Lili.
My sister was hit like this
because of me.
And before she passed out,
she kept murmuring about the contract.
She put so much effort on this project.
It can't be in vain because of me.
So we came up with this plan,
I pretended to be her and signed the contract.
Under the circumstances,
that was indeed the best way to solve the problem.
Right, don't blame yourself too much.
The doctor said
that Sister Xiaoran is out of danger now.
But...
when will she wake up?
It depends on Xiaoran's own situation.
It might take two days
or even longer.
Huh?
Did you find the perpetrator?
The license plate was fully covered.
I didn't see anything.
Besides the hit-and-run driver was also wearing a helmet,
and there was no CCTV on that road.
This is strange.
I will have Xiao He
to help the officer investigate this case.
Okay.
We must investigate the case.
The collaboration between Global Picture and Lemeng has just begun,
and Bi Xiaoran is in charge of this.
This can't go wrong anymore.
Later I'll transfer her
to my private nursing home for treatment,
untill she wakes up.
Thanks, Mr. Lai.
During this period,
you need to continue pretending to be Bi Xiaoran.
Me?
I pretend to be Bi Xiaoran?
You are the perfect choice.
No, no.
I can just played once.
If this became a long-term strategy,
I will definitely be exposed!
Don't worry about this.
I will help you
about work-related matters.
Bi Xiaoran worked on The Journey of the Youth
for three years.
I don't want her to see
everything she did was all in vain
once she wakes up.
What do you want to ask?
My sister and I have never
been seen in public.
Other than my family,
usually no one knows that
she has a twin sister.
How did you know about this?
Your sister mentioned about it once.
That's right.
You two are a couple.
So
it's also my first time to see my brother-in-law.
Greeting, brother-in-law.
We were pretending to be a couple.
Pre...
pretending to be a couple?
Your sister didn't tell you about this?
Never!
Bi Xiaoran was doing a great job
of keeping secrets.
It's not right!
Today, I'm Bi Xiaoran!
My sister's waist is so thin!
Did she eat or not?
Good morning, Sister Xiaoran.
My dear fellows,
good morning.
I'm sorry, Sister Xiaoran.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
-I'll pick these files up. -Just let me do it.
Sorry, sorry.
Bi Xiaoran.
Come with me.
Mr. Lai, what can I do for you?
Now you're Bi Xiaoran,
you're not Jiang Lili.
Everything you do
is under everyone's watch.
You must be aware of this.
I understand.
I need to be mean and more aggressive.
Am I right?
Come over here.
These people are your group members.
Xia Shan.
-Feng Shuangshuang -Sister, have a look at this.
Zhou Kaiwen.
Sun Xue.
They'll spend a lot of time with you in the future.
You need to remember them as soon as possible.
Don't worry.
I'm very good at remembering people's faces.
No mistakes.
Mr. Lai, Sister Xiaoran.
Shuangshuang!
Your lipstick color... is very beautiful!
I like it!
Sister Xiaoran.
This is the first time
that you call me without my last name.
Huh?
What is it?
Sister Qingyan has arrived.
She wants to meet Mr. Lai.
Ren Qingyan?
Alright, I got it.
You go back to work.
Is she the famous Ren Qingyan?
I'm her fan!
Can you let me see her in person?
Just let me take a look at her,
just for one glance!
Jiang Lili.
I won't speak anymore.
Since you want to see her,
then you'll talk to her yourself.
I...
What should I talk about?
Ren Qingyan came to our company is for
getting the female lead of The Journey of the Youth.
You should deal with her.
Okay.
I'll go.
It's on me.
I have the character.
They'll start shooting next week.
Why isn't this contract ready yet?
I'll do my best.
How do you guys doing your jobs?
Hello, sister Xiaoran.
What a bad luck.
I ran into a copycat
early in this morning.
This scene comes once a month.
Last month they dressed the same
and sister Xiaoran forced
Ren Qingyan to change her clothes.
And the month before that,
Sister Xiaoran poured a cup of coffee on her
and ruined that cloth.
What will happen this month?
The light of candle cannot be compete with the light of the moon.
This cloth is made exclusively for you.
I don't deserve to wear this.
She can't be crazy, right?
I don't think it's that simple.
I bet she's making a big scene.
I'm looking for Zhengyi.
Where is he?
Mr. Lai is busy now.
If there's anything, you can ask me.
This project of The Journey of the Youth has been opened.
Every marketing account has listed
all the possible actress candidates.
I don't know if our company
has a specific list of candidates.
We haven't made a specific list,
but there was a list indeed, it has...
Speak carefully, Miss Bi.
Greetings, Mr. Lai.
The information about The Journey of the Youth
must not be disclosed.
Otherwise, you will have to bear all the consequences.
Sorry.
It's fine.
My father is the shareholder of Lemeng.
Do I seem like an outsider to you?
Mr. Ren is
taking over the administrative work of the company.
Everything else remains confidential.
Zhengyi.
In order to celebrate
Lemeng taking down the contract with Global Picture.
My father has set a celebration dinner tonight,
you must come!
Okay, see you tonight.
I told you that
be aware of what you should say
and what you should not say, okay?
Speak and act cautiously!
It's fine.
It's your first time to be the producer.
Mistakes are bound to happen.
Just don't do it next time.
I promised, I won't do that anymore.
[The 26 restaurant]
Mr. Ren, I'll make the first toast.
Ranran.
The first toast belongs to you.
Your hard work
are there for all to see.
Congratulation.
For signing the contract with Global Picture.
Thank you.
I'll drink it up.
Let's drink together.
-Okay. -Good.
Come.
Zhengyi,
we should make the cast of The Journey of the Youth.
My daughter Qingyan is currently available.
She can play a role on the project.
That's right.
Qingyan is a member of our company,
there is no one better than her.
Now that Qingyan has always been played the female lead in recent shows.
What kind of celebration dinner is this?
They are bribing Lai Zhengyi
to ask for a role.
It's not easy for us to have a dinner together and relax.
It's so frustrating if we talk about works.
Here.
I'll make a toast to everyone.
Xiaoran.
You've been working hard lately.
I want to make a toast to you.
I can't drink anymore.
Are you kidding us, Xiaoran?
Everyone knows that you're a heavyweight drinker.
Come on, have a drink with me.
Then I'll drink a little.
Cheers.
Good things should be in pairs.
One more toast to you.
After drinking this one,
our previous misunderstandings
will be gone.
I'm good, I don't need it anymore.
Come on.
Don't pour too much.
I'm a terrible drinker.
Ah, Xiaoran.
What's going on?
I want to pour a glass of wine for her.
But she kept avoiding,
then I poured the wine on her.
It's fine.
I'm sorry, Xiaoran.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Xiaoyan, don't stand still
You two have a drink together.
Zhengyi.
Zhengyi, have a drink.
Here's a toast to you.
Cheers.
[The 26 restaurant]
Sister Xiaoran.
Who... who are you?
I'm Tianyou.
Last time, we went to an event together.
Sister.
Last time we talked about
The Journey of the Youth,
would you leave a role for me?
It's not up to me
to decide who's going to play.
Sister,
it's just a role.
You only need to put one word for me.
It’s not like that...
Don't...
Sister.
Damn it.
How dare you touch my woman?
Mr. Lai.
Are you gonna solve this yourself,
or should I help you with it?
I'm sorry, I apologize.
In the future,
don't let me see you within a ten-mile radius.
Get out!
Woman.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
It's okay.
Jiang Lili.
Sorry...
I'm really sorry.
I lost control.
Where is he?
He's gone.
Come here.
Although we're a fake couple.
Everything we do
will be amplified by the media.
Things like today
can't happen again.
Understood.
Oh my God!
How come that I started my delusions all of a sudden.
Jiang Lili.
You have to restrain yourself.
Let me take a look!
Don't... don't touch my book.
Zhengyi.
We've printed the photos.
Tomorrow we should post these photos online.
Put these photos on the trend for an entire day.
The banquet tonight is a private event.
How did this Li Tianyou
get there?
I heard that he wants to see Bi Xiaoran for a long time.
I did him a favor
out of kindness.
I don't know if I should ask.
What are you
doing all this for?
You've never been in a relationship.
You know nothing about it.
You...
I'll leave now.
Play by yourself.
Lili.
Jiang Lili.
[Ding Dong]
Hello.
Lili, there was an accident.
Get online quickly!
Wait a moment.
[Ding Dong]
The woman cheats on the man
and the man comes out of the closet.
[Bi Xiaoran, the producer of Lemeng Pictures]
This...
[was photographed having dinner at a restaurant with the new generation of actor, Li Tianyou.]
Isn't this the Li Tianyou as yesterday?
Mr. Lai.
[The woman cheats and the man comes out of the closet]
Lately, the celebrity boss Lai Zhengyi
and his assistant Xiao He have been photographed
kissing in the car by a passerby.
It can't be.
Morning, good morning.
I think I'm not late.
The reporters didn't give you a hard time, I supposed?
No, no...
I came through the back door.
There was no reporters.
How can you be laughing?
At first we made you a couple
is for catching eyes for the company.
Well, let's see.
Now, you two are giving the company a bad name.
Th-the bad
influence is
so strong
that our stocks are dr-dro...
dropping! -The stocks are dropping!
That's right, they are dropping!
You two represent our company.
Even if each of you have your own private life,
you should take care.
Now you made a scene like this.
It's not good for everyone.
No...
It's not like that.
There was a misunderstanding between Li Tianyou and I.
We can come forward
and clarify ourselves.
Is this your first day in the entertainment industry?
Do you think clarifying yourself is gonna work?
It will only make it worse.
Ex-explain...
Mr. Chen, you're being too kind.
You are my senior.
You don't have to call me sister.
Ex-explaination is a... co-cover up!
And a cover up is the tr-truth!
Do you understand?
I have an idea.
Let's take down this trend first,
and put some other trends to cover it up.
But by doing so
is equal to acquiescing in such a thing.
How about this?
Let us live together.
What?
Mr. Lai, think carefully.
All we can do now
is to play it by ear.
No.
What do you think?
What a smart move, Mr. Lai.
I hope those negative influences can be eliminated.
It's not appropriate.
Very nice.
It's a deal.
Can't... can't...
Mr. Chen has something to say.
You also think it's inappropriate, right?
Let's find another way.
Can't be better.
Do you think so?
Right.
Yes.
Leak the information of us living together.
The more people who know, the better.
So you are doing all of this
to abduct this girl
home with you?
This is not an abduction.
I was forced to do so.
Huh.
My pen.
In ancient times, Hua Mulan joined the army in place of her father.
Nowadays, the twin sister has to live with someone for her sister.
What kind of world is this?
Think of it as living in a dorm?
A dormitory?
There is no co-ed dormitory.
Sister.
I used think you were God's favorite one,
or Goddess Nuwa's favorite.
You have a large fan base,
getting both fame and fortune.
But now I realized,
it's not an easy task to be Bi Xiaoran.
It's so difficult!
I've only been here for a few days,
now I'm going to
living with someone else.
Sister,
you became like this because of me.
But I don't even have the courage to take the risk for you.
Jiang Lili,
what a coward!
Sister, don't worry.
You've worked so hard to get what you got,
and I will do my best to keep it for you.
It's just living with someone else.
It's not a big deal.
Mr. Lai, I'm coming.
You got this through.
For my sister,
I will do anything.
Smile for me.
Smile?
That's a good angle.
Come on, take a few more photos.
Staged photography, I understand.
Hurry up! Quickly, quickly!
Ah?
This acting is so authentic.
Fine, fine.
Then I'll make a sacrifice.
Wow, big news!
I get it.
I understand.
What are you doing?
I'm talking about you.
Your hair stuck to your face.
Huh?
Jiang Lili.
You are so dirty and stupid.
Suit yourself.
Make yourself at home.
If I have a house
like this someday,
I can wake up laughing.
This could be your house,
if you want.
I don't mind having one more person on my household register.
What? Household register?
I was joking.
Don't be nervous.
From now on, let's get along as friends.
Your room is on the second floor.
My room is on the third floor.
We don't interfere with each other.
If you really mind,
then I'll try to limit
my public activities in the future.
No, no, no.
I don't mind.
This is your house.
How can I limit your activities?
Suit yourself.
Let me help you with your luggage.
I'll do it myself.
It's fine.
No, no, no.
[The CEO's Indulgent Love for His Beloved Wife]
The CEO's Deep Depth of Love with Supreme Tenderness.
The CEO Has A Way of Hooking Up.
[The CEO's Indulgent Love for His Beloved Wife]
It’s not like that...
The CEO's Favorite.
These are nothing.
[The Beloved Wife of the CEO]
The Beloved Wife of the CEO.
It’s not like that...