♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Those underages may watch
with a guardian's permission.]
[All content is computer-animated,
please do not imitate in real life.]
[Previous episode]
San,
only you
can break through even more.
Send someone to contact Tian Dou Empire.
Mobilize all of our troops
to fight against the Martial Soul Empire!
Yes.
Haishen Hall?
Tang San,
how dare you?
Senior Bo Sai Xi wants to kill me!
Hang on until the end and combine as one!
I now see that the God of the Ocean
made the right choice to choose you.
God of the Ocean Seventh Test.
Draw the magical weapon,
God of the Ocean's Trident.
[Episode 199]
-Greetings, Seniors.
Greetings.
Haishen Hall is sacred
and must not be tainted.
Only the test attendances are allowed to enter.
All others must wait outside.
Please.
Master,
with the command
of General Dai Wei Si, Xing Luo Empire
captured two of our
important mining towns.
Go!
Tian Dou Empire also captured
an important lode.
We lost about 1,500 troops
in this battle.
Useless!
Mining is fundamental
to a country's future.
Our empire already lacks mineral resources
and we finally turned things
around recently.
With our current military power,
even the alliance between Tian Dou
and Xing Luo can't pose a threat.
But this failure might ruin
all of our previous efforts!
Master, please don't be angry.
I will immediately send City Guard
Soul Masters to recapture the land.
I don't want to own something temporarily,
I want their everlasting obedience.
More importantly,
no one can taint the foundation
of Martial Soul Empire's development.
Send my orders. Three days from today,
gather all the troops.
Yes.
All the military preparations were for this day.
This continent will be mine to rule.
Trident Mark
and the God of the Ocean's Trident
are sensing each other.
It feels like a call.
Greetings, Senior.
The Head Flamen has waited for long.
The scent here is deep,
sacred, and untainted.
This is the Haishen Hall.
This is the magical weapon,
God of the Ocean's Trident.
Tang San.
From now on,
you will officially begin God's test.
Tang San.
What's wrong?
It seems like even Senior Bo Sai Xi
didn't sense the God of the Ocean's
spiritual communication with me.
Nothing.
Before the Seventh Test begins,
let me tell you
the God of the Ocean's story.
Do you know how vast the ocean is?
It's about four times bigger
than the Douluo Continent.
That's why there were many more species
living in the ocean than on land.
Long ago, in order to fight
for power over the ocean,
war broke out between
the different ocean tribes.
Numerous tribes were hurt and killed,
but nobody wanted to stop the war.
Finally,
an extremely talented, level-99
ocean soul master appeared.
He held a trident and spent his life
traveling to every corner of the ocean.
He ended numerous battles
and saved all the ocean tribes.
And so
he became the God of the Ocean.
Yes.
The trust of tens of thousands
of ocean soul beasts and soul masters
created the Power of Trust,
allowing him to break to level 100
and become the God of the Ocean.
This is also the hardest way
to become a god.
Senior,
besides the Power of Trust,
are there other ways of becoming a god?
In theory,
as long as a soul master reaches level 100,
they will become a god.
But to reach level 100 from level 99
takes at least a thousand years.
Humans cannot live long enough to do so.
But there is a shortcut.
By heritage.
Receive the approval of an elder god,
and inherit their status.
Does that mean you've already won
the God of the Ocean's approval?
Xue, do you know the legend
of how the Angel became a god?
Not before.
The Angel was also a normal human
before becoming a god.
Back then, people lived under the torture
of sin and disease.
The Angel used a holy sword
to clear the world's sin and disease.
From then on, the people
were freed from darkness and reborn.
She won the trust of all
and became a god.
But it's a pity that even until now,
the remaining sin of the world
is still secretly accumulating its power,
trying to drag the people
back to darkness again.
The holy sword that the Angel left behind
is her hope for the Angel Tribe
to protect its honor.
Go forth, Xue.
This is your Seventh Test,
pull out the Holy Sword of Angel.
I will definitely pull out
the Holy Sword of Angel
and become the strongest in the world
to defend the Angel Tribe's honor.
That's right.
You, who received
the God of the Ocean's Nine Tests,
are the one chosen
by the God of the Ocean.
Once you've passed
the God of the Ocean's Nine Tests,
you will inherit
the God of the Ocean's position
and become the new God of the Ocean
to rule over all the subjects
of the ocean.
I will definitely extract
the God of the Ocean's Trident
and live up to everyone's expectations.
Tang San,
your true test from God is next.
Not only do you need to extract
the God of the Ocean's Trident,
but you also need to win its approval.
Win its approval?
I will.
[Soul Land]
Is this an illusion?
The more you pursue the light,
the more likely you are to be burned by the light.
Who is it?
Can you see?
Darkness is born from light.
Sneaky you, get out!
Face me with some dignity.
I have been looking forward
to this moment.
Finally, we meet today.
But light swallows the darkness.
The absolute light you pursue
has never existed.
Whether or not it exists is up to me!
Her face looks exactly the same as mine.
Is she my actual examiner
for the Seventh Test?
The game has begun.
I can't fly at night!
Fifth Soul Skill, Sacred Sword!
Sacred Sword.
I know everything about you.
The Holy Sword Platform switches
between night and day. But I can't fly at night.
She is the exact opposite.
In that case,
I need to force her into the light.
Sure.
You may have a try.
Six wings?
Its scent is heavy and deep,
repressed like the lowest depths
of the ocean.
The Trident is inserted
in the center point of Haishen Mountain.
The entire mountain exists for it.
So hot!
Hot like lava!
The Xuan Yu Hand is ineffective.
It looks like the God of the Ocean's Trident
wants me to use my own power.
That hurts!
My soul is about to be set on fire!
Hold on, you can't let go.
If you let go now,
then
you won't have the right
to hold onto this weapon again!
It's getting hotter.
The heat is still spreading.
My invincible body can't stop this.
It's as if my soul
is being burnt to nothing.
Jiubao Boosts!
Rules shall not be broken.
Dignity is not for you to trample on.
Do you want to take on my mantle
and become the Head Flamen of Haishen Island?
Do you want to know my past
with Tang Chen?
Scan this QR code.
Follow Soul Land's official WeChat.
I'll share with you
the untold secret of Haishen Island.
[Scan the QR code
and follow Soul Land's official WeChat]
[to witness the rise of the Shrek Seven Devils]
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 199 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1774 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 3004]
[Total scene: 71832]
[Total CGI: 31763]
[Total plan of action scene: 14679]
[Total scene model: nearly 615]
[Total character model: nearly 1125]
[Total props model: 13488]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolors♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one
I dreamed to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
The God of the Ocean's power
exists because of its will to protect!
Come.
Fall into the darkness with me.
The power of darkness is way purer than the light.
The more I transfer
the Light of the God of the Ocean into it,
the lighter the God of the Ocean's Trident
becomes!
We will become
the strongest in the world.
[Soul Land - The Legend of the Tang's Clan]
[New Episode on Every Saturday at 10 AM (UTC+08:00)]