SNOWDROP
ALL CHARACTERS AND EVENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 5
We're covering
the dorm's front door. Over.
We're approaching too as I speak. Over.
Lim Soo-ho!
Drop the guns!
Lim Soo-ho.
You're surrounded.
Stay away.
I'll shoot her.
Come down.
Stay away!
The students will get hurt.
Hey, it's all right.
Don't be scared.
It's all right.
Drop the guns.
Do it in three seconds, or she's dead.
One.
Two.
Lim Soo-ho.
Three.
Comrade!
Detective Jang.
Who shoots during a civil defense drill?
Don't tell me
war's broken out.
Hang in there, Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee, just hang in there.
You'll be okay.
Damn it.
God damn bastards…
Stop it!
I've run out of ammo.
-Hold fire!
Hold fire, you idiots!
Those bastards.
Ballistic shields, go!
Damn it.
-Aim guns!
We need backup inside the dorm.
We need backup.
The fourth unit, ETA one minute.
Shield unit, advance.
Watch out!
Mr. Lee!
He has grenades!
Drop the guns.
Lower your guns.
Lim Soo-ho.
She's just a student.
Get out.
All of you!
All units, withdraw.
Wait.
You're in charge, right?
You stay.
He's been shot,
but you'll hold him hostage?
Listen carefully.
If you attack us,
I'll kill him first.
All right.
I'll stay here,
but let the students go.
Are you crazy? You've been shot!
You hypocritical bastards.
Get out.
I'll never leave without you.
He'll never be able to escape anyway.
-Capture him if you can.
-Sir.
Go now.
Get out.
No…
No, I can't! Let go of me!
-All units, withdraw!
-No!
Let go of me, you bastards!
-Call for medics now!
-Many are injured.
-Let go!
I have to go back!
-Let go of me!
-Get the transportation ready!
Come with me.
What about Professor Han?
The other members will take him safely.
What do we do now?
We must get
to the rendezvous point by 22:00.
We'll get out of here
and join the other agents at all costs.
I'll block all of the doors.
Gather all the hostages
in the cafeteria on the second floor.
Yes, sir.
Come out.
Now!
Come out here!
Move it!
Move faster.
Faster.
Hey, you there.
Move it.
I'm coming.
Hey.
Come out here.
Move it!
You too, idiot. Now!
This is crazy. God damn it.
There are men injured. We need medics.
Black Tiger's been shot.
And he's taken hostage with students.
We need more backup right now. Over.
What do you mean?
Are you saying
they're holding people hostage
in the dorm? Over.
Taedong River 1 threatened
with grenades, so we couldn't help it.
But there are just three of them.
It won't be hard to take them down. Over.
Stand by.
Stay put until I give you orders.
-Over and out.
-There are men injured.
We need medics.
Hold people hostage
in the middle of Seoul?
What, do these bastards have a death wish?
Wait a minute.
If the chairman finds out
that I've sent the forces…
Damn it.
Ms. Choi.
Don't you know I'm fitting Ms. Hong?
It's your husband. I told him,
but he still wanted to speak to you.
It must be something urgent. Go ahead.
Excuse me, then.
What is it this time?
What? Spies?
Slow down. What's going on?
In the Hosu Women's University dorm,
Northern spies are holding people hostage!
Holding people hostage?
In the Hosu University dorm?
Wait. Hold on.
Whether he'll ascend into the sky
with a magical bead
or die from falling off a horse,
it all depends on 13 young virgins.
Oh, my God.
Then Eun Chang-su
is destined to become king?
What the hell are you talking about?
If our chairman finds out
that I sent the forces, I'll catch hell!
Honey.
Listen to me very carefully.
Eun Chang-su might be able
to become a future presidential candidate
instead of Nam Tae-il.
What?
The chairman might?
How do you know that?
This fortuneteller said…
Never mind. It's a long story.
Anyway, you mustn't get
on Eun Chang-su's bad side from now on.
Then.
What happened is that Gang-mu
went to catch him against my orders.
Of course. It's true
that bastard never listens to you.
Yes, it is! Wait and see.
Gang-mu, that bastard…
I'll teach him a proper lesson this time.
I'm going to Nam Mountain.
Get the car ready.
You can't pull that out.
If you do, we'll all die.
Hold on.
If you move, it'll explode.
Don't move.
Oh, no.
Stay still.
Don't move.
Move!
Keep your heads down!
Stay in line.
-Move faster.
-Stay in line!
What? There's more?
Move faster!
Keep up!
Go in a single line.
Eyes on the head
of the person in front of you.
Move faster. Keep up.
Move it.
In a single line.
Keep your heads down.
Walk.
Hey, you!
Keep up.
Keep your heads down!
Keep your heads down.
Move it, you bastard.
Put your head on the wall.
Now, you bastard.
Stay quiet with your head down.
I can't find Ms. Pi.
Has anyone seen the hall director?
Maybe she ran alone to save her skin.
-Seriously? No way.
-She abandoned us?
What do we do?
Quiet!
Lim Soo-ho!
Drop the guns in three seconds,
or she's dead.
Ms. Pi.
Hey!
Who are you?
What's this?
Are you sure you searched thoroughly?
Yes, I searched every floor.
Where have you been?
I'm the hall director here.
Do you think you guys know
about this building better than I do?
Shut up!
You little…
Ms. Pi.
Hush. Stop crying
and pull yourselves together.
Even spider webs can become
really strong when put together.
Keep in line!
You.
And you.
-Move!
-You.
Keep your heads down!
Stand by the windows.
Why? Why do they
have to stand by the windows?
Shut your mouth.
Don't be scared.
They're making you stand by the windows
so that they won't be attacked.
Hey.
You think that'll keep you safe?
You obviously stand no chance.
Since it's a counterespionage op,
military forces will be sent here.
It will be hundreds of
special forces soldiers…
and just three of you.
On top of that, you're injured.
Are you sure you can even hold out?
Wouldn't it be better to just surrender?
You're the one who shot me, aren't you?
If anything goes wrong,
I'll kill you first.
Stand by the windows!
You three! Move!
Move!
You stand over there!
Don't look back.
From now on,
I'll kill anyone who annoys me.
Understood?
Hostages?
Oh, my goodness.
In the Hosu University dorm?
Yes.
I thought it'd be impossible for
13 people to die unless war broke out.
What if 13 young virgins really die?
Watch what you say!
They're holding students hostage.
Shouldn't you be more worried about them?
How could someone in your position
say that?
I…
I apologize, ma'am.
I just thought
someone charismatic and noble like you
should be the future First Lady.
I was just worried, Ms. Cho.
No, you got it wrong. Just wrong!
It's not important for me
to become the First Lady.
What's important is
for my husband to become president.
You better stop being so thoughtless,
or I'll switch shops!
Wait a minute.
What the…
Both of them must take me for a pushover.
This is so annoying.
PATIENT TRANSPORT
Close it.
MILITARY OPERATION
DO NOT CROSS
-Step back.
-What's going on?
Are my roommates okay?
Then we can't go into the form?
No, a military op is being carried out.
So please just go home
and wait until further notice.
Hey, wait! Tell us what's going on?
Yes, ma'am.
Did you meet Yeong-ro?
Are you with her now?
No, ma'am.
I see.
Then she must be still in the dorm, right?
I'm aware of that.
Don't worry, and just come back here.
How dare they attack the university dorm?
Hosu Women's University
is where our chairman's daughter--
This is Mr. Kim. Are you there, Galaxy?
Galaxy standing by.
Among the hostages, there's a freshman
English Literature major named Eun…
Eun… Yes, Yeong-ro.
Check if Eun Yeong-ro is in there.
We're still putting together a list.
We must take out the takers first!
She's Mr. Eun's daughter.
Let me know once confirmed.
And stand by for now. Over.
Hang in there, Mr. Lee.
What are we waiting for?
We must rescue Mr. Lee.
Go check if there's an Eun Yeong-ro
among the hostages.
Eun Yeong-ro?
Who is that?
Number one's daughter. Mr. Eun's daughter.
God, this is crazy.
If they find out, we'll be in trouble.
We should extract her before they do.
First, keep it confidential
over the radio.
And get a secure line to the dorm.
A line directly from HQ too.
Yes, ma'am.
And wiretap the whole building.
Ammunitions go over there.
Hurry up!
Three hostages by the windows.
There are booby traps everywhere,
so it won't be easy to penetrate.
All units, stand by. There are explosives.
So the Northern team Taedong River 1 leads
just left the Port of Incheon
with Professor Han?
Finally!
As soon as he arrives in the North,
our ship carrying 100 million dollars
will head for Whiskey, November,
two, zero, two, three,
one, four, eight, one.
It'll rendezvous with your men.
As soon as we receive the money,
we'll make Professor Han
officially disclose
that the opposition party
is running for president
with our great Supreme Leader's funding.
You demanded four times
the original price for Operation Phoenix.
You already got 100 million dollars.
And you'll get 100 million more
once the ship gets there. As for the rest,
we'll send it to you
once you hold the press conference.
After the election is over,
feel free to come visit me.
If you want to hold the position for long,
you should visit here at least once.
If I visit there myself, it'll look bad.
Anyway, we'll be waiting for good news.
It wouldn't hurt to be in close touch with
them. Why did you have to
turn it down so coldly?
It's almost done.
Once Han appears on Korean Central TV,
the game's over.
We've jumped through hoops for this,
so let's have nice dinner tonight.
We'll pop the champagne a bit early.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Mr. Eun.
Mr. An wants to talk to you.
Chief An?
Let him in.
I wonder why that dung fly
came to see you.
Sir.
What is it?
In the Hosu University dorm,
Northern spies are holding people hostage.
A hostage situation?
Lee Gang-mu disobeyed your direct orders
and raided the dorm with military forces.
Wait. Are you sure they're spies?
According to intercepted radio messages,
he must've been sure of it.
How dare those communists make a mess
here in this day and age?
Call CFC right now and
mobilize all the Capital Defense forces!
Tell them to squash them without trace!
But I don't think
Gang-mu went there without a good reason.
Well, he went there
to catch Taedong River 1.
But Taedong River 1 just left Incheon…
So the students are being held hostage?
What do you keep asking him for?
What if articles are released
that say Northern spies are
holding students hostage?
People will be shocked.
We've put all this together, but if this
gets out, it'll all be for nothing.
We must be in the spotlight!
What if we suppress them by force
and the students get hurt?
Will you take responsibility?
Why are you so slow?
What I'm saying is
Han's press conference must happen first!
Anyway, it's under my jurisdiction,
so go pop the champagne by yourself.
This is exactly your problem!
You always dilly-dally,
and that's a liability to us!
If our plan goes wrong,
it's all on you.
I understand.
It's me.
Is Yeong-ro there?
I sent Mr. Kim to pick her up at the dorm,
but he couldn't even go near the dorm,
so he's coming back without her.
What if something happens to Yeong-ro?
She'll be okay, right?
I'll take care of it, so don't worry.
Okay.
Sir,
it's been confirmed
that your daughter is
being held hostage too.
Are you sure?
We've been keeping an eye on her
since she started college as Choi asked.
And upon hearing about the hostage
situation, we checked it first.
I swear on my life
that I'll rescue your daughter first.
Once the Capital Defense forces mobilize,
the press will find out.
Rescue all of the students
and kill
the spies if necessary.
Yes, sir.
We'll be discreet
and take care of it
without anyone knowing.
Also, sir…
On top of
disobeying your orders and
acting rashly to catch Taedong River 1,
Gang-mu's been shot
and is now being held hostage.
The way I see it,
Gang-mu is solely responsible for this--
Hurry.
It's not the time to decide
who's responsible.
You're right. Right away, sir.
-I will save your daughter!
-Get out!
Keep your eyes shut!
Keep them shut!
Don't come out of the curtain.
It's all your fault. This wouldn't be
happening if you hadn't hidden that spy!
That spy was Yeong-ro's partner, right?
Then has she known he was a spy all along?
Of course, she has.
They're dating after all.
Shut your mouth and stop talking nonsense.
Why is it nonsense?
I was right all along.
You should've let me call the cops.
It's not the time
to decide who's to blame.
Just think about how to get out safely.
Safely?
We might all end up dying in here!
Who is it?
Who's crying?
Be quiet.
Excuse me.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Me too.
Excuse me.
What is it?
Could I go to the bathroom?
I need to, too.
Don't.
Shouldn't we
let them go to the bathroom at least?
Close your eyes unless you want to die!
Close your eyes!
Look. It's a natural process.
How are we supposed to hold it?
I told you to shut it!
Do it. Do it here!
It's all your fault.
What on earth is going on?
Don't tell me you're the Northern spy.
A Northern spy?
Goodness, they say
you can't judge a book by its cover.
Are you really
a spy from the North? Tell me.
Then Yeong-ro's been fooled too?
How do you know this spy?
What kind of trouble
did you get yourself into?
You're the one
getting in trouble all the time!
-Goodness.
-Hey.
I don't know what happened
between you two,
but I have nothing to do with it.
So please let me go. Then I'll go back
the way I came very quietly.
Okay.
So if you'd just sent me the money,
I wouldn't have had to come here!
Close your eyes.
Breathe quietly.
Excuse me.
What?
He's bleeding.
Can I just stop the bleeding?
Are you crazy?
Lie back down.
Lie down!
He's bleeding. Let me stop it.
Shut up and lie down.
Eun Yeong-ro.
My God, what's going on?
Oh, my. What's happening?
My goodness.
Comrade.
What are you doing?
She wouldn't listen to me.
He's hurt.
Can't you see him bleeding?
We should give him first aid at least.
Let me go get the first aid kit.
-Are you crazy? Sit down!
-Wait.
You're hurt too.
Lead the way.
Are you really a spy
from the North?
Did I really
save a spy's life?
I'm warning you.
Stop being so nosy.
Or you'll get yourself killed.
Mr. Eun,
the man leading the hostage situation
in the dorm
is Taedong River 1.
Are you sure it's him?
What's the status?
Okay.
Put me through to Mr. Nam…
No, never mind.
DIRECTOR EUN CHANG-SU
This is Pyongyang.
Go ahead.
Mr. Lim.
I hear Taedong River 1 is holding people
hostage in the middle of Seoul.
Are you sure he's with Professor Han
right now?
What is this?
Why does this kind of thing
happen every time?
He was supposed to join the others
after retrieving our weapons.
Your men must've chased him!
Can't you do your job properly?
You are one to talk!
This is the Republic of Korea.
Did you think our agents
would just get out of the way?
He should've been good enough
to give our agents the slip.
Look, Eun!
Don't try to turn this around on me!
How dare you!
If you even lay a finger on our agents,
the deal is off!
Forget about the election!
Do everything in your power to get Taedong
River 1 out and send him to the North.
To us, he's more important
than the president of South Korea!
Understood?
So Soo-hyeok's been captured?
Did you call for me?
We'll head for Hosu University
in a minute.
With a full security detail.
Eun Chang-su himself?
But why? They're just small-fry spies.
His daughter is in the dorm?
After falling for his new wife,
he sent his son to the army
and daughter to the dorm.
What a funny guy he is.
But still,
he's the director of ANSP.
How could he go to the scene himself?
He should be pushing his agents to rescue
the others first. What the hell is he…
What?
Are you sure it's Taedong River 1?
Okay.
Keep me posted on Eun's every move.
All right.
I need a shirt.
Where's my shirt?
Darn it.
He didn't even report to me on it.
God damn it! Those damn communists
can't do anything right!
Damn it.
Do you have to go too?
Well, I don't have to…
No! Get it together!
I have to go! Where's my jacket?
My jacket!
You're the one who hid him, aren't you?
I'm sorry. I swear I didn't know then.
Don't be. It's all right.
You didn't know.
Helping without knowing
doesn't count as harboring a spy.
Oh, no.
Does it hurt a lot?
Close your eyes!
Hey.
Taedong River 1.
So this is how we finally meet.
To catch you,
I've been to Berlin, Munich, Frankfurt,
and Warsaw.
In Warsaw,
I almost died while chasing you.
Hey, stop right there!
Stop!
Stop right there!
You're a veteran.
Isn't losing Park Geum-cheol enough?
Do you want to lose the rest
while fighting a losing battle?
You must've only fought winning battles.
You see, I have so many things
I want to hear from you.
I have to avenge Jin-seong's death too.
But I'm so worried
that the military forces
might kill you
before I could do any of that.
NO OUTSIDERS ALLOWED
Not to break in?
Yes, sir. We won't break in rashly.
It might take quite long,
but we must kill--
You can't kill them.
All three of them must be unscathed.
Capture them no matter what.
I see. I understand, sir.
What's going on?
Why must the spies be unscathed?
We need to rescue his daughter
and the spies too? I mean, capture them.
Looks like we're the only ones suffering.
-Hello, sir.
-Open it!
We'll break in from these three points.
Hello, sir.
It's been 3 hours and 18 minutes
since he was shot. 3 hours and 18 minutes!
You think I've been slacking off?
I ran over here
as soon as I reported to Mr. Eun.
Let's break in right away.
There are just three of them,
and one is injured--
That's enough!
Attention.
From now on,
I'll lead
the operation.
Anything about this operation
can't get out of here.
So make sure not to let the press
release any articles about gunfire
or a women's university dormitory.
Yes, sir.
This operation's
top priority
is to rescue our director's daughter.
So right now,
set up a field phone in front of
the dorm and get me a megaphone.
Get me a bulletproof vest.
Lim Soo-ho.
Lim Soo-ho. Can you hear me?
I'm the person in charge of this scene.
We just put a field phone
in front of the front door of the dorm.
From now on, I'm the only person
you can talk to.
Lim Soo-ho. I know you're listening.
He's like a scared street dog.
I am a man of my word.
If you guarantee
the hostages' safety,
we'll guarantee your safety
at all costs.
We must negotiate with them
to get out of here.
I repeat.
Right now,
I need you to cover me.
come pick up the field phone
and talk with me to negotiate.
Is there any response?
Not yet.
I don't think I can hold it anymore.
You have to. Hang in there.
I need to pee. My goodness.
Hey, how about
you pee in your pants little by little?
Or just wet your pants.
It's all right.
-It's not embarrassing.
-Should I?
The grenade.
There's a grenade.
No… No!
-I shouldn't move! No!
-Wait!
No!
Oh, my.
You bastard! Why did you pee on me?
You.
Go to the front door.
Go with him.
Stay here.
Yes, sir.
God damn it! That prick!
Right now,
come pick up the field phone.
Lim Soo-ho.
I am warning you again…
You'll see a phone outside.
Go fetch it.
Pardon?
You mean, me?
Do anything stupid,
and your girlfriend dies.
Gwang-tae.
I love you.
You're the only one for me.
You know that, right?
It won't be that hard.
Just walk slowly there and bring it here.
Okay?
Go fetch it now!
Now.
NO OUTSIDERS ALLOWED
Someone's coming out.
Raise your shields.
That's not Lim Soo-ho.
I think he's a student.
All right.
Don't worry.
We will not shoot you.
Slowly,
take the phone and go back inside.
Gwang-tae, come on!
Lim Soo-ho's behind the door.
Really?
Who fired the gun? Who was it?
Hold fire!
We shouldn't shoot them.
Order them not to fire back.
Raise it! And get down. Lower your body!
Raise the shields!
Don't shoot.
Tell them not to fire back.
We shouldn't fire back. Hold fire!
Pick it up now.
Raise the shields!
All right. Pull back!
-Pull back!
Protect me! God damn it.
Keep the shields close!
-Pull back! Hurry up!
-Block me!
-Sir, you should wear the vest.
-Out of my way!
Do you have a death wish or something?
Look. I know you're desperate,
but are you crazy?
I know you don't care
about Mr. Lee at all.
It was the perfect chance to get him.
Once we get him, the other two will--
What if!
What if the other two shoot the hostages?
And what if Mr. Eun's daughter dies?
What will you do?
Are you the one who shot at them?
No, I'm not, sir. It was Han-na.
She was trying to save Gang-mu.
Don't you know our agents must put
our people's lives
before our colleagues' lives?
Jang Han-na,
you're banned from this scene.
Until ordered otherwise,
go stay in the office.
Mr. Eun. Sir!
I'll be expelled if I have to.
But let me stay at the scene.
Please! Let me stay here!
-Get her out!
-Mr. Eun!
Mr. Eun!
Sir.
I risked being sniped at
to give them a field phone--
Everyone, out!
Get up, guys.
Why? Will you take care of it by yourself?
Were you going to handle it
without even telling me?
That bastard's supposed
to be on the West Sea now.
But why is he in the dorm?
Explain.
My stomach…
My stomach hurts.
Yeong-ro, what's wrong?
Yeong-ro.
Didn't I say I'd kill you
if you said anything?
Look. She says she's in pain.
How could you do that--
Didn't you hear the gunfire earlier?
Your stomach hurts?
Are you faking pain
even after hearing gunfire?
Answer me!
Are you seriously faking it?
My back! My back hurts too.
No, I'm okay. Don't worry.
Gosh.
I'm fine. It's because
I've been lying down for so long.
Come in.
Why did they get changed?
Aren't they Seol-hui's pajamas?
-Look at them.
-What's with them?
Don't laugh.
We almost died.
We need to kill one of the hostages now.
Just wait.
This is the director of ANSP.
Am I speaking to Lim Soo-ho?
You suggested talking then fired a gun?
It was a mistake.
We didn't mean to shoot you.
A mistake?
Listen very carefully.
One of the hostages will die right now.
Because you made a mistake.
Aren't you supposed to rendezvous
at Yankee, Mike,
six, two, one, four,
seven, one, two, eight?
Don't worry.
Your agents will accomplish
their mission without a problem.
The person in charge who sent you guys
to Seoul is director Lim Ji-rok, right?
If that's true, just trust me.
We have no intention
of harming you.
We want to send
all of you back to the North safely.
Exactly 30 minutes from now,
come out through an emergency exit
in basement two.
What did those bastards say?
To come out through an emergency exit
in 30 minutes.
They say they'll send us
back to the North safely.
How can we ever trust those bastards?
I'll have to check if it's true first.
Do you really need to check to know?
It's obviously a trap.
It must be a put-up job, right?
"They're supposed
to be on the West Sea now,
but why are they in the dorm?"
And he said
something will all be for nothing.
On top of that, he ordered me to capture
them, saying they must be unscathed.
You're right.
Eun Chang-su must've arranged something
with the North secretly for the election.
What do I do?
It's against the National Security Law
not to investigate
when I'm aware of the charges.
Of course, Code 1 must've ordered them!
God, you're so frustrating.
Why are you so slow?
I mean,
how much longer
will you stay an errand boy?
And how much longer
must I stay a maid for them?
I don't know!
Whether or not you save Eun's daughter,
I don't care!
Charlotte.
Charlotte?
What is it, Ms. Kim?
"Whether or not you save Eun's daughter"?
What does that mean?
I guess you haven't heard yet.
Mr. Eun's daughter
is being held hostage
in the Hosu University dorm.
Oh, my God.
Really?
Then he must be desperate
to save his daughter,
forgetting about becoming president.
Yes.
Ms. Hong must be really anxious right now.
She can neither stop him
nor encourage him.
You're right.
I should go comfort her.
Cancel today's mahjong game.
Pardon?
What are you doing? Come with me.
Right. Of course.
If this song plays on Pyongyang channel,
it means the instruction has changed.
Remember that and obey the new order.
I will read out the 2,204th message.
Assistant Team Six.
This is a message for Assistant Team Six.
76,373.
20,100. 36,116.
59,789.
40,251. 20,073. That'll be all.
COOPERATE
WITH
SOUTH KOREA
The potatoes from our hometown
are the best.
Those from the South are too soft.
Would you like some potatoes?
Have some.
I keep having diarrhea.
Yeong-u.
Switch shifts for me just this once.
-Oh, my.
-God, you punk.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA MARINES
You're an administrative clerk,
but you want to be on a coast patrol boat?
Private Kim isn't feeling well.
So I'll fill in for him.
Really?
Okay, then. Be safe.
Salute.
I thought he was just one of those who
have powerful dads, but he's quite nice.
His father may be the director of ANSP,
but he's a Marine just like any of us.
It's impossible
the party has given such an order.
But it's true that
the Pyongyang channel told us
to cooperate with the South.
The broadcasting might've been fabricated.
They shot at us after suggesting talking.
What if this is another trap?
As you say, it might be a trap they set.
But what if it is the party's instruction?
If we disobey the orders,
it won't stop at our deaths.
Our families in our hometown
will suffer too.
You still want to
ignore their instructions?
The director of ANSP knew
the coordinates of our rendezvous point,
as well as the person
in charge of this mission.
But how could he have found out?
Our country must've made a deal with him
to save our lives.
As you know,
our party would never abandon us.
Understood, sir.
I'll do as you say
no matter what.
SERVING WINDOW
Exactly 15 minutes from now,
we'll escape through the emergency exit.
It's too foggy to see anyone coming.
Will we even be able to meet?
Isn't it time?
-They're coming.
-Good.
The sound is different.
Reporting.
Checking the reception.
Wild Goose 2, this is Stone 1. Over.
Stone 1, this is Wild Goose 2. Clear.
Wild Goose 2,
we'll proceed with reception, over.
We pulled back the SWAT team
and only placed your security detail
in front of the exit.
As soon as they come out,
we'll get them into the car
and get out of here.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey.
Do you think they'll come out?
Do you really think so?
I wouldn't trust you if I were them.
Don't you think?
There must be no one in front of the exit.
Pull back all of your guys.
We'll come out through the exit
in exactly three minutes.
Good. They'll come out in three minutes.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, you're so lucky, Eun.
We avoided the worst-case scenario.
I'm glad we're putting an end
to this case safely.
Deepest congratulations, sir.
Your ship is in the restricted area.
-Please go back to the fishery zone now.
-Damn it!
Your ship is in the restricted area.
Please go back to the fishery zone now.
This is the restricted area!
We know that. Our engine
broke down, so we've been drifting here.
Hey, go check if it's working now.
Okay.
We're almost done, so we'll leave soon.
Sorry.
-Report that it's a Korean boat.
-Yes, sir.
-At ease.
It's done. It's been fixed. We'll go now.
Thank you.
Do you need help?
No, it's been fixed.
-Get ready.
-Okay.
Hey! Come back in here!
Damn it.
Help me! Please!
Signalman!
Pull back!
Hurry!
What?
An engagement near Udo Island?
Udo Island?
What's the exact location?
What about the damage on our side?
Okay. Get back to me
as soon as you find out more.
Wait. This can't be…
It must not be
the ship for the spies, right?
Our ship hit and sank it.
God damn it!
Now…
Plan B is the only option now.
They're coming.
Everyone, retreat.
Stop.
Eung-cheol!
Are you okay?
We must kill them all.
Are you telling me to commit murder?
No, no. It's not murder. It's execution.
To shoot all the hostages dead
and blow ourselves up in a determined way
is the most honorable death for us!
Your life depends on me, your leader.
Don't forget that.
Let's just go in and eliminate them all!
What if all the hostages are killed?
I'll deal with the communist jerks,
so you stay out of it, scaredy-cat.
If you feel bad for me just a little bit,
let them go. Please.
Let them go.
And I'm planning to release you.
This all happened because of her.
Why does she get to leave?
She can't die and I can?
Stop!
You leave.
This is our dorm, you stupid communist!
BONUS
Translated by [Wayne Ryu]
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs