Our Secret
EP10
Hurry up and eat.
I'll take you home after meal.
I don't wanna go back.
Could you let me stay here for one night.
You wish.
You must go home, like it or not.
You're so petty.
Grown up already, ha!
able to run away from home?
Hello.
I
came across Ding Xian down the road.
so I took her to dinner.
Then I walked her home.
Thank you, Siyue.
You're welcome.
Siyue
Xianxian is a bit strange recently.
By the way,
Does Xianxian
have a boyfriend at school?
She didn't mention anything alike to me.
Maybe it's all in my head.
Xianxian has been
particularly rebellious recently.
She keeps a lot of things from me.
I can't help asking.
But I think Ding Xian is quite obedient.
So
you don't have to worry too much.
Please, don't let me keep you.
Take care.
Thank you for sending Xianxian back.
You're welcome.
Goodbye.
Tell me.
What have you done to my daughter?
I'm worried about her.
So I read her diary.
But I didn't say anything.
You just know how to conceal her faults.
Conceal her faults?
You infringed her privacy.
Do you know that?
You can't do this.
Better go cheer her up.
No.
I'm still angry.
You...
You're so stubborn.
Someone says that
when a person can confront loss calmly
and have learned to accept the reality,
his youth
begins to fade.
I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't do well on the exam.
You're not sorry for me.
You should be sorry for yourself.
These are the ones you can usually answer correctly.
How could  you make it all wrong?
That is it.
Go and think it over
Change your seat. Put more efforts on study.
Really?
Did you really fail the exam?
I was too nervous, so I didn't do well on the exam.
All right. Let's change seats.
What's going on?
I sit here?
All right.
I'm fine.
Please pass them on.
On this set of papers are the classic questions from previous years.
Please finish it today.
I'll explain it tomorrow.
Please take it seriously.
An extra point is gained
by getting one more question right.
Please take care
on your way home.
Parents' company is highly recommended.
If your parents can't come,
please go home in groups.
Class's over.
Siyue
Have you ever heard of Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School?
Let me tell you, my friend's brother
was robbed the other day.
That man bullies even children.
It's really scary.
Don't go.
Wait for me.
Don't you go after him?
I don't know what to say to him.
It doesn't matter, just tell the truth.
I'm afraid he'll go tell my aunt if I tell him.
So you're going to stay like this?
So you must help me think of
a good excuse to change the seat.
It's easy.
Just say you can't see the blackboard clearly.
My mom just got me a new pair of glasses.
Just say you're afraid of affecting Zhou Siyue's study.
Frankly speaking,
Song Ziqi affects his study more than me.
Or,
you can say you wanna sit with Kong Shadi.
He certainly won't believe such excuses.
I'm at my wit's end, sorry...
Zhou Siyue
Zhou Siyue is coming.
Didn't he go back?
What a coincidence.
You can't see me.
Order so much delicious food.
Don't order.
Let's sponge.
Please.
It occurs to me that
I have an art class to attend.
I gotta run.
Liar, you don't have any classes at all.
I can't stay here anymore.
Bye. I gotta run.
What's wrong
with you two?
It's okay.
All right.
Enjoy yourself.
Why do you walk so fast?
The teacher said we should
go home quickly after school.
It'll be terrible if we run into Evil Dragon.
Is there nothing you wanna tell me?
Why did you change the seat?
I'm not in good shape this time.
I'll definitely do well in the exam next time.
Can I not change the seat?
Sure.
Let Zhou Siyue come to me.
He has helped you so many times anyway.
So he can help you this time.
Forget it.
Let's go home.
Why do girls suddenly alienate someone?
It means you make her angry.
Who?
But I have no idea what I did wrong.
Girls are angry for no reason.
Kong Shadi is an example.
Who?
So what should I do?
It's easy to make girls happy.
Give her a present.
Who the hell is that?
He hasn't spoken to me all day.
You haven't talked to him either.
I didn't because I didn't find a proper chance.
If you don't talk to him,
someone will.
Why is Yang Chunzi
so close to Siyue?
Haven't you heard that
the boy who is close to her
has gone abroad?
So she starts going to Siyue again.
She always chops and changes.
Cut it out.
Stop taking up the cudgel for her.
Ding Xian hasn't spoken yet.
It seems that my change of seat
has no effect on him.
It's me who flatter myself.
You're jealous.
Go persuade her.
One track-minded
Song Ziqi, why do you drink my milk tea?
Terrible taste. Save it for yourself
Have I begged you to drink?
What happened to Ding Xian? so lost
Come on, nothing serious
Come on.
Can you hear what they're saying?
Hurry, use your pigsney to read
what they are saying.
Three strings of fish balls or nothing.
How dare you fish in troubled water.
Four strings.
My treat.
Deal.
Have you chosen the play yet?
They are going to see a play together?
I've already booked it.
I'll use the computer to send it to you later.
He said they weren't friends.
Liar.
Crows are all back.
I also think something is wrong with Siyue recently.
We discussed it in the group yesterday.
Zhou Siyue, you said you didn't know her well.
Then why do you go to the play together?
I'll study hard from now on.
I'll never talk to you again.
Why are you so angry?
I heard that
a new play has been staged in Binhe Theatre recently.
It's called Secret Love In Peach Blossom Land.
seems quite good.
You like watching plays?
I just got to know it casually.
Don't you like it?
I haven't seen a play.
But
I can learn about it.
I just knew it.
She wants to date me.
I'm back.
Xianxian is back.
Hurry up cleaning.
Let's go to Siyue's house.
His parents are back from a business trip.
Enjoy yourself and leave me alone.
Then no dinner for you.
I'm not hungry.
Mom, you look great in this makeup today.
You are also beautiful without makeup.
You look even better with makeup on.
What do you want?
Umm...
Pocket money...
Here you are.
Mom, can you give me more?
Ding Juncong
Multiple times this month already
Just five yuan.
Not a penny more
Ding Wencheng, hurry up.
I'm coming.
Let's go, Ding Juncong.
Okay, one second.
Hurry up.
Sister, you look so good today.
Don't even think about it.
Mom's right.
You should get rid of
the habit of wasting pocket money.
I wouldn't squander.
I'm going to give...
Forget it.
Even if I tell you, you don't understand.
What?
You just resort to sophistry.
By the way.
Why didn't Xianxian come?
She
didn't do well in the monthly exam, so she studies at home.
She really worries me.
It happens
to fail in the exam.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Xianxian
is different from Siyue,
who is very clever and learns faster.
See? He knows high technology things.
And Xianxian has become self-willed now,
Wanting to choose sciences.
Her score has deteriorated.
It'll be nice if she can get enrolled by a second-tier university.
We don't expect more
out of her.
Auntie
In fact,
Ding Xian's character is like this.
As long as she sets her mind on a thing,
she will stick to the end.
So even if it's difficult to be admitted to a key university,
I believe she can do it.
You don't have to worry.
Xianxian is a promising girl.
Don't worry.
Well.
Ding Xian
I've got a new information.
Would you like to listen?
I'm too lazy
to listen to girls' gossip. Bye.
It's about Zhou Siyue and Yang Chunzi.
It's okay to listen.
They once participated in a math competition together
in junior high school.
But gradually the rumors came.
In order to avoid suspicion,
Zhou Siyue estranged from Yang Chunzi.
Let it be.
I don't care about him and Yang Chunzi.
From now on, I'll study hard
and no more Zhou Siyue.
Don't disturb me.
Oh no.
Another one being possessed.
Siyue, here.
Wrong again.
Song Ziqi
Do you have an eraser?
No, I don't
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What are you going to do this weekend?
Have fun of course.
A new game center has opened nearby.
It's so much fun. Let's go together.
What happened to your eyes?
What about you, Xianxian?
I may study at home.
I don't know if my mother will let me out.
What about you, Siyue?
We'll see.
Song Ziqi, come out.
Why?
Hurry up.
Kong Shadi, what the hell do you want?
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it either. Do I provoke you?
Not you.
There is something wrong with them.
I can't let it go on this way
As long as they don't get along,
we won't live a happy day,
right?
Right.
What should we do?
Listen.
Let's get them out this weekend
and leave them alone.
I'm in charge of Ding Xian.
You're in charge of Siyue.
Why Siyue?
I don't care how you will do it, just do it well
don't come to me anymore if you failed
Kong Shadi
what about our brotherhood you mentioned?
You betray me
for Ding Xian.
We're not friends.
Idiot.
Or what?
Think for yourself.
Kong Shadi
You wanna
be my girlfriend?
Don't be narcissistic, okay?
You're disgusting.
Xianxian
Shasha
What will you do this weekend? Let's hang out.
Weekend? My mother won't let me go out.
Oh no. It's been a long time
since we hung out.
And let me show you.
Where did you get this ticket?
My dad's company.
He doesn't need this.
We need.
Forget it.
My mother will definitely not agree.
Why don't you go with Song Ziqi?
No, I just wanna go with you.
It's up to you.
Come on
Remember to dress up beautifully.
What are you doing?
How is the thing going?
You can always count on me
Really?
Sure thing.
-Why are you here?  -Just you two?
What about Siyue?
Is he still angry with me?
Don't flatter yourself.
Why are you here?
Call for help
I run out of my money.
Your dad deducted your pocket money again?
Soon after I get my lucky money at the end of the year,
I'll pay you back.
Double back
Shadi, you are so kind to me.
Here you are.
I...
I don't have much money.
Spin out
I saw a 100 yuan there just now.
No.
You're robbing me.
Who the hell are you? robbing my friend?
I didn't.
Cut the crap
You're Little Loach in Shen Hai High School
who likes to rob nearby, right?
That's Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School.
Came clean? Good
That's you. I'll call the police now.
Don't do it. He is one of us.
Let me introduce.
This is my friend Jiang Chen.
He is the school bully of No.18 Middle School.
Who is she?
I'm You Keke, the school babe of Shen Hai High School.
I know you.
You always
hang out with the boys at our school.
Don't talk nonsense.
The boys in your No.18 Middle School
are all jerks.
Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School is from your school.
What if it's not?
Impossible.
All right.
Let's find him out.
I must let you know that
the boys of No.18 Middle School are innocent.
All right. I'm not afraid of you.
Let's go then.
Go now.
Why do I feel like
we're both redundant?
Are you still studying the unreliable horoscope and fortune?
Don't talk nonsense.
This is very reliable.
That's what little girls would believe.
superstitious
You don't believe it?
I'll show you,
and you will know whether it is reliable or not.
All right. Go ahead
I just can’t wait to hear more
Umm...
What's the matter?
What's your zodiac sign?
Kong Shadi
We grew up together, and
You don't know my zodiac sign?
Should I have to mind everything about you?
Give it to me.
I'll read it for myself.
I'm an Aquarius. Please remember that.
Aquarius, here.
Aquarius should reduce travel this week
in case of losing money and red ruins...
Nonsense.
You're screwed, Song Ziqi.
Loss of money and a fatal disaster.
Shut up.
Ding Wencheng
Wake up, please.
What's up?
Look.
What?
Cinema tickets.
How strange.
It's been more than ten years
since we last saw a movie.
Why did you suddenly buy movie tickets?
They're not for you.
They're for Xianxian.
You let her go with her friends.
And together
with this dress to her.
You figured it out?
You started it
Go fix it by yourself. I won't go.
You such a guy!
Why is it so difficult to count on you?
This is your business.
If I give them to Xianxian,
should I do it in your name
or in my name?
I'll go
Mom
What's up?
You're going out?
Shadi asks me to a concert.
I have no choice
but to say yes.
Umm...
Mom, can I go?
Yes.
Thank you, mom.
You're gonna wear this?
I haven't made up my mind.
Umm...
I bought you a dress.
Take it
Mom
I
don't do anything wrong, right?
Oh no, poor thing.
Can't I be nicer to you?
Take this.
500 yuan.
300 yuan.
Mom, this is too expensive.
You better return it.
Just put it on
Enjoy yourself.
Remember to come back early.
Remember to answer my call
Thank you, mom.
You scared me.
What's the matter?
You come out in this?
So what?
The important thing is not to be discovered, correct?
Do I look handsome in it.
Hello, Shadi, where are you?
I'm on my way.
I'll be there in a minute.
I'll hang up first, bye.
Hang up so fast.
Is Zhou Siyue here or not?
I don't know. I already told him.
Zhou Siyue
What are you doing?
If I don't do this,
I'm afraid he would see me.
Why are you here?
I come to the concert.
They went in.
How did you ask Zhou Siyue out?
It's very simple. I said Ding Xian would go too,
and then here he is. I'm great, right?
Done, mission completed.
Retreat
Wait.
My dad gave me four tickets.
Thanks, dad.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
You're shoving me.
What's up?
Nothing serious. I just sprained my ankle.
Take a sit
Let me have a look.
This foot?
It's okay. I just need a break.
I felt that
you don't like talking.
I was born this way.
I don't know how to refuse
I dare not ask favors.
worrying too much most of the time
Even with words on the tip of my tongue,
I swallowed it
You don't have to worry.
We're friends.
Friends
should help
each other.
But I always give you trouble.
No one in this world
can do everything perfectly.
What's more,
I don't feel being troubled at all.
Can you tell me
what happened to you now?
Actually,
The Aunt came to me some time ago.
said
someone reported that we got along too close.
He asked me to change my seat.
I promised him that
as long as the score of this monthly exam was improved,
I wouldn't have to change my seat.
But
I didn't do well in the exam.
Just because of this petty thing,
you concocted excuses and lied to me?
No.
The Aunt said that every time something happened to me,
you helped me.
I don't want to get you into trouble
because of my own businesses anymore.
Luckily, you're not mad at me.
What?
It doesn't matter.
In short,
you just need to study hard in the future.
Leave the rest to me.
Starting from tomorrow,
I will tutor you alone.
I don't believe you can fail again in the exam.
What are you doing?
Look, how well I am disguised myself
Perfectly fit into environment
There is something wrong with me.
I can't believe I didn't hang out on weekends,
but accompany you here to wait for blackmailers
and endure the cold wind.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
You don't even try detaining me?
I think you're right.
You can leave now.
I'll wait here.
Nobody asked you out?
Who dares
Right, no one dares to ask you out.
You are smarter than me.
Otherwise, we both can't even catch a taxi.
Of course.
I consulted today's fortune before departure.
It says I'd better walk today
and fortune awaits
It's all a coincidence.
It also says that I'll have a fatal disaster.
But this week is coming to an end,
and I am still fine.
No one shows up for so long.
Is your bro countable?
Or...
What are you doing?
There are people here.
Does it cool down at night?
I'm so cold.
Here they come.
Let me give you some warmth?
What are you doing? You're so cheesy.
Where to go?
Go to the bathroom.
Don't follow me, psycho.
Rogue.
He's also very lecherous.
You stay here.
I'll go meet him.
If anything bad happens, call the police immediately.
Psycho?
I'm a psycho?
I think I look handsome in this coat.
Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School
You really don't need me to carry you?
My sprain has recovered a lot.
Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School
I must give you a piece of my mind.
The voice sounds so familiar.
It seems to be Jiang Chen's voice.
Wait here for a minute.
Let me take a look.
There you are.
He is Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School.
I must beat him up.
Don't hit me.
You're Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School.
What are you doing?
He is Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School. Hit him.
He is Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School?
Hit him.
Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School
Kong Shadi
He also knows my name is Kong Shadi?
Hit him.
Kong Shadi
You're stupid. It's me.
No.
Wait.
Why does his voice sound so familiar to me?
Who?
It turns out that I had fatal disaster.
Jiang Chen is to blame
for this today.
He told me about Evil Dragon when I came over.
You apologize to him.
Please have some food.
Don't touch me.
Are you a sore loser?
Let me beat you up?
All right.
I admit that
we both did something wrong today.
All right. Just cry.
Everything will be fine after you cry.
Here you are.
This works very well.
Ding Xian
It's OK if they are both bad.
Even you've gone bad.
I just got hurt too.
Can you compare your injury with my injury?
I suffered both mental and physical injuries.
I didn't cry either.
Enough.
I'm in pain.
Shut up.
Let go of me.
I have no money.
It sounds like my brother's voice.
Let go of me.
It's really my brother's voice.
Just wait here.
Hurry up.
Give me the money.
You are Evil Dragon in Shen Hai High School?
Who are you?
It's all misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Look at my face.
It's all because of you.
How dare you cry.
You don't even know to tell me about the blackmail?
Are you stupid?
I was going to tell you then.
But you were particularly aggressive that day.
It's your usual misbehavior to blame.
You either squander pocket money
or you love to talk back.
So I...
So it doesn't matter if I say it or not.
Your brother is just like you.
Brother
I know you're with my sister.
You're not with your sister?
No.
She especially hates me.
She's always mean to me.
How can she do this to you?
I'm right, right?
Look,
your sister sprained her ankle,
but she insisted on looking for you.
After she found you,
she tried to beat you angrily.
Fortunately, I stopped her.
She can't be so aggressive.
You don't even know my sister.
We're almost home. Please walk quickly.
You can go home if you want to.
Goodbye.
Take your time.
Your brother
is fine.
So I...
Goodbye.
Just give me a second.
What is it?
My present to you.
-Painting tools.  -Painting tools.
Painting tools?
You're welcome.
So
this's why you came to Yang Chunzi last time?
She has family members abroad.
So I asked her to book one for me.
What's the matter?
It seems I misunderstood you.
Misunderstood?
For what?
You remain silent again.
All right.
I'm going home.
Thank you.