( barking )
Come on. Get it!
Thanks.
Man in cap:
Thank you.
Brownie: Yeah. Pack of smokes
and Brown Thunder.
- Merle: Don't get cocky, boy.
- Thank you.
Cold drinks?
Been running
the freezers all day.
Not the most practical use
of the generators to my mind.
It's kind of amazing.
The Governor
feels it's worth it.
Well, to a great party.
Now, if you would just
drop me a hint about tonight.
Hmm.
Mere words cannot
adequately describe
the festivities ahead.
Hmm.
( music playing,
voices overlapping )
Hey!
( soft music playing )
( raspy breathing )
( snarling )
Penny. Penny, no.
Easy, Penny.
That's good.
( snarling )
It's nap time now.
Nap time.
( growls )
Penny, no.
Penny.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on.
Take it easy.
Hey, hey.
Come on.
It's all right.
- Hey, I'm here.
- ( Penny moans )
Daddy still loves you.
You know that, right?
- ( snarling )
- Hey.
All right.
Come on. Yeah.
Hey, Penny.
( Penny whines )
( theme music playing )
( crying echoes )
( panting )
( muffled )
Rick, you with me?
Rick?
Let me see the baby.
What are we
gonna feed it?
We got anything
a baby can eat?
The good news is
she looks healthy.
But she needs formula.
And soon or she
won't survive.
Nope. No way.
Not her.
We ain't losing nobody else.
I'm going for a run.
- I'll back you up.
- I'll go, too.
Okay, think where
we're going. Beth.
Kid just lost his mom.
- His dad ain't doing so hot.
- I'll look out for him.
( muffled baby crying )
You two get the fence.
Too many pile up, we got
ourselves a problem.
Glenn, Maggie, vámonos.
Rick!
Daryl:
Get the gate.
Come on, we're gonna
lose the light.
There's a Piggly Wiggly
on 85.
No, the baby section's
been cleared.
Lori asked me to keep an eye out.
I haven't had much luck.
Is there any place that hasn't been
completely looted?
We saw signs for a shopping
center just north of here.
Yeah, but there's too much
debris on the road.
A car will never
get through there.
I can take one of you.
I'll go.
No, Maggie,
after everything that you've
been through, okay, I'll go.
I want to go.
For Lori, I have to.
Okay.
I love you.
Be safe.
I will.
( revs motor )
( gate screeches )
( bangs )
- ( snarling )
- ( Rick shouts )
All right.
Hey.
First time we gathered,
there was nine of us
holed up in an apartment
with Spam and saltine crackers.
Well, look at us now.
( laughs )
We've built a place
we can call home.
May be held together
with duct tape and string,
but it works.
It's ours. I'll take it.
( laughs )
So today
we celebrate
how far we've come.
We remember those
we've lost.
We raise a glass... to us.
( cheering )
Man:
Hear, hear!
( thumping )
Milton: ...suggesting we delay
a couple of days.
Governor: We can't wait.
Everything's ready.
I love a party as much
as the next fella.
Trust me,
I love a party.
- But we're using a lot of resources.
- Yeah.
For instance,
the generators.
I thought
you love a party.
Merle: Come on, Milty,
lighten up, for Christ's sake.
Let your hair down, man.
Have some fun for once.
- I like fun.
- Then there's no problem.
If I might.
You know, I've been working
on an experiment all week.
It's been a challenge getting
the level of power I need.
And with everything
going on tonight--
What are you asking?
- Postpone tonight.
- No way.
Hang on.
Let's hear him out.
- How long do you need?
- I don't need long.
- How long?
- 10 days.
- No.
- Six?
- How about--
How about you enjoy
yourself tonight
and then begin the experiment
over in the morning, huh?
Uh, yeah.
That could work.
( flies buzzing )
( snarling )
( exhales )
( door creaks )
( bangs )
( door opens )
You get off on that?
Poking around other
people's things?
Hmm?
We got nothing
to hide here.
People with nothing to hide
don't usually
feel the need to say so.
That's fair.
We all have
our secrets, huh?
Like Penny?
You know about Penny?
Then you know
I loved her.
Bet you say that
about all the girls.
You got the wrong
idea about me.
I'm just a guy
trying to do right
by the people
I care about.
Now, you want to leave,
Andrea wants to stay.
So you want me to take
choice out of the equation.
You want me
to kick you out.
Actually, I was about
to give your sword back.
'Cause you fit in.
We've enjoyed having you.
This is a real problem
for me.
People follow the rules.
And whether or not it's true,
they believe it's what
keeps them alive.
You've turned that
upside down.
You've broken the rules.
If I don't do anything,
I invite anarchy.
How about this?
I keep a lid
on your little outburst,
you join the research team.
You obviously have skills
and you're not afraid of biters.
Merle will take care
of you and then--
( door bangs )
- Merle: How'd it go?
- ( chuckles )
She's all personality,
that one.
Do we have a problem?
No. No.
Send Andrea over to me.
You can take the research team
to get more grist for the mill.
I can handle this.
All right.
( door closes )
How's the perimeter look?
We got the walkers
spread out.
Need help?
Your friends, they--
they were good folks.
They were family.
I think I had one friend
like that my whole life.
You got a whole group.
Sorry you lost 'em.
I need two more.
- Rick?
- Still inside.
Okay, I'll get him.
A third of our group
in one day.
'Cause of one asshole.
Part of me wishes
that we killed
all the prisoners on sight.
Axel and Oscar
seem like good guys.
When the evacuations started,
T-Dog drove his church van to
the home of every senior he knew
just in case
they needed a ride.
He saved my ass
a thousand times.
He wasn't just a good guy.
He was the best.
Got bit closing the gate.
If he hadn't done that...
It could have been Maggie.
It's wrong, but...
I'd trade any number of people
for one of ours any day.
What's wrong?
Merle said it was urgent.
I need your help.
- It's Michonne.
- What about her?
She broke in,
stole her weapon.
She can't steal
something that's hers.
Then she went into
a private place
and slaughtered half a dozen
captive biters.
Why would you have
captive biters?
There's a good reason
I don't want to go into right now.
Okay.
Point is, I tried
to talk to her about it
and she pulled
her sword on me.
Held it to my throat.
Can't imagine
that surprises you.
She wouldn't do that
unless she felt threatened.
She makes people
uncomfortable.
Some people want her to leave
and I don't want that.
It's ugly out there and it's getting
worse every day.
But she put my back
against the wall here.
What are you saying?
I'm saying what works out
there doesn't work in here.
You know,
we're not barbarians.
- We got to talk.
- We got to go.
The Governor told me
what happened.
Michonne, you can't
do things like this.
You're freaking people out.
You're freaking me out.
The northeast wall
is guarded by some girl.
We can escape there
after dark.
We are not
prisoners here.
No one who comes
here leaves.
What are you talking about?
It's safe. There's food,
there's shelter.
There's people,
for God's sake.
That's what
they show you.
But you can't leave
unless they make you.
You are not making
any sense.
Mich, maybe you need
to sit for a minute.
You need to trust me.
And you need to give
me more to go on.
We got a good thing
going here.
- I thought this was temporary.
- And I think we need this.
I want to give
this place a real shot.
- I tried.
- Breaking into houses?
That is not trying.
That is sabotaging.
This place is not
what they say it is.
Rick?
Everybody's worried
about you.
You shouldn't be in here.
Come on out.
Rick.
You don't have to do
this all by yourself.
Okay?
Our cell block
is cleared.
We'll just close off
all the doors again.
Rick, why don't you
just come on out with me?
Okay?
- Rick.
- ( grunts )
( panting )
( softly )
Yeah... yeah...
It's me.
( high-pitched whining )
Hey, all right.
We got us a bite.
Yeah, we got us some.
Let's hook 'em up.
( snarling, moaning )
That's it.
Ho! Ho!
Ho, whoa!
Look what we got here.
Oh, yeah.
Come get it.
Whoa! Jeez!
Look at this one.
Little too little.
- We're gonna have to kill it.
- Hold on.
There's something
interesting in its eyes.
- So don't kill it?
- It's a maybe for me.
Here you go.
Get your hands
dirty for once, huh?
All right. Come on.
Come on down.
Let 'em down now.
- Come on, Milty.
- ( winch whines )
( growling )
Get her, boy!
Get her!
Oh, yeah!
Oh! Oh, man!
I tell you what,
I take back everything
I said about that jacket.
Come here.
Let me see her.
Merle, check this one out.
He's almost as ugly as you.
Holy shit!
Yeah, he's a mean one, huh?
Look at him.
Yeah, now get him down now.
Come on, get him down.
Get him down.
Yeow!
Easy now.
Open up, baby.
Got him! Yeah!
There we go.
Come on.
Don't give me
no shit, boy.
There.
- ( motor stops )
- Company's close.
Stay tight.
( smashes )
( faint rattling )
( scratching )
( hisses )
( squeals )
Hello, dinner.
I'm not putting that
in my bag.
( music playing )
Merle:
Hey, hey, hey, girls.
Where y'all off to
in such a hurry?
Huh?
Hey, come on, now.
Come on. Hey, hey, hey.
Y'all are breaking my heart
running away like that.
We're leaving.
It's almost curfew.
I'd have to arrange
an escort.
I mean, the party's
still going on.
All right.
Wait here a second.
Brownie.
Come here.
Listen up, bro.
The Governor told us we were free
to come and go whenever we liked.
Sweetheart,
nothing personal here,
but you're gonna
have to step back.
See?
There's always a reason
why we can't leave yet.
Clear.
Now if I was y'all, I'd find some
shelter before nightfall.
( gate creaks )
They knew we were coming.
This was all for show.
Do you hear yourself?
How can you know that?
And why would they bother?
- Ladies.
- Close the gates.
No.
I practically begged
the Governor to let you stay.
- I didn't ask for that.
- You didn't have to.
That's what friends
do for each other.
It goes both ways.
So you want to
run around out there
with walkers
on chains eating twigs?
- Is that right?
- We held our own.
Eight months. Eight months on
the road moving place to place,
scavenging,
living in a meat locker.
That was no life.
I'm tired. I'm tired.
I don't have another eight
months in me. Not like that.
And you, I...
What about me?
I'm afraid you're
gonna disappear.
We always talked about
this place, didn't we?
A refuge.
That idea is what
kept us going.
Are you coming or not?
Don't do this.
Don't give me
an ultimatum.
Not after everything.
Are you coming or not?
You'd just
slow me down anyway.
Michonne!
( bangs )
I'm sorry things didn't work out
with your friend.
Weird to lose someone
by their own choice.
Thought those days
had gone.
Not sure this will
make you feel better,
but I'm sure you
could use a drink.
Some company.
Something to take your mind
off of it for a bit.
Come on.
( snarling )
( motor roars )
Guys, they're back!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
You want some of this?
( gunshots )
Axel: You want some of this?
Come on! Come on!
( baby crying )
Beth.
Daryl:
How's she doing?
- Shh.
- I'm sorry.
Shh...
Come on.
( crying stops )
( chuckles )
She got a name yet?
Not yet.
But I was thinking
maybe Sophia.
Then there's Carol, too.
And...
( sighs )
Andrea.
Amy.
Jacqui.
Patricia.
Or... Lori.
I don't know.
Yeah...
You like that? Huh?
Little ass-kicker.
Right? That's a good
name, right?
Little ass-kicker.
You like that, huh?
You like that, sweetheart?
( faint grunting )
( snarling )
( grunts )
- ( screams )
- ( gunshot )
( grunting )
( shouting )
( music blaring )
♪ Like a black cat do ♪
♪ Two bodies laying naked ♪
♪ Creeper think he got
nothing to lose ♪
♪ So he creeps
into this house... ♪
Hey! How are you?
Come on up here.
Come on, this way.
I've got the best seats
in the house.
Hey, how you doing?
Yeah! Whoo!
♪ It's a Saturday night
special ♪
♪ Got a barrel
that's blue and cold... ♪
Forget about it.
Come on.
It's a little loud.
- ( music ends )
- ( cheering )
- Come on!
- I don't feel--
- ( music blaring )
- ( cheering )
Come on! Whoo!
- ( music continues )
- ( cheering )
Yeah!
( chanting )
Merle! Merle! Merle!
Merle! Merle!
Merle!
I'm gonna kick
his ass one-handed.
Oh, the hell with it.
No-handed!
Yeah!
( grunts )
- Yeah!
- ( cheering )
Whoo!
No hands!
Bring it on.
( snarling )
All right,
let's get it on!
( cheering )
( whistle tweets )
Yeah!
Come on!
Come on, get up.
Get up.
Want some more?
( snarls )
He's got nothing.
Nothing, folks.
- Get up.
- Come on!
Okay, come on.
Whoo!
- ( blows whistle )
- Hey!
Come on,
let 'em fight.
( crowd booing )
Merle: Come on, pretty boy.
Let's dance.
Hey, hey!
Where you going?
What the hell is this?
It's a way
to blow off steam.
Blow off steam?
You go for a jog
to blow off steam.
This is-- this is sick.
Look around.
Everyone's having a great time.
It's barbaric.
( quietly )
It's staged.
( laughs )
Yeah, we pull out
the biter's teeth.
It's just all for show.
( snarling )
That's crazy.
This is your reason
for keeping walkers around?
People need entertainment.
So your solution
is gladiator fights?
We're reducing these things.
We're controlling them.
We're shining a light on
the monster under the bed.
It's fun.
It makes people feel better
about the whole thing.
It's a slippery slope.
You're teaching them
that walkers aren't dangerous.
We're teaching them
not to be afraid.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Walk it off, huh?
Uno!
Dos!
- Tres!
- ( whistle blows )
( crowd cheering )
( baby's crying echoes )
( phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
Hello?
( theme music playing )