( birds chirping )
Hey!
Hey! Slow down!
Slow down!
Slow--
I'm begging you!
Please!
( walker snarling )
( tires spinning )
( snarling )
( walkers snarling )
Cover your ears.
( gunshot echoes )
Yeah, this'll work.
Tell me when.
( car door opens, closes )
Hey.
Put something
under the car like this
with a little gravel
and sticks.
It gives you traction.
Wouldn't have to do it
if she didn't get us stuck.
It was an honest mistake.
Why'd you let her come?
She took you to Woodbury
and you said she
just split on you.
- And Oscar died and you guys--
- It wasn't that simple.
I asked her to come today.
I didn't want to leave her
at the prison if I wasn't there,
not with Merle.
That and we got
common interests.
For right now,
we have the same problems.
So maybe we can work
on them together.
Carl:
Just for right now?
Rick:
Yeah, just for right now.
Man:
Hey!
Help me!
I'm begging you!
Don't leave!
Please!
- Hey!
- ( taps car )
- ( engine starts )
- Don't leave!
Please!
Let's go.
Man:
I'm okay!
Please!
Help me!
Stop!
( theme music playing )
( sighs )
Damn it!
You got any other
police stations in town?
I was the police here.
Me and a few other guys.
Ain't a big town.
There's other
places to check.
May not have as many guns
as were in here, but--
We need as many guns
as were in here.
- Ammo, too.
- Yeah, we do.
But right now,
I only got a line on a couple.
There's a few places
out on the main street--
bars, a liquor store.
Owners had a gun or two
behind the counter
that people
didn't know about.
I did.
I signed the permits.
They might still be there.
Do you have a problem
with that approach?
No, Rick.
I don't have a problem.
( rope creaking )
- What is it?
- I don't know.
( rats squeaking )
It looks like someone's
already made this theirs.
Doesn't mean they found
what we're looking for.
Couple of the places
are just up ahead.
Let's get in
and get the hell
out of here.
There.
Tyrell's.
A shotgun
and two handguns.
License issued
to Tyrell Debbs.
( snarling )
Rick:
Wait.
She'll get caught.
( gunshot )
Hands!
Now you drop
what you got and you go.
Your guns, your shoes,
and that sword.
All of it.
10 seconds.
- Run for the car now.
- 10...
- Dad.
- We need that rifle.
...nine,
eight...
- I think I can get up there.
- ...seven,
- six...
- Carl, go.
( gunfire )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
You okay?
Yeah.
I told you to run
for the car.
I didn't want you
to have to do that.
I had to.
( clunking )
He's wearing
body armor.
- He's alive.
- Do we care?
Yeah.
Keep an eye out
for booby traps.
Looks like he's gotten
pretty creative so far.
I thought we were just gonna get in
and get the hell out of here.
I'm not leaving him
on the street.
Look, I know you said
he helped you--
He saved my life.
He wasn't like this then.
Michonne:
Okay.
Jesus, he has a son.
You think he's in there?
( rats squeaking )
Don't.
You said booby traps.
Thank you.
Let's just get him
inside and go.
( Rick and Michonne grunting )
Whoa!
Carl, watch the wire.
I showed him that
weapons locker last year.
And it had
all of this in it?
No, not even half.
He's been busy.
The cot.
No.
We're gonna wait
for him to wake up.
Make sure he's okay.
He tried to kill us.
He told us to go.
He didn't know who we were.
He tried to kill us and we didn't
leave him for the walkers.
He's had a good day.
He doesn't need half of these guns.
We do.
We're waiting for him to wake up.
That's it.
Have you taken a look
around this place?
The axe, the spikes,
the walls.
- You think he's crazy?
- No.
I think he's dangerous.
I know him.
He wasn't
like this then.
We're gonna wait
for him to wake up.
( restraints zip )
What do you see?
Carl:
It's our neighborhood.
It's gone.
Is that why
you wanted to come?
To see the house?
Carl.
I just wanted to come.
( crunching )
We're eating his food now?
The mat said "Welcome."
I'm going on a run.
Where?
I thought maybe the one thing
people didn't loot was cribs
and there's that baby place
that Mom's friend Sara ran.
- It's just around the corner.
- Carl.
Dad, it's just around
the corner.
And there's all
those walker traps.
You're gonna need some help
carrying the box.
What?
If you're gonna get a crib,
you have to get the box.
It's big and heavy.
You're gonna need help
carrying the box.
You are getting
a crib, right?
That's what I said.
Then I'll go with him.
Right there,
that's the deal.
You get into trouble,
you holler, okay?
- I'll hear it from here.
- Okay.
( walkers snarling )
You don't have
to come with me.
I can handle it.
I told your dad
I'd help you.
Yeah, okay.
( squeaking )
( walker snarling )
Guess we should
take care of that.
Mmm.
Shit.
What the hell was that?
I want to do this
on my own.
You just passed
the baby place.
I'm getting Judith
something else first, okay?
I'm sorry
this happened to you.
( casing clinks )
( shouts )
Do you know who I am?
Do you see who I am?
People wearing
dead people's faces.
- Morgan, listen to me.
- No, I don't know you!
- You do know me.
- I don't know you!
- ( groans )
- You saved my life, Morgan.
You know me.
Look at me.
( groans )
You don't clear, man.
You turn.
You just die.
- You know me.
- I don't know anyone anymore!
You don't clear!
( screams )
( groans )
You know me.
You crazy
son of a bitch.
Please.
Please kill me.
( snarling )
( rat squeaking )
Just kill me.
Just--
just kill me.
You found me last year
in my front yard, Morgan.
You and--
you found me.
You fed me. You told me
what's happening.
You saved me.
My name is Rick Grimes.
You know me.
I'm not wearing
a dead man's face.
I gave you this.
I said I'd turn it on
every day at dawn
so you could find me.
Rick?
I know you.
Oh, man.
Damn it, I--
I know you.
I know who you are.
You said you'd turn
yours on at dawn.
That's what you said.
I mean, I hadn't
worked up to it yet, and--
then I did.
On the roof
every morning for days.
For weeks,
me and my boy.
And then...
me.
Just static, though.
Nothing but static.
And then nothing
but nothing.
You weren't there.
You were never there.
- I was.
- No, not when I tried.
I mean, you said you would
turn on your radio
- every day at dawn.
- Morgan, I--
You said that you would
turn on your radio...
- I did.
- ...every day at dawn
and you were not there!
I kept getting--
I kept getting pushed farther out.
I had to.
I didn't have a choice.
I found my wife
and my boy.
I had people.
I had to keep them safe.
We kept getting pushed back
deeper into the country.
I swear to God
I didn't have a choice.
You can have
your radio back
'cause it looks like
I finally found you.
You found your wife
and your son.
That's what happened, right?
You found them.
And did they--
did she--
did your wife--
did she turn?
No, she died.
So you didn't have
to see that, then.
Of course not.
( chuckles )
Not like me.
( laughs )
No.
Not like me.
Not like my wife.
You remember
what happened to her?
what she was?
Yeah.
Oh.
You gave me the gun.
You tried.
What did I try, Morgan?
- ( laughs )
- What did I try?
You tried to get me to do it
'cause I was supposed to do it.
I was supposed
to kill her, my Jenny.
Knew I was supposed to,
but I let it go.
Let it go like there wasn't
gonna be a reckoning.
We was always
looking for food.
You know, it always
came down to food.
And I was--
I was checking out a cellar
and I didn't want Duane
to come down there with me.
And then when I came up...
she was standing there
right in front of him
and he had his gun up
and he couldn't do it.
So I called to him
and he turned.
And then she was just--
just on him.
And I see red.
I see red.
Everything is red.
Everything I see is red.
And I do it.
Finally.
Finally was too late.
I was supposed to.
I was selfish.
I was weak.
You gave me the gun.
Hey, your boy--
is he dead?
- No.
- No?
He will be.
See, 'cause people
like you,
the good people,
they always die.
And the bad people do, too.
But the weak people,
the people like me...
we have inherited
the earth.
You think I was gonna
let you go in there?
I just think it's none
of your business.
You don't know me.
You don't know my dad.
I came out here to help.
You came out here
for common interests.
We have the same enemy
and the same problem.
And that's why you're here.
That's it.
This is important.
I'm going to do this.
And I know how I can.
You can't stop me.
Psst.
I can't stop you.
But you can't stop me
from helping you.
( bell jingles )
( squeaking )
( growling )
( growls )
( rat squeaking )
- ( snarling )
- In the kitchen.
( gunshot )
( gunshots )
No!
- I've got to go back in.
- Where is it?
We have to go back.
We have to. I have to.
It's the only one left!
( walkers pounding )
- Fine.
- Not like this.
I don't know you.
I get that.
But can you do
something for me?
Wait here.
- I can help.
- No. And no more bullshit.
You wait here.
That's how we get it done.
Hey.
I just--
I just thought
Judith should--
should know what
her mom looked like.
Thank you.
I was gonna go
back in anyway.
I just couldn't
leave this behind.
It's just
too damn gorgeous.
I'm not going
to kill you.
I don't think that's
what's supposed to happen.
I think you're supposed
to come back with us.
( laughs )
After all that?
After me trying to blow
your head off,
stab your heart out,
happily ever after together?
You couldn't kill me,
I couldn't kill you.
I'll take that as a sign.
Huh.
We found a prison.
The fences
can keep 'em out.
Is that where your wife died?
Just go.
Don't go back.
Don't stop.
Just get yourself
some more time.
Look, I can help you.
You can come back with us.
You can heal.
You're taking a lot
of guns, Rick.
No, I'm just saying that
that all is a lot of guns.
Why do you need
the guns, Rick?
'Cause if you got
something good,
that just means that there's
someone who wants to take it.
And that is what
is happening, right?
- We're gonna win.
- ( chuckles )
You can be there.
You can help.
You will be torn apart
by teeth or bullets.
You and your boy.
Your people, but not me.
Because I am not gonna
watch that happen again.
Man, you take the guns.
You know there's a chance.
That's what you can't square.
That's what hurts.
You know there's a chance.
I don't think you heard
a damn word that I said.
We both started out
in the same place.
Things went bad for you,
things went bad for me.
But you're not
seeing things right.
I don't blame you,
what you've lost,
what you've been through.
You're not
seeing things right,
but you can come back from this,
I know you can.
You have to.
This can't be it.
It can't be.
You got to be able
to come back from this.
- No.
- Morgan, please.
No!
I have to clear.
That's why
I didn't die today.
That's the sign.
I have to, man.
I have to.
I have to clear.
( growling )
Hey.
I was just about
to look for you.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
You're here now.
Oh, it's nothing.
Thank you.
He's okay?
No, he's not.
Wait. Hey.
- Carl.
- Morgan.
I had to shoot you.
You know I had to, right?
I'm sorry.
Hey, son.
Don't ever be sorry.
Everything okay with her?
I think she might
be one of us.
What?
Everything went okay.
( chuckles )
Hop in. I'll throw this
in the back.
You see something?
I know you see things.
People.
I used to talk
to my dead boyfriend.
It happens.
You want to drive?
Yeah.
Good.
I see things.
( music playing )
♪ O Lord,
live inside me ♪
♪ Lead me on my way ♪
♪ O Lord,
live inside me ♪
♪ Lead me on my way ♪
♪ Lead me home ♪
♪ O Lord,
in the darkness ♪
♪ Lead me on my way ♪
♪ O Lord,
in the darkness ♪
♪ Lead me on my way ♪
♪ Lead me home ♪
( humming )
♪ O Lord,
heaven's waiting ♪
♪ Open up Your door ♪
♪ O Lord,
heaven's waiting ♪
♪ Open up Your door ♪
♪ Lead me home ♪
♪ Lead me home. ♪
( theme music playing )