( raspy breathing )
( groans )
( door creaks )
( raspy breathing )
( crossbow twangs )
( whistles )
( can opener grinding )
( can clatters )
Psst.
( snarling )
( theme music playing )
15, you're on point.
We got no place
left to go.
When this herd meets up with
this one, we'll be cut off.
We'll never make it south.
What would you say?
That was about 150 head?
That was last week.
It could be twice that by now.
Hershel: This river could
have delayed them.
If we move fast, we might have
a shot to tear right through there.
Yeah, but if this group
joins with that one,
they could spill out this way.
So we're blocked.
Only thing to do
is double back at 27
and swing towards Greenville.
Yeah, we picked
through that already.
It's like we spent the winter
going in circles.
Yeah, I know. I know.
At Newnan we'll push west.
Haven't been through there yet.
We can't keep going
house to house.
Need to find someplace
to hole up for a few weeks.
All right.
Is it cool if we get to the creek
before we head out?
Won't take long.
We got to fill up on water.
We can boil it later.
Knock yourself out.
She can't take much more
of this moving about.
What else can we do?
Let her give birth on the run?
Do you see a way
around that?
Hey, while the others
wash their panties,
let's go hunt.
That owl didn't exactly
hit the spot.
( walkers moaning )
That's a shame.
- Watch the backside.
- Got it.
Hurry. Hurry!
( walkers growling )
( growls )
( panting )
It's perfect.
If we can shut that gate,
prevent more
from filling the yard,
we can pick off
these walkers.
We'll take the field
by tonight.
So how do we
shut the gate?
I'll do it.
You guys cover me.
No.
It's a suicide run.
I'm the fastest.
No, you, Maggie, and Beth
draw as many as you can over there.
Pop 'em through the fence.
Daryl, go back to
the other tower.
Carol, you've become
a pretty good shot.
Take your time. We don't have
a lot of ammo to waste.
Hershel, you and Carl
take this tower.
All right.
I'll run for the gate.
( snarling, moaning )
( shouting )
- Come on!
- Hey, come here!
Come on!
Sorry.
Hey, come on,
over here!
Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, over here!
( snarls )
( growling )
He did it.
Light it up!
Fantastic.
Nice shooting.
You okay?
- I haven't felt this good in weeks.
- Good.
Carol: Oh!
( laughs )
Oh!
We haven't had this much space
since we left the farm.
( laughs )
( growls )
Whoo!
Mmm. Just like Mom
used to make.
T-Dog: Tomorrow we'll put all
the bodies together.
Want to keep them away
from that water.
Now, if we can dig
a canal under the fence,
we'll have plenty
of fresh water.
Hershel: And this soil is good.
We could plant some seed,
grow some tomatoes,
cucumbers, soybeans.
That's his
third time around.
If there was any part
of it compromised,
he'd have found it
by now.
This'll be a good place
to have the baby.
Safe.
It's not much, but if I don't bring
you something,
you won't eat at all.
I guess little Shane over there
has got quite the appetite.
Don't be mean.
Rick's gotten us
a lot farther
than I ever thought he would,
I'll give him that.
Mm-hmm.
Shane could never
have done that.
What's wrong?
It's that rifle.
The kickback.
I'm just not used to it.
Hold on.
Better get back.
It's pretty romantic.
Want to screw around?
Pfft.
( both laugh )
I'll go down first.
Even better.
Stop.
Hershel:
Bethy, sing Paddy Reilly for me.
I haven't heard that,
I think,
since your mother
was alive.
Daddy, not that one, please.
How about
"The Parting Glass"?
No one wants to hear.
Why not?
Okay.
♪ Of all the money ♪
♪ E'er I had ♪
♪ I spent it
in good company ♪
♪ And all the harm ♪
♪ E'er I've ever done ♪
♪ Alas it was to none
but me ♪
♪ And all I've done ♪
♪ For want of wit ♪
♪ To memory now
I can't recall ♪
♪ So fill to me ♪
♪ The parting glass ♪
♪ Good night and joy
be with you all ♪
Both:
♪ Oh, all the comrades ♪
♪ That e'er I had ♪
♪ Were sorry
for my going away ♪
♪ And all the sweethearts ♪
♪ That e'er I had ♪
♪ Would wish me ♪
- ♪ One more day to stay ... ♪
- I had some.
♪ But since it falls
unto my lot ♪
♪ That I should rise ♪
♪ And you should not ♪
♪ I'll gently rise ♪
♪ And I'll softly call ♪
♪ Good night and joy ♪
♪ Be with you all ♪
♪ Be with you all. ♪
Beautiful.
Better all turn in.
I'll take watch over there.
Got a big day tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Look, I know
we're all exhausted.
This was a great win.
But we've got to push
just a little bit more.
Most of the walkers are dressed
as guards and prisoners.
Looks like this place
fell pretty early.
It could mean the supplies
may be intact.
They'd have an infirmary,
a commissary.
An armory?
That would be outside
the prison itself,
but not too far away.
Warden's offices would
have info on the location.
Weapons, food, medicine.
This place could be
a gold mine.
Hershel: We're dangerously
low on ammo.
We'd run out
before we make a dent.
That's why we have
to go in there...
hand to hand.
After all we've been through,
we can handle it, I know it.
These assholes
don't stand a chance.
Psst.
I appreciate everything
you're doing.
We all do,
but it's been a death march
and they're exhausted.
Can we just enjoy this
for a few days?
Baby will be here
in a few days.
There's no time
for a picnic.
No, but it's time
to get the house in order.
What do you think
I'm doing?
Your absolute best.
Don't patronize me.
I'm not.
I'm just saying
the baby is about
to be here
- and we need to talk about--
- About what?
Things we've been avoiding--
You want to talk?
Talk to Hershel.
I'm doing stuff, Lori.
"Things."
Isn't that enough?
I'm still here.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
( shop bell rings )
( growls )
( gurgling )
Ready?
Rick:
Daryl.
Come on.
Get tight!
( shouting )
- Come on, over here!
- Hey! Over here!
( shouting )
- Don't break rank!
- We need that.
T! T!
- Maggie! Maggie!
- ( grunts )
Rick:
Almost there.
Shit.
( growling )
I can't see them.
Can you see them?
Back there?
Daryl!
- Come on.
- We're good.
( growling )
See that?
( snarling )
Stop.
Well, it looks secure.
Not from the look
of that courtyard over there.
And that's a civilian.
So the interior could be
overrun with walkers
from outside the prison.
Well, if there's walls down,
what are we gonna do?
We can't rebuild
this whole place.
We can't risk a blind spot.
We have to push in.
( door squeaks )
( water dripping )
( loud clang )
( growling )
- What do you think?
- Home sweet home.
Rick:
For the time being.
It's secure?
This cellblock is.
What about the rest
of the prison?
In the morning, we'll find
the cafeteria and infirmary.
We sleep in the cells?
I found keys on some guards.
Daryl has a set, too.
Daryl:
I ain't sleeping in no cage.
I'll take the perch.
Come on.
Thank you.
Pretty gross.
Yeah, remember
the storage units?
It's actually--
it's actually comfortable.
Check it out.
You find your cell yet?
Yeah, I was just making
sure Beth was safe.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you.
( chuckles )
I'm so exhausted,
I don't even care.
Here, let me see.
What you doing?
Checking for scratches.
♪ It's late in the night... ♪
- You're okay.
- ♪ Late in the night ♪
♪ For a storm ♪
♪ It's quiet again ♪
♪ Too much for noise ♪
♪ To go home ♪
♪ To fill up the space ♪
♪ To fill up the rooms
on Sunday afternoon. ♪
( growling )
What are you doing
out here?
I needed some light.
( groans )
Take this.
How is it out there?
Same.
It's quiet.
You're lying.
We should go
in a few days.
They're coming.
- You should go.
- No.
I'll hold you back. Go.
I can take care of myself.
I saved your ass
all winter, didn't I?
( coughing )
I won't have you
dying for me.
Good soldier
won't leave your post.
Screw you.
We'll go in a few days.
If we stay...
I'll die here.
( gurgling )
Not bad.
Flashbangs,
CS Triple-Chasers.
Not sure how
they'd work on walkers,
but we'll take 'em.
I ain't wearing this shit.
We could boil 'em.
Ain't enough firewood
in the whole forest. No.
Besides, we made it this
far without 'em, right?
Carol:
Hershel.
Everything all right?
Yeah.
Nothing to worry about.
It's the baby.
I think I lost it.
- You haven't felt it move?
- Nothing.
And no Braxton-Hicks.
At first I thought it was exhaustion
or malnutrition.
You're anemic?
If we're all infected,
then so's the baby.
So what if it's stillborn?
What if it's dead
inside me right now?
- What if it rips me apart?
- Stop.
Don't let your fear
take control of you.
( sniffling )
Okay.
Then let's say it lives
and I die during childbirth.
- That's not going to happen.
- Why not?
How many women died in childbirth
before modern medicine?
If I come back,
what if I attack it?
Or you? Or Rick?
Or Carl?
If I do,
if there is any chance,
you put me down
immediately.
You don't hesitate.
Me, the baby,
if we're walkers,
you don't hesitate
and you don't try to save us.
Okay?
It might have
been better if--
- If what?
- ( exhales )
I'd never made it
off the farm.
You're exhausted,
frightened.
Yeah, that's true.
My son can't stand me.
And my husband,
after what I put him through...
We've all been carrying
that weight.
All winter.
I tried to talk to him.
He...
He'll come around.
He hates me.
He's too good a man
to say it, but I know.
I put him and Shane at odds.
I put that knife in his hand.
( crying )
You know who doesn't
give a shit about that?
- This baby.
- ( chuckles )
Now let's make sure
everything's all right.
You won't need that.
I need you to stay put.
- You're kidding.
- We don't know what's in there.
Something goes wrong,
you could be the last man standing.
I need you to
handle things here.
Sure.
Great. Let's go.
( lock clicks )
( spray can hissing )
( shrieks )
( softly )
Sorry.
( spraying )
( loud thud )
( growling )
- Go back. Go back! Move!
- Walkers!
Let's go.
This way.
- ( screams )
- Whoa. Whoa. Go, go, go.
Come on.
Come on, this way.
In here!
- Where's Glenn and Maggie?
- We have to go back.
But which way?
Maggie? Glenn?
- Glenn: Rick?
- Maggie: Dad?
Daddy?
Mag?
( screaming )
No!
( wailing )
- No!
- Maggie!
Daddy!
- Daryl!
- Oh, God, help me!
- Glenn!
- We're blocked!
Get back! Get back!
Go! Go!
- Hershel: Oh, God! Oh, God.
- Rick: Hold on.
Break 'em open.
Open the door!
Get in!
Shut the door!
You got it?
Have you got it?
( Hershel whimpering )
Hurry up!
Hold him down.
All right.
Only one way
to keep you alive.
( Hershel yells )
Oh!
He's bleeding out.
( whispers )
Duck.
Holy shit.
( theme music playing )