( snarling )
It's the only way.
No one else knows.
You gonna tell 'em?
Not till after.
We have to do it today.
It has to be quiet.
You got a plan?
We tell her we need
to talk.
Away from the others.
Just ain't us, man.
No. No, it isn't.
We do this,
we avoid a fight.
No one else dies.
All right.
We need someone else.
I'll talk to him.
I'll do it.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
Just me.
( fabric ripping )
Just looking
for a little vacation.
Best dope I ever had
was in a mattress.
Nothing.
This place must have
been no fun at all.
We need your help.
( laughs )
Do you even know why
you do the things you do?
The choices you make?
If we give
the Governor Michonne,
Woodbury stands down.
I don't like it, but it's what needs
to be done.
We need to make it quiet.
We need your help with that.
You ain't told
any of the others, huh?
Just Hershel,
Daryl and you.
Huh.
The inner circle.
I'm honored.
( chuckles )
You know,
when we'd go out on runs,
he'd bash
somebody's skull,
slash somebody's throat,
and he'd say,
"Never waste a bullet."
I always thought
it was just an excuse.
You go on.
Give him that girl.
He ain't gonna
kill her, you know.
He's just gonna
do things to her.
Probably take out
one of her eyes.
Both of 'em, most likely.
You'd let that happen
for a shot?
Whew.
You're cold as ice,
Officer Friendly.
You're gonna need wire,
not rope.
Wire. Nothing she could
chew through.
( chuckles )
Oh.
You know something?
You're right.
I don't know why
I do the things I do.
Never did.
I'm a damn mystery to me.
But I know you, Rick.
Yeah, I thought
a lot about you.
You ain't got
the spine for it.
We need to get her
to the Governor by noon.
( theme music playing )
- ( walkers snarling )
- ( Maggie shouting )
- Carl: Hey! Come on! Over here!
- ( pots clanging )
- Hey! Come on!
- Maggie: Over here!
Hey! Right here!
Over here!
- Come on!
- Here! Here!
Come on!
( shouting continues )
Daryl:
Come on, let's go.
They try to drive up
to the gate again,
maybe some blown tires
will stop them.
- That's a good idea.
- It was Michonne's.
We don't have to win.
We just have to make
their getting at us
more trouble
than it's worth.
( gate closes )
Hey.
Let's go.
Ain't no way.
Carol:
What?
Nothing.
What happened here?
We got any whiskey?
Hell, I'd even drink vodka.
Go to hell, Merle.
( laughs )
Are you with us?
Sure.
I'm not talking about
occupying the same space.
Are you with us?
I'm here for my brother.
Well, he's here for us.
It's not time to do shots.
It's time to pick
a damn side.
( laughs )
You ain't like you was
back in the camp--
a little mouse
running around,
scared of her own shadow.
It wasn't my shadow,
it was my husband's.
Well, you don't seem
scared of nothing anymore.
I'm not.
Hmm.
You're a late bloomer.
Maybe you are, too.
Hey.
You seen Merle around?
He say he was sorry yet?
'Cause he is.
He's gonna make it right.
I'm gonna make him.
There's got to be a way.
Just needs to be a little
forgiveness is all.
He tied me to a chair,
beat me, and threw
a walker in the room.
Maybe I could call it even.
But he--
he took Maggie to a man
who terrorized her,
humiliated her.
I care more about her
than I care about me.
( metal clinking )
Merle.
You down here?
Hey, little brother.
What the hell?
I was just about
to holler back at ya.
What you doing down here?
Just looking for
a little crystal meth.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Shit will mess
my life up
when everything is
going so sweet, right?
( laughs )
You talk to Rick yet?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I'm in.
But, uh,
he ain't got
the stomach for it.
He's gonna buckle.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
If he does, he does.
You want him to?
Whatever he says goes.
( scoffs )
Man.
Do you even possess
a pair of balls,
little brother?
Are they even attached?
I mean, if they are,
do they belong to you?
You used to call people
like that sheep.
What happened to you?
What happened
with you and Glenn
and Maggie?
I've done worse.
You need to grow up.
Things are different now.
Your people look at me
like I'm the devil...
grabbing up those lovebirds
like that, huh?
Now y'all want to do
the same damn thing I did--
snatch someone up
and deliver them to the Governor,
just like me.
Yeah.
People do what they
got to do or they die.
Can't do things without
people anymore, man.
( scoffs )
Maybe these people need
somebody like me around, huh?
Do their dirty work.
The bad guy.
Yeah, maybe that's how
it is now, huh?
How does that hit you?
I just want
my brother back.
Get out of here, man.
Hershel:
"Thou shalt not be afraid
for the terror by night.
Nor for the arrow
that flieth by day.
Nor for the pestilence
that walketh in darkness.
Nor for the destruction
that wasteth at noonday.
1,000 shall fall at thy side
and 10,000
at thy right hand.
But it shall not come
nigh thee.
Only with thine eyes
shalt thou behold
and see the reward
of the wicked.
Surely He shall
deliver thee
from the snare
of the fowler
and from the noisome
pestilence."
You're not there.
She's not there.
Hershel:
"He shall cover thee
and under His wings
shalt thou trust.
There shall no evil
befall thee.
Neither shall any plague
come nigh thy dwelling."
You okay?
What I wouldn't do
to keep you two safe.
( door opens )
Rick?
What you're
about to do--
I can't.
I won't.
- Michonne: So where is it?
- Merle: Around the corner.
We got to clear
some walkers,
then get the others
down here to barricade it.
A breach like this could be
an open invitation to the Governor.
He's not much
for subtlety.
( snarling )
You want to take
your chances?
( grunts )
Governor made Rick
an offer.
Turn you over and we all give
peace a chance.
I agree with you, though.
He would have blinked.
But not you.
( scoffs )
I'm being
straight with you.
You were straight
when you led me into the tombs.
Okay, maybe
I wasn't straight.
You put a bag
over my head.
I got it done.
He wouldn't have.
Keep moving.
He was a guy that came back
for me on that rooftop.
Nah.
It's all on me.
You know?
I figure that's why I was back
there in the first place.
Do the dirty work.
( walker growling )
( laughing )
May I?
I'll take that as a yes.
( growling )
( laughs )
Oh!
You know what?
I'd figured you would have run.
Wanted my sword back
before I get away.
( laughs )
It may go down
that way.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't get
my hopes up.
Move.
It's off.
We'll take our chances.
I'm not saying
it was the wrong call,
but this is definitely
the right one.
What's wrong?
I can't find Merle
or Michonne.
They've gone.
Come on.
He was in here.
Said he was looking
for drugs.
Said a lot of things, actually.
Like what?
Said that you were gonna
change your mind. Here we go.
Yeah, he took her here.
They mixed it up.
Damn it!
I'm going after him.
- You can't track for shit.
- Then the both of us.
No, just me.
I said I'd go and I'll go.
Plus they're gonna
come back here.
You need to be ready.
Your family, too.
I want to be
with my brother.
My brother, he wants
to be in the prison.
This little trip...
maybe it'll keep
that place standing.
If I pull it off,
maybe all is forgiven.
That's a whole lot
of maybes.
You got to play
the hand you're dealt.
I only got one.
You talk about the weight
of what you have to do,
how you can handle it.
A bad man,
someone truly evil,
they're light as a feather.
They don't feel a thing.
I've killed 16 men
since all this went down.
- Let's go.
- ( walkers snarling )
Look at what
that bastard's done.
Look at us.
He's one man.
There'll be others
like him.
There always have been.
I know.
It's like the walkers.
There's nothing
we can do.
When you gave me this...
I didn't fully understand
what it meant.
Such a simple thing.
I know what it means now.
I know what it takes.
I want to marry Maggie.
And we don't have
to have a wedding.
I don't even know
if we'll last the week.
But I want her to know
before...
who knows?
You have my blessing.
Thank you.
All right.
I think we're good.
Yeah, we're great.
( engine sputtering )
Come on.
- ( engine starts )
- Yeah!
That's the deal.
- ( car alarm blaring )
- Oh, shit.
( walkers snarling )
Merle!
Come on, Merle!
Okay. Okay.
( alarm chirps,
blaring stops )
Ah!
Come on.
Let's go!
( tires squealing )
So is this your thing, then?
You take out the trash?
Don't be so hard
on yourself, darlin'.
The Governor, Rick,
anyone who needs
their piss bucket emptied
and you come a-running.
( laughs )
Things are different
for your brother.
Yeah, they are.
Rick says jump
and he wants to know how high.
Mm-mmm.
Rick needs him.
Respects him.
He didn't ask him to do
this little job, now, did he?
No, 'cause he wants it done.
You keep telling
yourself that.
The truth is this could
have been your shot.
With your skills,
a whole new beginning.
But you choose
to stay on the outside.
No one's gonna mourn you,
not even Daryl.
He's got a new family.
You keep trying
to get under my skin,
I'm gonna cut
that tongue out.
Your buddy's
turning you over
'cause he's trying
to save his own ass.
You're as much
on the outside as I am, girl.
Maybe.
But once the Governor's
done with me,
at least I won't have
to live with myself.
( walkers growling )
( bones crunch )
You said you killed 16 men
since this thing started?
You ever kill
anyone before?
No.
And how about
before Woodbury?
Before you met him?
Huh.
So he saves your life,
cleans you up,
fed you a line of bullshit.
Why would you kill
somebody else for him?
You know, we can go back.
( chuckles )
Ain't happening.
Both of us.
We can just go back.
I can't go back.
Don't you understand that?
I can't.
Why?
( brakes squealing )
You go back with them.
Get ready for what's next.
I got something
I got to do on my own.
( snarling )
Hey!
Where's my brother?
You kill him?
He let me go.
Don't let anyone
come after me.
( music playing
over radio )
( music continues )
( laughs )
( turns up volume )
( music continues )
Man:
Where's it coming from?
Come on, come on.
With me.
We'll have to spread out!
You two with me.
Walkers!
All over!
Where's Michonne?
( screaming )
( gunfire continues )
Hey, over there.
( snarling )
( grunting )
You leave him to me!
( groans )
( groaning )
( shouts )
( screaming )
- ( arm cracks )
- ( groans )
( choking )
( coughs )
I ain't gonna beg.
I ain't begging you.
No.
- Hey.
Carl was looking for you.
He found me.
I think we should head over.
Rick has something to say.
Uh, just...
one more thing
before that.
Here.
Yes.
When I met
with the Governor,
he offered me a deal.
He said--
he said he would
leave us alone
if I gave him Michonne.
And I was gonna do that...
to keep us safe.
I changed my mind.
But now Merle took Michonne
to fulfill the deal
and Daryl went
to stop him
and I don't know
if it's too late.
I was wrong
not to tell you.
And I'm sorry.
What I said last year,
that first night
after the farm...
it can't be like that.
It can't.
What we do,
what we're willing to do,
who we are,
it's not my call.
It can't be.
I couldn't sacrifice one of us
for the greater good
because we are
the greater good.
We're the reason
we're still here,
not me.
This is life and death.
How you live...
how you die--
it isn't up to me.
I'm not your Governor.
We choose to go.
We choose to stay.
We stick together.
We vote.
We can stay
and we can fight
or we can go.
( munching )
( snarling )
( crying )
No!
- ( grunts )
- ( growling )
( crying )
( theme music playing )