( birds chirping )
( gate creaks, bangs )
( panting )
( gasps softly )
( flies buzzing )
( sighs )
( theme music playing )
( knocks )
May I?
That was, uh...
that was quite
a speech you gave.
Exactly what these people
needed to hear.
What about the prison?
As long as they leave us alone,
we have no problem.
- So no retaliation?
- No.
What would that get us?
I need to go see them.
( chuckles )
I thought this place could be
something else, you know?
Something better.
I wasn't up to the challenge
and I screwed it up.
I've done some terrible things.
I'm not fit to lead
these people.
But you are.
They don't need
to be terrorized.
Certainly not by
their own leader.
So you're abdicating?
You know, I really believed
if I kept her alive
long enough,
Milton would find a--
I just need time...
to get myself together.
So you want me
to fill in for you?
Who else can?
Milton? Martinez?
If you choose your friends in
the prison, I'd understand.
But these people need you.
I--
we need you.
( door closes )
( urinating )
There ain't nothing out here
but mosquitoes and ants.
Patience, little brother.
Sooner or later, a squirrel
is bound to scurry
across your path.
Even so,
that ain't much food.
More than nothing.
I'd have better luck going
through one of them houses
we passed
back on the turnoff.
Is that what your new friends
taught you? Hmm?
How to loot for booty?
We've been at it for hours.
Why don't we find a stream,
try our luck with some fish?
I think you're just trying to lead me
back to the road, man.
- Get me over to that prison.
- They got shelter.
Food.
A pot to piss in.
Might not be a bad idea.
For you, maybe.
Ain't gonna be
no damn party for me.
Everyone will get used
to each other.
They're all dead.
Makes no difference.
How can you be so sure?
Right about now he's probably
hosting a housewarming party
where's he gonna bury
what's left of your pals.
( spits )
Let's hook some fish.
Come on.
Right.
Now you said you found
Tyreese's group here?
- Yeah.
- We secured this.
He thought
he came through here.
Means there's another breach.
Okay.
The whole front of
the prison is unsecure.
If walkers
just strolled in,
then it's gonna be cake
for a group of armed men.
Why are we even so sure
he's going to attack?
Maybe you scared him off.
He had fish tanks
full of heads.
Walkers and humans.
Trophies.
He's coming.
- We should hit him now.
- Beth: What?
He won't be expecting it.
We'll sneak back in
and put a bullet in his head.
We're not assassins.
You know where
his apartment is.
You and I could
end this tonight.
( sighs )
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
He didn't know
you were coming last time
and look what happened.
You were almost killed.
Daryl was captured.
And you and Maggie
were almost executed.
You can't stop me.
Hershel:
Rick would never allow this.
You really think he's in any
position to make that choice?
Think this through clearly.
T-Dog lost his life here.
Lori, too.
The men that were here.
It isn't worth
any more killing.
What are we waiting for?
If he's really on his way,
we should be out
of here by now.
- And go where?
- We lived on the road all winter.
Back when you had two legs
and we didn't have a baby
crying for walkers
every four hours.
We can't stay here.
We can't run.
All right.
We'll stay put.
We're gonna defend
this place.
We're making a stand.
Carl, you and I will
go down to the tombs.
We need to figure out
where the breach is.
- You got it.
- Michonne: You'll need some help.
No, in case anything happens,
I need you out here.
Who's on watch?
( sighs )
Damn it.
( pulsating tone )
( gasps )
Ahem.
Alpha waves.
I was trying to induce
a meditative state.
I've been having trouble--
your battery, it's over here.
Man on radio: Okay, hold it.
Look at this jackpot.
You've been invaluable.
Do you intend to stay?
Leaving's never
crossed my mind.
Good.
'Cause I count on you.
And not just for your--
your expertise.
But I consider
you a friend.
I-- thank you.
I feel--
me, too.
I counted on
Merle as well.
Martinez,
he's a good soldier.
He'd take a bullet
if I needed him to.
Would you?
I would.
Yes.
And Andrea?
I'm not sure where
her loyalties lie.
I can see how
her previous affiliation
with Merle, no matter
how contentious it was,
could cause doubt.
You keep tabs
on her for me.
Of course.
( door bangs )
Where's Martinez?
I don't know.
Did you see him leave?
Yeah.
Who was he with?
Karen, it's okay.
You can tell me.
I don't know anything.
Milton.
Milton, stop!
You startled me.
Where is he?
Where's who?
The Governor.
He's out on a run?
Is that an answer
or a question?
I'm not sure...
where he is.
I mean, not whether it was
a question or an answer.
- It was an answer.
- A run meaning what specifically?
Supplies would be
a safe bet.
We were wiped out.
Milton, I want you
to give me a specific answer
to a specific question.
Where's the Governor?
On a run?
( sighs )
You know, I bet
he'll be back soon.
I'm sure he's okay,
if that's what you're worried about.
The tombs outside the boiler
room are overrun again.
That whole section
had been cleared.
It's a steady
stream of walkers.
Hershel:
We're wasting time.
The Governor is supposedly
on the way
and we're stuck
in here with walkers.
Trapped between a rock
and a hard place.
For the last time,
running is not an option.
Carol: Glenn, if the tombs
have filled up again,
it may just be a matter
of time before they push in here.
Or until some fence
gives way.
Axel: What if one of them herds
is passing through?
Or settled?
Can't handle that
with just the few of us.
Okay.
All right, we need--
we just need to scout
the far side of the prison.
- Find out what's going on.
- You're going out there?
- Take a car and make it quick.
- I'll drive.
No, you stay here.
Help with the fortifications.
I'll take Maggie.
You sure she's up to that?
( door opens )
Where have you been?
We need to find out how the walkers
are getting into the tombs.
Are we gonna talk
about this?
Maggie, you need
to talk about it.
I do? Or you do?
- What does that mean?
- What do you want me to say?
You want me to say
he made me get naked
and stand in front of him?
He came up behind me.
Pushed himself
against me.
Put his hands
all over me.
He slammed my head down
and bent me over a table.
Did he...
Rape me?
No.
Do you feel better?
- I'm not trying to--
- I had a choice.
Either I take off my shirt
or he would take off your hand.
I just listened to Merle beating
the shit out of you in the other room.
What could I do?
I'm sorry.
Go away.
You got your answer.
Now go away.
So we'll reinforce this with
some metal from the yard.
If anything happens,
we'll just duck.
( laughs )
I hope
nothing happens.
Guns scare the bejesus
out of me.
I robbed a gas station
with a toy gun.
Never even took it
out of my pocket.
You said Oscar
was the thief.
That you were in here
for pharmaceuticals.
Well, I didn't want y'all
to think I was a violent man.
If you follow me.
So what
are you saying?
You're in here
for a toy gun?
No, listen to this.
The next day the cops found
me at my brother's house.
Still had the water pistol
in my pocket.
I swore up and down that
that was the only weapon I had,
but they said they didn't believe
anyone could be
so stupid and get away with it.
So they turned my brother's
house upside down
and found his .38.
Said it "matched
the description."
There you go.
Armed robbery.
( laughs )
Tell you the truth, I don't even know
how to use this damn thing.
You're all about
the truth now?
Yes, ma'am, I am.
( clicks )
It's fully loaded.
Let's hope
it stays that way.
You're quite a lady.
Hmm...
( chuckles )
Merle: Smells to me like
the Sawhatchee Creek.
Daryl:
We didn't go west enough.
There's a river down there,
it's got to be the Yellow Jacket.
You have a stroke, boy?
We ain't never even come
close to Yellow Jacket.
We didn't go west.
Just a little bit south.
That's what I think.
( scoffs )
Know what I think?
I may have
lost my hand,
but you lost your sense
of direction.
Yeah, we'll see.
What do you want to bet?
I don't want
to bet nothing.
It's just a body of water.
Why's everything got
to be a competition with you?
Whoa, whoa.
Take it easy, little brother.
Just trying to have
a little fun here.
No need to get
your panties all in a bundle.
- You hear that?
- ( distant crying )
Yeah, wild animals
getting wild.
- No, it's a baby.
- Oh, come on.
Why don't you just piss in my ear
and tell me it's raining, too?
That there's the sound
of a couple of coons
making love, sweet love.
Know what I mean?
( laughs )
- ( walkers snarling )
- ( man yelling in Spanish )
- ( baby crying )
- ( gunshots )
( whistles )
Hey! Jump!
( laughs )
What?
Hey, man, I ain't
wasting my bullets
on a couple of strangers
that ain't never cooked me a meal
or felicitated my piece.
That's my policy.
You'd be wise
to adopt it, brother.
( man shouts in Spanish )
( gunshots )
( baby crying )
( speaking Spanish )
Daryl: Come on, man.
I'm trying to help you out.
Cover me!
( speaking Spanish )
( screams )
( growls )
Daryl! I got ya!
Go!
- ( speaking Spanish )
- Speak English.
( speaking Spanish )
( baby crying )
( shouting in Spanish )
Slow down, beaner.
That ain't no way
to say thank you.
( speaking Spanish )
Let 'em go.
Relax.
The least they
can do is give us
an enchilada
or something, huh?
Easy does it, señorita.
- ( sobbing )
- Everything's gonna be fine.
- ( rustling )
- Man #2: Hey! Hey!
( man #1
speaking Spanish )
( cans clanking )
( bottle rattles )
( sighs )
Get out of the car.
I know you're not talking
to me, brother.
Get in your car and get
the hell out of here.
Go! Get in your car!
( speaks Spanish )
( car engine starts )
( door closes )
( squishes )
( walkers moaning )
( faint thunder rumbling )
Merle: The shit you doing,
pointing that thing at me?
They were scared, man.
They were rude
is what they were.
Rude and they owed us
a token of gratitude.
They didn't owe us nothing.
You helping people out of
the goodness of your heart?
Even though you might
die doing it?
Is that something
your Sheriff Rick taught you?
There was a baby!
Oh, otherwise you would have just
left them to the biters, then?
Man, I went back for you.
You weren't there.
I didn't cut off your hand, neither.
You did that.
Way before they locked
you up on that roof.
You asked for it.
( chuckles ) You know--
you know what's funny to me?
You and Sheriff Rick
are like this now.
Right?
I bet you a penny
and a fiddle of gold
that you never told him
that we were planning on
robbing that camp blind.
It didn't happen.
Yeah, it didn't 'cause I wasn't
there to help you.
What, like when
we were kids, huh?
- Who left who then?
- What?
Huh? Is that why
I lost my hand?
You lost your hand 'cause you're
a simpleminded piece of shit.
Yeah?
You don't know!
( shirt rips )
I-- I didn't know he was--
Yeah, he did.
He did the same to you.
That's why you left first.
I had to, man.
I would have killed
him otherwise.
Where you going?
- Back where I belong.
- I can't go with you.
I tried to kill
that black bitch.
Damn near killed
the Chinese kid.
He's Korean.
Whatever.
Doesn't matter, man.
I just can't go with you.
You know, I may be
the one walking away...
but you're the one
that's leaving-- again.
Damn.
Glenn?
Glenn!
You're not going back
to Woodbury, are you?
No.
I'm just going out there.
- I'll go with you.
- I got it.
By yourself?
How can you possibly think
that's a good idea?
I can't just sit
on my hands.
You went on a simple
formula run
and got the crap
beat out of you.
- Maggie was attacked.
- Are you saying this is my fault?
- No.
- I did what I could.
I know you did.
So does Maggie.
She's one of
the two people
most precious to me
in this world.
I trust you with her life.
I still do.
This rage is going
to get you killed.
With Daryl gone
and Rick wandering Crazytown,
I'm the next in charge.
What are you proving?
( engine starts )
She's hungry.
Could you help me
feed her?
I want to make Daddy
something to eat.
Here.
Just keep the bottle
like this.
Otherwise she gets gassy.
Got it.
Here's this.
Hershel: Rick.
Rick.
You know I wouldn't have
hobbled all the way down here
if it wasn't important.
Are you coming
back soon?
Glenn's on the warpath.
Smart as he is,
he can't fill your boots.
I'm afraid he's reckless.
We need you now
more than ever.
Well, if you're
so worried about him,
you lead.
What are you doing
out here?
I've--
I've been--
I've got...
stuff out here.
Stuff.
How much longer
do you need?
I don't know.
I don't--
Is there anything
I can help you with?
I saw something.
Lori.
I saw Lor--
I'm seeing Lori.
Look, I know
it's not really her.
But there's got
to be a reason.
It's got to mean
something, you know.
Was it her on the phone?
Yeah.
Shane, too.
And the town.
Do you see them now?
You're looking for them.
I'm waiting.
For what?
I don't know. Something.
There's an answer.
I know
it doesn't make sense.
Well, it does.
It can make sense.
I mean, I think in time
it will make sense.
Rick...?
Come on in.
You need rest.
It's not safe out here.
I can't. I can't.
Stress getting
to your man Rick?
Can you blame him?
No. Not at all.
In here I've seen plenty
of dudes crack.
But not me.
I got on better
on the inside.
Things made more sense,
you know?
There were rules.
Life was more simple.
Didn't you miss
your brother?
My brother?
( laughs )
Hell, no.
He had a real
money problem.
- What kind of problem?
- He didn't lend me any.
( both laugh )
One time
that son of a bitch--
( gunshot )
( gunfire )
Come here!
( gasps )
( gunfire stops )
- ( door opens )
- Beth!
- Here.
- ( gunfire resumes )
Carol, go!
( distant engine roaring )
( engine roaring )
( laughs )
( engine rumbling )
( engine stops )
( snarling )
( clicks )
Hershel.
Get the hell out of there!
( snarling )
( clicks )
Oh!
( shouts )
( yelling )
( shouting )
Come on.
( grunting )
- You okay?
- Yes, baby.
( grunts )
( panting )
( laughs )
( snarling )
( theme music playing )