♪Confessing to the moon
in the rustling wind♪
♪Like a boat being swallowed up
among the cities♪
♪Watching the flowers fall in unease,
worries and troubles fill my mind♪
♪Am I going to where I want♪
♪To stay or to leave, you decide♪
♪Nations are different♪
♪One without desire
is one that is not alive♪
♪Looking at the sky side by side♪
♪We've gotten closer with time♪
♪One glance,
the city of Chang'an is bare♪
♪Among the ridiculous people
and things is me♪
=Dream of Chang'An=
=Episode 1=
(On the 9th year of Tai'an,)
(the Xing empire was hanging
by a thread.)
(In order to get out)
(of the eunuch's control,)
(Emperor Wenzong of Xing planned
to reclaim his authority as the emperor.)
(Prime Minister's Residence)
Prime Minister.
(Prime Minister, Wang Yang)
Something happened at the palace.
(Prime Minister's Residence)
(Eunuch Qiu is leading the Shencai Army)
(in arresting the perpetrator.)
(You...)
(You'd better leave.)
This secret passage leads
outside the city.
Official Wang.
Hurry.
Be careful.
Open the door.
Go.
(Duke Chu, Eunuch Qiu Ziliang)
You Ma.
Yes.
In the imperial court,
how many times did Wang Yang refute me?
Six times.
One is to one hundred.
And then
strike him 600 times
in dismembering him.
Yes.
Qiu Ziliang.
For many dynasties,
did any eunuch
who monopolized power have a good ending?
Grandfather!
(To scare the officials,)
(Qiu Ziliang ordered people)
(to bring Wang Yang's corpse)
(to the downtown area,
and cut it in half.)
Your Highness.
She's still alive.
(On January 4th,)
(Emperor Wenzong of Xing passed away.)
(His brother Qi Yan succeeded
to the throne.)
His Majesty has arrived.
Kneel!
(Emperor Wuzong of Xing, Qi Yan)
(Eunuch, Cheng Huaizhi)
Godfather.
What's the matter?
Qi Yan, you like the black one?
But I think
that only purple
can match you.
You're right, Godfather.
Since you like the black one,
let's use that one then.
Assist His Majesty in changing clothes.
Qi Yan.
You're all grown up now.
But I am
old.
How can you say that you're old?
Every land in the nation
belongs to the emperor.
Everyone within the nation's territory
works for the emperor.
From now on,
you are
the Xing empire's emperor.
Thank you, Godfather.
- Long live Your Majesty!
(Violet Bureau)
(Head of Violet Bureau, Cheng Xi)
(Violet Bureau, Li Rong)
Thank you for letting me win.
(Violet Bureau's Sword Bearer,
Cheng Ruoyu)
Wu!
Look at these people.
We agreed to come out
and have fun together,
but they disappeared.
After going into the palace,
perhaps I'd never see
such a bright moon again.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You know me?
Yes.
You're the one who can mobilize
the palace's imperial guards.
And everyone knows
that you like to hunt foxes
late at night.
Kill her.
- Yes!
Wait.
I'm not an assassin.
I'm from the Violet Bureau.
Your Majesty, please take a look.
I have the command token.
Your name?
Cheng Ruoyu.
You're Cheng Ruoyu?
Yes.
I'm the new Sword Bearer
of Violet Bureau.
My portrait has already been presented
to the palace.
You look just as foolish as you do
in the portrait.
(His Majesty looks so familiar.)
(I wonder where I've seen him before.)
What are you doing here?
I came here for a field trip.
I heard that the scenery here
is very nice.
And?
It's true.
And
I didn't know that Your Majesty
would come to hunt foxes here.
I came here first.
I just wasn't able to leave in time.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Scram.
(Hanyuan Hall)
Summon Violet Bureau's Cheng Xi
and Cheng Ruoyu.
Greetings from Cheng Xi, Your Majesty.
Greetings from Cheng Ruoyu,
Your Majesty.
Cheng Ruoyu.
Come forward to receive
the imperial command.
Yes.
"In accordance
with the will of the heavens,
I govern in a civilized manner,
but quell rebellions with force.
And a Sword Bearer
is the imperial court's pillar,
and a capable official of a nation.
Cheng Ruoyu
from the Violet Bureau
is skilled in martial arts
and has good virtues.
She's chosen
to become
the 23rd
Sword Bearer of Violet Bureau.
With this arrangement,
you've been appointed.
That's the imperial command."
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Please bring the sword.
Cheng Ruoyu,
23rd Sword Bearer
of the Violet Bureau,
listen to the imperial command.
Yes.
The Qingguang Sword
was used by Madam Gongsun before.
It's given to you today.
I hope you can fulfill your duty,
protect the emperor and love the nation
and carry out your seniors' legacy.
Don't fail
my trust.
Yes.
Gods in heaven and earth.
Spirit of the sword.
My heart is like a sword,
suppressing the wicked
and eliminating evil.
My sword is like my heart,
protecting the nation
and being loyal to the emperor.
(Hanyuan Hall)
Congratulations, Sword Bearer.
Stop.
Sir.
Are you going into the city?
Can you do me a favor,
and give me a ride?
(Chess of Generals Camp's Left Advisor, Yan Xiu)
I don't call the shots.
Who calls the shot then?
The Young Mistress.
(Chess of Generals Camp's Chess Overseer,
Qiu Yanzhi)
Miss.
Can you give me a ride?
Get in.
Thank you.
(Qiu)
Thank you for giving me a ride.
By the way,
I have
some preserved fruits.
Here.
Try one.
It's very sweet.
You don't want one?
I've read that one too.
It's a good book.
She disguised herself as a man
and killed her enemy.
She endured hardships
for her retaliation.
What an amazing girl.
You... You just started reading it?
Well...
There's a twist in the ending.
It might not necessarily be the same
as what I said.
(Su's Textile)
We're here?
We're here.
We can only take you to this point.
Aren't you the beautiful
and kind lady?
Why are you here?
The Heavenly umbrella?
You're the Chess Overseer?
I'm Qiu Yanzhi,
Chess of Generals Camp's Chess Overseer.
Cheng Ruoyu.
We meet again.
Thank you, Ms. Yanzhi,
for giving me a ride the other night.
I was worrying about how to repay you.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
It's not a big deal.
Don't worry about it.
No.
I must still repay you.
What do you want to eat?
I'll bring you there.
(Duke Chu's Residence)
It seems that your chess skills
improved a lot indeed.
You want to eat my elephant.
Then I'll
go one step ahead,
and eat yours.
I'll keep you in check.
Nothing can be hidden
from you, Father.
It seems like
I lost again in this round.
By the way,
how did you meet
the new Sword Bearer?
I gave her a ride the other night.
But I asked someone to check.
She just went out of the city
for a trip.
What do you think of her?
She has a mischievous character.
We don't need to worry about her.
We can't take her lightly.
People like to pretend
in front of others.
Don't get your plans ruined in the end.
So, Cheng Ruoyu
is the niece of Cheng Huaizhi
and Cheng Xi.
Yes.
Eight years ago,
Cheng Ruoyu's parents died,
so she came to the capital
to depend on Cheng Xi
and got into the Violet Bureau.
I have
seen her before.
Your Majesty went
to the Violet Bureau?
When I went hunting for foxes
the other night outside the palace,
she was there too.
Why was she there?
Investigate it.
Yes.
I'm exhausted.
Little Bell.
As the Sword Bearer,
I'm being treated well.
Look at my new room.
Little Bell.
Lotus petal pattern silver basin.
White porcelain amphora vase.
Even the poplar tree branch
for brushing teeth
is so intricate.
Peach blossom cake.
It's so delicious.
What a pity.
You can't eat it.
Little Bell.
The palace is a dangerous place.
Even I
must be very careful.
You must hide well.
But I'll visit you often.
Your Majesty.
Grand Empress Dowager
told the private kitchen
to prepare these biscuits carved with flower
for you.
Grand Empress Dowager heard
that you don't have
much appetite lately.
She's very worried.
Don't bother Grandmother
about such a minor thing,
so that she won't worry.
Your Majesty.
How would I dare to report that to her?
It's just that Grand Empress Dowager
is worried about you,
and she often asks about this.
By the way,
when she heard that the Sword Bearer
is Cheng Ruoyu,
she even admonished me.
Why?
Because
Cheng Ruoyu is my niece.
Your Majesty.
I swear to the heavens.
My niece, Cheng Ruoyu,
has become the Sword Bearer.
It's not because my sister and I
played favorites.
I believe you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But I'm still very disappointed.
When Gongsun Jing was alive,
I met her several times.
She was a quiet lady.
I only heard her say three things.
First.
Someone reported
that the Violet Bureau's
expenses are too high.
What do you think?
(Violet Bureau's
22nd Sword Bearer, Gongsun Jing)
A Sword Bearer doesn't need to think.
Wherever Your Majesty's eyes are looking,
that's where the sword
would be pointed at.
Second.
(Clear mind and heart)
How are you feeling?
Is it a serious injury?
Protecting Your Majesty
is a Sword Bearer's duty.
(Emperor Wenzong of Xing, Qi Ang)
And getting injured on behalf of His Majesty
is a Sword Bearer's honor.
The third one
was the morning
when my brother passed away.
Are you willing to follow me?
A sword is just ordinary iron.
It differs with the one using it.
If the emperor is kind,
the sword is loyal.
If not,
the sword is hostile.
Even if I'm a useless sword,
you
(still don't deserve me.)
A sword is just ordinary iron.
It differs with the one using it.
If the emperor is kind,
the sword is loyal.
If not,
the sword is hostile.
Then for me,
someone restrained by eunuchs
and considering one of them as my father,
someone people claim
to have become emperor
after killing my brother,
what kind of Sword Bearer
can I have?
Your Majesty.
The Violet Bureau and I
highly depend on each other.
If I want the sword
to be a precious weapon,
I must be a wise emperor first.
Otherwise,
no matter how sharp the sword is,
it will backlash on me.
Huaizhi.
Yes.
Am I right?
Your Majesty.
I think
that you'll always be
the sword's owner.
The owner will always be
the one holding the sword.
Even if you use it against the sturdiest
and hardest object
in the world,
I believe
that the sword won't hesitate
even if it means crushing itself.
Your Majesty.
Rise.
On another day,
come with me to visit Grandmother.
Yes.
Go.
Carefree Pill.
One pill, and you'll have eternal peace.
You've waited for many months.
It's finally done.
That's right.
He's tired.
He needs to rest.
After resting,
he won't keep pondering
about his dignity.
It's the will of the heavens.
That's why I want him to take this pill
for him to be carefree.
If the emperor is wise,
the officials are virtuous.
You mean...
Give it to Qi Yan.
Let him be
a carefree emperor.
Uncle.
What's wrong?
What's the matter with you?
Where did you go?
I...
You know what?
The Chess Overseer
requested to see His Majesty
early in the morning.
It's been over half an hour.
In the morning,
His Majesty asked me to go to Hanlin Academy.
You mean
the Chess Overseer...
The Chess Overseer
has been in there for so long,
and she's still inside.
Let me take a look.
You...
Your Majesty.
What is in it?
Carefree Pill.
It seems that you know what it is.
I don't need to say more then.
I'm already
very obedient to Godfather.
Why is he forcing me this way?
If you're really obedient
and loyal,
why do you insist
on keeping the Violet Bureau?
The female emperor established
the Violet Bureau.
They haven't made any major mistakes
in the past 100 years.
How can I just abolish it?
Father
was bitten once,
and twice shy.
Please understand.
Besides,
Father is being considerate
to you this way.
After taking this,
you'll feel carefree.
You won't need to worry
about state affairs.
What will you do
if I don't take it?
I know that I can't do anything
about it.
I can only ask Father
to come here personally.
Your Majesty.
On my first day of work,
I accomplished something major.
Shouldn't you
reward me well?
What did you accomplish?
The side hall was on fire earlier.
I went to put out the fire,
and it was extinguished.
However,
I almost burned myself as well.
It's really so hot.
Do you have...
You have a drink here?
However,
this is too little.
Is there anything else...
Guards.
Guards!
Cheng Ruoyu.
Yu'er.
Your Majesty.
I'll ask the imperial physician to come.
That's enough.
Stop pretending.
Your Majesty.
Uncle.
I'm fine.
I didn't drink that tea.
It's all here.
Your Majesty.
Did I accomplish something major?
Did you accomplish something major?
You were so rash.
You're utterly foolish.
I...
Your Majesty.
I disregarded my life to save you.
Forget about complimenting me.
Why are you even angry?
Aunt.
Your Majesty.
Yu'er.
What exactly happened?
I saw Qiu Yanzhi
forcing His Majesty to take
the Carefree Pill earlier.
Carefree Pill?
Your Majesty.
I didn't drink it.
I knew it's poisonous.
But I remember
you telling me
to think twice before doing anything.
That was why I thought
I must have
a fool-proof plan.
At that point,
my wisdom and ideas
kept flowing endlessly
like a river.
Then I...
It's not necessary
to say that.
And I pretended
to be very thirsty
after extinguishing the fire
and went inside to drink the drug.
Then I pretended to faint
and fooled Qiu Yanzhi.
Did I
do something wrong?
Even if you did it out of loyalty,
you were too rash.
What if you ruin His Majesty's plan?
Seek punishment from His Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I am guilty.
What are you guilty of?
I
think I did something wrong
out of good intentions.
You may
have been clever today,
but you only saw a small part
of the whole picture.
As the Sword Bearer,
you're my sword.
If it's used in the right way,
I'm fortunate.
If not,
it will bring disaster to the nation.
Cheng Ruoyu.
I'll only
give you one chance.
Yes.
Aunt.
Since you're poisoned,
you can't go anywhere.
I...
This is ridiculous.
Your Majesty.
I'm useless.
Rise.
In the past eight years,
the Violet Bureau was unable
to recover from a setback.
It failed the emperor's favor.
The late emperor passed away
with hatred.
Now,
we're seeing Your Majesty
in misery
and are unable to save you.
Everything
is my fault.
How can you say that?
You accepted the appointment
at a critical time.
Even if you're sick,
you supported the Violet Bureau.
You persevered until now
even under Qiu Ziliang's coercion
and even gave me a new Sword Bearer.
That's already not easy.
I know
that Your Majesty is not satisfied
with Yu'er.
She's erratic and rash.
And her ideas are very whimsical.
But like me,
she's loyal to you.
What happened today
can prove that.
After Cheng Ruoyu joined
the Violet Bureau,
she was admonished many times.
But that was because
she wouldn't change
her mischievous character.
In other aspects,
there's really nothing bad about her.
And she has nothing to do
with the various forces
outside of the Violet Bureau.
I think that when you met her that day,
perhaps it was really a coincidence.
How can anyone in this world
be that innocent?
That's rather suspicious.
I understand.
I'll continue investigating her.
Your Majesty.
Since Yu'er has already taken
the Carefree Pill,
in the near future,
Qiu Ziliang
won't bring you a second one.
But it's easy to dodge open attacks
and hard to guard against the secret ones.
Your Majesty.
Have you decided
on what to do next?
Madam Cheng.
Do you have any good plans?
Instead of backing down,
what if
you take a chance?
160.
161.
1...
Aunt.
Can I move now?
You're poisoned by the Carefree Pill.
Even if I helped you in forcing
almost half of the poison out,
based on the damage in your body,
you can't use your martial arts skill
for at least half a year.
Didn't I tell you already?
I wasn't poisoned.
This drug
will help you act like you are.
What do you mean?
We must hide it from people
and gain more time.
Sir.
Cheng Xi had already
removed the poison
from Cheng Ruoyu's body.
But Cheng Ruoyu is badly injured.
For the next half year, she won't
be able to use her martial arts skill.
After taking
the Careless Pill,
one will be in low spirits
and feel weak.
This drug is a slow-acting poison.
It shouldn't have activated
in her body immediately.
Yes.
I especially consulted
the Grand Councilor of the Left.
He said that Cheng Ruoyu
is a martial arts practitioner.
She has sufficient vital energy and Qi,
and it's unavoidable for her
to get injured.
So she had taken various medicines.
Perhaps the poison
conflicted with other medicines.
That was why the poison immediately
activated in her body.
Cheng Ruoyu
indirectly ruined
my plan.
I'm really unsure
if she's just pretending
or if she's really rash.
I was careless.
I wasted such a precious pill.
I'm willing to be punished.
Cheng Ruoyu's martial arts skill
is useless for now.
The Violet Bureau's wings
are cut off.
It can be counted as a gain.
Rise.
As for Qi Yan...
Father.
Forgive me for being bold.
Perhaps we don't need poison
to control Qi Yan.
♪Life is a dream,
how long do happy times last♪
♪In the windy rain,
where will my heart settle?♪
♪The sword can't break this karma♪
♪Look how blurry
and lonely the world is♪
♪Fate can't do anything
about the bleak bonds of this world♪
♪Still can't let go of this life
as time goes by♪
♪Even the iron and golden dagger-axe
cannot extinguish the fire in my heart♪
♪Remembering the past
and letting time while away♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪