♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 22=
Hello, Mr. and Miss Jiang.
May I ask when Mr. Lin will arrive?
(Press Conference)
Please be patient.
Any comments
on Lei Yuzheng's imprisonment?
Take it easy, everyone. Take it easy.
Please be patient. Please!
Excuse me, everyone.
(Entertainment Center Project)
If you have any questions,
please come in later and ask us.
Is it OK?
What happened to Lin Xiangyuan?
It is so late.
Dad. Let's go inside.
Whatever happens,
it shouldn't be you to wait for him.
Good morning, Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin, we have to hurry up.
There was a call from
the press conference.
Mr. Jiang is already there.
Is he? He is really free.
Then let him wait.
Sure. You're busy with work.
It's reasonable
to be a little bit late.
-Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin, may I ask you a few questions?
Hello, Mr. Lin.
What do you think of
the press conference today?
Mr. Lin, may I ask about
your comments
on Lei Yuzheng's imprisonment?
-Tell us please.
You were entrusted with the mission
at a critical moment,
and you brought the company
an investment.
How did you make it?
What's wrong with these journalists?
Dad,
you are the one who was entrusted
and also who steered Yutian.
Why is everyone focusing on him?
Actually, about these questions,
you should ask Mr. Jiang.
At the critical moment,
if it wasn't Mr. Jiang
who saved the critical situation,
there may not be this press conference.
Never mind.
Xiangyuan has also done a lot.
For young man as he is,
it's ok to show himself off
a little bit.
Mr. Jiang is not only my teacher,
but also my leader.
I owe everything I've done
to Mr. Jiang for his
help and support behind the scenes.
So, thanks to Mr. Jiang,
I can achieve success today.
Mr. Lin, can I ask you another question?
For further questions,
let's go inside and ask,
shall we?
Ok. Excuse me.
(Conference Entrance)
(Press Conference for the Progress of
Entertainment Center Project)
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Bro,
you have to watch
even if you don't want to.
This is the rule in the prison.
It's also called learning.
The press conference
on the achievements
of the phased construction
of Entertainment Center is held today.
(Press Conference for the Progress of
Entertainment Center Project)
It is reported that
this is the first press conference
of Yutian Group
after the imprisonment
of the former president, Lei Yuzheng.
Is it him?
Yes!
You don't look like that.
But I've been proven right.
I know you're not common.
So what?
Nobody is common in this room.
…Now he is in jail with us.
First of all, thank you all
for coming here. Today…
I guess,
your imprisonment
just gave this man a chance, right?
Make or break.
You can't blame others.
After the Entertainment Center project
is completed,
there will be
a grander celebration.
I'm full of confidence about it.
The Entertainment Center project
has experienced ups and downs
along the way.
Thus, on behalf of Yutian Group,
I'd like to express my deep gratitude
to everyone
who has contributed to this project.
Dad.
I still remember
when Yuzheng signed with S.G.,
it was also like this.
There was
a spectacular press conference.
Probably you have forgot.
But I haven't.
The person standing here
to give the speech
shouldn't be Lin Xiangyuan.
It should be Yuzheng.
Yuzheng is a good boy.
It's just...What a pity.
Fine. Forget it.
My little girl.
I'm not blaming you.
But since you're already engaged with
Lin Xiangyuan,
you shouldn't think about Lei Yuzheng
all the time.
What if Lin Xiangyuan is aware of this…
Dad,
I regret it.
At last.
What?
Please allow me to thank...
What's wrong, Fanlv?
Nothing. I just feel something wrong
with my stomach.
…It's my teacher,
Mr. Jiang Jin.
He turns out to be a rich person.
So what?
He is still imprisoned here
like us.
Come on.
Let me have an interview with you.
Talk about how you feel now.
-Yes. Tell us.
-Tell us.
What are you doing?
Wanna a fight?
If I don't know you're rich,
I will let it go.
Since I know that now,
I'll beat you up.
Yuzheng, what are you doing?
Don't bother.
There are guards at the door.
You are not content with that!
Not content!
What are you doing?
What's going on here?
Siyang.
Siyang, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
Siyang, are you ok?
What happened?
He had a heart attack.
Please call the doctor!
Call the doctor!
Open all the windows.
Ventilate the room.
Siyang, come on.
Is he pretending?
Isn't he?
Breathe, breathe.
It's real.
It's all right.
Breathe in through your nose,
and out through your mouth.
Siyang, Siyang.
Come on! Doctor!
(Press Conference)
Mr. Wang, I'll hang up.
(Entertainment Center Project)
Ok. Ok. Ok.
Miss Jiang,
you don't look well.
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
(Qingpu Branch of Zhongshan Hospital,
Fudan University)
-Qunfei.
-Yes?
You said that
Yutian has a press conference today?
Why don't you go there?
For what?
I am just nobody now.
It doesn't matter whether I go or not.
Besides,
I can't stand the showy look
of Lin Xiangyuan.
I'm afraid I'll punch him if I go there.
I should be blamed
for what happened to the Leis.
Xiaosu,
Mr. Lei's hand just moved!
Look!
It's really moving!
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor.
Mr. Lei just moved his hand.
Mr. Lei.
He's awake! Mr. Lei is awake!
Great！
Fanlv, how are you doing?
Are you still not feeling good?
I'm fine. Much better.
Dad, I have something to deal with.
I've got to go.
Ok.
Why is she distracted?
Mr. Lin.
Mr. Jiang,
I'll go to the construction site
with Mr. Xie.
Are you coming with us?
You go ahead.
I've been sitting all day,
and I've really got some backache.
I'm old and useless.
Come on.
You're vigorous.
Let me drive you home.
As a man,
you shall not nag me!
Business comes first.
Ok, take care.
(Press Conference)
Mr. Lin, let's go.
Mr. Lin.
The Entertainment Center project is
in great demand for money.
A hundred million is just gone
in the blink of an eye.
How much more money is expected?
There is nothing to expect.
You mean...
Not even a penny.
Yutian has other projects
other than the Entertainment Center.
Just put the Entertainment Center
project aside.
By the way,
what's wrong with Miss Jiang just now?
I just saw her vomit.
Vomit?
Keep an eye on her these days.
No matter what happens,
you must let me know.
Ok.
I'm telling you two that
the patient is incapable now
and can't express himself.
So, there must be someone
with him every minute.
Otherwise,
there will be problems.
Thank you.
Please leave.
Back off!
Bad guy.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mr. Lei.
Bad guy.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Mr. Lei,
you can't talk like this.
You're bad, too. Back off!
Ask bad guys to leave! Leave!
Fine, fine, fine.
Well, he is leaving right now.
He is leaving right now.
Mr. Lei, you're right.
I'm the bad guy.
Scold me.
He Qunfei, stop blaming yourself.
This is
the sequelae of cerebral hemorrhage.
He has no idea what he is talking about.
I should be blamed
for what happened to the Leis.
Xiaosu,
if Mr. Lei didn't wake up,
how could I explain to his son?
We were worried that
he could not wake up before.
But he's awake now.
So, we should be more confident now.
As long as he's not well,
we'll take care of him.
I believe that
he is gonna be fine one day.
Mr. Lei,
let's go home.
Here we go. Let's go home.
(Civilized Prison Cell)
Why are you back?
Why? You don't know me?
Are you fine?
Don't worry.
I'm a cat
with nine lives, and I can't just die.
Come over here. Have a seat.
Did you do it on purpose that day?
On purpose?
Are you pretending to be sick,
as you are afraid that
I'm gonna get punished?
My heart
has problems.
If it was not you that day,
I would be gone.
Why? Wanna change your career?
Don't wanna be a boss anymore?
Wanna take a job in finance?
Just take a look.
It seems like
you've also studied abroad.
Stanford Graduate School of Business.
That explains.
Your father is very far-sighted.
For such a large Group like Yutian,
there has to be someone to take over.
I failed them.
You can't put it this way.
You're not the only one to stumble
in the business world.
After I
graduated from Lancaster University
in the UK,
I joined
BlackRock in the UK.
In those years,
I was getting too arrogant.
See. This is where I am.
I haven't even asked you.
What's the reason?
Do you know
the Minsheng Road in Shanghai?
I
was the chief trader
in one of the fund management companies.
I don't need to tell you
the rest.
I don't get it.
I'm just like you.
Didn't you take all
the responsibilities on your own?
How do you know that?
Come out. It's time for exercise.
We have plenty of time. Take your time.
Mr. Lin, do you really wanna go there?
We should come sooner or later.
Since Lei Ting has been discharged
from the hospital,
we should come to see him.
He was the president of Yutian
after all.
Besides,
the one I hate is Lei Yuzheng,
not Lei Ting.
Let's go.
Mr. Lei.
Guys.
Hello, uncle Duan.
This is our regard.
So sorry to cost you.
(Luxury Gifts)
Thank you.
Not at all.
Mr. Lei is taking a nap.
He was here to get some sun, well...
He's awake.
Fine. I'll leave you alone.
I'll make you some tea.
Go ahead.
Mr. Lei, I'm Lin Xiangyuan.
Do you still remember?
Mr. Lei,
it seems you've recovered pretty well.
Great. That's great.
Then we can set our mind at rest.
Right, Mr. Lei.
Mr. Lin is very concerned about you.
As soon as he heard that
you were discharged,
he left his work
and came to see you.
Bad guys.
Mr. Lei, you're so good at joking.
We all work for you.
How can we be bad guys?
That's right.
Bad guys. Bad guys.
Back off! Back off!
Mr. Lin,
is Lei Ting really out of his mind?
Look at him.
He wants to eat us alive!
Mr. Lei,
don't you remember who I am?
I'm Lei Yuzheng's colleague.
Yuzheng?
Right. Where is Yuzheng?
Where is Yuzheng?
Bad guy. Give Yuzheng back to me!
I'll kill you! Kill you!
Mr. Lin.
Back off!
Let's go.
Or I'm gonna shoot!
Mr. Lei, calm down.
Can we take it easy?
Back off! Or I'll shoot!
Mr. Lei,
you wanna hit people with the stick?
All of you are bad guys! Bad guys!
Please don't. Give it to me.
What's going on?
Excuse me.
Mr. Lei suffered a bad illness.
He hasn't recovered yet.
He's still confused.
Are you hurt?
It's fine. It's fine.
Yuzheng, they are all bad guys.
They're guests.
You're bad, too.
Bad guy. Back off!
Look!
Back off! All of you!
Good lord.
He's yelling at everyone like this now?
He's out of his mind sometimes.
Let's make it another day, shall we?
Fine.
Ask them to leave!
They 're gone.
Excuse me.
What's that about?
It's bloody hell out of luck.
Got beaten for nothing.
He is out of your mind, isn't he?
Why is it so easy for him to get angry?
Never mind.
There is no need
to take offence at a patient.
Let him take it out.
Just consider it as
an apology I make to him.
Now Lei Yuzheng is in jail.
He is so sick.
Yutian shall count on me.
That's true.
You're the manager
of Yutian from now on.
You forgot about Jiang Jin and others.
Mr. Jiang is your future father-in-law.
He must be on your side.
Miss Jiang, congratulations.
You're pregnant.
Pregnant?
How could that happen?
Are you making a mistake?
Look at the report.
Don't worry. It's already
one month and a half.
(Qingpu Branch of Zhongshan Hospital,
Fudan University. Ultrasonography Report)
(Nanpu Bridge)
(Jiangkan Detention Center)
Yuzheng.
Fanlv.
Why are you so grief when you see me?
Is it because I'm getting old?
I just didn't expect that
we would meet here.
Look at you now.
I feel very sorry.
Don't worry. I'm great.
If only
we could go back to our childhood.
I still remember that
lemon soda was your favorite drink.
You liked to make fun of girls
with caterpillars.
You also liked to defend Zhenrong.
We were carefree at that time.
We used to be together every day.
How wonderful it was!
This is fate.
You're too young for believing in fate.
Don't you think so?
I don' t believe in fate.
I am used to
making fate submitted to me.
But I've gradually realized that
fate will always give you a blow
out of surprise,
so that you'll know that
your previous ambitions
were just a joke.
Fanlv, remember that,
no matter when,
I'm your family.
I know.
I didn't want you to treat me
like a sister before.
Now I've realized
how much I rely on you.
As long as you're around,
no matter what serious things happen,
I won't be scared.
Now I've grown up.
Now that I've made my decision,
I have to face it on my own.
I just came to see you.
As long as I see you,
I'll feel peace.
Fanlv.
Tell me.
Is there anything wrong?
Yuzheng, stop asking.
You're right.
Some things are meant to be happening.
Yuzheng,
don't worry.
No matter what happened,
no matter what I did,
I'll be good.
I'll wait for you to come out.
Take good care of yourself.
Fanlv,
I wish you are happy.
I will.
Don't worry about me.
Fanlv. Fanlv.
Listen to me.
Come in.
Mr. Lin.
This is what you want.
Leave it here.
Mr. Lin, please take a look.
(Qingpu Branch of Zhongshan Hospital,
Fudan University. Ultrasonography Report)
(Qingpu Branch of Zhongshan Hospital.
Dept. of Gynecology and Obstetrics)
She's really pregnant.
Why don't you tell me earlier?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I can be a father!
I'm a father! Yes!
I'm a father.
What? Anything else?
Mr. Lin,
miss Jiang is going to see
the obstetrics doctor tomorrow.
Ok.
Help me decline the work tomorrow.
I'll go with her.
Mr. Lin.
She...
She called the doctor for abortion.
Abortion?
That is my child!
It's my family's blood.
How dare she?
You're right.
Mr. Jiang,
here are
pine mushrooms, dictyophora,
wild fern, and hericium erinaceus
from my hometown.
These are all Fanlv's favorite food.
And this.
Last time when you were in my office,
you said this was pretty tasty.
So, I brought you two boxes.
Li.
Come over here.
Put them away.
Xiangyuan, you're really considerate.
I just said it,
and you keep it in your mind.
What's wrong?
Mr. Jiang, please don't tell Fanlv
those are from me.
Otherwise, she'll lose her appetite.
That's who she is.
Don't mind her words.
Come here. Have a seat.
Mr. Jiang,
Fanlv went to visit Lei Yuzheng?
Fanlv and Lei Yuzheng
grew up playing together.
It's natural to go to see him.
Mr. Jiang, you misunderstood me.
I'm just a little worried.
Although we are engaged,
but we're still not one family.
I'm afraid I'm wasting her time.
To be honest,
even if Fanlv regrets it,
I have no complaints.
I just hope that
she can find someone
who really loves her,
instead of wasting her time
waiting for someone
who doesn't deserve her love.
You're right.
It seems that,
as long as you're not married,
Fanlv's mind
won't settle.
How about this?
You prepare whatever you need.
I'll talk to Fanlv later.
Hurry up with your marriage.
Yes, Mr. Jiang, thank you.
I gotta go.
(Civilized Prison Cell)
Lei Yuzheng.
Get ready. Go to the reception room.
I don't wanna meet her.
Ok.
That girl is here.
You still don't see her.
Not willing?
I can't.
Why? Are you afraid you can't
hold on yourself if you meet her?
Look at yourself.
If I meet her one time,
she will come for another time.
So, I can't meet her.
In my opinion,
that girl is pretty determined.
Even if you go on like this,
I don't think she'll give it up.
Then, I'll find a way to make her give up.
People like me
have to be cruel.
That's being responsible for others.
What's the girl's name again?
Du Xiaosu.
Lei Yuzheng.
You are not cruel at all.
You love her deeply.
It really freaked me out
to take the flight of over ten hours.
Mrs. Shao, look at you.
Going abroad to recover really works.
You look much better
and are in a good mood.
What can I do?
Zhenrong has been gone
for more than one year.
I wanna be with him.
But the God doesn't allow me.
There is no way out.
I have to live a few more years.
Mrs. Shao, what are you talking about?
Fine. Forget it.
Could you please sort out the presents?
The nutrients are for Mr. Lei.
What happened to you?
Mrs. Shao, you have no idea.
When you're not around,
there was something wrong
with Lei's family.
We had a deal, right?
If you take the medicine seriously,
you'll get better soon.
I'm not sick. You are.
Mr. Lei, I'm coming.
Look.
Guess what I've brought to you.
Marshmallow.
Ok, here is the deal.
One bite of medicine,
one bite of marshmallow.
Come on.
Here.
Take it slow.
Great.
Take the marshmallow.
Actually,
there is no other way to coax him.
Just treat him like a kid.
Coax while persuading.
It depends on who it is.
Last time there were two guests.
Coax while persuading. It didn't work.
Mr. Lei kicked them out with the stick.
Who are they?
The last name of the boss is Lin.
They said they were Yuzheng's colleagues.
They specially came to see him.
Lin Xiangyuan?
It seems to be like him.
Du Xiaosu? What are you doing here?
Aunt Shao.
Why don't you come in first?
I'll explain to you later.
Mr. Lei, what's wrong?
You have marshmallow on your lips.
Like a Santa Claus.
Let's take it off.
Done.
What did you just call me?
Marshmallow.
Fine. Whatever you want.
As long as you're happy with it.
Marshmallow. Marshmallow.
Fine.
Mr. Lei, how about this?
As long as you're well behaved
in eating and sleeping,
every time I come to see you,
I'll bring you the marshmallow.
Fine. I promise.
Lei, this is Kaixuan.
Who is Kaixuan?
Mr. Lei, she's a friend.
Kaixuan is your friend.
A good friend.
A good friend?
He's confused again.
Aunt Shao, don't be sad.
The doctor said that
this is the sequela of
cerebral hemorrhage.
He'll get better in a while.
All we need to do is
to take good care of him.
You've been taking care of him recently?
Ms. Shao, you have no idea.
Thanks to Miss Du,
she has been coming all the time to
take care of Mr. Lei.
Though Mr. Lei is
confused sometimes,
who is the good guy or bad guy,
he knows it.
Don't you, Mr. Lei?
Marshmallow, good guy.
See?
Mr. Lei, how about this?
Let me talk with Aunt Shao.
Uncle Duan will take a walk with you
and get some sun.
Ok.
Fine.
Ok?
Great!
Let' go. Slow down.
I'll leave you alone.
Mr. Lei is just like a child.
As long as you spend more time with him
and talk to him,
he'll be happy.
Have you ever thought about it?
After he is recovered,
how are you going to
explain about Yuzheng to him?
I think...
I can't even think about it now.
Take one day at a time.
Aunt Shao, I didn't expect
we could talk like this.
It's all the past.
Thank you for helping Yuzheng
in the difficult time.
Lei Yuzheng offered me a lot of help.
He's in trouble now. I feel responsible.
There is one thing.
I hope you can do me a favor.
Lei Yuzheng is very stubborn.
He's in such a big trouble now.
He certainly doesn't need
the pity from others,
and doesn't want to get others
in trouble.
So, he doesn't wanna see me right now.
But I know,
whom he is most worried about
is his father.
If you visit him next time,
please help me take this picture to him.
Thank you.
Don't say that. That's what I should do.
Miss, have you really made up your mind
to give up this baby?
If you haven't figured it out,
calm down and think it over.
Generally speaking,
we don't suggest
to give up the first baby.
If you can keep it, keep it.
No, I've made up my mind.
Lin Xiangyuan, you are following me!
Fanlv.
I am concerned.
You've suffered from vomiting recently.
I'm begging you.
Could you please keep the baby?
This baby is ours after all.
I'm his father.
In any case,
you should discuss with me.
Yes, you're the father of the baby.
But you know that
it's not the right time for this baby.
I know.
This baby is not our plan.
You're not prepared yet.
No matter how much you hate me
or be mad at me,
We're the parents of this baby.
The baby is innocent.
I'm begging you.
Could you please keep this baby?
I know you're very angry.
I swear.
No matter what you wanna do to me,
I promise
I won't fight back or swear back.
Even if you ask me to disappear,
I'll be fine.
As long as you keep this baby.
Fanlv, I shouldn't be with you,
knowing that you don't love me.
I promise you.
I can disappear from your life.
Tomorrow...
No. At once...
I will resign at once,
and leave the company and the city.
But if you can give birth to this baby,
I'll try all my best to love him
and protect him.
As long as he can stay,
it'll be enough for me.
I swear.
Wait a minute.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle
in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪