Where are you going? Slow down!
Can you please slow down?
I can’t grab hold of everything.
Come. Get up. I’ll send you home, okay?
Don’t touch me. It hurts. It really hurts, you know?
It wasn’t me.
It was you.
Sorry. Come. Get up.
-Get up. -No!
Let’s go home.
I won’t get up. I have no home. What home is there?
I’ll -
I’ll go home myself!
Can you do it? Let’s go.
Don’t touch me. I’m sad. Put me down. Put me down.
You’ve drunk too much. How could I put you down?
Scum. Why are you carrying me? Let me down!
Let you down? Shouldn’t you get down by yourself?
If you don’t put me down, I’m going to bite you.
Don’t bite. Ouch!
Slowly.
Mom. I’ve really tried my best.
Why -
Why did it turn out this way?
Be good and go to sleep.
I didn’t want to let you down.
I know.
Can you see it, Mom?
Who’s making noise in the morning?
You two -
So soon?
You’re awake.
I -
Why am I here?
What do you think?
I -
drank too much?
Good that you remember.
How did you get back?
I carried her back.
What about your motorcycle?
It’s on the street. I’ll ride it back here later.
You abandoned your ride just to carry her back.
Great.
Go back to sleep in your room.
Understood. I won’t disturb you. I won’t disturb you. Hi, sister-in-law.
Relax. I’m not interested in drunkards.
Your battery went flat. I couldn’t contact your friend.
Thank you.
I’m really very sorry to have caused you trouble.
Do -
I go down from there?
I’m leaving.
Wait. We’re meeting your lawyer at 10AM.
Okay. I’ll see you there.
Brother Kong!
What are you doing in here? Get out!
I heard everything last night.
-Don’t tell me - -Heard what? Get out!
-No - -Get out!
It’s been a while. It’s been a while. Have a seat.
Have you thought it through?
Of course.
I will fully represent the involved parties,
regarding Ms Qiu Ying’s violation of Mr Ji Xiang Kong’s personal privacy
and personal reputation, to facilitate discussion.
My client is willing to accept reasonable compensation terms.
How much do you think is acceptable?
Name it.
One million. Not too much, right?
One million?
Is my reputation not worth a million dollars?
A million dollars? This is called a scam.
Watch what you say in front of the two lawyers.
Calm down. It’s okay.
Is there any room for negotiation?
Considering Ms Qiu Ying’s financial situation,
my client is willing to take the biggest step back.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Thank you.
How will you thank me? Please don’t say you’ll marry me.
I might really agree to it.
Excuse me. Lawyer Chen has barely left.
This is called teasing. Understood?
Regardless of your motive, thank you.
You’re welcome. I’m just saving myself some trouble.
Oh yes.
Let me give you some advice. Drink less in the future.
You’re so scary when you’re drunk. You talk too much.
What did I say?
Things that should’ve been said, things that shouldn’t have -
you said them all. Think about it. I’m leaving.
What did I say?
I don’t care about what you said.
Have you forgotten to tell me something?
Don’t pretend to be innocent or stupid.
You were drinking with Ji Xiang Kong last night?!
You lied to me and said you were with your friend!
Isn’t he one of my friends?
You -
Right?
You played me! Stand there, Qiu Ying! I’m not done with you!
Yi Yi. The snacks here are the best. Let’s go.
Let me get you some delicious food. Don’t be angry.
Welcome to Premium Snacks Liang Pin.
We won’t have to worry about snacks ever again.
Tell me the truth. What did you do yesterday?
Be honest or be punished!
Relax. We really didn’t do anything.
You didn’t do anything?
If you didn’t, why was he so willing to do the settlement today?
Who are you lying to?
I thought it strange too. Why was he suddenly willing to help me?
But nothing happened between us.
I had too much to drink.
You dared to drink too much?
You -
Yi Yi, this shrimp cracker is delicious.
Don’t change the subject. Tell me.
Did Ji Xiang Kong force you to drink?
No. He really didn’t.
Why did you drink so much then?
Don’t you know your own limit?
What if you drank too much and something had happened to you?
I was in a bad mood, so I drank a little.
I accidentally drank too much.
Even if you were in a bad mood, you shouldn’t have looked
for Ji Xiang Kong for a drink.
You could’ve had drinks with me! I’m so angry.
Alright. I’ll buy you more snacks. Don’t be angry.
I swallowed my pride to ask Jeffrey to step up.
What about him?
He turned around and reconciled with the female hosts.
The sponsors are asking for an explanation.
What explanation do I have? What explanation could I give?
I can’t be the manager anymore. I really can’t do it.
What happened, President Jin?
Did you know about the settlement between Ji Xiang Kong and Qiu Ying?
Settlement? When did this happen?
What do you mean when? It was yesterday!
Ask Lawyer Zhou about it.
Where is Ji Xiang Kong? Call him over.
I’m cancelling his contract.
President Jin. Calm down.
Ji Xiang Kong must have had his reasons for doing this.
Let me tell you. Don’t speak up for him.
President Bai is angry beyond belief.
If you don’t cancel Ji Xiang Kong’s
contract, this matter won’t blow over.
If this matter doesn’t blow over,
our team’s reputation cannot be salvaged.
Is pushing your teammate out once something bad happens
the working style of our team?
This matter was clearly orchestrated by someone
to harm Ji Xiang Kong and Chuan Qi.
Cancelling Ji Xiang Kong’s
contract without rhyme or reason -
aren’t you afraid the other teammates would feel let down?
President Jin. If we don’t cancel the contract,
how do we explain ourselves to our sponsors? Which is more important?
Zhao Yang. Have you managed to contact Jeffrey?
How have I not contacted him?
I have,but Jeffrey is ignoring me. What should I do?
What’s most important right now is to contact Jeffrey.
If Jeffrey could step up to clarify in person,
the problem will resolve itself.
Zhao Yang. If you truly have the team’s well-being at heart,
you will contact Jeffrey right away,
instead of sitting here and sowing discord between us.
What are you talking about?
You!
Who’s sowing discord?
-You! -Enough!
We’ll have a press conference on Monday.
If the problem isn’t solved by then,
we’ll cancel Ji Xiang Kong’s contract during the conference.
Has it gone through?
No.
Hello?
Brother Kong, have you met Jeffrey?
Not yet. The information might be wrong.
He might not be staying in this hotel.
Zhao Yang tattled on you in front of President Jin.
Hand it over.
Wait. Coach Luo will speak to you.
How could you not have discussed such a big thing with me,
and gone ahead secretly to settle with that lady?
Coach. Qiu Ying didn’t upload that video.
Do you have proof?
Not yet, but -
If you don’t have proof, why did you decide
to settle with Qiu Ying on your own?
You’re silently admitting to the rumors of your relationship.
If Zhao Yang bites on this point,
he can force the cancellation of your contract. Did you know that?
Coach, Qiu Ying is innocent.
She’s lost her job and sold her house.
With Zhao Yang’s methods, she would go bankrupt.
I cannot sacrifice innocent people to protect my own interests.
Looks like you’ve thought it through before the settlement.
Nothing I say will matter now.
No. No. Brother Kong.
President Jin wanted to cancel your contract today.
Coach Luo had a big fight with President Jin
before he compromised and gave you two more days.
Don’t talk like this.
Sorry, Coach.
I’ve caused you so much trouble.
The press conference is on Monday.
If Jeffrey could clarify things in person, things might just turn around.
I’m hanging up, Coach.
Jeffrey. Can I have a word with you alone?
I know why you’re looking for me.
I’ve seen the video online. It’s fake.
I hope you could step out to clarify that.
I heard that if this matter was seen as real,
you may be fired by your company.
Your attitude towards me that day made me very upset.
You paying a small price is acceptable.
If this is what it is, I don’t want to help a loser.
If you don’t clarify, do you want everyone to think
that you got beaten up by me?
Stop looking at the computer, Qiu Ying.
Put it away. Let’s eat.
Soon. Five minutes.
Our homemade spicy hotpot is here! Put away your laptop.
Come.
If you stare at the screen every day,
when will you eat on time?
Thank goodness for me. I’m an angel. Here.
Thank you, angel.
The man who marries you in the future will be so incredibly lucky.
Your tongue is so sweet.
Don’t eat it all by yourself.
-I want some too. -Mine fell.
You’re so selfish.
Look here, Yi Yi.
What’s that?
Ji Xiang Kong has released an audience survey on the Chuan Qi team.
A 70% support rate!
We’ve only made our settlement yesterday.
This went online today.
Did you know?
The key thing is our relationship rumors are being spread far and wide.
You have tabloids and you’re still laughing?
I’m not laughing.
-You are! -I’m not.
I don’t think Ji Xiang Kong
will be able to turn things around this time.
I heard that Chuan Qi’s sponsors
were beyond angry when they heard about this,
and threatened to kill the sponsorships.
At tomorrow’s press conference,
Chuan Qi may cancel Ji Xiang Kong’s contract.
What should we do? Can we help him?
It’s easier said than done.
Who are we? Who would listen to us?
How could we help him?
I don’t know.
Ji Xiang Kong helped me. I can’t stay out of this.
Most importantly, this started because of me.
Sister. You two have tabloids going on.
If you stepped up to say that
Ji Xiang Kong was innocent, who would believe you?
It’ll only get more complicated.
I could just put up the original video that I took.
Won’t that work?
How could you think of that? Look at the video you recorded.
You only managed to record the scuffle between the two of them.
Did you capture the
process in which Coach broke them apart?
Was it in there?
If you upload this video now, it will have no persuasiveness.
What should I do? Tell me.
Forget it. Eat up and we’ll think of something.
Hang on, Qiu Ying.
Look at that person. What about her?
She was filming this live too.
Maybe she captured the whole process.
If we could find this person,
and retrieve the complete video footage,
we can then prove Ji Xiang Kong’s innocence.
This person is overseas. How will we find her?
Are you going to Canada?
You’re so silly. Look. Isn’t this a tour group?
If it’s a tour group, they’ll have to come back.
If we find the tour group, we’ll be able to find this person.
If we find this person, and recover this footage,
we’ll have concrete proof!
Even if she came back,
there are so many tour groups in China. How will you find her?
Don’t forget that I’m a professional news reporter.
How could this little task confuddle me as Ms Reporter?
Don’t worry. Leave this to me. Hurry and eat up.
Look for the truth. Seek justice.
This is my true calling.
Silly girl.
Hello, Yi Yi. I found the tour company.
Their tour leader has brought a tour overseas
and will come back on an afternoon flight.
As long as you’ve found them.
Let’s pray that the flight isn’t delayed.
You predicted it. The flights are widely delayed.
Ji Xiang Kong is really unlucky. Even god isn’t helping him out.
There isn’t anything we can do.
Chuan Qi has notified the media.
The press conference will take place tomorrow morning
to announce Ji Xiang Kong’s contract cancellation.
I’ll wait a little more. Bye.
Brother Kong! You didn’t see my text messages?
Coach Luo just told me that Jeffrey has replied
and isn’t going to the conference. He’s leaving on a flight now.
Got it. Go back first.
No. Jeffrey is leaving. He’s on a plane.
Got it. Don’t worry. Head back to train first.
Whether my contract gets cancelled, we have to win this competition.
Are you okay?
I’m leaving. Jeffrey is leaving too.
Why isn’t the plane here yet?
It hasn’t departed.
It’s okay.
As long as the flight isn’t cancelled, we’ll still have hope.
Alright. I’ll wait here with you.
My Yi Yi is the best.
Come. Have some Jian Jiao to boost your energy.
Thank you.
I’m so sleepy.
Get up.
Take it easy.
What time is it? Look at your complexion.
If you keep waiting, you’ll look like raw ginger.
Go back first, Yi Yi. I’ll wait a little more.
Don’t wait anymore. It’s 3AM.
The press conference will start in a few hours.
Besides, even if you found the tour leader, it’s been so long.
She might have deleted the video.
As long as there’s a ray  of hope, I’ll wait.
Are you running a fever or did Ji Xiang Kong drug you?
Is he worth it?
It’s neither.
I feel like I should do something, or my heart will feel guilty.
Go back first, Yi Yi.
You still have to attend the conference.
Alright. I’ll head back first to prepare ahead of time.
I’ll be contactable anytime.
Take care of yourself. Bye.
Take care on the road. Bye.
Hello to everyone in front of their screens.
I am Lu Yi Yi, a reporter from Dong Gan E-Sports Magazine.
Now, we’re at Chuan Qi’s press conference venue.
Manager Zhao has said that today,
everyone will have an answer.
Now, please follow me to the live venue
to understand the latest happenings. Thank you.
Come in.
Manager Zhao.
-Come in. -Manager Zhao.
Here. How is it?
Here are the people today.
Not bad.
Not too shabby.
You’re more capable than I am.
Manager Zhao has led well.
I’ve spread some rumors that
Chuan Qi and Ji Xiang Kong are cancelling the contract.
That’s how it should be.
We have to really blow this matter up.
Do you know what President Jin likes?
Face!
After the contract cancellation,
even if Ji Xiang Kong was innocent,
he wouldn’t be able to come back. Right?
To be honest, Manager Zhao,
I’ve already prepared the contract cancellation letters.
Why are you still standing here? Ask him to sign them!
Got it! I’ll do that right now.
Please come in.
-Brother Kong. -Ji.
The press conference is about to begin.
There are many reporters outside. What should we do?
I don’t know why this press conference is necessary.
Great. Another pest.
You’re all here. This is the contract cancellation document.
If there are no issues, please sign here.
We’re not signing. Has the conference begun? What’s the rush?
That -   If there’s nothing else, I’ll take my leave.
Please go ahead.
Tell Zhao Yang that I’ll sign, but it will have to be after his entire act.
I’ll sign it right in front of him.
Hello, Yi Yi.
Qiu Ying. How is it going over there?
Look. Everyone is nearly here. The conference is about to start.
The plane has landed, but she hasn’t come out yet.
Will it really be too late?
What should we do?
Alright. I’ll wait for your news.
The bus is outside. Come.
Get up the bus here.. Follow me.
Wait!
Manager Zhao is here.
Welcome, everyone, and thank you for taking time
out of your busy schedules to come for the conference.
Our conference today will have -
Manager Zhao. According to reliable sources,
Ji Xiang Kong settled with Qiu Ying of his free will yesterday.
Is this true? Yes, Manager Zhao.
Can we say with certainty that the video
Qiu Ying had uploaded is completely real?
Ji Xiang Kong did indeed attack Jeffrey in Vancouver?
Also, Manager Zhao.
If Ji Xiang Kong’s contract is cancelled,
I mean if, will there be a new
team member joining Chuan Qi?
We’re concerned about this as well. Right, everyone?
Yes, Manager Zhao. Please answer, Manager Zhao.
Please remain quiet. Please have a seat.
Firstly, I hereby represent the company and
Ji Xiang Kong to give everyone an apology.
Wait! Wait!
May I know where your tour leader is?
In that car.
Thank you!
Excuse me, wait!
Watch out!
Are you alright?
I finally found you!
We’re deeply apologetic about this messy situation.
Hurry.
Therefore, the company will announce
the cancellation of Ji Xiang Kong’s -
Manager Zhao.
I have a video in my hands that can prove Ji Xiang Kong’s innocence.
Do you want to see it?
Really?
What video? Let me see!
Hurry, look!
Who is that? Who’s that in the video?
That’s all? Hurry. Take a look.
Ji Xiang Kong -
didn’t assault anyone.
He didn’t assault anyone.
What’s happening here? Please explain, Manager Zhao.
Despite the blurriness of this video,
you can clearly see that Ji Xiang Kong did not assault anyone.
Manager Zhao. Have you seen this video before?
Have you seen it before? Have you seen this video before?
Please answer, Manager Zhao.
What is it, Manager Zhao?
Take a look. Ji Xiang Kong didn’t assault anyone.
Yeah. Have you seen this video before?
Please answer, Manager Zhao.
What about it, Manager Zhao? Tell us more.
Neither I nor the company had seen this video before.
However, this piece of unofficial content
with extreme blurriness and without official confirmation
cannot be taken to be 100% real information.
Also, we will not negate the decisions
taken by the company because of this strange video,
or to needlessly protect our own team members.
Manager Zhao. Do your words represent the views of your entire team?
Now that we have evidence that could prove Ji Xiang Kong’s innocence,
you’ve denied it without confirmation.
Is it you or your team
that couldn't care less about the innocence
of your own team member?
Yeah!
Every word from me represents the entire company.
We treasure our team members,
but we will not forgive or accept these terrible acts of assault.
The decisions taken by our company were built on solid evidence.
To our dear reporter friend here -
if you really had
the powerful evidence of the involved parties,
and didn’t simply take out this
blurry video footage, we would consider it. Really.
-You - -Furthermore,
Jeffrey himself is no longer in the country, right?
Manager Zhao is right.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Ji Xiang Kong. They’re saying that the video
just now was fake.
Did you hit anyone? Ji Xiang Kong.
Please answer, Ji Xiang Kong.
Did you assault anyone? Ji Xiang Kong.
Please stay quiet.
The sudden surfacing of this video cannot be taken
as concrete evidence, due to precautions.
Who told you to come?
Your appearance will only make matters worse,
and cause more trouble for the team. Did you know that?
No one knows the details of the incident
better than I, the involved party, do.
I believe that everyone here in this room today
will hope to get some direct information from me.
Ji Xiang Kong. What actually happened that day?
Yeah. What happened?
Please calm down.
What I want to say has been viewed by you in the video just now.
If you still don’t believe it, you can ask Jeffrey himself.
Jeffrey has gone back home.
How will he corroborate with your story? Right?
Manager Zhao. What era are we living in now?
With our evolved telecommunication,
do we have to have them present before we can clarify matters?
What’s that? What’s that?
I have a video footage. Please take a look.
The footage online is fake.
How could I have been assaulted by Ji Xiang Kong?
That’s incredulous.
Ji Xiang Kong. I’ll admit that your strategy is strong.
I’ll wait for you in the next season’s global finals competition.
That means that the assault video footage was falsified?
Ji Xiang Kong was wrongly accused!
That’s right! Ji Xiang Kong was wrongly accused!
Ji Xiang Kong!
What’s the relationship between you and Qiu Ying?
Why did she have to do this?
What happened?
I trust that you are all clear about the assault incident.
As for the relationship between me and a
certain female host that you all care about,
there isn’t really a story to tell here.
She didn’t upload the falsified video.
Qiu Ying and I are both victims.
As for the person who falsified
the video and tried to frame me,
Chuan Qi and I will definitely find him and punish him by law.
Manager Zhao. Chuan Qi was intending to announce
the cancellation of Ji Xiang Kong’s contract.
However, now that his innocence has been proven...
That -
As I’ve said just now, if Ji Xiang Kong was innocent,
our company would definitely not cancel his contract.
Thank you, Manager Zhao, for your understanding.
Also, I hope that everyone present will help our
Chuan Qi team to capture the mastermind.
Alright.
After this, it’ll be the media interviews.
If you have any questions, please ask Manager Zhao.
I’ll head off first.
What will I explain? I can’t explain anything.
Please answer, Manager Zhao.
Please explain.
Who is this mastermind?
Nothing. Please continue.
Let me tell you, Qiu Ying. It’s been resolved.
It’s been resolved.
Ji Xiang Kong had some conscience.
It was worth the overnight stay in the airport.
I can’t do it anymore. I’m going to take a nap here.
You can’t sleep in the airport!
Don’t hang up. Wait for me. I’ll look for you!