[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 26]
Xiang Kong!
Please hold,
come to the front of the stage with me for a while.
Just a little of your time.
Come on, it's okay.
Here, let's invite Xiang Kong to the front of the stage
because there's a fan who is related
to you in the venue today
so
do you have anything you'd like to say to her?
How about
staffs,
I'll ask Mi Ya first.
Do you have anything to say about
Wei Teng's performance today?
Xiang Kong,
all the best to you.
Although today's competiton
is a little pitiful,
but I know you guys will be able
to get better results
the next time.
So you're still confident
in Wei Teng's following performance?
Of course
because I believe in Ji Xiang Kong.
I will always
stay by his side.
Even though he lost the competition
but in my heart,
he's always the best
professional player.
So
at such a time,
I want to gossip a little.
Why do I feel that
the relationship between the both of you
is unusual?
We grew up together,
we chased our dreams together.
He is my first love.
Today's job
is over.
Yoou've worked hard.
Head back and rest early.
Never thought there will be
a small segment after
the competition ended.
Then let me ask.
Xiang Kong,
do you have
anything to tell Mi Ya?
Thank you for coming
to support my competition.
I hope everyone will support Wei Teng
and follow us closely on our competition.
Thank you.
No wonder you have mood to compete,
you're actually in a triangle scandal
with the celebrity and commentator.
Qi Yue,
what the hell are you talking about?
What?
The competition is affected bc he's in a relationship,
is it wrong to tell him off?
Celebrity Girlfriend
came to watch you compete,
rumoured Girlfriend is the commentator at the venue.
Why?
Were you nervous till you're crippled?
Is that so?
Qi Yue,
don't push the blame here.
You know it very well
on why we lost the competition.
You dare to push me?
You really thought
you're the ace player of Wei Teng?
Qi Yue, are you done?
Brother Qi.
Li Gan, do you see it?
In your disciple's eyes,
we do not exist.
Aren't you letting go?
Sit well.
Master.
Sister Wen.
We lost this competition
too ridiculously.
I did not perform well
but the tactics
itself have too many problems.
Ji Xiang Kong is just...
I think that you've not sober up.
Everyone is unhappy
that we lost the competition.
Qi Yue,
apologise to Sister Wen quickly.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be drinking.
I've been working outside these few years,
I felt pressured that
my Mother is here this time
so I drank too much on accident.
I promise on the
next match...
Next match?
You still intend to
play the next round in this state?
Or do you want to bring
your Girlfriend along?
I do not object dating
but can you please
don't affect the competition?
Alright,
stop scolding him.
We're all tired, quickly
head back to your rooms and rest.
We'll talk about this tomorrow.
What do you mean?
You're letting this matter go?
You're just going to shelter
you disciple like this?
Nobody is willing to lose in the competition.
Qi Yue already know  that he's in the wrong.
If he really knows that, he wouldn't
have push
the blame to Ji xiang Kong.
Qi Yue,
from now onwards,
you don't have to play anymore.
Master,
you're putting me in the reserve too?
Ji Xiang Kong, you...
Brother Qi,
don't cause trouble anymore.
Despicable.
You can date
but others can't.
Qi Yue,
you can waste your talents
but I'll not allow you to ruin Wei Teng.
Shu Wen,
do you have to?
Isn't it just losing a match?
You're putting
Qi Yue in the reserve.
Qi Yue is your disciple,
but you don't even know
what he does everyday.
Li Gan,
Wei Teng is my everything.
I'll definitely not let it
get ruined in the hands of Qi Yue.
Yes, Wei Teng is your everything
but it's also my everything.
You have to remember,
I'm the biggest shareholder.
Have you thought
of discussing this matter
with me beforehand?
What do you take me as?
Okay,
I also hope you remember
that I'm Wei Teng's coach.
I have the rights
to handle the members.
Biggest shareholder right?
If you have any issue next time,
do hold a shareholder meeting.
I'll cooperate anytime.
Master,
I've won so many
competition for Wei Teng.
I'm also the first for MVP
but just because I lost a match,
you're putting me in the reserve?
Isn't Sister Wen
being too unfair to me?
Qi Yue,
you better think through
carefully on where you did wrong.
Otherwise, this Master of yours
can't help you anymore.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Ji Xiang Kong,
when were you
and Mi Ya together?
Did Mi Ya return to develop
because of you?
When will the official annoucement be?
-Say something.          -Everyone,
we still have
many competiitons,
please do us a favour.
We need to rest now,
okay?
-Qiu Ying is out.          -Quick.
Qiu Ying, you broke up other's relationship.
Shameless.
Anybody would like Mi Ya
and not you.
They were childhood friends
and you have to get involved.
Xiang Kong.
I did not break
up anyone's relationship.
Not in the past
and never in the future.
Trouble you to stay far away
from Ji Xiang Kong.
Stay far away.
Xiang Kong,
you mustn't go over.
What are you doing?
Follow me.
You can't go.
Don't leave.
I'm here.
Teacher Luo,
thank you.
Today,
let the work
you have on hand be.
Don't think about anything else.
Rest well.
I'm sorry,
I'm the cause of
such a big mess.
You did not let anyone down.
Those let those
messy voices
affect you.
He's my first love.
I'm finally successful now,
I can give him support
and help him fulfil his dreams.
Xiang Kong said,
he'll always be by my side.
Yi Yi,
what brings you here?
If I do not come,
what will become
of you from the bullying?
Who dares to bully me?
How's my first
commentary?
Don't change the topic.
Let me ask you,
do you already know about
Ji Xiang Kong and Mi Ya?
You went to Mi Ya's fanmeet
with Ji Xiang Kong
and came back drenched.
Does that have to do with this issue>
Mi Ya is Ji Xiang Kong's ex-Girlfriend.
Now,
she's back for him.
Then what are you?
Lin Yi Xuan even said,
that day,
he booked a secret garden restaurant
to confess to you.
I thought
he really likes you.
Yi Yi,
maybe we misunderstood him
from the start.
You don't know
what Mi Ya and Ji Xiang Kong
has been through together.
How much they sacrifice for each other.
At the venue just now,
when Mi Ya announced their relationship
infront of so many people,
I really admire her.
Mi Ya can really
give up everything
for Ji Xiang Kong.
No,
are you dumb?
She's your rival,
yet you're
speaking up for her?
I'm not speaking for anyone.
Maybe he only noticed me
because I imitated
Mi Ya's dance
at the start.
Rather than to suffer
in this relationship,
I should give up as soon as possible.
But
can you really do it?
From now onwards,
I'll put all my focus
on my career.
Alright,
as long as you thought it through.
Qiu Ying,
wait till you become Iconquer
best female commentator,
the whole stadium would
definitely
not be enough for those who wants to woo you.
Don't cry anymore.
What did you buy?
A gift for you
but you can't open it now.
Okay, I'll settle this issue. Yes.
Okay.
Yes.
This matter is my mistake.
Yes, it's my mistake.
I'll settle this matter well.
Yes.
Brother Tony,
Sister Mi Ya followers on Weibo
has dropped by a few thousand,
it's still going down.
Also, there's fans who wants Sister Mi Ya to....
Why don't I go on Weibo
and talk about the issue?
No way,
you can't do that.
I'll settle it.
Kai Lun,
post a statement under
the company's name.
-Hurry.           -Okay.
Hello, President Li.
Yes.
I'll get it settled as soon as possible.
Give me two days time.
Yes.
It's my dereliction of duty.
I apologise,
sorry.
Tony,
what did President Li say?
President Li said
that the company will stop
the production for your new album.
We also lost some business activities
but don't worry,
I'll get them back.
Hello,
yes.
Don't worry about your loss,
we'll definitely compensate you
so the following collaboration...
Sorry.
My apologises.
I want to head out for a breather.
I'm sorry, Tony.
Hello.
Eat up quickly.
You eat first,
I'm not hungry.
What's happening
between you and Mi Ya?
You're really good,
hiding it from me too.
Have you seen Weibo?
It's only been a few hours,
Mi Ya followers
has dropped by a few thousand.
Qiu Ying got it worse,
all the comments are scolding her.
Can you give
me some peace?
Aren't I just worried about you?
Although you're my Brother Kong
but  I siding Qiu Ying this time round.
It's not that Im afraid of Yi Yi scolding me
but I really think that you and
Qiu Ying are made for each other.
Put it down,
Can you not annoy me?
Go back to your room.
Okay,
I shalln't annoy you.
Calm yourself down,
okay?
Eat up.
Xiang Kong,
are you okay?
Are you angry at me for
causing such a mess?
I an very angry.
I'm only angry
at why didn't you
discuss it with me beforehand?
At least let me be mentally prepared.
If I were to discuss it with you beforehand,
will you still allow me to annouce it?
Mi Ya,
I've been with you for so many years.
Do you not trust me enough?
It's too late to say anything now.
You made such a big sacrifice
but the result might not be what you wish for.
Xiang Kong and I
been through a lot together.
Despite what the result may be,
I want to prove it to this relationship.
Is it worth it?
Through these years,
I've been living
under then fans' imagination and anticipation.
Dare not allow people to see-through me,
all the more I don't want them to be disappointed
but I want to be myself now,
just like any normal being
being able to date.
I'm prepared for the worst
when I decided to announce it,
just that I got you involved.
I'll think of a solution
to settle the company.
As for the media and sponsers,
we're still trying.
What's important now
is for the fans to accept your
relationship with Ji Xiang Kong soon.
You should know my situation now
better than I do,
you really don't have to go against the company
and delay your future
just for me.
I'll naturally leave
when you're of no value anymore.
Tony,
I've known you for many years
but I don't seem to know you well.
Sometimes,
you seem as cold as
a stranger
but now,
you're the only one I can depend on
when I'm in trouble.
Qiu Ying.
Can we have a chat
on some things?
I know you don't wish to see me
but some things isn't
like what you've seen.
Let us have a chat
okay, Qiu Ying?
Sorry,
give me some time.
I'll get it settled.
Cry if you want to.
You can take it as I'm not here.
Head out for a breather.
Feeling better?
You broke up with Ji Xiang Kong?
We
were never together.
That's good.
Now
there's many people scolding you online.
Pei Xi,
I thought
you only know how to play games,
you won't even look at
those gossips online.
I'm only concern about you
and Ji Xiang Kong.
Pei Xi,
thank you.
I'm feeling better now.
You should head back and rest since
you have competition tomorrow.
I'll go first.
Wait,
if you need help,
I can be your Boyfriend.
There are many other girls that like you,
you don't have to waste
your time on me.
You think too much,
I don't like you.
I only hope that you'll
not trouble Ji Xiang Kong.
I
trouble
Ji Xiang Kong?
This...
Time preparation for the competition is tight.
He's already in the losing group,
he can't lose anymore.
Both of your matters will only affect him.
Netizens will stop scolding you
if I'm your Boyfriend.
That way,
he can prepare for the competition at ease.
Pei Xi,
you're willing to be my Boyfriend
because of Ji Xiang Kong?
Your thoughts are really weird.
He's someone I admire a lot,
I hope that I'm able to play
against him again during competition.
You can
sacrifice yourself
just because you admire him?
It's not like I'm really being your Boyfriend,
I'm still willing to
make such a small sacrifice.
Why did you chase him out of Legends
if you admire him so much?
I did not.
I joined
Legends back then
because of him.
My only condition for joining Legends is
for Ji Xiang Kong to continue being the captain
but Zhao Yang lied to me.
When I wanted to leave after
knowing the truth,
Ji Xiang Kong told me
the responsibilities of what a
professional player should be,
can't just abandon our teammates.
Then why didn't you explain?
Don't you know
that all of us thought that
you chased Ji Xiang Kong out.
I don't care
what others think.
I only want Ji Xiang Kong to know
but
you guys don't
give me a chance.
You mean that time at Meng Lu Ren?
You gave us food and drinks
just so that you can speak to him?
Alright,
don't worry.
I'll not trouble him.
What do you intend
to do next?
How are you going to
deal with the questions?
Maybe
you really need a Boyfriend
as a shield.
Even so, I don't have to trouble you.
Otherwise,
you'll be my best guy friend.
What kind of expression is that?
If only I brought a
lollipop along.
What lollipop?
I'll go back now.
Head in quickly.
Turning of your phone won't solve the problem.
Xiang Kong,
you have to face it regardless.
I said whatever I have to,
I don't understand
why did she still do that.
Nobody is able to
let go of such relation
of so many years.
Furthermore,
she thinks that
the problem between the both of you
is that she's
unable to go public
with your relationship.
Brother Sun,
do I really have to
tell it to everyone that
I've already
broke up with her long ago?
Do you bear to do that?
Online says that her company
has stopped all the schedules.
If you step out now to say
that both of you are over,
isn't she going to be the biggest joke
in the entertainment industry?
Her career will be completely ruined.
But what about Qiu Ying?
She's innocent.
The three of you are all innocent.
No matter what
decision you make now,
one of them will definitely be hurt
or maybe even three.
Think about it after the competition.
You're not to blame for losing this match,
that Qi Yue
has terrible moodswings.
Luckily,
the problem is shown now.
Do your best to face
and solve it.
It's just that
you can't afford to lose anymore.
I know that.
Sister Wen must be the
most stressful one now.
Eat some fruits.
Eat up.
Let me tell you
this restaurant is really expensive.
Just to treat you to this meal,
I search for a long time.
Eat more.
Cheer me on later.
I don't have to mood to
eat these.
Don't even know
if Qiu Ying is feeling better.
She's busy now,
I don't want to disturb her.
Brother Kong is being too secretive,
he didn't even breathe a word
to me about his
relation with Mi Ya.
Right?
You say how scary can he be
to not even tell you about it.
Do you know?
Every official and marketing account
are spreading about Mi Ya and
Ji Xiang Kong's past
about how they were childhood friends
and how much Ji Xiang Kong helped
and supported her when she was
just a trainee.
It's Ji Xiang Kong's love
that lifted her dreams.
They seperated for 5 years
but never give up till the end,
finally together because of love.
Writing it as if it's a romance novel and even
hope that fans will give them their blessings.
Let me have a look.
Quick.
There's even a video.
Brother Kong
is really someone who priortise relationship.
No wonder he didn't have a
Girflfriend for a long time.
As if.
If he does,
why did he get close to Qiu Ying?
Don't get angry,
I'm definitely on your side,
right?
What's the use of it?
Main point is what does Ji Xiang Kong
treat Qiu Ying as?
A substitute for Mi Ya?
No,
I can guarantee for him that
he never had feelings for
any other girls before.
Really.
He definitely likes
Qiu Ying,
otherwise he wouldn't have confessed.
Now, Mi Ya
has already admitted
and announced it.
Why didn't he
step out and clear the air
if he has no relation
with Mi Ya?
What now,
everybody is saying that
Qiu Ying broke them up.
Evetybody is scolding her.
This issue is difficult,
new love on one side while the other is his old love.
How difficult.
Still new and old love,
let me tell you.
Birds of the same feather flock together,
you're not any thing good either.
What does it have to do with me?
Tell him that I said
if I see anyone
bullying Qiu Ying,
I'll be the first to
find him accountable.
It has nothing to do with me,
don't get mad at me.
Waiter, bill please.
Isn't it my treat today?
I don't care for your treat.
This...
Isn't approriate, is it?
This Mi Ya and Ji Xiang Kong
is pretty compatible.
Someone actually wants to be a third party.
The both of them
supported each other and
go through thick and thin together.
It's difficult to seperate
a couple like them,
someone actually harborevil intents
taking such advantage.
Even if this Ji Xiang Kong is a playboy,
he's just playing anyway.
To think that you believe
such act,
don't you even take a look at yourself?
What are you all talking about?
Seen all the information?
Yes.
Start the meeting.
Your followings are increasing again.
Never thought that
there'll be people who understands me.
The discussions are slowly
inclining towards us.
There's a few artistes
who spoke up for you yesterday.
They say,
it's everyone's freedom to date.
Everything an artiste do shouldn't
be controlled by their fans.
I can finally
let go of my burden.
Thank you too, Tony.
You have to thank yourself too.
Everyone got moved by
your persistence.
To be honest,
I'm also moved by you.
I still have to thank you
for everything you've done.
Tony,
Xiang Kong just lost in his competition.
Can I visit him?
Go ahead.
Keep it low profile, come back quickly.
-I'll let Kai Lun make the arrangements.         -Okay.
This is the
statistics for the practice round just now.
Liu Miao,
you played with us less so
you've shown a number of mistakes this time.
You're good at jungling
but not so good
for a support.
Shen Yue,
practice with him more.
Heighten up your teamwork.
Okay.
We don't have much time left.
How is it?
Going on smoothly?
-Sister Shu Wen.          -Sister Wen.
Sister Wen.
you don't have
to be too nervous,
cooperate with everyone more.
Mi Ya is here.
Sister Wen,
we're still having a meeting.
We still have to
practice later.
Alright,
I'll settle it for you.
Thank you, Sister Wen.
You guys continue.
All the best.
Let's continue.
Sister Wen,
Is Xiang Kong still okay?
I couldn't contact him for the past two days.
He also lost in his competition,
I'm pretty worried about him.
Xiang Kong is well,
don't worry.
Just that Wei Teng has
entered the losing group,
the following match
is very important to us.
We can't let the
the players get distracted.
Sister Wen,
I just want to tell him something.
It shouldn't
take up a lot of his time.
But Wei Teng
is now having
an enclosed practice training.
Xiang Kong is the leader,
he has to set an example.
You should understand him.
If you've anything to say,
tell him after the competition,
okay?
I really don't know
how can I express my
gratitude towards you.
No need to.
The tumblr you gave,
I like it a lot.
Qiu Ying,
Teacher Luo.
I found your notebook.
Where did you find it?
The cleaner
picked it up from the dustbin.
Just don't know who
tore it up.
Dustbin?
I spent a
long time writing these notes.
You see if
there's anything useable.
Talk about this later.
Go get prepared
for the competition,
I'll be right back.
I'll go prepare then.
Sure, let's watch the competition together.
-I'll bring you there.        -Okay.
Qiao Xin.
Teacher Luo.
You can go home now,
We don't need to host today.
Go home?
Why?
Yes, Teacher Luo.
Really,
Qiao Xin's performance
recently is especially good
so I...
Why?
Normal personnel transfer,
do I need a reason for it?
Teacher Luo.
I say this Luo Tiean is really....
What did you do
to offend him?
Teacher Luo,
I'm ready.
Okay,
if you have anything in the future,
tell me.
Don't get pushover by others.
Let's start.
Still okay?
Hello everyone,
welcome to the venue
of one of the final match of Iconquer.
I'm the commentator for today,
Luo Tian.
Hello everyone,
I'm commentator, Qiu Ying.
Legends will be up against
Dragon today.
The losing team will
enter the losing group automatically
to play against Wei Teng.
Yes.
So Qiu Ying,
who do you think will do better
among the two team?
Teacher Luo,
you're asking the obvious.
Both teams are equally as outstanding,
I can't offend any of them.
Dragon has been really eye-catching
throughout the entire season.
They have a very unique way of playing.
The top player has more economic
as compared to other players.
Also, their marksman is resistance to pressure.
Legends has met with lots of
difficulties in this season.
After changing their captaint twice,
they finally adapted to
Pei Xi's tactic of 4 protecting 1
throughout the season.
Indeed.
Legends are up against
Dragon today.
I believe it will bring us
a very different match.
I'll pass the time to
Ah can who's on stage now.
Attack.
Can attack, go.
Wait for me.
My skill is still around,
skill is around.
Lu Feng, damage.
Go.
Top, attack.
Middle, come here.
Lu Feng, damage.
I'm detouring.
Attack.
This wave of attack is okay.
Sir, you've drink
too much today
and we are also closing soon.
Why don't you...
What now?
Afraid that I can't pay, is that so?
That'snot what I meant.
Even you look down on me too.
Qi Yue,
stop drinking.
Sorry.
I'll take care of him.
Howdo you know I'm here?
Didn't you look for other guys?
Didn't you say I have no future?
Qi Yue,
you know it very well
on how I treated you these years.
I just want to be successful
but at the end of the day,
everything I do
is for
considering our future.
At times like this,
all the more I won't leave you.
Unless,
you don't want to see me.
Then I'll go.
Qi Yue.
Don't go.
If you were to leave,
I really have nothing left.
We are pretty similar,
we only want to be successful
but we don't get recognised.
Everybody looks down on me,
only you treat me the best.
Be careful.
What rights do they have to look down on you?
What Wei Teng has today
is all because fo you.
In the end,
they put you in the reserve.
There's no reason for me to stay
after they treat me like this.
At most, we'll go our own ways.
Are you dumb?
If Wei Teng were to get the champion,
that glory
will only belong to Ji Xiang Kong.
How will that even relate to you?
Unless,
you're willing to watch what's
belong to you get snatched
by others?
Even if they were to get champion,
it should be you who lead them
to the championship.
I have a plan,
are you willing to try?
Master.
I'm back.
It's my wrong previously.
Even cause you and Sister Wen
to fall out.
I promise you that
I'll never drink again.
Qi Yue,
I'm the one that taught you
and you're someone I trust most.
You should know it very well
on Wei Teng's situation.
I thought it through these few days,
if it's not for you to me a chance
to join Wei Teng,
I'll probably never be able to fulfil
my dream of a professional player.
Now that Wei Teng is in the finals,
it's just a step away from the champion
so
as long as I'm able to help the team,
I'm willing to listen to you.
Master,
forgive me.
It's good that you understand.
Yesterday,
Dragon lost to Legends.
We will be up against
Dragon who also entered
the losing group.
This is our only chance.
Master,
I've watch a number of
dragon videos recently.
I want to interact with the rest.
Have not eaten right?
Sit down and eat.
Talk later.
President Guo.
You're here, sit.
Why did you look for me for?
What's the reason for
changing Qiao Xin away?
Normal personnel transfer.
Technically,
I shouldn't be involved
in the commentator arrangements
but Qiao Xin's performance
is not bad in the analyzing table.
Her popularity is good too.
I can't accept
that reason for
changing her away.
After all, Qiao Xin is cultivated by
You Xing and us.
You have to give her more opportunities.
When she has the potential,
I'll naturally give her the chance.
Luo Tian,
commentary is the pride
of Ji Guang.
Skills
as well as character
are very important elements.
Yu should've heard about it.
Qiu Ying
is a big problem.
President Guo,
these are just rumours.
I don't if they are rumours
or the truth,
what I see is
Ji Guang's repuatation.
With all the negative news,
can you guarantee Qiu Ying's
working condition?
If Qiu Ying were to cause any problems
at work,
I'll take full responsibilities.
Luo Tian,
work and personal matters are different.
I hope you do not bring your feelings
into work.
President Guo,
I don't quite understand what you mean.
I've never seen you
being so nice to someone.
Furthermore, it's to a rookie commentator.
Sister Qiao Xin,
you're early.
Morning.
How's preparation?
Almost done.
Have you heard?
Wei Teng is in trouble.
What happened?
I heard Ji Xiang Kong
fainted in the meeting room.
Sister Wen is going crazy.
So serious?
Don't they still have a
competition tomorrow?
Seem like
Ji Xiang Kong can't play tomorrow.
Wei teng is in trouble.
What to do?
It's a pity.
Why isn't he picking up?