[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 15]
Brother Kong,
the days where you're not with the team,
I'm really not used to it.
Yes,
you're feeling uncomfortable
without me scolding you for days, right?
That make sense.
By the way, Brother Kong
I feel
that you going to an oversea team
is not a bad choice too.
Coach Luo said,
that is the world's
third team.
People is willing to spend so much money to hire you,
how sincere.
Enough,
I have my own plans,
you play well for your competition.
Don't worry.
By the way,
I asked you out today,
you know what I want to say right?
You don't have to praise me,
I should be hardworking,
I know.
You..
You don't have to listen to Coach Luo,
always making things complicated.
Brother Kong,
you have already changed your team,
can...
Stop.
You better stay
at Legends,
don't even think of going anywhere.
What are you thinking?
Who wants to leave with you?
My god.
What I mean is,
now that you are going to another team,
what if the both of us meet on the competition.
You hide a little from me.
I hide from you?
No,
all my technics are taught by you.
If I were to meet you,
I will definitely lose.
Look at your terrified look.
No, Brother Kong,
about the transfer,
I really thought about it very carefully.
You don't have to persuade me.
Really?
Let's hear it.
You see,
my contract with Legends now
have yet to end,
right?
If I want to leave, I have to pay.
Where do I have so much money?
You miser.
Okay,
looks like I don't have to persuade you.
Stay there.
Waiter, bill.
Thank you Brother Kong.
He's treat.
Before finding out
who harm you,
I will not leave.
Bill.
If nobody in the world
understands you,
then what's your ordinary?
Childish.
Thank you.
Isn't this the famous
Deception Master, Ji Xiang Kong?
Why are you free today
to visit our Wei Teng?
I came to discuss something with Sister Wen.
Sister Wen?
Such a sweet mouth.
Just got chased out by Legends not long ago,
so you come to
look for our Coach Shu?
You want her to let you join us, right?
What a joke.
Isn't it funny?
I'm leaving.
Stand right there,
as Wei Teng's future leader,
I can be responsible
and tell you,
we will definitely not look for you,
this cripple to pull us back.
If you still want face,
turn and leave.
Byebye.
What time did you asked to meet?
Two o'clock.
I confirmed it three times okay?
Let's not wait anymore, let's go.
You're not doing the interview anymore?
His time is precious,
ours is not?
You have already wait for an hour,
just wait awhile more.
Hello.
How are you guys?
Excuse me, I came late.
So you guys are
Gan Dong Magazine Publisher's reporters,
right?
Come, Prince Dan Jing,
ask anything.
Do you have...
Dong Gan Dian Jing Magazine publisher's reporter,
Lu Yi Yi.
Today,
I will be interviewing you.
Wait,
you're Qiu Ying?
You
know me?
You're famous,
the host that can't continue in You Xing.
Who doesn't know you?
Teacher Qi Yue.
We actually
arrange a two hours interview,
now we're left with forty minutes,
let's make use of the time,
okay?
Ten minutes is enough.
I will tell you guys
how will I lead Wei Teng into getting championship
in the new tournament.
Wait,
you mean
you will take over Pei Xi
and become Wei Teng's new leader?
If not,
who do you think it is
that can be the leader?
Start.
When you meet your idol,
you will afterall get a little nervous.
You...
Okay..
Sister Wen,
I will not beat about the bush,
I want to join Wei Teng.
First, tell me,
what are your views on Wei Teng?
Success is on Pei Xi,
defeat is also on Pei Xi.
Continue.
I believe you realised,
Pei Xi's leaving,
to Wei Teng
four protecting one,
is a big blow.
Relying on one person
for a team to win or lose,
is it really what you want?
Ji Xiang Kong,
you're still the first one
that dare to talk to me like that.
So people
don't usually like me.
Sister Wen,
you once got the championship,
you would know
Iconquer is a team competition,
not a solo show,
Wei Teng isn't lack of talented members,
what its lack is tactics.
In all of their hearts,
there's still a strength.
Sister Wen,
believe me.
I will give you
a whole new Wei Teng.
I want to ask you a question,
our situation now,
you know very clearly,
why do you still want to come?
Because Brother Sun told me,
your desire for the champion.
Wei Teng's leader position
is yours.
Thanks Sister Wen.
I wouldn't disappoint you.
Come, tell me about it.
This is my tactics analysis
on Wei Teng.
Brother Shen.
Why is Sister Shu Wen
discussing so long
with Ji Xiang Kong?
Would she really let Ji Xiang Kong
join our team?
I...
I don't know too
but I think Coach
will have her own thinking too.
Take it as I didn't ask.
Lu Sheng, what do you think?
I don't know.
What are you guys doing?
Waiting to get interviewed?
Still don't want to practice?
Brother Qi.
I'll not see you out.
Relax next time,
don't be too nervous.
This Qi Yue
really nose in the air.
If you didn't stop me,
I will want to...
Okay, don't be angry.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Who's that beside?
Shu Wen?
What do you the both of them is talking about?
So happy.
Okay,
let's speak outside.
Definitely there's a problem.
Let's go.
Ji Xiang Kong,
what is he doing here?
Is it...
He's coming to Wei Teng?
Qiu Ying,
as a reporter,
tell me,
there's something amiss.
Let's go take a look.
Why are you so busybody?
There's no grounds at all.
You suddenly go,
you're not worry people would chase you out?
You dumb?
Otherwise you say,
what is he doing here?
Actually, coming to Wei Teng is good too.
Afterall,
it is one of the top four best teams.
Last year,
the still got first-runner up,
lost a little to Legends.
But just now
you didn't see
Qi Yue's look.
Although Wei Teng is good,
but its not suitable for Ji Xiang Kong.
Whether it suit Ji Xiang Kong a not,
what's there to do with you?
Say.
Why do you care so much for him?
No, don't speak nonsense.
Are you telling me?
You... UFO.
Where?
Where? Qiu...
Qiu Ying, stand right there.
Tell me clearly.
Master,
Sister Wen,
about the leader,
can you confirm today?
Qi Yue,
give
me a bit more time.
We need to go through the process,
sorry about that.
Master,
that year when I was in Taiwan,
I already want to join the professional team,
its you who discover me,
and ask me to come here to develop.
Rest assured,
although Pei Xi left,
I still have that confident
to lead my brothers
to take down that
champion for Wei Teng.
Qi Yue,
go back to practice first.
Practice tournament is about to start.
Sister Wen,
Master,
you guys must have confident in me,
except for me,
there is no better options.
I will go practice first.
I intend to sign Ji Xiang Kong.
I already guessed it.
You already decided,
who you want to sign is okay,
but Ji Xiang Kong,
I don't suggest it.
Our team's previous problems,
you know very well.
Even if there is someone like Pei Xi
with high individual abilities,
but without tactics,
we still can't go far
and Ji Xiang Kong's ability,
you see it very clearly.
This isn't about ability,
its his personal problem.
He have too much negative news,
this make me difficult.
If you sign him in,
what would the sponsors think?
But according to
our current situation,
a good team leader
is more important that the sponsors.
You admit to it?
Yes.
But
Shu Wen
If there's still any more sponsors
that withdraw their investment,
the operation of Wei Teng
is a problem.
Settling the sponsors
is what you're best at right?
Li Gan,
when we first
establish Wei Teng,
we already said
we want to train
a team that can
take the world's championship.
Even if I have to
press on all my assets,
I'm also not afraid.
Okay,
then I
will go see
the practice tournament.
Cheers, come.
Brother Sun,
I really never thought
I will be able to discuss with
Sister Wen so smoothly.
She's someone with farseeing,
also,
once she firmly believe something,
she will keep going forward.
You in Wei Teng,
have a big space to develop.
Thanks Brother Sun.
Come, I'll toast to you.
Come.
Thank you for your care
during this time.
And also,
if not for your encouragement,
I will not have courage
to look for Sister Wen.
Cheers.
My roommate
stayed a few days,
and left.
Now I'm alone,
lonely.
Brother Sun,
are you still waiting for Sister Wen
all this time when you're single?
Rascal,
what nonsense are you saying?
Li Gan.
President Li.
Brother Yi.
You haven't change a bit
all these years.
You haven't change too. Take a seat.
Xiang Kong,
I came today
is to represent Wei Teng to look for you.
I will go get another bowl and chopsticks for you.
You guys chat.
Firstly,
I represent the team
to apologise to you,
we cannot sign the contract with you.
Another thing is,
I have a thought,
is to let you
tell Shu Wen personally
that you cannot sign the contract.
No,
President Li,
I don't understand
what do you mean?
Ever since the establishment of Wei Teng,
its been three years,
Shu Wen suffered a lot
to get the achievement she have today.
But now,
its at the live and death point again,
once Pei Xi left,
it brings three of our
biggest sponsor
and two is still hesitating.
Today after you and Shu Wen's discussion,
they got the news
and called me,
if Shu Wen
insist on signing you,
they will withdraw their investment.
Xiang Kong,
Shu Wen sincerely
admire you,
even she made ready
to press on all her assets
to protect you.
You can't just see her
hard work all these years
gone to waste right?
If you still care for
a friend,
a senior's loyalty,
you should personally tell her
you can't sign the contract.
President Li, don't say anymore.
I understand.
Its me
that brought trouble to you guys.
Thanks for you understanding.
I'll leave first.
Leaving?
Brother Yi,
owe the alcohol,
we will drink the next time we meet.
Just in time,
Ji Xiang Kong's contract.
Take a look.
Since
you already decided,
I respect your decision.
I'm planning to make a contract ceremony,
as for the time, it will be recently.
By then,
you help me contact
a few media,
I want to...
Sister Wen,
I'm not suitable for Wei Teng,
I can't come sign the contract.
What's the situation?
Sorry.
Ji Xiang Kong suddenly changed his mind.
Hello,
the number you have dial have switched off the mobile phone.
Switched off?
What does he mean?
Shu Wen, don't worry,
maybe Ji Xiang Kong knows
our current situation,
be it resources and money,
we are not like Legends.
He's a smart person,
he don't come,
we should understand him,
right?
No,
he's not someone like that.
I'm going to look for him.
I will think of any ways
to convince him.
Shu Wen,
don't go.
He wouldn't come.
How would you know?
You went to look for him?
Shu Wen.
Are you looking for
Xiang Kong?
Where's Xiang Kong?
He's upstairs,
I'll bring you to him.
Sister Wen,
I've already printed the contract,
do you want to sign a not?
Sister Wen,
if because of me,
I let Wei Teng get into bigger problems,
I...
I better not sign.
Sponsors withdrawing their investments
meanings getting into bigger problems?
In my eyes,
if not getting the world's championship
even with so many sponsors,
Wei Teng have no meaning being around.
Sister Wen,
I understand your feeling.
But you don't understand,
its five years ago that
the Kai Tuo Zhe gotten champion.
In all our hearts,
this champion,
we have waited for too long.
But Sister Wen...
Xiang Kong, don't worry,
even if all the sponsors
withdraw their investment,
I will also think of ways
to let Wei Teng hang on till the tournament.
Ji Xiang Kong,
I need you.
You promised me,
you will give me
a whole new Wei Teng.
Sister Wen,
I'm not satisfied with the yearly bonus.
Say any amount.
I'll be more satisfied like this.
One dollar?
From today onwards,
I will advance and retreat with Wei Teng.
Hide.
Nice!
Nice, great.
Qiu Ying, this operation works.
Leave.
I never expect even Brother Monkey
to get defeated.
Not easy.
Skinny Monkey, I'm sorry.
This kind of tactics
already let you guys in shock.
Dare to have a round with me?
Solo game.
Okay.
We'll compete then.
Since its to fight for the area's first,
why not
let's have an open competition?
Right.
Open competition is good.
How does this work?
Also challenging the area's first,
great.
Right.
Why, you afraid?
What's there to be afraid?
If I lose, I lose.
I'm not embarrassed.
Done saying.
I bet Qiu Ying would win.
No.
I think that girl will win.
Cannot be.
Then,
I'll bet with you,
if that girl losted,
I will treat you to a month
of Zi Hai Wo.
I can choose any flavour.
Any flavour, deal.
Qiu Ying,
all the best.
My one month worth of food
is on you.
Don't worry.
Brother Xia Tian,
why is there nobody here at Meng You Ren today?
I don't know.
Look.
Open competition.
Daring.
What's the situation?
Area's first, challenge Qiu Ying,
both are fighting now.
Your girlfriend can make it.
Challenging the area's first.
No,
She and I are just
normal friends.
Normal friends..
I understand.
Normal friends teach others personally.
She wants to be commentary
and came here to learn.
This girl is not bad.
She can use her visuals,
but she wants to use her skills.
Next time,
if there's such thing
you can just tell me directly,
it wouldn't be so strenuous.
I'm just afraid
to spoil your
Meng You Ren rules.
Don't be nervous,
even if she lose,
I'll still give her a chance.
Don't worry,
she will definitely win.
Losing blood, go back home girl.
Push the crystals.
Qiu Ying, don't go back.
Shock what?
Push the crystals.
Xiang Kong,
I finally became the area's first.
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
Pei Xi,
now I have the rights
to work here already right?
You want to fight the area's first
just because
you want to be an attendant here?
Yes.
Its not exactly for this.
Then what do you want to do?
I want to be the first commentary.
Me working at Meng You Ren,
there's so many skilled players here,
teaching me professional knowledge,
also fighting the area.
During this time,
I have a better understanding
on Dian Feng.
Its not that good to be a commentary.
Anything have to start from zero,
I'll take a step at a time.
Exactly.
This girls thoughts are pretty good.
Why are you doing this?
By the way,
let me introduce,
this is Meng You Ren's boss,
Brother Xia Tian.
I know.
You are
one of the five skilled player,
Tui Shi Zhe's best assistant,
account name, Xia Tian.
So after retreating,
everyone called you as
Brother Xia Tian.
I'm embarrassed talking about it.
You've done your homework.
Of course.
Hello Boss.
So fast you're calling the Boss,
he haven't said he want you.
I didn't say I don't want.
Exactly.
Congratulation,
for joining Meng You Ren.
Thanks Boss.
So now I can
go make my recruit?
Can.
Now you can follow me.
You two can continue talking, let's go.
You like her a lot right?
What?
You like Qiu Ying a lot right?
What's there to do with you?
You better stay away from her.
You like her?
I heard you have joined Wei Teng.
You say, this is quite coincidental.
Turn around,
my old house,
is currently your new
and your old house
have become my new.
Looks like we are destined to be competitors.
That's not too bad.
I wouldn't be soft on you.
Xiang Kong.
I finally become Meng You Ren's people.
Official worker.
Not bad.
You've found a job.
Then you should treat.
Of course.
Why not
Meng You Ren's strawberry cake?
How?
No, eat what?
Two piece of strawberry cake.
Two piece?
No,
why are you
more stingy than Lin Yi Xuan?
Forget it,
I've also found a job,
this meal, I'll treat.
Thanks.
Never thought that
within such a short period of time
in Meng You Ren,
you fight up to the area's first.
Immediately I'll be
on the competition.
I have to work harder.
Brother Xia Tian often would invite
including Teacher Luo Tian
from many industry
to be commentary.
If staying at Meng You Ren
can just right
stay and listen.
By the way,
what's the new job you've found?
I've signed with Wei Teng.
Really?
Wei Teng
is one of the strongest in the top four.
We have to drink
to celebrate.
- Waiter. - You sure?
You forgot the last time,
your alcohol tolerance, you..
Waiter, two bottles of beer.
Cheers.
Ji Shuai, your hot towel.
Thanks.
Why do you need a hot towel?
Does your hand hurt?
Come,
the strength you used,
can chase up with our practice already.
The next time you practice,
don't be over three hours,
know how to care for yourself.
The other hand,
how?
Do you feel better?
A lot better.
I have some medication with me,
the next time I'll bring it over to you.
Thanks.
Why so courteous
between brothers?
This time after I go Wei Teng,
I've already command the military order
to take down the champion.
Same for you,
after you go for the star next,
you can't lose, you must win.
Don't forget the promise between us,
to go to Dian Feng together for finals.
All the best.
Its already nine, why is she still not back?
Yi Yi, I'm back.
Where's she?
Why are you sitting here?
Come.
You still have the cheek to say?
What's wrong?
You made a table of dishes.
So great.
To celebrate
you fighting up to area first.
I've been preparing this table of dishes
since three o'clock.
You look at the time now,
you then come home.
You never said in advance.
I still have to tell you in adanve?
Such a big matter,
which time
we didn't celebrate it together?
Okay,
don't be angry.
Don't touch me.
I'm wrong, okay?
Angel.
Are you
on a date with Ji Xiang Kong?
Today is a special situation,
I just went to Meng You Ren
and he went to Wei Teng,
double happiness,
so we had a small celebration.
You have guys but you don't have humanity.
Cold war, I don't care about you.
Lu Ye.
You say cold war,
let's cold war for ten minutes.
Ten minutes later you come down okay?
Let me tell you,
I'm serious this time.
Okay, you're serious,
fifteen minutes.
Just nice I'll warm the dishes.
You havent eaten right?
I will accompany you eat again.
Its settle like this.
Warm the dishes.
Cold war ended?
Haven't ended.
Come here.
Why?
Look at this yourself.
You still remember
that time we went to Wei Teng
and saw the look of the both of them?
Isn't it very close?
I thought there's something amiss at that time,
so i wanted to go back to take a look,
you still stopped me
and not let me go back.
If the both of them
is really together,
they can help each other with them work,
isn't that good too?
Stop acting in front of me,
then what are you?
You don't tell me,
now
you only take him as a normal friend.
Why are you looking at me?
Do you really want to know too?
What he's relationship
with Shu Wen?
Their relationship
have nothing to do with you.
You keep toss ad turning
and you can't sleep.
Why?
But I just want to know.
He's in a relationship,
my heart is uncomfortable,
what's the point of you knowing?
Ji Xiang Kong
only treat you as a Brother.
Stand still as punishment.
Goodnight Jiang Jiang.
Brother Qi,
don't be angry.
Don't be angry.
Tong Long.
Sorry, Brother Qi.
Sorry.
Are you an idiot?
You can be more dumb.
- Sorry Brother Qi. - What you doing?
Brother Qi,
you say,
Sister Wen
wouldn't really have something
with Ji Xiang Kong?
She offended two big sponsors
because of Ji Xiang Kong.
What are you saying?
Outsiders can spout nonsense,
you also start this together with them?
Can my Master get greened?
Let me tell you guys,
I wouldn't let Ji Xiang Kong
have a good
so long as I'm still around.
From now on,
we must be on the same line.
I want to see how much tolerance he have.
Lu Sheng, I'm talking,
did you hear me?
Listening.
So long as the four of us don't cooperate,
I want to see how he be the leader.
Definitely.
We will all do
as you say.
Tong Long
I... listen to Brother Qi.
Anything.
See you guys, I'm fine with anything.