[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 16]
Tong Long, help me to food.
Hurry up.
Looks like
you another tough battle to fight.
Sister Wen, you signed me in,
isn't it to let me battle?
Moreover, these players,
we have already cross swards
with one another so many times on the playing field.
No worries, I have the confidence.
Why not you stay in room two.
Since Pei Xi left,
the room have since been empty.
Sister, is there joint rooms?
Lu Sheng's room
have a bed empty,
but, he's
character is a little solitude.
Its fine, I'll sleep with him.
I can communicate with him usually.
Then I'll bring you in.
No need, I'll go myself.
Hello Lu Sheng, I'm Xiang Kong,
we'll be roommate in future.
Okay.
What you doing?
What are you doing here?
I am Legend's new leader.
Next time,
this will be my room.
I don't allow you to stay here,
heard that?
Why did you take Brother Kong's note?
He left it in this room,
isn't it just for me to see?
No, I say you're so tall,
can you have some face?
Give it to me.
Giving stregth is it?
Give it.
You're so tall.
Lin Yi Xuan, what are you doing?
What happen?
Stealing, stealing Brother Kong's notebook.
Give it to me.
Enough, stop arguing.
Why not let's compete one round?
Sure, I'm not afraid of you.
Compete on?
You decide.
Heard that?
I'll decide what to compete on.
This place is so small,
I'll wait for you in the practice hall.
Everyone's here.
There's no other meaning,
I just to let everyone
be the witness,
if case some people
isn't convinced that he lost.
Afterall, he is the leader.
Don't come up with any underhand.
No.
Compete on what I'll decide,
this is what Leader Pei Xi said.
I just wanted to
come up with a good idea
to let you
play happily and have a great time.
Anything.
Start.
All competition
is friendship first,
competition second.
Today we will have
a friendly smile competition.
In one minutes,
who make make the other person laugh,
will win. How's that?
Isn't too much right?
Start now.
Pei Xi, is your facial nerve paralyse?
Is it very funny?
It's my turn.
I win.
Where's Li Gan?
Master said he have stomachache,
he wouldn't be coming.
Okay, then we'll start first.
I want to announce to everyone,
from today onwards,
Ji Xiang Kong will be joining Wei Teng.
Everyone welcome.
Entering the team,
everyone please show come care.
Ji Xiang Kong
isn't only a team member
but also your new leader.
Sister Wen,
such an important matter on the leader,
should you
communicate a little with my Master?
I am your Coach,
my decision
is also Wei Teng's decision.
Sister Wen,
its a good thing that there's doubt,
it means everyone is serious about the team,
just nice this can drive everyone.
I'm an airborne leader.
Stop saying nice words,
I have more rights than you
- to be Wei Teng's leader. - Qi Yue.
If you are capable, let's battle one round.
Okay, you form a team.
I will lead the substitute players.
This is what you said, don't get smack right in the face.
If I lost,
I will call you the leader.
What happen if you lost?
I will leave.
Sister Wen, this is what he said.
Everyone wouldn't disagree right?
Okay, let's do as you guys arranged.
Brothers, let's go.
Prepare a little.
I will demonstrate to him
what is a leader.
Don't worry.
It will be the same later, four protecting one.
The mid-way juggling
will all be mine.
You guys just have to follow up,
understand?
Brother Qi, don't worry.
We will fully assist you.
A cripple with four substitute player,
what's there to be arrogant?
How to play this?
There's no way to fight Qi Yue,
definitely can't win.
Qi Yue will definitely use the four protecting one,
then we will use the double call technique.
Double call?
Simply said, its to let us
go top and damage,
faster development.
Form an Ace with the opponent
to form a balance.
Qi Yue will definitely go the mid-way.
Then we will use the side way
to fight.
Even if Qi Yue is that strong, there's no use.
Come on, relax.
Listen to my command.
Aren't you not feeling well?
I'm better.
That's good then.
This is
Qi Yue and Ji Xiang Kong's duel?
Qi Yue isn't convinced,
Ji Xiang Kong called four substitute players
to battle a around with him.
Ji Xiang Kong let go of his Mid turret,
it's dangerous.
I think it might not be,
Ji Xiang Kong and his teammates
split into two ways,
one turret exchanging for three.
Its not a lost at all,
and Qi Yue's postworm?
Now its only relying on team embrace.
Unlike Ji Xiang Kong,
four person with one pushing, playing with an advantage.
It can not only avoid attack but also push the line.
This round our battle array is stronger,
fighting them at the start.
I'm at the mid-way.
Mid-way juggling developing.
I will assist right away,
becareful on your way.
Jungler have went over.
Assist, towars the river for more.
Let me tell you guys first,
if anyone touch my jungler,
try it.
Okay.
Looks like there no more suspense.
Qi Yue have no developed yet,
but Ji Xiang Kong's
two way preparation
have already formed.
His tactics
have won Qi Yue's four protecting one.
Looks like what you said is right.
I hope you can understand
everything that I've done
is for Wei Teng.
Take a look.
Ji Xiang Kong's contract.
One dollar?
He said he want to advance and retreat together with Wei Teng.
Li Gan,
I believe Ji Xiang Kong
wouldn't disappoint us.
Okay.
In awhile I'll go
submit the request to the website.
Thank you.
Continue doing damage,
stress them back home,
speed push the crystals.
Clear the troops.
What is this?
What are you playing?
Who looked for you?
- What are in thinking in your mind? - Qi Yue.
Master, let me have anoher round with him.
I'm not convinced.
Are you over it yet?
- Master. - Shut up.
Good win.
Okay,
a competition's of win and lose,
can't tell much
but I hope
you guys can see
the tactics.
Especially during competition,
tactics are very important.
Qi Yue,
this time you should know
where you lost at right?
Is there still anyone not convinced?
Okay.
The from today onwards,
Ji Xiang Kong will be your leader.
You guys still have to listen to his command.
Train according to his tactics,
understand?
Xiang Kong,
both your fight was great
but the tactics.
I will go persuade him.
Qi Yue, stand right there.
Master, I don't want to battle anymore.
I'm just not convinced.
Last time when Pei Xi is around,
let me play four protecting one.
I'm willing.
Now you're asking me to call Ji Xiang Kong leader?
I can't.
His solo game can win me?
The match just now already proved
although your personal skill is strong,
but Ji Xiang Kong
is more suitable to be leader.
Iconcure talks about team spirit.
Master, why even you
are siding that cripple?
Keep quiet.
If you have lost the competition, admit it.
Your arrogance
needs to know when to stop.
You are my disciple
and also Wei Teng's veteran,
take out some heart
and responsibility.
I hope you can let go of the miscellaneous,
compete well.
Don't because you're doing well once
and ruin your good career in front of you,
life is still long.
If you want to prove that you
are stronger than Ji Xiang Kong,
prove it during the competition.
Understand?
Why are you here?
What happen?
Who bullied our Master Qi?
Who else?
Ji Xiang Kong,
once day I'll let him leave.
I heard that your leader position
is snatched.
If not for Sister Wen protecting him,
what is he?
You say this Ji Xiang Kong,
where is he from?
He can come as he want.
Who knows?
Ji Xiang Kong
snatched my leader position,
I wouldn't let him live well.
Annoying, let's not talk about this.
Accompany me for a ride okay?
You messed up my styling.
Why? Going to see Pei Xi?
Your handsome boyfriend is here,
you don't want to accompany,
you want to look for other guys?
What are you saying?
Those online,
you believe what those netizens said?
Moreover,
not like you don't know
about the double row.
About the double row？
About the double row
is me taking his account
with your double row to teach Qiu Ying a lesson.
In the end,
my girlfriend
became Pei Xi's rumoured girlfriend.
Okay,okay,
our Master Qi is the best,
okay?
Like that, tomorrow,
tomorrow I have time,
it belongs to you alone.
How?
Today I really can't.
I need to go and see
the star tomorrow's organiser.
You want to compete?
I have someone I know at Ji Guang video,
I'll help you call.
No need.
I have already found doorway.
Byebye.
Can,
looks like it.
Okay then, let me introduce a little
on our job scoop here.
Anyways, its a morning and night shift.
Morning shift is ten o'clock,
night shift is two o'clock,
in between there will an hour break.
Take turns formation.
Basically, its just all these.
Okay, I know already.
Okay then, I'll find someone
to bring you to look around.
Okay.
Pei Xi.
Pei Xi,
come here.
Hurry up.
New worker, bring around.
I'm currently very busy.
Busy? Busy with what?
I'm really very busy.
I'm giving you
a chance.
What chance?
I've asked before already,
Ji Xiang Kong and Qiu Ying is not a thing.
How do you know?
Ji Xiang Kong told me himself.
Then I know already,
the chance you're talking about,
what do you mean?
You this child's mind,
is there water inside?
Just listen to me will do.
Go,go.
Then, trouble you.
Go.
No,
why is it a must for me to go?
Because I'm the boss.
You're the worker, you have to listen to me.
Get going, hurry.
Thanks Boss.
- You're welcome, byebye. - Byebye.
Let's go.
Why not forget about it?
- I can do it myself. - This is a procedure.
I,
tomorrow I have an interview to do.
Then you come back at night
to help me, give me the information,
send it to me later, can?
Okay.
Thanks.
Yi Yi, I'll leave first.
- Okay, byebye. - Byebye.
See you tomorrow, slowly.
Lu Yi Yi, I...
Do you have a problem?
Did I scare you?
I have to treat you to a meal,
- let's go. - That...
I know one
super good Si Chuan Restaurant.
Trying to bride me?
No.
Speak, why are you looking for me?
I.. I want to treat you to a meal
means I have something?
Do I look like someone like that?
No.
I do have something looking for you,
I... I want to let you
help me check on Zhao Yang.
Check on him?
He's indeed not some one good
but am I close to you?
Why should I help you?
I'm leaving.
No, you come back.
That...
Aren't you a great
reporter?
Kind and justice,
isn't it reporter's job?
Moreover,
checking Zhao Yang's
personal life clearly,
it will shock the whole industry.
That's so good.
What a good chance.
This chance,
I can give it to anyone.
I have to give it to you.
Don't.
I can't take this.
You saw it already,
I
am just a small periodical office‘s editor,
I don't have such a big responsibility.
Byebye.
No,no.
Grandfather Lu, Grandmother Lu.
Beautiful Ms Lu.
Beautiful Ms Lu can?
Are you asking for a beating?
Let me tell you, if you still follow me,
I will call the police.
Even if you call the police, its useless.
When I come out,
I will still follow you.
You..
okay.
Take it as I'm afraid of you, okay?
I'll help you.
Justice.
Let's go eat,
let's eat and discuss.
That Si Chuan Restaurant is great.
The queue is very long.
By the way,
are you familiar with Wei Teng's Shu Wen?
Shu Wen, of course familiar.
That's my previous sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law?
Yes.
Ji Xiang Kong, that slag man.
No.
What's there to do with my Brother Kong?
What's the situation?
No, why did you hit me?
Are we eating, Lu Yi Yi?
Coming.
Look at me later.
Hello, both of your coffee.
Come, becareful.
Isn't this Qiu Ying?
That's weird.
You're perfectly good,
why are you here
to be a waitress?
Previously online
is spreading you and Ji Xiang Kong's matter.
The both of us are really curious,
whether is it true?
You guys don't have to care.
No, don't go.
Don't touch me.
Ji Xiang Kong have Shu Wen,
did you get desolate?
This small booklet, you still gave it to me.
What you doing?
We don't welcome you guys here.
Get out.
Isn't this Pei Xi?
What's so amazing?
I'm asking you guys to get out.
Let's go. People is chasing us out.
Let's go, let's not play anymore.
Ji Xiang Kong's.
Thanks.
If there's any problem in future,
you can ask me directly.
So long as I'm here,
nobody can bully you.
Previous sister-in-law.
Lin Yi Xuan told me personally.
Shu Wen is his previous Sister-in-law.
Ji Xiang Kong is his Brother Kong's.
This relationship,
do you know?
She will go to Wei Teng
definitely because of
wanting to get together with Shu Wen.
This liar.
Yi Yi,
can you not
get all this information
from Lin Yi Xuan?
I get all this information from Lin Yi Xuan
isn't it because I'm afraid you got lied at?
You're so dumb,
since you havent give everything in,
I have to hurry.
- Hurry. - You're thinking too much.
Now, I
don't have the strength to think of all these.
I still have the house loans to pay
and preparing for the star tomorrow's competition,
and being a waitress for Meng You Ren.
I know very well
what I'm doing everyday.
Whether I can become a professional commentary,
there is only this one chance,
I have to go all out.
I can't waste a minute.
Okay.
Let's not talk about it
but promise me,
don't see him in future anymore.
The most important thing now
is the peacefully
preparing for the competition.
Don't worry.
You're tired for a day already,
hurry go bath and sleep.
Okay.
You sleep early too.
You're back.
You play basketball too.
Don't play anymore.
This have been there for very long already.
I'll put in air for you.
No need.
I intended to throw it away.
Okay.
By the way, I have a question
I want to communicate with you.
Okay, you say.
Recently, I
looked at the statics,
and realised that you played
every position before
and you played very well.
Then do you think
your current position
is suitable for you?
What do you mean?
What you mean is
my current level
can't play my current position.
What you mean is
I'm pulling my teammates behind?
Please
take a good look at the statics.
Which one did I not play well?
No, that's not what I mean.
Maybe I did not
explain clearly,
what I mean is...
I want to say
all your position
and every round's play
is very stable,
its even like a straight line.
So from another angel
to understand,
you do have
a very big potential
to exert.
You just came to be the leader of Wei Teng,
you want to open tables
I can understand
but I'm someone like that,
very direct.
I don't like to beat about the bush.
So i advice you
to not waste your energy on me,
care about yourself.
I just looked at the statics
and wanted to speak to you.
I think you
have a very big space to improve.
Of course, if you do this others will.
Now is rest time,
can I sleep?
Okay, sorry.
Good night.
Tong Long,
why are you eating so much on your own?
This is Brother Qi and Brother Shen's.
Morning.
Its this three again?
Can you have some creativity?
Buy some buns next time.
I want meat bun.
Okay.
Morning leader.
Morning.
Not eating something?
How do you have strength
to fight me?
Anyways, you will also get bashed.
You know the search engine tomorrow
is what?
Prince Dian Jin
bashing cripple Ji Xiang Kong.
Morning Sister Wen.
- Morning Sister Wen. - Morning.
Breakfast is very full.
Sister Wen.
Let's go out for a chat.
Okay.
Eat slowly.
Go out for a chat?
What's there to chat about early in the morning?
I'm not eating anymore.
You just came to the team,
you need to give them some time
to get used to you.
But Qi Yue this person
is more rush,
sometimes he's very direct when he speaks.
Qi Yue is an veteran, arrogant.
Probably when Pei Xi is around,
he's also not convinced.
Shen Hong this person have some backbones,
he's currently together with Qi Yue
but I might not be able to convinced him.
What about others?
Lu Sheng skills is very all rounder
but he
see through the world of mortals.
He only ask for stability, not improvement.
Tong Long is the youngest,
and also the least daring.
But in all,
their skills are all still good.
You can, its just a few days
and you already know the character
of these people clearly.
Autumn's competition is starting,
time is precious,
but
I have already looked through
their statics,
next up,
is to go according to their specility
and plan their practice.
You will have to spend a bit more thoughts into it.
If not when you execute the plan,
there might be difficulties
but don't worry, if there's any problem,
I will be first
to help you solve it.
Thanks Sister Wen.
I know what I'm supposed to do,
it might be  certain risk
but don't worry Sister Wen.
No matter what I do,
please allow me to preserver on.
Since I looked for you to come,
I will definitely support you fully.
Master, this Ji Xiang Kong
is a attractive young man,
Sister Wen trust him so much,
I believe he definitely
did something to Sister Wen.
You actually believe
something without evidence?
Master, you really not worry?
Sister and Ji Xiang Kong...
Enough.
What kind of a person is Shu Wen,
I know it better than anyone.
Master.
Why do you have to tolerate all this?
Qi Yue.
My problem, you don't have to care.
You just have to
practice properly for competition.
Taking out some real capabilities
is more important.
Don't forget
what I told you in the past.
Okay, I know Master.
I'll go practice already.
Get going.
Pei Xi.
Pei Xi, I send you messages,
why did't you reply?
I'm not free.
Pei Xi, I know you're busy
so I came early
to see you.
Why not, let's have a chat?
Have you eaten?
Don't disturb me from my job.
I came this time
to is learn.
I came to listen
to Teacher Luo Tian's compound.
Ain't you a host?
What does compound have to do with you?
How is there no relation?
Definitely there is.
I joined
the star tomorrow's competition.
I'm prepared to be a professional commentary
from a host.
Like this,
next time we can
meet each other on matches.
You also want to be a commentary?
Yes.
Who else?
Who else is there other than me?
Waitress.
What happen to the computer?
It can't be turned on.
Qiu Ying.
Waitress.
Coming.
Okay, I'll get it for you immediately.
Hello.
What do you want to order?
I'm thirsty.
What's there to drink
here?
You introduce me.
Just nice, take a look yourself.
This menu's words are too small,
why not, you read to me?
This is tea, juice,
plain water,
what do you need?
Just this little things.
Is there coffee?
Yes, cappuccino.
Okay.
Then I want a cup of
cappuccino.
Wait..
I want to be a commentary recently
so the water temperature should not be too hot.
My vocals will not be able to take it.
Also, my stomach is not good,
the water temperature should not be too low as well.
Somemore,
I'm recerntly
on diet,
so I don't want milk and sugar.
Remember that?
No milk
it will become Americano.
But what I ordered is
cappuccino.
I'm sorry,
cappuccine without milk
we don't make.
What kind of attitude is this?
Be careful, I'll complain you.
Pei Xi, did you see that?
That's too much.
Today there's only a type of coffee,
latte, give you.
Pei Xi,
thank you for helping me.
You're thinking too much.
I did not help you.
There is already short of people here.
There's still a lot of customers waiting.
Remember,
you just have to do your thing right.
I know.
Waitress,
where's the compound?
This way, this way in.
Let's go.
Waitress.
Coming.
You come here and take a look.
What is happening to my computer?
Okay.
Is it very hard to choose?
I don't know what you mean.
You have to at least choose one
so I can help you,
right?
I don't need your help.
I think you're really very bored.
Or is it you want both?
Can, rascal.
Yo're like me last time.
Do you want me to give you some suggestions?
I said already, I don't need.
Good child, you're a grown up,
learn to think on your own.
Do you want
me as an experienced person,
give you some suggestions?
Are you very free now?
The bar is lack of people,
there is not enough people.
Do you want to help?
You look at me now
looks very free?
I'm doing this for your happiness.
I'm thinking so much for you.
Teacher Luo.
Teacher Luo, you're here.
This child run faster than anyone else.
What have you done to Pei Xi?
Shy, youthful times.
You're gossiping about others again?
Private life.
How can you consider this as gossip?
I'm a brother,
shouldn't I have the responsibility on an older one?
What time is it?
It's time. Let'sgo in.
Such big formation.
Spend quite a lot of thoughts into it.
Let's go, everyone is waiting for you.
Come.
Teacher Luo.
Teacher Luo is here.
Teacher Luo is famous.
Everyone,
good afternoon.
This is
our professionaly Dian Jin industry
famous commentary,
Teacher Luo Tian.
I believe everyone know him.
Of course.
Teacher Luo Tian
is the first time here.
Next time, every week
Teacher Luo Tian
will come to Meng you Ren
to conduct with everyone
the compound video commentary.
Welcome everyone.
Teacher Luo,
I am You Xin Iconcure's
host, Qiao Xin.
I really admire you.
Thanks.
I admire you too.
Okay, go up. Have a good speech.
All to you.
Hello everyone, I'm Luo Tian.
Welcome everyone to join
my compound commentary.
Today, I'm giving everyone
compound is
insider game's finals.
This competition is Wei Teng
as a two vs. zero's advantage
and won Legends.
Because its to test the new updates
insider game,
both teams have to choose
at least one new hero
but in this competition
Legends as one vs. zero
as a losing situation
choose two
new heros to play.
Come,
this competition base on its scale
actually Legends
is at an advantage.
Through assistance,
the deep sea control
Lu feng's balance.
It's useless.
What?
You copying notes down,
it's useless.
Then what is useful?
You asking Luo Tian directly.
This is a up front professional
right in front of you,
ask him directly.
Its ten times more useful than copying notes.
Makes sense.
Just this brain of yours,
still want to be a commentary?
Of course, the key
isn't this tactics.
Can anyone see
anything from the middle?
Teacher Luo Tian, I have a question.
Very hardworking.
Yes.
I want to become
a commentary like you in future.
So I have to
learn more from you.
Okay, then can you see
anything from it?
It should be Ji XIang Kong's entrance
can make damage,
after dying, the team members
did not cooperate.
So it cause the lost.
Is there anyone else
who have a different view?
Teacher Luo Tian,
I think this round key lost
is the tactics.
I think the wrong doesn't lie in Ji Xiang Kong
but his team members
did not assist well,
causing to not control well,
Wei Teng damage the marksman
causing an anti-kill.
That's right.
The real reason is
Huo He's mistake.
During the crucial moment,
release his skills.
Legends assistance here
every round is with
Pei Xi's hell angel
conducting a life taking battling method,
is isn't as simple as a mistake.
Not a very good position,
this is for the back
Legends lost
doing a protector.
Today's compound commentary
will end here.
After today, I'll be at Meng You Ren
bringing more competition
compound commentary,
I hope everyone can show some support.
Our Iconcure competition.
Thank you everyone.
Thank you Teacher Luo Tian.
Can I take a photo with you?
I want a photo too.
Thanks.
Its my turn.
Teacher Luo Tian.
Thanks Teacher Luo Tian.
Thanks Teacher, all the best.
Step on me.
Teacher Luo, hello.
Just now Brother Xia Tian said
he would be waiting for you at the Bar.
Okay.
Teacher Luo, I'll bring you
to the rest area to wait.
He should be here soon.
Come.
Just sit here.
Teacher Luo.
Do you want to drink anything?
We have everything here.
No need. Go get busy.
When he finished his things,
you can come let me know,
that's enough.
Teacher Luo.
You want a signature?
You're my idol.
I not only want a signature,
I still have a lot of questions
regarding commentary
to ask you.
This is my notes.
Did we meet anywhere before?
Luo Tian, how do you see?
All trainees now
are so random ?
I remember now,
Ji Guang video's commentary room.
Teacher Luo, I
I'm sorry.
It wasn't on purpose that day.
A person that don't even dare to raise their head,
how can you let me believe
you are confident to speak on the commentary stage?
Okay.
I know.
No problem.
Just do as I said.
Okay.
Sure.
I...
I'll not talk to you anymore, someone is here.
Okay, I know.
I know.
Okay.
Byebye.
Teacher Luo.
Your Meng You Ren's waitress
all have dreams.
Got found out.
I admit
I purposely arranged it.
I don't to let think think
I look like I using the back door.
This isn't called using the back door.
But, is there a way to convince you
to give her a chance.
Coming close to me,
looks like she have some tactics.
That girl doesn't have tactics.
She's really hardworking.
You know?
Because we want to come here and learn,
in one month
she fight into the area's first.
Everyday, she come the earliest and leave the latest.
How rare?
This can convince you to help her?
This kind of host,
I've see too much.
On the outside, they look hardworking,
but in the end,
they still rely on looks and skills
to get fans.
She think of ways to get famous,
this kind of vase,
we commentaries don't want.
I understand your concern,
I just
want to provide her with a chance.
Whether its a success a not,
its up to her hard work.
But i dare to give you the ticket,
this girl definitely isn't
the kind of person you say.
You're so sure?
Xia Tian,
its been long since I seen you
so nice to someone already.
I really admire her.
You say this girl
look not bad too.
She can rely on her face
but she want to use talent.
This girl
is currently very less.
Didn't you always say
you are lack of people?
Truth is?
Its Pei Xi.
You know, Pei Xi
like that girl.
Say earlier.
So its actually your future Sister-in-law.
Its not sister-in-law.
The numbers have no counted yet.
Main thing is
I admire her.
But you got to know
my standards are very high.
Not anyone
can enter my eyes.
I know.
You're such a professional one, right?
Professional person is
different from normal people.
You can bring anyone,
that is great.
Okay, come.
I will toast with you tea instead of wine.
Sure.
Phony.
Hello, Yi Yi.
You say if now i dash over
to look for Teacher Luo,
is it a little
too rush?
Let me tell you
you can only make big things with thick skin.
Okay then.
Go.
They're out.
I'll talk to you when I'm home, byebye.
When are you coming the next time?
- I'll call you. - Okay.
Teacher Luo,
I'm sorry.
I know just now
my performance was horrible,
but I really want to
become a professional commentary.
Probably you think I'm currently
a little rackless,
but I will definitely
press on to do this.
So
So what?
I want to ask you to be my Master.
Anyone can shout this,
will can be set by anyone.
Then tell me,
what's so special about you?
Okay, if there's nothing,
I'll leave first.
You...
Drive slowly.
Okay, its fine.
He's usually strict with others.
But,
he have never taken in any disciples.
You're really daring.
Then
do I not have a chance anymore?
Isn't that you don't have a chance.
I think
what he meant was
don't keep saying the catchword,
take out some legit actions
to prove that you're special.
- Is it like that? - Yes.
I've known him for many years.
He's always like that.
Then that means
I have a chance.
Yes, there is but its a chance
that you have to fight for.
Hint you a little,
the star tomorrow,
Teacher Luo Tian is the main examiner.
Didn't you sign up?
Work harder in front of him.
Then he will going to the venue too?
Don't say I'm the one that tell you.
Thanks Boss.
I will definitely work hard.
Okay, don't call me Boss in future,
call Brother Xia Tian.
Thanks Brother Xia Tian.