Episode 6
When we practiced previously,
we always fought with Dragons.
How do we compete like this?
Yes.
Why are you freezing here? Go and ask.
I'll go find them.
No, there's no way we can win like this.
We already practiced the tactics.
Suddenly we're changing competitors.
we can't compete, we won't win.
Even if we compete, it'll be a waste.
Why did we come?
Manager Zhao, think of something.
I know.
Don't be nervous.
I told Wang Bin to arrange
and it became like this.
Don't be nervous.
I'll go and ask personally, okay?
Wait for my notification.
Manager Zhao, make the decision for us.
Okay.
We are relying on you.
We are trusting you.
You've worked hard, Manager Zhao.
Fighting.
Hello everyone.
Welcome to everyone who has came.
Conquer's new advanced level
internal trial competition's site.
I am your host for today,
Luo Tian.
I am Ah Can. Welcome everyone.
Then, let's use our applause to welcome
the VNG team and Dragon team.
Welcome.
Okay, then we shall announce
the commencement of the competition.
Let's welcome both teams' members to have a seat.
Lu Yi Yi, are you busy?
Nope, what happened Director?
Is there any urgent task?
If you're not busy,
then,
I'll let you handle the news of
Gu Fang quitting.
Really?
No problem, count on me.
Don't be so excited.
You don't need to go to the venue.
You just need to contact the relevant staff
and those in the same industry.
For this news report,
you just need to summarise the above,
and that'll be all.
Anyway,
we don't have a media invite.
We can't enter the venue too.
Just do this, it'll be okay.
The taste of this is not bad.
I'll take it away, thank you.
I didn't get it wrong right.
Gu Fang is holding a departure ceremony today.
You're telling me now.
Maybe, this is a good chance
heaven has given me and Qiu Ying.
How's the preparation over there now?
They're discussing tactics.
The past few days they've always
been researching how to battle the Dragon team.
Now I predict that even if they think till it's dusk,
they can't come up with a tactic.
I'll do it.
Let us see,
can Pei Xi's team get a quintuple kill.
Quintuple kill, nice.
This is literally a miracle.
First wave, push up the crystal.
Nice, congratulations VNG for
winning the Dragon with a 2:1.
Taking down the first win.
Congratulations.
Deserving to be called "rising mid-solo star player".
These hands' speed doesn't lose to
Gu Fang at his peak.
Pei Xi will be my staff sooner or later.
That is for sure.
Manager Zhao, it's almost our turn soon.
You can just wait and see.
Now,
we can relax.
And prepare to face the next round well.
Congratulations, Coach Shu Wen.
You guys won another round.
You're really the hero amongst women.
Fighting to you too.
Let's meet at Gu Fang's departure ceremony.
I won.
I know. And so?
So, you better not lose too.
I don't think you need to worry.
Okay.
Then let's meet at the finals.
I will persist until the end, see you at the finals.
Is he trying to challenge us?
Who cares about him? Let's go.
Let's go, fighting.
Fighting.
Next, let us welcome
the two teams,
Legends and New Land, please.
Okay, we now announce
Conquer's new advanced level's
the second round of
internal trial competition
officially begins.
Let's invite both teams' members to have a seat.
Now we've entered
the route selection segment for both teams.
For this round, let's opt for speedy push.
Okay.
Let's choose two heroes to push the towers.
Legends has chosen two-
Why did they choose two
two tower pushing heroes?
This is too risky.
Are they aiming for a speed push? Or?
You need to be quick for a speed push.
You should be more economical at the start.
New Land team is also good at development.
I don't know where Ji Xiang Kong
got his courage from.
Daring to challenge them at development.
Even if they're developed, so what?
Once they fail in pushing the tower,
the initiative will return to the opponent.
This way, Ji Xiang Kong's
speed push tactic,
will completely go to waste.
Li Nan, Lu Feng,
go to the wild area opposite,
let's do an ambush.
Okay.
I'll go over there now.
Ah Xuan,
take all of our gains,
Okay.
Yao Ge, be at the army line.
go to help at the wild area.
Once you're done there,
Okay, no problem.
Quickly develop everyone.
- Okay.
No problem.
Let's see, for Ji Xiang Kong's team
three members have come mid field
and preparing a surprise attack.
First blood, nice.
Legends did a nice job
at catching solo players.
And the new member, Li Nan,
cooperates with
great chemistry, in my opinion.
First blood and gains
have all been given to Lu Feng.
Lu Feng is also developing miraculously fast.
Yes.
Double kill, great.
Luck.
Don't say anymore.
This can be considered a dreamy starting right?
Yes.
Prepare to have a team battle.
This wave.
We definitely must keep the initiative.
Go.
My skills are trapped.
Evil, my best move is avoided
by Lu Feng.
Chase.
Press the tower.
Go.
Hold on.
- Hang on.
Retreat.
Okay.
Look.
Youngsters these days,
you have to give them a little pressure.
- That's right.
So they can 'run faster'.
Come.
Ji Xiang Kong guided the team well.
That's right.
At least, they started off well.
But according to what I know,
for this competition,
they have always thought
their opponent was Dragon.
Not being fearful on the spot,
only Ji Xiang Kong can do that.
No.
They amended the competition details,
and didn't inform everyone?
Is it because Zhao Yang
is too busy recently?
And he overlooked it.
I wish it was that case.
Or else, the Legends team
will be in big trouble.
In that case,
I will personally ask him about this.
If he purposely did it,
I will definitely notify everyone.
Chairman Jin, I still think
Xiang Kong is the best choice
for the team leader position.
You're really affectionate
towards your disciple.
I understand this completely.
But everything
must be decided by the semi-finals.
Let's not talk about this.
It's your departure ceremony tonight.
You are the main lead.
I already followed your request,
and dismissed all the reporters.
Tonight,
there'll only be your industry friends.
After going through four teams'
intense battle,
let us congratulate
Legends and VNG,
the internal trial competition.
for being eligible to partake in
Fox Zhao, bye bye.
At the same time,
I feel that today both teams,
did very well.
Be it Pei Xi's quintuple kill,
or Ji Shuai's tactics.
I feel that they both made the live audience,
really passionate.
Let me tell everyone another
good news.
That is Conquer's new heroes
will be meeting everyone
at the internal trial competition's
finals's competition site.
So, Ji handsome,
are you anticipating?
I already can't wait.
Then, let me ask Pei Xi too.
What about you?
I'm anticipating using the new heroes
to defeat Ji Xiang Kong on the finals.
Still that same sentence, I'll persist until the end.
The tension
is already strong from the start.
I believe that the finals
will be absolutely exciting.
So many people?
VNG is also here.
Security brother,
let us go in.
Let us go in.
Let us in.
Legends team.
The Legends team is here.
Ji handsome,
Ji handsome.
Lin Yi Xuan.
Ji handsome, Ji handsome.
So many people.
Let's go, have a look.
Go back.
We are not accepting interviews today.
What right do they have to not let us in?
This is a private gathering for Gu Fang.
You guys can't go in.
You brought me here,
because of Gu Fang's
departure ceremony?
The department handed Gu Fang's
departure ceremony's news to me.
I have to do well.
Besides, the people here today
are all famous people in the industry.
If you know a few,
it'll be beneficial, what do you think?
Do you want to go in with me?
Isn't this bad?
What's bad about this?
You're scared that you'll meet
Ji Xiang Kong, that cheater, right?
Why should I be scared of him?
Aren't we not supposed to not enter?
It's fine.
I'm very familiar with this hotel.
I have solutions.
Follow me.
- Let us in.
Where are we going?
Let us in.
Wait, have you acted before?
Acted once or twice.
Okay.
Heads up, chest out, don't be nervous.
Deep breaths.
Let's go.
What's with you?
Gu Fang is already here, and you're only here now.
It's my first time handling such an important task.
It's your first day at work,
and you've already caused me so much trouble.
Sorry, boss. I'm wrong.
Did you bring the videos and details?
Yes, it's in my bag.
Hurry.
The screen is empty now.
What are you guys doing?
I already got scolded, did you not see?
Can you afford it if
the departure ceremony is delayed?
What kind of attitude are you giving?
Sorry brother.
There's really no time.
I'll educate her properly after this.
Can't you guys enter from the front door?
Let me tell you.
Your salary this month's gone.
Here.
Right.
Did you guys see
Fox Zhao's
expression earlier?
Xuan Ge, I didn't see it clearly just now.
Imitate it for us to see.
You didn't see?
- You're making me really angry.
Lu Feng.
Okay.
If Zhao Yang saw you,
I predict he'd definitely want a revenge.
I'm scared of him.
Kong Ge is going to support me.
Don't drag me in.
I don't want to
suffer his revenge with you.
We have different temperaments.
When did you
become so unloyal?
I can't be loyal when it comes to this.
So many people.
It's not time yet.
Let's wait outside for a while more.
Let's go walk around.
Let's go.
Come.
Let me tell you.
There's a mini kitchen here.
In a while, let's sneak in.
And then,
steal two uniforms out.
And sneak in.
I can gurantee no one will find out.
Can we?
Believe me.
When did I ever get you into trouble?
Let's go.
Let me tell you.
Gu Fang's departure ceremony today
can't have any problems.
If you dare to make another mistake,
I'll ask you to go home.
And don't come back again.
You useless thing.
Okay, boss.
Let's go.
It's so pain.
I was acting.
Let's go.
You're good.
When did you learn that?
I'll tell you when we get back.
Do you see it? The uniform is there.
There should be no one now.
Let's go.
We're getting the clothes.
What are you two doing?
Stomachache.
- What are you two doing?
We can't hold it anymore, stomachache.
We were looking for the washroom.
Stomachache.
You two ladies
were looking for the washroom in the kitchen?
We don't know the way.
Go upstairs to find it.
Leave quickly.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I can't hold it in anymore.
You, go take the clothes.
Me?
Go.
Brother,
I really can't find the washroom.
Sister, why are you back again?
I let you go.
You know too,
Out of ten girls, eight to nine of them
are bad at directions.
Okay.
Do you have pen and paper?
Yes.
Let's find a place with better lighting.
Come.
Do you see it?
What's the situation?
There seems to be mice here.
What's going on?
There's mice here?
No.
Finish the drawing.
I have to go have a look.
Once you finish drawing,
I'll help you catch.
Do you see it?
Go out, turn right, do you see it?
Go all the way to the end.
And then, turn right again.
Walk to the end and turn right again.
- That's not right.
And we're back?
You made me
confused.
I made you confused?
Look.
I remember it now.
- Thank you, brother.
Go out and turn right.
I remember it now.
Sister, don't go.
I haven't finished telling you.
Go out, turn right and right again.
Okay.
Go.
This sister is really weird.
Scared me to death.
You still have the audacity to talk about me.
Your acting isn't that good either.
But didn't we succeed?
Let's go, find the venue.
Let's go.
- Hurry.
So stylish.
Why's this so heavy?
Exert more force.
Go.
Go this way, be careful.
So many people.
It's so pretty.
Yes, I want to take a few pictures.
Be careful.
No problem.
Come.
Chairman Jin.
Congratulations.
Okay, you guys continue talking.
I'll sit them down first.
Okay.
Here, this way please.
Ever since,
we won the championship,
I started doing commentary,
Summer opened Dream Journey internet cafe.
Li Gan and Shu Wen
have both become coaches.
They formed VNG.
Only you were still competing.
It's a pity that now...
Actually, I've always still wanted to see
your holy spirit princess
showing great power.
been constantly updating.
In the recent years, the games have
This hero
is already reduced to nothing.
This also means
I may never be able to
come back to Conquer forever.
Look over there, Gu Fang, Luo Tian.
I've seen them before.
Then look over here.
Shu Wen, Summer, Li Gan.
They're the top five players to found this.
They are all here today.
You're good.
Came to work for a few days,
you already know who started?
Of course.
But,
You were only half right.
The original
ancient top five players
are Gu Fang, Luo Tian, Summer,
Shu Wen and Sun Ze Yi.
Wait a minute, who's Sun Ze Yi?
This Sun Ze Yi,
very little people know of him now.
He was one of the founders previously,
he was the team's commander.
Four years ago, which means,
The year they became champion.
Before the competition, he suddenly
quit without a reason.
They replaced him with Li Gan.
So,
and the world remembered Li Gan.
And forgot Sun Ze Yi.
There's actually such a thing...
Then do you think Sun Ze Yi
came?
Where is he?
He didn't and he won't.
He already disappeared
from the public's eye for a long time.
What are you guys doing? Serve the wine.
Okay.
Scared me to death.
It's okay.
Yi Yi.
Everyone at that table knows me.
It's okay.
Lower your head and push, I'll serve.
Anyway, they don't know me.
Then, block me a little.
Stop looking.
Don't look.
- Leader.
Teacher Luo, leader.
Still calling me leader?
No matter when it is,
you're still our leader.
I heard that right now you
are the stand in leader for Legends.
Fighting, I think highly of you.
Thank you Teacher Luo.
Xiang Kong,
you guys fought well for today's round.
Since I already made the decision,
then I must persist till the end.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Ji- let's go.
When you guys have an event to celebrate,
I will help you guys out if necessary.
It's not cheap right?
Money is trivial matter.
But, why didn't you two
go to Dream Journey internet cafe to have a look?
Now, I feel that meeting you guys
are harder than meeting celebrities.
When the competition is over,
we will definitely visit your place.
Okay, I know you guys are busy.
Ever since we disbanded,
the both of you built VNG
empty handed.
Being able to get these type of results today,
It's really not easy, really.
Come, have a drink, come.
You're so happy.
What are you guys talking about?
It's so crowded today.
Why didn't I see Pei Xi?
My cousin firstly, doesn't fit in.
Manager Zhao.
You care so much for Pei Xi,
you're not trying to take our ace right?
Listen to what you've said, Shu Wen.
I'm the type to cherish talents.
I especially like
players like Pei Xi.
At first I was looking for opportunities
Am I right?
to understand and get to know Pei Xi.
Besides,
Coach Shu Wen, who dares to
recruit your ace?
I wouldn't dare.
Is that right?
You guys continue talking,
I'll go ahead and be busy.
Chat.
Come.
Pei Xi is who we've
trained from the start.
How dare Old Zhao think of this?
This Zhao Yang.
Is becoming more and more obvious.
Whether or not Pei Xi joins Legends,
I can't make the decision.
Kids these days,
aren't as obedient as us before.
Besides, I'm only a cousin.
It's useless.
This Zhao Yang,
is well known for doing things improperly.
You two ought to pay attention.
What do you guys think
the results will be
if Pei Xi pairs up with Ji Xiang Kong?
Should be pretty spectacular.
No, from the way you phrased it,
do you want to recruit Legends's ace?
What are you saying? Two years ago,
if you weren't so quick and a move first
Ji Xiang Kong
would be VNG's member.
Whether it's good or not,
he won't join you guys.
Okay.
You've already retired.
Why do you still care so much?
Let's go to the table.
Come.
Scared me to death.
That Summer,
is still half your enemy.
I don't even know him.
What hatred do I have with him?
That Ti Qiao Xin,
is chasing your Pei Xi everywhere.
Is she your enemy?
He's Pei Xi's cousin.
You know quite a lot don't you?
Let me introduce, this is-
Oh my god, look.
What are you thinking of?
Thinking about Sun Ge.
Logical.
We're just missing him now.
Give him a call.
Ask him to come over.
Why not I give it a try?
Call.
Water for you two.
Sun Ge, my computer is a little laggy.
Let me have a look.
[Ji Xiang Kong]
You switched on all the special effects.
Our computer can't support that.
Sun Ge,
are you coming to leader's departure ceremony?
We're just missing you.
It's still okay, hurry.
Yi Ge and the rest are all here.
We're just missing you.
I'll send the location to you. Hurry.
Sun Ge, come over for a while.
Okay.
Isn't this Legends who are second place?
Battleground's fake winner, right?
What's up?
Why did you guys organise it so extravagantly?
You really think you're the champion?
Yi Xuan.
What's wrong? We can have a talk outside.
Sit down.
As a support, you are pretty arrogant。
Look opposite.
Four supports.
Do you think you can win?
Bad hands.
My master is here.
I won't argue with you today.
Who's this?
A new assistant you guys found?
I've seen your VNG competition before.
Only Pei Xi is worth anticipating.
Repeat that one more time.
Don't need to mention Pei Xi.
When he's not here, I'm the senior.
If you have anything to say, tell me.
Don't have to mention Pei Xi.
- Disrespectful.
This is?
Do you know why Legends lost?
Talking too much.
And this is?
Double moon team, have you never heard before?
Remember well.
Shen Yue Yue, Qi Yue Yue
Double moon team.
Nobody can win them.
Double moon.
Okay.
I particularly hate people who only know how to talk.
If you have the skills, we'll meet on battleground.
Lin Yi Xuan, toast to you.
I remembered you.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening everyone.
I am today's host, Luo Tian.
Welcome everyone
to my bestest bro,
Gu Fang's departure ceremony.
Four years ago,
because of Gu Fang's
holy spirit princess,
he saved us from a desperate situation
in Vancouver.
and allowed us, the founders,
to win the first champion that belongs to China.
Four years later, this last hero,
has also chosen to quit.
China's top gaming commentator.
This name is truly well deserved.
That's of course, he's too handsome.
We practiced together,
I want to go over there and take two photos.
I'll go over there alone first.
You be careful.
Okay, you be careful too.
Okay.
Today, the last warrior
is also choosing to quit.
As a good friend,
I sincerely feel happy for you.
But as a professional commentator,
I feel regretful.
Because from now on,
at Conquer's competitions,
we lost another top summoner.
I won't say too many mushy words.
Let's invite tonight's main lead,
Gu Fang.
Okay.
Hurry and go.
Go. Hurry.
I wasn't prepared.
Good evening everyone.
I didn't expect so many people to come.
I also didn't expect Summer
departure ceremony.
to be able to organise such an extravagant
At first, I thought there'd be only three to five people.
Eat some melon seeds, talk and we're done.
Everyone knows
My first team was the founders.
We chose this name
because we're the founders with a gaming dream.
There's fans who sneaked in for pictures.
Go have a look.
Everyone thought that
we are a group of crazy kids who
hobbies as entertainment.
didn't do honest work and only had
But, we didn't give up.
Although we weren't sponsored or supported,
in order to save money, the few of us
shared a bowl of noodles.
We laid mats outside the venue
but I was still happy in the process.
Because deep down we know
the path we take,
is the path to our dreams.
You really know how to find places.
It's you?!
Us, this group of youngsters gathered together.
Since we're familiar,
Hurry and give it to me.
let's not beat around the bush.
If not I'll call the security.
I remember you said you won't hit women right?
Why? Do you still want to hit me?
Quick, give it to me, hurry.
Hurry.
No, why would I want to hit you, right?
Gu Fang cried.
Actually, we didn't have our thoughts.
Wait.
We just weren't satisfied with losing.
We hoped that someday,
we could stand on a worldwide stage.
we are from China.
And say loudly and proudly,
Good.
I'm very honoured we did it.
Everyone who is sitted here today,
and those who aren't.
Those that aren't satisfied with losing.
I believe,
we will remember yesterday's dreams.
Helping our country to receive such high glory.
Don't forget your intentions, chase your dreams boldly.
Creating extremes continuously.
Stand at the top of the world,
this is our calling.
Come, lets raise our glasses.
Wishing today's version of you will be better.
Wishing for China's team to have a better future.
Okay. Cheers.
Finish it.
If you don't want to be embarassed,
follow me right now.
Stand there.
I have no energy anymore.
You're still running when you have no energy?
Don't run.
If you continue chasing me, I'll call the police.
No use calling the police.
Brother, do you need to go to this extent?
Even if I didn't hide in the female's toilet,
do you dare to search my body?
A girl's body?
Search. I definitely won't search you.
But if you don't give me the photos today,
I'll stay here and consume your time.
You.
Hooligan.
Excuse me.
You.
It's just a few pictures. Do you have to do this?
Do I have to do this?
My leader told me
he wanted to quit quietly.
He doesn't want outsiders to know.
What the.
If the pictures are out, I take the blame.
Tell me if I have to do this.
Brother. How about this?
Just treat it as you didn't see me today.
Look, if I don't say, no one knows, right?
Once it's done, I'll treat you to a meal.
So nice.
No.
Let go. I can walk by myself.
Let me go.
It seems like not only your acting is exaggerated,
you're also thick skinned.
Ji Xiang Kong, don't be too overboard.
I'm overboard?
If you weren't caught by me,
your live stream tonight would top again.
you didn't know it's a private gathering today.
Don't tell me,
Give your phone to me.
I didn't take photos neither streamed.
Look at it yourself.
Do you think I'll believe you?
Have you seen enough?
Do you still have anything?
Don't let me see you again.
Ji Xiang Kong, I'll prove it to you sooner or later.
So, you say, if I lose my job again,
then I'm too useless.
No, listen to me.
I have to go back to sending deliveries.
If the pictures are out,
Let's understand each other shall we?
I feel really bad now.
How about this,
let me quieten down alone.
Let's discuss after you're done okay?
I'll quieten down alone, I'm okay.
Are you okay alone?
Yes, don't worry.
I can handle alone.
So pitiful, I nearly cried.
Kong Ge, that-
I pity you.
But pass the pictures over.
You.
Shu Wen.
I'll go make a call first.
You.
Such a serious thing, you made it so simple.
I've already quit.
What's there to be serious?
No one understands Lao Gu's thoughts.
Do we not understand?
His heart is still heavier than everyone else.
it's already a beautiful ending.
To be able to persist till today,
Right. Let's drink together.
Come, take a glass of wine for me.
Come, celebrate the founders.
Celebrating the glorious departure of our last warrior.
Come, congratulations.
Thanks everyone.
We're only missing Lao Sun today.
Did he reply you?
Replied.
What'd he say?
What can he say?
He's just busy.
He has no time.
I can understand.
He can't hire someone to work at the internet cafe,
so he's looking after it himself.
If he doesn't come, how about we go find him?
Good idea.
It's been so many years, we should go have a look.
Yes.
The team has things on, I'll go soon.
I can't make it today.
Can we not miss anyone?
Don't mess around, the team has things on.
No energy.
- Wen Jie.
Wen Jie.
Xiang Kong. Take care of your leader.
I'll leave you first.
You all work hard.
Let's meet at the competition.
Wen Jie, let's meet at the competition.
Bye bye Wen Jie. Bye.
Why are you looking at me?
I said the wrong thing.
Obviously.
I-
Leader, why don't we leave too?
Okay.
can't forget the past,
Forget it. Seems like the one who
is not only Lao Sun alone.
Let's go to Dream Journey internet cafe.
Go.