[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 24]
This is so cool.
Of course.
It's all designed by my Brother Sun.
Be careful of this.
Don't spoil it.
Brother Sun.
Qiu Ying.
Yes.
Xiang Kong always mention about you.
Since when?
I'm hungry.
Let'sgo eat something.
Wait,
did you reincarnate from hungry ghost?
I have not self introduce.
Don't need for that. I know you.
You are Sun Ze Yi,
one of the five ancient master.
Did this rascal told you?
No,
I've watched all your competitions.
You are the leader and the commander,
totally like the soul
of the team.
I'm a bit shy after being
praised by your girlfriend.
Take a seat first
and have a chat,
I will make some good food for you all.
Thank you Brother Sun.
What are you thinking of?
Not..
Nothing.
Let me take a look at
your game analysis.
Okay.
Then...
Not bad.
There's improvements.
The...
If you look at me like this,
I cannot
focus.
Are you thirsty?
I will go get you a bottle of water.
Yi Yi, I'm back.
You're back?
Quick, come here.
Why are you so happy?
I'm
looking at your
game analaysis that you uploaded.
Nice!
You saw it so fast?
It's on the hot search
how can I miss it?
But I just posted on weibo,
how did it became hot search.
Because this afternoon,
Qiao Xin
uploaded a game analysis too.
The netizens
compared both of your
articles
and they all said that
yours are better.
Let me take a look.
Here.
You see.
I bet this Qiao Xin
must be very angry now.
Really.
Your game analysis
really
gave her a slap in face.
Well done.
Come.
This Qiao Xin,
only knows how to
act all day long.
Actually,
she just found a ghostwriter
so she needs to be hit by the reality.
Ghostwrite?
That
means
this is not written by her?
It must be written by Ah Can.
You see
the style and choice of words
is totally Ah Can's style.
I'm telling you this
to remind you
to be careful of Qiao Xin and Ah Can.
They are now a team.
Beware of them.
I know.
But I
don't have time to think of them now.
Whatever they want.
Right, don't think of them.
Come,
hungry?
Eat this.
Indeed Hot Pot is still the best.
I will go cook one.
Sit here.
I have already cooked it for you.
I'll go get it.
Love you.
There's a delivery on the table.
Open it up and take a look.
Coming coming.
So hot.
Move this away.
Move it move it.
Put here.
What is this?
Tickets for Mi Ya's new song release?
Who gave that to you?
Mi Ya gave it to me.
She gave it to you?
During the finals of Next Star,
she told me
to go her meeting session
and can go to the backstage.
But I didn't expect her to really send it.
Didn't know that
there's such good stuff.
When can we go?
You faster eat.
So happy!
Are you free tomorrow
5pm?
I have a surprise for you.
Okay.
As for the candidate for the advertisement,
why don't you consider Qi Yue?
He is the MVP
of this tournament.
Xiang Kong is here.
Let me introduce
this is our VNG's leader
Ji Xiang Kong.
Hi.
I have been following VNG's competition
and really salute your skills.
Actually I am a Dian Feng fan
if there's a chance,
I hope we can play together.
This is my honour.
But Miss Mi Ya is so busy
and is also a public figure
who needs to be careful of your behaviours,
I doubt you will have many chances
to play Dian Feng right?
Maybe it is before that
but I have already
discuss with my management company,
my work focus
will shift back to China
and especially with Dian Feng
collaboration.
It's like this,
Miss Mi Ya
have a lot of new endorsement recently
and specially appointed to interact
with VNG.
VNG is my favourite team
and I hope to bring more
resources for everyone
so that you all can focus
in your competitions.
As for the advertisement candidate,
I hope it's Ji Xiang Kong.
Not sure
if you will be willing to do it.
Our leader
is your super fan.
He must be very happy.
Xiang Kong
express your decision.
Hope our cooperation with a pleasure one.
Why are you
so quiet the whole trip?
Are you
angry that
I went to your team?
No.
I was thinking of something else.
Go back early.
Xiang Kong.
I am too selfish last time.
I ask you to
help in my career growth
but I neglected
that you are in your downs during that time
and you also need accompany.
I won't do it again.
This time
I will support you
with what I have got
over the years
and help you fulfill your dreams.
If two wants to carry on
it doesn't mean that one
have to sacrifice for another one
what it take is the accompany
and helping each other.
Your success today
is not because of me.
So
you don't need to make up for that.
When I see you shining
on the stage,
I know that the decision
is the right one.
But I regretted.
When I reach the peak
that I thought
I realise
no matter how beautiful the scenery is,
it's nothing with your accompany.
Xiang Kong,
can you help with something?
Give me a moment.
Please don't go.
Xiang Kong,
do you remember this guitar?
This Taylor
have been with me for years.
Even though the colour is old,
but the tone is very good.
Take a look.
Can I pay by monthly installment?
Or can I work for you?
Taylor's guitar.
Where did you get the money
to afford such an expensive guitar?
Actually,
it's not as expensive as you thought.
This is a second hand guitar.
But the tune is very nice.
Listen.
The tune is nice
but it's old,
so it's hard to tune.
But don't worry,
I have already learn how to tune it.
Next time,
I will tune it
before you plays it.
Then I must
use this guitar forever,
so that you will tune it for me
forever.
How is it?
Okay.
You said you will
help me tune it forever.
Will you still
tune it for me now?
Okay.
Xiang Kong.
Sorry,
I forgot how to tune it.
I got to go.
Xiang Kong.
You insisted on doing it your own way,
agreed to that few endorsements
to help Ji Xiang Kong.
How did it end up?
Did he thank you after knowing?
It's not important.
I've already decided.
I will use
double the time
Xiang Kong waited for me
to make up and wait for him
till he is willing to accept me.
You will regret
because of your
stubborn character.
Isn't you
chose me
because of my stubbornness
and accompany me to conquer everything
till today.
Tony,
don't stop me.
Even if I will regret,
let me be crazy one more time.
Okay?
Mi Ya,
some people won't come back
even if you wait.
Ji Xiang Kong said before
both of you
have changed.
Furthermore,
he has
Qiu Ying now.
Qiu Ying is just my stand in.
She has my shadow.
So,
today's new song release
you arrange her to go backstage find you
is to have it out with her?
To tell her
your past with Ji Xiang Kong
and ask her to leave?
Thank you.
Ah Can Teacher,
not that I am petty,
but we just
complete a game analysis,
Qiu Ying also wrote one.
What does she mean?
Newbie is like that.
Thinking of all ways to stand out.
This is understandable.
But all the comments are saying
her analysis
is accurate and professional
while ours
is not up to the standard.
What's going on?
My...
My analysis is not up to the standard?
When I was is GDV,
she don't even know
what is commenting.
I not capable?!
Ah Can Teacher,
actually
you don't need to be so angry.
This is obviously Qiu Ying
paying people for the good comments.
She used to do this
when she was in You Xing.
She love to put people down
to raise her values.
Okay.
Newbies nowaday
are so arrogant
even before going on to the stage.
I will to let her know
what is called respecting the seniors.
Let's see how great she is.
Thank you. You are welcome.
CEO Guo, are you looking for me?
Take a seat.
Is this article on weibo
written by you?
Yes, it's written by me.
Is there any problem?
There's no problem with the article
but Qiu Ying
you are still a newbie
so you might be unsure of
culture with GDV.
For GDV to have today,
everyone have to be on the same line,
I don't hope that anyone
will destroy the relationship in between colleagues.
No, CEO Guo,
I don't understand what you mean.
This article is written by me
but I didn't want to destroy
the relationship in between colleagues.
Qiu Ying
you rush for
success.
Write articles to bring down your colleagues
just to stand out.
How do you want
the outsiders to see GDV?
Ah Can Teacher,
I just merely did an analysis
for the competition,
I don't mean to bring down anyone.
Enough enough.
You don't need to explain anymore.
You posted an article
right after Qiao Xin have posted.
And the angles of the article are about the same.
Isn't it very
obvious?
I don't want to see any
internal disputes again.
Do you understand?
CEO Guo-
CEO Guo, the materials you want.
Pardon me
I overheard your
conversation earlier on.
Why don't I feel that
Qiu Ying's article
is against anyone?
Just because Qiao Xin posted an article,
doesn't mean other cannot post.
Does that mean that
Qiu Ying is attacking someone
when her article
is better than someone else's?
CEO Guo,
GDV
have seventeen commentators
including the interns.
If one wants to stand on the stage,
they need real work.
Furthermore,
Qiao Xin's article
is too shallow.
Ah Can,
from your professional point of view,
what do you think?
Teacher Luo
is always right.
Enough.
Stop discussing about this.
Go back to work.
Brother Kong,
you say finally we got
some off days
and you don't ask Qiu Ying out
to sing or what.
If you want to ask Lu Yi Yi out,
just go ahead.
Don't disturb me.
Who say I want to ask her out?
I'm just panicking for you.
Pei Xi has already confess.
Secret Garden?
Isn't this the popular
confess restaurant?
Are you thinking of confessing to Qiu Ying?
My Brother Kong has finally grown up.
It's not easy.
Go go go.
Go help Brother Sun.
Don't close the webpage.
This is very hard to get.
They will only release the reservation for the night
at 3pm everyday.
If you don't hurry, it will be gone.
Go away.
Don't disturb me.
You might not get it with just one computer.
What's that...
Brothers,
That Chen Qi Meng, Chai Hao Wei,
today
whoever who can help my Brother Kong
get the reservations of Secret Garden
you will get three days free to
here.
Is it okay, Brother Sun?
I agree.
You see.
Captain Ji,
who are you dating with?
Is it Qiu Ying?
Tell you a good news.
Teacher Luo say
I can go on the commenting stage.
That's great.
I will prepare a feast for you tonight.
This sour taste.
Go go go.
Didn't you say you want to help?
Go and get it.
Okay.
You scared me!
How dare you to be late.
Late?
I'm not late.
It's just nice 6.30pm.
On the point.
You should be
early than me.
What did you bought?
A gift for you.
For me?
Let me see.
But you can't open it now.
Why can't I open it now?
You just can't open it now.
If not I will be angry.
Let's go.
You have not tell me
where are you bringing me to.
Don't care about it.
Quick. So many people.
This way this way.
Isn't the entrance there?
You don't care, just follow me.
You stepped on me.
Okay.
Dear audiences,
good afternoon to everyone.
I'm now at
the press release of
Fu Mi Ya's China first album
"Tian Kong Zhi Wai".
Quick.
What event is this?
So secretive.
And you bring me though the back door.
You can meet
the person that you have been wanting to meet.
Is this a big surprise?
Are you sure you know
who I always wanted to meet?
Of course.
You see.
How is it?
You brought me to Mi Ya's-
Today is Mi Ya's
new song press release.
She gave me two VIP tickets
and we can meet her backstage
and ask her for autographs.
I want to go out for a while.
Don't be shy.
Let's go. Quick.
Don't be shy, come.
Go in.
Xiang Kong.
Why didn't you tell me you are here?
Or did you saw
my message?
Qiu Ying?
You..
you all...
know each other?
Come.
Do you remember
during Next Star
competition,
I said that
I have a friend
who love competitive sports?
He's Xiang Kong.
Also,
we
grow up together.
Right, Xiang Kong?
Mi Ya,
let me introduce to you.
Qiu Ying,
my girlfriend.
Xiang Kong,
are you blaming me for
not persisting for our love?
You chose Qiu Ying
is it because
she's very similar to me?
Is it because
she was like the me five years ago
right?
She is indeed very similar with you
but-
Enough.
The love story in between the both of you
have nothing to do with me.
Please don't
drag me into it.
I doesn't want
to be the tool
that both of you use to test your love.
Qiu Ying. Xiang Kong.
Xiang Kong,
can you give us another chance,
let's start again okay?
Sorry,
I have someone I like already.
Qiu Ying, listen to my explanation. Qiu Ying!
Qiu Ying!
Sorry.
Listen to my explanation.
You are Mi Ya's first love right?
The song "Tian Kong Zhi Wai"
is for you
right?
The one who she hugged beside the pool
is not Ren Xu,
is you right?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why must you make me so embarrassed?
Qiu Ying, sorry
but
it's not what you're thinking.
Why must you tell her
I am your girlfriend?
Ji Xiang Kong, what am I to you?
You can't forget her.
Why must you make me misunderstood
that you like me?
Qiu Ying, I really like you.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
Really.
But I can't bring myself
to believe this.
Ji Xiang Kong,
you can't forget her.
You be friend with me
cause because you can find her shadow
in me.
I'm just a stand in.
Qiu Ying, it's not what you are thinking.
Listen to my explanation.
Let's go of me, let go.
I don't want to listen to your explanation.
I will wait for you at Secret Garden.
Give me a chance to explain to you.
Hello,
the number you have dialed is unavailable.
Sir,
your meal
should I serve it later on?
Thank you.
Okay.
Ji Xiang Kong.
I believe you will
stand on the top of the world.
I hope that day
it's you
who is standing at the commenting stage
announcing to the world that
China team
is the world champion.
Promise.
Thank you for riding
pass the low period of my life.
If this is fate,
I hope I can hug you tightly
and accompany you to the top of the world.
Qiu Ying
be strong
and finish this notes.
Forget
about what happened today.
Tomorrow
is a brand new day.
What are you doing so late at night?
Teacher Luo.
What happen
to you?
I got to go.
Wait.
Let me send you back.
Sir,
sorry.
We
are closing.
Okay.
Sir, sir.
The deposit you paid
includes our restaurant's
special secret garden cake.
If your friend
couldn't come today,
we can help you
remake another one next time.
Thank you.
Maybe there's no more next time.
Always
didn't have the chance
to thank you.
I really like the cup.
Sorry,
Teacher Luo
for showing this side of me.
It's okay.
Everyone will have sad moments.
But
I hope that
you can adjust your condition as soon as possible.
As an intern,
you should know
how cruel is the commenting stage.
If you can't make it
for the upcoming tournament,
maybe you might
even lose the chance of
sending materials.
I got it.
Teacher Luo.
Is it here?
Thank you Teacher Luo.
Sorry for bothering you.
You're welcome.
I'm going up.
Oh ya.
Here.
Take it.
Go back and take the medicine.
If you really caught a flu,
how are you
going to face the camera and audiences?
Thank you.
Bye bye Teacher Luo.
Bye bye.
You finally came back.
I thought
you got kidnapped by Ji Xiang Kong.
Quick, tell me
what did you all did
today.
What happened?
Why are you so messed up?
Give me your bag.
What happened?
Nothing.
It was raining.
I have no umbrella.
What is Ji Xiang Kong doing?
How can you be drench like this?
I'm going to shower.
Qiu Ying,
tell me
did Ji Xiang Kong bullied you?
Tell me,
if yes, I will make sure he pay for it.
No.
Yi Yi
I'm cold.
I going to shower first.
Something is not right.
There must be something.
Hello Lu Reporter
you finally gave me a call.
Do you want to eat supper?
Eat what supper?
I ask you
tonight
did you Brother Kong
ask Qiu Ying out for a date?
Yes.
I even help to reserve the restaurant.
Secret Garden,
super hard to reserve.
It's a restaurant for confession.
Confess?
You don't know?
Oh ya, how was it?
Did they...
I say can your brain
be more clean?
Qiu Ying came back
all wet
and very unhappy.
I
I see her state,
I didn't dare to ask much.
You say
did you Brother Kong
bully our Qiu Ying again?
Impossible.
My Brother Kong is very gentleman to ladies,
how would he bully Qiu Ying?
Maybe
Qiu Ying rejected my Brother Kong.
Qiu Ying like him so much
it's impossible to reject him.
Wait wait wait wait
what what what?
Enough, I don't want to talk to you anymore.
No point asking you.
Hanging up. Bye.
Such a grown up
and still don't know how to take care of yourself.
Drink some ginger tea and warm up.
No wonder
Mi Ya will fall down on her new song
release event.
You didn't saw the news?
Looks like
Mi Ya won't give up so easily.
Brother Sun,
what should I do now?
Qiu Ying this girl,
even though I only met her once
but can tell that
she won't tolerate
any flaws
in the relationship.
She doesn't want to listen to my explanation.
Both of  you need to
calm down now.
The tournament is
starting few days later.
This is very important to you and Qiu Ying.
No matter you are thinking of yourself
or being responsible for her,
you all should concentrate
on the tournament.
But I hope that
you can adjust your condition as soon as possible.
If you can't make it
for the upcoming tournament,
you might even
lost the chance of sending materials.
Hello.
Sorry,
I know this call
is very sudden.
But I really want to meet you.
Can I?