Episode 11
Reporter Lu.
What do you want?
Thank you for your help just now.
Don't need to.
I can't stand your thank you.
I only ask that you
don't provoke our Qiu Ying anymore.
Please and thank you.
In order to find this video for you,
she waited to at the airport for a night.
do you know?
And something nearly happened to her,
What happened?
Where is she now?
She's fine now.
Let me tell you.
Stop trying to take her advantage.
No.
My Kong ge is sincere.
You can't say it like that.
As long as he
stops messing with our Qiu Ying.
I'll be sincerely grateful.
Is this what she wants
or is this what you want?
Is there a difference?
What I want
is also what she wants.
Our Qiu Ying is naive,
simple and kind.
Let me tell you.
Don't try to take advantage of her.
Or I'll never forgive you.
And you.
What has this got to do with me?
You're going?
Take care.
Remember to send WeChat messages to me.
Something's going on.
Interesting.
Not- not interesting.
I-
Am I that obvious?
You know it yourself.
You're going?
We've suffered a lot today.
It's okay.
Don't do anything today.
Sleep early.
You didn't really sleep well last night.
It's fine.
I slept on the chair at the airport.
Waist hurts a little.
Obviously. It'd be surprising if your waist didn't hurt
while you're pressing the chair like that.
I saw online that
so many people were apologising to Ji Xiang Kong.
I just feel that
my efforts weren't wasted.
I don't understand.
What has he 'sinking into the snow'
got to do with you?
You're worry about him the whole day.
No way, I'll go to the toilet first okay?
My stomach hurts a little.
Sleep early.
Go.
Where's my phone?
It's there.
Sleep early.
[Is it alright if we have dinner together?]
Ji Xiang Kong
[You're polite, I should be the one treating.]
Qiu Ying
Gong Shu district, Hang Zhou City]
[Location: Top Roast Meat,
Ji Xiang Kong
[This store has pretty good roast meat.]
See you.
Yi Yi.
I'm suddenly really sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't disturb me later.
Goodnight.
She really slept?
What are you doing?
Acting all suspicious.
Didn't you say you were going to sleep?
I'm suddenly a little hungry.
I want to go and buy some instant noodles.
We still have a lot at home.
What are you buying for?
Our house-
I want a seafood flavoured one.
Buying instant noodles?
What are you holding in your hand?
Hand it over.
You're going to wear this
to go and buy
instant noodles?
Who are you lying to?
Did someone ask you out?
That person or Ji Xiang Kong?
No.
This guy is really perseverant.
I clearly rejected him
in the afternoon for you.
He still dares to ask you out?
Yi Yi,
but he also helped us previously?
Just having a meal together, it's not too much right?
He asked you to eat out when it's so late.
Then why don't he ask you
tomorrow morning or afternoon?
It's so late, he definitely doesn't have good intentions.
You're thinking too much.
We are just purely going out for a meal.
Tell me honestly, you
Have you already fallen for him?
What joke are you cracking?
We are just normal friends.
How is that possible?
I swear.
We are just simply eating a meal.
Sure.
What are you doing?
If you want to change, that's fine.
Come here, change into this.
And for the pants, just keep this on.
Change your top into this.
It'd be best if you're
covered from head to toe.
You definitely can't be this exposed.
Okay.
[Lu Yi Yi]
Hello?
Hello? Lin Yi Xuan.
What's up?
Let me ask you.
Is your Kong Ge going out?
How did you know?
Where's he going?
A roast meat store
that we always go to.
Roast meat store?
Then since it's this way,
send the address to me later.
Wait for me there.
You want to ask me out for a meal?
What are you saying?
Move quicker, bye.
Okay.
How do I look? Am I handsome?
No.
You're going to have a meal with me.
What are you wearing?
This is the trend for next year.
What do you know?
Trend for next year.
Be quieter.
Okay.
Have a look at the menu.
Thank you.
I'm declaring first.
I'm treating for this meal.
Thank you for willing to reconcile with me.
It's necessary.
You waited at the airport
throughout the night.
And helped me out so much.
So I'm treating for this meal.
But-
Stop fighting with me.
Okay.
Since you're so persistent,
you'll be treating for this meal.
I'll definitely treat the next meal.
We just sat down,
you're already arranging for
for a next meal.
You
can't be serious for more than three seconds.
Hurry.
What do you want to eat?
Slow down.
Where is it?
Is it here?
It's here.
This is Kong Ge's car.
Why are you looking for him?
He's not here too.
He's not here.
Come down.
What if we get discovered?
It's okay.
Then you-
Exactly why are you looking for him?
We have to find him first.
Am I right?
Where is he?
Sorry.
Let's go there.
Oh my, they're really there.
Sorry.
They're sitting in an isolated corner.
They're definitely not up to anything good.
This Ji Xiang Kong,
better act more honestly.
Can I ask something?
What did we come here to do today?
Are you done?
It's so obvious can't you tell.
You're following them?
I still thought that
you were asking me out for a meal.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I have to go in.
I have to hear what they're talking.
People are dating.
It's immoral for us
to eavesdrop on them.
Date!
You also think it's a date.
How dangerous is a date?
I can't not supervise them.
What has it got to do with you?
Are you going or not?
Going.
Did we order too much?
Actually, usually at this time,
I don't eat.
I'm on a diet.
You're already so thin, and you're
still dieting?
At least eat a little.
Then I'll help myself.
Let's barbecue this first.
Let me do it.
Let's sit there.
Okay.
One, two, three, let's go.
One, two, three.
What are you two doing?
Tying our laces.
Sorry.
What are you two doing?
Gastric.
Look at what you'd like.
Just give us-
We'll just
get any barbecue meat.
Anything's fine.
No.
We don't want barbecue meat.
That- we have to drink some hot drinks for gastric.
Just serve us some porridge.
Those that are free flow.
Why are you so stingy?
I ate before coming here.
But I didn't.
Let's talk later.
Oh right, do you want to order some drinks?
Or beer is fine too.
Let's not drink beer.
No problem, if you're drunk,
then you can tell me your house's address.
I'll send you home!
Besides,
we are in a 'no discord, no concord' relationship.
I'll apologise to you first.
For spoiling your mom's necklace.
How do you know that's my mom's necklace?
That night when you were drunk,
you treated me like I was your mom.
Sorry.
I didn't expect that necklace
to be so important to you.
I misunderstood you.
and for the 2V2 battle, reality show
the things I said to you
were too overboard.
I apologise to you.
I almost don't recognise you when you're like this.
The necklace is fixed.
Actually,
I ought to apologise to you too.
method to get on your car.
I shouldn't have used that
and selfishly played the 2V2 battle with you.
It was right that you educated me.
Then, from what you say,
we are even now.
Cheers.
That's not right.
Why do I feel like
the plot deviated a little.
Isn't this good?
You still want them both to fight?
We didn't order this.
This is what you ordered.
No worries.
Leave it here.
To express my gratitude,
this is for you.
How can I let the girl do the cooking?
I should be serving you.
Come.
I'll wrap one for you.
Here.
What's wrong? Is it not easy to take?
Or do you want me to feed you?
No need.
Right.
I almost forgot.
This is a gift for you.
You don't have to be too thankful towards me.
What is it?
Although your video
and had many errors,
was badly produced, excessively made,
but for a newbie like you,
it's already good enough.
and had many errors.
Badly produced, excessively made,
You are the anonymous netizen?
You can't deny.
I dare to confirm that it's you.
As for the hitting video,
it's already cleared.
with UXStar videos.
I will invite the team to communicate
So as to allow you to continue working.
Fulfill your mom's wish well
and become an excellent host.
Thank you.
I don't really want to go back anymore.
If I stay at UXStar,
Conquer host.
there's nothing else I can do besides be a
Actually, it's not possible to learn
anything professional.
I'm only nice to look at.
The moment I sold my house,
I thought it through.
No matter what I do,
I will have to succeed.
The best is to become so professional
that others can't pinpoint.
Then, did you ever thought of
doing professional gaming commentary?
Professional gaming commentary.
Because a lot of people are
following up with esports now.
There are also many players that are pretty good.
But there are very little commentators
that can comment well,
understand the team's tactics and
and the players.
Especially female commentators.
Majority of them are
just pretty to look at.
Or are female-
No,
I don't mean it that way.
I wanted to say.
If you're willing to work hard,
I trust that you'll have a good future.
I- can I really?
Why not?
People like me who have unskilled hands
are still able to get into the Vancouver finals.
You definitely can do it.
I'm really stuffed.
I really don't know why
I called you here.
You only know how to eat.
If we don't eat it, it would be very wasted.
Now that we're full, how was it?
Pretty good.
Waiter, we're paying.
Coming.
Hello,
the total will be RMB 460.
RMB 460?
Okay, thank you.
Settle the bills for both sides.
He's paying.
Kong ge, what a coincidence.
Kong ge what a coincidence.
Qiu Ying, you are here too.
Stop being enigmatic and
suspicious with me.
Yi Yi.
What are you doing here?
Reporter Lu,
I'm returning Qiu Ying to you
in one piece without any flaws.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Qiu Ying, it's so late.
You're still fooling around outside.
Follow me home.
I'll wait for you outside.
Then, I'll go back first too.
Thank you for dinner and the notebook.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Okay, I'm going too.
Go and pay the bill.
Kong ge, you...
asking me to pay?
You're chasing women and
This isn't appropriate.
Kong ge, you're really leaving? Kong ge.
No, don't leave, I didn't bring-
Kong ge, Kong- I-
- Sir.
Kong- Kong-
I'm not leaving, I'm just looking.
You haven't paid.
No, he-
Please pay. Come.
Let me check the receipt for you.
Okay, speak.
This is that table's bill, RMB 460.
This is your table's, RMB 600.
Mine is RMB 600?
No worries, that-
Sir.
No, I-
Bro, no.
Don't go.
Do you know the Legends team?
No I don't.
Do you play games?
I am Lin Yi Xuan.
Can I get a discount?
Who?
I- I'm Lin Yi Xuan.
I don't know you.
Let me tell you.
The meal earlier.
Even if you guys have reconciled,
for your own
blissfulness,
In future, block him on wechat,
block his number, don't even think about seeing him.
Do you understand?
I'm talking to you.
Do you hear me?
You're ignoring me again.
Yi Yi, I've decided.
I want to become a
professional commentator.
are you having a fever?
You're doing this again,
I'm being serious.
I've decided.
I've decided to become
a person like Luo Tian.
What are you saying so late at night?
I know.
Is it because Ji Xiang Kong
convinced you to do commentary?
The first time I
saw Luo Tian,
I already had this thought.
From today onwards, I want to
move towards my dreams.
I'm stopping you.
Don't talk to me about dreams.
About dreams,
I know more about them than you.
Then let me ask you.
Are you satisfied with the present?
I have to be.
I'm living so comfortably now.
I don't think about so many things like you.
If you're really satisfied with the present,
you wouldn't
have acted like that at the press conference.
How did I act?
You said because of my dreams, I
have to seek for the truth.
Oh my god, I have to stop you.
I didn't act that way.
Stop pretending in front of me.
Listen to me.
You said you could.
And you definitely can.
Stop saying those things like
"my dreams died on the way."
Okay.
I'm scared of you now is that okay?
Stop telling me motivating things.
Let's go home.
Are you shy?
When am I shy?
Enough.
I especially hate when others
tell me motivational things.
Move quicker, yes.
I asked you to carry this away long ago, hurry.
Director.
Worrying me to death.
What's the occasion today?
Why's everyone so busy?
Lu Yi Yi.
You finally came.
Look at this.
[Dynamic esports magazine reporter persistantly asks for the truth for justice.]
Isn't this me?
Why am I on there?
You're going to be on hot trends soon.
I'm going on hot trends?
Oh gosh, isn't it good Director?
Good?
Is that not good?
Come.
Then, look at this too.
This is what
the Legends fans
specially sent for you.
In order to praise you.
Praise me?
So, Director, look,
such a good thing.
Right? But why do I feel like
you're a little
unhappy?
Yi Yi.
You really can't tell
whether I'm praising or
insulting you?
Do you know?
I'm definitely
it's the biggest challenge
for our company ever since I've started working here,
Throughout the morning, I've received
four to five calls from the leader.
He wants to come down in the afternoon
for a check and ask some questions.
My days of tasting tea and reading books
won't be back forever.
Sorry Director.
What's the use of apologising?
We are merely a
small magazine company under the organisation.
Why do you have to make such bold moves?
What's the use of the leader coming?
No matter how many times the leader comes,
they're unable to increase our budget.
We still can't go out for interviews.
Look, now GDV
wants us to go out in the afternoon
for an interview at special event.
We struggled and worked hard for many years.
Who went out for an interview before?
Director.
Me. I can go and try.
But doesn't it still have to be you?
Whoever started the blunder
has to be responsible.
Go.
I'll go now.
Quickly go. Take away those flowers.
Right, Director. Where's the venue?
Where could it be?
GDV office.
Then I'll go now.
Go quickly.
Bye Director.
Quickly go.
What has happened to the world?
I did the work and still need to suffer criticism.
Hello Lu Yi Yi.
I'm at GDV.
This place is too big.
Every level is GDV.
Where are you?
Just walk in.
The interview is
going to start soon.
If you don't deliver it to me now,
I'm doomed.
I know.
You have to tell me which
which level you're at.
You left without bringing your things.
Luckily I was home.
I'm at the seventh floor.
Hello?
Can't be.
It ran out of battery at an important moment.
Hello, do you need help?
It's fine.
I already found her, thanks.
Okay.
My phone ran out of battery at an important time.
Can Qiu Ying find me?
- Yi Yi.
Qiu Ying.
You're finally here.
- Here.
Where's the documents?
I really love you.
My phone ran out of battery.
I was so nervous.
You're a professional reporter
and you didn't even bring your materials out.
I got here on short notice okay.
These documents
are my summaries after studying.
Then when I go for interview,
I have to be at least a little prepared.
Hurry.
Qiu Ying, the interview is going to start soon.
Let's talk later.
Sit here and drink some water, wait for me.
Love you, mua, bye bye.
Commentary table.
Hello everyone.
I am commentator Qiu Ying.
Today, what I'm sharing with everyone is
the first round of the Spring competition's
conventional competition.
VNG versus Legends.
Let us have a look at the screen.
This really is
an exciting competition.
Oh gosh.
Both teams are both shooters.
Are they trying to output later?
Luo Tian, what do you think?
Do interns do as they please
when they practice?
Or do you think the commentary script
are simple words that just flows out your mouth?
Sorry.
I'm not an intern.
I went to the wrong place.
So sorry.
Qiu Ying, oh my god.
You're done with reporting? How was it?
So tiring.
Thankfully, you sent the materials to me on time.
Or else, I'd be unprepared.
I don't even know how I would 'die'.
Why are you
looking so love sick?
Yi Yi.
Wasn't I researching on
how to be a commentator lately?
I met a big opportunity.
Do you know GDV
are conducting a competition called
'Tomorrow's star'.
The champion will be partnering with Luo Tian.
You still get to host Conquer together.
Luo Tian, forget it.
Luo Tian is the top in making snarky comments.
If you partner with him,
he'll argue with you all the way.
He's someone so excellent.
It's normal for him to be a little more strict.
Besides, I've already registered.
Sister, you entering the competition
with your current standard.
You'll only be his denominator.
Anyway,
I'm not going back to UXStar anymore.
But I don't want to leave the industry.
I don't want to miss out on
such a good opportunity.
I can't miss out on it.
Later, you drink this quickly.
Then follow me to the bookstore.
And buy some related books.
So that I can study.
Not going.
I have no more energy. I'm so tired.
Yi Yi.
I know a software that has everything.
Even things about gaming.
Let me search it for you.
Gaming.
Okay. Choose.
So cheap!
The cost of a new book is good enough for you to buy two of three here.
That's of course.
It's a second hand site.
Am I good?
Is it authentic?
Of course, choose quickly.
This, this and this.
It's so cheap, I want everything.
Then I'll order now.
I estimate that it'll reach tomorrow.
Done, nice.
My knowledge and understanding
finally has some landing.
But how am I able to quickly raise
my experience with commentating.
Yi Yi, quick, help me think.
How would I know?
I know that in the industry,
there's an internet cafe
that has scheduled competition livestreams
and competition analysis.
Especially suitable for people like you
who are seeking help last minute.
Really? Then let's go.
Let's hurry and go.
Here.
How's it? Not ordinary right?
There are so many people over there.
Follow me.
Wait a minute.
Let me tell you.
There wouldn't be little people in the industry
in this kind of places.
We have to change our accent.
But remember.
Talk less, listen more.
Do I need you to teach me this?
Let's go.
You walked to the wrong place.
Here, sister.
So cool.
There are Conquer's elements all over.
Didn't you come here previously?
I came here before.
When I came here previously, it didn't look like this.
Okay.
Look at that skinny guy,
I know him.
Nickname: Fat cat.
Was first in the previous server.
But, now his first place
got defeated by someone called skinny monkey.
Skinny monkey
What do you want to drink?
My gosh. He's also here.
How come you don't even
know what I like to drink?
I want a 'scream'.
What colour?
Blue, hurry.
What time is it now?
The competition over there is almost starting.
Aren't they rivals?
Why are they acting like friends?
How do you know everything?
That's a must.
But these two,
the skinny one is called Fat cat,
the chubby one is called Skinny monkey.
They're a match made in heaven.
What are they looking at?
Come, let's go see.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Let us through.
Thank you.
Go.
This girl is so cool.
What are you doing?
Go, attack.
Top route's army line.
Use your skills.
Quickly go back, they're pushing your crystal.
Nice.
Excellent.
Consider yourself excellent.
Are you okay?
First time I met a girl
that incredible.
She's too good at this.
Jie jie,
are you in the current server rankings?
Then you fit in the hiring notice here.
Yes.
I don't serve others tea or pour water for them.
Move away.
Okay.
Cool.
She's a little cold.
Cold.
Hello, I know you guys.
You know us?
Fans.
Yes.
were talking about?
What was the hiring that you guys
Dream Journey's hiring.
It's over there.
[Hiring waitresses]
[1. If you're not a girl we don't want you.
2. If you don't like professional gaming, we don't want you.
3. If you're not the first in the server, we don't want you.
Oh my god.
You have to be first in server,
just to even be a waitress.
Really frenzied.
This can only prove that
their standard is high.
Maybe the ones delivering tea and water,
are all masters.
Qiu Ying, look.
Pei Xi.
This cold facade?
The last time you played 2V2,
he and Qiao Xin were trying to kill you.
What kind of person is he?
Forget it, it's already in the past.
But what's he doing here?
And he's wearing the waiter outfit.
Right.
I remember.
The boss here is his cousin, Summer.
Then that's why.
A top player working as a waiter here,
what are they planning?
Forget it, let's not bother about him.
Come, play two rounds with me.
Let's go.
Chairman Jin, you were looking for me?
Xiang Kong.
Come, come quickly.
Sit.
Today, I called you and Manager Zhao over
not for something big.
Previously, during the press conference,
there seems to be a misunderstanding between you two.
I apologise to you on behalf of the company.
At the same time, I also hope you can understand
after the video had went out,
everyone in the team is jittery.
At a moment in time, the company
made a special decision.
We were forced to.
It's okay, Chairman Jin.
It's over now.
Manager Zhao.
Just give me an appropriate apology and that's okay.
Of course,
Manager Zhao wants to sincerely apologise to you.
Sorry, it's all my fault.
Sorry.
I've worn the earpiece for too long
I didn't hear clearly, what was it?
Sorry, it's all my fault.
You're too polite, it's okay.
Actually, everything that Manager Zhao
is for the good of the team.
We understand very well.
Completely understand.
Everyone is part of the 'family',
don't take it personally.
The most mission currently
- Yes.
is the internal trial competition.
Don't worry.
I won't let you guys down.
Since it's this way,
We will just wait for
our Ji handsome to make a glorious return.
If there's nothing else, I'll go first.
Manager Zhao,
since we are a 'family',
shake hands with Xiang Kong.
Treat it as this is over,
President Zhao, have some tea.
Not drinking.
No, don't be angry.
He's just lucky this time.
Made me apologise.
Was it done cleanly?
Relax, it was done cleanly.
They won't be able to trace it down to us.
Ji Xiang Kong.
You're playing with me. I'll play you to 'death'.