[English subtitles are available]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 1]
When the empress was enthroned,
the dynasty was in turmoil.
To consolidate her domination,
the practice of tipping off was made popular by the empress,
[Reward]
allowing all commoners to enter the capital
and became informers.
All of a sudden,
whistle blowing became a trend in Luoyang.
Until the fall of oppressive officials during Daqing period,
the practice declined gradually,
and there was no more informer.
Until the third year of Taicheng period,
an informer suddenly appeared
and interrupted the peaceful life in Luoyang.
[Xiaoyu, Chen Buyi, Qi, Da Zhameng, Xiao Haozi
Jianchun Gate]
[South City]
[Tang-dynasty Coin]
[The Unwelcome Well]
[Chunqiu Divine]
[Second word]
[South City]
[The Prince: The Victim]
[Yulou Cave Plum Buns]
Tanghulu.
[The informer: Lin Zhong]
[Lin Zhong's daughter, Lin Yan]
Great!
-Great! -
Look at the nice wine here.
Mister.
Yes?
May I know the way to Dangyang Tavern?
After crossing the bridge,
turn left and there it is.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Come, mister.
Look at the liquor here.
[The Inner Guard: Yuehua, Wu Siyue]
This place is so lively!
The South City has the most shops
in Luoyang.
[Hundreds of fine...]
Precious and unique goods from the north and the south
are being traded here
and sold to other places.
Your Highness,
follow me closely.
Don't get lost in the crowd.
[Princess Yongchuan: Li Lu]
Yue, look at this!
Over there!
Don't be tensed.
It's not easy to be out from the palace.
Take a stroll with me.
Great! Great!
Good job.
[Dangyang Tavern]
Eaten raw, the sashimi is sweet and delicious,
without losing its tastiness.
It is indeed a delicacy.
Wait a minute.
[Dangyang Tavern]
[The Councilor of Ministry of Works:
Baili Hongyi]
You can slice any fish
but not this snakehead fish from the cold seep.
It can't be eaten raw.
Snakehead fish from natural cold seep.
Bloodletting, deboning and getting the flesh
need to be done in one go.
The fish fillets need to be sliced as thin as the cicada's wings
and boiled in broth
before they are eaten.
The flesh is tender.
The texture is smooth.
You said that this snakehead fish
tastes fishy when eaten raw.
I'll add some shredded ginger
and it'll remove the fishy taste.
Although ginger can remove the fishy smell,
it is spicy.
It doesn't go well with snakehead fish.
At this moment, in your mouth,
not only will you not taste any sweetness of the fish,
you will only taste the spiciness.
Impressive! Erlang.
Yes.
Beans alleviate blood circulation.
The broth removes the foul smell.
This broth,
is able to remove
the spiciness in your mouth.
The broth is hot.
It can remove the greasy fish fat,
thus the meat will be fresh and refreshing.
However, the meat of the snakehead fish is crunchy.
If the fish fat is removed,
the texture will be dry.
We need wind
to cool down the meat before we eat it.
The meat will be smooth and tender.
Only Dangyang Tavern in the South City has "not bad"
given by Baili Erlang.
Excuse me.
Please step aside.
[New wine]
Sugar figurine!
Good!
Great!
[The Inner Guard: Beidou, Li Beiqi]
It looks great!
Excellent!
[Dangyang Tavern]
Excuse me.
Step aside!
Give way!
Please step aside!
Excuse me,
is Baili Erlang here?
He's there.
There he is.
Thank you.
[Dangyang Tavern]
Baili Erlang?
Lin Zhong?
Yes, I am.
You wrote to see me?
Someone asked me and my daughter
to come all the way from Lianshan
to Luoyang.
To tip off in capital.
You are an informer?
When we reached the outskirts of the city,
we were attacked.
We were also separated from the soldiers who escorted us.
We had no other choice
but to come and see you.
If you want to blow the whistle,
you should see the empress.
Why do you want to see me?
Baili Erlang!
[Dangyang Tavern]
Go!
Don't run!
[Dangyang Tavern]
Get out of my way!
Step aside!
Great!
Let's go!
Step aside!
Give way!
Go away!
Move!
Step aside!
Protect the princess!
Yes sir!
Step aside!
Give way!
Erlang!
Are you crazy?
It's too dangerous!
Heaven's still waiting for you there!
Someone's trying to tip me off.
We can investigate it later.
Come with me!
Go!
Let's go!
Give way!
Go!
Keep him alive!
Bring him back.
Yes sir!
Here!
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Come!
[Taichu Palace]
[Xianju Hall]
[The Imperial Attendant of the Inner Guard: Wu Youjue]
Your highness.
Sorry for frightening experience, Your Highness.
Are you alright?
Thanks Imperial Attendant for the concern.
[The Crown Princess: Lady Du]
Princess was stubborn,
and insisted to visit the South City.
Sorry for troubling
the inner guards.
Your highness was being attacked.
It was all our fault.
I will punish those responsible for that.
This is just a small matter.
I believe,
you will act impartially,
and will not let empress be worried.
We definitely won't disappoint the empress.
We will give the crown princess
and the princess an explanation.
How's your chronic disease?
Is it better?
I'm fine.
Princess' trip to the South City
was supposed to be confidential.
I do not know how those murderers
got to know about it.
The inner guards are from noble families.
All of them are innocent.
No one would have blown the gaff.
The inner guards are the empress' right arms.
All these happened because of Yongchuan's stubbornness.
You should not take the blame.
Your Highness,
there are still many doubts in this incident.
Has the princess met the empress?
When I was on my way here,
the empress got to know that princess was attacked.
She was worried.
There are doubts in the assassination of the South City.
Why didn't you allow me to tell the crown princess?
What are the doubts?
Firstly,
the princess is not involved in any government affairs.
Why would someone want to kill her?
[Xianju Hall]
Secondly,
why would the murderer kill the innocents?
Thirdly,
after the murderer was caught,
why did he kill himself immediately?
The job of the inner guards
is to protect the empress,
protect the imperial clan,
and guard the capital.
[Xianju Hall]
What you've just told
are the responsibilities of the Court of Judicial Review.
You always say that the inner guards' job
is to share the burden of the empress.
If that is so,
why are you trying to
pass the buck?
Are you trying to say that I'm playing the blame game?
Yes.
You...
I've spoiled you.
Since you became an inner guard.
You always fight and kill.
I just turn a blind eye.
But don't you know where we are now?
You were such a big mouth.
I did it for your sake.
Youjue.
[The Heaven Project in Taichu Palace]
Erlang!
next time don't disappear
without a word.
If anything happens to you,
how should I explain to master?
Have you found
the pair of father and daughter who was hunted down?
The South City is being locked down now.
[The guard of Baili's mansion: Shen Fei]
For the time being,
I can't get any news.
Why do you want to know about them?
Is it something important?
Who made this Dougong?
Baili Erlang.
This is made
according to the drawing you provided.
I told you to use willow.
You used pinewood instead.
The pinewood would expand when it is damp.
It would not be able to hold
the beams of the main hall.
Rework.
But...
Baili Erlang,
we did this
as we wanted to complete the job within the time frame.
To wait for the willow to be transported to capital,
it would take more than half a month.
If we rework,
our work would be delayed.
The empress will blame us.
Let the empress blame.
Today will be my last day
calling for a roll call.
Goodbye.
But...
[Minister of Ministry of Works: Baili Yan]
Dad.
Where are you going?
I have delivered my resignation letter.
I shall leave now.
Even if you leave the Ministry of Works,
you are still my son.
You can resign.
You can stay away from home.
I know what you're thinking.
You just refuse to get married.
I'm telling you,
the marriage has been decided.
You can't run away from it.
[Chief Justice of the Court of Judicial Review: Gao Sheng]
Master Gao, after the incident,
we have locked down the South City,
and controlled the situation.
The South City is an important city in Luoyang.
We've locked it for half a day.
About 17 or 18 people
from various ministries have come to ask me.
Be quick!
Bring the body and the convict back to investigate.
The morticians of the Court of Judicial Review,
have all arrived.
The convict...
Speak!
...has been taken away by the inner guards.
The inner guards were there during the incident.
So...
The inner guards have overstepped the bounds.
Bring back the convict!
Yes sir!
[The mortician of the Court of Judicial Review: Gao Bingzhu]
Hurry up!
Morticians,
carry the body back to the Court of Judicial Review!
Come!
Let's go!
[The Inner Guards' Office]
Yuehua,
What's wrong?
the people from the Court of Judicial Review
have snatched the body and the criminal.
There was a big case today.
Working in the Court of Judicial Review
is so tiring.
But we've got more money
than what we usually get.
Let's find a place
and have a drink.
Sure! Let me drink with you.
She died at a young age.
Such a waste.
Have you heard about it?
The only captive,
have been snatched from the inner guards
by the Court of Judicial Review.
Really?
He was brought back here?
Move!
Official Chen.
This criminal is the key person
in the case of the South City.
Stay alert.
And watch him carefully.
[The Registrar of the Court of Judicial Review: Chen Que]
If anything goes wrong,
I will kill you!
Yes sir!
Official Chen.
Who are you?
Zhang Qiushi sent me here.
I'll send you to meet the master.
Thank you, my friend...
The father and the daughter are dead.
A big success is coming soon.
I'll die without any regrets.
The informers are dead.
Have you destroyed the tip-off letter?
There was no letter.
You're not one of us.
You might not have known.
I've been following you for the whole month.
In five years,
I've met 12 people
from Chunqiu Divine.
I've tried 12 different ways
of interrogation,
but they refused to spill the beans.
You are number 13.
Tell me,
who was the man who used a polearm?
Where is he now?
Who the hell are you?
Don't worry.
I stabbed you thrice,
none could kill you.
Think of dying?
Not so easy.
Take your time to think about my question.
I'll be back for you.
Master Gao.
I didn't know that you would be here late at night.
I didn't come to meet you.
I'm sorry.
The captive in the South City
was caught by the inner guards.
However, your people have snatched him away.
If I weren't the person-in-charge,
I would've thought that it was the empress' order.
He tried to assassinate the princess Yongchuan.
He is a rebel.
It is our job
to interrogating him
as soon as possible.
How could you say that we snatched him away?
I don't care
how you work.
But I need to be involved in the interrogation.
Well...
I'm afraid it's against the rule.
Do you have
the stamped official document?
No, I don't.
Then I'm unable to help you.
It's late now.
It is not an urgent matter.
We shall talk about it some other day.
Master Gao.
I just wanted to interrogate the convict.
Why do you keep stopping me?
How dare you!
The Court of Judicial Review is the head of the nine courts and five prisons,
the reference of the law.
If you are not satisfied,
you can write to the empress.
Guards!
Send the guests off!
Master Gao.
Oh no, there's a jailbreak!
Master Gao, what is this?
The Court of Judicial Review is where the prison is.
Bring along the official document
to come next time.
If this person dies at here,
I will definitely inform the empress.
In front of the empress,
I hope that you'll still be able to talk with confidence.
[The Managing Clerk of the Court of Judicial Review: Pei Jian]
Who stabbed you?
Stop the interrogation!
Keep him alive!
Send him to the doctor.
Yes sir!
Guards.
Erlang,
your uncle asked me to send you
this white fungus soup.
Have you found the informers?
Not yet.
I even asked around
but no one has seen them.
Erlang,
why did they look for you?
What did they want to tell you?
I want to know too.
[A coffin shop in South City]
The father and daughter are dead.
[The informer and his daughter]
[The victim]
I've met 12 people
from Chunqiu Divine.
You are number 13.
I've been following you for the whole month.
A big success is coming soon.
I'll die without any regrets.
She died at a young age.
Such a waste.
Have you heard about it?
The only captive,
have been snatched from the inner guards
by the Court of Judicial Review.
[The guardian from Lianshan to Luoyang: Gao Bin]
[From Lianshan to Luoyang]
Lianshan.
[The Inner Guards' Office]
Know your mistake?
What is it then?
I trespassed the Court of Judicial Review
without an official document.
You were there to investigate,
it was an official affair.
There was nothing wrong with that.
I shouldn't be rude to Master Gao.
The people from the Court of Judicial Review
wanted to snatch our convict.
Obviously, they're trying to contest for merits.
Do you think that
we inner guards are useless?
Then?
I shouldn't have gone...
The only captive in the South City
almost got killed.
This morning,
Gao Sheng sent someone to question us.
I know.
It was my fault for not protecting the convict.
It was your fault for
almost getting yourself into trouble.
If the only convict was killed,
the empress would be angry.
The reason Gao Sheng is doing this,
is to make you
take the blame,
and cause you to be killed.
To serve the empress
is the job of the inner guards.
If the empress were to blame us,
I should take the blame.
You're asking for troubles
and offending people.
These are just small matters.
I can still solve these problems for you.
If you continue to act recklessly,
how are you going to protect yourself in the palace?
What is Baili Erlang eating?
Is it delicious?
Not bad.
[Refined, good, not bad]
Not bad!
[Not bad]
-Not bad. -Not bad.
Baili Erlang says it's not bad.
Such a great compliment!
It's elating!
Congratulations!
I mean...
it's just not bad.
Baili Erlang, please stay.
I'm from Xing Jiao Fang
the barbeque shop in Yuanxing.
My boss would like to invite you to our shop
to taste our food.
The Tao family in the Little South Bridge,
is serving their first bowl of mutton soup.
Baili Erlang!
Baili...
You need to queue to invite Erlang for food tasting.
You are number 63.
He would be there soon.
Thank you, Baili Erlang.
Have a safe journey.
Congratulations!
What I talk about,
you won't listen to me.
You won't change.
Let me assign you to
an important official affair,
so that
you won't fall into other's trap.
[Letter from the informer]
The informer?
[Order for the inner guards. Take in the father and daughter from Lianshan]
A few days ago, we received an order.
A pair of father and daughter
came from Lianshan to capital to tip off.
The soldiers of Weizhou
were supposed to escort them to the inner guards.
But when Li Chun arrived at the Longmen Wharf,
he found out that the cabin of the escort team
was empty.
It has been years since the capital
has any informers.
Could it be someone who pretended to be
an informer
and lost his way on purpose?
[Lin Yan, Lin Zhong]
If you're not interested,
I'll ask someone else to go.
Baili Erlang, welcome.
[Tao's Mutton Soup Restaurant,
South City]
Baili Erlang!
what do you want to eat today?
A bowl of mutton soup, please.
Sure.
This is mutton soup.
Enjoy your meal.
Have a seat.
It's so crowded.
All the seats are taken.
Give me a bowl
of the mutton soup Baili Erlang recommends.
Sure.
I've never reviewed this shop.
Really?
I was wrong then.
Enjoy your meal.
A Qingzhou ram is fresh.
A Hezhou ewe is fragrant.
Nice to meet you. I'm Gao Bingzhu.
This is the first time
I've heard something like this.
Lianshan in Hezhou.
Have you heard of it?
I only know the copper mine in Lianshan,
which is very famous.
Lianshan mutton is also delicious.
But the mutton from Lianshan
when transported to the capital
needs to be done through water and land.
Not only that,
merchants often face the threat from bandits.
It is dangerous.
You are right.
In short, the journey from Lianshan to Luoyang
is not easy.
From the moment you sat down till now,
you have mentioned Lianshan four times,
and looked at me four times.
But you didn't realize
you've finished your soup.
You're not here for the soup.
Why do you look for me?
When the mutton arrives in Luoyang
it becomes a delicacy.
But when people arrive in Luoyang, they die.
Such a young lady.
It was her first trip here with her dad.
She didn't even get to see
the hustle and bustle of Luoyang,
and she's dead.
They're dead?
Don't you know?
How did you know that?
You've eaten at
more than 70 food stalls in Luoyang.
More than 20 are acceptable.
Only one is excellent,
which is Dangyang Tavern.
The father and daughter
don't look like
frequent visitors of Dangyang Tavern.
You did not meet by chance.
You were also there yesterday.
After they ran away,
I have not seen them since then.
How did they die?
I left my money at home.
My treat.
It's not the end yet.
We'll still see each other.
Erlang!
You're here.
The pair of father and daughter whom you asked me to investigate,
I've been investigating for the whole day
but no news about them.
They're dead.
Dead?
Let's go!
Go to the Court of Judicial Review.
Erlang, wait for me.
Depart!
Yes sir!
Yuehua,
why are you here again?
Are you worried that
I'm here to investigate
the assassination of the criminal last night?
Cases in the South City are managed by the Court of Judicial Review.
All the evidence...
The reason I'm here today,
is because the guards need cooperation from the Court of Judicial Review
to investigate the murder of the informers.
[Lin Yan, Lin Zhong]
Did you find any token or letter
on their bodies?
In reply to your question,
we only found an official document
on their bodies,
to prove that they were from Lianshan.
Did anyone touch the bodies?
[Fairness]
[Morgue]
When you moved the bodies here,
did you take any belongings
from their bodies?
Official Yuehua,
"do not take the belongings of the dead"
is the rule of our job.
Unless you want to go to the Infinite Hell when you die.
Nobody would ever do that.
Yes!
Nobody dares.
Official Pei.
The murderer who was caught in South City
has been sent to the cell to recuperate
as he was stabbed last night.
However, when I went to send food to him this morning,
I realized that
he's dead for quite some time.
He suffered three stabs,
but he survived.
And now he's dead after being sent for treatment.
Official Pei,
what a good show
the Court of Judicial Review
has put up!
That's a dirty lie!
If it weren't the instructions from the superior,
there must be traitors
in the Court of Judicial Review!
Stop talking nonsense!
He died because of serious injury.
It has nothing to do with us!
What are you still waiting for?
Whoever have entered
the cell where the murdered was held,
get all of them.
Interrogate them one by one.
-Yes sir.
I killed him.
How is it possible?
-Yes.
-Right.
How can it be you?
Gao Bingzhu.
Please don't joke.
Impossible!
Gao Bingzhu was drinking with me last night.
I've worked with him
for years.
It can't be him.
-It can't be him.
-Right.
I am Gao Bingzhu,
the mortician of the Court of Judicial Review.
That person.
I killed him.