[English subtitles are available]
[Love Under The Full Moon]
[Episode 18]
Chu Xia.
Lei Chu Xia disappeared!
She really disappeared!
It's finally over.
Xuan He,
so to you,
letting Chu Xia return to her universe
because you don't care
about her life?
To live or die
is between her
and her universe.
I'm just a human.
It's out of my hands.
Tell me if
what Lei Chu Xia said before she disappeared
is true.
Is it true?
Tell me.
Answer me.
Answer me!
Do you wish that it was true?
Qin Yue,
could you use
that brain of yours and think?
Lei Chu Xia never
belonged to this world.
I'm just putting everything
back where it belongs.
Get it?
Listen,
all that I've done
is for the both of us.
Xuan He!
I've succe...
I've succeeded.
I've succeeded!
Debug the machines.
Da Li,
Give me all the data we have.
Professor Chen...
Xiao Dong, we're ready.
Go.
Xiao Dong,
I've brought the computers over
based on what you asked in the call.
The computer has
a GPS system that's
specially developed to locate Chu Xia.
Xiao Dong,
don't be anxious.
If we could
get Chu Xia back the previous time,
we'll be able to do it again.
Yes,
thank you.
Professor Chen,
let's begin.
It'll be alright.
[Astrophysics Centre of Tongcheng University]
Okay.
Wang Yi Xin's abandoned factory
is empty now.
Even the machines are gone.
Xiao Dong,
Wang Yi Xin will definitely
bring all the parts with him.
Wang Yi Xin is still the key to
whether Chu Xia
can return safely.
I will save her.
Xiao Dong.
What's wrong with all of you?
Darling.
Xiao Rui...
No,
what happened?
Say something.
Aunt Wei Wei,
Chu Xia disappeared.
An odd phenomenon
happened on the day
of the Super Moon,
and that odd phenomenon is
Chu Xia?
I don't think that
we should worry too much now.
I believe that
the two greatest men in my life
will be able to bring Chu Xia back.
I believe that too.
It'll be great if
one day I can become
as strong as you.
I was just like you
ten years ago.
Helpless.
But I went through
a lot after that,
and understood that the
strength that adults show
is from the things that happened
and we get used to things.
The people who are there for you
when you're most frightened
and worried
are the most important ones.
Xiao Dong.
What's this?
This is a little secret
that your mother told me
when I was young.
Draw a star on your hand,
pray sincerely,
and your wish will come true.
That's too sloppy,
not logical.
There are a lot of things
that can't be explained with science.
Why would my kind sister
and brother-in-law
would pass away so soon?
Why did Xiao Dong and I
have to go through this misfortune?
But my sister said
people are just specks of dust
in this wide universe.
How many people who love each other
never got to meet anymore?
But
only love
can break through the constraints of time and space
and convey each other's yearning.
So I believe
that if we look forward with love,
Chu Xia
will return to us
once again.
Professor Chen,
this is my logic of love
that's different from science.
[Only love can break through]
[the constraints of time and space]
[and convey each other's yearning.]
Chu Xia,
wait for me.
[November 17th 2011]
Chicken offal with cow peas.
Here, the last one.
You're back.
Come and eat.
Hurry.
Dad, Mum,
I miss you so much.
What's wrong with her?
Maybe she's getting cold feet.
Or she's on a diet
and is in a bad mood.
Why would you talk bad about me in front of me...
I wouldn't dare.
say bad things about comrade junior Lei?
Eat.
You'd need to lend me two guts.
Hurry, eat.
Senior Lei, can you lend me your phone?
Where's yours?
I need to borrow yours.
Alright.
Whatever junior Lei says.
Here.
Thank you.
Are you calling Xuan He?
You have such a bad memory.
Didn't Xuan He say
that he's on a work trip
and might not pick up
unless it's important?
Lies.
Nothing.
Let's eat.
Dad, Mum,
if something happened,
and no matter what you do
you might not be able to
change the outcome,
what would you do?
Persevere of course.
How would you know it won't change
until you reach the end?
Sometimes people don't
do things to get results,
but to avoid regret.
We really are a family.
You read my mind.
I think so too.
By the way,
I picked up a
weird phone call.
A strange woman
said she was looking for
Old Fairy Lady
and said that her nephew
is running away from home.
It's just bizarre.
I hung up immediately.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
I'm going out.
What is
this child doing?
So mysterious.
I've been looking for you for half a day.
Why are you still thinking of running away from home?
Is it because your dad didn't come back
and you're afraid that he
won't keep his promise?
I'm an adult now.
I'm very independent.
I don't need him.
If you're independent,
why are you
so close to home
when you run away?
People say
when you miss someone,
you'll look up at the moon.
Do you know why?
Because the moon never changes.
When you miss someone,
the person you're missing
is probably looking at the moon too.
♫ Ah ♫
[Unable to locate Chu Xia's sub-system]
♫ Stepping on the galaxy ♫
♫ Sensing your direction ♫
♫ We look at each other from afar ♫
♫ We will meet again ♫
♫ Finger tips coursing through time ♫
♫ Touching you ♫
♫ The face under the moonlight ♫
♫ Is covered in stars ♫
♫ In just an instant ♫
♫ Secretly making a wish ♫
♫ I'm from summer and you're from winter ♫
♫ with autumn as our axis ♫
♫ Before the first leaf falls ♫
♫ Let's meet again ♫
♫ Those who have met will meet again ♫
♫ Some day ♫
♫ We won't need to worry about distance ♫
♫ Remember to look up ♫
♫ When the moon is full ♫
♫ Believe that parting is a romantic journey ♫
[November 18th 2011]
[Piggy Tech New System Press Conference, November 18th 10:00AM]
Dad, Mum,
I'm going out.
[It's 2011,]
[Three hours to Piggy Tech's Press Conference]
[November 18th,]
[The press conference for Piggy Tech]
[is starting soon.]
[A new time loop]
[will restart.]
[I need to change it.]
[Invitation]
You dropped your invitation.
Madam,
the press conference hasn't started.
You can't enter yet.
I need to talk to Wei Xuan He.
I don't know who Wei Xuan He is.
Zhao Yao Yang works too.
Mr Zhao is busy. He won't entertain guests.
Thank you.
I have something
very important.
I need to see them before
the press conference begins.
Madam,
do you have an invitation?
The thing is
you can't enter
without an invitation.
[Implicit Equity Entrustment Agreement]
[New Era of Media Technology, 2011 Piggy Tech New System Tech Conference]
Mr Wei,
the agreement has been
checked by both our lawyers.
The earnings in the future
will be taken from my
part of the share in Piggy Tech.
You can get a huge payout
without showing yourself.
Mr Wei,
why are you still hesitant
about such a beneficial deal?
You just need to give us the patent
to get so many shares.
Mr Wei,
this is a trade without any cost,
a very beneficial thing.
That's such a good opportunity.
Okay,
Mr Zhao,
This implicit equity entrustment agreement
looks good.
Mr Wei,
let's work together.
Let's work together.
Mr Wei,
I think
I'm getting some luck from you.
Ms Gu
took on
such a huge risk
all because of you.
Not only did she come up with a plan
to get the full patent,
but also distracted Xu Wei Yi
so that Piggy Tech
can have a smooth press conference.
I'm utterly
impressed with
Mr Wei's charm.
Very impressed.
I'll leave you to it then.
Okay.
Let's work together.
Come in.
Mr Wei,
someone outside called.
Ms Lei Chu Xia is looking for you.
Chu Xia?
Why is she here?
Chu Xia,
why are you at Piggy Tech's
press conference?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you angry at me
because I switched my phone off
while on a business trip?
Were you really on a business trip?
Why?
Is Madam Chu Xia losing trust
in her boyfriend
and soon-to-be husband?
Stop working with Zhao Yao Yang.
Don't steal from others
with dirty tricks.
What are you talking about?
I know everything.
The system source code that
you gave to Piggy Tech
for your cooperation with Zhao Yao Yang
was stolen from Xu Wei Yi,
isn't it?
Let's talk about this somewhere else.
Who told you
all that you said?
Don't trust in the lies.
It doesn't matter who told me.
Stop the press conference.
Don't work with Zhao Yao Yang.
This patent
is the blood and sweat of Xu Wei Yi.
By doing this,
you're pushing him over the edge.
To ask me to stop the press conference now
is pushing me over the edge.
You're finally admitting to it.
I'm doing this because
my hands are tied.
You know that
my company is barely surviving.
I can't
ask for money from my family
and I can't let my father know that
his son
is such a failure.
It's not too late to turn around.
Or else you might
bring misfortune to a lot of people.
Misfortune?
Do you know what's
the biggest misfortune?
I, Wei Xuan He,
son of Wei Guo Peng,
born to an affluent family with all eyes on me
but have no success.
With Xu Wei Yi's patent,
I can get my first pot of gold,
I can carry on with my entrepreneurship,
and I can bravely face
the criticism that people
throw at me.
If I have to stop now,
I can only beg for mercy
from my father.
I'll be turning into
a good for nothing
spoiled rich kid,
a degenerate who only disappoints my father
and shames the family?
But why
are you stealing from others?
Xu Wei Yi isn't just anyone,
he's a genius.
But this genius
just had to develop things
that are in the same direction as me.
He's the one
who's pushing me over the edge.
A genius can develop
the first revolutionary system,
and he'll be able to make the second,
third, fourth, fifth...
With his brains,
countless patents will be his
in the future.
But I
only have this one chance.
Have you changed
or have I never
really understood you?
Why am I doing this?
I'm doing this
for the both of us.
This success
will not only give you
a better future,
my father will officially
accept you.
I've rejected
the marriage arranged
by my family for you.
Was I wrong?
Chu Xia,
I'm begging you.
Don't you want to be
with me happily?
You can't build your happiness
on the suffering of others.
Xuan He,
you really shouldn't do this.
You'll ruin yourself.
I only have this one chance.
It's not like that.
You have talent and capability.
You can proudly
get achievements that only belong to you.
You don't get it.
I really only have this one chance.
I'm not as good as you imagined.
Wei Xuan He!
Anyone there?
[2012]
Mr Wei, you asked for me?
Tell the related departments
to get everything ready.
The Family First system
will be launched soon.
But Mr Wei,
the technical team said
that there are problems related to the system
that haven't been resolved.
Didn't I already
give Xu Wei Yi's source code
to them?
Do they need me
to hold their hand?
Proceed.
There's no time
for worries.
Xuan He!
Okay.
I'll get it done.
Xuan He!
You've been avoiding me for a day.
You haven't answered my question.
Xuan He,
could you answer me?
Have you been
working with Wang Yi Xin
and forcibly removing Lei Chu Xia
without caring if she lives or dies?
So...
So everything Lei Chu Xia said
was true?
You stole Xu Wei Yi,
Xu Xiao Dong's dad's patent?
You were the one who caused Lei Chu Xia
to fall off the cliff a decade ago?
I've never thought of
putting her in harm's way.
She was the one who tripped.
Xuan He,
I've always thought
that we're the same type of people.
We'll never hide our desire
when it comes to things that we set our eyes on,
and will go all out to get it.
But I was wrong.
We're nothing alike.
I will never
build my success
on the sufferings of others.
Xuan He,
was I wrong about you,
or have I never
known the real you?
[You can't build your happiness]
[on the suffering of others.]
[We're nothing alike.]
[I will never]
[build my success]
[on the sufferings of others.]
[Have you changed]
[or have I never really understood you?]
[Was I wrong about you]
[or have I never]
[known the real you?]
[Astrophysics Centre of Tongcheng University]
[415 Research Lab]
Xiao Dong,
have some breakfast and take a break.
You haven't slept a wink.
Aunt Wei Wei, the professor and the others
are all resting there.
The only way to get Chu Xia back
is to locate Wang Yi Xin as soon as possible.
[Position]
But your body won't be able to take it
if you go on like this.
Xu Xiao Dong!
What's going on? Are there...
Are there clues about Wang Yi Xin?
Not yet.
You're here, Yuan Yuan.
Qin Yue, why are you here?
Wei Xuan He and you
did this to Chu Xia.
Are you ashamed to
show up here?
I came to apologise.
I didn't know that Xuan He
had been lying to me.
And I didn't know that
Xuan He and Wang Yi Xin
set up a trap.
I almost killed Chu Xia.
I'm sorry.
Don't blame yourself.
If you didn't give
the bracelet to Chu Xia,
she would be in more danger.
Thanks, Xiao Dong.
But I have to
make amends.
How do you plan to do that?
Can you get Chu Xia back?
Wang Yi Xin is in hiding.
No one can find him,
but I have an idea on how to get him.
I can get Wang Yi Xin out
with Xuan He's name.
Who's there?
It's me.
Qin Yue,
Why are you here?
Xuan He sent me.
Where is he?
Why didn't he come instead?
He's busy.
There's something important
that he wants me to pass to you.
Open up.
Open up, Wang Yi Xin.
Wang Yi Xin,
hand over the machine.
Qin Yue,
you lied to me.
Where's the machine?
Stop. Where's the machine?
Tell us.
I can let you use the machine,
but it's broken now,
and only I can fix it.
I have my conditions.
What are your conditions?
I want to return to 415
and continue being part of the research.
Okay.
I accept that.
I won't let you off
if you
play any more tricks.
What tricks can I play?
But you
shouldn't have too much hope.
I can't guarantee
if Chu Xia will come back.
Is anyone there?
[2011]
Open the door for me.
[Piggy Tech New System New System Press Conference Sign In]
Xiao Dong,
I'm back.
Good that you remember to come back.
Aren't you on a business trip?
I will try very hard
to keep my promises to you.
Is there a bug
in this game?
I still failed when
I followed
your cheat codes.
Since the start of the invention,
the computer program
has been used on numerical calculations
and logical calculations.
But do you know
what's the future direction
of computer developments?
What is it?
It's AI.
Programs will soon
have human-like intelligence.
And it'll get better at
studying the delicate emotions
of human beings.
Does that mean
it's something like the Turing Program
[Turing Plan]
that we've been researching?
Yes, that's right.
So
when you're gaming,
don't just focus on the superficial technology
or the cheat codes
and get limited by them.
You have to trust your heart.
Follow that gut feeling
and connect with the game,
and win
in the end.
I hope that your life
works like that too.
Trust your heart
and solve each and every
problem in life.
Okay.
By the way,
some weird person was looking for you.
She asked you to contact her
once I see you.
She left her phone number with me.
But I threw it away.
I think Aunt Wei Wei picked it up.
Did she
say anything to you?
She said something about
Piggy Tech.
Piggy Tech?
Piggy Tech!
[20 minutes to Piggy Tech's press conference]
I have to go out immediately.
Also,
don't skip school today.
Alright. Adults are so long-winded.
Good.
That's a promise then.
I'll bring a cake back
tonight.
We'll have it together.
I have to go now.
Slow down.
The roads are slippery.
Can someone open the door for me please?
You again?
Thanks.
Control complexity with simplicity.
Get in touch with the future.
This is our topic
for Piggy Tech's press conference today.
Thank you.
Wait!
I'm sorry, everyone,
I need to cut in.
I'm the Chairman of
Wei Yi Tech, Xu Wei Yi.
This system that
Piggy Tech is announcing today
is the result of
diligent research
by my company for the past three years.
We've also registered for a patent.
You're plagiarising.
you must pay in the name of law.
Mr Lee.
Do you have anything to say about this?
What's going on with Piggy Tech?
Please settle down.
Listen,
here
I would like to firmly announce
that Piggy Tech
has successfully
registered our patent earlier on.
This is a patent document
that has full legal effect.
See for yourself.
That's impossible.
If we're looking into plagiarism,
we should look at you, Xu Yi Wei
for copying the results
of our development.
The one who should be paying
is you.
What is this?
Mr Xu,
our patent submission
has been rejected.
Why would that happen?
I believe that you didn't
copy or steal,
but
the evidence
is in front of you.
You heard what she said.
We need to always look at the evidence.
Mr Xu,
did you really plagiarise?
What is this?
Could you explain, Mr Xu?
Please explain what's happening.
Mr Xu.
Could you explain, Mr Xu?
-Mr Xu.
Please explain what's happening, Mr Xu.
Mr Xu.
All of these still happened.
[Patent Application Form]
October 17th 2011
was a month ago.
Wei Xuan He and Gu Xiao Qi
must have stolen the patent document.
I still missed the chance
to turn things around.
Xu Xiao Dong,
Why are you here?
Are you here to
collect a debt from my dad too?
Listen,
my dad isn't like that.
My dad
would not steal from others.
He wouldn't steal some patent.
Forget it.
You won't believe me anyway.
Xu Xiao Dong,
remember that
you should never
lose your courage to face
all your problems.
I believe that you
can face any problems
and solve them,
and embrace the light.
Furthermore,
someone is
trying their best to help you
when you can't see it.
It's not the end yet.
We can't give up yet.
We still have a chance.
Everything can be changed.
[Wei Yi Tech]
[Unscrupulous profiteer, return my hard-earned money]
[Evil businessman Xu Wei Yi, get out of Tongcheng]
Camera?
[On the day that Xu Wei Yi]
[Wei Yi Tech forced by investors for rights protection]
[was exposed for plagiarism,]
[corporations that have signed agreements with him]
[went to his office]
surrounded him and asked for reimbursement.]
I don't know him.
Yes,
that's why I want to ask you,
if you don't know him,
why were you at his office?
Here's the evidence.
[Tongcheng Daily]
You can verify it
if you don't believe me.
Pay up.
I get it now.