[English subtitles are available]
[Happiness]
Congratulations, Grand Tutor.
Chief Cabinet Minister and Her Highness are married at the same day.
The capital today is so alive.
Yes.
Free at kisskh.me
Is Her Highness's wedding
more glorious than this?
Now there is no one above the Chief Cabinet Minister except His Majesty.
For an important thing such as getting married,
he may not be less glorious than the royal family.
That's right.
We have a lot to watch today.
Sir.
If we miss the good time,
it will be difficult to respond to His Majesty.
Hyah.
Sir, you can't do this.
Your Highness.
Chief Cabinet Minister, have you thought this through?
If you insist on going inside,
you are violating the edict.
You are no difference to those treacherous ministers and traitors.
Your Highness.
I am taking you home.
[Be My Princess]
[Episode 8]
Distinguished guests,
ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the wedding ceremony of
the couple.
Now walking towards us are
our lovely flower children.
And our handsome
best men and beautiful bridesmaids group.
Today, we have so many friends here.
This is a good time
for our couples to get married.
Now,
our best men and bridesmaids group
are standing by the side of our stage.
Now,
let's invite each of our guests and friends...
-Have you noticed? -To witness
-Our skirts are immersed into -the most important moment today.
the background.
Let's
Han Xiaoya is worth her title
-Her title of "the scheming girl" -Draw all our attention to
the back of our stage
Never mind.
-Even if she did this -the door of Happiness.
-We are still the most precious background flowers. -Let's invite the main characters today.
The bride and groom appeared shiningly,
dressed in a white wedding dress.
Their hearts are together and their hands are closely held.
A new couple are walking towards us slowly.
Now, our couple
is standing on the stage.
Thank you for the blessings and applause
given by our guests here today.
The romance
is the prelude of our life.
When the marriage arrives,
bride and groom,
you will be the heroes and heroines
of this love story.
-Thank you, thank you. -Drink more.
-Thank you. -Here.
Stay healthy. Stay healthy.
You are the classmates of the bride, right?
Let me have a toast to you.
A tiring day.
Who is this?
Pass me it, right.
Xiaoya, Xiaoya.
What is the name of your classmate?
She looks attractive.
Bye.
Everyone.
thank all of you
for coming to my wedding today.
I am afraid
that you might persuade me to drink wine.
But I have an
important mission today
that I have to do first.
Ming Wei,
would you please come to the stage first?
Why?
Come on, quickly.
Come on, up here.
What is she going to do?
Why?
Wei is my best roommate
and my best friend in college.
See.
Wei is so beautiful
and with good conditions.
But do you believe
a beautiful girl like her
is still single?
No.
Xiaoya, what are you doing?
You have told me before
you have met someone unreliable, right?
But feel assured, Wei.
I will find you someone reliable now.
I will do what I have promised.
Don't do this.
Everyone here today has a benefit.
Whoever wants to chase Wei,
raise your hands.
Wei, take a look. I have told you
you should be confident.
Here.
Do you want to promote yourself to us
and fight for your happiness?
Say something!
I am not in a hurry to find a boyfriend.
I understand.
You are once bitten twice shy.
You don't trust your judgement, right?
Don't worry. I will help you.
Enough.
Everyone.
Ming Wei has strict requests
for her boyfriend.
It must be someone who will treat her sincerely
and never regret.
So,
anyone who thinks he can do it,
be sure to seize the opportunity.
Ask the waiters around you for
love stickers.
And stick them on Ming Wei.
Han Xiaoya.
This is too much!
Wei, how can you say this?
I did this for you.
Gentlemen, the more you stick,
the more connection you have with Ming Wei.
Fighting!
Come here.
Go up, up.
What are you doing? Don't come here.
Don't crowd the stage.
Move away.
What are you doing?
Let me stick. Just one, just one.
I will call the police if you do this again.
What are you doing?
Who is this?
Mu Tingzhou.
It's true.
It's Mu Tingzhou.
You mean the Best Actor is here?
Why is he here?
Your Highness, I'm late for your protection.
Are you okay?
Grand Tutor,
I'm fine.
Grand Tutor.
Grand Tutor, what are you doing? Release me quickly.
Come.
Grand Tutor. Let me down quickly.
What are you doing?
I'm afraid I cannot let you down.
Everybody.
This is the biggest surprise
I prepared for today,
inviting Mr. Mu, the Best Actor to my wedding.
Mr. Mu,
thanks for coming to congratulate me in person.
I'm a big fan of you.
And I'm a best friend of Ming Wei.
Such a evil and
mean woman
dares to claim yourself a best friend of Your Highness.
You don't deserve it.
Wei should be Mu Tingzhou's girlfriend.
I didn't imagine that he is the overbearing CEO style.
I'm turning to his fan now.
Why does everybody leave?
So irritating!
Grand Tutor, I'm in the car now.
Can you loosen me up?
Grand Tutor, I don't feel well in this condition.
I really don't feel well.
Grand Tutor, loosen me up.
Please.
According to Commandments for Women,
women should behave elegantly and calmly, guard chastity, model each act on the best usage and wear neat clothes.
As a princess,
you are belittling yourself regardless of your reputation.
This really makes me sad.
Well, what?
How... how did I neglect my reputation?
How did I belittle myself?
You expose too much skin, Your Highness.
This is not what a nice lady should do.
Xiao Zhao.
Be a judge here.
Am I exposing too much skin?
Xiao Zhao is an outsider.
How can you be so frivolous?
Say something, Xiao Zhao.
I'm not frivolous, am I?
How am I frivolous?
Calm down, you two.
Please tolerate it, Your Highness.
Don't rush to break this.
We can talk after
we settle down and have a seat.
OK?
Don't spy.
What are you doing? I'm driving.
Are you okay, Your Highness?
No, not okay.
Xiaoya, Xiaoya.
Don't cry, Xiaoya.
It's okay.
-Alright, alright. -Honey.
Don't cry.
There, there.
There, there. Don't cry.
Our whole wedding is ruined by Ming Wei.
Don't cry.
Alright. Don't be mad.
Look.
Ming Wei and Mu Tingzhou are on the news.
This.
Alright. Alright.
Don't take it seriously.
[#Newbie Ming Wei netted the Best Actor#]
The Best Actor Mu Tingzhou
took a bridesmaid in front of the crowd.
[Princess]
Bridesmaid.
[#Profile of the Best Actor's Suspected Girlfriend#]
Look, look.
[You are my princess.]
Who is this woman?
I heard that she is the heroine of the new play of the Best Actor.
Don't tell me that!
Hurry up and give me the solution.
This way.
Prepare the documents for me first.
If anyone starts to expose info of Ming Wei on the official account,
control the situation immediately.
If anyone dares to guide the public opinion,
inform me immediately, understand?
OK.
After we reach a conclusion through discussion,
we will definitely give the media a reply.
OK.
Thank you, Mr. Zhao.
Sorry for the trouble.
OK.
Everything is supposed to be done
according to the planned schedule.
The press briefing will be held tomorrow for the official announcement.
Why did such a thing happen?
Why didn't you stop Tingzhou?
I couldn't.
I could neither persuade him, nor defeat him.
My career
almost collapsed
in the past week.
This is a shock, ok?
Hello, honey.
Right, right, right.
It's so urgent.
That's why I'm asking you
to suppress this immediately.
Hello.
You misunderstood, dad.
Mu Tingzhou is not my boyfriend.
Delete as many as those documents possible.
Well, it's a small issue.
I just saw it.
Wait a minute.
And the news of Tingzhou.
OK. OK. I owe you. I owe you.
I will treat you dinner, honey.
Yes, yes. Delete it. Delete it.
What Princess and Grand Tutor?
He just thinks you are beautiful
and pretends it to pester you.
Wei.
I understand your concern,
but...
I seriously doubt that his intention is ill.
No, dad.
He was gentle
before he lost his memory.
And now he kneels down for me frequently.
You say it,
what normal people do that?
I bet he never did that to his parents.
Wei, listen to me.
Don't get involved in this.
Wei,
or we can quit acting, ok?
Mom,
I like acting.
I think
it is more interesting than translation.
Alright.
Just be careful.
Don't worry about us.
Dad, mom,
don't worry.
The agency
will handle it for me.
I will definitely protect myself.
I will go back and visit you
after this period.
Don't worry.
Are you worried that
her biological father will see it?
No matter what happens,
four members of our family
will be together forever.
I will always protect you three.
Ming Qiang.
I'm still worried.
What if we go to visit Wei?
I really worry that she will be harmed,
since she just became an actress for a short time.
Don't worry.
I will handle this.
Please have some tea, Your Highness.
Thank you.
Your Highness,
I have made some mistakes.
What are your mistakes?
I didn't protect you well
and let you be harassed by those
I should have sent them to prison.
But I think,
the clothes Your Highness wore at that time
was destructive to the morals
and not proper.
The late Emperor assigned me as your tutor,
and I think I have the responsibility to guide and teach you.
I think
I'm not wrong on this point.
Grand Tutor,
my thoughts are contrary to yours.
You fought for me
when others harassed me.
I was quite moved.
You did nothing wrong.
But
about the clothes,
I think
you don't really know modern clothes.
These are clothes for modern ladies.
And mine is
just normal.
You are a princess, Your Highness.
How could you compare yourself with ordinary ladies?
There are principles for a princess.
Grand Tutor,
look at this.
You keep persuading me
not to expose my body.
But people from all over the country has
seen this picture of yours.
Don't you
need to watch out of your own reputation?
Or
men from the past
can show their bodies to the public and
let other people watch.
Actually,
you have a good body
that is better than many other models.
Your Highness, please be careful with your words.
I am just your minister and you are Your Highness.
We should not be mentioned in the same breath.
Grand Tutor,
you really have a double standard.
If we need to follow the etiquette of the past,
I am not allowed to show myself to the public.
If we follow your logic,
why would you want to be my assistant?
Would it be better to
send me to The Forbidden City,
and let a couple of palace maids and eunuchs to take care of me?
It is not because I do not want to,
it's me being useless.
I cannot change the lustrous and dazzling reality;
cannot give the honor of Your Highness back or
provide Your Highness a carefree and lighthearted life.
The only thing I can do is
to stand by your side
and to protect you for whole life.
Grand Tutor,
if you really want to stay by my side and protect me,
you need to learn to
adapt to this world.
Otherwise,
how could you keep your promise?
I just saw Ms. Shen and Xiao Zhao
have got extra work to do because of the mistakes we made.
It makes me feel guilty.
I don't know what you are thinking.
No matter what,
I feel that
in order for us to
cooperate continuously,
we have to make some rules.
You are not in the mood?
I cannot be happy about anything.
It looks like you are confused from what happened today.
Ms. Shen,
I was just a outsider when I
heard the scandals
and fake news
of the celebrities.
I never thought
that this kind of things would have fallen upon my head.
I am really muddled.
You need to get used to it.
I want to be a actress who has good acting skills
and who is brilliant at acting,
not only a celebrity with scandals.
More slanders you have suffered from,
more praises you are worthy of.
Since you cannot avoid it,
you would need to consider it as a test.
It's press conference tomorrow,
buck up!
Alright.
Okay, I know.
See you at the conference tomorrow.
Have a early rest.
Thanks for all the work.
What are you thinking?
I am thinking
why I am here in this world.
In this world,
I am always the trouble.
I cannot do the things I want to do, and I
cannot protect the people
I want to protect.
First of all,
no more getting down on your knees.
It is not allowed at anytime.
Secondarily,
you can talk to me
and we can discuss in a calm mood
when you think
I am wrong.
But,
I have the authority to
take charge of my own behaviors.
You cannot force me to do anything
when there is no result of the discussion,
including what kind of clothes I wear.
It's fine if you don't agree,
then we will only mind our own businesses.
Your Highness.
You have agreed?
I agree,
but Your Highness, please also keep your promises that
you must tell me first
no matter what you are
planning on doing.
Alright, let's meet each other halfway.
Besides these two points,
what else do you need me to do, Your Highness?
Grand Tutor,
I know you think of me
as the princess.
But,
between the sexes there should be a prudent reserve.
From now on,
you need to act cold against me,
do not talk to me if you don't need to,
no body contact either.
Otherwise,
we are unable to give a convincing explanation if other people see us.
In your opinion,
am I
unreasonable?
Yes.
But you don't listen to reasons because
your thinking is from the past times and
it is incompatible with the modern world.
Tingzhou.
I have to call you Tingzhou.
Even though you don't recognize it,
I still want to tell you that
you are ill actually.
You are not physcially ill
but psychologically.
No matter you are Mu Yun or Mu Tingzhou,
you are my brother.
No matter where you came from,
and where will you be in the future,
I will always be by your side.
Don't over think,
and relax.
Steward Xiao,
you are a person of loyalty and righteousness.
If there is an opportunity,
I would deliver a piece of advice to His Majesty and
offer you a general post and confer a title of nobility.
Alright.
Thank you, Grand Tutor.
[Weibo]
Hello, everyone.
I am actress Ming Wei.
Grand Chief Cabinet Minister
is the first TV series I am in.
It's my honor to
cooperate with Mr. Mu
and other seniors.
I am deeply sorry
by knowing the situation of Mr. Mu's illness,
the only thing I can do
is to cooperate with his treatment following doctor's notes.
Here I promise,
I will respect him always
no matter
he is the best actor or Grand Tutor.
Please help to maintain
a good public opinion environment.
Hope Mr. Mu will recover his memories soon and
come up with more excellent works.
First of all,
I need to thank media and the public on behalf of Tingzhou
[I suddenly feel that the setting is romantic, looking forward to see what happens next.]
for all the good care he has received.
[This is an official announcement?]
[I have to say that it is so handsome of Grand Tutor to save the beauty at the wedding scene.]
During this period of time,
[Can someone tell me what happened?]
we are touched by
all the good wishes.
Now, I need to give my special thanks to Ming Wei.
Tingzhou thinks of himself as the Grand Tutor.
Many thoughts of his
are antiquated idea of the past times,
including the video yesterday.
[Wake up, husband, I am your real princess.]
It is because Tingzhou thought it is inappropriate for the
[Please be alright soon.]
princess to wear that gown,
[How lucky Ming Wei is, I am so jealous.]
so he took her away from the sight and caused
the chaos at the scene.
It sounds ridiculous.
Tingzhou became like this,
and Ming Wei's life and work
are affected.
We apologize here
and also give thanks to Ming Wei.
We hope everyone who likes Tingzhou can
support Ming Wei more,
and do not give her the pressure
of public opinions.
What is it?
I want to speak to my media friends that
Tingzhou is a public figure
[Oh my God, this is going to be an official announcement? Be my princess?]
who receives attentions
that is one of the obligations
coming from his acting career.
If everything is normal with Tingzhou....
It's not a surprise that she stopped badgering,
I thought she was innocent,
it turned out that she got her hands on Mu Tingzhou.
Please give Tingzhou some privacy and
some time to recover.
You are better than her.
If Tingzhou's condition is deteriorated because
he is pushed too hard from some media.
We will appeal to the law
and there must be accountability.
[Follow, Ming Wei.]
Your Highness,
no matter how cruel
the outside world is,
I will try my best to protect you,
maintain your noble status and
make you carefree and lighthearted.
Sir.
let's go.
You dress so formally.
Are you attending a red-carpet event?
We are going to the Princess Palace.
Let's go.
Your Highness, please enjoy the meal.
Why do I feel a bit dizzy,
being spoiled like this?
You are a great entertainment agent.
But you are forced to work like an actor.
It must be tough for you.
Thank you for your understanding. I'm getting used to it.
Come and join me, guys.
In order to respect Your Highness,
we can only eat
after Your Highness have finished your meal.
Your Highness,
please enjoy.
Grand Tutor,
I have told you
that all humans are equal in the modern society.
We can all eat and talk
at the same table.
No, we cannot.
This is the first time I've seen an alive ancient man.
My goodness.
Fine.
I've got plenty of time today.
If you don't eat, then I won't eat.
Your Highness,
please be reasonable.
We have different statuses.
Let's eat.
Come on.
Dig in.
Your Highness first.
Let's eat.
Have some soup, Grand Tutor.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Have some.
Sister, I'm done.
I have some things to do at school. I have to go now.
Thanks for the meal.
Grand Tutor.
See you.
Bye, Sister.
Be careful on the road. Bye.
Your Highness, allow me please.
I will just put them in the sink.
Ming Wei,
just leave them there.
Let him do it.
Bye the way,
what are you going to wear
for your training class?
I
will just wear a jacket
and put on a pair of jeans.
No.
You two have just announced your relations.
The reporters are gonna pay close attention to you
over the next few days.
If an actress shows bad taste in clothes,
it could be bad publicity.
If you don't mind,
can I
take a look at your wardrobe?
Yes, sure.
No, you cannot.
Grand Tutor,
Xiao Zhao is just helping me put together an outfit.
Don't worry.
I will sort out my closet first
to make sure all things are appropriate.
A consort kin is not allowed
to be in Your Highness's bedroom.
Please bring your clothes out here, Your Highness.
Steward Xiao.
I...
Are these all of your clothes?
Grand Tutor. Uh...
Your Highness, please choose whatever you like.
I have brought enough cash.
Grand Tutor, this isn't appropriate, is it?
This...
this is so lavish.
Just treat it as your life experience.
My life experience?
This is the life experience
of the heroine in a Korean drama, right?
Don't you know his personalities?
It's better for you to pick your own clothes
than let him choose randomly.
The latter will cost more money.
Your Highness.
After you.
Welcome to our store.
Please come inside.
Your Highness.
After you.
Go ahead.
All of them are so pretty.
I don't know which pair to choose.
[Bank Card]
Excuse me, are you Ming Wei?
Sorry.
You've mistaken me for someone else.
You are Ming Wei.
I like you so much.
I'm a fan of yours.
Can I have your autograph, please?
Do you really like Ming Wei?
Yes, of course.
I've been following you on Weibo
since you were a Han costume model.
You really are
my favorite actress.
I will sign for you.
Sh!
Thank you, Princess Ming Wei.
Who dares
to approach Her Highness in broad daylight?