[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 3]
♫ The window curtain covered
one side of your face ♫
Two feet four.
I can't tell
you have such a good figure.
You usually dress casually.
♫ I'm watching you smiling nearby ♫
Those clothes
cover your good figure.
♫ The sunset clouds reddened my face ♫
Leave it to me.
I'll help you get a makeover.
♫ I breathe fast,
and my heart beats fast ♫
♫ Telepathy across the coastline ♫
♫ Time through Greenwich ♫
♫ I'll be the postman
and deliver the galaxy to you ♫
Try it on.
So many.
♫ Perfect love ♫
Is it many?
♫ The tipsy air feels like youth ♫
♫ Falling in love ♫
This...
♫ Carefully planning
the romantic plot ♫
This...
Hurry up.
♫ I overcame gravity ♫
All right then.
Go for it.
♫ Slowly flying towards the sky ♫
♫ The center of gravity became
the trace that attracted me ♫
♫ Even if the galaxy listens ♫
♫ There are traces of me loving you ♫
♫ Love surrounded you in circles ♫
♫ Looking for a planet ♫
♫ And I'll name it for you ♫
♫ Entangling you through
the gap of time and space ♫
♫ Projection under clear sky ♫
♫ Letting love fall slowly ♫
♫ Piercing through the night sky
and packing it in your eyes ♫
I think these dresses aren't ours.
This gentleman just asked me
to buy these dresses for you.
Thank you for
helping me so much.
Well.
I'll bring you to change
your
hairstyle.
Hello. Your hair is pretty long.
Here.
I'll trim here for you.
I think the top can also be trimmed.
Let's thin out the hair.
And I think your bangs
should be trimmed.
I'm not doing this.
Liu Ruo Chen.
Please.
Get a haircut.
You'll look cool
after this.
Please.
I beg you.
Good boy.
Lu Fan Fan.
Can you give me the glasses?
I can't see clearly.
I'll give this to you.
Just use it from now on.
Young Master.
I'll pick you up at three o'clock.
Master asked you to attend
the birthday party of Ren's daughter
at six o'clock.
I'm not
going for that.
[A Brief History of Time]
Is there anything important?
I'll learn how to drive in the evening.
Uncle Li.
You may stop here.
We're not there yet.
It's okay.
I can walk till there.
All right.
Then I'll stop here.
Goodbye, Uncle Li.
I don't believe in love anymore.
Mom.
I'm in love again.
How cool.
How handsome.
He's so cute.
He looks cute when smiling.
Let me see what you took.
Qin Yang.
What are you reading?
May I have a look?
[Wormholes and Time Travel]
This book may be too dull for you.
Qin Yang.
The solution you said last time
was very good.
Can you teach me?
Sure.
Qin Yang.
Are you free tonight?
Let's have dinner together.
I may not
be free tonight.
How about this weekend?
Let's go for a picnic this weekend.
That's it.
I'm going riding this weekend.
What about next week?
Yi Xiao.
Qin Yang is so amazing.
He's good-looking.
He has good grades.
He can do both riding and shooting.
If I could marry him,
our children would be brilliant.
You're thinking too far.
Is he that good?
Oh, right.
You said
he wooed you before.
You didn't agree.
What a waste.
Give it to me if you don't want it.
Wait a second.
He's so good-looking.
Gosh.
Our assistant is so handsome.
He's as good-looking as Qin Yang.
Two handsome men are in our class.
I feel so happy.
I promise I won't skip class again.
Let me introduce him.
He's your senior, second-year
post-graduate of the Faculty of Law.
Liu Ruo Chen.
He'll be
the teaching assistant this semester.
Please give a round of applause.
All right. Keep quiet.
Class will begin soon.
Ruo Chen.
Sit at the back first.
Okay.
What have you done this summer break?
I barely recognize you.
I also barely recognize myself.
Even the campus queen
Zhu Yi Xiao noticed you.
I ship them.
They look cute together.
They're killing me.
[Who's that? How handsome.]
[He's a perfect match with
the college hunk Qin Yang.]
[I'm going to ship them.]
[Where are they?]
[I'm coming over.]
[Really handsome]
[Classroom 305 on the first floor.
Hurry up.]
[I'm drooling]
[I'm so in love, love to the end]
[My heartthrob, too handsome]
[I'm going to fall in love... Haha]
[They're really cool.]
[How cool, like Korean celebrities]
[How good-looking.]
[Anyone wants to
see handsome boys together?]
What's going on?
Get your hand off me.
Well, no.
I mean,
you always dress like an old man.
Why did you dress up properly today?
Tell me the truth.
I did it for my future girlfriend.
Do you believe it?
Future girlfriend?
I won't believe it.
Will girls like you?
No.
I mean,
are you interested in girls?
I'm not you.
You're only interested
in physics questions.
Study well.
I haven't met a girl who understands me.
[What a familiar street.]
[Zhanqiao Bookstore]
He's not here.
You've mistaken him.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
This...
I saw it first.
Do you like Qian Ming Yue?
Yes.
I've liked him since his debut.
It's his new album.
And then?
I saw it first.
You don't pay yet.
It's not yours.
Double.
I'll pay double.
No way.
Triple.
Sir.
I can't afford more.
Please.
I'm his superfan.
I really want this album.
Please give it to me.
You'll be rewarded.
Cut the crap.
Don't you have one hundred yuan?
Come on. Take it out.
Do you want to get beaten?
Hurry up. Don't waste our time.
Little girls.
Do you know
it's wrong to bully your classmate?
Who are you?
You bully others at such a young age.
It's not good when you grow up.
Old lady.
It's none of your business.
[How dare you call me an old lady.]
[I must teach you a lesson today.]
[And you'll know who I am.]
Yu Xiao Yue.
Who are you?
Why do you know my name?
I'm Fan Fan.
Xiao Yue.
Do you know what you're doing?
Who do you think you are?
You're in no position to bother me.
Let's go.
Xiao Yue.
This is for your sake.
Mind your own business.
Silly Lady.
Xiao Yue.
Boss. Bill, please.
Okay.
Total
eighty yuan.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Take care.
Are you all full?
You know what we're going to do.
What do you mean?
It costs at least 70 or 80.
Do you have money?
No.
I don't have either.
Listen to my order later.
When I say run,
let's rush out.
Are we not going to pay?
It's not good.
Why not?
They earn a lot.
It's okay
even if they get less payment.
Girls.
Is there any problem with the food today?
So, he didn't come today.
He stood us up all the time.
Run!
Hey.
You didn't pay and yet hit my wife.
I have no money.
No money?
Call your parents.
I have no family.
You!
Xiao Yue.
She's my friend.
I'll go after her.
What's going on?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
My arm was hit.
Yu Xiao Yue.
What's wrong with you?
Silly Lady.
Don't care about me.
If you don't say it,
I'll keep following you.
It's been years
since someone cared about me.
Who are you?
I'm your friend.
I have no friends.
And I don't need them.
Stay away from me.
[You protect me in 2024.]
[In 2012,]
[let me protect you.]
[Why was Xiao Yue]
[like this in 2012?]
I found a way for you.
Although there's not much money,
it's enough for your mom's hospital fees.
[Forget it.]
[I can't understand it now, anyway.]
[Oh, right.]
Liu Ruo Chen
should have
become popular
at college
after getting a makeover.
Great.
Go for it, Faculty of Law!
Keep it up!
Go for it!
What a familiar smell.
Cheer up!
Assistant Liu!
I haven't had it
ever since junior high school.
Luckily,
I got the last box.
My rice balls.
I'm sorry.
How much is this? I'll pay you.
It's all right.
Well.
I'm sorry.
[2024]
Hello.
Hello, is Miss Lu speaking?
I'm Qin.
I'd like to order a nutritious meal
for tomorrow.
Okay.
Wait a second.
You may go on.
Please make it effective
for one with an eating disorder.
Eating disorder?
[Yes.]
[I'll send you the address later.]
[Well, see you tomorrow.]
Okay.
I asked her out for you.
Tomorrow,
seize the opportunity.
Will it work?
She can't remember anything now.
But maybe
you can recall her memories.
I'll give it a try.
[Hai Tian Center]
Nice to meet you.
I'm Qin Yang.
I'm Lu Fan Fan.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm sorry.
There's a traffic jam on the way.
It's okay.
It's worth
the wait.
You arrived a little late.
But we meet again.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
By the way,
we didn't talk about it earlier.
So, I prepared
some more effective lunches.
When you're free,
tell me about your conditions.
I'll adjust it for you accordingly.
I don't have
an eating disorder.
Well.
Please follow me.
Miss Lu.
Please have a rest here.
Help yourself.
Puppy.
Why are you here?
Are you hungry?
It's called Pikachu.
Mr. Liu.
Aren't you going too far?
You fed my food to the dog before.
Yet now,
you asked someone to find me.
What do you want?
I run such a big law firm.
Why would I make such a joke with you?
Look.
This is the picture we took
on the wishing boat in 2012.
I don't know
how you got the picture.
But if you keep on bothering me,
I'll sue you for harassment.
Don't be mad, Fan Fan.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I just came to deliver meals.
Please enjoy the meal.
Thank you.
[2012]
Cheer up, Assistant Liu.
The Faculty of Law and Faculty
of Economics are playing basketball.
There are many handsome boys. Come on.
Is it too late to go now?
No. Hurry up.
The Faculty of Law?
Could it be
Liu Ruo Chen playing basketball?
Come on!
Cheer up!
Keep it up, Faculty of Economics!
Go for it!
Block him.
How cool.
Liu Ruo Chen is so cool.
Who is she?
How dare she call Assistant Liu
by his name?
Yes.
Why did she call him so?
Ridiculous.
Run, run.
Block him.
Cheer up!
Watch out for the rebound.
Assistant Liu.
Assistant Liu, drink some water.
Take mine.
Have some water.
I bought it specially for you.
Assistant Liu.
Take mine.
Please have some water.
Assistant Liu.
Gosh.
Why did he drink her water?
Who's that?
Why would he drink her water?
Zhu Yi Xiao was rejected.
That's right.
It doesn't matter
if she's rich and good-looking.
She was still being turned down.
[178 Average Benz]
[Hello, Yi Xiao.]
What's the matter?
[I'm outside your college.]
[I want to ask if your class is over.]
Did you come to my college?
[Yes.]
[I'm at the gate.]
Come in then.
I'm at the basketball court.
[Okay.]
Yi Xiao.
Is that your boyfriend?
No.
I haven't agreed yet.
Did you purposely come to see me?
I didn't.
I just happened to pass by.
That was my student.
I didn't ask you about it.
I just think that
it's not good.
Well.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
How about this?
Let me treat you to ice cream
and bring you around.
♫ When everything stops ♫
As an apology.
♫ Only time goes by ♫
Is it okay?
♫ Repeating day by day ♫
♫ Until I met you ♫
Mom.
I cut some fruits for you.
Come on.
Have some fruits.
Are you sleepy?
If you're not sleepy,
talk to me.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Well.
There are many things
I can't remember recently.
For instance,
Mr. Liu said
he's my boyfriend.
But I don't remember him at all.
I also think
Mr. Liu looks familiar.
As you know,
I won't interfere much
in your relationship.
So
if there are any doubts,
you should ask clearly.
Don't avoid it.
Okay.
Liu Ruo Chen.
Fan Fan.
Put your clothes on.
I've put it on.
I thought you wouldn't come to me again.
Don't think too much.
I just want to
talk about
our relationship.
If I mean a lot to you
as you mentioned,
why do I have no impression of you?
You don't remember me at all?
Yes.
But I only remember
that you're Mr. Liu
I've seen on television.
That's all.
Apart from television,
do you have the impression
of other places?
Oh, right.
It's the wishing card
on the wishing boat.
It's our token of love
and my promise to you.
Among all things in the world,
[You're the most special one for me]
you're the most special one for me.
Yes.
It's the wish we made together.
How?
Did you recall it?
I have no idea.
And
it's not like my style.
Twelve years.
I've been waiting for this and
those words for twelve years.
How could you even forget it?
It was our promise.
Maybe
it's not me
who made the promise.
I shouldn't come here.
Mr. Liu.
Take it back.
[You're the most special one for me]
Fan Fan!
Fan Fan.
Are you okay?
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
[August 12,]
[2012.]
[It's another morning without any hope.]
[I filled the paper]
[with musical notes.]
[What has been put together]
[is just a piece of aimless music.]
[They hopped and spoke]
[the voice of my heart]
[as if they were alive.]
♫ I'm looking forward ♫
♫ To our Wednesday date♫
[Xiao Yue.]
[My dear sister.]
♫ Catching ♫
[It's been ten years.]
[I've been looking for you.]
♫ The last movie together with you ♫
[But I couldn't find you.]
♫ I'm afraid that I'm overthinking it ♫
[Where exactly are you?]
[How are you doing?]
♫ I'm hesitating about my last move ♫
♫ Remembering your name ♫
Xiao Yue.
Let me play a song for you.
Okay.
♫ Catching ♫
♫ The last movie together with you ♫
♫ I'm afraid that I'm overthinking it ♫
♫ I'm hesitating about my last move ♫
♫ Remembering your name ♫
♫ The ending of the story was light ♫
[I wish I could see you again.]
♫ I have zero luck today ♫
[I wish we could]
[still be as simple]
♫ The weather forecast last night
foresaw a sunny morning ♫
[and happy]
[as we were young.]
♫ But it's drizzling within my heart ♫
♫ I cannot resonate with you ♫
♫ I heard your voice all of a sudden ♫
♫ Why do you sound
as cold as a cloudy day? ♫
♫ I have the same longing ♫
[I wish I could meet you again]
♫ For you today ♫
[and play a wonderful melody.]