[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 5]
[2024]
♫ Love can be ♫
♫ Hurting sometimes ♫
♫ Healing every wound ♫
♫ But for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to be brave ♫
♫ Taking the risk,
no matter what they say ♫
Did we come here often?
Yes.
Once,
I lost you at the aquarium.
♫ When you gets hurt ♫
What happened then?
Did you find me?
♫ Please think of the old memories ♫
I found you.
Since then,
I've told myself
♫ When you feel lonely ♫
not to ever lose you again.
♫ Please think of my whispers ♫
I see
many had happened between us.
♫ Whenever your dream
is falling apart ♫
It's a shame that I don't remember any.
It doesn't matter.
Even if you don't remember me,
♫ I will be on my way ♫
I will always be with you.
♫ To ignite the fire of hope ♫
I will always be there to protect you
and never leave you again.
If you keep quiet, I'll take it as okay.
Lipstick.
Why?
I have use for it.
You won't get mad, will you?
♫ The window curtain
covered one side of your face ♫
♫ I'm watching you smiling nearby ♫
Let's make a stamp
as a promise.
♫ The sunset clouds reddened my face ♫
♫ I breathe fast,
and my heart beats fast ♫
Fan Fan.
♫ Telepathy across the coastline ♫
Let's start over.
I
♫ Time through Greenwich ♫
[2012]
♫ I'll be the postman
and deliver the galaxy to you ♫
♫ Perfect love ♫
♫ The tipsy air feels like youth ♫
♫ Falling in love ♫
Please help me get the key.
♫ Carefully planning the romantic plot ♫
Can't you get it yourself?
What do you think of this room?
I think it's good.
I'll take this room.
So
I'll leave your things here.
You can start unpacking.
I'll wait for you outside.
I see you are asleep,
so I put a blanket over you.
Let me get it.
Zhu Yi Xiao.
Why are you here?
I got your address from our classmates.
Can I come in?
You
I didn't expect
things to progress so fast.
Am I disturbing?
It's not what you think.
Come in and talk.
Thanks.
So,
what can I do for you?
My mom's hospital bills
is costing me a lot of money.
And you know
my family's situation.
I can't afford the medical bills.
So,
can you help me?
I'll pay you back very soon.
I have found a part-time job,
and I'll do it whenever I have the time.
Why are you looking at me?
What do you think?
Of course you will have to help.
How much do you need?
RMB 7,000.
Okay.
Give me a minute.
Don't worry, your mom will be fine.
Well, actually
we're quite similar.
When I was 13,
something happened at home,
and after that,
I had to pay for my mom's medical bills
and worked hard to live on
at the same time.
So, I understand you.
So you too
Don't worry,
everything will get better.
Here's RMB 10,000.
For your mom's medical expenses
and get her some supplements
to boost her health.
Thank you.
I will pay it back as soon as possible.
No hurry.
Pay it when you have it.
And thank you too
for sharing your story with me.
I'll leave now then.
Sorry for bothering you.
Thank you.
Take care.
Safe journey.
Will do.
Your good-heartedness will be rewarded.
I'll go to bed first.
Good night.
[Unity of Knowledge and Action]
Excuse me.
You student card please.
Sir.
I forgot my student card.
Can you let me go just this time?
It's the rule.
Sir.
I know,
but we have final exams
this week,
and I kept thinking about
which book to borrow
and what to study,
I was in a hurry, and I left it.
Can you let me go just this one time?
Fine.
Get in.
Remember to bring it the next time.
Thank you.
Rice ball.
Aren't you the one who stepped on
my rice ball?
Haven't I apologized to you the last time?
Perfect timing.
Let's start over.
I am Qin Yang,
I'm the best friend of Liu Ruo Chen.
You must be
the one that Ruo Chen spoke of,
the girlfriend from the future.
Lu Fan Fan.
Nice to meet you.
But,
do you really believe that
I'm from the future?
Time travel is not impossible.
When the space is warped
by the force of gravity,
time will also fly pass at different speed
due to the huge gravitational force.
When the black hole
and white hole are connected,
if the entrance to the black hole
and white hole
overlaps within a small range
and you jump through it,
you will find that
you have skipped the passage of time.
This is what we called time shift.
It's so complicated.
I don't understand.
But,
it sounds cool.
Have a sit.
So,
can you tell me
how to get back to where I came from?
This, I don't know.
In today's science,
only the parallel space theory
supports the time shift phenomenon.
It's just that
these have not been proven.
I can prove it.
I really came from year 2024.
Well then,
how does 2024 look like?
Much more fun than now.
There are VR games,
livestream videos,
artificial intelligence
and driverless cars.
Even software can identify its owner
based on just the iris.
Car theft will never happen.
That convenient?
But
there are pros and cons.
If your personal information is stolen,
right on the next day,
your bank card,
ID card,
personal privacy,
will all be made public,
and you'll make the headlines.
Your 2024
is hard to imagine.
Do you not believe me?
No, no.
It's just that the world you mentioned
is too perfect.
I'm looking forward to it.
So,
if I can find a way back,
I will definitely look for the future you
in 2024,
and then prove it to you.
It's a promise.
Oh, by the way,
this thing here,
is it yours?
Why do you have it?
I've been looking for it for a long time.
I found it at the basketball court
the other day.
Now
it's returned to its owner.
Thank you.
[An Ren Hospital
Hospital Payment]
It's me.
Don't scream!
What are you doing here?
This is the hospital.
Have you paid all the hospital bills?
Is there any more?
I have no money.
I am completely broke now.
Show it to me.
Isn't this money?
I borrowed this.
This is for mom's medical bills.
Go and borrow more.
I need it for emergency.
I've promised him that
these will be used
to buy supplements for mom.
My lovely daughter.
Not bad.
Have you found another boyfriend?
He treats you well.
He even gives you money for supplements.
Who will like someone like me?
Why doesn't he like you?
My daughter is so pretty.
He has a girlfriend
and I don't want to
ruin their relationship.
My lovely daughter.
Tell me,
is he rich?
No.
And I will never
borrow money from him again.
Stop lying.
I watched you grow up.
Let me tell you,
as long as he is rich,
you have to get him!
As for that girlfriend,
leave her to me.
It won't be that easy.
Looks colorful, aromatic and flavorful.
Of course.
I am a famous top notch nutritionist.
Can you cook every day from now on?
What's so hard about cooking?
I'm talking about every day.
Make sure there is no leftover today.
Finished everything.
Okay!
Bon appetit!
It's delicious!
It's really good!
Liu Ruo Chen.
Are you drunk?
I'm just
a little sleepy.
Let me take a nap.
Liu Ruo Chen.
You
Walk properly.
Don't drink so much if you can't drink.
Such a light drinker.
Liu Ruo Chen!
You liar!
You're just pretending to be drunk.
No, I am really drunk.
Continue to be drunk then.
Fan Fan.
I'm really drunk.
[I wanted to confess to her
by pretending to be drunk.]
[Such a failure.]
[2024]
[This world here,]
[is this really the world I exist in?]
[What happened when I was in a coma?]
You are really here.
Why are you here?
Isn't there a meteor shower today?
Auntie told me,
you're here waiting for shooting stars.
There's shooting stars!
Quick, make a wish.
You're done? That's fast.
Shooting stars can't realise my wish.
What do you mean?
I just hope
the wish you just made has me in it.
What a shame,
every time there's shooting stars,
it doesn't last long.
There's not enough time for more wishes.
Do you want to see shooting stars again?
Do you think shooting stars belong to you
and that you get to see it
whenever you want?
You are not Doraemon.
Who knows?
Close your eyes.
Doraemon and me
will make your dream shine.
Quick, make a wish.
I hope
the people around me
will be safe,
healthy
and happy forever.
It's a bit different from shooting stars,
but it's still beautiful, isn't it?
It's really beautiful.
Thank you.
Thank you for today.
Don't mention it.
How did this happen?
Don't worry.
Don't be afraid.
I'll call the police right away.
Did I offend anyone?
[He's now targeting Fan Fan.]
Don't overthink.
Let the police handle it.
You can't stay here tonight.
Come to my place.
For your safety,
not just tonight.
If you nothing important to do these days,
stay at my place and don't go anywhere.
But
At your place?
Won't it be inconvenient?
Safety is most important.
I want to lodge a police report.
[2012]
Zhu Guo Feng.
Come here.
When will you pay up?
In four days.
When?
Four days.
Say it again!
Four days!
It's broken!
Three days, right?
Three days!
Right?
It's broken!
Three days.
Brother!
I'll pay up in three days for sure!
Three days!
Don't hit me!
Brother Feng.
It's me.
Get up.
You scared me!
Brother Feng.
I saw debt collectors
at the door just now.
This time they are for real.
I can see that.
Alright, alright.
Xiao Hu.
I want to ask you something.
What's the fastest way possible
to make a woman
leave a man?
Brother Feng.
Are you preparing for a funeral?
What nonsense.
I have a way to get money.
[Stay tuned for the post-credit scene!]
♫ A little bit caught in ♫
♫ A little about jokes ♫
♫ Life seems to be a strange riddle ♫
♫ I don't know who to tell the story ♫
♫ And I don't know why
you just disappeared suddenly ♫
♫ Better slow it down ♫
♫ Or else my heart
will be crushed to pieces ♫
What good food are you making?
♫ Because losing you ♫
Didn't I say yesterday that
good-hearted people will be rewarded?
Today,
someone is making you breakfast.
By the way,
I've lent my money to Zhu Yi Xiao,
♫ Is just too unbearable ♫
what to do now that
I don't have money for food?
For the sake of your righteous,
I'll take care of your daily meals
from now on.
Can you add some red beans?
♫ You said I am a fool who is not loved ♫
No one add red beans to omelette rice.
♫ Because I just can't forget you ♫
Don't cause trouble.
Go and get yourself clean.
♫ And I can't forgive you
for what you did ♫
♫ You left me alone in emptiness ♫
♫ In a mysterious room without sunlight ♫
♫ Go tell the world
that I still love you ♫
♫ I can't get you out of my mind ♫
♫ But you never will find me ♫
♫ Craving the affection from you ♫
Bon appetit.
Omelette rice.
What is it?
Nothing.
This is the tastiest
and sweetest omelette rice
I've had in my life.