[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 6]
[2012]
In the future,
you shouldn't be this careless.
Thanks.
I'll make a move first.
Are you going to return home?
Since I'm already here,
I might as well walk around.
I'll return home by myself later.
You don't need to care about me.
Qin Yang!
Fan Fan!
Let's head inside for now!
Let's hide first!
What's the matter?
Hide!
That Qin Yang,
he actually barged into my lab
instead of studying law.
If I catch you,
I'll teach you a lesson.
What did you do?
I just did
a Helmholtz coil experiment in the lab.
As long as the magnetic field response
and the energy of an area
are strong enough,
we can transport a person
from one timeline
to another timeline.
By then,
we can prove that you did come from 2024.
It sounds complicated.
But,
isn't my existence
the best proof of them all?
Are you willing to tell me about
the time-travelling process
you had undergone?
I can analyse it for you.
I remember now.
On that day,
the entire city had a blackout.
After that,
I saw a streak of light
on the door handle.
Just when I was about to touch it,
that was when I realised
I was transported here.
Was that information useful?
A blackout?
A streak of light?
I think it was caused by a magnetic field.
Maybe it's a geomagnetic storm.
caused by the mutated sunspots.
Don't tell me it's due to
the Fermi Bubbles?
That's right.
It's the Fermi Bubbles.
They showed it on TV during that day.
Qin Yang,
you're really amazing.
So, it was what I expected.
I've done my investigation.
In August 2012,
the Bermuda Triangle,
the Crop Circles,
all of those phenomena
proved that Earth's magnetic field
was experiencing turbulence.
The turbulence resonated
with the magnetic field line
in your timeline.
That's how you were able to time-travelled
from 2024 to 2012.
So, does that mean
if the Fermi Bubbles appear again,
I might have a chance
to return to my timeline?
I guess so.
I can finally go back!
Go back?
Qin Yang,
is this experiment
very difficult?
It'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Just leave the experiment to me.
By the way,
I remember that
there was a book in the library
that talked about the
time-space continuum.
Maybe
it might be useful to us.
I remember that book was in Zone G.
It should be nearby.
Why can't I find it?
What's the name of the book?
"Letters to Lily".
Let's look for it together.
Okay.
It's over here.
Thanks.
Shouldn't you return to class right now?
It's fine.
It doesn't matter even if
I'm late for the class.
I don't think you should do that.
How about this?
You can borrow this book for me.
I'll return it to you once I finish it.
Okay.
Let's go.
[When will your class be over?]
[I'm helping out my lecturer right now.]
[It might take quite a while.]
[Why don't you return home for now?]
[Okay then.]
[I'll buy some groceries
and make something delicious tonight.]
Is Lu Fan Fan truly
your girlfriend from the future?
What do you mean by that?
From the future?
[2024]
Are you living alone?
My parents went overseas when I was young.
I'm living alone.
Isn't this place too luxurious?
Let me show you something first.
Do you remember this conch?
This kind of conch
is pretty common.
That's right.
What about this?
It's a picture of me.
Why do you have it?
I have more than your pictures.
I also have our pictures.
This is...
Did we take this picture
together in the past?
That's right.
I have more of them.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did you remember something?
No.
Since you're exhausted,
you should rest in your room for now.
This is?
This was your room in the past.
I left the room just as it is
just in case you returned.
You can stay here tonight.
Your room is cleaned every day.
It's clean.
Do you need anything else?
None for now.
Thank you.
My room is upstairs.
You can find me if you need anything.
So,
you should rest for now.
♫ I'm looking forward ♫
♫ To our Wednesday date♫
♫ Catching ♫
♫ The last movie together with you ♫
♫ I'm afraid that I'm overthinking it ♫
♫ I'm hesitating about my last move ♫
♫ Remembering your name ♫
♫ The ending of the story was light ♫
♫ I have zero luck today ♫
♫ The weather forecast last night
foresaw a sunny morning ♫
♫ But it's drizzling within my heart ♫
♫ I cannot resonate with you ♫
♫ I heard your voice all of a sudden ♫
♫ Why do you sound
as cold as a cloudy day? ♫
♫ I have the same longing ♫
♫ For you today ♫
[Xian Lu Restaurant]
We're here.
Wait.
I have something for you.
Why did you give me a watch?
This isn't an ordinary watch.
I can't stay beside you 24/7.
So, if you were in an emergency,
you could press the button on top.
Remember,
you need to press it three times.
By doing so,
I'll receive a message from you.
Press it three times.
Remember that.
Goodbye.
[You never repent.]
[Your Achilles' heel is your weakness.]
[Do you understand?]
[How does he know]
[about my every move?]
[He even took a picture
of me and Fan Fan.]
[Could it be that he had installed
hidden cameras in the house?]
[Did he install them
right beside the house?]
The show will begin soon.
Here.
The weather has turned cold.
You should cover yourself.
Thank you, Mum.
You too.
Have you been feeling better
these few days?
I feel much better.
It's just
that some things
and some people
feel muddy
to me.
I cannot remember them.
Were you referring
to Lawyer Liu?
He told me a lot of things.
It...
It felt unfamiliar,
but it didn't seem fake.
It's fine.
Take your time.
Don't stress yourself out.
Everything will get better.
Mum,
so...
What if, one day,
I forgot
the way home?
What should I do?
Silly child,
no matter where you are,
I'll be able to find you.
It's because our hearts
are interconnected.
Hello, Mr. Qin.
Chen,
I found Gao Ru Wen.
What should we do now?
We don't have concrete evidence
against his crime.
We can't do anything to him for now.
But you can't just let him
spy on you all the time.
Moreover, there's Fan Fan.
What if he tries to harm Fan Fan?
Let's go and meet him then.
Chen,
do we need to call the cops in advance?
What's the room number?
1801.
[Liu Ruo Chen,]
[you're one step too late.]
Chen,
come and take a look.
[Lu Fan Fan, 24 years old, nutritionist]
Gao Ru Wen is too much.
And,
if he does intend to harm Fan Fan...
I think we should notify
Fan Fan about this.
That way, she'll be able to
keep her guard up against him.
Let's go.
[2012]
I remember
that it's nearby.
Why can't I find it?
Strange.
I remembered that it was here.
This is the place!
Mister!
I want this!
That's 50 cents.
Uncle Xiang!
Do I know you?
Of course.
I used to frequent this shop.
But,
back then,
your tummy
wasn't this big.
Let me foot the bill.
Brother Feng,
she's inside.
Do we strike now?
Let's wait a little longer.
There are too many people around her.
Once someone calls the cops,
we'll be sent to the police station.
Brother Feng,
I think we should quit.
We can think of something else
to gather the money.
It has already come to this.
If you plan on quitting right now,
I'll show you no mercy.
Brother Feng,
there are people everywhere.
We don't have a chance to strike.
We have to wait for our opportunity.
If we kidnap her successfully,
we'll be able to enjoy a luxurious life.
Alright then.
Brother Feng,
I'll follow your instruction.
But Brother Feng,
let me tell you this first.
If something goes awry,
I'll escape first.
Save your breath.
Just wait.
Let's wait.
Lu Fen Jin,
look at how cloudy it is out here.
It's almost raining,
yet you had to drag me out
to play the swing.
Dear,
you don't understand.
It's only romantic during rainy days.
♫ The most romantic thing
I could think of ♫
♫ Is to grow old together with you ♫
♫ Together ♫
Dear,
are you okay?
My heart feels uncomfortable.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You scared me.
Fan Fan didn't bring an umbrella with her.
Yeah.
I think her class should be over by now.
Look!
I told you it was going to rain!
Dear, sit tight.
Here's our romantic moment.
Isn't it romantic?
Doesn't it feel great?
Yeah, it's romantic.
You can bask in the
romantic moment yourself.
I'll make a move first.
Wait for me!
Big Sister?
Why are you here?
I thought you were
supposed to be on a trip?
I...
I just came back.
Is that so?
So,
where did you go on your trip?
Did you take pictures of them?
Did you buy any gifts for me?
Why didn't you return to the restaurant
since you're back?
I...
I was just about to
return to the restaurant.
And I bumped into you here.
Seems like we're growing
distant from each other.
You've started to hide things from me now.
I was wrong.
This...
I was planning to give this to you.
Don't try to shift the topic.
So,
where did you go?
Something happened.
Now, I'm staying
with Big Brother temporarily.
Are you two in a relationship?
No!
Actually,
I do hope for you two
to be in a relationship.
Why?
Because
Big Brother is a nice person.
He's nice to you.
He's nice to us.
I think it's most important
for a family to get along with each other.
I think
he can be part of our family.
I give you my permission
to be in a relationship with him.
Who needs your permission?
You're so mischievous.
When it comes to a relationship,
it's only meaningful
when both sides are contributing
to the relationship.
Let's go.
It's raining?
Brother Feng, she's out.
Both of them are girls?
Kidnap both of them.
Come.
Follow me!
Follow them!
Okay.
Follow them
What are you doing?
Get inside!
Boss,
I've tied them up.
[This weekend, we need a car model]
[to work in the convention centre.]
[1,000 yuan for two days of work.]
[Do you want the job?]
[I'll take up the offer!]
[Zhu Guo Feng]
Hello?
My daughter,
send the guy's phone number to me.
Why do you need his number?
I kidnapped the girl.
Now, I'm going to call that guy
and ask him for a ransom.
What did you say?
Listen!
You better don't try anything funny!
I'm doing this for your sake.
If you can't get his heart,
at least you need to get his money.
This is illegal!
Boss!
This place is great.
[It's remote and spacious.]
[Even the loan sharks can't find us here.]
Keep it down, won't you?
Alright.
Remember to send me his number.
I'll be waiting.
[How did it end up like this?]
[What should I do?]
[Should I call the cops?]
[No.]
[Mum will blame me if I do so.]
[But, if I don't call the cops,]
[what should I do
if something bad happens?]
[Zhu Guo Feng]
[Hurry and send me his number.]
[I was just saying.]
[Why did you kidnap Lu Fan Fan?]
Zhu Guo Feng!
What exactly are you up to?
Big Sister!
It's fine. I'm here with you.
Give me Liu Ruo Chen's contact number.
Big Sister!
I don't have it.
Big Sister, I'm scared!
Big Sister!
Stop crying!
What exactly are you up to?
Find her phone.
What are you trying to do?
Brother Feng.
[Lu Fan Fan]
Hello?
Lu Fan Fan is in our hands.
Prepare 500,000 yuan immediately.
[If not, you won't get to see her again.]
Who are you?
That doesn't matter.
Just prepare the ransom immediately.
What's wrong?
I can prepare the ransom for you,
but let me listen to her voice first.
Speak.
Speak!
Brother Ruo Chen!
Please save me and Big Sister!
[Hello?]
[Did you hear them?]
Remember,
place the money into the garbage bin
[in Qinglong Street within an hour.]
Do not call the cops.
Remember that.
What's the matter?
Fan Fan is in trouble.
Ruo Chen!
What exactly is going on?
Liu Ruo Chen!
We can talk when I'm back!
It's regarding Lu Fan Fan!
What else do you know?
My father was the one who kidnapped her.
I truly didn't expect things
to turn out like this.
I'm sorry.
This isn't your fault.
Our priority right now is to save Fan Fan.
But most banks are closed at this time.
Where can I gather such a huge sum?
Why don't we
approach my father?
No.
We mustn't let your father about this.
We must avoid implicating them.
But,
where can we gather such a huge sum
within an hour?
And, we have to send the money
to Qinglong Street as well.
Did they tell you guys
to go to Qinglong Street?
What's the matter?
When my father called me,
I heard someone saying
that they were in
a remote and spacious place.
He said even the loan sharks
couldn't find them.
I'm sure that place he mentioned
wasn't Qinglong Street.
Remote and spacious?
A factory?
That's right!
My father was in a lot of debts
due to his gambling habit.
He would hide in that factory
whenever the loan sharks
were looking for him.
Even the loan sharks
couldn't find him over there.
If that were the case,
that must be it.
The factory
was where he used to work.
After that, it was abandoned
after it closed down.
I don't care anymore.
Let's head there for now.
Brother Feng,
we're going to receive 500,000 yuan!
We'll strike it rich soon!
Be calm.
Sit down.
500,000 yuan?
We'll be fine.
Hello?
[Hello, Sir.]
Have you gathered enough money?
[No.]
What?
[I didn't see them in person.]
I thought he loved you?
Look at me!
He couldn't even prepare such a small sum.
Seems like your life isn't
that important to him!
I told you already!
We're unrelated by any means!
You should release us.
He won't give you the ransom.
Seems like I'm too gentle with you!
Lu!
Big Sister!
What about Yi Xiao?
Should we let her stay in the car?
After all, this is her father
we're talking about.
Release Lu immediately!
Big Brother!
Are you okay?
How did you guys find this place?
Release them!
You want me to release them? Fine!
Where's the ransom?
The ransom is on the car.
Release them first!
Stop wasting our time!
I'll kill her!
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
[#Gold Digger#]
[#Scheming Wretch#]
[#Fake Wealthy Girl#]
[#Pretentious#]
[#Green Tea Girl#]
[#Fake#]
[Sometimes, when we
put on a false front for too long,]
[we will forget
how we look like in the first place.]
[Who am I?]
♫ The ending isn't perfect,
the plot is reluctant ♫
[Why am I doing this?]
[Where am I going?]
[Why am I putting on a false front?]
♫ Walking through the four seasons,
hand in hand ♫
[I grabbed hold of the things
I didn't want to let go of,]
♫ Our memories are being replayed ♫
[ignoring the gossips and rumours.]
[I'm living in an illusionary world]
♫ I was lucky ♫
[because I want people
to treat me gently.]
♫ That I was once crazy about you ♫
♫ Looking at the stars
in the middle of the night, I smiled ♫
[An illusionary world]
[is meant to be shattered.]
[The unpaid medical bills
on my mother's bed]
♫ As I observe your life in silence ♫
[had woken me up.]
♫ A trip, a workout, a book, and a movie ♫
[I spent the first half of my life]
♫ You're getting better at doing makeup ♫
[in fate's cage.]
[I was dragged along.]
♫ It's a pity that now ♫
[I couldn't escape from it.]
[Now,]
♫ I'm not beside you ♫
[this is the start of my new life.]
♫ Maybe you will smile
more often with me around ♫
♫ I hope you think that it's worth it ♫
♫ Even though you might have
regretted your decision ♫
Zhu Yi Xiao!
♫ If we miss out on each other ♫
[In the time tunnel
towards another realm,]
♫ Please trust that
it's none of our fault ♫
[you might find a version of yourself
who longs for happiness.]
♫ Thank you for loving me once ♫
♫ You made me the happiest person ♫
[And that version of you
is trying her best]
♫ Trying my best to predict the future,
it was me all along ♫
[to head towards]
[a warm]
[and wonderful world.]