[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 1]
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Any resemblance to actual persons
or actual events is purely coincidental.]
[2024]
This is the best lawyer in town,
Liu Ruo Chen.
To date, he has never lost a case.
He is young and handsome
but he is tactful and ferocious at work.
Rumour has it
that he would do anything to win a case.
The case
that he is currently conducting
has once again pushed him
to the cusp of the public opinion.
Will he ace yet another legendary case?
Mr. Liu.
Good morning.
Here you are, Xiao Lu.
Here are
the two sets of nutritious breakfast
specially prepared for you.
It's too noisy here.
Why don't we go to a quieter place?
You can explain to me in detail later.
Sure.
[Hai Tian Center]
Mr. Liu!
Will you please answer our questions?
Will you accept our interviews?
Mr. Liu, please accept our interviews.
Mr. Liu.
Why do you choose
to defend a murder suspect?
The Court has convicted him.
Why do you insist on defending him?
Are you trying to gain public sympathy?
Or is it because of the huge fees?
-Please respond.
-Excuse me.
Mr. Liu.
I have made an appointment for you
at the boxing gym.
As for Zheng Qi's case,
all the evidence is against the suspect.
Now, the public opinion is one sided.
Most of the people think
that you are trying to garner attention
and gain free publicity.
It's prejudicial to your reputation.
We have prepared
a few breakfast sets specially for you.
Let me explain to you.
Come nearer.
Like this?
Can you see it clearly?
Yes.
So clearly.
Your skin is fair and flawless.
Xiao Lu.
Tell me.
Do you look so pretty
because you had the nutrition package?
Mr. Liu.
We...
I think we should
focus on the nutrition package.
If I were to choose,
I would choose you.
Xiao Lu.
Have a nice ride,
Mr. Liu.
Ruo Chen.
This is the document you asked for.
Why did you ask
for Gao Ru Wen's documents?
I think he is still
serving sentence in jail.
He was released earlier
due to his good performance in prison.
He was released earlier?
With his personality,
he must be holding grudges against you.
Perhaps he is hiding away,
waiting to seek revenge on you.
I'm not worried about that.
But I'm worried
that he would come after people around me.
You'd better be careful lately.
Let me know right away
if you sense something is wrong.
Got it.
Don't worry about me.
In that case,
do you find any clue from the documents?
It's important to know your enemy.
I just want to know him more.
It's the sixth time, right?
It's only the fifth time.
You remember it so clearly.
Have you forgotten
why did you work so hard to make money?
Little Yue.
We have been friends for so long.
You will help me, right?
I didn't say that I won't help you
but you have to deal with
a troublesome client of mine
who is really hard to please.
It is a great deal.
I can't afford any mistake.
Those reporters claim
that you are bullying the victim's family.
What do you think?
I have no comment.
Are you not going to
harmonise the relationship?
There is no need.
Are you not going to speak more?
I'm not in the mood.
Where are you?
How do I find you?
You are thinking about her again.
Wake up.
She doesn't exist.
It's none of your business.
[Hai Tian Center]
[Taxi]
[I'm doomed.]
[Knowing that the client is sticky,
I'm still late.]
[Hai Tian Center]
[Little Yue will kill me if she knows.]
Finally, you are here.
Let's begin.
[To cope with Anorexia, one must
take care of their spleen and stomach.]
[Omurice.]
[The ratio of meat to vegetables
is one to four.]
[The ratio of vegetables to fruits
is two to one.]
[The ratio of steamed food]
[to stir-fried food is two to one.]
[Today, I'm making]
[omurice.]
[Anorexia is nothing.]
[No one can say no
to the omurice made by me, Lu Fan Fan,]
[not even the client who is
the hardest to please.]
[Perfect!]
Mr. Liu.
Here is your omurice.
Did you make it?
It smells so good.
It's delicious!
This is the best omurice I have ever had.
It's out of the world!
Ms. Lu Fan Fan.
Will you be my personal chef?
It's all yours.
Use it.
There is no password.
Ms. Lu?
Is it done?
It's done.
[Liu Ruo Chen]
[Signed by, Dr. Xu Yong Sheng]
The suspect has never
gotten in touch with the deceased.
It's impossible
that he committed the crime
without a motive.
[Haicheng Personal Health Insurance]
[Basic coverage, 5 million yuan]
Zheng Qi?
Five million yuan...
[Haicheng Personal Health Insurance]
[CT Scan Report]
Mr. Liu.
This is the omurice
cooked by the new chef.
Judging from the smell,
I think
I can gobble down five bowls of rice.
It seems
that your anorexia
can be cured soon.
Pass me the spoon.
It's not her.
I'm sorry, Ms. Lu.
I'm afraid...
you are here for nothing.
What do you mean?
Your cooking
is not well received by my boss.
So, he doesn't like it?
Ms. Lu...
Please calm down.
Being impulsive brings trouble.
Just you wait.
But he refuses to work with us.
He refuses to say anything.
What do you
expect me to do?
Just you wait.
Give it to everyone.
Ms. Lu,
please stop cooking.
Everyone in the office except for Mr. Liu,
even Pikachu has eaten it.
What is Pikachu?
Alright.
I will leave.
I will pack up and leave.
Thank you
for the hard work.
I'll get going then.
[Liu...]
[Ruo...]
[Chen...]
[How dare you feed my cooking to dog?]
Miss.
I'm looking for
Mr. Liu.
Liu Ruo Chen.
Did you make an appointment?
I'm the nutritionist
engaged by the office.
You might not have seen me before.
I'm sorry.
I can't let you in without an appointment.
But it's something urgent.
Would you kindly
make an exception for me?
No.
Fine, I'll make an appointment now.
Come on the 26th
of the coming month, at 5 am.
You have 10 minutes to see him.
Next month?
Five o'clock in the morning?
Well...
He goes home after work, right?
I'll make sure
I catch him.
The couch is over there.
You may wait there.
Why is everyone still here?
That's right.
As you haven't left the office,
so...
Go home now.
Have some supper before that.
It's on me.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
Go home now.
Join them for supper.
Here, let's go.
I know of a nice hotpot restaurant.
Hurry up!
Hello?
Hello, Fan Fan.
Are you done with the client?
I have checked in a presidential suite
in a hotel.
Let's have a gathering.
No one is allowed to go home sober.
Got it.
Hurry.
It's already 10.42 pm?
Where is he?
Everyone has gone home.
How was it?
Was it a success?
From your look,
I guess you have failed.
I made a bet with Xiao Yang
that you would get it done for sure.
I treat you as best friend.
But look at you.
You made a bet
on my job.
Don't be mad.
The client is a handsome guy,
and you have been single
for so many years,
I'm trying to match you two up.
That's the way to a handsome man's heart
is through his stomach.
It's such a good deal.
Many people would die for it.
Good deal?
I have bad luck lately.
What happened?
He fed my cooking to dog.
Why are you laughing?
He is such an unethical lawyer.
Even if someone gives him to me for free,
I won't take him.
[Here's the latest legal news updates.]
[Let Liu Ruo Chen,
the best lawyer in town,]
[unveil an insurance fraud case for you.]
Look.
-Liu Ruo Chen just won a case again.
-[The victim was diagnosed with cancer.]
-[Insurance fraud case?]
-[She tricked the adjusters]
-[I've misunderstood him.]
-[to her place,]
[to create the illusion of murder.]
-Why are you spacing out?
-[The case is strange and mysterious.]
-Are you thinking about Liu Ruo Chen?
-[The police...]
[I'm not think about him.]
I'm worried
about my mom's hospital bill
for the coming month.
What should I do?
Mom!
[Balance 65.6 yuan]
I have taken care of it for you.
It's not much
but it's enough to foot the hospital bill.
Little Yue.
You are so nice.
If you were a man,
I would have married you.
[Beauty.]
[Are you interested to grab a drink?]
A handsome guy just asked me out.
That's all for today.
I have to go.
Yu Xiao Yue!
All right.
The room is all yours.
I have even prepared pajamas for you.
Give yourself a break.
Bye.
Are you leaving for real?
Hey!
What a terrible woman.
Fine.
Let me
be a happy single lady.
[Here's the latest weather news.]
[At 8 pm tonight,]
[the Fermi Bubbles
in the Milky Way halo]
[will continue stretching]
[for over 250,000 light-years
both above and below]
-Fermi Bubbles?
-[the center of the Milky Way.]
-[Fermi Bubbles...]
-What is that?
[are the largest Galactic structure
found on the Milky Way.]
[It was discovered in the year 2010.]
[It is made solely]
[of powerful gamma rays]
[and X-ray.]
[It can't be detected with bare eyes.]
[The scientists assume,]
[the gamma rays]
[could be a form of shock wave.]
[formed when a massive black hole]
[devours a star.]
This suite is awful.
I can't believe a black out took place.
What is this?
You!
Don't look at me!
Liu Ruo Chen?
He deserved it.
After all, he refused to eat my cooking.
But...
His chest muscles
are not bad.
If I knew earlier,
I would have touched them.
Why don't...
I take another peep?
[2012]
♫ Love can be ♫
♫ Hurting sometimes ♫
♫ Healing every wound ♫
♫ But for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to be brave ♫
♫ Taking the risk,
no matter what they say ♫
You...
Were you trying to commit suicide?
Commit suicide?
Are you joking?
If I fall off this high,
even if I don't die,
I will sustain fractures all over my body,
or worse, become paralysed.
I don't have the guts.
Just now, you...
I...
I wonder why too.
The last thing I knew,
I was already standing there.
Where is this?
Why did you do this to me, Dear God?
[2024]
Hello.
My name is Gao Ru Wen.
Are you
troubled by something?
You may say so.
Then,
I met the best friend
of my life.
She kept me company all the time
and she always helped me out.
She sounds like a nice person.
Why are you drinking alone?
My best friend
has gone missing.
I only have one friend.
But she...
She has just gone missing all of a sudden.
Your best friend...
Who is she?
Trust me.
You will eventually find her.
You will live a happy life.
[2012]
Why are you smiling?
I...
I'm not...
Don't deny it.
You're grinning from ear to ear!
Pajamas...
Slippers...
Could she be
a rebellious young girl
who has just run away from home?
Do you really don't know where is this?
Why don't
we go down?
Where is this?
This is a food street.
This place is so familiar.
Missy, take a look.
[The summer class of 2012
will begin soon!]
Why don't you
register a class for your kids?
Do I look like
I have kids?
I'm sorry.
[The summer class of 2012
will begin soon!]
It's 2012?
Yes, it's 2012.
I think it's wrongly printed.
No, it's right.
It's 2012.
Are Yu Xiao Yue and you pulling my leg?
Who is Yu Xiao Yue?
I don't know her.
Why did I end up here?
I didn't get involved in a car crash.
I didn't get struck by lightning either.
Don't think that you can fool me.
I want to go home.
I forgot to bring my mobile phone.
Lend me your phone.
I want to summon a taxi.
If you want to summon a taxi,
you just have to
stop one at the mouth of the street.
Why do you need a phone?
This...
This mobile phone is an antique.
This is Xiaomi Mi 1.
It was launched two years ago.
How could you not know that?
It's 2012.
[2012]
[2024]
[Criminal Law Book I - Theories of Crime]
[Since the first day Fan Fan
transmigrate to this universe...]
In another universe...
It turns out
this is what matters the most to you.
[Criminal Law Book I - Theories of Crime]
Liu Ruo Chen.
[Long time no see.]
Gao Ru Wen, it's you.
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
[2024]
♫ A little bit caught in ♫
♫ A little about jokes ♫
♫ Life seems to be a strange riddle ♫
♫ I don't know who to tell the story ♫
♫ And I don't know why you ♫