[English subtitles are available]
Si Yan?
Had I known, I wouldn't have held it like so.
Rehearsing the wedding for the master
is tiring.
Why do you agree to marry her?
Bao,
it doesn't concern you.
Why did you do that to Si Yan?
Don't go.
Explain yourself.
Qi Yi!
Brother Da!
Since you were young,
you have never changed.
You own everything,
but you want everything from others.
You don't like Tong Rui.
Why do you agree to marry her?
Say something!
I have nothing to say to you.
Let him go.
Your flute sounds
miserable and mournful.
People might think you just broke up.
Parents' orders.
Matchmaker's arrangement.
A well-matched couple
loves each other.
But who should marry whom?
If you want to see me, Uncle,
send me a message and I'll go to you.
You don't need to make a trip in person.
Where is the thing?
I haven't found it.
Is it that you haven't found it?
Or you don't want to look for it?
Have you forgotten
how your dad tragically died in East City?
If you can't find the heartbreak grass recipe,
I'll take over.
If I hurt Prince Xiu by accident,
don't blame me for that.
Don't go.
You can only leave
after finishing the wedding wine.
Si Yan,
listen to me.
Tomorrow's wedding
has other purposes.
Prince Yi,
the only emotion I have right now
is gratitude.
Please dismiss me.
Mother?
Vengeful?
The woman you love and the crowned prince title
are both taken away.
Prince Da, you are miserable.
If you are here for a late-night stroll,
please excuse me.
I see that you don't wish
someone could solve the problem for you.
Why is my father's half piece of
Tiger tally with you?
It doesn't matter how I got it.
What's important is
how you get what you want with it.
Don't you know it's a crime to take the tally
without permission?
It depends on who takes it.
If the future King of East City takes it,
it's not a crime.
Do you mean...
I should
revolt?
Everything belongs to you.
It's not revolting.
You are just using it
to get what you want.
You fulfilled your duty for East City,
but it's all for nothing in the end.
I don't know how you feel.
Right now, my brother has
the other half of the tally.
When the two halves match,
you can deploy the troops of East City.
As long as you commit to it,
the Mins shall spare no effort.
What do you want?
I'm doing this for Rui.
I can tell that
the person in her heart is you.
I don't want her to follow in my footsteps
and marry someone she doesn't love
to uphold the Mins' power and status.
I trust that you
wouldn't want to see that happen.
Now the chance
has presented itself to you.
It's up for grabs if you have the courage.
Qi Da,
is it you?
Farewell.
After tomorrow...
After tomorrow,
East City will be mine.
What are you going to do?
Don't you always want me to become
the crowned prince?
If this is what you want,
I'll give you that.
I don't care if I'll risk everything I have.
You can't change the ending anymore.
Master,
you've been sitting here since yesterday.
You have been waiting for the whole night,
and haven't had any water.
Who are you waiting for?
Why did you nod your head
and then shake your head?
I'm waiting for someone who'd never come.
I'm not sure if I should keep waiting.
Is it a friend?
A confidant?
Or a lover?
She's everything.
It seems that you've expected the outcome.
You can say that
I used to be a person with no future.
Only after she walked into my life,
I started to save many moments.
Are those the moments of
you loving each other and being together?
Quietly standing next to her,
I watched as she busied herself in the kitchen.
When she messed up on her makeup,
I watched the messy look on her face.
I watched as she went on the hustle and bustle
of her everyday life.
I even...
I even watched her taken into the arms of someone
with tears in her eyes,
feeling hurt and wronged.
Time-out, Jack!
Master,
to love someone or not, that is the question.
I believe that
in her eyes,
there must be you.
Can she see me?
Yeah,
her in your eyes
reflects you in her eyes.
After tonight,
you can get out of here.
Si Yan,
thank you,
but are you sure that
you want to stay here?
After you get out,
if there's a chance,
please say hello to my old man for me.
Tell him
that I'm fine.
Tell him not to worry.
Si Yan,
did you think it through?
I know
you won't complete the task of killing Qi Yi.
But to give up your family who's been waiting for you,
are you sure you're ready for that?
Everything here
is a world constructed by data.
It looks realistic,
but dangers are everywhere.
Though we are players,
when it comes to the business in gaming,
you either win or lose.
My lady,
The Second Lady sent me to tell you that
General Min went to Treasure Pavilion
to pick up the special wedding gift he got for you
and was delayed.
He may not make it back by the auspicious time.
The auspicious time shall not change.
Please wait for my father outside the mansion
and tell my aunt that
the ceremony will proceed as planned.
Yes, my lady.
Lan Miao!
Where have you been?
Give my hairpin back.
Qi Yi,
talented in academics and martial arts,
born with intelligence and wisdom,
gentle and well-mannered,
dutiful of parents and respectful to siblings,
capable of battling at war
and governing at court.
I announced Qi Yi as the crowned prince.
He shall carry on responsibilities
from ancestors
and unify the people of East City.
Yi,
it's your wedding day.
After today,
the weight on your shoulders is heavier.
I must not disappoint you, Father.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Crowned Prince.
Commence the ceremony.
Bow to the earth and sky.
Bow to the parents.
Bow to each other.
Doctor, the patient is responsive.
Big brother!
Da!
What are you doing?
It's a family business.
Get lost if you don't want to die.
Okay.
All of you, leave now.
Run! Prince Da is committing treason!
Hurry! Run!
Si Yan,
I have a bad feeling.
On my wedding day,
my father didn't show up.
I'm afraid
something is wrong.
Do you suspect
General Min to be behind all this?
Based on my understanding of the game plot,
General Min is a good person who's loyal to East City.
I hope that I am over-worried.
This is bad. I have to find General Min.
Say what you are scheming.
I want to leave with the woman I love.
Since I can't rightfully take her with me,
I can only get those
that are supposed to be mine.
Brother Da...
Don't call me brother!
Yi,
don't stop him.
Let him speak his mind.
You're an unruly son!
Merely for a woman...
Enough!
She is the only person who understands me.
She never looked down on me,
unlike you.
No matter what I do,
I can't get your recognition.
You never cared about me.
If you hate me so much,
why did you bring me to the world?
Didn't you say that
I accomplished nothing,
and I am a failure?
I'll show you what I can do today.
You wouldn't make me the crowned prince.
I'll make myself one.
Look at this yourself!
Father,
Luna is a scapegoat.
Someone else is behind this.
Yi,
I have an idea.
I want to make you the fake crowned prince
and use the wedding as bait.
The person behind this
would certainly take action.
Father...
The patient's vitals are dropping!
Her breathing is weak.
Rui?
Rui!
General Min?
Prince Bao?
Prince Bao!
Are you still worried about Prince Yi
and Si Yan?
Do you still have feelings for
Si Yan?
Lan Miao,
don't you think
my mother has been acting strange?
What makes you think so?
She suddenly asked us
to bring the baby princess to the royal retreat
and we must set off right away.
It is very unlike her.
The Second Lady told us the reason, didn't she?
The weather is warm in the retreat,
so it's better for the health of the baby princess.
She also wants you to take a break
and get some fresh air.
But...
now that you mentioned it,
I do think that
the Second Lady looked downhearted recently.
Every night when she held the baby princess
in her arms,
she was secretly shedding tears.
Since when was she like that?
Since the assassin died.
The Second Lady said the assassin had so much grudge
that it was unhealthy for the baby princess.
After dinner,
she dismissed all the guards
and page boys
and didn't allow anyone to wait on her.
Lan Miao,
we have to go back.
Qi Da! Qi Da!
You can't even complete a simple task.
No wonder the King said that you're useless!
You planned all of this!
You finally showed yourself!
The Qixi assault case,
the Cloud Brothel case,
and the loss of food and fodder...
You are behind them all, aren't you?
Three years ago when Cloud Brothel had a fire,
it wasn't a coincidence that you were there.
You went there to meet the Northland King
and plotted
to trap Prince Teng!
My Teng?
You're right.
I sent Qi Teng to the Northland King,
but I didn't expect him
to threaten me because of that.
He asked me to provide food and fodder.
He would have exposed me had I said no.
But that worked out just as well.
I could strengthen my power by the war.
It's you who got Teng killed?
Dear...
Mother!
Dear!
Min Ling,
I order you to withdraw the troops immediately.
Or else
you are doomed.
You should worry about yourself first.
Nobody moves!
Min Ling,
what exactly do you want?
Re-draft the edict
and make Qi Bao the crowned prince.
Never!
If you don't agree,
they'll die in front of you one by one.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll do it.
Hold on!
Let General Min through.
Brother.
Bring Rui out of here first.
Please stop here!
The rebels have been purged.
Don't make any more mistakes!
I'm about to succeed.
East City will be mine soon.
It will belong to the Mins soon.
Why are you stopping me?
Didn't you want me
to earn my place in East City?
For that, despite my pleading,
you married me far to East City.
I'm about to have everything,
but you're pointing at me with a sword.
Ling,
what happened to you?
Why?
You turned me into this.
The Min household turned me into this.
For the Min household,
I gave up my love,
but what did I get in return?
Qing Yan died in front of me,
but I had to pretend that I didn't know him.
I had to suffer in silence!
This place is like a prison.
I can never escape.
Only Qing Yan...
He was always by my side.
I swallowed the pain, worked hard, and step by step,
I made you the most powerful minister in East City.
The Min household became a rainmaker
in East City because of me.
And now you're asking me
what I've become?
You were the one who told me
only power can set me free!
Just as I'm about to
get everything,
you're pointing your sword at me!
You...
You have turned my whole life into a big joke!
What has happened to me?
Min Ling!
A loser has to accept his fate.
I lost.
Why did you come back?
Let go, let go, let go!
Mother...
Bao...
Father,
please forgive my mother.
I'll accept any consequences for my mother
even if I die.
No, no!
Drop the sword. Drop it!
Drop it now!
Please don't...
I was late
to the rescue!
I beg for Your Majesty's forgiveness.
Everything that happened
was caused by the Min household.
I ruined Ling's life.
I beg Your Majesty to let Ling live.
If it's not enough,
please take my life instead of hers.
Forget it...
What happened today
has nothing to do with you.
Take my order!
Strip off nobility of Min Ling.
Make her a commoner.
Exile her to the north region.
She shall never return to East City.
Mother,
don't be sad.
I'll do give everything I can
to protect both of you.
Bao,
I have wronged you.
In this big world,
there must be somewhere we can settle down.
I never desire nobility or power.
I only ask to stay by your side
to take care of you.
Furthermore,
I also wanted to
go to the north region.
Prince Bao!
Prince Bao...
Stop the horse!
Lan Miao,
why are you here?
It's cold in the north region,
so I packed you
some winter clothes.
There are some of your favorite snacks.
If you are not used to the food there,
at least you have these.
How considerate!
Thank you, Lan Miao!
Going forward,
please take care.
Your Highness,
please allow me to go with you.
Nonsense!
Go back!
It's not nonsense.
I mean it.
Although the north region isn't as nice as East City,
and one has to sleep in the open,
and lack clothes and food,
I am not afraid.
Please let me take care of you and the Second Lady.
I am no longer a prince in East City.
Don't be silly.
As for you,
I don't have any feelings for you,
and I don't need you to care for me.
Prince Bao!
You kept
this purse.
Prince Bao,
I like you.
I know I was born lowly,
but
I can't control myself from liking you.
I like Qi Bao
regardless of his status
and identity.
I want nothing but to stay by your side.
I want to keep you company.
Take me with you.
Okay.
You said yes!
But on one condition.
No more crying.
The hidden task of the Second Lady is completed,
which means
I won't need to kill Qi Yi!
Si Yan,
I'll be waiting for you at the posting station
until you come.
No one can
separate us now.
Wait for me.
There's something I need to do.