We want Gene
to write us another Boy Love novel!
What?
They're going to have a casting
for "Bad Engineer The Series".
They want you to join.
Number 18, Nubsib please come in.
You're mine.
Gene!
It's me, Tum.
I'm working as an artist manager.
I think you already met him.
Nubsib?
There's something urgent.
Can you come to see me?
Your condo has three bedrooms, right?
Can Nubsib...
No!
I haven't even finished...
You've said so much,
do you think I can't guess?
Please, Gene!
I'm having a bit of
an accommodation problem.
Can Nubsib stay here for just one month?
No.
-Three weeks?
-No.
-Two weeks?
No matter how many days,
the answer is still no.
Please, I'm begging you!
It's not that I want to bother you,
but I'm out of options.
Nubsib's home is so far
but he has to go to class and work...
so I had him live at the agency's
building but Tam got new recruits,
and this is all because of Nubsib,
I don't know how he spoke to her...
and get so mixed up that
he doesn't have a room.
Now I'm in deep shit because
I can't find a place for him to live.
The series is starting the shooting soon.
Why don't you just rent out a hotel?
The agency is so damn rich.
It's just a small amount of money
to pay for the kids.
Are you crazy? Nubsib is famous,
if people
see him at a hotel we'll be screwed.
Fans waiting in the
lobby and even stalkers!
Hotels aren't very private.
What about your home?
At first, I was going to do that but
my house is even further than Nubsib's.
It's worse!
Please? You're the best option
and Nubsib can help you with housework.
He's very good at it and he cooks too!
Tum, I'm not close with Nubsib...
and even though you
say it's just temporary,
but I work from home
and I can't think of a new plot.
Everybody wants their privacy,
not only me but Nubsib too!
Nubsib doesn't have a problem, right?
Don't you guys have other options?
I'm at my wit's end.
I understand that we've just reconnected
so it's too soon for you to trust me...
but I have nobody else.
Please, Gene.
Nubsib will not stay here for free.
He'll pay the water
and electricity bills and the...
I can help clean the room if Gene is busy.
Nubsib is the best at housekeeping!
You won't see any dust!
Please? Only one month.
You guys are really hard selling.
So...
Fine, don't need to come up
with so many excuses.
One month is fine.
It's only because you're in trouble.
Do you know even my older brother
hasn't even slept here?
As for the cleaning, it's okay
and never mind about the utility bills.
Gene, you're a lifesaver!
Enough I'm going to throw up.
=Lovely Writer=
Gene.
What? Why are you calling me?
Please get some rest, I'll do it.
Let me nap for a while, I've been
thinking so much about work lately.
I'm a writer so my
working hours are different...
and I'm working on a new novel
so ideas only come to me at night.
If you're going to live here,
the only thing
I ask is to not bother me while working.
Do you understand?
This is your room, make yourself at home.
Gene.
What?
Do you want to toast in the morning?
Sure, put mountains of jam on it.
Like this?
Are you getting on my nerves?
I'm just doing what you told me.
How do you normally get to classes?
Sometimes I take the bus or a taxi.
Get ready, I'm taking
you to the university.
Really?
Why would I lie?
Go and get ready.
You don't have to be nice to me.
I'm letting you stay
because I feel sorry for Tum.
Just stay in your lane
and don't bother me.
Do you understand?
Go get dressed.
What are you doing?
You forgot to buckle in your seat-belt
so I wanted to help.
I can do it myself.
Don't forget to buckle your seat-belt.
Here's your key-card,
I forgot to give it to you yesterday.
Don't lose it, it's expensive.
I'm never going to lose
something you give me.
Let's go, you're going to be late.
Thank you for dropping me off.
Study hard!
Please drive home safely.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Earn.
Mhok! You startled me,
when did you get here?
Just a second ago.
You're Mr Popular now.
Can I have your autograph
before you get famous?
You're exaggerating.
I'm not! Look at the hashtag on Twitter.
Everybody tweeted photos of you.
It's not like that
I'm not even the main cast.
Not like Aey...
Can I ask you something?
If you're going to ask about Aey,
he's doing fine.
He's bubbly and friendly with everyone.
Thank you.
But he's not answering my texts.
Maybe he doesn't want
to talk to me anymore.
It's not just you,
I'm standing right
there in front of him and he ignores me.
We're not kids anymore.
At least he's not doing
bad things to others.
That's enough right?
If you see him,
can you tell him to answer my messages?
Sure, I'll tell him.
So how is Med school?
It's stressful.
I don't know
if it's from studying or something else.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
I think it's good that Aey didn't
choose Med school...
as his Dad told him to like me.
Aey is brave enough to defy his father,
sometimes I get really jealous.
I want to be like him too.
Hello, Mom.
What are you doing?
I just got back to my room,
what are you doing?
I miss you so I called to talk.
I miss you too, how are you?
I'm tired from work but hearing your voice
makes me feel much better.
What about you? How was work?
Everything is the same.
Why won't you come to visit?
If I can get a day off
I'll go home to you.
How is dad?
Same old, I don't want to talk about it.
Don't think too much.
How can I not? He's spending so much.
I don't know how he's getting
into so much debt and trouble.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Never mind.
Be patient, it'll get better.
Quickly come home, I miss you.
I miss you too, I love you.
I love you too.
(Tum: Tell Nubsib I'm picking
him up tomorrow afternoon)
(to take him for the series refitting.)
Geez, he keeps bothering me.
Are you awake?
The way you're looking at me,
I'm getting shy.
I've been awake for a while, I'm hungry.
I'm going to go find something to eat.
Can I go with you?
Have you been home long?
For a while.
Why didn't you find something to eat yet?
I was waiting for you.
Why did you wait?
I told you that my work hours
are different from others.
Next time if you're hungry
go get something to eat.
Go put some clothes on.
Am I making you shy?
Shy my ass, you can stay here freely...
but that doesn't mean
you can walk around half-naked.
Go put on some clothes now.
Don't you like it?
I think I have a great body.
It's not that I don't like it.
So you like it?
Why do you have to
know if I like it or not?
So I can be the most
perfect character for you.
You're exaggerating,
go put on some clothes.
What are you looking at?
Just choose what you want to eat.
I don't know what I want to eat.
I'll choose for you.
Judging from your abs,
it must be something lean.
You remember my body?
Sure.
I mean, I didn't meant to memorize it.
It's just...
I remember it.
I'm just kidding,
but this is almost expired.
How do you know?
It has the yellow price tag.
Right.
Just eat it, it's just almost expired
but it hasn't gone bad yet.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me, are you an actor?
No.
I don't think I remembered
the wrong person.
What's the name... It's Nubsib, right?
I think you've got the wrong person,
but people make that mistake all the time.
I'm sorry, did you just move in?
I'm going to get water.
Yes, I just moved in with my boyfriend.
Please excuse me.
What were you thinking saying that?
I wanted her to really believe
that it wasn't me.
I have to live here.
If people knew it was me
there will be big trouble.
What about me?
You're only staying here for one month.
And I have to stay here.
I don't see anything wrong with that.
Sib!
Why are you laughing at?
Nothing, I'm just glad.
The hell with that, why are you laughing?
I'm really glad.
I'm glad because the way you spoke
made me feel like we're getting close.
Like what? Calling you Sib?
Yes, I don't want you to feel
awkward when you're with me.
I want us to be close.
So should we just say Gu-Mueng?
If you're okay with that
then I'm down with it.
You started this.
You buffalo! Bastard!
Stuck up! Tall! Superstar! Softie!
Ass!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for my boyfriend.
Sib!!
You're doing it again.
If you cussing at me makes us
come closer then I'm okay with it.
Are you alright in the head?
Why won't you call me Phi?
I don't to call you Phi.
Are you getting on my nerves again?
When we're close,
I'll change your title.
His lip were quickly
crushed by the tall protagonist.
He was out of breath
while his mind went blank...
but he kept his eyes closed during the
kiss out of fear of being unprofessional.
He begun to feel unsure
if what was happening...
was just something
in the scene or really happening.
Hey, Gene.
How does he look?
Khin, the lead of your novel.
I just wanted you to see Sib's outfit,
your lead! Do you like it?
Do I look like a fashionista to you?
Then you can trust me because
I guarantee that he'll be so handsome...
that everyone will fall in love with him.
Wow, you're good at going over the top.
Well, I am looking after him!
So, what are you up to?
I'm working.
You're writing a novel?
What are you working on? Can I ask?
Well, it's just in a film production set,
but the outline isn't quite done yet.
That's great, you can do research
by coming to the series' set.
-Tum.
-What?
I'm changing to the next outfit,
who are you talking to?
I'm talking to Gene.
Gene.
Yeah.
He's a wake?
Gene, how long have you been awake?
For sometime.
Did you have toast for breakfast?
I ate whatever I could find.
There's a sandwich in the fridge,
I made it this morning.
Don't forget to eat
or you'll get a stomach ache.
Okay.
Are you going to stay
in and write all day?
Something like that.
I know you can do it.
We have to go now. Bye, Gene.
Bye.
There's a sandwich in the fridge,
I made it this morning.
Do you want toast in the morning?
Sib, hold Aey like this and Aey
put your hands on his chests firmly.
Slightly look at him and smile,
like you guys are very much in love.
It's a photo but the feeling
has to come from within.
Okay, are you ready? Clear the set!
Take the picture,
don't block each other's faces.
Let me check, the lighting is good.
Look in love! Yeah!
Closer and more intimate.
It's not okay yet! Again!
Look in love and intimate!
Don't block each other.
Can you get closer?
Hold on to his arms tightly and relax.
Mai, the lead has to be a ship couple,
but they're standing miles apart,
it doesn't really scream "in love".
I'll get on it.
Sib and Aey can we do it again?
Stand closer.
Even closer, like you're becoming as
one and Sib squeeze his arms harder.
Aey push his chest like you're saying,
don't come any closer, don't touch me!
But you actually want him to
come closer, look more in love?
The lighting is great, snap on.
Get in with your inner feelings, great.
Aey, would you answer
Earn's texts? She's concerned.
Did she tell you to tell me that?
Could you stop being her spy?
It's irritating.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for Nubsib's wallet,
I don't know where it is.
Do you need something?
Nothing, but you're looking sharp today!
Gene's lucky to have you.
What? Gene is an old friend.
You're talking nonsense.
You don't need to hide it, I can see it.
See what? There's nothing.
-Hey.
-What?
Is this brand good?
-This one?
-Yeah.
It's great, it's perfect
for sensitive skin.
That great, I want to try it.
This lipstick color is cute.
-Hey.
-What?
Can you help me put makeup on?
Do you think that's a good
idea? We haven't asked...
All the makeup crew are
on set, no one's coming.
Quickly, come on.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Done.
It's a really nice lip color.
Your face is all oily.
Let me help.
Help?
-I'll help you.
-It's okay.
Just stay still, let me do it.
Your face is oily.
Close your eyes.
Done.
How do I look?
You're so pretty!
You could put on a wig and be a girl.
I'm going to the toilet.
Who dropped you off?
Someone from the shoot because
he had to come this way anyway.
Where are you going?
I'm going to go find something to eat.
Find something to eat?
At a mall around here.
Have you eaten? Do you want to join me?
Are you inviting me?
Yeah, are you going?
If not, I'm going to go now.
Wait for me, Gene.
The series is starting to shoot soon.
Do you remember your lines yet?
I've read it but I haven't practiced yet.
So I'm a bit stuck about the character.
Oh, yeah. Last time you said you were
going to ask me about the character.
You can ask me, don't need to hold back.
Then when we get back to the room...
Can you help me practice my lines?
What? Help you practice?
Yes.
Acting and reading the scripts
isn't really what I'm good at.
And it's weird to write it and read it.
You just read the lines to answer me,
no need for acting.
Just reading it?
Can you say the lines? No way.
I can, you just have to read them.
Please? Can you?
Do you know what you've done?
Gene.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
Clumsy.
I'll wash it for you.
Never mind.
Then what do you want me to do?
Just clean it and don't leave a mess
that will make me mad.
But it's not...
Can I...
Shit.
I'm sorry, Gene, are you hurt?
No.
It doesn't hurt.
Does it have to be that real?
Maybe we should just read the lines?
But reading is not
like acting out the lines...
to make it realistic and I don't
mess it up while I'm on set.
But you're practicing really hard
so I think it's going to be realistic.
And you're making me
play this role, I don't want to.
I'll act it out
and you just read it, okay?
Act alone? That's weird.
Or do you want to join?
No.
Just read it, that's enough.
You look innocent
but you're pretty stubborn.
Wait, what are you going to do?
Practicing my lines.
But this is a kissing scene?
You want to act this one out?
Do you care about the kissing?
No, I'm okay with it
but do we really have to kiss?
On set,
I have to play it with a guy any way.
But I'm not an actor.
Then...
What were you feeling
when you were writing this?
The reason I want to try...
because I want to know how you feel.
If you're not comfortable with kissing,
then never mind.
I don't want to put you
in an uncomfortable position.
Fine, we can kiss.
I said it's fine if we kiss,
I don't see anything wrong with.
Another thing is I wrote this scene.
Are you sure?
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
Just kiss me already.
In this script you have to be startled...
but you can keep your eyes closed.
Those soft lips
slowly moved on to my lip...
making me feel hot,
warm and soft.
The moment it touched my lips,
I froze like my body was
making me wait...
out the shock on purpose.
I felt a strange tingle, my mind...
went blank while my face was burning.
Sounds of moaning crept from my lips.
Barings his tounge unto my teeth.
While delicately placing those soft lips.
Pushing out and pulling in until.
I felt my breath shorten
but I couldn't break away.
Scared that I would break
from the character I was playing
Cut!
This is a Boy Love series!
The kiss has to be passionate and hot!
Gene? When did you get here?
Don't worry, I'll be your guardian.
I think you're cute.
That's dangerous, be careful!
But from now I want hot and steamy scenes.
Gene?
A sex scene.
If I help, you might finish early.
Are you for real?
You don't need to worry.
I learned it in a Workshop.