[English subtitles are available]
[Cohabitation Agreement]
[Jang Ki-yong, Lee Hye-ri]
[Kang Han-na, Kim Do-wan]
[Bae In-hyuk, Park Gyeong-hye]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]
Actually, there's something
I want to tell you.
It may be too early to say,
but I think you'll be excited to hear it.
What is it?
Well...
My goodness!
What are you two doing?
[My magic suddenly wouldn't work.]
You can feel it when I'm in danger.
[And I can't feel any ominous signs
or people's energy.]
Maybe you're about to become a human!
I might...
I was wrong.
What?
I think
the end is near.
What do you mean, the end is near?
Will you be a human soon?
I mean, if you can't use any magic
and can't feel anything,
it means you've become ordinary.
My gosh.
Congratulations.
["Goryeo, the Truths
and Misconceptions of History"]
[Professor of History, Shin Woo-yeo]
Ta-da.
[Bye, Gumiho.]
I prepared this to celebrate
after hearing you'll be a human soon.
Say goodbye to the long, tiring years
you've lived as a gumiho,
and I hope you become a human soon.
Wait, maybe we should
grab a drink tonight to celebrate.
Well, I guess it could be a bore
to open the champagne too soon.
Okay, on the day you become a human,
I'll get 100 bottles of champagne for you.
What's wrong? What's with that face?
So everything was
a sign of your dissipation.
You couldn't use your magic,
you lost your sixth sense,
and your hand began to disappear.
You still have a few months
until your 1,000th year. So why already?
We have no time to sit here.
Let's go meet the old man.
If we can find out what's going on...
I've been looking for him.
But he won't give me a response.
What?
I'm sure it's not a big deal.
That old man can be pretty nasty,
but he's not the type
who would break his deadline.
So don't get scared,
and focus on coloring the Marble blue.
You can become a human
before you get vanished.
But you know...
Hey, Dan. Is everything all right?
-Have you had lunch?
[-I'm fine.]
Why do you sound so down?
Is something going on?
Did I keep you waiting for long?
I did wait for a while,
but it's all right. You're pretty.
Gosh, that just made my heart race.
When I sit here like this,
all I can think about is you.
So I'll continue to do my best.
If anything, for your sake.
Actually, I got too excited
to sleep last night.
But I have to be away from home
for a few days at this important time.
I'm sorry.
I just got off the phone with Dan.
He'll be in a tournament in a few days,
but his record hasn't been too great.
So it seems like I need to go home
and help him stay calm.
You've been doing well,
so let me go home for a few days.
-Don't go.
-What?
I need you too.
It's not like I'll be gone forever.
It'll be just a few days.
So you don't want to be separated
for even a moment?
No, I don't.
What is this?
It feels like you're too controlling,
but why do I somehow feel nice?
Your brother is an archer, right?
Who is he?
[Final Episode]
Oh, you should meet him.
He's my boyfriend.
Please. Don't say something
that can offend other people.
I'm sorry.
My sister can sometimes be insane.
Hey, he really is my boyfriend.
Nice to meet you.
What? Are you serious?
What? Why? Why are you her boyfriend?
Did she blackmail you?
Or did you lose a fight?
What's wrong with you?
He really is my boyfriend.
He came to give you advice
to get you out of your slump.
Right?
He used to shoot a little.
Were you a professional archer?
That's not exactly the case.
I don't know about this.
Professional archery is different.
I'm not doing this as a hobby,
and I'm a reservist on the national team,
so I've already worked
with all kinds of coaches.
May I borrow this for a moment?
That's an expensive bow.
What? He's holding the bow like that?
Do you want to give it a try?
Your shoulder will hurt less
if you fix your posture a little.
My gosh. How did you know
my shoulder is in pain?
-Shall we?
-Yes, Brother-in-law.
What's with you? Brother-in-law?
What's with that guy?
My gosh. He just met him.
But a brother-in-law?
Gosh.
I think your advice was helpful.
He broke his old record.
He asked me to thank his brother-in-law.
Why does he keep calling you that?
Why not? I like it.
Get a good rest, then.
Thank you.
I know you did that for my sake.
And it was also for me.
Your brother needed to be all right
for me to have you by my side.
And to be honest,
I wanted to meet your family.
Sir, you really seem to have changed.
You wouldn't even say hi to him before
and used your magic to disappear.
But you wanted to meet him first,
so you had me surprised.
You said it seems like the end is near.
Maybe you've become a human already.
It'd be great if I have.
Come in.
You aren't asleep yet.
-I wanted to sleep with you.
-What?
I'm going to sleep next to you
every single day.
-Wait, why?
-I told you before.
I never want to be away from you.
-Miss Dam.
-Yes?
Let's fall asleep together
every night.
Do you want simple toast for breakfast?
But you don't like eating a simple meal.
That's true.
We both don't have any class now,
so let's go out and eat.
Why do you always tempt me with food?
You make my heart race.
I'll get dressed, then.
I put together
something like this.
Ta-da.
I asked you for the things
you wanted to do the most
when you become a human,
and you said you weren't sure.
So I tried making a list for you.
Now, look.
Number one,
lining up at a good restaurant.
[Things to do when my sir
becomes a human: Bucket List]
It's really tough to line up for hours
unless you're seriously craving that food.
So I wanted to do that
when you actually have an appetite.
And number two, looking after your health.
The human health can fail
from time to time.
I was worried you might lose your health
once you suddenly become a human.
So I wanted to work out with you.
Miss Dam.
Let's discuss the future later.
What do you want to do now?
Now? We have to go to class.
I don't want to go to school.
Let's cut class.
Almost there! Yes!
Let me help you.
-Magic, right?
-Skills.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
I always wanted to come here.
I'm the one who wanted to cut class today,
but you seem to be having more fun.
Well, it is fun,
but I can't do this anymore.
I have to raise my GPA.
Okay.
Let's go over there.
[Only good things for my family!]
[I hope my family stays healthy.]
Look at all these people's wishes.
You should make a wish too.
Me?
No, thanks. I've been traumatized
after making a wish.
Traumatized?
When we went on that trip together,
I made a wish on the stone tower,
but you erased my memories,
and our relationship ended.
I'm scared of making wishes now.
Did you have a tough time
back then?
Of course.
You can't end a relationship like that.
You know, going out of touch is
the worst breakup.
I still think that was really harsh.
You made me really sad.
Then in your opinion,
what do you think makes a good breakup?
A good breakup?
A good breakup.
That's like happy starvation.
Isn't that an oxymoron?
I'm not sure what a good breakup is,
but I just hope it's nothing too sudden.
It's heartbreaking to say goodbye
without any preparation.
You'd need some time to accept it,
and you should say one last goodbye.
Let's go.
Sir.
Where did he go?
Sir, what just happened?
Well, it's...
That was an awful prank.
You really shocked me.
Don't ever disappear without a word.
[You know,]
will it be okay for you and her
to live in the same house?
If by any chance
she sees
your disappearance,
she'll be greatly shocked.
[It'll be greatly shocking.]
[And]
[I'm worried too.]
[I'm afraid]
[she'll be left alone here
once I disappear.]
[She might end up]
[crying alone.]
You want me to return home?
All of a sudden? Why?
Come to think of it,
you should be there for your brother.
I've been too selfish.
But I promised to stay here
until you become a human.
You've been of great help,
so I think it'll be fine now.
Goodbye, then.
Sir, did I do something?
When I wanted to go home for a few days,
you held me back saying
you wanted to be with me.
So it feels kind of odd to have you
kick me out this late at night.
Is there another reason?
There's no other reason.
I feel a little sad and lonely
to think I'll be away from you.
And it's making me a little sadder
to see you seem so fine.
Bye.
No.
What brings you here this late?
You said you haven't been sleeping well,
so I brought you some wine.
If you drink a moderate amount,
it's supposed to help you sleep well.
Thanks.
-Do you want to come in?
-Sure.
Do you want some too?
No, I said I'd be home soon,
so I have to go.
Anyway, it's not because
something is bothering you, right?
It's not.
-Should I leave it there?
-Yes.
Have a glass of wine, then sleep well.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
What's this? It's very antique.
Antique? It's just a very old article.
Yes, that means it's antique.
Oh, really?
It looks really old.
Did you get it from your mom?
I don't have a mom.
I see. Then was it from your dad?
I don't have a dad either.
-Did they pass away?
-I never had any.
What?
I'm sorry.
She had no family.
She must've been lonely.
All right. From now on,
I'm going to stay by her side.
I won't ever let her be alone.
What's this?
[Commissioner of Seoul Regional
Military Manpower Administration]
Military Manpower Administration?
My gosh. You startled me.
Why did you suddenly come?
I suddenly wanted to grab a drink.
Then come in through the door.
I wanted to see
if I could still use magic.
You must be unbelievably troubled
to be drinking, on top of that, with me.
It was a relief to have you around.
Are you
saying that to me right now?
Yes, you.
I know you're concerned about me.
You disappeared, then showed up again
right before my 1,000th year
because you were worried about me.
I know that.
Thank you for everything.
Don't do that.
Don't say goodbye
as if this is your last moment.
Let me ask you for a favor.
I'm going to share the truth
with Miss Dam.
So...
I think the end is near.
Then in your opinion,
what do you think makes a good breakup?
That was an awful prank.
Well, it's...
Wasn't it a prank
when he suddenly disappeared?
Come in.
What? Weren't you staying with Soo-kyung
until summer break? Why are you here?
I wanted to focus on my studies,
so I came home.
I see.
Anyway, is my brother-in-law leaving?
-No, why?
-When he came to help me,
he asked me to look after you.
And he sounded like someone
who's about to go somewhere far away.
Dam!
[I can't bring myself to tell you]
[when I'm with you.]
[So I write this letter hoping
you won't ever have to see this.]
[It seems like I'll have to let go]
[of this long life I lived.]
[Yes.]
[I've lived this life]
[for such a long time.]
[I've been through too much.]
[I was tired of everything
as if I have stayed up all night.]
[At times,
I felt weary to face another day.]
[Things were like that
until the moment I met you.]
[You were my only joy,]
[the only reason
why I waited to face another day.]
[Perhaps I knew from the beginning.]
[That you would]
[change my destiny.]
Sir, I'm on my way right now.
And you know,
did you mean something else
when you said the end is near?
I have a weird feeling about this.
Sir.
Sir!
[Perhaps I knew from the beginning.]
[That you would]
[change my destiny.]
[bring meaning into my meaningless]
[and worthless life.]
[I can't bring myself to tell you
when I'm with you.]
My sir disappeared.
He was trying to save me. It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
If anything, we should blame destiny.
Don't blame yourself.
There's no such thing as destiny!
He promised he'd stay by my side.
This is just not fair.
[I can't bring myself to tell you
when I'm with you.]
Dam, aren't you going to eat?
What's wrong?
Wait. Why is he...
He's not gone yet.
If I wait,
he might come back.
[I needed the vain hope ]
[to hold on]
[to get through the times. ]
It's spring.
[Spring came,]
[but I didn't feel warm at all.]
[I was still living in the cold winter.]
Until when will you stay here?
Until he comes back.
He's not coming back.
He can't.
Now I get why he asked me this favor.
He knew you'd be silly like this.
"Favor"?
What do you mean?
If Dam seems to have a hard time
after I disappear,
could you erase her memories
using your Marble?
Do you even hear yourself?
You know how hard it was
for me to turn the Marble blue.
The mountain spirit is
granting me one wish,
and you want me to use it for you?
You know what?
I’ve been saving that blue Marble
for a once-in-a-lifetime emergency
just in case
I have trouble with the human society.
Why don't you try
to become a human instead?
Don't give up until the end.
I'm sorry. Please do me the favor.
This is the final decision he made
after living 1,000 years.
He wants you to be happy
even if you don't remember him at all.
Miss Dam.
[I take pity on you
and will make your wish come true.]
[Before 1,000 years is up,]
[before you grow more than nine tails,]
[if you manage to learn to be patient,]
[to love,]
[to sacrifice,]
[and to eventually
find a reason to live...]
[If someone who desperately
wishes you to live is waiting...]
No.
I don't want to forget a single moment.
Even if I have to be heartbroken
for the rest of my life
and even if I can never see him again.
How have you been, Miss Dam?
[Before 1,000 years is up,
before you grow more than 9 tails,]
[if you manage to learn to be patient,
to love, to sacrifice,]
[and to eventually
find a reason to live...]
[If someone who desperately
wishes you to live is waiting,]
[you will turn into a human.]
Hye-sun, I'm here.
What's wrong?
I can't believe this happened.
Why are you crying?
-I'm so relieved.
-What?
-It's okay.
-I thought he was really dead.
He's not. It's okay.
I'm so relieved.
Fragile. Easily broken. Gosh.
Fragile. Easily broken.
[Military Service, D-7]
There's only one week left
until you start the military service.
Poor you.
Hye-sun must be crying every night.
No. I'm the one who is crying every night.
Hye-sun doesn't know about it yet.
I couldn't tell her.
Not yet? What were you thinking?
Did you tell her
why you were taking a year off then?
I just said I had a situation.
The thing is, whenever I told my exes
that I was going to the army,
they dumped me right away.
I'm afraid Hye-sun wants
to break up with me too.
You're afraid of what?
What is it? What is it
that you're so afraid of?
-Actually, Jae-jin is...
-Ghosts.
-I'm afraid of ghosts.
-What? Ghosts?
Yes. I'm usually a tough man,
so I understand this may look odd,
but in fact, I'm very scared of ghosts.
Vampires, Satan's doll, Gumiho...
They're so scary.
Even Gumiho?
Of course. They take humans' livers.
Gosh, it creeps me out.
[I didn't take any human's liver,]
[but I guess it's better to keep it
a secret that I was a Gumiho.]
[I will have to tell her
the secret at some point.]
[Gosh, when should I tell her
I'm going to the army?]
By the way,
I don't see Dam around these days.
Right. Professor Shin is back, so I guess
she's busy hanging out with him.
He must be busy.
He's practically reborn, so there must be
so many things he wants to do.
"Reborn"?
Well, that distant cousin of mine
was seriously ill.
He didn't want to worry Dam,
so he didn't tell her
he was going abroad to get treatment.
Now he's fully recovered,
he's practically reborn.
He was ill?
Anyway, they must be having fun.
Every single day must be
so precious to them.
-Is that the place?
-Yes.
[Granny's Stir-Fried Octopus]
I think we will have to wait for at least
an hour. Are you okay with that?
Of course.
I have this interesting new desire
called appetite now,
so I'm more than happy to wait.
If you're pushing yourself
because of my bucket list...
I'm not pushing myself.
While I was away,
I endured the time, thinking about
queuing with you for restaurants.
Thank you for waiting.
You're saying that
in front of Granny's Stir-Fried Octopus?
Let's talk about the details
when we stir-fry the rice.
-Sounds good.
-I can't wait.
I'm sorry. We ran out of ingredients.
Please come again next time.
[Sorry, we are closed.]
No way. I was so close to taste
the chewy octopus, crunchy bean sprouts,
and the sweet and spicy sauce.
And I was so excited to stir-fry rice
with the sweet and spicy sauce
and then eat it with shredded dried laver.
Now you're speaking my language.
But don't be disappointed yet.
I'll make it for you at home.
What? With your cooking skills?
Why don't we get some food delivered?
Miss Dam.
I was a horrible cook
only when I was a Gumiho.
Since I got the sense of taste,
I've become interested in cooking.
And my cooking skills have
significantly improved.
You won't be disappointed.
How did you stir-fry the octopus
to make the kitchen look so...
What's important is
that I managed to quell the fire
without panicking.
And a company will soon
come and renovate this place.
Obviously you worked really hard for it.
So I can't even nag at you.
We should have ordered food
in the first place.
-Is there anything you'd like to eat?
-Pork backbone soup.
Yum woon sen, garlic chicken,
spicy jokbal, sandwich.
These just crossed my mind. Pick one.
A man who can name so many dishes
that he craves. So attractive.
Shall we start with some sandwiches then?
[Order]
What would you like to have?
-I'd like a shrimp sandwich.
-Shrimp.
I'm bored.
When do you think you'll be done?
How could you do this to a person
who almost died?
I'm in my senior year.
I should work myself to death.
I need to get a job soon.
I envy you. You don't need to get a job.
I'm getting a job too.
But I can't change my career so often
any more, so I'll be careful.
Then why don't you continue to write?
Many people liked your writing.
You got a lot of comments too.
-Really?
-Yes.
"So touching", "This is so much fun",
"This is so stupid.
Has the writer ever learned history?"
"Stop writing..."
-Let me...
-No, I don't think that's necessary.
Kids these days are so spoiled.
Back in the days,
you had to walk all the way
to the capital city to file complaints.
But now, all you need to do
is to type the keyboards.
Sir, you're a human now.
Why don't you stop talking about the past?
It's already past 10 p.m.
You should go to bed now.
You must be tired.
Why do I have to go to bed early?
I'm not a child.
Well, you're not nocturnal any more,
so I thought you might be tired.
Tired? I'm just as healthy
as I was before.
I've been exercising
for a thousand years to stay fit.
Right. Speaking of which,
let me bring you some healthy tea.
Why are you taking vitamins?
You said you were just as healthy.
I'm taking it for you.
Taking care of each other's health
was also on your bucket list.
Oh, I see. You did it for me.
Looks like Seon-woo is
leaving for good tomorrow.
Until now, he was only visiting the place
for the meetings and all.
Have you been in touch with him?
What? I read it in the group chat.
Awesome.
I can use your room now.
Your room is bigger
and your desk is better than mine.
What's the point of having a good desk
when you never sit at it?
You're like a trip I look forward to.
Because I want you to leave
as soon as possible.
Be nice to your brother.
Come on and get in.
Take this and get lost.
[I have too many things to carry anyway.
You can have it if you like.]
Seon-woo.
I'm happy, but I'm sad.
I'm sad, but I'm happy.
This is all because
of that Dan or whatever's sister.
If only she didn't dump my brother,
he wouldn't have had to leave so sadly.
My bag! Hey!
Give me my bag!
-Hey! Stop there!
-Throw it.
-Hey.
-Darn it.
See if you got everything.
-Congratulations.
-Cheers.
-This is nice.
-You can drink as much as you like.
I promised I'd buy him 100 bottles
of champagne when he becomes a human.
I would like to ring the silver bell
if there was one here.
You mean, the golden bell.
You'd better treat me well.
Since I became a human first,
I have a lot of useful tips to offer.
I don't know.
You may have become a human first,
but your case was much easier.
So I'm not sure about that.
-What?
-Goodness.
You see,
my hand almost disappeared,
and my Marble cracked.
I experienced all kinds of bad omens
and even nearly died
before I finally became a human.
Compared to that,
I feel like you didn't do anything.
You feel like I didn't do anything?
I went through a lot too.
Breaking up with a man tore my heart out,
but then I fell in love again.
Then I got my heart broken again.
Then I fell in love again.
If I had collected all the tears I shed
to become a human,
it would've made a whole river.
And you got lucky
because of the mountain spirit's trap.
-I got lucky?
-Am I wrong?
It was a test to see
if you would sacrifice your life for her,
and you fell for it.
Stop acting like you're so cool
because you're not.
I'm not just acting.
I was willing to sacrifice my life
for someone I love.
I learned how to love, to be patient,
and to sacrifice.
So I found a reason to live,
which means I acquired humanity...
I can't hear you.
-I'm not done yet...
-I can't hear you.
Come on. Every time I hear this story,
it touches my heart.
I especially like the part
that hearing me cry woke you up.
It means you could come back
because I waited for you.
Right, Woo-yeo?
That's right, Dam.
When is Jae-jin coming?
Why don't you talk about
your sweet story when you're alone?
Let me go get some water.
-I'll go get some water.
-I'll come with you.
You take care of this. Okay?
Take care of what?
Gosh.
Well, it is kind of nice
that they're unswayed by it.
I don't like having secrets either.
Hye-sun.
Jae-jin, what took you so long?
You've been away for so long.
I don't want you to get sick tomorrow,
so I got you some hangover pills.
[Maybe I should tell him now.]
[Even if I get dumped after that.]
[I should tell her now.]
[Even if she dumps me after that.]
-Actually...
You go first.
-I used to be a Gumiho.
-What?
I was a Gumiho for over 700 years
until I became a human five years ago.
You seem quite drunk.
You should take the pills.
I'm not drunk. It's true.
That's why I don't have parents or family.
Believe it or not, that is how it is.
If you don't like that,
we can just break up.
Hye-sun, why would you say that?
Whether this is a joke
or your drunk talk, I don't care.
Even if you actually used to be a Gumiho.
-What?
-Even if you're still a Gumiho,
I really don't care.
I can give you my liver and everything.
I probably shouldn't be saying this
in this situation.
I don't want to burden you.
What about the situation?
Right. You also wanted
to say something to me.
What is it?
The thing is...
-I'm entering the army.
-What?
When?
The day after tomorrow.
Why are you saying this now?
I was afraid you would break up with me
when I say it.
Jae-jin.
Why would you say that?
How long is it these days?
About a year and a half.
Compared to 700 years, that's nothing.
-I'll wait.
-What?
It's okay. I don't want to trouble you.
You don't want me to wait then?
I want you to wait.
I'll be a cool man when I'm back.
You're not so bad already.
My, Jae-jin!
Oh, no. Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
-I'm just messing with you.
-Hey!
You and Hye-sun seem like
really good friends.
You may say mean things to each other,
but she was really happy
when you came back as a human.
Well, she wouldn't have been
happier than me though.
To be honest, I was really scared.
I was afraid you might never come back.
I was afraid too
that I might never be able
to come back to you.
What's the biggest change you noticed
since you've become a human?
Sometimes, I realize I didn't know
how chilly the air was at night.
And
sometimes, I want to sleep until late.
[Actually, nothing much has changed.]
[My heart still flutters when I see you.]
Hey, Dan.
Congratulations on winning the gold medal.
[Strawberry Milk]
Thanks. But why would you congratulate...
I don't like talkative men.
-Why are you suddenly holding...
-Shush.
I don't like questions either.
You got some money as a prize,
so tteokbokki is on you.
I didn't know we were that close.
We are. Starting today.
Because
I'm going out with you starting today.
-What?
-Let's go.
Wait. Why so suddenly...
We really don't have much time left now.
I know.
Hold on a second.
I made a list of good restaurants.
[List of Good Restaurants]
And this is a first-aid kit.
Please don't get sick while I'm gone.
What do I do?
I'm going to miss you so much.
I really don't want to go.
When I think about
how lonely you'd be alone,
I just don't want to leave.
I see.
[I still want you by my side.]
His username is Handsome Face?
He must be really handsome.
They're friends,
so they must be both handsome.
Right? I'm so excited!
Hello, are you Wingless Angel?
I'm Handsome Face, Kim Moo-geun...
-What are you doing here?
-What's this?
You're Handsome Face?
You should be Gruesome Face!
Delete that dating app right now.
What about you?
You're Wingless Angel?
[Sometimes, something unexpected
may come up]
[and trouble us again.]
So you had a fight and then left?
Hey, grow up.
[Whatever. Are the girls there pretty?]
[If you make a girlfriend in a week,
I'll wire you 100,000 won.]
I don't do bets any more.
[But like I always have,]
[I will change to get along with you.]
Hi, Soo-kyung.
I liked your presentation today.
Right.
I know, but thank you anyway.
I'm sorry.
[You will]
[always be my destiny.]
Miss Dam.
You were supposed to keep the Marble,
not fall in love with its owner.
You were supposed to steal my energy,
not my heart.
Then
since we ended up falling in love
despite death,
let's stay together for a long time.
Shall we go home now?
Yes. Let's go home.
[Thank you for watching
My Roommate is a Gumiho.]
[Bye, Gumiho.]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]