[English subtitles are available]
[21st. The tenth. Ai heads to Africa. ]
[One more week left]
[till Mr. Ai heads to Africa.]
[I need to complete the research
on Africa for Mr. Ai.]
[A Medical Volunteer's 10 years in Africa]
What are the African viruses?
[Baidu: What are the African viruses?]
There are a number of viruses
originating from Africa.
The main causes include...
Zeng Li.
How many books have you
read about Africa?
The locals wouldn't
understand Africa as much as you do.
Mr. Ai is a busy man.
He probably doesn't have time to read,
but I do.
I shall help him
with the research.
That way, he could leave at ease.
He may leave at ease,
but could you be at ease?
Let me take a look.
The Lassa Virus
is transmitted to humans
through contact with
urine of Mastomys rats.
That's frightening.
You should try stopping Mr. Ai
to cancel his trip.
Mr. Ai has his reasons to do so.
I respect that.
When people are in love,
their intelligence would deteriorate.
You should
beg him
and behave adorably around him.
Who knows he might
not go after all?
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 20]
[Recommendation Form for
Foreign Aid Medical Volunteers]
[Name: Ai Jing Chu]
I've decided, Mr. Ai.
I'll go instead.
It's fine.
You were volunteering
on my behalf in the first place.
I've always wanted to go.
I registered last year.
You just started a relationship.
Things aren't stable yet.
Things are fine. Don't worry.
What happens
if Ms. Zeng finds someone else
during the next six months?
You should go.
Of course she wouldn't.
I was just kidding.
Ms. Zeng is smitten with you.
Forget about six months.
Even if it takes three years,
she would wait for you.
[Service Period of Choice: Six Months]
Mr. Ai, run faster.
Zeng Li.
Something's weird today.
Back at home,
you kept stuffing me with food.
Next, you got me to jog when we're out.
What's the matter?
Are you trying to get me
into the national team?
No.
I read a book today.
It says,
Africa is a seedbed of
various viruses.
Although vaccinations are available,
a small number of viruses
still rely
on humans' own immunity to resist.
Thus, you should
maintain a balanced diet
and strengthen your body.
That way,
my Mr. Ai
will not be defeated by the viruses.
Next up,
my girlfriend's next book
would be titled African Strategy.
You're teasing me, Mr. Ai.
The file I sent to you,
have you read it yet?
Of course.
I spent an hour reading every day.
That's good.
By the way, Zeng Li,
I've something I meant to ask.
You stopped
trying to convince me not to go.
If I tried to stop you,
would you listen?
Yes.
The more I shouldn't stop you.
You're responsible
and compassionate.
Volunteering at the medical aid of Africa
is something you've always wanted to do.
Places with unfavourable conditions
need more doctors.
Your job isn't only to treat illnesses,
you're saving lives.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just suddenly
realised I finally found someone
just like me.
Previously, I've always thought
of myself as the loneliest person.
For the remaining 27 days,
I'm going to cling on you
like a koala bear.
Okay?
Okay.
What kind of a koala
are you?
This koala bear could ride a bike.
Would you like to
join me with a jog?
Okay.
Let's
run with weights.
With weights?
Let's go.
However, I realised
you sure
are well-fed.
What do you mean?
In a while,
carry that
bike along as well.
No.
Hurry up.
I don't want to.
You called me heavy.
That's enough.
Okay.
What did you find out?
Recently, are you experiencing
dry mouth,
fatigue and tightness in the chess?
After falling asleep,
you'd sweat and feel irritable.
Not bad at all.
This is a sign of asthenia of renal yin.
That's because of
imbalance amount of work and rest,
and bad eating habits.
Over consumption of
greasy
and spicy foods contribute to this.
What else is wrong with me?
Here.
Physician Liu,
please examine my pulse.
What's wrong?
This is the pregnancy pulse.
I gave you the green light
and you've started to spew nonsense.
What are you talking about?
It's really similar.
However, it also could be
the slippery pulse caused
by spleen deficiency.
I'll check your pulse once more.
Forget it.
You're diagnosing me
with the pregnancy pulse.
If you go on,
I'd probably end up
with a terminal illness.
No.
Has your menstrual cycle been consistent?
Yes.
It cannot be any more consistent.
I'll prescribe you to some
medication to
strengthen your spleen.
You will feel better after that.
I've learnt a lot
of new remedies from
Physician Liu recently.
Are you addicted to diagnosing patients?
Go and get a shower.
I'm going to take a shower.
Go.
[Today: 11th April, 2021.]
[I think my period is one week late.]
Is this accurate?
I read this online.
They make mistakes sometimes.
I brought the remaining
nine kits I tested on.
Would you like to take a look?
No. It's fine.
I was just kidding.
I threw the other nine that
showed two stripes away.
What are you and Liu Yu Cheng
planning to do?
Are you holding a wedding ceremony?
For safety purposes,
it's better to host the wedding
after giving birth to the child.
No.
Think about it.
Once your tummy grows,
you wouldn't look good in a wedding dress.
No.
Eating too much
would give the same effect too.
Guys.
Are you eating or not?
-Of course.
She has a large appetite
since she's eating for two.
I need to prep my body well
for the surgery.
What do you mean?
It's not the right time
to have a baby.
It's too abrupt for
Liu Yu Cheng.
I support you.
Realistically speaking,
I cannot imagine
Liu Yu Cheng as a father.
He's pretty young after all.
He
probably has nothing figured out.
Think about it properly.
You may discuss this matter with
Liu Yu Cheng as well.
I've made my decision.
That's it.
We're settling this matter on this table.
I only told the both of you.
Do not tell anyone else.
Okay.
I promise.
This is the part.
It's really funny.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Is something troubling you?
Nothing much.
Clearly, something is up.
Tell me.
Mr. Ai.
I need to tell you something,
but you're not
allowed to tell anyone,
especially Liu Yu Cheng.
I need to hear about it first
before making a decision.
[Mr. Ai]
Who is it?
Mr. Ai.
Hello, Mr. Ai.
I need to tell you something.
No, you can't.
-Go on. I'm listening.
-Wait.
You can't tell him.
If you do,
I'm breaking up with you.
-I'm begging you.
-Wu Ying...
You can't tell him.
She's pregnant.
I can't believe you told him.
You...
You found out?
Zeng Li, that traitor.
Don't worry.
I'll resolve the matter.
What do you mean?
I'm undergoing the surgery next week.
What kind of surgery?
An abortion.
Why would you abort it?
Have you decided to do this
without telling me?
Besides,
it's a life.
Calm down.
Listen to me.
Come here. Take a seat.
Come over here.
Sit.
Think about it logically.
You're only 21 this year.
Are you going to be a father?
Let's talk after you think it through.
I'm going to take a shower.
Wu Ying.
Let's give birth to the baby.
I don't mind complying
with you for other matters,
but this isn't a joke.
Wu Ying is pregnant with the child.
She has the rights to make the decision.
The child belongs to Liu Yu Cheng too.
He has the rights to know.
No.
Wu Ying made up her mind.
If you told Liu Yu Cheng about this,
it'd only cause more troubles.
Think from another perspective, Zeng Li.
If I was in
Liu Yu Cheng's shoes,
if you made
such a decision on your own,
I'd be enraged.
Fine.
Think about it from another perspective.
If you're mad
over this matter,
I think you do not understand me at all.
You're being selfish.
Do you hate kids?
No.
It's not a problem then.
You like kids,
so do I.
You love me,
and I love you too.
Once the child is born,
the three of us
would love each other.
Isn't that great?
I like children,
but that doesn't mean
I'm giving birth now.
Having a child is not
within my plan right now.
Do you understand?
But...
There will always be
changes in your life's plan.
Forget it.
We're not discussing
this matter anymore.
I'm the child's father.
You can't ignore my view
completely.
Fine.
Your view
is to keep the child.
Yes.
However, my view
is to undergo abortion.
It's decided.
Go to bed.
You said,
this is a matter between the both of them.
Why would we interfere?
This is bad.
Wu Ying would kill me.
I didn't want to get involved,
but since I found out,
I must deal with the
situation the way I deem right.
Hold on.
Right now, I feel like
I've betrayed my best friend.
Since we were kids,
I betrayed her for the first time.
You already told me.
You...
Since you've decided
to tell me about this,
it shows that
subconsciously, you agree
it is inappropriate to keep this
from Liu Yu Cheng.
No.
That's because
you're my boyfriend.
The both of us should
keep this secret together.
It feels like
the person I trust the most
just betrayed me.
The core of this issue
lies in the respect
two must give each other
when they are together.
Fine.
Teacher.
You're the best at reasoning, alright?
Whatever the reasons are,
none of it matter.
I can't convince you anyway.
I'm done talking, okay?
Zeng Li.
[WeChat: Currently]
[No new notifications.]
[Are you mad at me?]
[Congratulations. This is very dangerous.]
-That means you care about me.
-What?
Mr. Ai, I told you
not to tell anyone.
Especially Liu Yu Cheng.
How could you tell him?
Since when
have you become so nosy?
Grandpa, I want this one.
Sure, go ahead.
Hold on.
Come here.
Grandpa. Auntie.
Uncle, Xiao Xiao.
Good morning.
Good morning, sister.
Xiao Zeng, time for breakfast.
Xiao Chu isn't wake yet.
Go and wake him up.
I'm running late.
I'm skipping breakfast.
I shall get going.
You're in a hurry to leave?
It's only 8 in the morning.
Bye.
Xiao Zeng is running late for work.
Hurry up and send her off.
Stop standing around.
Hurry over.
Hurry up.
Go on.
Yes, I'm moving in as soon as possible.
Stop the construction if possible.
It's fine, sir.
There's no need to get into the details.
Zeng Li, I...
If possible, please finish up by tomorrow.
Okay. Thanks, sir.
[Hello.]
Sir.
Previously, I mentioned
besides the living hall,
the other rooms
require complete waterproofing as well.
The construction cannot be
finished by tomorrow, right?
[If I were to complete it all,]
[I wouldn't make it anyhow.]
There's no need to rush the construction.
We're not in a haste.
[The female tenant just]
[called me,]
[asking me to wrap it up.]
It's fine. I'm paying anyway.
Just listen to me.
Make sure everything is safe.
[All right. Sure.]
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Boss.
You can't ignore your customers.
I've been waiting forever.
Why aren't you taking my order?
Customers are always right.
How could you ignore customers?
What else are you trying to say?
Go on.
I was wrong last night.
Is this considered
an argument?
Yes.
Arguments
are something
all couples experience.
We need to resolve the matter proactively.
We shouldn't avoid them.
Sure.
Tell me. How should we resolve this?
I thought about it.
Since we've disagreements
about the child,
let's list out the pros and cons of
keeping the child.
Let's determine what are the
things we can overcome,
and what are the underlying issues.
That way,
we can make a better decision together.
I don't see a single benefit
this situation would bring us.
You may list the cons first.
Firstly,
I do not have plans
to have children right now.
It's impractical to have a child.
We're completely unprepared.
Besides,
taking care of a child is not
part of my three-year-plan.
I've a job to attend to.
This would greatly affect your job,
but I'll do my best to assist you
and minimise the concerns
you have.
Taking care of a child
is not as simple as you imagine.
You have not
graduated university.
It's too much pressure to raise a child.
That's the easiest thing to deal with.
My family
back in Malaysia is pretty well-off.
would support us completely.
I can study while
make a living.
If worse comes to worst,
I'll drop out.
I've a degree
in engineering anyway.
Finding a job wouldn't be an issue.
Once things settle down,
I'll proceed with my studies.
Are you implying that,
in order to give birth
to this child,
I should give my job up
while you drop out?
Do you think this is worth it?
Why not?
In order to resolve a problem,
we're creating
countless of troubles.
In my opinion, it is not worth it at all.
Wu Ying.
You're seeing
the child as a problem right now.
Thus, everything
related to the child would be a hassle.
However, if
you think of the child as a gift,
everything related to the child
would be a surprise.
Liu Yu Cheng,
you're a child yourself.
You're only thinking about the present
when considering a problem.
You've no plans for the consequences.
If we rush into getting married
and giving birth,
forming a family,
it's no different than
playing house.
I'm not playing house,
I'm being serious.
I thought about this
all night long.
I listed all the possibilities
and impossibilities.
[What to do/What not to do]
[We should keep the child.]
[We shouldn't abort the child.]
[We should believe that the child]
[would bring happiness.]
[We shouldn't see the child]
[as something unfortunate.]
Yes.
I may only be 21 this year,
but over the past 21 years,
no matter what I place my mind to,
I'll do my best to achieve it.
I'll bear responsibility to the end.
Be it studying Traditional
Chinese Medicine,
or falling in love with you,
wanting to take care of you
for the rest of my life,
they are all the same.
Go back to class.
I need to work.
The problem
doesn't lie in the child,
you do not have faith in me.
You do not want to build a family
with the child and I
for the rest of your life, right?
I don't want to
talk about this anymore.
Answer me.
You've never thought of me
as someone capable to be a father.
Right?
Yes.
Hence, in your heart,
this relationship
is only temporary.
That's not what I mean.
I get you now.
I'll think about it on my own.
I was wrong.
I didn't know
this would happen.
I shouldn't have told Mr. Ai.
I was wrong, Wu Ying.
That's enough.
I'm satisfied.
I was wrong.
Forget it.
Honestly, I knew
it is disrespectful to keep this
from Liu Yu Cheng.
Therefore,
do not ever say this
to your best friends.
Let me tell you something.
You mustn't tell anyone.
Because to your friends,
boyfriends aren't just anyone.
Someone without
a boyfriend like me
is more reliable,
right?
I caught the child's father
crying by the streets.
What's going on?
It wasn't me.
I swear.
I told you not to tell anyone.
I warned you.
You told me
not to tell anyone,
but you did not mention
about bringing this up
to the people involved.
How amazing.
One pregnancy
and it's made known to half of Donghu.
That's enough.
It's all my fault, alright?
Give me a chance
to make it up to all of you.
I'll take you guys some place fun.
[Ai Jing Chu]
[Darn that Mr. Ai.]
[He wouldn't reply my texts.]
Forget it then.
What's wrong, sister?
Is something wrong?
Did you argue with Dr. Ai
because of me?
Forget it.
Let's drink up.
-Cheers.
Let me summarise
the root of your problem.
Let's hear this
nonsense you come up with this time.
Listen to me.
The problem with you guys
is that you often drag your partners
into your circle of friends.
What is the point of your friends?
For you to vent.
Once you're done venting,
you return to where you belong.
After all that,
you return to the sweet
embrace of your partners.
On the contrary,
not only are you guys
in a relationship,
you even strengthened the friendship
between your boyfriends.
That's why issues would arise.
That actually makes sense.
Not exactly.
They were mentor and
apprentices to begin with.
They were already close without us.
That means you chose to date
the wrong people.
Stop looking for
men from the same circle.
If you do so,
it's easier for them to
form an alliance.
Do you understand?
Perhaps, this time,
Liu Yu Cheng and I
would break up for real.
It's not that serious.
Listen to me.
I rushed into
registering for marriage.
It shouldn't go to the extent
of breaking up.
That's unnecessary.
He insists to keep the child,
I refused.
Over a disagreement
as significant as this,
breaking up is the only
way to resolve this.
Hold on.
How dare you criticise us?
What's wrong with me?
Look at the relationships I had.
I've never introduced anyone
to the circle.
Yes, you haven't,
but you did not
explain yourself after
taking away one of us either.
Let's drink up.
Let's drink.
Come on.
Not so much.
♫ My old home ♫
♫ Is in this village ♫
♫ I grew up in ♫
♫ This village ♫
I thought Mr. Ai and I
would never argue.
Just a little over half a month,
we had our first argument.
Do you think
we're not meant for each other?
You're acting spoiled.
You're influenced by Ma Yi Yi.
I thought
the relationship we shared this time
would finally be the one,
but it was all futile.
The both of you rushed into a relationship
and marriage.
Things aren't worked out yet.
It's just an argument.
It gives flavour to your relationship.
You're right.
Yes, it destroys a relationship.
Are you deaf?
I don't want it
to destroy my relationship.
There, there.
If I make him look for me,
he'd get mad.
We're trying to get him mad.
[Ai Jing Chu]
Mr. Ai, I was wrong.
Please come to me right now.
I'll not
make you mad again.
Don't ignore my texts.
Don't worry, sister.
There's no need to apologise to family.
Bones may be broken, but
you're still connected.
Isn't that right?
Your voice changed.
You changed.
You changed after one day.
You can't do this.
This is...
Shut up.
Zeng Li, I'm here to pick you up.
Mr. Ai, is that you?
You're not allowed to leave.
I'm not leaving.
Do you have any idea
how much I like you?
All right.
No, I'm clinging onto you.
I'm clinging onto you.
You can't leave.
We shall make a move.
We should leave as well.
Let's go.
Get the bill.
We're going home.
The bill, please.
How much is it?
Watch out.
Hurry up and...
Watch your head.
I'm getting the bill.
-We can't go.
-Alright, sir.
Get him out of here.
Come on.
Mr. Ai.
Let's stop arguing, alright?
Okay.
I really like you.
I can't watch.
Dr. Ai.
Zeng Li's purse.
Okay, thanks.
Hurry up and go home.
Don't go.
I'll send you guys home first.
It's fine.
Once I send her off,
I'll leave on my own.
Go on.
Let's go.
This village...
-My old home...
-Yi Yi, get up.
Move it.
I live in this village.
-If you wouldn't budge,
-Don't sing anymore.
I'll leave you in this pit.
Watch out.
I'm driving.
Your head.
Your legs.
Next.
-My old home...
-Shut up.
Stay safe.
Bye.
I live in this village.
After learning how much I've done
for someone else,
are
you upset?
You and him shared a song.
We must share a song too.
Where are we going?
Let's have some fun and
do something crazy. Come on.
Do you remember this song?
Yes.
I'd never forget this
song for the rest of my life.
This shall be
our song from now on.
Okay.
Sister.
I remember you.
I don't want to waste her time.
Why would you waste
my time?
Because I like you.
I like who you are.
You're all I see.
Wu Ying.
I love you.
I want to be with you.
Can you stop calling my name?
What am I to you?
My boyfriend.
Well,
am I your boyfriend now?
You pervert. Stop it.
Wait, what are you doing?
The baby is a life.
Let's give birth to the baby.
I want to take care of you
for the rest of my life.
Taking care of a child
is not as simple as you imagine.
You're a child yourself.
You do not have faith in me.
You've never considered
building a family
with a child like me.
Hence, in your heart,
this relationship
is only temporary.
Right?
[Brat.]
[What's wrong with being a child?]
[If I force you to grow up
before you're ready,]
[you'd only resent me in the future.]
I don't know what
this child is up to.
She wouldn't answer my calls.
What does she need a phone for?
Seriously.
Good gracious.
Zeng Li.
Where is she?
Goodness.
How could this happen?
Excuse me.
Where is the tenant here?
Are you referring to this unit?
Yes.
Where did she move to?
Who are you?
I'm her mother.
Her deliveries were redelivered to
Yunxi Villas.
She probably moved there.
Yunxi Villas?
That isn't where Ma Yi Yi stays.
It's not where Wu Ying stays either.
What is she doing over there?
This child
wouldn't pick up my calls.
She didn't even inform me
over such a huge matter.
I'm so mad.
[Deng Hao Ran]
I just dropped him home
and he's calling me already.
What is it?
[What's the matter?]
Why are you laughing?
Speak.
Why are you poking at me?
Stop it.
Speak.
I'm hanging up if you won't.
How annoying. I'm hanging up.
One.
- [You chubby thing.]
-Two.
Three.
[Switch to voice call.
End call. Flip camera.]
She wouldn't pick up.
Over here.
Mr. Ai, where are we going?
Our house is over there.
A bug.
Let's go home.
Zeng Li?
Auntie.
Zeng Li.
Zeng Li, where have you been?
I called you many times.
You didn't pick up.
Mum.
Mum, why didn't you come earlier?
Don't be afraid.
I'll protect you.
Mum.