[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 16]
Have you ever been outside the Pass?
Yes.
The scenery's beautiful there.
Next spring,
I'll take you to Yanmen Pass.
Really?
Can I really go?
Why not?
I'm not sure.
What if Mother found out…
But it doesn't matter.
A general does not always follow the orders of His Majesty when abroad.
A daughter does not always follow the orders of her mother when she's not home!
Master.
What's wrong with Shiyi?
I accidentally stepped in a muddy pit
and twisted my ankle.
Prepare a coffin to bring to the Central state
and bring the grand mentor back.
As you command.
Wait.
After entering the capital,
find a way to meet Qin Yan
to find out
the whole story behind Grand Mentor Xie's illness.
Understood.
Do you think there is something off about his death?
There's no harm in knowing
what there is to know.
Let me carry you.
Ah, I'll go and have a talk with the deer.
♫Like a gust of wind gently brushing♫
♫Like a cloud waiting for the rain to fall♫
♫There is a corner in my heart♫
♫Where my expectation is glowing♫
♫It's the shooting star lighting up the night sky for you♫
♫There are so many wishes I want to say to you♫
♫There is still a hidden sore of longing♫
♫My thoughts stained three feet of white snow♫
♫Counting the days for your return over and over again♫
♫Flowers blossom and flowers fall, my heart only clings for you♫
♫My obsession is silent♫
♫I use all my life to guard only one person♫
♫I say nothing, only hoping to spend my life with you♫
Didn't you say you wanted to meet with Yun?
Yeah.
♫I'm full of love for you♫
Can you wash your feet by yourself?
♫Waiting to unlock the years of time♫
♫Our eyes will still be full of stars when we reunite♫
Of course.
Your Highness.
You can leave first.
Yes.
When you came to live here with me,
who sent you here? Do you still remember?
My adoptive mother.
Xie Chong is your biological father.
Your mother
is from the former empress dowager's family, the Gao family.
Master.
I had also considered this for a long time
before I decided to tell you the truth.
You are the smartest
among all my disciples.
You may guess
the reason why I hid it from you.
You were afraid the Qi family
would seek revenge and kill me.
Grand Mentor Xie wanted to hide it from you all your life.
But I don't hope
his son doesn't see him off after he died.
I was more afraid that,
if I died one day,
no one would
tell you the truth.
Face the Central State
to bid farewell to your father.
[Library]
General Hong is in Shouyang.
The young master went to Taiyuan to be a prefectural governor.
General Xie has stayed in Luyuan.
General Zhou went to the Central State.
And the rest of the generals are elsewhere.
Only you and General Feng
are left at the mansion.
You should have finished your apprenticeship earlier.
You have to leave sooner or later.
If it weren't for the late emperor's
delay in granting you a marriage,
you would have tied the knot long ago.
You wouldn't have had to wait till now.
I wanted to stay
to spend more time with my master.
My beloved mother.
I miss you dearly, as I've been away from home for so long.
Since Grand Mentor Xie is gone,
one thought has been gripping my heart,
making me uneasy all day long.
What did Shiyi say in the letter?
Something foolish.
My Ladies.
Palace Attendant Cui is coming,
and with him comes
a chamberlain
of the Prince of Guangling.
My Lady.
Chamberlain Meng.
Palace Attendant Cui.
Cui Wenjun.
What important matter is to be discussed,
to have brought you two here together?
Or did you just run into each other?
I was entrusted by the empress dowager
to accompany Chamberlain Meng to deliver an edict.
What's it about?
What has Cui Feng done?
General Cui works as the prefectural governor in Taiyuan
and is on an equal footing with General Jin.
He is an example to other courtiers.
Don't worry on that count.
Then what's the edict about?
This is the handwritten letter from Her Majesty.
It's for you.
And Her Majesty's edict granting marriage
is in the hands of the Prince of Guangling
Edict granting marriage?
What marriage?
The Prince of Guangling asked for a fiefdom.
Before he leaves the capital,
Her Majesty has agreed to fulfill his wish.
Wenjun.
Considering
the strength of your family,
it will be a great honor for you
to marry your daughter to the Prince of Guangling.
I think
you should get  prepared early
and call Shiyi back from the Western State
to get married.
The Prince of Guangling is ill and can't come
to Qinghe
to meet you in person.
So he specially ordered me to send the betrothal gifts here.
[Gift List]
Here is the gift list.
Why do you hesitate?
Do you want to resist the edict?
I dare not.
Pack up your winter clothes.
This time we're going to
spend some time away from home.
Miss.
Wait until I finish shooting this arrow
before you speak.
Her Lady has arrived.
My mother
must have read my letter.
Here.
My mother has arrived.
She is inside.
Mother, Aunt.
Your Highness.
Please get up.
Take a seat.
I still remember clearly
the day Shiyi acknowledged you as her master.
My daughter has been living in your mansion for many years.
Thank you for caring for her all this time.
She left her hometown and came to the Western State.
It's natural I should take good care of her.
You must be guessing
why I came here this time.
The empress dowager has arranged a marriage for her.
We came to take her back to Qinghe
for her wedding.
What marriage?
Your mother is talking with your master.
Sit down.
What marriage?
When was this set?
It's still the old one.
Even after all that,
it is still the Prince of Guangling.
How did you get hurt?
Your Lady.
Leave now.
Alright.
It's fine.
The palm won't scar so easily.
Did you read my letter?
Do you hope I have read it
or do you hope
I have never received it
and we won't even mention it again?
I want to know
what you think.
You said you wanted to stay in the Western State,
and compile classics and histories all your life.
Do you not want to get married,
or is it that you can't marry
the one you like?
Do you want to hear the truth?
You don't have to say anything.
I've just seen it with my own eyes.
I never had any delusions.
I just wanted to stay in the Western State
to stay with him.
You're no fool.
You should know it won't work.
Since you came back to the Western State,
there have been rumors among the commonfolk,
saying that the daughter of the Cui family and the Junior Prince of Nanchen
have an improper relationship,
disregarding his apprenticeship
and all ethics.
Who said that?
He and I have never crossed a line
and we never will!
There are also rumors that
the Junior Prince of Nanchen wants to rise in revolt
to ascend the throne himself
and the Cui family will
offer him this young beauty and help
to divide the country
so that the Cui family can rise in stature.
All noble families in the world
and his political enemies
have their eyes on you.
They won't give up any chance
to destroy and slander the people of Nancheng Royal Mansion
and the Cui family.
How could anyone believe this?
People love to praise heroes,
but also feel pity watching heroes fall from grace.
It has been so since ancient times.
Isn't there any room
for us to maneuver our way out of this?
Even if just for him,
instead of for all of us,
you must leave.
Before I meet you,
I've gone over countless scripts in my mind
trying to find words to persuade you.
But they didn't work.
I can't even convince myself.
I've been
through this pain.
Your cousin has experienced too.
I've thought that
in any case,
I won't let you experience the pain I've felt.
I've even thought that
if you fall in love
with any of your senior brothers,
I would help you
regardless of the family's dignity,
all to make you happy.
But you can't
marry the man in your heart.
I understand.
I never had any wild thoughts.
I just
want to be with him
and stay by his side.
That's enough.
Please, I beg you
to give me a few more days.
I just want to
stay here for a little while longer.
Palace Attendant Cui and Chamberlain Meng
are waiting in the post house.
You can stay
till tomorrow.
Okay.
This is Nanchen Royal Mansion.
It's inconvenient for us to live here.
So we shall stay at the post house tonight.
We'll give Shiyi time to
say goodbye to her senior brothers and sisters.
Tomorrow, we head out.
You still haven't worn the dress
His Highness ordered made last year.
Do you want me to take it out?
Take it out.
Sure.
Who is it?
Master, it's me.
It's time for dinner.
The military advisor said
you haven't allowed anyone to come in.
I have something urgent to do.
Can you light a lamp first?
In the first two years after I came here,
whenever you left on an expedition,
I would sleep here.
At that time,
I was not familiar with the guards
and so I was afraid of them.
I guessed your study
must be a forbidden area
where ordinary people didn't dare intrude.
So it seemed safest to sleep here.
You never told me about this.
You seldom come back.
I'm only too happy
to say these little things when you're back.
I cooked all these.
I don't know if you like them or not.
Have a taste.
Is it good?
Then take your time.
Where are you going?
I forgot the wine.
♫The shadow lingers, the sudden downpour comes♫
♫Been long waiting♫
♫Picked up a dream, coming for whom♫
♫My concern is put on the inkstone♫
♫Can't bear it, my heart is burning♫
♫The dependence I feel♫
You were gone so long.
♫I'm suffering with you♫
You couldn't wait, Master?
Such good dishes
♫Suffered so much from this sea of pain♫
should be tasted with wine.
♫I can leap down for you♫
This is mine.
♫Stain my painful love red♫
♫The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♫
♫Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♫
♫Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♫
I'll drink this with you.
♫The snow falling, the sand flying♫
♫It's hard to leave him unattached♫
I recall, when you were in the imperial palace,
you looked for wine everywhere.
♫The shadow lingers, the sudden downpour comes♫
♫Been long waiting♫
I broke my promise.
♫Picked up a dream, coming for whom♫
Not at all.
♫My concern is put on the inkstone♫
I promised to take you home.
♫Can't bear it, my heart is burning♫
But after we came back,
I couldn't keep you.
♫The dependence I feel♫
♫I'm suffering with you♫
♫Suffered so much from this sea of pain♫
♫I can leap down for you♫
♫Stain my painful love red♫
This place
♫The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♫
has always been my home.
♫Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♫
♫Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♫
♫The snow falling, the sand flying♫
♫It's hard to leave him unattached♫
Please go back for now, you two.
Miss is having dinner with His Highness.
A farewell dinner.
Farewell to who?
General Feng.
The empress dowager has ordered
the marriage of Miss Cui and the Prince of Guangling.
The edict was passed today.
Tomorrow,
Miss Cui will go back to the Central State.
General Feng.
Let's give them some time.
♫Can't bear it, my heart is burning♫
♫The dependence I feel♫
♫I'm suffering with you♫
♫Suffered so much from this sea of pain♫
♫I can leap down for you♫
♫Stain my painful love red♫
Don't go.
♫The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♫
♫Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♫
♫Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♫
♫The snow falling, the sand flying♫
♫Untie my attachments, follow my wishes♫
I'm not leaving.
It will be dawn in two hours.
Let Cheng Xi
come to bathe and dress you.
I still remember
what you wore the day I took up my apprenticeship.
Really?
Do you remember
♫I can leap down for you♫
what color my dress was on that day?
♫Stain my painful love red♫
♫The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♫
Yes.
♫Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♫
♫Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♫
♫The snow falling, the sand flying♫
♫It's hard to leave him unattached♫
♫Untie my attachments, follow my wishes♫
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for a piece of clothes.
Someone is waiting for you in the Council Hall.
Who?
Palace Attendant Cui.
He brought the empress dowager's verbal instructions.
Greetings, Your Highness. I'm Cui Zheng.
Palace Attendant Cui.
Your Highness,
I came here
to escort Shiyi back to the Central State.
But also, I brought the empress dowager's
verbal instructions to you.
Proceed.
The empress dowager said that,
although the gossip and rumors are not credible,
the Nanchen Royal Mansion and the Cui family
are noble families
admired by all scholars.
In order to stop the rumors,
the best solution is for Your Highness
to adopt
Cui Shiyi as your daughter.
♫Maybe it's the snow falling without a sound♫
♫Maybe it's the flower in the mirror without a trace♫
♫I've seen all the scenes of the passing years♫
All right.
♫They're not as good as you, not as good as you♫
I already have ten disciples.
I will call you Eleven.
Is that okay?
♫I look at a ripple♫
♫It's like there's no wind and no sunshine♫
♫The more silent my love becomes♫
♫The more my heart turns to rain♫
Disciple Cui Shiyi,
♫There is grace in your eyebrows♫
bids farewell to her master.
♫I'll spend my whole life looking for it♫
♫Don't blame me for the sporadic sweet talk♫
♫I wake up from my dreams and I'm even colder♫
♫My heart that can't stand being away from love♫
The empress dowager has made a decree
♫Hides nothing from you♫
for me take you as my adoptive daughter.
♫The scene I look down for♫
Eleven,
♫Gets clear after saying goodbye♫
is this acceptable to you?
♫Every glimpse means missing you♫
♫Even if to be a stranger to you♫
Okay.
Then I
will reject this decree.
♫I've asked if I know the heart of that person♫
♫Run out of the last hope♫
♫If I can't stay in the wind, I'll go with the wind♫
♫All is well, all is well♫
♫Who knows which glimpse obsesses me♫
♫Though covered with dust, it's still clear♫
♫If this proud body won't yield to parting♫
♫All the past can be mentioned♫
♫There is grace in your eyebrows♫
♫I'll spend my whole life looking for it♫
♫Don't blame me for the sporadic sweet talk♫
♫I wake up from my dreams and I'm even colder♫
♫My heart that can't stand being away from love♫
♫Hides nothing from you♫
♫The scene I look down for♫
♫Gets clear after saying goodbye♫
♫Every glimpse means missing you♫
♫Even if to be a stranger to you♫
A good bone structure...
what's so special about these bones?
Even the royal family fears them
and all the people in the land praise them.
♫I still remember how I felt when I came♫
♫So it's harder to forget every back of you♫
You've been in the Western State for ten years.
♫Me in that year♫
You haven't seen
♫Spent my whole life's luck on the will of God♫
all of it, have you?
Let me show you.
♫Been a mediocre person all my life♫
Mother said there were rumors among the commonfolk…
♫I just want you won't feel sad when looking back♫
Don't pay any attention to them.
♫When everything is calm♫
♫I can see who's under the moon♫
♫Turns out we've already been destined♫
There are eleven gates in the Western State.
You've only been to Xi'an Gate
and Chucheng Gate.
I'll take you to pass all the gates today.
I also want to visit Weiyang Palace.
Sure.
I'll let them
open all the palace gates.
Weiyang, Changle,
Mingguang Palace, North Palace, and Gui Palace.
You can see them all.
Feng Qiao said
since you entered the Western State,
you've never visited here.
Thank you
for disobeying the decree
and making an exception for me.
Have you brought the key?
It's as if I can see
the scene of them running away.
What do you want to do?
I want to leave a word on here.
When we leave and lock the gate,
no one can enter again.
Leaving a word here
is like leaving a secret just for us.
What do you want to write? Let me write it for you.
Chen.
I mean "morning", it's morning right now.
How meaningful.
♫The snow before the pavilion softly kisses the lattice♫
♫I don't want to dive deep into my heart to see how much I miss you♫
♫Sing my whispers while I'm slightly drunk♫
[Shiyi]
♫Listen to it, can you see that I miss you♫
♫The snow won't stop, the person won't show up, my heart won't clear up♫
♫The snow in front of the garden keeps falling♫
♫I can't wake up from your smiles♫
♫I'm willing to run to you even for millions of miles♫
[Shiyi]
[Nanchen Royal Mansion]
Master has ordered
me to escort you
to the Central State safely.
Where is he?
When you leave through the gate,
you'll see him.
[Shiyi]