Come on! Run!
Go get the ball!
Let's go get it!
Techno!
It hurts
Can
Are you ready to get in the field?
But Techno…
You can do it!
Fight for the team!
Yes
Let's go
Why are you guys sad?
We didn’t win this time
Next year we can still win
Just shut up
Look! There’re so many cute girls in this university
If you guys are still sulking, you won’t get any girls
Can you shut your mouth first?
Ae!
Did you just scold at me?
We still have next year
But this is Techno’s last year
Look at you, little monkey
Are you worried?
It hurts just a bit
I will get better in a few days
Stop it guys
Don’t be sad
Let’s go back to our university
We will get scolded if we’re late
Let’s go back
Let’s do better next year
I’m sorry
Why are you saying sorry?
I will come back and play football with you
But right now
You should go back now
Do you understand, little monkey?
You can go first. I drank too much sports drinks
I will go to pee first
Come back quickly then
♪How many rainy days have passed?♪
♪How long has it been?♪
♪No one is right here beside me♪
♪There's just me and loneliness♪
♪When will I get a chance to meet the one?♪
♪Give me just one minute♪
♪To meet that person who I've been waiting for♪
Can
♪The one...♪
Tin
Come here
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
We lost
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking for just once♪
Do you hear me?
We lost
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking for just once♪
Why do we have to lose?
Why?
We practiced so hard
We practiced everyday
We passed only two rounds
If Techno didn’t get hurt
If I didn’t go in
We wouldn’t lose
I’m the reason that we lost
Do you hear me?
It’s not because of you
You’re good enough
No
No, I’m not
I’m suck
I’m the reason that we lost
I’m the reason
Do you hear me?
It’s not because of you
Are you saying that the person who chased the ball endlessly is not good?
Are you saying that the person who worked so hard
even though he knows it’s hard is not good?
I don’t know
I don’t want to be just good
I want to win
I just want to win
Tin
It hurts
It hurts…
I know
I know what it feels like
I want to cry
You’re crying now
I want to keep crying
You can cry
I will keep crying
♪So I will no longer be lonely♪
You can cry so you can forget about it
You can cry in front of me
♪I've been praying♪
♪With a heart full of hope♪
♪With a heart full of dreams♪
♪I will wait for a new day♪
♪The day that I will finally meet you♪
Tin
I’m sorry
♪The day that I will finally meet you♪
I didn't mean that I don't like you
Please don’t disappear again
♪Why am I still hoping when there is no hope?♪
Don’t disappear again, Tin
♪I still hope and wait for the lonely nights to pass♪
I’m right here
♪In the pain and torment♪
Always right beside you
♪It might take a lot of time that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪We can only be friends♪
♪That's what we are♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, I won't make you sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
Three months ago
I’m late!
I’m so late!
Mom! Why didn’t you wake me up?
Breakfast for you
Do you want anything else?
It’s okay
I’m late!
Mom! Why didn’t you wake me up? My teacher is very strict
You too, Lemon!
Why didn’t you wake me up?
Why do I have to do that?
Why do I need to take care a lazy person like you?
You’re such a bad sister
I’m not talking to you anymore
Mom, I’ll go first. I’m late already
Why are you shouting so early in the morning?
Look at him. He didn't even dress properly
He’s eating while running. He will choke to death
You’re not used to it yet?
He’s always like this
Am I right?
You have to wake him up next time
High five!
I’m so dead
I won’t make it in time
Where’s the bus?
No bus
Where’s the motorcycle?
Sorry
I’m late already!
Why are you like this?
Can't you see that I'm in a hurry?
What should I do? What time is it now?
I don't have a watch!
Teacher will scold at me for sure
Main street!
I’m late
I’m so late!
Why are you driving like this?
Are you in a hurry to go to hell?
We’re in the university!
Just because you're driving a luxury car
so you think you can do anything you want?
Where’s Ae?
He doesn’t seem okay these days
Don’t ask him too much questions
Really?
Our friend is driving motorcycle now
He’s so cool
Why are you not talking to me?
Are you okay?
Ae
Where are you going?
Don't follow me
You’re not going to class?
Pond
Can you just leave me alone?
What the hell is wrong with him?
What's wrong with you, Pond?
You too, Ae!
You also, Pond!
I’m sure he’s the guy from the English program
What’s wrong with you?
Why are you whining?
I’m not whining
Do you know that I almost didn't come back in one piece?
I don't know who the hell cut off me
I survived because I prayed respect to the shrine
The shrine…
What are you talking about?
Are you going to listen to me or not?
I haven’t told you that I will listen to you
He just drove away
I was so unlucky this morning
I woke up late
I choked on a bread
I waited for so long for the motorcycle
And he drove too slowly
I had to run all the way to the university
And there was this inter guy who cut me off
Don’t get confused how I know that he’s an inter guy
He drove a luxury car
I’m not saying that people who drive luxury cars are bad people
But he was driving to the international college building
So, I’m pretty sure it’s the inter guy who hurt me
I guarantee you
Are you going to keep talking?
You said that you don’t mean every inter students
So, it’s just only him
Don’t lie to me
I don’t know
I hate him
Be careful
You will get what you hate
Are you serious?
Yes
I hate money then
Money, I hate you
I will get what I hate
Come to me money
Why there’s no money falling from the sky?
Type is not here to help me
How long are you going to do that?
Until you lose your mind
Until I lose my mind, right?
Fine
Come here
Go change your clothes now
Can, come here
Where do you think you’re going?
Come and practice
Where is Ae?
Ae?
Your friend’s over there
Ae seriously breaks up with Pete?
How am I supposed to know?
Why don’t you ask him yourself?
Who would dare to do that?
He might look calm but he’s so scary when he’s angry
Really?
Can you ask him for me?
Of course, not
I don’t want to die young
You should ask him if you want to know
You know what?
I think you should stop sticking your nose in other people’s business
Let’s go practice!
Everyone
Good job
That’s good
Why love is such a mess?
I don’t want to fall in love
I should find something to eat
Hey!
Can
Where are you going?
Come and practice first
Ae
Ae, stop being like this
Ae!
He’s not here with me
He’s not here with me anymore
That’s right
He’s not here with you
If he sees you become like this
Do you think he will be happy?
The reason that he breaks up with you
Because he wants to help you
But I don’t want him to do that
Do you understand?
Just leave me alone
Tin
I don’t know what to say
But I would like to ask a favor
I know that you hate students from Thai program
You don’t like Ae
But everyone is really nice
I want you to open your heart
But that’s not what I will ask of you
Tin
Can you take care of Ae for me?
I know that I’m troubling you
But you’re my only friend
The one that I trust
I’m not asking you to look after him all the time
But if he’s in trouble
Can you promise me that you will help him?
This is my last request
I don’t know if this will be my last e-mail to you or not
We might not meet each other again
Could you please be his friend for me?
That's right!
Damn it!
What's wrong?
Isn't it obvious?
My unfortunate life, my friend
My friend, Ae, is gone
I can never win the game. Damn it!
Game...
BnS Evolution?
Um
I'm playing it too
Eat this
Thanks
I won't get any item
But at least I get to eat this yummy snack
This is not just a snack
You can use it to get the item in the game
Really?
Yes
Awesome
Can I have it all?
This
Under the tray
Use the code to get the item
Really?
There's a code
Let me have it all
You said Ae is gone?
How is he doing?
Nothing much
Except...
What did you just eat?
Eat
Poop
Since when did you come?
It doesn't matter when I come
You should continue what you're saying
How's Ae? I want to know
You want to know?
Yes
I'm not talking anymore
Why?
I'm going to eat my snack
Why you're like this?
I might not know anything about Ae but at least I get to eat snack
It's yummy
Let me have it all
Bow!
It's mine!
Why is she like this?
How can I be friend with someone like this?
Exactly
I can’t stop being curious
Why did Ae and Pete break up?
They loved each other so much
You’re in the way
You mean who?
Get out
I’m going to walk
I won’t
There’s so much space for you to walk
Get out of the way
I want to walk
Then you have to wait
Because I won’t get out of the way
Why?
Is your dad the owner of the university?
You don’t know who my dad is?
Nope
Your dad is that important to be recorded in the history?
Even if he’s in the history
I still don’t know him
I failed history class
My surname is Medthanan
So?
Talking to a stupid person like you is such a waste of time
Why?
I admit that I’m stupid
Do you admit that your parents didn’t raise you well
that’s why you behave like this?
Are you done talking?
Let go of my hand
I don’t want to waste more time
What the hell did you just say?
Damn you! Come back here!
I get hungrier when I’m angry!
Let's go, Can. I'm hungry
Can!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm angry!
Who does he think he is? How dare he talked to me like that?
He called me stupid! I was in the way! So what?
My parents never talked to me like that
Did you eat too much or too less?
Why are you so crazy?
I'm not crazy!
A crazy person won't admit that he's crazy
You should go check
I will take you to the first aid room. Everyone is annoyed by you now
Job! You're my friend! You should be on my side
He said I was in the way and I was stupid
Just because I didn't know his dad
Everyone loves me. You can ask Techno, Champ and Type
I'm the most beloved member in the football team
Everyone is happy to be with me
Job, where are you going?
I don't know!
I'm hungry
I too tired to listen to you
I wanted to join the football team with you
But I change my mind now
You make me lose my mind
Wait for me!
Job, you're my friend!
Job
This weekend can I sleep over at your place, dad
About that
He's not ready yet
That's what I thought
It will turn out this way
You're walking out like this
That's not nice, Tin
What do you want?
I'm just talking to my brother
Is that weird?
You should stop pretending
What do you want?
About your internship
I want to work at dad's company
You're just nineteen
When you were nineteen, you also worked there
As a messenger
You won't be able to do it
I can do it
You cannot
You're not raised to face the difficulty
You told dad
to not let me do it, right?
Why are you so negative towards your brother?
I told you to stop pretending
I want to puke
A nice brother, huh?
No one will believe you
Then you should know
No matter how hard you try until the day you die
You can't keep up with me
I'm not full yet
I will go ask Techno to buy me food
I'm sorry
How come you're here? Are you going to mess with me?
I'm ready to fight
I'm sorry. It was an accident
It won't go off? Let me help you
Don't bother me
It's my fault. I'm sorry. Let me help you
Let me
Can't you just leave me alone?
Get out
No
I told you to get out
Fine...
But...
I should be responsible for what I did
Come with me
Stay still
Don't you know that you have to clean it asap?
My mom taught me this
Because my shirt always gets dirty
Look
Dirty like this
Damn it
Don't worry
It will be clean for sure
Whatever
I will throw this shirt away anyway
Such a waste
My mom taught me to use money wisely
Especially the money that your parents earn
You shouldn't waste it
Also, my mom taught me to be responsible
I made your shirt dirty so I have to clean it
See?
It's clean already
You should address me properly
I don't know your name. What do you want me to call you?
Should I call you a bad person?
My name is Tin
Tin Medthanan
My name is Can
I didn't ask
How can you talk like that to a person
who just cleaned the shirt for you?
I didn't ask you to do it
You're a bad person! You ungrateful!
You're...
Whatever
Even though I didn't ask
You already cleaned my shirt
What do you want in return?
Dude!
The reason that I cleaned the shirt is because I made it dirty.
I'm responsible for the thing I caused
I don't want anything in return. I don't want your money!
You can't buy me with money!
Damn you, my tummy
I was so handsome just then
What are you laughing at?
Nothing
I can see that you're laughing
I said no
Yes, you are!
I have a candy
Maybe it can help
Remember that
My name is Tin
Who said I want to know you? I don't want to know
Tummy, why are you so embarrassing?
♪There's just me and loneliness♪
♪When will I get a chance to meet that person?♪
♪Give me just one minute to meet that person who I've been waiting for♪
♪The one...♪
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪So that I...♪
♪Will no longer be lonely...♪
You're not here with me anymore
Dirty
You're insulting me again
I won't say sorry
And you should stop bothering me
You're annoying
♪Do you hear the sound outside the window? The sound of thunder scares me♪
♪It's so cold♪
♪Do you hear the sound outside the window?
The sound of thunder makes my heart tremble♪
♪Can I hold your hands to calm my heart?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪You know that I like the way you hug and the way you say I love you♪
♪Just whisper the words in my ears♪
♪I can't barely stand the thought of you leaving me♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪