Don't be naughty like that boy.
I'm not naughty like that younger brother.
A naughty child...
that no one wants.
Why don't you tell him
who made him become like that?
I used to think that my brother
was everything to me.
Can I go to see you?
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
Do you think I’m pathetic?
Who told you that?
Tell me who.
I’ll punch that person in the face.
I really despise your brother now.
How can he do that to his brother?
I have one sister.
No matter how mean she is to me,
but if someone hurts her,
I'll fight for her.
I’ll punch that person in the face.
Thank you.
For what?
I didn’t do anything.
You did.
What did I do?
Staying by my side.
Okay.
I’ll be right here.
What’s wrong?
I’m angry at your brother!
I'll hit him in the face when I see him.
Promise me.
Promise you what?
If you meet my brother,
don’t mess with him.
You’ll never know
what he’s going to do to you.
But…
Promise me.
Fine.
I’ll try to do that.
But Tin,
to deal with your brother,
it should be an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
That’s what my captain taught me.
Tit for tat.
By the way,
I’m sorry.
I didn’t let you go inside the house.
It’s already late. Everyone’s probably sleeping.
Lay will stab me if we make noise.
I don’t want to die yet.
Tin!
This is enough.
You should go inside.
It’s already late.
You kissed me without permission again.
Go now.
Tin!
Go back inside the house now.
It’s late.
Good night.
Alright.
You should go back too.
If he does something to you,
punch him in the face.
Okay?
I’m going to bed then.
Thank you.
Mom, I’m back.
Don’t make that face.
I’m okay.
It's okay, son.
I’m right here.
Okay.
Hey, crybaby.
What are you guys doing here?
We’re here to console you,
our little shorty.
What the hell are you guys doing here again?
We come here to visit you.
We see each other every day.
I have to see you on weekend too?
Ae.
It’s a blessing that you get to see my handsome face every day.
He's just nosy about your life.
And you just want to drink.
At least I’m better than you who doesn’t know the pleasure of drinking.
What’s wrong with you two?
You guys always fight.
I don’t know if it’s the right decision that I asked Mai to come.
Who will you ask instead?
Do you think other people can deal with Ae?
Even you can’t do that.
That hurts.
Enough, will you?
I’ll give you a punch.
If you dare.
Why not?
I'll run away first.
Dude.
Ae is laughing now.
I want to cry.
This is his first laugh after many months.
Thank God.
You’re overacting.
Finally, he laughs.
You guys should keep your nose out of my business.
Hey.
Our Ae is back.
That’s right.
We should take a photo.
Our old Ae finally comes back.
You’re overacting again.
Can’t you do that for me?
Fine.
Let’s take a photo.
One. Two. Three.
(My friends come to see me today.)
(I go back home today.)
(I have a quiz today.)
(I go back to practice football today.)
He posts it again.
He’s a very interesting guy.
Let me take a break.
I'm out of energy.
(I’m waiting in front of the field.)
Tin, are you okay?
You brother didn’t hurt you, right?
Are you worried?
Of course.
You're so sad last time when you came to see me.
I thought you'll be in trouble.
So, there’s nothing wrong
but you just want me to come out?
Why are you like this?
What did you just do?
Here.
Tin!
I told you.
Money can’t buy you.
I know that.
I’m not giving it for free.
What are you doing?
You always like to kiss me.
Since you won't give it for free,
then I'll let you kiss me wherever you like.
What are you doing?
You already paid me back.
Since when?
Remind me next time
that I shouldn’t do it when you’re sweating.
It’s salty.
I’ve got to go now. I have class.
I’ll call you later.
Don’t call me.
I won’t pick up.
You have to.
Why do I feel ticklish like I want to poop every time he does this?
Can, stop thinking.
Stop thinking.
This looks yummy.
Damn it.
The exam was freaking hard.
I couldn’t do it.
Can you do it?
Easy.
For me?
It’s my favorite.
I’ll eat it now.
This is for Techno not for you.
Do you have to come all the way here to his university?
Just give it to him before he goes to practice.
What do I get in return?
You have to cheer on me
and I’ll give you what you want.
Deal?
If you say so.
Just go.
Technic.
What are you doing here?
Kengkla asked me to give you this.
He knows that you like to eat it.
So he bought it for you.
(I want to be your favorite like this Bento.)
You’re turning red.
I think this flavor must be very spicy.
Shut up, Technic.
You won’t eat it?
You come here just to give me this?
Why don’t you eat it now?
Why is your face so red?
You can leave now.
You already gave it to me.
I have to study.
You’ll give it to me for sure?
Of course. I’m a man of my word.
You have to help me just a little bit.
Tell me then.
You have to let me play the next match.
I want to show off.
You want to show that pretty nurse?
That’s right.
Fine.
Now, give me the movie tickets.
You’re awesome.
Here.
What the hell, Can?
Yeah. What's wrong with you?
Why are sneaking up on us?
What if I have a heart attack?
Where’s the ticket for me?
None for you.
Why not? Why you only gave it to Techno?
Fine! I’ll tell everyone that Techno is taking bribes.
He likes to take free stuff from others.
Shut up! Stop talking so loudly. Others will hear you.
Can!
Tin.
How come you’re here?
Come with me.
Stop pulling me. It hurts.
Are you the son of rickshaw puller?
What did I do?
Why did he look at me like he wants to kill me?
Do you know why?
How am I supposed to know?
I’m with you all the time.
Whatever.
As long as I have excuses to get out of the house,
then I've got nothing to worry about.
No need to worry about Can.
Wait.
Why do you have to run away from home?
Well…
Why’s that?
I don’t think you have to know everything, Job.
What’s wrong with him?
Techno, wait for me!
The football field at night is so scary.
Tin, slow down.
Can’t you see that my legs and your legs have a different length?
Why did you suddenly stop walking?
What’s wrong? Why are you so grumpy?
You should smile.
When you’re with me, you have to smile more.
I like to be with people who are in a good mood.
Does that mean you like that guy?
You mean Techno?
Of course.
I really like Techno.
He’s a nice person.
He always scolds me, but he still buys me food.
Anyway, I’m still angry at them.
Job asked Techno to the movies but he didn’t ask me.
Then you suddenly came in and interrupted us.
I almost got a free ticket.
Do you want to watch a movie at my house?
What do you say?
You’re actually rich.
So, have you decided what movie do you want to watch?
There’re so many movies that I want to watch.
I want to watch a zombie movie.
The new horror movie seems fun too.
But if I watch all of it,
then I don't think I can go back home.
Don’t go back then.
I can’t.
My mom makes steamed rice noodle rolls today.
I already asked a chef to prepare a full course Italian dinner.
Italian…
Full course.
Let me eat it too.
Good.
This sounds more like a date.
How can it be a date?
We’re just hanging out.
Watching movies then eating dinner.
Even the most stupid people know that it’s a date.
Movie.
Dinner.
Let’s go.
Let’s go on a date.
How can it be a date?
I really don’t like your brother.
Uncle Tin!
You’re home today.
You’ll stay home with me, right? I’m so lonely
Yes.
This is your brother’s son.
How are you?
Are you a bad person like your dad?
Don't insult my dad. He's a good person.
He has a great personality.
Are you sure?
Maybe he's evil.
Uncle Tin.
He insulted dad.
He insulted my daddy.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's not Phupha or his mom's fault.
If I want to take revenge,
it will be on my brother only.
Fine.
Well…
Let’s make up.
You insulted my dad.
I’m mad at you now.
Come on.
Are you a good kid?
If you are, you have to make up with me.
I’m a good kid.
You’re lonely, right?
I’ll play with you all day long.
Tin.
You already sent your nephew to bed?
I like you.
I know that.
I’m hitting on you.
So what?
I am hitting on you now.
I already know that.
Why do you keep saying that?
Just do whatever you want.
You can hit on me.
You can like me.
I just…
I still don’t know.
I don’t know if I’m okay with you or not.
What are you doing?
Collecting interest.
What interest?
Interest from all the food you ate.
You’re going to kiss me again?
Fine.
Can.
Open your mouth.
No!
Open it.
I said no!
I like you.
What’s wrong with you?
You crazy!
Hey! Tum.
Why do you stop?
I’ll be right back.
What?
What’s wrong with him?
Do you know, Keen?
It’s probably about his brother.
I’ll be right back.
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
That’s all.
Okay.
Is your brother okay?
Did I tell you that it’s my brother?
No. I just guess it.
Nothing’s wrong.
He texted me that
he couldn’t contact mom.
I thought it was a big deal,
but nothing serious.
I must be crazy.
You’re not crazy.
You’re just worried about your brother.
There’s only you who understand me.
Well…
Do you want to understand me too?
What do you want me to understand?
Whatever.
About your inspiration.
I found this guy.
I think he’s quite interesting.
How?
Hello, Tum.
Hello, Tar.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I have a long holiday and I’m planning to go back.
When?
I’m going back soon.
But I haven’t booked the ticket yet.
Will you be free to pick me up?
It’s okay if you’re not. I can go home by myself.
I’m a grown-up now.
I’m also much better than before.
How are you lately? Are you doing well?
Not too bad.
How about you?
I’m fine. No need to worry.
I have the same question for you.
What is it?
Do you want anything from here?
I have the same answer for you.
I don’t want anything.
I’ll ask our parents if they want anything.
Okay.
Anyway, I’ll let you know once I get a flight back home.
Sure.
Also, there will be a music festival in my university.
Let’s go together.
Of course. I’m free to go.
See you later then.
Okay.
Bye bye.
What’s up, my good boy?
Why are you still up?
I’m not sleepy yet. I'm the best.
My good boy, what did you do today?
I was fighting with Uncle Tin's friend and I won.
He said you're a bad person.
I couldn’t let him say that.
I'm a good boy, right?
My son,
why don’t you tell me about uncle Tin’s friend?
Of course!
You can trust me on that.
Search about Tin's friend, Can, for me.
I want to know who is Tin's important person.
I hope you won't be angry.
Ae.
What is love?
Why are you asking me?
I’m just wondering.
Right now, I feel…
I feel that the food is not tasty.
I can’t sleep well at night.
I’m struggling to poop.
I’ve been thinking all the time if I like him or not.
That’s why I’m wondering what is love actually?
I don’t know what love means to others.
But for me.
It means Pete.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
I’m sorry that I can’t give you the right answer.
Try to think it over.
You can do it.
Why all I can see is pain?
I don’t want to be like you, Ae.
Cantaloupe.
I told you not to call me by my full name.
Call me Can. Just Can.
“Just Can.”
Are you messing with me?
Why are you smiling?
Why are you hiding from me?
Who told you that?
I didn’t do that.
Who’s hiding from you?
You’re overthinking.
You do.
But I’m glad.
Why are you happy about that?
Are you crazy?
Because that means you’re actually thinking about me.
It’s all in your head.
I’m not thinking about you at all.
Where are you taking me?
Let's find somewhere quiet to talk.
I won’t go.
If you want to talk, let’s do it here.
What is it?
Will you be boyfriend, Can?
♪I wish you could be with me forever and always.♪
♪I wish you could be my one and only.♪
♪I’ll let you be my sky when I’m flying. ♪
♪I’ll let you be my guiding star when I lost my way.♪
Tin, do you have a girlfriend?
Can you be my boyfriend?
Calm down, Can.
Stop imagining things.
Dude.
What’s wrong with Can?
He’s practicing very hard.
Does he want to win a world championship?
If you’re worried, why don’t you go in?
We have a match tomorrow. You should come.
I think he wants you to come.
Why are you helping me?
♪I never understand the meaning of love.♪
♪What is it?♪
♪Why do we need it?♪
♪I don't understand why.♪
♪Maybe it's just me♪
♪who don't understand my own heart.♪
♪I don’t realize that my heart is missing someone.♪
♪All I know that it is not the same as before.♪
♪Every time I sit next to you,
my heart starts beating fast.♪
♪It starts racing out of the blue,
and now I’m getting tired.♪
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won’t listen to me anymore.♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you,
but my heart keeps calling out for you.♪
♪It’s just you and there’s only you
that my heart is yearning for.♪
♪I don’t know since when, but now I love you with all my heart.♪
♪The way you look at me.♪
♪It makes my heart trembles.♪
♪I don’t know what is the reason that makes me think of you.♪
♪Every time I sit next to you,
my heart starts beating fast.♪
♪It starts racing out of the blue,
and now I’m getting tired.♪
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won’t listen to me anymore.♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you,
but my heart keeps calling out for you.♪
♪It’s just you and there’s only you
that my heart is yearning for.♪
♪I don’t know since when, but now I love you with all my heart.♪