What's the blood type of most cops?
Blood type?
Take your time. I'm going to the restroom.
Okay.
I've read that somewhere...
Was it A?
WI SEUNGHYUN
Blood type...
Hello?
Hey, Seunghyun.
Is that you, Juchan?
Yes.
Eunkang went to the restroom.
Where are you?
Are you together now?
Never mind.
I'll call her later.
Bye.
The most common blood type of cops is...
B-woo, B-woo.
What's that?
What? It's type B.
B-woo, B-woo.
You little punk.
What? You're just upset
that you didn't get the answer.
-Hey, you got a bump.
-Really?
-Just kidding.
-Gosh, you're so immature.
Seriously.
Go on in.
Okay.
Juchan.
Chin up. You'll get through this.
When things get too hard, call me.
I can buy you a drink.
-You're being cheeky.
-What? I'm a grown-up now.
-I'm old enough to drink now.
-Just go home.
Okay.
-Good night.
-Bye.
EPISODE 8
Hurry up.
Gosh!
Slow down. You might upset your stomach.
The food tastes amazing.
I feel like I'm in an Olympic Village
these days.
I wake up so early in the morning
and all I do is to eat, sleep, and run.
But it made you much stronger now.
At first, you could barely
make half the course.
At this rate, I'm going to be the winner.
Just focus on finishing the course.
That's your goal.
You don't know anything about me.
I got the best score
on the physical fitness test at my school.
Really?
I ran 1,000 meters in
4 minutes and 50 seconds.
I did 35 push-ups
and my grasping power measured 35.
I may not look it,
but I'm actually quite strong.
Okay. Then let's get right to it.
Forty...
...nine.
Fifty...
Gosh.
You said you did 60 sit-ups
on the test. Was it a lie?
That was last year.
I'm a year older now. It's so hard.
One more sit-up. Then we call it a day.
-Really?
-Yes.
What was that?
I was almost there. You messed it up.
You're just making an excuse.
I just laid one finger on you.
Haven't you heard
of the expression,
"The straw that broke the camel's back"?
Apparently, she's still got some energy
to joke around.
Make sure to be hard on her.
Don't let her fool you
if she pretends to be sick.
What? Oh, okay.
-What are you doing this evening?
-What?
You said you'd buy me a drink.
Right. I'm free after classes.
I'll call you.
Okay. Keep it up then.
Gosh. My whole body aches.
-Keep going.
-Let's take a short break.
-Come on. Ten more sit-ups.
-Are we done after ten more?
Just do it.
When he was my tutor,
I once faked being sick
because I didn't want to do homework.
I hate math so much.
Don't tell the others
that Juchan was my tutor.
Okay.
Where should we go?
There are too many students
near the school.
Do you know any quiet place
where we can talk over a drink?
Not really.
Are you talking about something serious?
Well...
It's just that
Juchan is having a hard time these days.
-Then maybe I should come too.
-What?
I'm free this evening too.
The more the merrier.
Ahh...
No. Not today.
Let's hang out together
another time. Okay?
-Okay.
-See you.
Bye.
-Hey, Seunghyun.
-Yes?
-I saw you applied for the Cheering Squad.
-What?
Good luck. I'm looking forward to it.
Cheering?
I signed us up.
The highlight of Cheongram Sports
Festival is the freshmen's talent show.
Who else would do it besides us,
the handsome Freshmen Four?
What are you saying? Who said that?
Well, obviously, I say...
And I know we all agree with me.
Your mind, my mind. My mind, your mind.
In the end, we are all of the same mind.
Whatever. Good luck with that.
I'm out of this.
You can't be out. You're the center.
The name of our team is...
Wivengers.
Wow. You finally lost your mind.
You know what?
I've always thought of you
as our leader ever since we first met.
Having you in the center
makes me feel safe.
-Why am I...
-Don't ask why.
It's just because...
you're my favorite.
You're acting weird these days.
Does Seunghyun have something on you?
-Why are you sucking up to him?
-You little...
Hey. Seunghyun is not that kind of guy.
How could you not know how great he is?
You're even his roommate.
Gosh. You're upsetting me.
You're not mad, are you?
Anyway, I can't do the talent show.
Let's do it.
I want to try it.
It'll be a good memory too.
If you really don't feel like it,
we don't have to.
Okay. Let's do it.
Come on. Bumju wants to do it.
Let's do it.
Yes!
Okay.
I actually found some videos
that might help us.
You did?
EAST GYEONGGI PROVINCIAL POLICE AGENCY
Here's the information
about Seunghyun's roommate you asked for.
Thanks.
DOCUMENTS FOR APPROVAL
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: KIM TAK
His parents ran a small business
before dying in a car accident,
and his brother died ten years ago.
He was a KNPU student.
My name is Kim Hyunsoo
and I'm a 4th-year law student at KNPU.
I'm Kim Hyunsoo.
Should I do more research?
No, it's okay. You can go now.
HIS BROTHER KIM HYUNSOO DIED
IN A CAR ACCIDENT WHILE ATTENDING KNPU
Did you bring your wallet?
Hello.
-Hi, Ari.
-Goodness.
Hi.
Hey. You want the one with red bean?
It's sold out.
Why would he give me the strawberries?
Is he playing hard to get or what?
-Who's playing hard to get?
-What?
-No one.
-Hey, it's melting.
Darn it.
Gosh!
Why does he even like this?
Then give it to me. I love it.
Come on. Who is it?
Who is this boy tantalizing you?
He's not tantalizing anyone.
I'm not interested in him at all.
If anyone, he'd be the one
being tantalized, not me.
Tsss... So there is a guy.
I don't know!
He's not my type anyway.
I hate corny country boys like him.
Like I'd care
if he has a crush on me.
What are you doing this evening?
I'm free after classes.
I'll call you.
Cheers!
THE CAFE IS OPEN
TAKEOUT AVAILABLE
RESTAURANT ENTRANCE
It's cut like a pizza.
Right. Pizzas like this are really good.
Right. But I haven't really tried.
-You haven't?
-No. Not so many times.
Oh.
-Hey.
-I didn't know you were here.
-Hello.
-Hey.
What are you doing here?
-I came to grab a drink.
-Alone?
I love drinking alone. Well...
I just came across this bar.
It seems nice, so I came in.
What a funny coincidence.
Actually, Seunghyun,
why don't you join us?
Is that okay with you?
I hope I'm not bothering you.
Could we have another glass, please?
Cheers.
Help yourself. It's my treat.
-No, it's on me.
-There you go, being cheeky again.
I said I was going to pay today.
You always paid for me.
-I'm not that shameless.
-You can be shameless.
That's an unusual color for a wallet.
It really stands out.
Really? Eunkang got it for me.
I gave it to him for his birthday
when I was a high school freshman.
But Juchan,
I think you should get a new one.
It seems all worn out.
It looks fine to me.
I can use it for at least ten more years.
It's not even real leather.
I couldn't get you a good one
because I didn't have money then.
But I really like this wallet.
To be honest, I lost it twice.
But it always found its way back to me.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I must be destined to keep it.
-How interesting.
-Right?
-You must not have had much cash in it.
-I guess so.
-I think that's probably why.
If there was,
it wouldn't have been returned.
Maybe you're right.
I'm going to use the restroom.
-Let's drink.
-Okay.
-Eunkang is a fine girl, isn't she?
-Pardon?
Right.
She may look stubborn, fussy, and fiesty,
but inside, she has a soft heart.
She's also very caring.
I know.
Please take good care of her.
-You're her colleague, so be nice to her.
-Okay.
That's a weird thing to ask though.
It's not like she's your girlfriend.
I've known her since she was little,
so she has always been
like a little sister to me.
But seeing her at school now,
it feels different.
These days, I even find myself
relying on her when things get tough.
It's natural that you feel comfortable
around the person you're familiar with
during hard times.
-I have to get this.
-Sure.
RESTROOM
Eunkang.
Can we talk for a moment?
It looks like
Seunghyun came because of you.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to make you feel better today.
I think he likes you.
What?
Oh, no.
There's nothing going on between us.
It's not like he confessed to me.
Then can I say it first?
You once said you liked me.
Do you still feel the same?
I...
like...
you too.
But I like you as a senior.
I like someone else now.
I see.
The person you have reached
is unavailable...
Where did he go? Why won't he pick up?
47TH CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL
Athletes' oath.
Athletes' oath!
We promise to take part
in the 47th Cheongram Sports Festival,
respecting and abiding by the rules
that govern them,
and in the true spirit of sportsmanship,
for the glory of sport
and the honor of KNPU.
Order arms.
UNITE AS ONE CHEONGRAM FAMILY WITH PASSION
47TH CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL
BE A WARNING TO THE PEOPLE
Today is finally the day
of the Cheongram Sports Festival,
which you've been looking forward to.
I know how hard you've worked
for the midterms.
Today, I hope you can make the most of
all the strength you've been building up,
showing us your youth and passion.
But what's most important is
that we don't have any injuries.
I hope we can all sweat
and compete safely,
and that this event
will bring us all together.
Now, let's begin
the 47th Cheongram Sports Festival.
BLUE FLAME OF STUDENT SQUAD 1
STUDENT SQUAD 2 IS THE ONLY WINNER!
STUDENT SQUAD 3, SNATCH THE VICTORY
STUDENT SQUAD 4 FOR THE WIN
STUDENT SQUAD 2 WINS
CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL SCOREBOARD
STUDENT SQUAD 1 VS STUDENT SQUAD 2
SHIN ARI VS GI HANNA
STUDENT SQUAD 3 VS STUDENT SQUAD 2
KIM JIEUN VS WOO JUYOUNG
STUDENT SQUAD 2 WINS
Professor Bang.
Let's drop rank during the game, okay?
Don't be easy on me
just because I'm the dean.
But how can I...
All right, then.
-Fair play!
-Ready.
Let's do this!
Pull!
Guys! Pull!
One!
One! Lie down!
Just lie down!
Pull it!
Lie down!
Just lie down!
RELAY RACE
Ready.
UM HYUK IS WATCHING YOU!
STUDENT SQUAD 1 IS THE CHAMPION!
CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL SCOREBOARD
JUCHAN WILL LEAD US TO VICTORY!
Hurry!
-You're almost there!
-Come on.
Hurry!
UM HYUK IS WATCHING YOU!
TODAY'S PAIN WILL BRING SWEET VICTORY
THUMBS UP TO US!
STUDENT SQUAD 2 LOSES
Hey, Daeil, are you all right?
It can happen to anyone.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Help yourself, Professor Bang.
You worked hard today.
He's right. Eat up, Professor Bang.
Professor Bang.
I've discovered a new side of you today.
If Student Squad Two wins this year,
you should be the MVP.
Come on. You're just being humble.
She was really famous
even back when she was a student here.
Do you know what she was called?
-Ms. Loud Voice.
-What?
Because her voice was so loud,
she was called Ms. Loud Voice.
She was infamous.
It's tasty.
Well, you can call it
a skill too.
I mean, they say
even the ancient Roman soldiers
shouted in the battlefield
to sap the morale of their enemies.
By the way, you know what?
I still can't believe...
that you two were in the same class here.
I studied law for two years before
coming here, making me two years older.
Still, it's hard to believe.
Hearing that you were colleagues
surprises me every time.
Is it that hard to believe?
Professor Cha.
She's saying you look old. Okay?
Ahh...
KNPU
-We've got to really get it together.
-Just you, man.
That's why
you should be good at running.
But still...
Women's triathlon
will decide everything.
As expected,
it's a battle between Squads One and Two.
We're winning for now,
but we've got to be careful.
There's only a five-point difference.
The games in the afternoon
will decide the victor.
TOTAL SCORE, CURRENT RANKINGS
Be careful not to hurt yourself.
Got it?
STUDENT SQUAD 1'S INTELLIGENCE AND PASSION
WILL LEAD TO VICTORY!
What's wrong with your foot?
Oh, hey. I just hurt it a bit.
-Are you okay?
-I can still run. Don't worry.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should have told me
even if it's a small injury.
I didn't have the chance.
You even told me
to practice alone yesterday.
Sorry. Our team had a meeting that day.
What kind of meeting takes the whole day?
Tell me. Are you mad at me?
You left the bar without telling me,
and you didn't answer my calls.
No. I went home that night
because I wasn't feeling well.
All triathlon participants,
please prepare for the game now.
All trench fight participants
may also wait in the arena.
Let's get going.
You've been training hard,
so I'm sure you'll do a good job.
Take it easy though.
-Your goal is to finish the course.
-Okay.
Good luck to you too. Don't hurt yourself.
Thanks.
Seunghyun.
There's something I want to tell you
after the game.
What is it?
I'll tell you after I win. See you later.
Don't hurt yourself.
Good luck.
If you get injured or don't feel well,
wave the handkerchief immediately.
On your marks!
TRIATHLON
Trench fight is all about strength.
We're going to make use
of our physical advantage to the utmost.
Let me pair you up
with each of their players.
Make sure to mark them thoroughly.
Who's marking Kim Tak? It won't be easy.
Right, he's strong.
-Hey, Juchan is...
-It'll be tough even for Juchan.
-Kim Tak?
-We'll have him marked...
by you.
Pardon?
You need to push the entire
opposing team out of the trench to win.
Take one step out of the trench,
and you're out. Understood?
Yes, sir!
Captains.
Shake hands.
Let's go.
All right.
Let's do this!
-Okay!
-Let's do this!
Go for it!
Let's go!
LET'S GET 1ST PLACE
You're out!
Out!
This is the final lap.
If Tak is our last man standing,
we'll win hands down.
Our goal is to cover him
and make it a one-on-one match.
Squad One will try
to make Tak their last man standing.
We will sacrifice a player
to remove him before that.
Out!
But what if Tak gets pushed out first?
When that happens...
I'll stall for time then.
Lift him up.
Come on.
Juchan! Look at Seunghyun! Look at him!
Come on! Juchan!
Squad Two, out!
If you'd come a little later,
the whole plan would have failed.
But I didn't. Gosh. This is killing me.
Student Squad One wins!
STUDENT SQUAD 1 WINS
Come on. Stand up.
-We've got to win.
-I'm so sorry. Go ahead.
-Sorry.
-See you soon.
Kim Semi of Student Squad Two forfeits.
This is the halfway point!
-Okay!
-You can do it!
-You're doing great!
Ko Eunkang! Ko Eunkang!
Yes! Yes!
She might make a comeback.
Baek Sunyu!
Baek Sunyu! Baek Sunyu!
Pace yourself. Take it slow.
47TH CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL
COURSE 2
Go! Go! Go!
It's raining!
I think it fell
because of the rain.
I don't think I can fix it.
That's a shame.
I guess we should use the radio
to see how it's going.
How strange though. The forecast
didn't say it was going to rain.
I know. I think it'll stop soon though.
Why does it have to rain now?
It hurts.
All right!
This is the halfway point!
You got this!
COURSE 2 HALFWAY POINT
Thank you.
-You can do it!
-Go for it!
The last contestant
has just passed the halfway point.
47TH CHEONGRAM SPORTS FESTIVAL
COURSE 2
Hey. Hanna.
Thank goodness.
I knew I wasn't supposed to die here.
Please help me. I can't walk.
Just forfeit.
The staff is coming soon, so tell them.
What?
Hey, you can't just leave. Help me.
Why should I help you?
Because we're on the same team.
You never shoot friendly fire during a war
no matter how much you hate them.
If this is a war, it's a great chance
to shoot your teammate quietly.
COURSE DIRECTION
Hey.
Hey! Why do you hate me?
What is it that I did so wrong?
Telling the Training Corps
that the spy cam belonged to you?
I did that because you framed me for it.
Don't you remember
what you did to me first?
Do you even have a conscience?
I told you I didn't mean to
frame you for it.
And I said it was an accident.
Anyway, if you hadn't brought
the charger to the Training Corps,
things wouldn't have become
so complicated.
Then you acted
like you worried about me.
Seriously.
So stop being such a hypocrite.
Hypo...
I'm not being a hypocrite
and I wasn't necessarily
worrying about you either.
Why would I care about you?
I've got my own problems to deal with.
I brought it into question
because I thought it was unfair.
But fine. I get you're mad.
But thanks to what you filmed
with the spy cam,
Cheongram Education got abolished.
That's all that matters, isn't it?
You filmed it to let others know
how absurd the punishment system was.
And you achieved your goal.
Technically, we abolished
Cheongram Education together.
So you should be happy about it.
Now I get why I hate you.
Being with you
makes me look like a horrible person.
That's why I hate you. Happy now?
The leading group
is passing the main gate.
They're coming.
She's here!
Baek Sunyu!
Get up.
With this, everything's settled
between you and me.
This is for saving me from being expelled.
Wait.
COURSE DIRECTION
STUDENT SQUAD 2 WINS
What happened to them?
I don't know about Hanna,
but Eunkang was in the lead
until the halfway point.
Maybe she tripped somewhere.
-What's wrong with your foot?
-I just hurt it a bit.
Hey! Where are you going?
It's great you decided
to take responsibility for your actions.
I'll gladly accept your offer.
So we're all good now.
Do you know what that means?
We start all over again.
Back to square one.
Gosh!
Be quiet, will you?
I'm tired.
Could you slow down a little?
It really hurts.
We can't win anyway.
No one's waiting for us.
Hey, Misook.
Well done.
Everyone came back
except Eunkang and Hanna.
Maybe something bad
happened to them.
Okay.
It seems the radio isn't working
in the mountains right now.
The staff don't know
what's going on either.
I'll go check out the mountain.
Hey.
There they are.
I'll walk myself. Just hold me.
It's okay. That'll take forever.
Guys!
Eunkang.
-What happened? Did you get hurt?
-Yes.
You should have taken your phone
with you in case of emergency.
-We need to call the ambulance.
-It's okay.
I want to finish the race.
I know I can't win,
but I want to finish it.
Hanna, let's go.
Hey. Give it.
Shouldn't we be stopping them?
-Are you sure?
-My gosh.
-That must hurt.
-Really.
I think she's bleeding.
-You're almost there! Keep going!
-You can do it!
Are you okay?
-Yes. Water...
-Ari, get her some water.
I'm sorry. I wanted to win.
You're being cheeky again.
Well done.
You finished the race
and didn't abandon your friend.
STUDENT SQUAD 1 IS THE CHAMPION!
Hanna.
Thank you.
I wouldn't have made it to the end
without you.
Let's start from square one again.
Well done.
You were pretty cool back there.
You did a good job.
If someone asks me
why I like Eunkang,
my answer would be
because she never gives up on people.
All right.
Come on, Tak. Get closer.
-Come on. Come closer.
-Hurry.
All right. Here we go.
This is our first group photo.
Okay? Let's get this done at once.
Do we have to take a photo
when we're all sweaty though?
I look a bit messy now.
You're the prettiest here. Actually,
I've never seen you this pretty...
-Really?
-No.
-One, two, three.
-Three.
-Should we take another one?
-Let's take another one.
Okay. Smile.
One, two, three.
All right. That was
just the beginning of the show.
The next team has
such an extraordinary name.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please give a big round of applause
to Gentlemen Always Pay for Dinner!
The senior students'
dance party!
My gosh.
Our seniors are so hot.
Are you nervous?
I'm sure you haven't performed
on a big stage like this,
but don't you worry. I got your back.
Worry about yourself
and focus on getting the beat.
He's right. You started
too early at the final rehearsal.
-I'm worried.
-Don't you worry, boys.
I'll be good
once we start the actual performance.
Hey, where's that thing from earlier?
Hang on.
Calming pills.
-Can I have one too?
-Sorry. I've only got one.
Then can I have the half...
All right.
Let's do this.
One, two...
-I need to use the bathroom.
-Wait, me too.
I want to pee too.
My gosh. Look at
our hot seniors! Make some noise!
We watched the seniors' dance moves,
now we have to watch the freshmen too.
-For sure.
-The freshmen will take the stage next.
Let me introduce
KNPU's four prettiest boys,
Wivengers!
That's stupid.
You don't know
if you're uncomfortable or excited?
It's confusing.
That's why I'm asking.
Then meet someone
who doesn't confuse you.
If you really like someone,
you won't be confused.
Don't quit.
Let's see through it to the end.
How could they be sexier than me
when I'm dressed like this?
-This is not fair.
-My gosh.
That's not true!
The freshmen
really made my heart flutter.
Sadly, now we only have
the final highlight of the festival left.
However, this is the moment
you can be as passionate
and crazy as you want.
It's time for the dance battle!
Are you ready?
Yes!
It looks like you're not ready.
I'll come back next year then.
All right. That's better.
Let me ask you again. Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's begin the dance battle!
Student Squad One, come on out first.
Can we talk for a second?
What an outstanding move!
Do it before the professors
see you. No. They're going to freak out.
Student Squad One,
you can come back in.
Student Squad Two.
You don't want to lose, do you?
Come on out.
Student Squad Two!
You said you had something
you wanted to tell me after the race.
-Yes.
-What is it?
Hmm...
Well...
I...
I think I like...
Let me say it first.
I know you like someone else,
but I still like you.
What?
But you're the one I like.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs