(My Forever Sunshine)
If I felt anything towards you,
my heart would tremble
with excitement, right?
But I don't feel anything at all.
You were so blindly obsessed
with me in the past.
Back then I was so stupid.
I was stupid like a donkey.
Why are you picking me up?
Are you crazy?
Are you planning to bite me?
From now on,
I will love you as a friend.
We're going steady.
Are you jealous of me?
Who'd be jealous of a jerk
of a friend like you?
If you're not,
then what's up with you?
- Show her some respect.
- Why should I?
Paeng's my girlfriend.
I have to protect her.
How did you get together with Non?
Answer me.
Artit, look after her for a bit.
I'll be back.
Oh?
Non,
you lied to me.
What did I lie to you about?
About Paeng.
You and her aren't a couple.
Think what you want.
Because if you are with her,
you wouldn't have gone after Ling.
I'm still adapting.
I'm not used to
not caring about Ling.
Because you love her.
I do love her.
Then why are you in a relationship
with Paeng?
I just want to try it out.
You can't do that to her.
You don't love her, so how can
you be in a relationship with her?
Ling won't accept my love
so I had to get over her.
And I think Paeng's lovely.
I can probably be with her.
You can't treat women as toys.
Or are you possessive of Paeng?
So you're admitting that you're not
possessive of me
bur actually Paeng?
Why would I worry about
someone like her?
Then stop getting in between us.
And stop making
those angry eyes at me.
I'm going to go shower now.
You're a jerk of a friend.
Do you have any sugar left?
Just a second.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Are you here with friends?
That's right.
It's pretty cold out.
Are you here with friends as well?
I don't like traveling alone.
I wanted to come with
friends but they were all busy.
What should I call you?
It's Paeng.
Paeng?
I'm Mark.
Do you go to university?
I already graduated.
Really?
You have such a babyface.
What's your job?
I work in a rose garden.
Unbelievable.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
You seduce everyone.
Are you sleepy, Paeng?
We got up early.
But we'll be arriving at
the school shortly.
I'm not. It's quite fun actually.
If you are sleepy,
you can lean on my shoulder.
What's wrong? Did you fall
asleep at the wheel?
No. I wouldn't be able to fall
asleep anyway.
Should we take
some photos, Non? I'm bored.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Hey,
thanks for the help.
Paeng,
are you hungry?
I brought french fries.
Yes, I'm hungry. You're the best.
Wow!
Would you like some, Ling?
No, thanks. I'm not hungry.
You've got sauce on your face.
You're so funny. It's right here.
- Can you wipe it off for me?
- At the corner of your mouth.
Artit, can you drive more carefully?
Are you hurt, Paeng?
Right here.
It's all red.
I'm begging you, Artit.
I'm about to throw up.
Thank you very much.
The children will be very happy.
We brought some sports equipment
this time too. They might like it.
You come to donate every year.
It's been very helpful.
Don't hurry back yet.
We're not intending to anyway.
We'll throw you a Khan Toke Banquet
as a thank you.
That would be great.
There are two rooms available
at the teacher housing.
I'll have someone prepare
them for you.
It's okay. We can do it ourselves.
Is that okay?
We can do it, right?
- Let's sleep here tonight, Paeng.
- Okay.
It's time for the children
to have lunch.
Would you like to go now?
- Let's go.
- Please.
- Okay.
This way, please.
- Please.
- Over this way.
(Eat hot food, use a serving
spoon, and wash your hands)
Who hasn't gotten any yet?
Would you like some?
Here you go.
Are they hungry?
Here it is.
Pass it on.
Pass this on to your friend.
Thank you.
Where's Non?
I don't know.
He's probably taking care of Ling.
I thought you liked Non?
Why are you indifferent
when I say that?
They're friends. It's not strange
for them to take care of each other.
Non loves Ling.
And why are you telling me this?
Well, I don't want to see
a dummy being fooled.
Paeng,
I think that you and Non
aren't really in a relationship.
Am I right?
I don't know.
Non asked me to be his girlfriend.
I like him so I said yes.
I'm telling you that he loves Ling.
If he does,
then why would he ask me
to be his girlfriend?
He's lying to you.
I'm okay with that.
So you want to be a donkey?
That's right. I'm okay
with being a donkey.
I can wait for him.
Hee-haw!
Non!
Where are you, Non? Are you around?
Nang, pretty lady.
What are you doing here?
Have you seen Non?
"Kot, you handsome guy.
Have you seen Non?"
Be polite to me first.
No!
Then I won't tell you.
Okay.
Kot, you handsome guy.
Have you seen Non?
I haven't.
You're being cheeky.
I'm not. I'm telling the truth.
You're his sister, so why
don't you know where he is?
I'm not his keeper,
I don't know his every move
I'm not either.
Jerk. I'm not talking to you.
What a waste of time!
Non!
"Jerk. I'm not talking to you.
What a waste of time!"
Walking away like that.
You think you're a model?
Oh?
- Hello, Auntie.
- Hello.
I made you some fish congee.
Thank you.
Is Artit still asleep?
Oh?
Didn't you know then he went on
a charity trip up North with Non?
- Oh? Did they?
- Yes.
I didn't know. Non didn't
tell me anything.
Who went with them?
I heard there are
four people on the trip.
There's Ling, Kot, Artit, and Non.
Why are you making that face?
Anything's the matter?
Kot didn't go with them.
- Huh?
- Who's the fourth person?
Oh?
It's Paeng.
What?
Non asked for my permission.
Kot! What do you have for sale?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Why did you slap me?
So you'll know that
you're not dreaming.
Whoa.
I've helped you.
It's time for you to help me.
Again? I don't want to.
No, you have to come
with me right now!
Nang, hold on. What's going on?
Do you see? Non
tricked you into coming on a trip.
Not at all, Ling.
It's fun. I like it.
Where is it?
I'll let Artit fix it for you.
Uh...
Here. There's a nail poking out.
I'm afraid it might snag someone
when they walk by.
Artit, can you hammer it down?
Paeng,
would you like some water?
My hands are dirty.
I'll help you.
It's so refreshing!
It's nice and cold. One more sip?
Artit, are you okay?
I knew it.
I'll go check on Artit.
I'll do it.
I think
maybe let Paeng do it.
Okay.
Uh...
Aren't you going to clean the floor?
Keeping cleaning.
Here. I'll wash it for you.
Paeng might overthink things
if you do this.
She won't.
Believe me.
What's up with you?
You're making me feel bad.
Do you know that?
What did I do?
Put it on.
Really!
I'll do it for you.
Hey!
It's not done yet.
Stay still.
Don't be nice to me.
I won't fall for you like Non did.
You don't have to fall for me.
Just stop hating me.
I'm probably hoping for too much.
Then,
I'd like to ask you
to hate me less. That's all.
I'm sorry.
That's virtually impossible.
Are you upset about me and Paeng?
I'm not.
Don't lie to yourself.
A person who runs away
from their feelings
won't be happy in life.
We've reached this point.
I think you should admit it.
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
I'm not trying to win over Paeng.
And I'm not in
a relationship with her either.
I'm doing this
because I want to know how you feel.
What about Paeng?
She's working with me.
You're so mean.
If I wasn't mean,
then I won't know how you feel.
Why did you have to lie to me?
It's you
who's lying to yourself.
Stop running away.
I know we feel the same way.
I don't want you to love me.
I can't do that.
And I don't want to love you.
Why not?
I'm afraid that
I'm not good enough to deserve you.
Ling,
I don't care about the future.
But I'm going to make
the best out of today.
When we reach our final day in life,
we're not going to be sad
over the mistakes we've made
but over the things we never did,
even though we wanted to.
I think
we shouldn't let our lives
go on like that.
If you don't love me,
I'll stop
and I'll let you go.
But if you do,
let's give it a go.
Are you cold, Paeng?
Put on a sweater.
Artit, have some
spicy Northern sausages.
I don't have an appetite.
Eat up.
You can always have more.
Thank you. Everything is so tasty.
Does it suit your taste?
I'd probably be so fat
if I stayed here for a month.
Please make yourselves comfortable.
Thank you.
Paeng,
do you want some spicy minced pork?
I'll serve you.
It's okay. I can do it.
Non, I think he's reached his
maximum hate level towards me.
Don't be afraid of him then.
Here you are.
Don't get full yet.
I've got you something good.
What is it?
It's a local drink.
It's unique to this place.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
It's so sweet.
Isn't it nice, Ling?
Very nice.
Hey!
Move out of the way!
I'm walking here!
Are you crazy?
Get out of the way!
You keep getting in the way.
Why are you like this?
Paeng, Paeng.
Are you okay?
You're picking a fight with a tree.
- Tree?
- Yes.
Tree!
I'm thirsty.
- I'm thirsty.
- Easy, easy.
You're such a lightweight.
I should have let you drink so much.
A lightweight?
Who are you calling a lightweight?
Who? Who?
I'm so thirsty.
Who turned off the lights?
She's wasted.
I'll look after her.
You? Looking after her?
Get lost. She's mine.
I mean she's my employee.
It's not working hours right now.
And this is not your farm.
Paeng, come with me.
Where are we going?
Paeng,
- come with me.
- I won't.
- Artit.
- What?
Come here, Paeng.
Paeng, Paeng.
Come on.
- Paeng.
- Don't pull me. It hurts.
Should we split me into two parts
so that you can have each half?
Really.
Paeng, where are you going?
- Paeng.
- Mister,
please check on your friend.
She's very drunk.
Okay. Artit.
I'm thirsty.
Ling?
How are you feeling?
Non,
I feel like throwing up.
Not yet. This way.
Here. This way.
Are you okay?
I don't usually see
you drink this much.
Why did you drink so much tonight?
It was so sweet.
Are you still feeling nauseous?
Would you like some water?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
I can take care of myself.
I'm tough.
Ling? Ling?
Don't tell me you've fallen asleep.
Hey?
You've fallen asleep.
Come here.
Walk carefully
or you'll fall off a cliff,
you sassy girl.
Who's sassy?
Who?
- Huh?
- You're so tough when you're drunk?
Right. Yes.
Do you think I'm scared
because you're bigger?
Power-hungry jerk.
And you're still insulting me?
No, I wasn't.
I was insulting the wind, the sky,
and the water.
But if you want to take it,
I'll let you have it.
Cheeky.
Go to bed.
I won't. Non! Where are you?
Why are you calling him now?
- Stop! Stop!
- Non!
Let me go. I don't
want to be with you.
I don't trust you.
You're mean and narrow-minded.
You like bullying and tormenting me.
I hate you!
Hey, Paeng!
Do you think I want to have
anything to do with you?
Don't throw a fit around here.
It's embarrassing.
- Let's go.
- I'm not going!
Oh, you're not?
You're not?
Artit, let me go!
- Let me go! Non!
- Stay still!
You meanie! You bully women!
It hurts.
You wanted me to let you go,
didn't you? I have now.
You black-hearted person.
You're cruel
and inhumane.
Whoa, you're good at hurling out
the insults when you're drunk.
That's right. I'm good.
Do you think you're so handsome?
And that's why I'd want you?
I was just too oblivious
in the past.
Wanfahmai!
Hey!
You narrow-minded person.
You're fixated on the past.
I'm not the same person anymore.
Stop talking. It's annoying.
No, I'm going to talk.
You're not the same person.
You used to be so much better.
I used to be so in love with you.
But now,
even if I got paid 20 million to
marry you, I wouldn't take it.
Eww!
I said stop talking.
Or I'll find something
to tape your mouth shut.
I don't want to be near you.
I hate you.
It's my room.
Paeng?
I'll take you to your room.
Leave me alone!
Paeng, come on.
I'm sleepy. I'll stay here.
Why am I worried about her?
Nonsense.
How come I'm worried about her?
No way.
I don't feel anything at all.
I don't like you.
It's obvious.
Even when I'm this close to you,
I still don't feel anything.
You just provoked me,
you sassy girl.
Paeng!
I'm comfortable. Don't fret.
Kot, are we going the right way?
Of course. According to the GPS,
we'll make it there for sure.
Don't worry.
(Dead end)
Hey!
Kot, you jerk!
You said you were following the GPS.
I was but I...
I might have put
in the wrong destination.
I'm sorry! Stop! I'm sorry!
Reverse then!
Reverse? Okay.
- Oh, shoot.
- What?
What?
What's wrong with the car?
What's wrong with the car!?
Nang,
how long are you going to sit
like that?
Don't be angry or hate me.
The car just ran out of gas,
that's all.
Do you think the car running
out of gas is a small issue?
You're the driver.
Why didn't you check the fuel gauge?
You can't just drive and
not pay attention to anything else.
I'm sorry.
Nang, it's my fault.
Don't be angry or hate me.
No!
I'm not okay.
And I won't forgive you easily.
I think you should get some rest.
Tomorrow morning I'll hitch a ride
and get us some gas, okay?
Maybe not.
Non.
Did you go inside the room?
I went to grab some clothes
and then came here for a bath.
What did you do to Paeng last night?
Nothing.
I stayed with Ling
until I fell asleep.
Hold on.
You stayed with Ling.
But what about Paeng?
I thought you were her boyfriend.
Well, weren't you watching over her?
It's a nice view. Good location.
Take off your clothes and get in.
It's comfortable.
Whoa!
Whoa! It's so cold!
One, two, three!
It's not my room!
Did you stay with me
the whole night?
Where's Paeng?
Artit was with her.
What's up with those two?
Let them be.
I don't want to know.
I only want to know about us.
I told you everything last night.
I'm still waiting for your answer.
Whether you want to be with me,
or not.
Aren't you afraid that someday,
if we can't make it work
that our friendship
would also end?
If I'm afraid,
I wouldn't have waited
for you for so long.
Aren't you afraid someday
I'll make you feel sad?
I'm not.
Aren't you afraid someday
I'll leave you again?
I'm not.
I'm ready to face everything.
No matter what's going to happen.
I'm not afraid of things
that haven't happened yet.
I just want to be with you now,
to love you,
and to take care of you.
As long as I know that your heart
is with mine,
I don't need anything else.
Be with me, Ling.
Who should I ask?
What's up?
Well...
I was drunk last night.
I woke up in your room.
You don't remember anything?
Last night,
you were going to assault me.
- That's impossible.
- It's already possible.
- That's not true.
- It is.
I don't feel anything
for you anymore.
If you don't, then why
would you do that?
I didn't mean it.
Artit, I'm sorry.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I really didn't mean it.
It's because you want me.
I didn't know what I was doing.
How are you going to atone for this?
What do you want me to do?
I'll let you know.
You're going to be dead for sure.
Oh, shoot!
Don't ever drink again, Paeng!
Ahh.
You followed me here?
It doesn't matter if it's heaven
or hell, I'm going to follow you.
So cheesy.
- Paeng.
- Don't fight each other.
Get lost.
I'll go find some help then.
So who do you want?
Artit or Non?
It would be nice if I could get
the both of them.
I'm not going to let
you have anyone,
not my brother or Artit.
You'll never get either of them.
Are you finished?
You parentless child!
You orphan!
You should've died in the
car crash with your parents!
I want to know
how long you're going
to be this evil.
Thank you
for making me realize
that I don't feel any pain from
your words anymore.
Let her go.
Ouch! Ouch!
Who are you?
It's you who should to stay
away from her.
Are you hurt?
A little bit.
Thank you.
I'm Mark.
Mark,
so we meet again. Perfect timing.
Why is she bullying you?
We've been arguing for a while now.
But I don't want to make
a big deal of it.
Because if I want to fight,
she wouldn't stand a chance.
I'm serious.
Okay. I believe you.
It's strange though.
We've met two days in a row now.
That's true.
From that mountain
to this one.
That's true.
You told me you grow roses.
Is it for fun or business?
I turn them into products to sell.
Really?
I'm very good at marketing.
If you're interested,
I could be your consultant.
- Really?
- Yes.
Artit, hurry.
Nang, have you seen Paeng?
You just saw me, but instead
of being worried about me,
you're asking for someone else.
Artit, I wanted
to come on the trip too.
But Paeng...
Where is she?
Paeng's with a guy.
They look really close.
It's like they agreed to meet.
They're over there.
Go ahead. You might find them.
Come on.
Come on!
Let's go.
Here.
That's true.
Who is that, Artit?
You sassy girl.
- I'll have to excuse myself.
- Okay.
I'll see you later.
Come on. Time to go.
Paeng,
Ling will come with us.
Really? That's great.
Paeng, come to my car.
Come on, Ling.
Hold on. I just got here.
Kot, bring my sister home.
Can't we at least share a meal?
Non!
Really!
Is this even possible?
I haven't even had any sleep.
Do you know that guy?
I asked you a question.
Are you deaf?
I didn't know you're talking to me.
You just spoke suddenly.
There's only the two of us.
Who else would I be talking to?
Who is that?
It's Mark.
Who is he?
I don't know him.
You don't know him?
You look liked you were close.
That's impressive.
What is?
Your seduction skills.
I didn't seduce him.
Last night,
did I really do something to you?
Do you think I was lying?
Do you want to see the pictures?
I don't have any.
Who's going to take a selfie
during that kind of thing?
What did you do then?
I hurried out and slept outside.
I can't let my guard down
when you're around.
Miss Paeng!
Why did you come back
with Mr. Artit?
And why the long face?
Was he bullying you again?
What did he do to you?
Oh?
He didn't do anything to me.
But I did something to him.
What did you do to him?
He'll get you back again. Haven't
you learned your lesson?
He also threatened me
and said that I'll be dead for sure.
Dead?
What are you going to do?
I'll do anything.
Anything to atone for my mistake.
Huh? What did you say?
Artit came back with Paeng?
That's right. Just the two of them.
I couldn't stop them in time.
They just disappeared.
Krongprateep!
You said Paeng liked Non.
She's actually waiting for Artit.
What should I do, Nang?
Don't worry, Auntie.
I'll take Artit back.
What are you going to do?
You've made so many mistakes.
Auntie, trust me.
I won't lose Artit.
We'll fight together.
Okay. We'll fight together, right?
Yes.
Get off!
What are you thinking?
Oh!
I was thinking...
about work.
Since you got back,
I haven't seen you.
Are you trying to avoid me?
I'm not.
Why would I do that?
When you do something wrong,
you always avoid me.
I...
I just wanted to hurry back to work.
I was gone for so many days,
everything is backed up.
Are you sure that you're not going
to tell me the truth?
What truth?
Well, there's the fact
you came back with Paeng.
Who told you?
Nang did.
We live at the same place.
It's not strange to carpool.
But for people who hate each other,
isn't it uncomfortable
to sit in a car
together for that long?
I just put up with it.
Don't lie to me.
Artit,
I'm telling you now.
Don't you ever give in to her.
What are you doing, Miss Paeng?
Aren't you going to experiment
with the soap you made?
I tried it out.
My face was so soft.
Aueng,
I just tried making body soap.
It smelled so nice.
It's a waste to only use it
only on the body.
Your tea smells nice too.
It looks really pretty
and delicious.
Are you making some for me to try?
Wow, I'm so lucky.
Make lots of them, Miss Paeng.
Come in.
Miss Paeng made something for you.
In hopes that her punishment
might be less harsh.
Is she scared?
A little bit.
She said that
if you're not going to eat and
throw it away, she's okay with that.
Are these rose petals edible?
Of course.
She grew the roses just for this.
For food, desserts, and products.
This is her first product.
And you're the first to taste it.
So I'm the guinea pig?
Just to taste it.
"To atone for what I did.
This is for you, Artit."
Anyway, what did she do?
Something very severe.
And I'm very angry.
She guessed it right.
Guessed what?
That you're still angry.
But she also said,
that she'll be nice to you,
little by little.
So that I'll give in?
What if I don't forgive her,
what would she do?
She'll keep going.
What if she keeps going,
but I still won't forgive her?
What would she do then?
Uh...
I don't know anymore.
I have to go now. Goodbye.
What kind of guy would
eat something like this?
- Aueng!
- Miss Paeng.
Bad news?
Yes. It's a waste of time.
It's going to be difficult
to get him to forgive you.
Miss Paeng!
Artit,
you two left me with Nang.
I'm exhausted.
What a high-maintenance woman.
Can you believe that I felt like
I was in a living hell?
She wouldn't even let me stop for
street food.
She's angry with you and Non but
took it all out on me.
I don't understand it at all.
All the way from the summit
to the foot of the mountain,
my ears are numb.
I haven't eaten anything.
Hey!
I can't even eat this?
Why are you so heartless?
I had to put up with Nang's rant
- from the summit to the foot.
- Here.
Go buy something for yourself.
Now, this is what you call
friendship.
Would you like anything?
It's my treat.
No? I'm going then. Thank you.
This is the first rose
that blossomed in my garden.
Please wish me success, Mom and Dad.
You little rascal,
what are you doing?
I want a sibling.
Miss Paeng,
aren't you going to bed?
What are you writing?
I'm about to go to sleep.
Wait!
It's good that you're awake.
Uh... Well...
Let's go to the kitchen.
Why?
We're out of drinking water.
And I forget to get some.
The way to the kitchen is so dark.
I'm too lowly to walk
there by myself.
It's "lonely."
That's it.
You're afraid of ghosts.
Hey! Miss Paeng, don't say that!
Otherwise, they might come.
Okay, I won't mention them.
I'll keep you company.
You're the best.
- Let's go.
- Aueng,
you're this scared, huh?
Everyone, concentrate.
This is serious.
You can't be fooling
around with this.
Since you thought of doing it,
then you have to it.
Geeve mee the eensense.
Huh?
Give me the incense!
Come on!
It's the language of
the divine spirits.
The loitair.
- Huh?
- Lighter!
- Oh, the lighter!
- Just say it!
Poot ye hans togezer.
Put your hands together.
You're such a know-it-all.
Of course.
Alright. Focus.
Concentrate.
Put your finger on the cup.
Phut-Tho-Tha-Ya
What are you doing?
Come on!
You startled us!
You came out of nowhere!
You might get possessed!
What are you doing?
Playing Hi-Lo, maybe?
Ouija board?
That's right. Oh yeah board.
Ouija board.
(Rest)
Do you know it?
I've heard of it.
But I've never used one.
What are you doing? It's insulting.
Aren't you scared?
I'm not.
Last time, my friend got
three numbers.
- The lottery?
- Puppies.
Of course, the lottery.
Then, I'm in.
Aren't you scared anymore?
If they're here to bring us good
luck, then don't need to be scared.
You're just like me, Aueng.
If we summon a spirit we know,
the winning numbers are going to
be even more accurate.
A spirit that I know?
I don't want to! I'm scared!
Is it really possible
to summon them?
It's up to each person's judgment.
It's just for fun, Miss Paeng.
It's nothing serious.
Miss Paeng,
you can ask anything.
Anything you'd like to know.
But on one condition,
if you're rude,
they might not answer you.
But if you want to ask, fire away.
So I can ask anything?
Then I'm in.
Alright!
Mom,
if you can hear me,
I'd like to talk to you.
Put your finger on the cup.
Phut-Tho-Tha-Ya
Whoa! Th-th-they're here?
Are you the person I summoned?
Don't tell me...
Miss Paeng, ask anything you want.
Can you tell me
who killed you?
Don't let your finger
get off the glass
Where is it going?
"A"
"M"
"N"
A man?
Do you know what his name is?
- What is it?
- Why is it going in circles?
What is it?
Oh?
What are you playing at?
Mr. Artit.
Pong, it's ruined.
Will we be possessed?
That's right.
Who's possessed? An ouija board?
Tell me who started it.
It's late. You should all be resting
so that you'll be energized
for work tomorrow.
What is this?
It's nonsense.
Pong,
you're the oldest.
Why didn't you stop them?
Uh...
It's Pong who asked us.
You too.
Are you crazy?
Why did you join them?
You have a bachelor's degree but
believe in something like this.
Did you ever consider
that you're a woman?
You got out late. People will say
you're out seducing men.
Do you want people to think
worse than they already do?
Isn't that too harsh, Mr. Artit.
No, it's not, Pong.
You're an adult now.
Can't you think for yourself?
You're in a circle of men.
There's probably only one thing
on your mind.
No decent woman would do this.
Go! Get back to bed!
Disperse.
Is it so wrong that
I wanted to know?
I haven't caused you
trouble for a while now.
Why do you have
to keep harassing me?
What did you want to know?
It's my business.
I don't care what people
think of me anymore.
Because I didn't do anything wrong.
It's you who keeps finding
fault with me.
Are you accusing me of doing that?
That's right.
You're always harassing me
because you hate me.
You hate me!
I hate you too!
I hate you, Artit!
And do you think I'm so into you?
Miss Paeng!
Saeb, what happened?
Tell me.
Well,
Aueng and Miss Paeng
came to get some water.
Well,
we put out the ouija board to ask
for some lottery numbers.
But when Miss Paeng came,
she asked to join.
- She summoned the ghost herself.
- That's right.
Who did she summon?
I don't know.
But Miss Paeng wished inwardly.
And she said something like,
"who killed you?"
"Who killed you?"
That's right.
And the ghost said "a man."
Enough! Nonsense!
Get back to bed.
You're an adult now.
Can't you think for yourself?
You're in a circle of men.
There's probably only one thing
on your mind.
No decent woman would do this.
I haven't caused you
trouble for a while now.
Why do you have
to keep harassing me?
You're always harassing me
because you hate me.
I hate you too!
I hate you, Artit!
And do you think I'm so into you?
Dad.
Where's Mom?
She's probably in the kitchen.
Dad,
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Well,
didn't Paeng's parents
die in a car crash?
Why are you asking me that?
Did Paeng's parents
really die in a car crash?
What did you hear?
Why are you mentioning this?
It's none of your business.
I want to know, Dad.
Can you tell me?
No.
That's Paeng's private matter.
And it happened a long time ago.
It shouldn't be dug up.
Some guy is at the rose garden.
He's really handsome.
He's Miss Paeng's type.
I told Lin to invite Paeng over.
Are you going to come?
I'm not coming.
- Who are you?
- Someone Paeng has to listen to.
Ling, I'm going home.
They're being romantic in public.
They don't respect
you at all, Artit.
I'll see you at home, darling.
Where are you? Tell me!
He's your type? You like him?
Very much.
He's exactly my type.