(My Forever Sunshine)
I have nothing to lose!
My parents are dead!
I don't need to care
about anyone anymore.
- He tried to rape me.
- Liar!
Hey!
Mr. Artit was in a car accident.
Go and live in Bangkok.
When things get better,
you can come back.
Live a better life, Miss Paeng.
He's very popular nowadays,
both in and out of the field.
Girls are clamoring for him.
Non, it's me.
I was the one who answered.
I heard everything.
Are you going to leave me?
You love him, don't you?
Do you know
that you're bad at lying, Ling?
- Paeng!
Just a moment, Uncle.
Just a moment.
It's very delicious.
I've gained weight
because you feed me so well
every time I visit you.
A present for the new graduate.
Uncle!
Thank you so much
for always taking care of me
We're not strangers.
You're like one of my own.
How could I ever abandon you?
You've graduated.
What are you thinking of doing next?
Can I have a taste?
You've surprised me
with many things.
Ever since you chose
to study agriculture,
what have you been thinking?
I have you as my idol.
- Hmm?
- It's true.
I saw the flowers grow
and bloom.
It's like I've turned
over a new leaf.
Like what I once told you,
growing flowers.
is what I do best.
And flowers are
for women, aren't they?
I want to turn petals into perfume,
food, and tea.
Because I graduated
directly from that field.
I'm relieved.
I was worried
about how a little girl like you
could be a farmer.
I did that too.
Huh?
Ta-da!
This is the land that I bought.
Isn't it beautiful?
Very beautiful. Fabulous!
I'm thinking of
digging a pond there.
And grow some roses on that hill.
And build
a small factory over here.
Isn't it good?
It's good. But...
where are you going to sleep?
You need a house.
That's true. I forgot.
I kept thinking about roses.
Instead of
digging a pond over there,
why don't you build a small
a one-story house?
A cute little house like in
"Beauty and the Beast."
- Awesome, Sister.
- Isn't it?
Uncle,
do you like it?
You're a little girl.
How can you be a farmer?
I can do it.
Paeng, everything isn't
as easy as you think.
Being a girl
and living alone
on a farm isn't safe.
From now on,
I can't let you do things
on your own.
Is it that depressing?
Uncle made me agree
to do an experimental plot.
If I'm successful within two years,
he'll let me fly solo.
That's good. So you won't have to do
the trial-and-error run on your own.
Good my butt.
The people at her uncle's farm
don't like her.
They don't just dislike me,
they actually hate me.
Wow, trouble ahead.
How are you going to go back there?
I'll probably die if I do.
I won't survive.
What are you going to do?
I don't know!
Gosh!
This is giving me a headache.
Why did Master tell us
to clean this room?
I have a bad feeling that
rotten Paeng is coming back.
You're saying unlucky things.
I can't help but think about that.
Master hasn't let us open up
this room for years.
Then suddenly, he calls and
tells us to hurry and clean it up.
It's like somebody's coming to stay.
Don't you agree?
I hope rotten Paeng is gone for good
and never returns. Sathu.
Paeng, I'm hungry.
Please let me go my own way.
I really can do it.
But I can't.
Paeng, if it's like this,
how am I going to face
your dad when I die?
I'm only asking for two years.
I'm not asking for your whole life.
Let me keep my promise.
Let me look after you.
Let me repay your Dad.
But I really can't go back there.
You know why.
Why are you overthinking it?
No one thinks about it anymore.
But I still feel guilty.
Well? You can go back
and fix things then.
You have to go back and show
them that you've changed, right?
If you keep running,
you'll have to keep running
and feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
And in the end, the person
who feels guilty
is me.
Do you want that?
Uncle!
I've already prepared your room
for you.
You can go back tomorrow.
Uh...
What do you say?
Uh... then
I'd like some time to pack
and psych myself up.
Of course.
Well,
have you told the others?
Of course I have.
What did they say?
No one said anything.
Really?
And
what about the other others?
What did they say?
The other others?
They didn't say anything either.
No one complained at all?
Paeng, I've told you
it's been six years already.
Nobody's thinking about it anymore.
What do you say? When will you come?
Should I pick you up?
It's okay. I can get there myself.
But I...
I'd like to go on the 15th.
Okay.
Gosh!
Wanfahmai!
- What is it?
- A treasure map?
No, it's a map of Sunshine Farm.
If you can't contact me
for more than three days,
go and look for my corpse here.
My corpse should be buried there
because it's the back of the farm.
People don't go there often.
Is it that scary?
So are you going to start a new life
- or kill yourself?
- Right?
It's probably the latter.
Paeng,
- your former potential husb...
- Stop.
I really can't let you in
on any secrets, okay?
Alright, Artit. Is he that scary?
It's not him
but me. I've done
so many things to him.
Paeng,
if you know what you're
going to encounter,
- why would you go back?
- She is right.
I have to go no matter what.
To atone for my sins.
What sins?
Huh? I have to go today?
Yes, sir.
But my niece is coming today.
Let Pong go in my place.
I really can't go.
You can't do that, sir.
They want to talk to you alone.
If you don't go and see them today,
they'll cancel all orders
until the end of the year.
That's not good.
I'll go then.
You two,
can I get a hug?
It might be the last time we meet.
Of course!
You jerk, don't talk like that.
I'm about to cry.
Come on.
What do you want to eat? I can
make merit and send it to you.
- Jerk.
- I didn't really mean it.
I'm going now.
Hey! Paeng, call me
when you get there.
Okay.
Call me every day too.
- Hey!
- Hey, Khanoon!
Enough or she might not get to go.
She's not going to face death.
Come on, Paeng. Get in the car.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
This is disastrous.
That girl's coming back today
and you're telling me now?
It's good that I tell you now
so you can't refuse.
Even if you tell me now,
I'd still refuse.
Paeng is coming.
Let her stay in the same room.
I'll be away for 2-3 days
and I'll hurry back.
I don't want to be a part of this.
Up to you.
But don't cause any trouble.
Go and tell that girl.
I won't be the one
who starts a fight.
I hope that's true.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
- I have to go now.
- Hold on, Krongprateep.
Have you told Artit
that she's coming today?
I haven't. You tell him.
I have to go now or I'll be late.
Krongprateep!
I'm not a mailbox.
You keep asking
me to relay messages.
Big news, everyone!
- What?
- Big news!
What's the big news!
Let me breathe a little.
If it's not big, I'll kill you.
It's big! Really big!
Bigger than my face!
Listen carefully, everyone.
I'm going to say it once
and I won't repeat myself.
Because it might not be the same.
Come on.
Just say it already!
Miss Paeng is coming back!
Oh, oh!
You're all stunned! See?
Is the news big enough?
Where did you hear that from?
Straight from Madam's mouth.
Holy spirits save us.
The spirits won't be
able to save us.
I knew it.
That's why Master told us
to clean up her room.
Why isn't she leave for good?
Why is she coming back again?
What does Mr. Artit say?
Does he know?
It's not important
if he knows it or not.
Master actually ordered
Miss Paeng to come back.
Who's going to defy him?
Would you dare?
And she dares to come back?
I don't know about that.
But I know.
Huh? What do you know?
I know that from this day forward,
there won't be peace on our farm.
Come on, Pong!
Our farm has been quiet
for many years.
It might be entertaining and fun.
Paeng's return will be
la-la-la, la-la-la.
La-la-la. La-la-la.
Huzzah, huzzah.
Are you happy
that our farm going to be chaos?
What should we do?
Why would she come back?
Wait, you're not at the farm?
That's right. I have some urgent
business to attend to.
It won't take long.
How many hours?
Around two to three days.
Huh? That is long, Uncle.
Then, I'll...
I'll return to Bangkok.
I'll be back in three days.
Paeng, Paeng! Hold on.
Paeng,
I've arranged everything.
They're probably
expecting you at the farm.
Just go and wait for me there.
I'll see you in three days.
(Sunshine Farm)
Three more days!
Will I survive?
Hey!
Just go ahead
if you're in such a rush?
Hey!
They're doing that on purpose.
What on earth is going on?
Your parents didn't raise you right!
(Sunshine Farm)
Who's here?
Madam Tubtim!
Madam! Madam!
If I'm carrying a bamboo basket,
then it's exactly like in the novel.
Why are you smiling at her?
I haven't seen her in a while.
I'm just being polite.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
You haven't changed.
Still ill-mannered as always.
Hello, Tubtim.
Who is she looking for?
I wonder.
Where's Artit?
- Oh?
- Where's Artit?
Oh!
Look at her, Madam.
She just got here
and already she's asking for him.
You're still haven't given up
to have Mr. Artit
as your husband, haven't you?
You're very brazen.
You only just arrived and you're
already asking for my son.
Please don't get me wrong.
I don't feel anything
for Artit anymore.
When pigs fly.
Who's going to believe you?
Krongprateep let you stay here
because he pities you.
Don't go asking
for anything from us.
I'm not going to ask for anything.
I came back
because Uncle asked me to.
Are you saying that
Krongprateep is the one
who told you to come?
I'm not talking down on him.
Madam, she's talking back at you.
What a rude girl!
You're still as bad as always.
You're not even remorseful
for what you've done.
And now you've brazenly
marched back here.
Your skin must be
as thick as concrete.
Madam, watch out.
She's clenching her fist.
She might hurt us.
I'll go to my room now.
Hold on!
What?
You go.
Go.
- Go on.
- Go.
Is she going to punch me?
Your room
is in the workers' shack.
I thought Uncle said
no one would mind if I came.
I think it's more like
no one has forgotten.
Whoa!
Come on, Paeng!
Keep your head down
and accept your fate.
You've done a lot to them.
Oh, no.
How are the ducks?
- Three eggs? How many ducks?
- Thirty.
Thirty ducks
- but only three eggs?
- Kaew!
Kaew!
Where's Mr. Artit?
- Why are you asking?
- Don't ask me.
Just tell me where he is.
You're good, Wanfahmai.
I'm so hungry.
Six years.
So many things have changed.
Uncle's pretty amazing to have
done so much.
I'm starving.
Where am I going to eat?
Are you that surprised?
Artit.
Uncle didn't tell me that you're...
Handicapped?
Artit, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it. I'm sorry.
Can I exchange your apology
and break your legs instead?
If you knew what I lost,
you wouldn't have
said that stupid apology.
Then,
what do you want me to do?
You can tell me.
You're the one who made me
end up like this.
How are you going to repay me?
I'm happy to do anything
to make you feel better.
Anything?
Yes.
You said it yourself, Wanfahmai.
Don't say that I'm mean.
Artit, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it. I'm sorry.
If you knew what I lost,
you wouldn't have
said that stupid apology.
Follow me.
Where are we going? It's still dark.
Oh? It's already morning?
Follow me.
What are you going to do?
Not me.
It's you who has to do it.
Clean it up.
But you have to
finish up before noon.
Because I have another job
for you in the afternoon.
But I'm not...
I thought you said you'll do
anything to repay for what you did?
I'm so hungry.
Gosh.
Grilled beef.
I'm sorry
for thinking negative
things about you.
So hungry.
Food's here!
- Food's here!
- Food's here?
Mister, you've brought food?
Thank you!
Why are you thanking me?
You're like an angel from heaven
blessing me with food.
These are for the cows.
For the cows?
Don't be sad.
Mr. Artit said to tell you to go
and see him at the canteen.
Canteen?
But the canteen is far away.
- Are there any bikes here?
- There aren't.
It's only a 20-minute walk.
A 20-minute walk?
It's so far.
There.
Eat up.
You're a laborer.
The food's nice today.
Why don't you let him
give the compliments?
What are you doing?
I'm here to eat.
Mr. Artit told you
to wash the dishes,
not to eat.
But I'm hungry.
It's your business, not mine.
What's that stench?
You stink of manure!
Yuck! Go away!
People will lose appetite.
What are you doing?
If you hurt me, Mr. Artit won't
let you get away with this.
I'm just going to say
that I won't put up with it anymore.
Right. Get lost then.
And don't ever come back.
She can't even take it.
That's right. Someone like you
shouldn't have come back,
since you were the reason
Mr. Artit got into a car accident.
She's got some nerve.
Duang,
if you don't say anything,
no one's going to call you a mute.
- Just eat your food.
- Oh?
Why bothering talking?
You're a busybody.
- And I let her get back at me.
- Yes.
Go and get all the dishes and
pots and pans in
the kitchen for her to wash.
If she's going to be brazen and stay
then we should put her to work.
So she gets what she deserves
for hurting Mr. Artit.
Of course, Thongkhum.
I'll let her have it.
Keep an eye on her.
I'm going to see Madam.
I'm so hungry.
Whose dish is this?
They didn't even put it away
or wash it afterward.
See? There's a lot of leftovers.
I'll put it right here.
Uh...
Hurry up and eat. Take big bites.
Someone might see you.
Would you like anything else, Madam?
This is a lot. I won't be
able to finish it all.
Thongkhum, how is she doing?
Mr. Artit's coming down hard on her.
First, she has to clean
the cattle pen in the morning.
Then she had to wash the dishes
for the workers in the afternoon.
Now she's removing the grass
from the farming plots.
She deserves it.
Just let her bear with it
as she pleases.
Madam, I've heard
that Master is going to
let her stay forever?
Oh! I don't think so.
He told me she's going to be here
for two years and then she'll go.
Sathu. I hope it really
is two years.
If she stays forever,
my life expectancy will decrease.
I can't even stand seeing her face.
But I don't think she'll be
able to stay for two years.
I should've brought some sunscreen.
It's really hot, Artit.
What's stinky?
Cow manure?
I didn't even get to shower
or brush my teeth.
Now I stink of manure. Oh, well.
Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
Miss Paeng!
Come on. It might be too late.
Paeng,
Mr. Artit is asking for you.
Not just yet. I'm not done here.
Can the other jobs wait?
I don't think it's about work.
He said for you to meet
him at the house.
- At the house?
- That's right.
What part of the house?
He said for you to go
see him in his room.
But
I can't remember
which room.
I forgot on the way here.
Oh!
Why did you come in here?
Uh...
Or are you going to do
something to my son again?
I'm not going to do anything to him.
Your mouth says you're
not asking for anything.
But your actions
don't go along with it.
I guess it's true,
personality can't be easily changed.
Before, you were just rotten
on the inside.
But now it's outside as well.
Well, Artit told me to come see him.
I don't believe you!
My son would never
call you into our house!
I told her to come.
Why did you do that?
Aren't you scared?
Mom, don't worry.
How can I not worry?
I can't even stand seeing her face.
Oh, dear. I have to go and
run errands too.
Let's do it this way.
I'll let Duang watch over you.
I don't trust her.
I'm going to give you a chance,
but only for today.
Go home.
But if you stay,
you'll face things
harsher than before.
When that time comes,
you'll have missed the chance
that I'm about to give you.
Yes, Dad?
Artit, where's Paeng?
She's right here with me.
I can't get a hold of Paeng.
I'm very worried about her.
No one did anything to her?
Your niece is perfectly safe.
Don't joke around with me, Artit.
Can I talk to her?
Artit, I'd like to talk to her.
Uncle.
Paeng, how are you doing?
No one did anything
to you, did they?
No one.
I told Artit to look after you
and help train you for work.
He didn't defy my orders, did he?
Artit,
is doing a good job
looking after me.
If anything happens,
just hang in there.
Promise me
that I'll get to see you
when I go back.
Yes, I promise.
Bye.
What did you promise my dad?
I promised him that
I'll wait here to see him.
Wanfahmai.
I'm just waiting for him.
Alright.
Then I'll consider it your refusal
to the chance I'm about to give you.
You'll die on my watch.
I'm going to tell Uncle.
Wanfahmai!
I can help myself.
It's like talking to a brick wall.
You can do anything you want to me.
I've already told myself
that I'll stay so I can pay you back
until you forgive me.
Okay, I forgive you!
Go home then.
If you actually forgive me one day,
I will go.
I'm going back to work now.
Hey!
What's going on?
This is not the time to be broken.
What are you doing, Wanfahmai?
Stop it now! Stop!
Get your filthy hands off me!
Hey! Stop that!
Let me go! I can do it!
You're here, Mr. Artit.
His wheelchair broke down.
So I brought him here.
Have some dinner.
I'll go and eat at the canteen.
Don't go yet.
Take me to the table.
It looks delicious.
I've cooked all of your favorites.
I did my best.
You've been working hard all day.
I think you should eat now.
Thank you.
Wanfahmai!
Come and eat with me.
Is he possessed?
Come and sit over here.
What's wrong with him?
How should I know?
Come.
Sit.
Who told you to sit here?
- Duang.
- Yes?
Bring Dizzy's bowl.
Okay, sir.
Here you go.
Your place is right there.
Eat up.
Come on.
If you don't feel comfortable
eating with me,
I'll go.
Do you think you're going
to be able to trick me?
How am I tricking you?
You're not like this.
A person's personality
isn't something that can be
changed easily.
That's too polite, sir.
More like it's her true colors.
That's right.
Personality can be changed.
But true colors can't.
Have it your way.
If you want me to do anything,
just have someone fetch me.
Arrogant!
Darn it!
I was so satisfied
when Mr. Artit
threw the food on the floor.
Her jaw dropped.
I'm satisfied too.
Next time, I'm going to record
a video of her face.
Is there going to be a next time?
If she's still going to be
brazen and stay, there will be.
We have to let
Mr. Artit go hard on her.
I never thought he could
be this mean.
- That's true.
- It's so satisfying.
He really put a smile on my face.
By the way, do you think she'll
be able to endure it?
Come on. Even if she doesn't,
what else can she do?
Oh, did you forget
how evil she can be?
Beneath that calm
and innocent exterior,
she might be concocting something
or lose control of herself.
If she dares to do it,
then just go ahead.
There's Mr. Artit, Madam,
and all the farmhands here.
If she dares do it,
then come and get it.
That's true.
I'm so satisfied.
Gosh!
What am I going up against?
Oh! Uh.
Hi.
Hey! Oh my gosh,
what have you been doing?
- Why are you battered like that?
- Did you climb three mountains?
Worse.
I don't get to eat.
I'm sleep deprived.
I don't get to shower either.
Hey!
I don't want to get into details.
In short, I'm atoning for my sins.
I'll go and wash my face.
Come on! The water's not running!
Where's your uncle?
Why isn't he helping?
I know right!
I came when he's away for work
so they're hazing me.
I'm just unlucky.
What did you do to them?
Something serious?
I'm choosing not to answer you.
I'm starting to worry about you.
- Me too.
- Is it going to get any worse?
Right?
Is there going to be
anything worse than this?
Paeng! Paeng!
- The screen just went black!
- Paeng! Hello?
- Let's pack it up.
- Okay.
I'm so hungry.
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
I'll eat it.
Have you done packing things up?
Hey!
How come you allowed
her to eat my food?
She just came over and grabbed some.
Next time, don't let just
anyone come and eat my food.
People can be so shameless.
Well, I've already eaten it.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
I almost didn't see you there.
You want to die?
I don't want to, sir.
Mr. Artit.
She didn't get to eat. She's
been working hard the whole day.
She doesn't have
access to utilities either.
She might not be able to make it.
Who told her to endure it?
But she's a woman living alone
in a dark room.
Should we let her have some light?
Just torture her during the daytime.
If you turn it on for you,
go and be on her team.
You left me some candles?
Do I have to be thankful?
My battery is dead.
Do not show her any mercy.
Do not help her.
Anyone who defies my orders,
be prepared to find a new job.
Whoever can chase
this woman out of the farm,
will be rewarded.
Whoa, right in front of me.
But if she's still being stubborn
and I lose control and kill her.
Just turn a blind eye,
understand?
Go back to work.
I mean you. Get to work!
But I haven't eaten.
How will I have the energy to work?
The grass you removed. Just eat it.
Artit,
you can make me work
as hard as you want.
But humans need food and sleep.
If I get to eat,
I'll have the energy to work.
So I can work for you.
Isn't that better?
But I don't want you to.
I don't want you to
set foot in here.
My family's already paid
off the debt to you.
Why are you still here?
Consider it my repayment to you.
I don't want it.
You really want me to go?
Artit,
there's not going to be a day
that you forgive me, is there?
Look at me.
And tell me
if you deserve forgiveness
for what you've done.
Promise me,
that I'll get to see you
when I go back.
I don't want you to
set foot in here.
My family's already paid
off the debt to you.
Why are you still here?
I'm only asking for two years.
I'm not asking for your whole life.
Look at me.
And tell me
if you deserve forgiveness
for what you've done.
You have to go back and show
them that you've changed.
If you keep running,
you'll have to keep running
and feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
Hiya! Hiya! Whoo!
Good vibes only! Today I,
I can do anything
to impress the ladies
Yo! Yo! Yo!
I'm single. I need love.
Anyone can come to me for love.
It's Paeng's car.
What's the rush?
Or maybe!
Duang, you have to be
my eyes and ears.
Artit is busy
trying to kick her out.
I'm afraid he might fall
for her tricks again.
Don't worry, Madam.
I'll be your ears, eyes, mouth,
hands, and feet.
Excellent.
Mr. Artit! Mr. Artit!
Mr. Artit! Madam!
I'm so tired! Where's Artit?
- What...
- What's up? Say it.
Well... Well...
- Come...
- Come on. Just say it.
- The thing is...
- Again?
Duang, you don't have to
be my mouth right now.
What's the matter, Saeb?
Paeng's left the farm.
Huh?
I'm so tired.
Why did you bring me here?
Why didn't you drive me?
Madam, you practically ran here.
Duang, check inside to see
if she's actually gone.
- Okay.
- Wait, wait.
I'll do it myself.
Gosh!
What's the matter, Madam?
- All her belongings are here.
- That's right.
Saeb, so what is it?
Is she gone or not?
I saw her. She's really gone.
Was she in a rush
and left her stuff?
Saeb, are you sure that you saw her?
With my own eyes, Madam.
She drove away so fast.
Let's do this. Move all her
things out.
I'll let Krongprateep send them
back to her by mail.
Should we just burn all of it?
That's going too far.
Go and pack up her stuff Go.
It wasn't that hard to
chase her out after all.
Right?
Who ordered that stuff?
What's all this?
Why did you bring them here?
Please sign for them, ma'am.
I won't. I didn't order them.
But the instruction
says to deliver here.
This is Sunshine Farm, isn't it?
That's right.
But I didn't order these.
Portable stove, plates,
a blender, and a lot of dried food.
You can just sign for them.
Everything's already been paid for.
Take them all back.
Don't try to con us.
People these days are sleazy.
But the customer's
name is Wanfahmai.
- Huh?
- It's mine.
Huh?
You came quickly. You got here
before me. The service is great.
But do you mind delivering
them to another location?
- I'll lead you there.
- Of course.
- This way, please.
- Okay, miss.
Move them all out.
I'm not allowing this.
Well, then. We can just
put them here for now.
Understood.
Duang, she got inside!
Oh?
Come here! Get out now!
Where are you taking that?
Madam won't allow this.
Give it to me.
But I bought it.
Why can't I take them inside?
No!
Ah! Madam!
It hurts!
Paeng,
how dare you hurt her?
If you weren't so biased,
you'd see that I didn't do it.
What should I do with you?
What are you doing to my mom?
I thought you were gone.
You're still being brazen
and staying?
I didn't say I was going.
I just went out shopping.
Take these things away.
You have no right to do
whatever you want here.
What do you want me to do?
I can't eat at the house.
I can't eat in the kitchen.
I can't use Thongkhum's
kitchen to cook either.
I can't eat via
photosynthesis either.
Are you being cheeky with me?
I wasn't. I was only explaining.
Cheeky!
You're deliberately
getting on my nerves.
I really came here to work.
And since I have to eat,
but everyone here won't let me
use anything from the farm,
I need survival gear.
You've gotten better
at talking back.
I'm not talking back.
I'm only explaining.
If there's anything you're upset
about, just tell me.
Or if you're still thinking
that I'm invading your farm.
If you want me to pay rent
and utility bills,
you can just tell me.
I'm happy to pay.
If it makes everyone happy.
I'll be happy
when you leave.
People don't want you here
but you're still being so brazen.
I have to stay here.
Look at her, Madam!
Don't you even have
a shred of emotion left?
I do.
I caused this to happen to you,
so I need to pay you back.
I know what I've done in the past
makes it hard for you to believe
that I'm truly remorseful.
But I will do it.
I will prove to you
that I fully intend
to apologize to you.
I don't need an apology from you.
I believe
that if I put my mind to it,
you'll see it.
Alright.
You said you won't be
a nuisance staying here.
Then I'll take back the house.
Go put up a tent and you there.
You're being sarcastic.
I'm not.
I'm just doing what you want.
How am I going to sleep tonight?
Think for yourself.
Aren't you good at problem-solving?
Artit, can you be
a little reasonable?
It's because I hate you,
that's my reason.
But you have no right to hurt me.
You have no right
to ruin my life as well.
But if you want to prove it,
I'll let you do it.
Do you dare?
Okay.
You want me to make some charcoal?
Not make charcoal.
I want you to make wood vinegar.
Don't tell me that
you don't know it.
Didn't you study agriculture?
I know it.
Wood vinegar is produced
from burning charcoal,
from the destructive distillation of
wood at 300-400 degrees Celcius.
It's very useful for agriculture
and livestock development.
It can be used
to kill microorganisms
and mold.
It can also kill many kinds of
plant diseases and insects.
Your theory is top-notch.
But I hope you're also practical.
I can do it.
If you can't,
you have to leave the farm.
Okay.
Good.
Consider it an agreement.
Here's the pail.
Find some soil yourself.
- Let me help, Paeng.
- No!
Let her do it alone.
And I'll be back to
check up on your work.
Move this wood to somewhere else.
Don't leave even a single stick.
Yes, sir.
Gosh!
What perfect timing!
They're out of wood
right when I need it.
Fallen branches.
Fallen branches in the woods.
That's it.
It's good I learned about this.
Oh, where's the wood?
What a bummer!
It's a bummer for me too.
I thought she's going away.
She's so shameless.
She knows people hate her
but she stayed anyway.
"I'm going to have my own kitchen."
"I won't bother Sunshine Farm."
She's rich. She can do anything.
She solves her problems with money.
I hate her.
Why doesn't she buy a fridge and
a washing machine then?
Hey, Thongkhum.
Has she bought them
but they haven't been delivered?
Then that means
she's staying permanently?
No! I couldn't handle it.
I couldn't handle it either.
What should we do?
I know. We can curse her
so that there's an incident that
forces her out.
Just go. Gone for good.
And never come back.
Sathu.
Stay here. Don't go anywhere.
I'm exhausted!
I'm going to whack you
to death if I catch you.
I'm mad now.
Hey! Oh, it's a kid!
- Come here!
- Let go!
Let me go!
Why, you little!
Who are you calling little?
The name's Madeaw, sister.
This is my turf.
Next time, address me right.
Okay, Madeaw.
Why are you stealing my sticks?
I ain't stealing, fool.
You didn't ask permission
to collect those sticks.
So I've got to exert my power.
Bro,
then I'd like your permission
to collect these sticks.
Alright, sister. You're lucky
I'm fond of cute girls.
There's a 20 baht concession fee.
Twenty?
Acting gangster at this age?
When are you going to finish?
Working piece by piece like that.
No one's helping me.
Do you want to help me?
It's five baht per stick.
You're going to charge me?
It's alright. I'll do it myself.
Then, it's five baht
for the whole gig.
Special promotion.
Okay, deal.
How do you know to do all this?
With a pretty face like that,
you don't look capable.
Madeaw, can you help me hold this?
Right here.
That's all?
Yes, that's all.
Wait for the furnace to cool.
Tomorrow we'll be able
to collect the charcoal.
That's impressive.
I didn't expect this from a girl
with a pretty face.
Don't underestimate me.
Here. Take 10 baht.
Thanks for helping.
Yes! I've got money!
Later, sister!
Let it be known.
Bring on the bullying.
Endure it.
I made Artit handicapped.
That's why he's so angry.
I ruined his life.
I have to accept it.
Just be patient.
Mr. Artit's asking for you
to go to work.
It's morning already?
I feel like I haven't had any sleep.
Oh, sir? Have you seen Paeng's work?
The color's really nice.
She definitely knows
temperature control.
- It's just a fluke.
- I don't think so.
I had to train for a while
to be able to do this.
We even hid nearly all the wood.
Should I fire you
and hire her as your replacement?
No, sir.
- Just get lost.
- Okay.
Hold on.
I have an idea.
I have a job for you.
Give that back!
Come on!
Miss Paeng.
Miss Paeng,
Mr. Artit told you to go
and organize some stuff.
Let's go.
Please come in.
He told you to organize
the stuff in this room.
Where is it?
Just inside.
Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?
Why are you locking me in?
Hey!
You sicko!
Mr. Artit!
You seem very happy today.
Your face was so red
with anger the other day.
What are you happy about?
- Do you want to know?
- Yes, I do.
Give me 500 and I'll tell you.
Whoa, 500?
I don't have that much.
I only have 50. Is it okay?
Here, sir.
I locked her up.
I'm thinking of
leaving her for a couple of days
and letting her starve.
Gosh! Sir!
What if she actually dies?
What are you going to do?
You're now a co-conspirator.
Because you know everything.
Mr. Artit!
I didn't mean it!
I didn't want to
conspire or anything.
- Too late.
- Sir, can I have my money back?
Sir, please don't hurt me!
Please don't do this to me!
I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
I'll give you another 100 baht.
Everything will be silenced.
Take it, sir.
- You know everything.
- Come on, sir!
Car key.
Toothbrush.
Instead of bringing a phone!
Jeez, Paeng!
You're so unlucky, it's like
a TV show.
Whoa!
This is so high.
Alright, then.
I'd like to dedicate the merit made
from the offering this morning
to all my karmic relations.
Bogeymen, wicked ghosts with
no relatives, and wandering spirits.
Please come and revel
in the merit I've made.
Sathu.
Do you know where Artit is?
Dear, dear.
You rushed over like
you're chasing merit.
Look at you. You look like you just
left your grave.
Are you a bogeyman
or a wicked ghost?
Probably both.
I have something
important to talk to Artit about.
Madam, Madam! We just made merit.
You have to calm down.
Why would he be here?
He's in his office, of course.
- Thank you.
- Huh?
Why would you tell her that, Madam?
- Oh, dear.
- You shouldn't have been stupid...
What? Duang!
Are you trying to say I'm stupid?
No, I said I wanted
to have some stew.
I'll smack you in
the head with this.
See? I haven't even finished pouring
the ceremonial water yet.
Let's finish it, Madam.
- Why did you come in, Saeb?
- Let's let Miss Paeng out.
- Are you that worried?
- Yes, sir.
- Saeb!
- Sir,
the pen broke.
Don't be angry, please.
Think about it,
you locked her up like that.
What are you going
to do if she dies?
If she's that weak,
then she's a lost cause.
Come on, Mr. Artit.
She's only a tiny girl.
You being too harsh on her.
If she got sick and died,
you'll be cursed.
Saeb,
are you siding with someone else
more you do with me?
No... No, sir.
I'm only worried about you.
If Miss Paeng dies,
you'll get arrested.
You're exaggerating.
Come on, sir!
- Sir...
- He's not exaggerating.
I can press charges
for unlawful detention.
Miss Paeng!
You got out! I'm so happy!
You're so good! She got out, sir!
If there's anything,
please talk nicely.
Calm down.
No need to make those angry eyes.
Focus on reconciliation.
Leave us, Saeb.
Okay, sir. I'll go.
No need to shoo me away.
Because I don't want
any part of this anymore.
What should I do?
Thongkhum, should I go to see my son
or wait for the news here?
- Just wait here, Madam.
- Really?
Paeng won't dare do anything to him.
It anything's going to happen,
it would be Artit
who snaps her neck.
So I don't have to be
worried about my son?
- Don't worry.
It's you who's being childish.
Childish?
Do you think I'm playing with you?
That's right. You're being childish.
A vengeful child.
What did you say?
Be careful or your heart
might shatter into pieces.
Who caused me to end up like this?
Artit, I know I was wrong.
I'd like to atone for
everything I've done.
But you have to
give me a chance too.
Let me prove that I'm a new person.
You can order me around
as much as you want.
But not like this.
I will do it until you're gone.
I will tell Uncle.
Go ahead.
Anytime something happens
you just run to my dad.
My dad believes
everything you say anyway.
Do you want to have him then?
I'll give him to you.
You're angry that he loves me.
That's true.
He loves you.
But he has mercy on me
because he's seen
what I've been through.
I've been through a lot more
than what you've seen.
Don't worry
that he will love me more than you.
Because that's impossible.
He wants me here
just to learn the ropes.
Once he sees that
I can manage things,
he'll let me go my own way.
It's only two years, Artit.
Can't you just endure it?
You ordered me around
for three days.
it was exhausting
but I was able to withstand it.
You can't compare
two years and three days.
Look at me.
If you were me, would you be able to
put up with being like this?
Both my dreams and my future
are ruined.
Everything I'd accomplished was
ruined because of you!
I needed therapy for years on end.
I couldn't eat or sleep
because I was afraid that
I'd be handicapped.
Would you be able to endure it?
Would you?
I almost became handicapped.
Almost handicapped?
That's right.
But I'm sorry
that I didn't end up that way.
Kot!
Are you happy to see me?
I'm very happy!
Seeing her be happy
with the person she loves
makes me happy too.
Wise but heartbreaking.
You couldn't seduce me
so you're seducing my friend?
You can't stand not
having a guy in your life?
Snake! Snake!
- Snake! Snake!
- Paeng!
For some things,
if you wait too long,
you might miss it. You might have
to wait for the rest of your life.
I'm not eating anymore!
Are you trying to be a ringleader?
She started a mob.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Where's Paeng?