(My Forever Sunshine)
Kot!
Are you happy to see me?
I'm very happy!
Seeing her be happy
with the person she loves
makes me happy too.
Wise but heartbreaking.
You couldn't seduce me
so you're seducing my friend?
You can't stand not
having a guy in your life?
Snake! Snake!
- Snake! Snake!
- Paeng.
Because for some things,
if you wait too long,
you might miss it. You might have
to wait for the rest of your life.
I'm not eating anymore!
Are you trying to be a ringleader?
She started a mob.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Where's Paeng?
Your papaya salad and
grilled pork are the best!
Papaya salad and grilled pork,
these are all my favorites!
Thank you, Pong.
Tell me if you want anything.
Your wish is my command.
Miss Paeng, Could I have some more?
Hold on, Saeb!
I'm an old man. I should go first.
You don't even have teeth.
Give it to me.
Potty mouth. Put it down
or I'll beat you up.
Easy there. No need to argue.
Everyone will be served.
I'll do my best to make sure
it's so delicious that you won't
want to leave.
- Yes!
- Hooray!
It's a shame Artit won't
let us work for her.
Or we'd be able to eat
like this every day.
Lately, Thongkhum's been cooking
the same thing every day.
I can't stomach it anymore.
That's right.
Seriously,
Artit should be a bit
more open-handed.
I don't know why he's
so angry with Paeng.
Now we're in trouble for that too.
Greetings, sir.
What, Pong?
Why?
Do you think Artit would come here,
right now?
Impossible. I'm not buying it.
- Saeb.
- Saeb, Saeb.
That voice is just like him.
That's a great imitation.
Let me turn around
and see who he is.
Saeb!
The face and voice are the same.
The power of my kick
is the same too.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
- I'm sorry, sir!
- He could bust your face.
That's right. You all worship her.
But be careful.
You might get poisoned.
How do you know
I'm going to poison them?
You're clever!
I'm not.
But I know your true colors.
I was being sarcastic.
Did you fall for that?
Then you're not clever.
Sir, she insulted you
for being stupid!
I know that!
Where did you get those papayas?
Uhh... from this tree.
- Duang.
- Yes?
Throw them all out.
Okay, sir.
Hey! Don't.
Don't you dare touch
my papaya salad!
Who says it's yours?
You picked these papayas
from a tree grown on my farm.
So that means they're mine.
The eggplants and chilies as well.
Don't ever take my stuff again.
You're being unreasonable.
Why? It's my nature.
If you don't like it, then get out!
Paeng started a mob?
That's right.
Nonsense.
How could you believe Duang?
You know they don't get along.
But I believe her.
Be careful. She might take
over the farm one day.
She wouldn't do that.
Why wouldn't she?
She already had Artit's
farmhands working for her.
Good thing Artit took them
back just in time.
So no one's helping her at all?
That's right. No one.
I'm putting my foot down.
You cannot touch anything
on this farm.
You cannot fraternize
with my workers either.
What about me?
Can she fraternize with me?
It's getting out of hand.
I'd like to tell you all that
you can help Paeng.
You have my permission.
Dad,
but I'm their boss.
If you do this, then you're
undermining me.
But
I'm the father of their boss.
Who has more power?
That's true, Pong.
That's true.
Saeb, Aod, Kaew.
From now on, if Paeng needs help,
go help her right away.
I permit you. No need to be
scared of anyone.
Dad!
Tell me the truth, Thongkhum.
How many days in a row did you
make chili paste and
boiled vegetables with omelet?
Uh, well...
Don't make a big deal out of this.
It's a balanced meal.
I think the farmhands
are just being difficult.
I think you should let
Thongkhum answer.
What do you say?
How many times did you make that?
- Five.
- Five meals?
Five days.
- Huh?
- What?
Five days?
So that's fifteen meals?
Oh, dear me!
Thongkhum, did you cook anything
else for them?
Some days I make clear soup.
Oh, dear.
Aren't you bored of it too?
Well, I don't eat with them.
- Oh?
You vary the menu for yourself.
Think about their feelings.
That's right.
Try putting yourself
in their shoes for a change.
These farmhands work hard.
They deserve good food.
Think about it.
If you had to eat the same thing
every day, how would you feel?
You wouldn't like it either.
Treat others how you would like
to b treated.
This time
I'll let it slide.
Next time, don't do it.
Don't do it again.
Understood.
- You can go now.
- Okay, Madam.
How could she do that for
fifteen meals straight?
Really!
I'm so unlucky.
Who told Master?
Probably a worker.
A worker?
Would they dare?
I cook for them every day.
That's true?
Who'd want to pick a fight
with the cook?
Oh! What if it was Paeng?
Definitely.
She's the only one who would
want to pick a fight with us.
She must be angry
that we insulted her
so she took revenge.
Rotten Paeng!
I won't let you get away with this!
Me neither.
An eye for an eye.
Otherwise, don't call me Duang.
Now that's food! Sun-dried pork
with mushroom Tom-Yum soup.
The omelet has now been reborn.
Don't haunt us anymore! Sathu!
No more ghosts of chili paste
and boiled vegetables.
That's right. I hope those menu
items are gone for a long while.
Extra pork, please.
Okay. I'm serving it to you.
Here. Is that enough?
I'm sorry
for making you all eat the same
thing over and over again.
From now on, if you want
to eat anything,
just tell me!
- So satisfying!
- Really?
Really.
Then tomorrow
I'd like some tasty larb.
Your wish is granted.
Awesome!
You do it yourself.
Take as much as you want.
Quick! Quick!
Thongkhum, what are you thinking?
It's good.
But aren't you tired?
I'm tired
but I have to because I don't
want a repeat of yesterday.
That's right.
Thongkhum and I
don't want the farmhands
messing around with Paeng.
She's so promiscuous.
Do you remember
when she tried to assault Artit?
- I do.
- That's right.
Once she sees a man,
she can't leave them alone.
Watch out for your husband.
She wouldn't have a farmhand
as her husband.
You can't underestimate her.
She always makes those eyes when
she talks to the farmhands.
She's evil.
Okay.
All done, Uncle.
Today I've improved
and fermented the soil.
As for the product research lab,
I'm just waiting on the contractor
Oh! You got it?
They're coming tomorrow?
Yes!
Thank you.
Paeng,
is the contractor coming?
That's right. They're coming to
pick up the blueprints tomorrow.
Excellent!
So, they're going
to start right away?
I'll tell them to start right away.
So the job will be done quickly
and I won't have to be an unwanted
presence for much longer.
I feel uncomfortable too.
It's going to take two years.
Two years can pass by quickly.
But it can also feel
like a long time.
So that's why we have
to stay focused.
Every second of our time
is valuable.
We have to do our best.
Sathu! I wish
everything goes smoothly!
Your face is already red and you're
not even working that hard.
But you're so enthusiastic
when you're getting paid.
Work's never easy. I feel hot too.
- Pong.
- Yes, sir?
Why are you alone?
Where are Saeb, Aod, and Kaew?
Uh...
Those three went to work
for that woman, didn't they?
Aod, do your best!
Don't let Paeng down.
I know that!
Can we start
with the construction right away?
Sure. The plans are very detailed.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
- Aod, Saeb!
- Shoot!
Yes, sir?
You're slacking off at work.
Do you want to get reprimanded?
Well, we're working here.
Did you forget that your dad ordered
the two of us to help her?
You have my dad's permission
but I didn't say for you
to come and help her.
Come with me.
Yes, sir.
No, stop right now.
Oh?
These two are my people now.
What are you babbling about?
I pay these two, not you.
But Uncle assigned them to me.
You heard him.
My dad is too optimistic,
that's why he fell for your trick.
This is real life, Wanfahmai.
We're not playing house.
I don't like the farm
using free labor
especially with something...
that will never succeed.
How do you know that it won't?
I'm just getting started.
Because I know you well enough.
Come on. Come with me.
No, you can't!
You have to stay with me!
What should we do, Saeb?
Miss Paeng, Mr. Artit.
Should we try rock-paper-scissors?
Whoever wins will...
Oops.
You have to stay with me!
You can't go anywhere else!
If you have a problem,
go and talk to Uncle yourself.
Do you remember what he said?
I'll repeat it for you.
Uncle is your father
and also the owner of this place.
In conclusion, he ranks
higher than you.
Don't threaten me with my dad!
Do you think I'm scared?
If you're not,
I'd probably be out of this farm.
But I'm still here.
Alright.
I'll show you
who's the boss of this place.
Oh, wow!
You can't even
win an argument with me!
Oh!
Let's get back to work.
Don't care about him.
- Okay.
- Right away.
This way, please.
It's him!
Miss Paeng! Watch out!
- What, Saeb? I can't hear you?
- Watch out!
Miss Paeng! Watch out!
What is it?
Saeb! Help me!
Saeb! Saeb!
Run, Miss Paeng. Run!
Artit, calm down!
Come on!
Artit!
Saeb!
Hurry up, Paeng!
Saeb! Help me!
Saeb! Saeb!
Saeb!
- Go!
- Come on, Saeb!
Miss Paeng!
- Miss Paeng!
- Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I wasn't hurt.
I wasn't hurt!
Come on.
Pong,
can we harvest these grapes
according to the order?
- Yes, sir.
- What about the quality?
- Definitely up to standard.
- Good.
I'm meeting a client.
- Take care of the transportation.
- Yes, sir.
- What are you looking for?
- Yes.
- Pong!
- Yes?
I asked what you're looking for.
For a dog.
What dog?
This morning Miss Paeng
was bitten by a dog.
What a vicious dog.
Her knees are all scratched.
This dog only acts tough
towards children, women,
and the elderly.
If I ever see this dog,
I'll give it a swift kick
to the butt.
Bad dog!
Oh, I got carried away.
Aren't you in a hurry
to get to your meeting?
Pong,
be careful.
You might get bitten as well.
I think it might be a rabid dog too.
- Pong!
- Yes, sir!
Is it underneath the car?
Artit!
Artit! Artit!
What now?
How can you go?
Your tires are flat.
Gosh!
The other side as well.
What?
Who would dare do this?
There's only one person.
Who?
The dog!
That dog again!
Not only did it bite Miss Paeng,
but it chewed on the tires as well.
Better hope it doesn't run into me.
I'll kick it's back legs out.
- Pong.
- It even chewed on the tires.
Give me the keys to your car.
You're in a hurry
to get to the meeting?
Change the tires too.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Need to lure it out.
Gosh, Miss Paeng!
Taking revenge like that,
aren't you scared?
You know how I am.
If I let it go, then he'll
think I'm scared.
And we'll always get bullied.
But aren't you scared
that he'll get you back?
I'm not scared.
Gosh!
If you're not, then come here!
- Mr. Artit!
- Let me go!
- Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
- Artit!
- Aueng, help me!
- Miss Paeng!
Oh, no!
- Help me!
You punctured my tires, didn't you?
Get in!
- Miss Paeng!
- Get in!
Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
- Miss Paeng!
- Aueng!
Let Miss Paeng go!
Stay still!
Be still!
What are you going to do to her?
If my dad hears about this,
your boss will be missing
some limbs on her return.
Okay.
Miss Paeng!
Artit!
I thought you weren't scared?
Alright.
Artit!
Okay.
Do you still dare to defy me?
You're not remorseful, are you?
Okay, then!
Hey! Hey!
Hold on!
Unlock it!
Not yet! Not yet!
Get down!
Are you ready to keep going?
Where are we going?
To your murder in the woods.
I thought you're not scared.
Your eyes are bulging.
I'm not scared. Death is death.
If you want me to die,
then I'm okay with it.
Are you being cheeky?
But I hope you can
get away from the cops.
Do you still dare to threaten me?
I wasn't threatening you.
You'd go to jail for your crime.
What about you?
Oh, maybe a woman raping
a man doesn't have to go to jail?
Artit, you're going too far.
I wasn't going to rape you.
That was rape.
Back then, I...
You what?
You can't even say it?
I was young!
So that's why you
didn't have to go to jail?
Then call the cops
so they can throw me in jail.
How many times will you keep
shaming me for that?
With your thick skin,
I'm sure you don't feel a thing.
Just stab me if you're
going to be that harsh.
- Alright.
- Artit! Artit!
- Don't!
- Let go!
No!
Let go!
If you don't want to die
a premature death,
then don't ever touch me again!
- Get in!
- What?
I'd like the grape festival
this year to be extra special.
There'll be wine tasting.
So that grape-lovers can taste
our newest wine.
What's even more special,
they will be able to mix the wine
flavors the way they want.
That's a good idea.
This will attract high-end tourists.
If the customers are satisfied
or want to order more,
we'll also offer a delivery service.
Excellent. It's convenient this way.
That's right.
And this is...
Hey.
Where are you going?
Come here.
Hey!
Artit, let me go.
I can walk on my own.
No, or you'll run away again.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I'm not.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
I'd like some crispy pork
and sausages.
Here it is.
Wow!
It's so tasty!
Yum!
I'm so full.
Artit...
So many leftovers.
Here.
Here, you.
Eat up.
Eat lots, doggie.
You're so cute.
Waiter, payment for
the food is here.
Are you coming to the car?
Or are you going to walk back?
Why did you drive into a pothole?
I didn't see it.
Even I saw it! Are you stupid?
What are you going to do now?
Get out!
If I do, then how am I going
to make my way back?
Who told you to go back?
You're going to push.
What?
Get out!
Go!
- Ready?
- Ready!
Push harder!
This is all you've got?
Find something
to lever the wheels up.
Hurry up!
Yes!
Go sit in the back.
You're dirty.
Go!
Artit,
I didn't tell anyone.
Where did you leave Paeng?
What?
Get down.
Miss Paeng!
You're still alive!
But how did you end up like that?
It's fun taking revenge.
Have a think
about how you're
going to get back to me.
Because I'll be thinking about
how I'm going to
get back to you too.
Careful.
Psycho!
I've returned her
with all her limbs intact,
just as I promised.
Yes, sir.
Wait for me, Miss Paeng.
He didn't even let you eat anything?
Here you go.
Not only did he not let me eat,
but he fed a dog in front of me too.
Whoa.
What did you do to him?
I warned you but you didn't listen.
There!
You saw it.
He hurt me first.
And is it worth it to be continually
getting back at each other?
And when will Artit forgive you?
Oh, Aueng!
Please stop mentioning that name!
I'm stressed!
So stressed!
Drink up.
There, there. Some more water.
Why did I open it?
I don't know how to fix it anyway.
That's true.
Here.
Let me give you a lift.
It's okay.
I can call Artit.
I'm right in front of you
but you won't even let me help.
Do you really hate me?
No, Non. I've never hated you.
Then get in my car.
I'll drop you off.
- It's okay.
- Ling,
don't refuse a friend's kindness.
Don't overthink it.
Follow me.
Those apples look tasty.
You can't eat them.
They're for Artit.
What's this? Huh?
You're giving them to Artit again?
He's got heaps on his farm.
Mine are tastier.
I'll win him over
with my hospitality.
Hey,
Artit's already got a girlfriend.
Stop messing around
with him. It looks bad.
He can still break up with her.
He's not even married.
But even if he is,
he can still divorce.
Hey, give that to me.
You're going too far.
Who taught you this?
Hey.
Non,
stop acting like an old geezer.
It's annoying.
You're my sister.
Artit and Ling are my friends.
I can't let you do this.
You worry more about other people
more than you do your own sister?
I'm actually worried about you.
Other people might think
of you in a bad way.
I don't care.
I have the right to choose
and so does Artit.
It's the freedom of the heart.
Do you understand?
But freedom
must also be based on morales.
Do you understand?
I'm here! Non! Nang!
You two, what lovely sibling
moment are you having?
- What?
- Non, this is my happiness.
Don't be selfish.
You're getting carried away. I have
to stop you when you're wrong.
So what? It's my business.
Understand?
And how am I selfish?
Everything.
- Let me go.
- You can't go.
- No one hears me when I talk.
- Still not letting me go?
- Oh, my. I'm probably...
- No!
This chance is within my reach.
- What am I...
- This looks delicious!
He can look after himself...
Whoa, so fresh!
Kot!
- What?
- I have to do it again!
- Why?
- Kot, you jerk!
What did I do wrong?
- You didn't. You did well.
- Right?
Shrimp paste, sugar, fine sugar.
Paeng said to buy snacks
for the farmhands.
And then...
Household items.
That should be all.
Let's go.
Hey!
You little brat! Hey!
Hey! You brat!
Hey! Stop!
Saeb, catch that kid!
Where are you going?
Don't let him get away!
- Oh!
- Catch him!
Stop, Madeaw!
Madeaw,
do you know stealing is bad?
I know!
Then what are you going
to use that money for?
To buy toys.
Why didn't you ask your mom?
I did. Mom wouldn't give me any.
So you stole?
Madeaw, this is my money.
If you took it,
how could I buy the stuff I need?
If someone stole your money,
how would you feel?
I don't have any to begin with.
Really!
Don't waste time. He's naughty.
- He won't listen anyway.
- That's right.
You have to whip him.
But if you don't want to do it,
then tell his mom.
No!
Wow, you're scared of your mom?
That's good then.
Let's go and tell your mom!
She'll hit you if she knows.
No! Don't go!
No! No!
Don't go! Don't tell Mom!
Now you're powerless.
Madeaw, don't cry anymore.
If you want money,
I'll give you some.
Miss Paeng!
Do you know there are lots
of ways to earn money?
If you work and don't steal,
you won't be punished or scolded.
Remember, next time
if you want money,
you have to come and tell me.
It's a promise.
You're so lovely, Miss Paeng!
Paeng!
Madeaw!
Why did you steal?
I don't have money.
How many times have you done this?
It's the first time.
What about the money I gave you?
Where is it?
I gave it all to my mom.
Aren't you afraid that your mom and
grandmom will be sad if they know?
Grandmom is sick
so I gave the money to Mom.
I want Grandmom to get better.
Why didn't you tell me?
Hey,
I'll take your grandmom
to the doctor.
Don't worry, okay?
Really?
Really.
I'll do my best to take beautiful
photos for you, Artit!
Don't be too loud.
Someone might hear us.
Alright?
I made you lunch.
Thank you, Ling.
I feel so guilty.
Don't be.
Try it.
I'll go ahead then.
Wow!
What are you planning to do?
I'm thinking of turning it into a
center for all things rose-related.
Not just grow them here,
but I'll produce
things made from roses.
Uncle trusted me.
So I want to give it my all.
I don't want to disappoint him.
You've changed a lot.
You've matured and are more skilled.
How do you know?
Judging from how you taught Madeaw.
You've also matured
and are a lot more beautiful.
Non and Kot have got
a lot more handsome too.
Everyone's changed for the better.
Except for Artit.
It's true. He's changed a lot.
His face has aged a lot.
But how is he going to stop that?
He keeps frowning and twisting
his face all day long.
Please remind him to not
throw too many tantrums.
He might die prematurely
from cancer.
You might die prematurely from
gossiping too much.
Artit.
Ling, if you want to
make merit, just tell me.
I'll take you to feed some dogs.
They're more grateful than humans.
Potty mouth!
Come on, Artit.
Why aren't you going back to work?
Well, I've missed you.
I'm full now.
Hold on. How can you be full?
You only had a few bites.
Let her be.
You're too kind.
You can't expect anything in return
from certain kinds of people.
Once you give in
and start pitying them,
they'll stab you in the back.
It happened to me before.
I'm warning you because I'm worried.
You've gone too far, Artit.
I don't think so.
She deserves it. There she goes.
These look tasty.
Can I have some? Let me eat too.
I made these for Paeng, not you.
I'm hungry. I've been
working really hard.
You jerk.
You keep following me around.
Did you make these yourself?
Happy, aren't you?
Smiling from ear to ear.
Do you want to eat with me?
It's so good.
So happy.
Yum!
I made these for Paeng.
She walked away.
So they're for me now.
I drove her away because of this.
Cheep,
I have something to
talk to you about.
Once you start preparing,
please add more food
and beverage kiosks
because there might be
more guests that day.
- Please handle this for me.
- Okay.
Hello.
Hello, Non.
Are you here to see my dad?
He's not here today.
He's got a meeting somewhere.
I'm here to see you.
You're going to share the festival
with my farm this year?
That's right.
I discussed it with Artit.
But as for the details, I still have
to meet up with a lot of people.
Paeng also told me that you helped
look at the construction plans
for the rose garden, right?
That's right. But Paeng's plans
are already good.
I just gave her some advice.
I don't have a lot of time.
If you do,
please help me look after her.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best to help her, anyway.
I'll give you a tour
of the festival space.
Please, this way.
Jook.
Hello, Mr. Artit.
Where's your mom?
She's inside.
Take me to her.
Okay, sir.
Hello.
How are you doing?
I'm much better now.
Jook, has she gotten better?
She was a lot worse two days ago.
Her asthma was acting up and
she couldn't sleep.
So I bought her some medication.
What medication?
- Uh...
- And
why hasn't anyone told me?
She told me not to.
Why not?
You've already helped us so much.
I'm was trying to be considerate.
You're in my care.
I have to look after you.
Why do you have to be considerate?
I haven't worked
for a year or so now.
That's unrelated.
You used to work for us.
You never left us,
even when we're struggling.
I consider it as a debt
we owe you for helping us.
Today,
you've fallen sick
and you need treatment.
If I don't take care of you, how can
I consider myself a human?
You didn't tell me.
If you get worse,
I'll be even more worried.
Next time, please let me
know if there's anything you need.
Okay. I won't do that anymore.
I didn't think you're in trouble.
I forgot that Jook's working alone.
From now on, I'll give you a salary.
Jook, come and get them from me.
Okay, sir.
I can't accept it.
If others know,
they might bad-mouth you.
I'm very transparent
in how I treat my people.
Don't worry.
Jook,
where did you buy the medication?
From the market, sir.
Bring me the medication
and help me bring
your mom to my car.
I'm taking her to the doctor.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Next, come and get your payment.
Our paychecks are here!
Hey, who's interested in going
into town and to eat Mala with me?
Saeb,
do you dare to eat Mahler now?
Not Mahler!
Mala! It's Mala, Chinese food.
I'm coming.
But first,
I have to get some new threads.
I'm not coming.
I have a date.
We're watching a movie.
You all spend
your paychecks right away
and don't save any.
When are you going to be rich?
Are you not coming?
You're going to stay home and
fill your piggy bank?
Of course I am.
But I'm not going to eat
Mahler whatever that is.
I'm going to have a hamburger.
Hamburger?
For you, the bread for the fish
at the temple is considered posh.
I'm not a catfish. I'm a human.
- Really!
- Pong, your turn.
Here's your paycheck.
- Gladly, sir.
- There he goes.
Here it comes.
Receiving before signing.
The envelope?
Where's mine, sir?
- Mine too.
- Also mine.
Pack it up.
- What about Mala?
- Mala?
I didn't even get paid!
- Artit!
- Sir!
Saeb, Aod, Kaew.
I thought you said
you were going into town?
Oh?
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Calm down, Paeng!
Artit!
- Artit!
- Paeng!
Artit! Come out and talk to me!
- Artit!
- Calm down, Paeng!
Artit!
What's up?
Why didn't you pay them their wages?
It's against the Labor Law.
Apart from studying agriculture,
you've studied the law as well?
I'm not paying.
Because these three
aren't my employees anymore.
Even if they're working for me,
they're still the farm's employees.
If they're not working for me,
then don't expect me to pay.
You all asked for it.
Everyone,
see this as an example.
If you want to work for me,
don't betray me like they did.
Are you going to play this way?
But then again,
it's your first mistake,
I'll forgive you.
Are you going to come back
and work for me?
What should we do, Saeb?
Saeb,
how much is your wage?
I get 3,000 baht.
I'll give you 3,500 baht.
Whoa!
You don't have to go anywhere.
Stay with me.
I'll look after you.
- Thank you, Miss Paeng.
- Thank you.
- I'm rich!
- That's right!
Working for Miss Paeng is easy!
Most importantly, it's less tiring
than farm work.
I earn more.
It's definitely worth it.
We don't have to clock-in. We can
also finish work whenever.
That's right. Miss Paeng
is also generous.
She always brings us food.
Miss Paeng, you're
my guardian angel!
What are you eating?
Share with me.
Miss Paeng,
you took away Mr. Artit's workers.
That's why he's angry.
Of course he is.
I saw his eyebrow
twitching like this.
- Like this?
- He picked a fight with me first.
What if Mr. Artit is vengeful
and takes revenge on you again?
If it's about work,
I can take it.
But if he bullies me,
I'll fight him.
From this day forward,
I'm ready for anything!
Bring it on!
Miss Paeng, what's that mob?
- Miss Paeng!
- Hurry up!
- Stop! Stop! Stop!
Miss Paeng, I'd like 3,500 baht too.
I don't want to work for Mr. Artit.
I want to work for you.
- Miss Paeng!
- No.
Calm down!
I warned them but no one listened.
Good, Pong.
I'd like to know what
that woman is going to do.
Mr. Artit! Mr. Artit!
Mr. Artit!
The workers wouldn't listen.
Can you please come
and take them back?
I'm not going.
Artit, let me apologize
on behalf of Miss Paeng.
Your boss is tough, isn't she?
Let her deal with it herself.
Mr. Artit!
What's going on?
Mr. Krongprateep!
Everyone, calm down.
I can't hire all of you.
You can hire
just some of them.
Please hire me.
I'm very hardworking.
I'm hardworking.
What should we do?
I don't know either.
But if I hire all of them,
I'll go bankrupt.
Everyone,
please go. The three of us are
already enough for her.
- There are no openings.
- That's right.
Saeb, you selfish man!
Uh...
Everyone, calm down!
Please don't fight!
Please go back. I'm begging you.
No, we won't.
- Please hire us.
- Please, Miss Paeng.
- Please go back.
- Everyone, stop!
- Master's here.
- Uncle?
Miss Paeng!
Saeb, Aod,
return the money to Paeng.
- Huh?
- Why do we have to do that?
- That's right.
Because you are my employees.
You are the workers of this farm.
You work equally.
You get paid equally.
Go on. Get back to work.
But but Mr. Artit said...
This rose garden also belongs to
the farm.
Paeng is helping me.
I should actually be paying her.
Therefore, you have no right to
request payment from her.
Uncle, please don't scold
Saeb and the others.
They didn't start it.
I know.
Don't let a misunderstanding
like this happen again.
Can you get back to your work now?
Yes, sir.
Come on. Hurry.
Quickly.
Now no one got a raise.
I'm begging you.
Don't let something like
this happen again.
Come on, Dad.
How can you blame me?
You can deal with it
but you wouldn't.
If you want me to deal with it,
then your niece must
work under me directly.
Hold on.
Do you mean I have to
be your subordinate?
You already let me take care of
everything in your place.
If Paeng works for you,
then that means she's
my subordinate.
Is that right?
Is that right, Dad?
Yes, that is right.
What's all this?
Your work schedule.
You're the worker of the farm.
You have to do something
for the farm too.
But I'm already working
on the rose garden for Uncle.
The rose garden?
You don't even know
if that's going to make it.
I don't count that as work.
From now on, your mornings will be
spent doing the farm's work.
You can work on
your rose garden in the afternoons.
Product harvesting,
feeding the calves,
daily production record.
Why do I have to this?
Because it's the boss' orders.
You have to do it no matter what.
You saw this as a chance to
cause me problems, didn't you?
Paeng!
Kot?
Paeng, darling!
I have some goodies
to present to you.
Hurry on in! You can take
a closer look.
This is an automated
hydroponic grow box.
You, you, you and you
won't have to bend down
and dig the dirt anymore.
You only have to put vegetable seeds
into all these holes,
then you just plug it in.
Simple. You can control both
the temperature and light.
Then you can just lie down and wait.
Because now you
will have clean, safe,
and non-toxic vegetables.
It really suits your work, Paeng.
Kot, this is great!
If it's great, why aren't you
coming closer?
Step closer
and take this brochure. We still
have many other innovations.
It's all safe and sound.
Here you go. Please.
- You can just eat like this?
- Sure. We've tested it.
That's right. There are multiple
shelves. Five of them!
Try it out.
- It's really nice!
- Very clean and no toxins involved.
Redo the surface of the dirt.
- Then you can start planting.
- Yes, sir.
Alright.
Mr. Artit, hold on!
Look here. This is very interesting!
Automated hydroponic grow box?
Nonsense.
Not at all, sir.
If you have a whole building
for them,
I guaranteed you it'll work.
That's right, sir. It really can
be used to grow vegetables.
I know it can.
But it's not suitable for our farm.
Don't you want to try it out, sir?
I've seen a grow box in action.
Where did you see it?
Miss Paeng, she bought on.
Not just that,
she bought many things.
It's very sturdy. You're going to
say it's "awesome" when you see it.
What now?
Awesome!
It's so cool!
Over there!
Whoa!
It can sprinkle water too!
It's just water right now.
But we'll use it for fertilizer.
This is so cool.
Much easier than just walking
and spraying the fertilizer.
Besides, my beautiful skin won't get
stained from the fertilizer either.
It's going!
Oh, Miss Paeng.
Your karmic relation is here.
Hurry! Hurry!
I'm sorry.
What a desperate woman!
How am I desperate?
You don't even know how to
use your brain.
The drone and the grow box
are wasteful.
It's you who's not
using their brain.
Everything I've bought will help cut
back on manpower.
We can work faster with them.
The drone can cover an area
of eight acres in an hour.
It will save both manpower and time.
Do you all agree?
Agreed!
But we have to put
our hearts into farming.
Not just finish up in an hour.
Each grapevine and all of
our produce requires our attention.
And not just aim
to finish work for the day.
Do you all agree?
Agreed!
Then let's just keep the grow boxes.
- No.
- You're black-hearted!
Who are you calling black-hearted?
Isn't it true?
Why don't you consider it from
the point of view of the workers?
It's bad for our health
if we work too hard.
If we can cut back on manpower,
the farmhands will
have more free time.
Then they can spend that time
with families.
They will be harmonious and their
kids won't feel neglected, right?
Right! Come on!
Artit, the grow box is really good.
They will help improve our farm.
The grow box. Isn't it obvious?
You can't grow grapes,
melons, or mulberries.
And look, at this farm
the soil, water,
and the sunlight is great.
Those cabinets need to be plugged in
and temperature control.
It's a waste of electricity.
Don't you agree?
Agreed.
Those things are meant
to be used in the city
where there is limited space.
You only have money and no brain.
Saeb! Saeb!
Miss Paeng,
Mr. Artit's got a point.
I'll show you that what I bought is
useful on this farm.
It will also give the workers
more time to rest.
If these things were no good,
why would I buy them to test out?
Don't you agree?
Right.
Come on! Come here!
In conclusion,
you all agree with her
that we should buy these things.
That's right.
Okay.
I'll let you buy them then.
Thank you, sir!
But I'll fire everyone!
Because I won't need
human labor anymore.
It's a deal, then?
What should we do?
Everyone's going to lose their job.
Sir! Sir!
Quick! Hurry!
Sir!
Sir! Sir!
Calm down, sir!
Sir!
Sir, please don't fire us!
If you do, we won't be
able to feed ourselves.
So do you want to buy them or not?
No!
Good.
Then get back to work!
Thank you so much, Artit!
- Pong.
- Sir?
Why are you standing there being
all old and shriveled? Back to work!
Miss Paeng, let's get
back to our work.
Don't go yet.
Your boss wants to see you.
Come on. Just talk to him.
Did you forget that you're the
employee and I'm the boss?
You have no right to do
whatever you want.
You have to consult me first
and not just use your money.
The workers might get out of line
and start to defy authority.
That's a mouth full. Which orifice
do you use to breathe?
I can breathe from
whatever orifice I want.
Remember, Wanfahmai.
From now on,
you'll be receiving your
monthly salary from me.
Okay. I can go now, right?
Wait.
Give me your ATM
and credit cards right now.
You don't have to be that disgusted.
Give them to me!
Hand them over.
I won't. They're mine.
Then that means someone like you
is only good for having money.
At a loss for words?
Okay. Take them.
I'm going to show you that
I can survive without money,
Get back to work.
Kot!
Oh, no!
Yes, Mr. Piya.
I'd like to order five grow boxes
and five fertilizing drones.
When will they be ready?
Thank you very much.
Please rush it for me.
Goodbye.
Who's ordering this many?
It's Paeng.
Why did you hit me?
What did you con her?
Hey, Ling.
Con? If the stuff is good, then I
should let other people know.
Paeng is clever with her purchases.
Unlike you, you never buy anything
even though I tried to convince you.
It's called being stingy.
It's called being clever
with my purchases.
You make it sound so nice.
Oh, Paeng.
Just in time. I was about to call.
You'll get your order in three days.
- Kot...
- Too long? I'll rush them.
- Mr. Piya, the stuff I ordered...
- I'd like to cancel them.
I'd like to cancel them.
Please wait for a moment, Mr. Piya.
How come?
I'd like to cancel the order, Kot.
- Well...
- Because?
Artit disapproved of it.
There it is. It's over.
It's all over.
Artit! You killjoy!
Kot, I really have
to apologize to you.
I didn't want to cancel the order.
But Artit's my boss.
I really don't want to defy him.
Is it a huge loss for you?
It's okay, Paeng.
But
the stuff you've ordered previously
can't be canceled.
You still have to pay up.
I thought I can still return them if
I paid for the first installment.
You can't for that order.
What is it?
It's Artit.
Thanks.
Here.
Thank you.
It's your favorite, carrot cake.
I saved it for you.
Perfecting timing. I'm hungry.
Wow.
You took away Paeng's
ATM and credit cards, didn't you?
Tattletale
She not a tattletale.
I kept asking her
until she finally told me.
So?
Did she ask you to come
and ask me for her cards back?
No. I'm here on my own.
She doesn't know any of this.
So don't scold her.
Ling, can't you see that she
hasn't changed?
She uses money to solve problems
like she's a spoiled child.
She's self-indulgent,
so I have to teach her a lesson.
I'll see if she can get
through this like she said.
What if she can?
What are you going to do?
I don't have to do anything.
It's not fair.
You keep watching
to see if she'll make a mistake
so that she won't be
able to stay here.
If she proves herself to you,
that she's really changed,
you should give her a chance.
And not just say that
you don't have to do anything.
Think about what I said carefully.
Ling is such a lovely girl.
It's 50,000 for the grow boxes.
Then it's 70,000 or so
for the drones.
How am I going to pay
for the installments?
Huh? Miss Paeng?
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
You have to go to the temple
early tomorrow morning.
Okay, Aueng.
It's time to sleep now.
Boss?
Hey,
why would you take pictures
when I'm with her?
You told me to take
photos all the time.
I did as you told me.
Next time just take
pictures of Paeng. Understand?
Alright, sir.
Did I hire the right person?
Trim all the stray twigs.
- It's losing its shape.
- Here?
Right. At the bottom too.
Krongprateep, where are you going?
To the temple to make merit.
It's the anniversary of Therathep
and Pimnapa's deaths today.
Do you want to come along?
Just the two of us or with Paeng?
Tubtim.
If it's with her, I'm not going.
Otherwise, I'd be committing sins
rather than making merit.
Can you let it go just for a day?
Don't make such a fuss
over making merit for them.
It's something we should do.
I'm not making a fuss
over making merit.
But I'm fussing over Paeng.
Dad! Mom!
Good morning.
Are you going to town now?
Doesn't the seminar
start at 10 a.m.? What's the hurry?
Oh? You have work to do.
How can you go
and make merit with Paeng?
Let her go alone.
We'll do it later. Okay?
Will I make it in time
if I go to the temple first?
Are you crazy? How will you make it?
I already promised Paeng.
Be prepared to dedicate your merits.
Venerable monk,
I'd like to ask you something.
What's the matter?
These merits we make for the dead,
they will actually
receive them, right?
Certainly.
Focus your mind
and the merits will
reach the recipients.
If the recipient has
committed a grave sin,
these merits can help them, right?
It will help partially,
but not completely.
Everyone is born
with their own karma.
Think of it as growing a tree.
Whatever tree you grow,
you will get the same kind of fruit.
- Venerable monk.
- Hmm?
Apart from the dead,
can we dedicate merits
to the living as well?
Of course you can.
Such as sick people
or karmic relations
that are still alive.
That's good.
I should do it too. So I can finally
get rid of my karma.
Merit dedication
is a good deed.
The only condition is
to have a pure heart,
show mercy to each other,
and not wish bad things
for each other.
What will happen
if you wish for bad things?
It will come around to you instead.
Let's get started.
Venerable monk, do you
have another one?
Why are you asking
so many questions?
You're so demanding.
It's a waste of time.
Pour the ceremonial water
and receive the blessings.
Just as rivers
Full of water
Fill the ocean full
Even so does
What is given benefit the dead
- Over there too.
- They're huge, Aueng.
Are you done yet?
Why are you doing so much?
You can go ahead if you want to.
How can I? I came with you.
I don't know.
Miss Paeng,
why did you ask
the venerable monk that question?
A grave sin?
What's that?
What are you worried about?
Let's go home, Aueng?
Okay.
Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
- What's wrong?
- Miss Paeng!
- Paeng!
Let's put her down over there.
Miss Paeng!
- Miss Paeng!
- Paeng!
I'll go find a menthol inhaler.
Paeng?
Dad!
Here's the inhaler!
- Paeng!
- I'll do it.
Paeng?
Miss Paeng?
You fainted.
Don't look at me like that. Take it.
Let's go now.
Miss Paeng, can you get up?
I'll help you.
Walk slowly.
Are you okay?
You can take a rest if you need to.
I'm fine now.
- Hey, Miss Paeng's back!
- Miss Paeng!
- Come on!
- Wait up.
- Did you get it, Miss Paeng?
What?
The winning lottery numbers.
What did the venerable monk
say at the temple?
- Huh?
- Did you bring any holy water?
- Candle wax tears are fine too.
- Or the ashes of the incense.
Calm down, everyone.
I went to make merits.
Not to win the lottery.
Miss Paeng!
We can't get hopes up
with you, can we?
- That's true.
- No number. So disappointing.
No one's disappointed about anything
because I have it right here.
That's it!
Eight-five! Eight-five!
Six-three!
When did you take it?
Something this important?
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Can you make it out?
What number it is?
- Two-eight-five above!
- Six-three under!
- Reverse it too!
- That's right. Reverse it.
Why would you buy these?
The chances of winning are very low.
Most people lose every time anyway.
Save your money
for when you need it.
Buy the necessities.
Miss Paeng, you don't understand.
The lottery is
the poor people's hope.
That's right.
At least we can afford dreams.
Every time we buy a ticket, we have
good dreams for 15 days!
It's better if you don't.
We should save up our money
and invest in something.
The money will grow from
our investment,
and then we'll be rich.
Once we're rich, it's not going
to be just a dream anymore.
It's too difficult.
We'll die before we're rich.
We can only save 10-20 baht a day.
- It's better to play the lottery.
- That's right.
Let me have that, please.
Here. This one.
Five-seven. Five-seven-three!
Reverse it too!
Oh, Artit!
Are you safe?
Did Paeng do anything to you again?
You had to wait for me to come home?
Well, I was worried.
You shouldn't have told Dad that.
I should've gone with her myself.
- By the way, Mom.
- Hmm?
Uh...
What does a grave sin include?
Why are you asking me that?
I heard at the temple
so I was wondering about it.
Well, I'm not really
knowledgeable about this.
A grave sin
is committed by murdering someone
or killing oneself, I think.
Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
First prize
for 17 January.
You all lost!
It's called the man's way.
It's all about dignity.
I didn't that I'm in
a relationship with Ling.
- Artit!
- Hey, hey!
I'm going to uncover
how you really feel.
It must be Mr. Artit.
There's only one person
who would dare pull
a prank on me like this.
I'm the mastermind behind all this.