(My Forever Sunshine)
The first prize for
January 17, 2020...
You all lost!
It's called the men's way.
It's all about dignity.
Paeng, what are you doing to my son?
Who cued her in?
What perfect timing.
I haven't said anything
about being with Ling.
- Artit!
- Hey, hey, hey!
I'll prove your feelings towards me.
Ouch!
It must be Mr. Artit.
There's only one person who dares
to pull a prank like this on me.
Everything that has happened,
I'm behind all of it.
No matter how nice she is,
I won't forget what she did.
Aueng,
I don't have any more clean shirts.
Not just you.
Me neither.
I have to go shopping with Non.
He's taking me.
Miss Paeng,
there are two outfits here.
Here.
Just wear them for the time being.
See?
This too.
Aueng,
The skirt part on this one is short.
The other one has such a low-cut.
Do you want the dogs to howl at me?
Do you want to be naked instead?
Just wear it.
I'll do the washing for you.
Which one do you prefer?
I don't want you
to do something like that.
But I didn't come up with it.
Someone told me to do it.
That's right.
I told her to drive Paeng out.
What's up? Checking out
your masterpiece?
I'm sorry
but I've cleaned it all up.
I'm relieved to see
that you're okay.
Aren't you disappointed
that I'm not hurt?
It's good that you're not.
I never thought that you're
the backstabbing type.
Next time, man up
and don't do it behind my back.
It's my business whether I do it
in front or behind your back.
I forgot that you can do anything.
That's right. I can do anything.
I'm sorry that it failed.
It will be successful someday.
Non,
why are you here?
I'm taking Paeng shopping.
Huh?
Paeng, why are you so dressed up
just to go to the market?
I'll be back, Artit.
Come on.
Non, thank you very much.
It's no trouble.
What's wrong with Artit?
Ignore him. He's sick in the head.
Hey!
- Where are you taking my guy?
- Shopping, of course.
I didn't ask you.
I'm asking her.
Oh? Non's your guy?
Non's my friend.
Are you jealous?
That's right.
She dressed up like this
to seduce you. Can't you see?
Artit!
Artit, I'm not your boyfriend.
And be nice to Paeng.
Give her some respect.
Why should I?
I think you should leave.
Artit, your dad told me
to look after her.
I'm taking her to shop
for some agricultural tools.
You're taking it too far.
You intend on burning through
my farm's money, right?
Watch your mouth.
I won't do it to Uncle's money.
But I can't be sure about yours.
You don't have to.
She's my employee. I can take her.
Employee?
That's right.
And stop being overfamiliar
by calling me by my name.
- Artit.
- Again?
I'm an only child.
I have no relatives nor siblings.
Artit, you've gone to far.
Do you want me to not
have any friends too?
It's okay, Non.
I'm sorry for wasting your time.
Time to go or it might get too hot.
Go on.
Power-hungry jerk.
How am I friends with him?
Artit.
Mr. Artit.
You're annoying.
Are you here to keep an eye out
or to be cheeky?
I must approve of everything
that you're buying.
But this is Uncle's money.
I didn't ask for yours.
The rose garden belongs to my farm.
It needs my money.
So everything you're going to buy
must be worth the value.
I need to use this one.
Too expensive.
This one's better. It's cheaper.
You have money but no brain.
- I'm taking this one.
- Hold on.
Take a good look
at the expiration date.
This one is old.
Take this one. It was recently
produced, so it's newer.
What's up, Khanoon?
What?
Wait right there. I'll hurry back.
What happened?
My friend's in trouble.
I have to go to Bangkok.
Paeng!
Are you going to go in this state?
How are you even getting there?
I'll take you.
Your friend had an accident,
why didn't she go to the hospital?
This is the accident.
She got kicked out from home.
What kind of person gets
kicked out from home?
She's an adoptive child.
That's her family's business.
I thought she was going to die.
You brought me here
just for a small issue?
Who brought whom?
You volunteered to come.
Think about it and don't blame me.
And your small issue
is actually big for me
and my friend.
Khanoon!
She's an adoptive child
so you think you can
do anything to her?
She's not my child!
That's going too far!
- Paeng?
Khanoon is not a pet.
You can't just adopt her
then abandon her
when you feel like it.
Even animals get treated
with love and mercy.
She's human.
But why don't you love her
or have mercy on her?
She's the person who's been calling
you her mother for 20 years.
So what? This is my family!
All of you should get lost
or I'm going to call the police.
Go ahead.
I actually want a cop as a husband.
What kind of parents are you
kicking your child out like that?
The Dream Team is here, huh?
Khanoon,
you're so ungrateful.
You told them to pick
a fight with me.
- Go away! You ingrate!
- Go!
Since you decided to adopt her,
then you should always
take care of her.
Not keeping the inheritance
for your own flesh and blood
and kicking her out.
Why? It's my money.
What's wrong with keeping it
for my own child?
What do you even have?
This old, run-down house?
Khanoon can find
a better home than this.
Rude brats!
If you can find a better one,
then go ahead.
Go and use that agricultural
knowledge to work in a rice paddy.
- Go!
Let's have a fistfight
with that mouth of yours!
She's crazy!
Let me go!
Watch out, Paeng!
Stop, Wanfahmai.
You adopted her but have you
ever given her love?
You used her for work like cattle.
What's wrong with you?
Are you even humans?
Khanoon,
if you're unhappy, you can report
them to the authorities.
As far as I've heard,
you didn't adopt her
to be your daughter.
So why did you adopt her?
Please don't make me
uncover the truth.
Khanoon can ask for a compensation
and she can report you
to the authorities.
According to the law,
you can't cancel an adoption
unless there are compelling reasons.
Have a lawyer on hand.
Come on. Have a seat here.
Sit here for now, Khanoon.
I'll find some clothes
for you to change into.
Come on, Pony.
Okay, Paeng.
It's okay to feel sad
but spare some time to think about
what you're going to do tomorrow.
Think carefully.
This could be the chance
that you can have the freedom
you never had.
Do you know that nothing else
can make you as happy
as having control of your own life?
You can go anywhere and do anything.
Everything depends on your outlook.
You can't change others
but you can change yourself.
Here.
You won't be able
to wear my clothes.
So I borrowed some of
Phokin's clothes for you.
I'll hurry and wash
and dry your clothes.
Take them.
Go and change, Artit.
The bathroom's over there.
Go on. Leopard pattern is lovely.
Paeng,
I don't know if Artit's
well-spoken or good-looking.
I just met him
but I believe in everything he said.
Paeng, I know now
why you used to love him
and was so willing to
give him your virginity.
If I were you, I'd go for him and
I wouldn't make a mistake like you.
Pony, that's enough.
Well, he's so handsome!
Artit,
my clothes fit you perfectly.
The leopard pattern
looks really lovely.
Why are you scooting away?
Do you wear this regularly?
Of course I do.
It's my iconic pattern.
I always score with this one.
Actually, I'd like to score
with you too.
Hey,
you can go away now.
I'm going to talk to him.
You're always such a killjoy.
Artit, you can go home now.
I'll find my own way back.
Do you want me to go back
in this get-up?
The washing's going to take awhile.
It's okay. I can wait.
I'm hungry too.
Should we eat out?
You can go out in this too.
Wanfahmai.
I'll make you something simple.
What's something simple?
Well, what do you want?
Be polite.
What would you like, Mr. Artit?
A burger.
I don't have any.
- A lobster.
- Are you crazy? There's none.
Oh? Then why did you ask?
So I can order something for you.
No one lives at this condo.
There's no food.
Oh,
did I come to the wrong room?
You didn't, Auntie.
I'm not Auntie.
It's better if you call me Sister.
Okay, Sister. You're not wrong.
Your husband?
No, he's Paeng's.
Are you really Paeng's guy?
Oh, my. Leopard pattern.
Why? Does she usually
bring guys over?
My!
Never.
You're the first to be here.
I can guarantee it.
My little Paeng
has never been with any guy.
She's still pure.
Stop right now.
You always go overboard.
I only asked you
to deliver the food.
Stop being so extra.
Here.
How much is everything?
Let's calculate later.
You didn't tell me
you have a pet leopard.
I'm going now.
Just go. Hurry up and go away.
Hold on.
I guarantee.
I never lie.
- I'd like to scratch you.
- Okay.
Eat up, Khanoon.
Paeng,
she eats anyway
when she's stressed or sad.
If you keep urging her to eat,
she might explode.
I really don't have
an appetite this time.
Very good.
So you'll be slim with curves
in all the right places.
Look there. His plate is so empty.
Paeng, serve something for Artit.
He can use his own hands.
Just a little bit.
Hey.
What Sister said just now,
is it true?
About what?
The thing about no guys wanting you.
Says who? It's me
who doesn't want anyone.
You're waiting for me, aren't you?
Too bad. I don't want you either.
Or do you want it on the mouth?
So you can stop talking.
You can't quip back fast enough
so you resort to violence?
Power-hungry psycho.
Don't embarrass me.
Why?
Why do you have to fake it
in front of my friends?
They already know everything.
Know what? What did you tell them?
Nothing.
I think
Artit's not just her former
husband-to-be.
Oops.
Heard it with my own ears.
I think he's suitable for you.
That's true.
He's not scary at all.
He's actually delectable.
Look at the leopard pattern!
Khanoon.
I'm sorry for waking you up.
Just cry.
Cry as much as you want.
It might be really hard
for you today.
But once you get through it,
it'll be only
a tiny part of your life.
Khanoon, remember
that there's no one who can hug you
as warmly as you can hug yourself.
Khanoon, don't worry.
You can stay at my condo
as long as you want.
I'll be back
in a year and eight months.
Well...
I have to go. I've arrived.
Bye.
Thank you for going with me.
We've arrived for ages.
Get out of the car.
If you're so disgusted,
why did you go with me?
Artit, honestly
are you bipolar?
You're nice for a moment
and then you're mean again.
I'm starting to feel
like I can't take it.
I'm always like this.
You have to be able to endure it.
It's a year and eight months, right?
You'll see this everyday.
You can get out now.
Are you human or an evil ghost?
Hey!
Paeng!
Watch out. The clip might
end up on social media.
You sly girl,
open the door right now.
What's the matter, Artit?
Give me your phone.
Hey.
I won't give it to you.
You're not?
Hey, Paeng!
Delete that clip or you'll get it.
It's you. Go home
and don't provoke me again.
Or the whole world will see
your sexy dance moves.
It's not an empty threat.
You're not going to listen to me?
Give it to me!
Give the phone to me!
Don't run away!
Come here!
Artit, let me go! That hurts!
Let the phone go first.
I'm not giving it to you!
Artit, let me go.
- It hurts!
- You let go then!
What's the password?
Who would tell other people that?
Are you going to tell me or not?
I'm not.
Alright.
Come here you!
That hurts, Artit!
Stay still.
Simple as that.
Meanie.
You started it, so blame yourself.
Do you understand now
how it feels being secretly filmed?
Understand what?
I don't have to understand anything.
You deleted your clip.
You have to delete my pictures
in your phone too.
What pictures?
The ones you secretly took of me.
Paeng,
do you think I can stand
having your pictures in my phone?
I've deleted them ages ago.
Thank you, then.
Artit,
I'd like to make a deal with you.
What deal?
Can we live together peacefully?
If you really hate me,
then let me be.
We just mind our own business.
Because I have no hopes
in you anymore.
Do you expect me to believe you?
Paeng!
If I felt anything towards you,
my heart would tremble
with excitement, right?
But I don't feel
anything at all.
I'm holding your hand
but I don't feel anything.
So I won't do anything to you.
We should just mind
our own business.
You can just ignore me.
Isn't that good, Artit?
No.
Why not?
Because I don't trust you.
This is the new way
to seduce me, isn't it?
I was so startled.
Paeng, you tricky girl.
If there's any problem...
Koi,
I have to borrow
your boss for a day.
Feel free to do so.
I'll take care of the shop.
Koi.
You're not going to stop, are you?
We haven't even started dating,
so how can I stop?
Even if we do,
I won't stop loving you.
Is this what you're talking about?
The thing you bought for me?
Are you admitting
that you feel the same way?
I'm not.
I'm telling you
the reason why I kept it
because I thought it's still useful.
But now,
I don't want to keep it anymore.
Ling.
Throw out the trash for me.
And don't let me see it here
when I come back.
Non, you're here.
I'm looking for assistance.
On what?
Try my rose tea.
If it's nice,
I'll market it right away.
It's delicious.
Are you okay?
You seem distracted.
Did something happen?
I don't understand women.
I don't understand them at all.
Non.
Who's the girl? Do I know her?
You do.
Who is it? I can't think of anyone.
Don't tell me that it's Ling.
Whoa!
What have I missed?
I'm quite sure
that she likes me.
But she won't admit it
and she always refuses me.
Really?
I thought Ling and Artit
are into each other.
They're not.
What should I do?
I have to go up North with them too.
Is there anything I can do to help?
If there is, will you help me?
With my utmost pleasure.
This rose tea is really nice.
It's good, right?
Yes!
- Hello, Uncle.
- Oh hello, Non.
Have a seat.
Are you here to see Artit?
I'm here to see you.
I have something to ask you.
Do you remember
the annual project I do with Artit?
The one where you donate stuff
to schools in the mountains?
Yes. I'd like to invite
Paeng too this year.
Of course you can.
I'm not worried if she's with you.
That's good. So she can
take a break as well.
Please look after her.
Thank you.
I got the green-light from Uncle.
You can come.
Okay. I'll help you the best I can.
I hope your plan works.
I don't know. But we have to try.
Let's do our best.
But you have to help me too.
Help with what?
Help protect me from Artit.
If he sees me, he'll snap
my neck for sure.
Artit's not that violent, I think.
You underestimate him.
Probably not just my neck,
he might also break my limbs
and chop me up.
Hey, is that even possible?
It is!
You just have to
dress up beautifully.
If he sees you, he might soften up.
I think an armor might
be safer for me.
If he knows that you're there
to help me,
he'll be okay with it.
I'll talk to him.
Let's eat dinner at Artit's tonight.
How come?
You invited Paeng over for dinner?
I invited both Non and Paeng.
You know I don't want
to see her face.
Tubtim, be reasonable.
If I wasn't, I would've
chased her out a long time ago.
If you're scared that Paeng might do
something to our son,
you can just forget it.
I won't.
I heard that
Paeng now has someone she likes
and it's not Artit.
Who is it?
Artit's friend.
Non?
But I saw him
with Ling.
What is it?
Who's coming to eat with us?
Hello.
Make yourself at home.
Who invited you?
I did.
Non hasn't been over
for dinner in awhile.
There's food at his place.
Why aren't you happy that
your friend came for dinner?
I'm just surprised.
Besides,
he's not here alone.
I invited both of them.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
If it wasn't for your help,
Paeng's rose garden
wouldn't have been successful.
I don't think so, Uncle.
Paeng's already skilled.
The helper is the skilled one.
You're so good at
complimenting each other.
I'm happy that you're helping
taking care of Paeng.
Eat up.
- Enjoy.
- Let's eat.
Thank you, Non.
Are you handicapped?
Can't you do it yourself?
Artit.
Let them be.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Paeng?
He's staring. I shouldn't have come.
Ignore him.
Hurry up and eat.
I have to talk to you.
Non!
Hold on!
What's up?
Leave us. I'm going
to talk to my friend.
Please don't go yet. Wait for me.
What's up with you?
You liked Ling the other day.
So what's all this?
You think that Paeng and I...
It's not just me,
but my parents as well.
What did you do?
Paeng's like a sister to me.
I haven't done anything.
You haven't done anything,
then how did it turn out this way?
How should I know?
You should just stay away.
Don't give me anymore trouble.
Artit,
you don't seem like
you're possessive over me.
But you look like you're
possessive over her.
Possessive my butt. I hate her.
I just don't want to see her happy.
You're such a psycho.
I have to go now. Later.
Do you feel relieved now?
So you won't have to be worried
about Artit and Paeng.
I hope it's true.
I'll pray to the Holy Spirits
that Non will take her away.
That's good.
So I can have Ling back.
What does Ling have to do with this?
Oh? Non loves Ling.
I heard it with my own ears.
As for Ling, I'm not so sure.
I saw her walking away from Non.
Is that true?
Did I misunderstand something?
But your niece is really something.
She probably seduced Non
until he fell for her.
That's why he's taking care
of her so well.
I hope it's true.
So I can be relieved about Artit.
Who are you angry at?
Definitely Miss Paeng.
I probably give her
too much free time.
That's why she has time
to seduce other guys.
- Saeb.
- Yes?
Tell Paeng to come see me.
Where, Mr. Artit?
The cucumber patch.
What's the matter?
You have to work mornings again.
Bring it on. Do as you please.
You can work me as hard as you want.
I'll just die at most.
You probably won't die easily.
Why? Is it so tormenting
to see me being happy?
Sort of.
You have time to seduce my friend
and my parents misunderstood you.
I'm telling you,
Non doesn't like you.
I don't like...
I don't care
if Non likes me or not.
But I really like him.
Because he's cool
and a gentleman.
Unlike someone.
You were so blindly obsessed
with me in the past.
Back then I was so stupid.
I was stupid like a donkey.
Alright. I don't want
to argue with you anymore.
Let's get started.
What do you want me to do?
Follow me.
Nang, where have you been?
I really have to apologize to you.
I didn't mean to tell on you.
But you know
how scary Artit gets
when he's angry.
It's okay. I understand.
I know my son well.
I'm so relieved.
Why are you here today?
I wanted to ask
if Artit is still angry with me.
If it's about you trashing
Paeng's place, don't worry.
He actually said he was behind it.
That means he's not
angry with anyone.
If he's not,
then I still have a chance
with him, right?
Of course you do.
At least you have me on your side.
Honestly,
my daughter-in-law can be you
or anyone else,
except Paeng.
No, it can't be anyone else!
Then you have to keep up
and impress him.
I'm waiting to welcome you
as my daughter-in-law.
Thank you, Auntie.
You're welcome.
- Fighting!
Count how many there are.
Count what?
These tomatoes.
Artit,
you can use me all you want.
I'm willing to do anything.
But you shouldn't
bully me like this.
Who's bullying you? This is work.
We have to know how many we have
so we can estimate the number
of customers who can pick them.
Is that true?
But there are so many!
I thought you're willing
to do anything.
If you can't do this,
then don't say so.
Artit, don't eat that!
I already counted over there.
I have to taste and see
if they're ripe enough.
You can taste somewhere else.
I have to taste everywhere.
Just subtract the amount
from what you've counted.
Where was I?
I forgot!
Start over.
Saeb.
You always bully her.
Do you want me to punch you?
Madam told me to fetch you.
Let's go.
He smiled!
Artit,
have a seat.
Here.
Would you like some dessert?
Nang made it.
Is Nang gone?
Yes. She's embarrassed
about the other day.
Don't be angry with her.
I just scolded her. I wasn't angry.
That's good.
So I can call and tell her that.
She'll be happy.
Actually,
Nang's quite lovely.
Do you have your eyes on her?
- Not at all.
- Dear me!
That's mean. You're so frank.
Or are you gay?
If I'm gay, would Madam Tubtim
be able to accept it?
I can as long as it isn't Paeng.
Five one nine,
- five two zero,
- You're here.
five two one,
five two two, five two three,
five two four, five two five...
Hello!
I was looking all over for you.
Did you come in peace or not?
You shouldn't ask.
Have I ever come in peace?
Don't worry. It's just warm.
I don't slap anyone
just for fun anymore.
Good.
People have to improve
and not always be a bad person.
Mostly, I'm only bad
to a bad person.
Mostly,
you started it.
Mostly, you provoke me first.
Five two five.
What?
Please help me memorize it.
Five two five.
What's up?
Artit's not here.
Don't pretend to be working hard.
You didn't come back to work.
You're just here to get Artit.
You want to provoke me,
but your brain is only capable
of thinking about this?
It's getting old.
Your behavior always
reminds me of it.
Who shamelessly
tried to assault Artit in his room?
It's already old news.
You're upset
because you want to do it too
but you were too scared, right?
That's right.
Oh, are you crazy?
I don't need to stoop
so low to do that.
Auntie Tubtim
approved of me being
Artit's girlfriend.
Really? Congratulations.
You can stop being jealous of me.
Use the time to book a hotel
for your wedding.
Or find a kindergarten
for your children.
There's a snake in the house.
How can I rest assured?
I can relax
when you packed your things
and get out of this farm.
I don't want him anymore.
Even if he was handed over to me
on a gold platter.
You can rest assured.
I don't believe you.
Have it your way.
It's none of my business.
You're done for today?
What was the number again?
Five two five.
Five two five. Thank you.
Five two five,
five two six, five two seven,
five two eight,
five two nine, five three zero...
You unpredictable psycho!
I was going to go
to the rose garden.
Why did I come home?
Is this the CCTV you talked about?
Are you going to
track my every move?
Ouch! That hurts!
Help!
Anyone, please help me!
How did you get here, Artit?
I drove here, of course.
I know you drove.
You probably wouldn't have
ridden a buffalo.
You're being cheeky.
I guess you've gotten better?
Why would you shout your head off?
I haven't done anything.
Excuse me, please keep
your voice down.
I'm sorry.
See? It's your fault.
It's your fault
for bullying me.
How did you know
I'm at the hospital?
Not just me,
but the whole farm knows.
You made quite a ruckus.
Wow, that was fast.
It's time to go.
Why aren't you careful?
You're crippled.
That's going too far.
Wait here.
I'll get you a wheelchair.
It's okay.
I don't want to be in a wheelchair.
I can just walk carefully.
Oh!
What are you doing?
Don't think anything of it.
I'm just annoyed.
Wait here.
Miss Paeng. Come, I'll help you.
Here. Slowly.
Watch your step.
Here's your boss's medicine.
Have her take it on time.
Okay, sir.
Use cloth over some ice and apply it
to the spot to ease the swelling.
Understood, sir.
Come on, Miss Paeng.
Let's get inside.
Walk slowly.
Step.
There.
Thank you.
Careful.
The steps. There.
There.
Walk slowly.
Why are you carrying me?
At this rate you'll reach
the house when it's night time.
It's like a groom carrying his bride
to consummate the marriage.
Aueng,
get me a piece of cloth
and some ice.
Yes, sir.
I'll show you
how you should apply it.
Artit,
I think
you don't have to show her
how to do it.
It's easy. Aueng can do it.
When you fell, you should've
landed with your mouth.
So you'd stop talking.
Bear with it.
I hung up some washings.
I have to go get them.
Aueng!
Are you crazy?
Are you planning to bite me?
Artit, are you crazy?
You deserved it.
All done.
Why are you doing this?
Because I'm afraid you're hurt
and you won't work as much
as I'm paying you.
Get better soon.
So I can torment you again.
You're stingy and psychotic.
Thank you very much
for worrying about her.
Who's worried?
I don't want your boss to die here.
I don't want any trouble.
I thought Artit would
soften up to you.
But instead...
He's still as mean to me as always.
And he pretended to be good to you.
He still hates me
and keeps finding ways to bully me.
He's only afraid that I'm hurt
and I won't be able to work.
But they say
that you'll get what you hate.
Maybe
someday he might end up liking you.
You're delusional.
You can't be sure.
It's giving me goosebumps.
Make sure that you
don't forget anything.
I won't forget. I checked
three times already.
The sports equipment for
the school is in this one.
The medical equipment
is in Non's car.
I was just making sure.
Ling, I'd like to ask you something.
Why won't you ride in Non's car?
Are you disgusted by me?
I'm not. I just want to know.
Then I'll choose not to tell you.
It's so beautiful.
Why hasn't Non arrived?
We'll be late for the donation.
Give him a call.
Hey, Artit! Ling!
- You're here.
- Have you waited long?
Have you waited long?
Ages. Come on, let's go.
There's still one more.
Did you forget that Kot's
not coming this year?
I'm not talking about Kot.
Who is it?
Whoa!
Watch your step.
Paeng!
Come here right now.
What are you doing?
What did I do?
Why did you invite Paeng?
I saw her being lonely
so I felt bad.
So I brought her along
for some fresh air.
I don't feel good about this.
Why didn't you ask me?
- I'm not okay.
- But I'm okay.
If you have a problem with this,
then mind your own business.
I'll take care of Paeng.
I'm annoyed when I see her face.
And what do you want me to do?
We're already here.
- Well...
- Can you stop feeling annoyed?
We're here for the donation.
I'm happy that you came.
How come you're with Non?
Oh, he invited me.
But I don't know if I made
the right decision.
It's so upsetting
when Artit saw me.
Are you gossiping about me?
I was saying
that you saw me
and you're already upset.
You already know this.
But you came anyway.
Actually, I didn't want to come.
Then take a bus home.
Artit, enough.
Come on, Paeng.
You should get into my car.
Thank you very much
for donating these.
We were in dire need of them.
You've been here before
to give donation, correct?
That's right.
That's why we know that
this hospital needs
oxygen concentrators and many other
medical equipment.
That's true. We never have
enough for the patients.
We are only a small hospital.
But there are many patients.
For example, there are only five
oxygen concentrators
in the entire district and
we have to take turns using them.
Take turns?
That's right.
For the elderlies in hospice,
if they want to spend their final
moments with their family,
we'll give it to them
to use at home.
That way, they'll be able
to spend time with their family.
It's their final happiness.
And it helps with the overwhelming
number of patients at the hospital.
It's so sad.
But it's the truth
we all have to accept.
Wow! Everything looks so delicious.
I'm hungry. Can I dig in?
Glutton.
Who caused me this much trouble?
You did it to yourself.
Don't blame others.
Who told you to come back?
You should've stayed away.
You like this, don't you?
I remember.
Serve Paeng. I can do it myself.
Okay.
Here you go, Paeng.
Non, I'd like some shrimp too.
- Can you serve me?
- Sure.
Here.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
How is it? Good?
It's so good.
It's probably because I'm hungry.
Actually, because you served me.
Eat up.
That's enough. I'm going to puke.
How did you two
get together?
Since we've come this far.
Paeng and I
are going steady.
I'll go check up on Artit.
Non, I was so shocked.
But I think Artit's
more shocked than you.
That's true.
I think I'll be dead for sure.
But Ling didn't react at all.
I won't survive the night.
I think Ling's face fell too.
Did you see that?
But I think
your face is worse than Ling's.
I'm scared Artit will kill me.
It's okay.
I'll protect you.
Artit!
Artit, what's wrong!?
How did those two become a couple?
I don't know either.
Do you like it here, Paeng?
The atmosphere is so nice.
Here. I'll do it.
Go and help Paeng.
She can wait for me.
What are you smiling about?
This is the guys' tent.
Artit, help me set up this tent.
I'll go and help Paeng with hers.
Where are you going to sleep?
With you, of course.
I'm going to help the girls
set up their tent.
Or should I sleep with Paeng?
Non, are you kidding me?
Why would I?
It's normal. We're a couple.
- You...
- Don't think dirty thoughts.
There's nothing between us.
But I'm not sure about later on.
Ling, please come over to this side.
What are you mad about?
Are you jealous of me?
Who'd be jealous of a jerk
of a friend like you?
If you're not, then what's wrong?
Here.
Help me pitch the tent.
So are you jealous or not?
What are you looking at?
The person I want to react
doesn't have a reaction at all.
And the person I expected
to react the least is going crazy.
It's so scary.
Paeng, from now on you have to
watch your own back.
Oh?
You said you're going to protect me.
He's this troubled.
I'm not sure anymore.
Ling,
are you still hungry?
You didn't eat much earlier.
I've brought some warm milk.
Would you like some?
It's okay. You drink up.
What's wrong?
You've been angry all day.
Don't you see
what Non has been doing?
You don't like Non
being close to Paeng, do you?
It's his right
to like anyone or flirt with anyone.
The same goes for Paeng.
If they like each other,
and can be happy together,
how is that bad?
You don't feel anything at all?
It has nothing to do with me.
Paeng,
help me and look at Ling's reaction.
Nothing. It's just Artit.
He's stretching his neck so much
he's turning into a giraffe.
I'm probably going to get
my heart broken again.
Don't give up yet.
If I don't,
then I have to keep trying.
Here.
Again?
Careful.
You can sit here.
You look like you're
herding a cattle.
What? Isn't that true?
Or have you suddenly
become paraplegic?
Is that why you're acting all weak?
Artit, give her some respect.
Why should I?
She's my employee after all.
She's my girlfriend.
I have to protect her.
How brave.
You've successfully seduced
my friend. Were you that lonely?
Artit, look after her for a bit.
I'll be back.
Oh?
Tell me,
how did you get together with Non?
Artit, let me go first.
You tell me first.
What does it have to do with you?
I told you to stay away
from my friend.
If you're not going to listen,
you're going to get it.
You can tell Non yourself.
Do you want to die by my hands?
How did you get together with Non?
Answer me.
Hey, are you going
to tell me or not?
Alright.
Once we got back,
I'm going to work you to death.
Go ahead. You're only
good at bullying me anyway.
It hurts. Are you going
to let go now?
You're only tough with women.
Paeng!
What? Can't stand the truth?
I'm having a breakdown.
Can you not make me angrier?
You know yourself?
Alright.
Just choke me to death
with your own hands.
You want to kill me anyway.
Here's your chance.
No one will miss me if I disappear.
I'm all alone. I have no relatives.
No one's going to save me.
Go on.
Stop.
I thought you've got guts.
Put it on.
You might get sick. It's cold.
Go and take care of Paeng.
I can take care of myself.
I left Paeng with Artit.
I'll go back later.
And why did you come after me?
It's a force of habit.
I've been doing this for years.
I'm afraid Paeng might
misunderstand me.
She won't overthink it
unlike someone.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I've always looked at you this way.
We're friends.
That's right.
From now on,
I will love you as a friend.
Hurry back to the tent.
You might catch a cold.
I'm telling you.
The reason why I kept it
was because I thought
it's still useful.
But now,
I don't want to keep it anymore.
We're going steady.
- Come with me.
- Paeng, come here.
Just split me in two
so you can have each half?
I don't even feel anything
being this close to you.
I'm only waiting for your answer
whether you're going
to be with me or not.
Paeng's with a guy.
They look really close.
It's like they're on a date.
Why do you have
to keep harassing me?
You always nag me.
You hate me!
I hate you too!
She wished inwardly.
And she said "they've been killed."
Who killed them?
Did Paeng's parents
really die in a car crash?