(My Forever Sunshine)
You two have a lot in common.
Ling, what do you think
if a friend changes his status
into a boyfriend.
I don't think it's good.
You might lose a friend.
No matter what happens,
You have to be strong.
Why are you saying this to me?
Dad! Dad!
Dad, don't leave me!
Paeng!
Thongkhum! What's going on?
I won't accept this.
I'm not going to let this go!
- Little Miss!
- Please don't!
Probably no one
because her parents are dead!
Oh, dear!
this is your home.
Everyone here is your family.
You're not alone anymore.
I know what's my happiness now.
(Wanfamai's flower bed)
Grow fast
and absorb a lot of fertilizer
so you'll have lots of flowers.
Miss Paeng,
I'm here to help.
- I'll help water them.
- It's okay.
Saeb, I'll do it myself. Artit told
me to take care of them myself.
Oh, wow. Miss Paeng.
You're very obedient to Mr. Artit.
I have to be so that he loves me.
Aw.
Miss Paeng, would you like
Mr. Artit to love you?
Of course, Saeb.
I love him.
And I want him to love me.
Wow!
Miss Paeng, can I ask you something?
In what way do you
want him to love you?
Saeb.
In what way do girls love guys?
You shouldn't be asking.
Are you happy?
Turn around and let me see.
Why the long face?
It's your first day of school.
Aren't you happy?
I don't want to go.
I want to stay home with Artit.
Mr. Artit won't go anywhere.
You'll see him today
when you come back.
Come on. Let's go to school.
I'll carry your backpack.
Come on now.
You'll definitely see him
after school today.
Artit, you're up already?
Yes.
So, it's your first day of school.
Are you happy?
Why not?
Artit,
stop talking to her.
She's about to be late.
Come on.
Can you give me a lift?
I was planning to.
No need, Artit.
I told Saeb to do it.
It's okay, Mom. It's her first day.
I can drop her off.
You're the best! Let's go.
Hold on.
Say goodbye to my mom first.
Goodbye.
Come on.
Really!
She's got that long face
just a few moments ago.
How dare she holds
my son's hand like that?
Oh, dear.
What am I thinking?
MIss Paeng!
We've arrived, Paeng.
Can you come pick me up
this evening?
Sure.
Can you give me a lift every day?
Every day?
You have to go back to university
in only a month.
Then I won't get to see you anymore.
You will.
I'll try to come back every weekend.
Really? You promise?
Well, only if you behave.
Don't be naughty
or pick a fight with people.
Then, I'll keep my word.
Then I promise I'll study hard.
Excellent.
You can go to school now.
Bye!
I'll see you this evening.
Love you, Artit.
Can I order something?
Oh, Non! How did you get here?
Boo! I'm here too.
Are you free today? Have a seat.
Wait.
Ling told me to sit first. I have
to go first and you wait.
See? I'll sit first
and you sit later.
Wow, so many refreshments.
Very funny.
That's the wrong side.
It's still the refreshments.
Jerk! It's this side.
When are you going to order?
It's not going to be in the exams.
If we hurry, then we won't
get to talk much.
Be considerate to other tables.
I'm working.
Umm...
When do you finish work?
At 09:00 p.m.
Can you leave early?
I'd like to invite
you to the movies.
I'm not the owner, just an employee.
I don't understand you at all.
Your family is well-off. Why do you
have to work a part-time job?
Because I take my life seriously.
When will I grow up if I keep asking
for an allowance from my parents?
Oh? Is she talking about me?
- Right.
- You too.
You two get along well
like steak and salad.
I'll have shrimp paste fried rice
and chicken macaroni.
Just that for now.
Now you can go take orders
from other tables.
- All right.
- Here's the menu.
Non, I ordered two dishes just now.
You ordered four right?
Can I eat some of your food?
You order whatever you want.
It's my treat this time.
You said it.
Then I'll order takeout too.
Excuse me, can I have the menu?
Hurry! Hurry! This way!
Don't open your eyes!
- Don't open them!
- Hold on.
Why don't we go
into the house first?
- Where are you taking me?
- I have something to show you.
- Don't open your eyes!
- Okay.
This way.
Why can't I open my eyes?
Where are you taking me?
I have a surprise for you.
This is the spot.
You can open your eyes now.
- Ta-da!
- Wow!
You let me plant
Japanese Chrysanthemum.
Didn't you? Aren't I good?
Very good.
Smile like this often.
I like it when you smile.
I will.
Artit, do you know
that you're the first person
I feel happy when I'm with
apart from my parents
I want to have you
by my side forever.
You can be quite sweet sometimes.
Are you proud of them?
- Are they beautiful?
- They are.
Let's take some pictures.
Wait. Not in that position.
One, two, three.
Oh, Paeng.
you're not going to bed yet?
It's only 08:00 p.m.
Can I watch TV with you?
Sure. Sit next to me.
What are you watching?
Nothing in particular.
I'm waiting for a TV drama.
- Do you want to change the channel?
- It's okay.
What's wrong?
Are you lonely?
Do you think
there are customers who stay
as long as we do?
We've been here since 03:00 p.m.
It's now 08:45 p.m.
I'm so stuffed and gassy.
Kot,
we dropped by the place,
aren't you going to wait for Ling?
Are you really going to wait
until the shop closes?
I can't keep eating any longer.
You deserve it.
You were eating non-stop.
What do you want me to do?
You'll get kicked out
if you don't order anything.
You ordered tons of food
but then you don't eat it.
So I had to.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm leaving.
Are you really going to leave?
Really. Bye.
Ling, someone's here to see you.
He's outside.
Hey,
who is that?
Can I have the bill, please?
Just ask Mom.
She's so rich.
She gave me a lot each year.
And I've given it all to you.
I've also spent it all up.
That's why I'm here to ask for more.
Tell Mom that you're sick
and you need money.
I don't want to lie to her.
And do you want me to suffer?
Dad, I'm tired.
I only have this much.
I don't know if it's going to
be enough for the electricity bill.
I'm getting paid in two days.
Just come back here then.
All right.
Don't change jobs to avoid me again.
I love you, Ling.
Get home safe.
Oh? I thought you went home.
I thought you did too.
Get in the car.
I'll give you a lift.
Are you tired?
Eat something.
How do you know I haven't eaten?
I work at a restaurant.
There is a lot of food.
But did you get to eat them?
I saw you working the whole day.
Who's calling?
It's Artit.
Just eat.
Ling's not available
to talk right now.
Yes, it's me. Later.
Hey...
Non! You backstabbing friend.
Did you really do that?
Yes, I did.
Eat up, Ling.
A girl with a gaunt face
isn't pretty.
Here.
There's another one.
See which one you like.
Wow.
This one's pork belly.
- Kot?
- Help me.
I'm having a bad stomach ache.
Help me, please.
What have you been doing?
I had dinner with Non.
I ate too much.
Did you go see Ling?
We did, but I left first.
I had too much food
so I'm having a stomach ache.
You left first?
So, you left Non
and Ling alone together?
How could you say that? They're not
alone. There are a lot of customers.
But can you help me now?
My stomach's hurting so bad.
I don't know whether it's just gas
or food poisoning.
What medicine should I take?
Can you tell me?
Just take whatever.
Artit? Artit?
Gosh, you're such a bad friend.
Non.
What are you laughing about?
Why are you happy, ugly toad?
I'm happy
that Miss Paeng will end up
with someone decent like Mr. Artit.
How dare you say that.
You're saying like she and Mr. Artit
are going to get married. Dream on.
I'm not dreaming. It's happening.
You're delusional.
This is the first time
I see a toad bragging.
An insane toad too.
Don't go talking yet.
People might not believe it
and they'll say you're assuming.
Who cares about them?
Let's think about
how we're going to
rearrange the kitchen
after we kick out these pests.
- You toad!
- What?
What's the matter, you cockroach?
You want it?
Cross it!
Cross the line so I can
tell Mr. Krongprateep.
You cross it.
Why would I? I'm not stupid.
- Jaem.
- What's the matter?
Let's go and shop for something
for the kitchen.
I'm feeling so happy today.
Come on, then.
You heard what she said?
She might be telling the truth?
What do you mean?
I mean what I said.
Miss Paeng and Mr. Artit professed
their love to each other?
That's right, Pong.
I heard Miss Paeng professing to him
with my own ears.
Whoa!
Aueng and I kept watching Mr. Artit.
I want to put my money on this.
- Within this year...
- What?
They'll definitely get married.
Saeb, you're just assuming things.
Miss Paeng just got
into high school.
Why would Mr. Artit rush it?
You're too old. You've got grey hair
all over. I'll pluck it.
Go on. If you're not afraid of
your hands cramping.
Pong, you don't understand
young people's love.
- What?
- Would you like a challenge?
Do you want to bet on this?
Gambling?
Did you forget that Master forbade
us from gambling on the farm?
It's just for fun, Pong.
It's not fun.
Gambling is bad.
It has turned many decent people
into villains.
There are fathers
who hurt their children
because of their gambling obsession.
Fire still leaves you with the land.
Gambling will take even the pole.
- What pole?
- North Pole.
North Pole!
You're still not sorry?
I'm sorry, Pong.
- Hello.
Are you Ling's dad?
How do you know?
I'm Ling's close friend.
I have something
to talk to you about.
Here you are.
Why do you think you
have to give me money?
I don't want to see Ling suffer.
We're friends.
Just think of me as a relative.
I'll accept it.
You're a good and generous person.
If you're this close to her,
just call me Dad.
Yes, Dad.
If you need money again,
call me.
You don't have to call Ling.
Do you want to do it that way?
Then
can I have your number?
Here.
Thanks.
I have to go now.
I stayed home the whole day.
I'm starving right now.
I'm starving too.
Hey.
Are you a new student?
I'm Maew and she's Toom.
Friends
make us feel like we're
not alone in the world.
Friends are there to listen to
your secrets and feelings,
both ups and downs.
Or they're there to give you advice
when you can't talk to adults.
I'm Paeng.
Come sit with us over there.
If you have any
questions, just ask us.
We know about everything
in the school.
But if it's about studying,
don't ask us
because we don't know.
Come on. Let's go take a seat.
You sit here.
We'll sit next to you.
You can go to buy lunch.
I'll keep watch of the table.
- What should we eat?
- I don't know. Let's check it out.
Come and sit with us.
Sit down.
Toom, Maew
why didn't you tell me
that you want to switch seats?
So I can sit with you.
Who said you can sit?
Do you own the cafeteria?
- No.
- If you don't, I can sit anywhere.
How dare you talk back to us?
You're younger.
I'm not talking back.
I'm telling the truth.
Enough.
Don't mind her.
She's an orphan
so there's no one
to teach her manners.
Paeng,
go sit somewhere else.
We'll sit with Nang.
Your friend said so herself.
I didn't say it.
Get going now.
Go away.
Or do you want us to drag you away?
I thought you've got guts.
I'm going home.
Perm, you can drive home.
I'll go home by myself.
I'm so happy to see you, Paeng.
Are you happy?
Don't fake it. I'm not stupid.
Don't see me in that negative light.
What do you want?
My driver said that
the car broke down.
Can I hitch a ride with you?
You know that Artit's picking me up.
Artit's picking you up?
I didn't know that.
Not believable.
Good. So we won't have to fake it.
What do you want?
I just want to hitch a ride.
- I'm not allowing you.
- Did I ask for your permission?
I can ask Artit myself.
Artit is mine.
Says who? I met him before you.
Remember that.
I've met him since I was five.
I've met him since I was four.
Paeng, let's go.
Oh, Nang.
Artit, can I hitch a ride with you?
My driver said the car broke down.
Okay.
No, I won't let her.
It's okay, Paeng. Get in, Nang.
Get off right now.
I'll sit at the front.
I can't sit the back.
I might get carsick.
I said get off now.
Paeng, behave.
Paeng.
Paeng, get in the car.
I'll sit at the front.
Get down from my seat now.
You're not very nice
behaving like this.
How can you be harsh like that?
Artit, if Paeng's not happy.
I can sit at the back.
Then go ahead.
Paeng,
we're home. Go inside.
I'll drop Nang off
then I'm going to see a friend.
I'm coming with you.
Paeng, get out of the car.
What time are you coming back?
- I'll drop Nang off and...
- Paeng,
give him some alone time.
If you're too clingy,
he might be uncomfortable.
I'm not talking to you.
You're an outsider, don't butt in.
- Oh, my!
- Paeng,
don't be rude. Get out of the car.
Go on.
Let's go, Artit.
Nang, is Non home?
He's not back yet.
I'll drop you here then.
Artit,
is there a problem with Paeng?
I'm worried about her.
Aren't you angry with her?
I'm not.
Thanks so much.
I'm sorry on behalf of Paeng too.
Paeng is all right. Don't mind her.
Does she have a problem at home?
Is that why she
has to live with you?
Uhh...
That's Non.
Do you miss me so much you have
to come all the way here?
Get out now. Out.
What's up with you?
- I'll switch the engine off first.
- Quick.
I haven't even rolled
the windows up yet.
- Come talk to me over here.
- What?
Come here.
Where have you been?
Kot's sick.
So, I went to take care of him.
Was it Kot or Ling?
You weren't free.
How can you be angry at me?
I have to take care of Paeng.
Don't take advantage of this.
If you have someone to take care of,
don't do two things at once.
Take care of Paeng if you're worried
about her. I'll take care of Ling.
I have to take care of her.
Dad asked me to.
- You have to?
- Right.
Why?
He's not back yet.
Paeng, come in and talk to me.
I'm going to wait for Artit.
But I have something to talk to you.
Her parents have all passed away.
That's right.
They both died in a car crash.
She has no relatives either.
So Dad had to take her in.
I feel so sorry for her.
Right?
That's why I have to
take care of her.
She's really fond of me too.
I think you're doing
the right thing.
You have to give her a lot of time.
A child who's been
psychologically traumatized
might harm or kill themself.
You have to keep a sharp eye on her.
You're doing the right thing.
I think
you should just stay here
during the break.
What about you?
I think I'm going back to Bangkok
and take care of Ling.
You're taking advantage of this.
- How dare you?
- Artit! Artit!
- I'm only joking!
- How dare you?
Hey, hey!
I want you to behave
more appropriately.
You're a girl.
You must be reserved.
Do you understand?
What are you trying to tell me?
What am I doing wrong?
You're growing up into a woman.
You can't just go and lean
on a guy's shoulder.
Did someone tell you something?
I don't care.
I didn't do anything wrong.
How aren't you wrong?
I'm trying to teach you.
You're a girl.
What's all the yelling?
Why can't you think
what's proper or not?
What's the matter, Tubtim?
Someone told me
that the other night
she was leaning on
Artit's shoulder while watching TV.
Is that true, Paeng?
Artit didn't even say anything.
Why are you scolding me?
I'm always wrong in your eyes.
But is it appropriate?
Why can't you figure it out?
Tubtim, calm down.
There's probably nothing.
Are you going
to wait until there is?
Anyway, I'm going to talk to Artit
once he's back.
You're trying to get in our way.
You don't love me!
What are you saying?
I love Artit. I want to be with him.
What's wrong with that?
Paeng!
- Calm down.
- Did you hear that?
Did you hear what she's thinking?
Calm down.
I can't calm down anymore.
Artit is with Non.
I'm going to talk to him today.
Let's leave it for another day.
You're going to stress him out.
It's already late.
Don't you feel anything at all?
Aren't you afraid of
what she's going to do next?
Tubtim,
Paeng's only 16.
She's not as bad as you think.
Are you sure?
She's vile, that girl.
Just you wait.
I can't even stand
just thinking about it.
What if
- those two are really in love?
- What?
What did you say?
What if Artit loves Paeng?
No way.
I won't accept that girl
as my daughter-in-law.
Never.
Whoa, hey!
How did you come in?
You forgot to lock the door.
What time is it?
It's late. I'll be late for school.
Huh?
Wait. I'll take a shower
Why didn't the alarm go off?
Paeng, you're still here?
You told me to wait.
Why didn't you wait outside?
Get out now. I'm getting dressed.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you get dressed.
I can help you. Don't be shy.
I can do it myself.
Wait outside.
I'm putting on my pants.
Don't be shy.
- I'll turn around. I won't look.
- Paeng, get out.
Hurry or I'll be late for school.
All right, then.
Paeng,
next time don't come into my room
like this, understand?
People might see us. It'll look bad.
You're scolding me about this too?
- Are you done yet?
- Not yet.
Hurry up, Artit.
I'm finished.
Come on. Let's hurry.
What time is it?
It's exactly 06:00 a.m.
Six...
Six o'clock?
I thought you said you're late.
I want you to take me out
for some breakfast.
Paeng!
Let's go, Artit.
Yes?
I've just arrived at the dorm.
Later.
- Hello?
- Non, it's me.
Yes?
Dad, what's the matter?
I need another 5,000 for something.
I just gave some to you.
I know. I'm feeling guilty too.
But it's really necessary.
But if it's inconvenient
for you, then it's okay.
I can ask Ling.
Hold on, Dad.
Ling won't have it.
Right?
That's why I called you.
Let's meet at the same place.
The same ATM
close to where Ling works.
I'll see you later.
Dad? Hello? Dad?
Here you are.
Thanks.
Dad?
Non?
Do you know each other?
Is this your dad?
- Hello.
Are you Ling's friend?
What's your name?
- It's Non.
- Oh.
Why does it look
like you were talking?
I was withdrawing some money.
Then I turned around and saw you.
Why are you withdrawing money here?
I was thinking of eating
at the shop.
So many questions.
It's nothing. We just met.
Since we've met now,
let's eat together.
You too.
No, Dad.
I have to work.
You can take leave for a day.
All right? Eat with me.
I'll ask for a leave for you.
Come on. Let's eat at
a place around here.
I'll help you take leave.
Eat it all up.
It's my treat this time.
- How much did you order?
- Not much.
Come on. We eat together
once in a while.
Here. Fried chicken
is Ling's favorite.
Get some for her.
- Come on.
- I can do it myself.
No, you're a girl.
Let the gentleman serve you.
Go on.
Just like that.
You go to the same university?
Same faculty as well?
Yes, sir.
What do your parents do?
Dad!
They own a business.
What is this business?
A resort.
A resort? Wow, you must be rich.
Ling is very good at English.
Let her work for you
after graduation.
My daughter is still single.
She's beautiful
but she's still available.
Would you like to apply
to be my son-in-law?
Dad, that's enough.
I was only kidding.
You don't mind, right?
I don't.
See? He doesn't mind.
Eat up. Here.
This is very delicious.
This spicy salad is your favorite.
We're here.
I'm sorry, Non.
What? What are you apologizing for?
Do I even have to answer?
It's nothing.
I don't really mind him.
Don't mind him too.
You don't understand.
Dad's always like this.
Do you want to go for a walk?
Here. Eat up.
You'll feel better.
Does that even work?
It does. Snacking helps
you feel better.
Try it if you don't believe it.
Look at that face. Here.
Here.
No more.
Good. You deserve it.
What are you smiling about?
You're pulling pranks on me.
Does that mean
you're feeling better?
Yes.
If there's anything,
just let it out sometimes.
Don't keep it to yourself.
You'll lose all your hair.
No one will love you if you're bald.
Are you giving me snide remarks?
No.
It's direct.
I can see you're feeling better.
I feel relieved now.
Don't act like you can read my mind.
How many years have we been friends?
I know everything about you.
What's the matter?
Why are you silent?
I'm grateful
that I have a good friend like you.
Don't cry.
Is it that touching?
Jerk.
I'm grateful for having
a good friend like you too.
- Are you trying to be touching?
- Stop.
My hair's all messed up.
If you don't have anyone,
you always have me.
You have Artit and Kot too.
Right.
How pitiful. An orphan.
I understand why you're like this.
You have no parents to educate you.
How is that anyone's business?
I feel bad for you.
Your parents are dead.
You must feel terrible.
What are you talking about?
How did you know about me?
Everyone knows that.
Your parents are dead.
You must feel terrible.
Stop talking right now.
I said so because
I'm worried about you.
Let's do it this way.
I'll let everyone know
what happened.
So everyone will feel sorry for you.
Stop that!
Why?
Are you embarrassed?
If you don't want anyone
else to know,
then stay way from Artit!
Remember that.
Come here!
Why did you do that to her?
Good thing someone found them.
Or there might be serious injuries.
You can punish her
as much as you want.
I have no problems with it.
I'm not guilty.
She started it first.
It's not true.
I was only greeting her
because we know each other.
But I don't know
what she's angry about.
She grabbed my hair
and slapped me repeatedly.
Why are you like this?
I'm so sorry, Nang.
Are you hurt?
I'll take you to the doctor.
Oh, dear. How am I going to look
Ms. Ladawan in the face?
Why doesn't anyone believe me?
I'm not guilty. She started it.
What did she do?
I asked you so many times.
But you didn't say.
Say it.
Oh, no.
Wanfahmai. In front of a teacher?
I'm going to have you
clean the toilets for ten days
and your behavior points deducted.
If this happens again,
your punishment will be harsher.
Hold on. Stop right now.
- We have to talk.
- Paeng!
Mom, what's going on?
It's Paeng. She slapped Nang.
What's wrong with her?
Why did you do that?
So she'll know
not to pick fights with me.
Picking fights? I've known
Nang for a long time.
She's very nice and well-behaved.
She wouldn't do that.
- You're stupid for buying that.
- Paeng!
Don't be rude to my mom.
Let's go apologize to Nang.
No, I'm not going. I hate her.
Tell her to leave me alone.
- Or I'll slap her again.
- Paeng!
Don't do this again.
I don't like it.
How can you be so rude?
- I'm not going!
- Go! Go!
- Artit, no!
- This little brat!
Help! Anyone?
- Let me go!
- Paeng!
I'm not going!
Mom!
What's going on?
- My hip.
- Are you hurt?
Dad, look after her.
- Are you okay?
- Paeng.
She's such a brat.
I can't take this.
Did Paeng really say that?
I don't know if she's mentally ill
or just ill-mannered.
No matter what it is.
If she's going to be rude,
then we can't live together.
Calm down, Tubtim.
I've already reached my limit.
Look at her and what she's done.
There's the thing about Artit.
Now she slapped Nang too.
If she really is ill, then we have
to take her to the doctor.
Or we can just let
her live somewhere else.
No, we can't.
Why not?
If we're doing this to
pay back to Mr. Tharathep,
we can just give her money.
We can let Aueng
and Jaem take care of her.
They probably won't abandon her.
I don't want to live under
the same roof with her anymore.
We can't do that.
Paeng must live here forever.
Why?
Is there any other reason
I don't know?
Paeng.
Stop.
You can't just kick Mom
and run away like this.
I didn't mean it.
If you didn't, then go apologize.
You can't be
a naughty girl like this.
Go apologize to her.
Will you stop being
angry with me if I do?
You have to go to Non's with me.
You have to apologize to Nang.
No, I'm not going.
Paeng!
You don't know it. She hates me.
She likes to bully me.
If I go there,
she'll laugh at me for sure.
But you hurt her.
You have to apologize.
Your mom too.
She hates me. Your maids hate me.
Paeng,
stop being rude to people
and stop blaming others.
No one hates you.
You didn't see it.
You wouldn't know.
Before blaming others,
look at yourself first
why they don't like you.
Why do you have to scold me?
Because you're being like this.
You keep on being rude
and very headstrong.
You never listen to others.
Who's going to love you?
You don't believe me.
You're siding with those people?
Who are you calling "those people"?
My mom?
Don't make hate you also.
You hate me!
Okay, okay. Paeng.
About Nang,
I'll wait for you
to calm down a bit.
But for now,
you have to go inside
and apologize to my mom.
Understand?
That's right.
There are other reasons
I haven't told you.
Well,
what are they?
But you have to promise me
to calm down and wait
for me to finish talking.
What is it, then?
All right, all right.
I'll listen. Just say it.
Do you remember the day Tharathep
dropped Paeng off with us?
That day you asked
what we're talking about.
And I told you it's nothing.
I remember.
Actually, there is something.
Tharathep.
Just say what you want to say to me.
Do you remember your promise
that you're willing to
help me with anything?
Of course I do.
What would you say
if I want to
let Paeng
get engaged to Artit, your son.
What did you say?
Why are you quiet?
It's not that I don't like Paeng.
But isn't it too soon
for us to talk
about things like this?
Our kids are both very young.
That's what I'm worried about.
If
one day
I'm not here,
I'm afraid Paeng will
meet some bad people.
Why are you saying that?
Just in case.
My Friend,
can you promise me?
Think of it
as a way for you to help me
feel relieved.
Can you do it?
How could you agree with him?
Why didn't you discuss it
with me first?
Everything was happening so fast.
Tharathep also seemed in a rush
so that's why he dropped Paeng off.
You should ask for time
to consider it regardless.
This is our son's entire life.
You know I can't do that.
We owe a lot to him.
We owe him.
But you're doing this.
It's like you're selling our son.
I want you to keep it separate.
I decided to let Artit
get engaged to Paeng
not because of the debt.
Engaged?
I decided to let Artit
get engaged to Paeng
not because of the debt.
Engaged?
I'm not selling my son.
Even if those two got married,
I'll pay Paeng back anyway.
That's good.
Since we're talking about this,
I'd like everyone in this house
be nicer to Paeng.
She's not living here like a tenant.
She's living here as our creditor.
But you're the one
who took out the loan.
Are you going to let our son
pay off the debt for you?
I told you those two matters
are separate.
And I can't break
my promise to Tharathep.
I won't accept it. I can't take it.
What if Artit refuses?
What if he loves someone else?
Would you let him break up with her
and marry someone he doesn't love?
I won't let you destroy
his happiness and future.
Artit must marry Paeng
no matter what.
Artit.
I don't love you.
Dad.
I don't love her.
I will never marry her.
Artit, wait for me!
Artit! Artit!
- Artit! I love you!
- Paeng.
- Don't leave me. I'm marrying you.
Let me go.
No!
Artit! I love you!
I want to marry you!
Artit, don't leave me!
Dad,
I don't love Paeng.
I'm not going to marry her.
Artit,
listen to me.
What's left for me to listen?
I've heard everything.
But I gave Tharathep my word.
Do you want me to break my promise?
But this is my life, Dad.
I'm happy to do anything to pay back
to Tharathep,
but not by marrying Paeng.
It's never going to happen.
I hope you're aware of that.
But it must happen.
Because this is Tharathep's only
request before he died.
And I will never break
my promise to my friend.
Be prepared.
As soon as she graduates,
I will have you engage to Paeng.
Your only duty is to do as I say.
Do you understand what I said?
I asked if you understand
what I said.
I understand.
But I'm not going to obey.
This is my life, not yours.
Therefore, I'm the only person
who can choose how to live it.
You can't force me.
Artit!
Do you really have to marry Paeng?
That's right. Look at
what my dad said.
What's this?
You were like siblings yesterday.
Now you're engaged to each other?
This is as huge as
the Big Mountain Festival.
I feel bad for you.
You didn't even do anything.
But you have to repay
for what you didn't do.
What are you going to do?
If I don't get married,
I'll be in trouble with Dad.
Are you going to get married?
Are you crazy? Who would? I won't.
It's like you're in trouble
either way.
So what are you going to do then?
There's only one thing.
I have to convince Paeng.
She doesn't really love me.
It's because I'm the only person
who's kind to her.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Now she's just confused.
I'm going to explain to her
what true love
between a woman and a man is.
It's not
how she's thinking about me.
It'd be good if she listens to you.
Everything will be easier.
If Paeng and I keep refusing,
Dad will give in.
I hope so.
I'll get you something to eat.
Come inside.
I'm not dreaming, aren't I?
Paeng and Mr. Artit
are getting married.
Why did you slap me?
So you'll know you're not dreaming.
But at least it's a good thing
that Mr. Artit refused
Master outright.
And do you think
that Master will be okay with it?
That's true.
What if she became our mistress?
Don't we have to give
the kitchen to Aueng?
You're only worried
about the kitchen.
Worry about a place to live instead.
That's true.
What should we do, Thongkhum?
I don't know.
Paeng.
Artit.
We have something to talk.
I have something to talk to you too.
I really love you, Artit.
Paeng,
it's not like that.
You're latching on to me
because I'm kind to you.
You mistook it as love.
I didn't.
I know I love you.
You love me
as a brother.
No.
I want to marry you.
This is not something to joke about.
I'm not joking.
You told me to
find my own happiness.
I know what it is now.
My happiness is you.
Artit,
please don't leave me.
Stay with me
just as you promised.
Paeng, let me go.
I don't love you.
I never did and I'm not going to.
I never feel towards you like a man
would feel towards a woman.
You're like a sister to me.
You have to get over me.
And you have to tell my dad
that you're cancelling the wedding.
No.
I'm not going to get over you.
Paeng,
listen to me.
You love me like a brother.
Paeng!
What are you doing?
I'm letting you know
how I love you.
You have to marry me.
You have to be mine and only mine!
- Please, Artit!
- Let me go!
You're not making any sense.
We shouldn't talk right now.
Artit!
Artit! Artit! Where are you going?
I think we should stay away
from each other.
I'm not letting you go.
Move away.
- No.
- Move!
- You're mine!
- Paeng!
Artit!
Get away!
I didn't mean it.
- Paeng.
- Don't leave me!
- Artit!
- Let go. Let go!
Artit!
Artit! Artit!
Artit! Don't leave me!
Artit!
I don't love you.
I never did and I'm not going to.
I never feel towards you like a man
would feel towards a woman.
Jaem, Aueng.
Artit doesn't love me anymore.
He hates me.
What should I do?
Now Mr. Artit too?
I thought he'd understand you.
He's like everybody else.
Little Miss, if the people here
don't welcome us anymore,
should the three of us
go back to Bangkok?
That's true. I want to go
back to our home.
I really hate Duang.
Nobody likes us here either.
Should we go back to our home?
It's a big house.
The kitchen's much nicer.
It's more comfortable there.
The air conditioning is great.
And the bedrooms are big too.
Let's go back to our home.
No, I'm not going home.
I'm not going! I'm not going!
I'm staying here!
Little Miss, how can you stay here?
I don't want to die like Dad!
I'm not going to be weak like Dad!
I don't want to die like him!
I'm staying here! I'm staying here!
I'm not going! I'm staying here!
Little Miss,
why are you saying that?
That's true.
Please don't talk about death.
I don't want to go home.
Little Miss.
Darn it.
I knew it.
I knew you wouldn't
be able to convince Paeng.
I have to get away from here.
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm going back to Bangkok.
Are you coming?
I don't think
running away is the solution.
You should talk it out with Paeng.
I tried but I failed.
I think it's enough.
Did you get slapped?
Worse.
- What? A punch?
- Enough. Stop asking.
Just answer me.
Are you coming or not?
You go ahead. I'll follow you later.
- That's all.
- Oh?
Oh, hey, hey. Look at you.
Why is he so angry?
I'm worried about him.
It's okay. I understand everything.
Just stay in Bangkok and be happy.
Don't worry about over here.
I'll talk to Dad for you.
Okay.
Tubtim,
have you seen Artit?
He's gone to Bangkok.
Why is he in a rush?
Go ask that girl
what she did to him.
She's so brazen.
What did she do?
What, Tubtim?
Jaem, what should we do?
She wouldn't reply to us as all.
Little Miss,
what's wrong? Can you tell me?
Master.
I know about everything.
Come on. You can go.
- Yes, sir.
Paeng.
Mr. Krongprateep.
Artit doesn't love me anymore.
He left me like my parents.
No, he didn't.
He didn't mean to leave you.
He's probably just in shock
about what's happened.
Am I wrong
for loving him?
You're not wrong
for wanting to love someone.
But you have to know the limits.
If it's too much, you might make
them uncomfortable.
I made Artit uncomfortable.
Give him some time, okay?
Don't cry.
It's okay.
- Hey, hey!
- Enough, Artit.
Do you think being drunk
will make everything better?
Everything will be the same
the next morning.
Ling's right.
Instead of drinking,
you should think of
how to refuse your dad?
Because I couldn't think
of how to refuse Dad.
That's why I have to drink.
Is that so?
What did Paeng say to you
when you talked to her?
I'm letting you know
how I love you.
You have to marry me.
You have to be mine and only mine!
Hey, hey! Easy!
How many has he had?
I only know as much as you do.
I don't know what Paeng did to him.
Why did you order so many drinks?
Hey, hey!
You can't even walk straight.
Where are you going?
I want to be alone.
Artit.
- Artit! Artit!
- You can't walk anymore.
I'll go after him.
You stay here and pay.
Can I have the bill, please?
One, two, three, four, five drinks.
Five drinks and one popcorn.
I have...
I have 200 baht.
That's not going to be enough.
Hey, Ling!
Come back!
I don't have enough money!
I'm here to keep you company.
Ling,
let me hold you for a bit?
Do you feel better now?
Yes.
Ling,
Paeng confessed her love to me.
Why aren't you surprised?
I already know.
Women can see each other through.
But I don't love her.
The only one I love
is you.
Ling, can you be my girlfriend?
If you're my girlfriend,
my dad probably won't
force me to marry Paeng.
You're the only one who can help me.
Artit.
I...
I can't be with you.
I'm sorry.
I see.
You don't have to apologize.
You can't force
things like this to happen.
I think this is not the solution.
Let Paeng calm down
and talk to her again.
It's probably the best way.
What did Mr. Artit
do in his past life?
Why did he have to meet
a brazen girl like this?
That girl's worse than I thought.
She's evil beneath
that innocent facade.
I'm guessing
that she's been with so many guys.
Aren't you going a little too far?
Not at all, Thongkhum.
A girl this young who knows how to
kiss a guy must be promiscuous.
Hey!
What about people who gossip
behind people's back?
What do they call it? Is it nosy?
So what?
Are you going to argue that
your mistress didn't kiss Mr. Artit?
You can't, can you?
So what? What does her kissing Artit
have anything to do with you?
Why is it strange? They're engaged.
Oh, right!
Dream on.
Mr. Artit doesn't love her.
It's only your mistress
who's lusting after him
even though he doesn't want her.
What a shameless!
- What? Spit it out! Say it!
- Stop
I won't.
Whatever will be, will be.
I've endured this far too long.
Then don't.
Get out. I'm firing you.
Oh!
Did you hear what she said?
Who does she think she is?
Do you own this place?
You're just living here.
I'm not surprised
why your parents
are in such a hurry to die.
Look at their daughter.
Who can stand her?
Let's go. It stinks around here.
What stinks?
Rabid dogs.
Paeng!
Let her have it Paeng!
Give her your best shot.
Let me go!
My head!
You want to fight me?
- Do you?
- Come here.
MIss Paeng, don't.
I'll squash her myself.
- Stop!
- There you go!
You crazy girl!
How could you do that?
Come and get it if you don't want
to live to old age.
She's gone crazy!
Yes, I'm crazy
and I can be even crazier than this.
What's next?
Go ahead, Miss Paeng!
Stop! Stop right now!
Madam!
Please help me!
Here. I'll feed you.
- Oh!
- Aren't you a little too serious?
Some things are acceptable
and some aren't, Artit.
Go gather Paeng's things
and dump them outside.
Since you're throwing my stuff out,
I'm going to throw yours too.
Stop that!
If I do this, things will escalate.
So Paeng can finally get over you.
I'm not going to keep
enduring this anymore, Aueng.
Go wherever you want
and do whatever you please.
I'm not going to care
about you anymore!
We're engaged.
We're going to get married.
- Don't take Artit from me!
- Paeng, calm down!
Your mine. Don't ever cheat on me
and don't mess around with
other girls. I won't accept it.
You're really not making any sense!
It's like talking to a crazy person.