(My Forever Sunshine)
I'm happy to wait
until you're ready.
Artit! Artit!
You have no right to do this to her.
Who has the right then?
Paeng wants to reopen
her mom's murder case.
Aunt Pimnapa
didn't die in a car crash?
I want to take care
of your daughter,
but she never thinks of me.
Mark?
The prime suspect in the
murder of Pimnapa was her husband.
That's not true. I don't believe it.
If someone accused Uncle,
would you just accept it?
I told you to leave her alone.
I'm the one who asked him to come.
Are you only going to talk
about your own matters?
Are you done talking? So we can go.
I have to go now.
You stuck your nose
where it didn't belong.
Wha's up, Non?
Have you found Paeng?
I have.
Mark brought her to the condo.
Thanks for sending me the location.
Mark is so sleazy.
He took her there. What would've
happened if you weren't there?
You have to be careful and not let
Paeng go anywhere with him again.
Okay, I'll try.
You can't just try.
You have to let Paeng see
how worried you are.
Okay, okay.
Just "okay"?
When they left together,
You were desperate when you called
me. Your voice was so shaky too.
When are you going to
reconcile with her?
Non,
I can't say much
because you're on speaker, okay?
Oh, really?
I'm sorry. Why didn't you tell me?
Hello, Non.
Hello, Paeng.
You two can keep talking to each
other. I won't bother you anymore.
Artit,
don't you have anything
to talk to me about?
I don't.
No matter what I do,
I'm always wrong.
Artit,
I didn't want to argue with you.
I just
have to do what I have to.
Then can I ask you something?
Why did you go with him?
I can't answer you that.
Paeng,
I don't know if this is an excuse.
But the reason my dad tried to
stop you from opening this up
is because he's
very worried about you.
I know.
I know that Uncle is very worried.
I'm sorry for chastising him.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry
that I didn't know how much
you had been through.
I left you
to face this alone.
Paeng,
from now on, whatever
you want to do,
just tell me.
I will fully support you.
Really?
What if it is something you
don't agree with,
are you going to support me?
If it makes you happy,
I'll help you.
Why?
Because you're very important to me.
Can you tell me
what you want to do?
Last night, I couldn't sleep at all.
I kept thinking
about the conversation I had
with the officer all night.
He said
both the physical evidence
and eyewitnesses
indicate that my dad killed my mom.
So?
I want to meet one of the witnesses.
This is all the details that were
recorded that day.
Please have a look.
Is anyone home?
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
- Hello.
I'm here to see someone
named Sudjai.
Oh, that's me.
You used to work at a hotel
in Thong Lor, right?
What's the matter?
There was a murder case
and you were one of the witnesses.
Do you remember that?
Why are you asking me this?
It's all in the past.
I can't remember anything anymore.
I'm the daughter of the deceased.
And the person you testified
against was my dad.
I think that you
misunderstood something.
I didn't.
I already told the truth.
Please don't ask me anymore.
I can't remember anything.
Please help me.
Move! You're in the way!
Please go.
Ma'am, we come in peace.
- You can go now.
- Ma'am.
Just go.
Paeng.
Yes?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We should go.
Come on.
We're here.
You've been silent the whole trip.
What are you thinking about?
Artit,
when we're at the house.
I...
I saw...
You saw what?
I saw Mark.
He followed us?
Is he insane?
Artit,
how does he know where we are
and what we're doing?
He might be watching you.
And
is he going to follow us everywhere?
Are you scared?
Who is it?
It's me.
I thought you returned to the hotel.
Why did you come back here?
Do you want me to keep you company?
I can sleep on the sofa.
Stop thinking about it.
You have to get some rest.
Do you want to take a shower?
You can shower first.
Go.
Do you have any sugar left?
It's so strange. We bumped into each
other two days in a row now.
From that mountain
to this one.
That's true.
There's a guy at the rose garden.
He's handsome.
Mark, why are you here?
I followed you from the festival.
Mark?
Mark, I'm here to meet a client.
Your client
is me.
It looks like a tattoo.
I've seen it on someone.
Please help me.
Move! You're in the way!
Artit!
Paeng, what's wrong?
Paeng?
Paeng,
what are you afraid of? Tell me.
Let me know
what you're afraid of.
I think
there's someone else involved
in my mom's case.
Who?
How are they involved?
I might be misunderstanding things.
I don't want to accuse anyone.
If that's what you believe, then we
have to find a way to prove it.
That's right. I have to.
Then tell me.
We’re going
to figure this out together.
I told you
I will fully support you.
Let me be a little certain first.
How are you going to do that?
Paeng.
Paeng, I'm sorry.
You must be so stressed.
I think
you should get some sleep.
Paeng,
I know this is a big deal.
But not sleeping and
thinking without any leads,
you're going to get sick
before you find out the truth.
Artit,
if we're scared of something,
we have to confront it, don't we?
That's right.
But that thing can't pose
any harm to you.
Go to sleep.
We can figure out what to do
next tomorrow.
That's enough.
You can stop thinking now.
Artit.
Hmm?
Can you hold my hand
while we sleep tonight?
Of course.
I'll hold your hand
for the whole night. I won't let go.
You can sleep now.
I promise
that I won't let go until morning.
You can go ahead and sleep.
I want to watch you sleep.
If I shouldn't blame her,
then who should I blame?
She's the reason
why Artit almost died twice.
I won't let you get into
trouble anymore.
I promise.
Artit,
if we're scared of something,
we have to confront it, don't we?
I think
there's someone else involved
in my mom's case.
If that's what you believe,
then we have to find a way
to prove it.
That's right. I have to.
I saw...
You saw what?
I saw Mark.
He followed you?
Mark!
What's up, Paeng?
Are you at your condo?
I'm about to go over.
I'd like to talk to you.
What time will you be there?
I'm on the way.
I'm out right now.
But I can come back to see you.
Am I bothering you?
I'm sorry for not telling you first.
I have something on my mind.
So I'm in a rush.
You're not bothering me.
I always have time for you.
How long will you be
before you're back at the condo?
About an hour.
I'll see you then.
If I arrived first, can I wait
for you in your room?
Well, I didn't tell Artit
that I was coming.
So I don't want to wait
at the lobby.
If he follows me here,
we won't get to talk
to each other again.
But if it's inconvenient for you,
- I'll...
- Of course, you can.
I'll let the front desk know.
Once you've arrived,
you can wait upstairs.
Thank you.
Okay.
Okay. Certainly.
Hello.
- Hello.
- I have a meeting with Mark.
I'd like to wait in his room.
I'm Wanfahmai. Paeng.
Oh, Wanfahmai.
Mark just called.
I'll get the lift for you.
It's on the fourth floor, Room 444.
Please.
Don't do anything crazy, Paeng!
(Paeng)
Why is he here so soon?
- What's the matter?
- Room service.
I didn't order any.
It's Mark's order.
Pick up, Paeng!
(Artit)
Oh, hold on.
Yes?
I forgot the covers.
- Here you are.
- Thank you very much.
It really is you.
Why don't you ask me nicely
what you want to know?
I know that you're still in here.
Just come out. Please?
Do you want to play
hide-and-seek with me?
- Artit!
- Paeng!
Please help me!
Where are you?
I'm in Mark's room.
I'm here to find evidence
but I couldn't get out in time.
Please come and help me. I'm scared.
Why did you go there alone?
I don't know.
Paeng, it's Mark's condo, right?
Send me the floor and room number.
I'll call the police.
Okay.
Why didn't you tell me that you
like playing hide-and-seek?
Don't you have something
to talk to me about?
I think we should talk outside.
It's uncomfortable in here.
Come on.
Come on, Paeng.
Let's go.
Walk carefully. Don't rush.
Okay. Stop there.
Do you want it back?
You have to talk to me first.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I thought you said
you wanted to talk to me.
Then I'll start.
Do you know
that I've waited
for the day to have you here
with me for a very long time?
Why?
Because you're important to me.
I've never waited
for anything before,
and definitely never this long.
But you're special.
Come on. Have a seat.
Calm down.
Here.
Would you like something to drink?
No.
Why do you seem so stressed?
I ordered room service
because I was hoping
that we could relax, eat, and chat.
They're all of your favorites.
I'm not hungry.
It's good.
Don't worry about the food.
Ask me what you want to know.
That tattoo.
You know about it now?
What did you put in there?
Calm down.
Do you know that
you're too stressed?
You'll feel better if you take
something for your nerves.
Drink it. You'll feel relaxed.
I won't.
But I want you to.
I'm not going to drink it.
Why are you so stubborn?
You're just as stubborn as your mom.
Your eyes are like hers.
They remind me of her.
It's okay if you don't drink it.
I'll drink it myself.
Let's exchange glasses.
Why did you kill my mom?
What are you talking about?
Me? Killed your mom?
If wasn't you, then who did it?
You're assuming things.
I didn't do it.
I remember that tattoo.
Why did you kill her?
You used to
mess around with my mom.
I'm not going to deny that.
Because your mom
was very charming.
And I really loved her.
But now,
I've given all the love I have
to you.
It must be destiny
that brought us together.
From now on,
I promise
that I'll take care of you.
Don't touch me.
Why not?
Didn't you have feelings for me?
I've done everything for you.
What else do you want?
Why are you talking to me like that?
Tell me the truth.
Why did you kill my mother?
You want me to say it?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Hmm?
You're going to make me talk
and then hand over the recording
to the police.
Do you really want to know?
That's right.
I'm the one who killed your mom.
I killed Pimnapa.
But I didn't plan to.
But do you know why?
Because she broke up with me.
She told me
she felt guilty about
her husband and daughter.
But she never felt any guilt
towards me.
Even though I was faithful
and was so nice to her.
But she didn't love me
like I loved her.
She didn't want me
like I wanted her.
She was going to leave me,
so I...
Enough!
Why?
You wanted to know how I killed her,
so I'm explaining it in detail so
that you'll be able to imagine it.
You killed her
just because she was leaving you.
Just because she was leaving?
Do you know
how it feels to be abandoned?
It hurts more than death.
I've been abandoned too many times.
It will never happen again.
It won't happen to me ever again.
You have to tell me.
Tell me and make me feel happy.
Tell me that
you won't leave me.
Say. Say it.
Why does it have to be me?
Because
you're Pimnapa's daughter.
You're her daughter.
You live a similar life.
You're an orphan like me.
So I'm the one
who understands you the most.
I want to take care of you
and protect you.
Okay?
I don't need a psycho
like you taking care of me.
Don't come any closer.
What can you do
with a knife that small?
You wanted me to tell you so
I did. What else do you want?
Psycho!
If you come any closer, it won't
just graze you this time.
You're so stubborn.
You and your mom
are so hard to understand.
Come here.
I didn't even want to hurt you.
But you forced me to.
Huh?
Let me go!
A card?
Miss, can I have
the keycard to the lift?
Who are you here to see?
I need to get upstairs
to Mark's room.
I have to call him first.
Just a moment, please.
That's okay.
- Just give me the keycard.
- I can't do that.
I need the owner's permission.
It's protocol.
Don't come any closer!
Don't be afraid, Paeng.
I'll try my best to be gentle.
He's about to kill my girlfriend!
What are you going to do?
The police are coming.
If you don't let me go upstairs,
you'll be arrested for conspiring.
- This way.
- Room 444.
Ouch!
Paeng!
Mister, I'll get it.
Paeng! Don't!
Paeng! Stop!
Let me go! I'm going to kill him!
He killed my mom!
Paeng!
Calm down!
You're always butting in!
What on earth is wrong with you?
Don't!
Paeng, run.
I said run!
No.
- Don't do this.
- It's you who shouldn't do this.
I've been so nice to you.
But in the end, you chose him.
You're as vile as your mom.
You have no right to
insult my mother.
It's you who's vile.
Do you want to die
with that mouth of yours?
Stop! Drop the gun!
Go!
Restrain him!
- Get off!
- Stay still!
Let go!
Stay still!
He lured her over to rape her.
This is my room.
I didn't lure anyone to do anything.
It's him
who barged in here and hurt me.
You're lying. He's here to save me.
All of you will need to go to
the station to give a statement.
So annoying.
- Go!
- Busybodies.
Please.
Wait.
I have to get my stuff.
I'd like to charge him with false
imprisonment and attempted rape.
Hey,
don't accuse me
if you don't have any evidence.
If you're going to charge me,
I'm going to charge you back.
Officer,
breaking and entering.
Look, she hurt me.
And she brought this guy
to beat me up too.
It was only self-defense.
You're such a scumbag.
I can sue you
in front of the officer.
Please calm down.
I'd like to know right from
the beginning. Who'd like to start?
I'm going to wait for my lawyer.
I'll start.
Please.
Artit! Artit! Artit!
Artit! I'm sorry!
Why did you do that?
Do you know how much
I'm worried about you?
I told you that I'm going
fully support you.
Why did you risk yourself?
I...
I didn't want to get you
into trouble.
And have you ever thought
how I would feel if something
happened to you?
How would I feel?
I'm sorry, Artit.
I won't do anything like this again.
Paeng,
Why would you do that?
Why did you go and see him?
I wanted to look for evidence.
What evidence?
Evidence that he murdered my mom.
Is that true?
Mark?
You got in a fight already? You've
only been gone a short time.
Who would want to be in a fight?
If I didn't call you,
I wouldn't have known
what you've been through?
Next time, call us.
So we'll know where you're
being beaten to death.
Right.
Paeng, don't listen to him.
Oh, I wasn't blaming you, Paeng.
It's just friendly banter.
Have you eaten anything?
I have.
Mark is so evil.
He's been arrested, right?
He made bail.
Can't we charge him at all?
We have to go to court.
He's very cunning.
It won't be easy to go after him.
This is what Paeng and I
are concerned about.
Artit, I'm not sick.
You look depressed.
I'm afraid you might get sick.
I'm just exhausted.
After what you've been through,
I'd be scared
if you still had energy.
You're still in the mood to joke.
Nothing good is going to come out
of being stressed.
You always get hurt because of me.
This is nothing.
Don't worry about me.
Let's sleep here tonight.
Why aren't you bringing me home?
It's late. You can go tomorrow.
I know that you're still in shock.
Thank you very much.
If you hadn't saved me in time,
I might have ended up becoming
a murderer.
Or if I couldn't fight him,
I would have...
I don't want to be so weak.
You don't have to be
tough all the time.
Be vulnerable sometimes
so that I can take care of you.
It's time to sleep now.
I know that you won't
be able to sleep.
I don't want you to think too much.
I'll watch over you.
I'll let you be paranoid about me
rather than being scared
of something else, okay?
I won't be paranoid of you.
I know you're a gentleman.
And I'll feel safe and warm
to be close to you.
You can't trust me.
Because
I can't even trust myself.
I'm kidding.
It makes me happy to see you smile.
Go to sleep.
I'll be right here
to watch over you.
Are you up now?
Someone woke me up.
Did you sleep well?
I did.
I've made you some food.
Let's go see my dad
after we've eaten.
Okay.
Dad must be waiting
for you on the balcony.
Paeng,
what's wrong?
I'm afraid
Auntie will get angry at me.
That's good. So I can talk it over
with her while you're here.
Don't.
I'm begging you. Not right now.
Paeng, what are you afraid of?
We've been through a lot.
It's only Mom.
We have to get through it as well.
Mr. Artit is right.
Thongkhum!
- Hello.
- Have you recovered?
I'm fine now.
I really have to thank you
for not standing around
and letting me die.
Who'd do that?
How could I let
anything happen to you?
You're too kind.
Even though I was so mean to you.
I really
have to apologize to you.
Please forgive me.
Thongkhum, don't do this again
Because you're much older than me.
I don't know how to pay you back.
So I'd like to show you
how grateful I am to you.
Whatever you need me to do,
you can tell me right away.
I'd like to repay you
for what you did.
Then I'd like some of
your delicious food. That's all.
Roger that!
I'll get to that right away.
And you can eat with Mr. Artit.
I'll go to the market now.
Duang, come on.
Let's go to the market.
See?
Even Thongkhum loves you.
Soon, my Mom will love you too.
You found the murderer?
That's right, Uncle.
I wasn't expecting that he'd
be someone close to me.
What is this?
Did I misunderstand
everything all along?
At the time,
I believed all the evidence
to the point that I accepted
Tharathep was the culprit.
Why?
Why didn't I trust my friend?
Even though I knew
how decent of a person he was.
I'm so sorry for not believing him.
I understand.
Anyone would've misunderstood.
What if
you didn't try
to find out the truth?
It would never have been revealed.
I told Artit to try and stop you
from looking into this.
She understands
that you meant well, Dad.
That's right, Uncle.
Please don't overthink it.
I understand everything
you've done for me.
Why did I let my best friend
become the prime suspect?
Uncle, don't blame yourself.
I actually have to thank you.
Even though you believed that
you still loved me
and showed me mercy.
You've always wanted
the best for me.
That means that deep down,
you knew my dad's a good person.
That's right.
I've always known it.
Your dad was a very good man.
And I owe a lot to him.
Uncle, don't speak
of the past anymore.
Okay.
And what are we going to do next?
We have to go through
the legal process.
We have to sue him for what
happened first.
And for Aunt Pimnapa's case,
evidence needs to be
collected first.
I want to apologize to your dad.
I should find some time
to go to the temple
and make merit for your parents.
You can come with me.
I intend to make merit for them too.
Hold on.
How can it be just the two of you?
Can I come along?
Very well.
Shall we go tomorrow?
Good idea.
Am I even visible?
No one here seems to see me.
You all probably think
that I'm invisible.
Tubtim!
It's okay.
I'll go and explain it to her.
Tubtim.
Can you see me?
There are so many things
that I haven't told you about Paeng.
If I tell you everything
and you still hate her,
I won't complain anymore.
Back then,
Tharathep and Pimnapa
didn't die in a car accident.
What?
I found Paeng
when she was in shock.
She had just found her dad's body.
He had just killed himself.
Oh.
And what's worse,
the police called me to say that
they had found Pimanapa's body.
She was murdered
around the same time.
She was so traumatized
about her parents
that she ended up in the hospital.
When I was taking care
of her at the hospital,
her mental condition
deteriorated so much.
She had to remain
under the doctor's supervision.
Before she was able
to overcome the ordeal,
it was a very difficult time for her
It's my fault
for bringing her here
without telling you and Artit
about the problems
that she was going through.
That's why she became
a troubled
and disobedient girl.
Because she thought
no one understood her.
Oh, dear.
A girl lost both her parents
at the same time.
And then she found out
that her mother was murdered.
It must have been such a shock.
And I was mean to her.
It's not your fault
that you didn't know.
I didn't tell you the truth either.
I thought it her problem
to go through.
But I was wrong.
When we don't know
about a child's problem,
we might misunderstand them
and think that they're a bad person.
Instead of looking after
her carefully,
we rubbed salt on her wounds.
We perceived her
as a disobedient girl.
So instead of getting better,
everything became worse.
Help! Anyone!
- Let me go!
- Paeng!
I'm not going!
Mom!
You want this?
Stop! Stop right now!
Who taught you to be so rude?
There probably wasn't anyone.
Because her parents are
dead already!
- Oh, my!
- You want another?
I didn't know that
she has been through so much.
Otherwise, I would've
understood her more.
Then,
please don't stay angry
with her for what's happened.
Come on. Do you think I'm that mean?
I know that my wife
has a kind heart.
Tomorrow,
I'm bringing Paeng to make merit
for Tharathep and Pimnapa.
Would you like to come?
Back then, Tharathep and Pimnapa
didn't die in a car accident.
And what's worse,
the police called me to say that
they had found Pimanapa's body.
She was murdered
around the same time.
I now know
that she has someone she likes
and he's not Artit.
Who does she like?
It's Artit's friend.
Non?
But she came with a guy. Who is he?
I met him in the North.
She must've invited him.
I want you to give her a chance.
I'll never forgive her.
Even though she's the woman I love?
I love Paeng, Mom.
(Mrs. Pimnapa Wararit)
Mom, Dad.
I've found the murderer
who killed Mom.
I'm going to make him pay
for the sins he committed.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me
for misunderstanding you.
Please don't worry.
I'll do my best
to take care of Paeng.
You can head inside.
I'll give Paeng a lift.
Artit,
I'd like to have a word with Paeng.
Then let Saeb give Paeng a lift.
Let's get back to work.
- Hmm?
- Okay.
Let's go.
It won't take long.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know
what you had been through.
Please don't be angry with me.
That's okay, Auntie.
I was never angry with you.
I really feel sorry for you
for having to go through
all of those things.
But you were very strong
and resilient
for being able to get through it.
It's very admirable of you.
I'm not strong at all.
That's why I acted up
like that when I was young.
It's me who should apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Um...
You've apologized to me many times.
This time
I forgive you.
Let's leave everything
between us in the past.
But
I'm still worried
about you and Artit.
I know that Artit loves you.
He told me.
But I'm still worried.
I think
that you pose a danger to him.
Whenever he's in trouble,
the reason is always you.
I'm scared. I'm very scared.
I still can't change my thoughts
and feelings about this.
Please don't say
that I'm superstitious.
But I'm very scared.
Do you understand me?
I do.
Uh...
I don't object
to accepting you as my niece
or a close relative.
But as for a daughter-in-law...
I understand, Auntie.
Then,
can you promise me
that there's not going to be
anything between you and Artit,
other than being siblings?
I know you well.
If you give your word,
you always keep it.
Well,
if it makes you happy,
then I promise.
Thank you very much
for understanding me.
But I'm asking you
to keep this between us.
Don't let Artit know.
Okay, Auntie.
can you promise me
that there's not going to be
anything between you and Artit,
other than being siblings?
Are Non and Ling really
getting married?
Why are you making that face?
Don't you believe me?
No, it's unbelievable.
Are you really going
to marry my brother?
You're not helping and
you're trying to be a killjoy too?
I'm joking.
Ling, you're so lucky
to have found a nice guy like him.
It's a happy ending.
I'm very happy that
my daughter-in-law will be you.
Unlike the previous women
in his life.
Oh, Mom.
What were the other women like?
His type
is fair, plump, and curvy.
Dad,
you've ruined my reputation.
Ling,
you know I've never laid eyes
on anyone but you.
I can vouch for that.
I'm sorry. I was only joking.
Have you found an auspicious date?
I was going to ask you for help.
Of course. I'll handle it.
Let's do it soon.
Hopefully, it will be this year.
Why does it have to be this year?
So that I might get a grandkid
next year.
Do you really have
what it takes, Non?
What's wrong with him?
Are you going
to celebrate joy or grief?
You're getting married but you look
like you're drinking the pain away.
That's right. You look like
someone who's about to die.
Don't say that you're afraid of
getting married all of a sudden.
I'm not afraid of getting married.
I'm afraid of not being
able to do so.
Huh? How come?
You proposed to her.
Everything's ready to go.
My mom told me to cancel.
- Huh?
- What happened?
- Right. What happened?
When did this happen?
This afternoon, I took Ling
to meet my parents.
And? What's next?
Just tell us.
I think we should get on
with the wedding.
So that we'll get to see
our grandkids soon.
What's wrong, Ling?
Why are you so pale?
Well...
I have something
important to tell you.
I can't have children.
I'm really sorry for not
telling you this initially,
and for disappointing everyone.
Why are you apologizing?
It's okay if you
can't have children.
But it's not okay for me.
I'm sorry for being frank.
I only have one son.
I hope that he will bear children
to continue our bloodline.
But if it's like this,
I'm...
I understand.
It's my fault.
Ling.
I understand everything.
You don't have to be worried.
Thank you for
understanding us so easily.
Ling.
I'm sorry
for not telling you about this.
I was being selfish.
I was afraid that if you knew,
I would lose you.
Ling,
we've been through a lot together
and you still don't know me?
The only thing I want
is to marry you
and build a family with you.
I don't want any children.
If it means that I have to lose you,
I'd rather not have any.
Thank you for loving me so much.
But marriage
isn't up to two people.
It also depends on your family.
If your family doesn't accept me,
then we can't love
each other anymore.
Of course we can.
I'll talk to my mom.
I'm only asking you for one thing.
I want you to believe in me
so that we'll be able to
get married.
Please wait for me.
Did you bring a guard dog today?
You're the one who's the dog.
Because you like to bite people
behind their backs.
I have evidence.
I'd like to play an audio recording
which serves as physical evidence
in this case.
You organized a meeting
with the defendant
and you used this knife
to hurt him, is that correct?
That's right.
I deny the accusations.
You won't get away with this, Mark.
You're as vile as your mother.
Once I've finished up my work,
I'd like to get out of here.
Don't go, Paeng.
No matter what reasons you have.
I've made my decision.
Hold me tight.
Don't prank me, okay?
I don't know
what to do to make you stay either.