(My Forever Sunshine)
Here. I'll feed you.
- Aren't you a little too serious?
- Somethings you just can't let go.
Oh! Blood!
You've got such beautiful hair.
It would be a shame.
Gather her things
and dump them outside.
You're throwing out my stuff
so I'm throwing out yours too.
Stop that!
There could be trouble
if you do this.
So that Paeng can
finally get over him.
I'm not going to put up with this
any longer, Aueng.
Go wherever. Do whatever.
I don't care anymore!
We're engaged.
We're going to get married.
Don't mess around with Artit!
Are you really
going to get rid of her?
If it's possible
then I want to do it.
Are you thinking
of getting rid of me?
Excellent. How did you know
that I wanted to eat this?
You're so chatty with women.
But when it's me,
all you say is "Mm!" or "Urgh!"
Mm!
Saeb,
don't take so much.
Or we might not have any left
for people behind you.
Really.
Are you going to be
able to eat all that?
Of course I am.
I'm starving!
Saeb, Master wants to see you.
Right now.
Go on.
This is mine. Nobody touch it!
Jerk! Look at him.
Who's going to eat your food?
Once your all full,
let's get back to work.
Ouch, Ouch!
My stomach hurts!
- Oh?
- Ouch!
What's wrong?
- Huh?
I can't hold it in anymore!
What's going on?
- Hey, hey?
- You need to go to the bathroom?
Hey?
What?
What's going on?
Oh, over here too!
Ouch!
- You too, Pong?
- I won't make it to the toilet.
I need to sit down.
What did the doctor say?
Food poisoning.
Luckily, most people are alright.
But some will need to get an IV.
How could this have happened?
You don't have to think hard.
It's because the food that Thongkhum
and Duang made was unhygienic.
It's not true, Madam.
Duang,
did you wash the vegetables
properly?
Of course. I washed them
as I always do.
See?
If it was clean, would people
have gotten sick?
It's an adult matter. Go back to
wherever you came from.
I'm worried.
This time the workers have diarrhea,
but next time
it could be Tubtim.
- Oh?
- You've gone too far.
Thongkhum is always
careful when she cooks.
Don't make empty accusations.
That's right, Madam.
Who's making accusations?
The whole farm has diarrhea.
Does someone have to die first
before you'll admit to it?
Enough, Paeng.
I'll deal with this myself.
What will you do?
I think someone needs to be fired.
Go way.
It's none of your business.
Are they going to be fired?
I'm so satisfied. They deserve it.
I don't think so.
They've worked here for a long time.
Master wouldn't be so harsh.
But all the workers have diarrhea.
At least, their salaries
should be deducted.
But it's strange.
They've worked in the kitchen
for 10 years or so.
How could they've made a mistake?
That's true. The whole farm getting
diarrhea isn't a common thing.
And wouldn't those people know
if they've eaten something spoiled?
- Huh?
- That's true, Jaem.
If they've been poisoned
then that's a different story.
You're right.
What if?
I don't know.
But I feel so satisfied.
Really!
But that's true.
I won't let you fire them.
I don't believe they made a mistake.
Master! Master!
Excuse me,
I have something to tell you!
Don't cry.
Don't cry, Thongkhum.
Sir wouldn't fire you. Believe me.
Why wouldn't he?
The workers ate our food
and they've all been hospitalized.
I don't know.
But Master is a fair person.
There must be a way out.
Stop crying or I'll cry too. Please?
Oh?
Where is the evidence, Saeb?
Over there.
- Lead us.
- What evidence?
What evidence?
It's a laxative.
How did it get here?
Don't ask. Give it to me.
I know who did it.
You're here, you little brat.
You said if anyone causes trouble,
then they have to
leave the farm, right?
Here.
It's you who has to leave.
What are you talking about, Auntie?
Don't act all innocent.
Saeb, say it. Tell us what you saw.
Well...
- Well...
- Say it.
I saw Paeng doing
something in the kitchen.
You saw me going into the kitchen
but it doesn't mean that I did it.
See? Are you admitting
that you went in there?
Paeng,
what did you do in the kitchen?
I...
Just tell us what you did in there.
You're upset with Thongkhum and me.
Is that why you tried to frame us?
You're getting more and more
our of control each day.
I won't accept it this time.
I can't stand her behavior anymore.
What if someone actually died?
What are you going to do?
I think we should just
hand her over to the police.
They won't die.
It's just a laxative.
Oh? Are you admitting to it?
Saeb, take her to the police.
- Yes, Madam.
- Calm down.
Paeng,
please be honest with me.
Did you really do it?
- Paeng!
What should I do? What should I do?
Artit, please help me.
You've reached the voicemail of...
Why are you so worried about her?
She'll come back.
It's already dark.
She's a little girl,
and it's raining.
Instead of worrying
about her wellbeing,
you should worry about what
she's going to do to other people.
Have some mercy on her.
If you can forgive her,
then please do.
Her story is more
than a child can take.
She's not the only
orphan in the world.
And other orphans aren't like her.
You don't know what I do.
Well...
Anyway, I'm begging you.
When pigs fly.
Master! Master!
- Master!
- What's the matter?
I've found Paeng!
- Oh?
- Uhh...
Please look after her, Aueng.
If there's anything, just call me.
Yes, Sir.
Paeng,
let's go take a shower and change.
Miss Paeng, would you
like some warm congee?
I'll make some for you.
- Oh?
Jaem!
Miss Paeng,
please get up and change first.
You might get sick.
Miss Paeng.
- Miss Paeng.
- Please get change.
It's okay.
Miss Paeng, please get up and
get change. You might get sick.
Miss Paeng!
- Oh, Miss Paeng!
- What should we do, Aueng?
What can we do?
Miss Paeng,
are you up?
Miss Paeng.
She's burning up!
Can you get up?
Let's go to the doctor.
I'm not going!
Then I'll find you some medication.
I'm not taking any.
Just let me die.
Miss Paeng!
Please help.
She won't listen to me.
Okay. I'll go check on her.
Don't go.
She might get cocky.
Tubtim,
she's sick.
Believe me.
She's only crying for attention.
If we give in, when is
she going to learn?
She'll cause more trouble.
So you're not going to let
me check up on her?
- No!
- Okay.
Oh? Krongprateep!
Krongprateep!
You're not listening to me!
Why did you ask me then?
You too.
Why did you come back?
She'll keep crying for attention.
I don't want Dad to be upset.
I heard Paeng's very sick.
She did this to herself.
Dad wants to take her to the doctor
but she won't go.
Look at how high-maintenance she is.
You're still complaining?
Thanks so much
for helping me, Artit.
Do you really want Artit to
bring Paeng to the doctor?
It's okay, Mom. I know a way.
Paeng,
Artit's back.
Go and see the doctor with him.
Artit?
Thanks so much
for coming with me, Nang.
My pleasure.
I told you I'm always happy to help.
I can do more than this too.
And what should we do next?
Where is Artit? Why isn't he here?
You can't do this.
I want to go home!
I don't want to be here!
You can't do this.
What now?
I want to go home.
How can you go home?
You've still got a fever.
Didn't you want to get sick?
Just stay at the hospital
and let the doctors treat you.
I don't want to be alone.
I'm scared.
You have to stay with me.
You're capable of feeling scared?
You always act so tough.
Stop being so silly.
I'm not being silly.
You have to stay here.
Because I don't want you
to die at the farm.
You've caused everyone
enough trouble already.
- Come on, Nang. Let's go.
- Okay.
Rest up. Hopefully, they can cure
your craziness.
I'm sorry that Artit prefers me
to you.
Just in time!
You dragged me all the way from
Bangkok just to listen to your rant?
That's right.
Why? Are you my friend?
Oh, Nang!
- Come back and sit here!
- No!
Enough, Artit.
You have to drive home.
Just one day.
I'm stressed.
I can't take it anymore.
Alcohol's not the solution.
Understand?
That's enough.
Non, why are you stopping him?
If he can't drive,
then you drive him home.
Why do you keep siding with him?
Are you my sister or not?
Hey.
Actually, I feel bad for Paeng.
- Huh?
- Why would you feel bad for her?
The person who you should
feel bad for is Artit.
Are you really his friend?
Why did you side with her?
You're only defending him.
Enough! Artit,
you and Paeng don't
have to get married yet.
Something might change.
I have to take your temperature.
Excuse me, another bottle.
No, that's enough.
Enough, Artit.
- Hey, I...
- That's enough.
You've had a lot already.
Right? And you were enabling him.
Excuse me, another bottle!
I said enough.
I'll drive you home
No, I can drive.
Can I have the bill, please?
- Hey, hold on.
- Hold on. I'll have another bot...
Help me! Help!
Grab him.
Watch your step.
Let's go.
I'll drop you off. Walk carefully.
Hold on. Have you paid yet?
- I'll deal with it.
- Can I bring another bottle home?
No, you can have more at my house.
I can't get a hold of Artit.
Paeng's also disappeared
from the hospital.
That's good. She can
disappear all she wants.
So our son can
finally live in peace.
Or he'll have to keep
cleaning up after her.
She's such a brat. She keeps
bringing us trouble.
Well, what should we do?
I'll go and look for them.
Why would you?
Are you going to find them yourself?
It's already late.
It's because it's already late
that I have to go.
I think those two might be together.
I don't want anything to happen.
I'll come with you.
It's okay, Aueng. Let the men do it.
Saeb, tell the workers to take
the cars out and find them.
Yes, sir.
I'm coming with you.
I'm worried about Artit.
- Then let's go.
- Okay.
Jaem, we should go
and look for them too.
Let's go. Hurry.
You always say you're okay
even when you're not.
I'll take off my shoes first.
Aren't you going to?
Steady, Artit.
Here. Stand up properly.
Here are your keys.
I think I should carry
you to your room.
It's okay.
- I can walk.
- Are you sure?
Yes. Later.
Watch your step.
Nang, Nang, come here.
Come here!
Get over here!
- Non!
- Where are you going?
To help Artit!
You saw him.
Will he be able to walk?
He's at home now.
Are you going to see
him off in his bedroom?
Can you step back a little?
It's getting a little too obvious.
Come here.
- Artit, Walk carefully!
- Sure!
- I'm going!
- Really!
Artit?
Why are you so drunk?
Paeng?
How did you get in here?
Why did you drink?
It's not good being drunk like this.
Go back to your room.
I'm worried about you.
Did you pretend to be sick?
I wasn't pretending.
I don't believe you.
Get out now.
Do you really hate me this much?
Why? We used to be friends.
What did I do wrong...
Get away from me!
I'm not going. I love you!
Paeng!
Paeng! Get off me!
Here they come.
Have you found Miss Paeng yet?
Let me go!
Let go! Let go!
Decent women wouldn't
do something like this.
I love you!
But I hate you!
Have it your way.
Paeng!
Paeng! Get off!
Paeng! Hey!
Paeng!
Let me go!
You can't do this!
I have nothing to lose!
My parents are dead!
I don't need to care
about anyone anymore.
Paeng! Paeng! Stop!
Let me go!
Paeng! Paeng!
You're not going to let go?
Alright.
You deserved it.
Why do you have to
hate me this much?
What did I do wrong?
It's you. You're wrong.
Remember, Wanfahmai.
Even if you were the only person
left on earth,
I'd never take you as my wife!
I'd also like to know
if you'll be able to do that.
Paeng! Paeng!
These are Artit's shoes.
He's back.
Let me go!
What's that?
Paeng, let me go!
Paeng!
Okay, okay.
You really want me?
That's right.
Okay.
I surrender.
Artit! Artit!
Do you want to die?
That's why you're doing this?
Alright! Fight me!
I'd like to know how strong you are!
- Let me go!
- Fight!
Fight!
- Let me go!
- Alright, fight!
I want to see you fight!
You want to get hurt?
- Alright. I'll...
- Artit!
What are you doing to her?
Uncle, help me!
Mom, Dad.
I wasn't doing anything to her.
If you weren't,
then what were you doing?
Answer them.
Tell them what happened.
Get over here!
Have you been drinking?
Just a little.
But I'm aware of everything.
I didn't do anything to her.
It's not true. You're lying.
He tried to rape me.
What?
I never taught you
to take advantage of women.
I insist
that I didn't do anything.
You were caught in the act.
Do you still dare to deny it?
Are you saying she ripped her
own shirt and jumped onto the bed?
That's right.
Tubtim, you weren't there.
But I trust my son.
I raised him myself.
He knows right from wrong.
He wouldn't do something like this,
especially to this girl.
Dad, I always admit it
when I'm wrong.
I didn't do it. I won't admit to it.
I wasn't lying.
I saw that he was very drunk
so I went to check up on him.
But he...
I couldn't fight him off.
Liar!
Artit!
If you're not going
to speak the truth,
I'm going to kill you right now!
Why would she lie?
What women
would want something
like this to happen?
This woman, Dad!
She can do anything!
You still don't see her true colors?
I'd like to affirm it once more.
I didn't do anything to her.
Dad,
don't you trust me?
I trust what I saw.
But it's not what you thought.
Both of you are going
to get married anyway.
Therefore, you're going to
get married next month.
Dad,
I won't marry her.
Krongprateep, be fair to him.
You're hurting him.
But we need to do right by her too.
My decision
is final.
I won't marry her.
I won't marry her
even if I have to die!
Artit!
- Artit!
- Artit, where are you going?
- Watch your step.
Where are you going?
It's all because of you.
That's why he ran away.
I tried my best.
You need to understand me sometimes.
Call me tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep.
Kot, hold on.
I said call me tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm coming to see you.
Artit,
aren't you at the farm?
That's right.
I'm driving to your house.
Hold on.
How important is this?
It's very far to drive
from there to Bangkok.
Why do you sound like that?
Are you drunk?
Who are you coming with? Non?
No one. Just wait for me.
Later.
Artit!
Artit, can you hear me?
What's going on, Artit!?
Artit!
Answer me!
Confess right now
that you went into my son's room
and tried to seduce him.
Tubtim, everything is obvious.
What's obvious?
You said I wasn't there,
but what about you?
Don't push me past my limit.
If you're going to force him
to marry this girl,
then let's divorce.
Tubtim, we've talked about
this so many times.
How isn't she suitable for him?
She's from a good background.
Or is it you don't like the fact
that she doesn't have any parents?
I'm not one to judge
a book by its cover.
I've never cared about a family's
background or wealth.
I don't even care that
she's inherited billions of baht.
But what I can't accept
is her personality.
I don't want to see my son
living in hell.
Why are you judging me?
How am I judging you?
You can't do housework.
Your grades are bad.
You're not even
responsible for yourself.
You're rude.
You cause trouble every single day.
I can't even stand being
under the same roof.
Do you think you're the only one
who can't stand it?
I have to endure you too.
You can hate me as much as you want.
But you can't break your promise
to my dad!
- Miss Paeng, calm down.
- Paeng!
Don't forget
that everyone here owes him.
That's right. He's already dead.
So you think that you can
do whatever you want to me!
It's not like that, Paeng.
This is getting out of control.
Why isn't it like that?
If you break your promise,
then you're a vile person too.
- Paeng!
- Please don't, Miss Paeng!
Paeng, you can't talk like that.
Apologize to her.
Look at her.
Do we want someone like her
as a daughter-in-law?
Paeng,
apologize to her.
And go back to your room.
Master! Madam!
Mr. Artit's friend called.
What is it?
Mr. Artit was in a car accident.
Huh?
Artit!
Watch your step.
If anything happens to him,
it's because of you!
Let's go now.
Are you satisfied now?
You're such a little devil!
Miss Paeng.
Jaem, I didn't mean
for this to happen.
I didn't really mean it.
How is Artit doing?
He's still not out of the woods.
There are no
external injuries.
But internally, a lot of his
bones are broken.
A rib bone punctured his lung.
He has a concussion.
The doctor said we have to wait for
him to wake up and then we'll know.
If he wakes up, that is.
I'm sorry.
I'm wrong. It's my fault.
How can it be your fault?
When he's the one who drove away.
If he admitted to
his guilt that night,
it wouldn't have happened.
No, it's not his fault.
He didn't do anything to me.
I lied.
Thank you.
Thank you for admitting your fault.
Actually,
I believe that he'd never
do something like that.
I know my son well.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
We're all at fault here.
I am too.
Uncle,
can I go and see Artit?
I'm in the wrong. I'd like
to watch over him.
Please let me see him.
You shouldn't.
If you really want to help,
please stay away
from him for a while.
Do you understand why?
The doctor said
overall he's responding
well to the treatment.
But he's still unconscious.
He has to stay in the hospital
for a while.
If the doctor said he'll get better,
then that's good already.
Soon enough, he'll be better.
Please don't be worry.
Once he wakes up,
I'll make him some dessert.
Okay.
Artit,
wake up already.
You're so strong.
If you don't wake up,
I'm going to curse you.
Kot,
be considerate of his mother.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I already notified the university
that he's been in an accident
and won't be able to attend classes.
If it's really necessary,
we'll help with
the paperwork for the deferral.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, everyone.
You're in trouble because of him.
It's because of that girl.
That's why he ended up like this.
Please don't think too much.
And what about
Artit's Father?
He just went home.
He went to see Paeng.
Why is he so worried about her?
He's more worried about her
than his own son.
When are you going to leave?
Do you want me to prostrate
myself to you?
Look at her.
She still has no remorse.
Come on, Duang. Just let her be.
Uncle!
How is Artit doing?
Paeng,
I'd like to talk to you
about something.
Go and live in Bangkok.
I'll handle
the school transfer for you.
Go and study there.
I'm worried about Artit.
There's no need to worry
about anything here.
I'll do my best to
take care of everything.
And I'll take care of you
just as I promised your dad.
I will never leave you.
Please trust me.
You understand me, don't you?
I do.
Live there for a while.
And wait for things to get better.
Once Artit has recovered,
you can come back.
I promise
I'll visit you often.
I don't want anything else
apart from Artit being safe.
I just want him to be safe.
I just want him to be safe!
Artit?
Nurse! Nurse!
- My son's awake.
- Let me check the monitor.
Mister, do you know where you are?
Can you speak?
Mister?
Are you alright?
Get out of here and never come back.
- Thongkhum.
- What?
I'm thinking of telling Madam
to host a huge merit-making ceremony
to get rid of the misfortunes here.
So that she can remove
all the unlucky things
and wash away all the filth.
Good.
Do it for three days and nights.
Let's go.
Uncle is waiting in the car.
Please take care of Artit, Saeb.
We don't do favors.
Why would you nod?
That hurts.
Miss Paeng.
Don't worry about us.
I'm going home.
And Aueng will find
work at home as well.
If you miss us,
feel lonely or
have no one to talk to,
you can call us anytime.
Okay.
I'll miss you both.
Paeng,
we have to go now. Or it'll be late.
I'm going now.
Okay.
Miss Paeng.
Live a better life, Miss Paeng.
Look after yourself.
We will never forget you!
Miss Paeng!
(Football field)
- Hey, hey!
- Non!
- Whoa!
- Go!
- Come on, Non!
- Go, Non!
- Go!
- More, Non!
- Come on!
Shouldn't you be happier?
Come on! Be more cheerful.
That's it!
Can you take a photo for me?
Artit, Non's getting
even more skilled now.
Here! I'll show you the photo!
He's replacing you now.
He's very popular nowadays,
both in and out of the field.
Girls are clamoring for him.
Not just clamoring,
they're dying for him.
Here, look at this.
I've taken so many photos.
Have a look.
Huh?
This one took a while.
I'm telling you
I was really rooting for him.
In the last second,
just before time was up,
Non just got the ball
out of the blue.
he just ran and touched down.
Then time was up.
They won by a hair.
Besides, he was awarded
player of the match. Isn't he cool?
Why did you throw my phone?
My screen's all cracked.
What's wrong with you?
Are you angry
that Non and Ling didn't come?
Come on, Artit.
They're trying to finish up
their final projects.
Non also has rugby practice.
- Don't think too much.
- Why were you able to come?
Don't vent your frustrations
on others.
Get out, Kot.
Get out!
What's going on?
Kot, what's up with him?
He's crazy.
Not only is his body broken,
but his heart and brain are
broken as well.
I said get out.
Get out!
Artit.
I'll go then.
I'll just leave this here.
I'm thinking of visiting him.
I'm coming with you.
Do you still dare to go?
He's angry with me
because of you two.
Huh? Are you going just
to have him kick you out?
It's actually because of you.
Oh? So I'm wrong?
Yes, didn't bother to ask us first.
You know how dedicated he is to
rugby. You rubbed it in his face.
How should I know? I just wanted
to let him know. How am I wrong?
You're wrong
because you don't understand him.
Artit is happy every time he gets
to play rugby.
It's what he hopes and dreams about.
But now,
he can't even walk.
So he's frustrated.
That's why he acted like that.
The thing he needs right now
now is our support.
I'm thinking that I'll stay
with him for a few days.
Let's do this.
I'll pick you up from your dorm.
I have to work. Can you pick me
up here instead?
Right. I'm the forgotten one.
You have to come with us.
I'm not going.
I'm still angry at him.
You look like you deserve a slap.
You deserved to be yelled
at by Artit.
You'll get it too.
Amen. I hope you get it even worse.
You'll get it yourself.
I'm not going.
How could he do this to me?
I'm his close friend.
Just a second.
Hello?
I'm busy right now.
I'll call you later.
Hey,
Ling and I know
who you're talking to.
You're talking to
a girl, aren't you?
Tell us. What faculty? Which year?
What does she look like?
Jerk. That wasn't a girl.
Here, eat up. So you can stop
being delusional.
No, I'm on a diet.
I might gain weight.
Artit, Non's getting
even more skilled now.
He's very popular nowadays,
Girls are clamoring for him.
Here, look at this.
He was awarded player of the match.
Isn't he cool?
Oh, aren't you getting in the car?
Aren't you going away for two
nights? Where's your luggage?
Oh, I forgot it at the shop.
Just a second.
Ling, I'll go get it for you.
Wait in the car.
Okay.
Whose is this?
Tattered like this?
It's definitely Ling's.
Ask her if you don't believe me.
Non wants to talk to you.
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
See? I knew it.
It's so tattered, it must be yours.
Hey!
Give it to me.
What is she doing?
Oh?
Is she going to just throw it away?
What?
I threw it but you
patched it up again?
What is it?
It was on sale,
so I bought it for you.
It's pretty cheap.
Do you like it?
I do.
Non, it's me.
I was waiting for you
to call me back yesterday.
I'm trouble, it's serious.
Otherwise, I wouldn't bother you.
Can you transfer me
about 30,000 baht?
Hello? Non?
Did you hear what I said?
Why didn't you answer me?
If you're not going to transfer it,
I'll go and ask Ling.
What's the matter, Ling?
Dad, it's me.
Ling?
You just...
Yes.
I was the one who answered.
I heard everything.
Listen to me.
Dad, I'll talk to you later.
I...
Ling!
Listen to me.
What else do I need to listen to?
When I've already heard everything
about you giving my Dad money.
How much has he asked from you?
Can you calm down and listen to me?
I know you're having money troubles.
I just wanted to help you.
This is not helping.
If you really want to help me,
you wouldn't do this.
But I mean well for you.
Other people
have no say
in my family's problems.
Other people?
How can you see me as that?
We're friends.
Friends have to help each other.
But not this way.
What you did
makes me pity myself.
Are you thinking too much?
Yes, I think too much.
It's the way I am.
You don't know me at all.
Ling!
(Dad)
Oh, Non? It's me.
Can you transfer me
about 30,000 baht?
Mom,
I'm coming to live with you.
Ling, do you have to be this angry?
I'm sorry. I know I'm wrong
for intruding into your life.
But I'd like to talk to you.
Can you give me a chance to explain?
Ling,
I'm sorry.
I know I'm the one who's at fault.
I'm sorry for
overstepping the bounds.
I admit that I didn't
think it through.
I'm sorry for making you feel bad.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry that I haven't
visited you very much.
It's okay. I understand.
Did you come here alone?
Yes.
What about
the others?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
Why do you look worse
than the patients here?
I'm here to say goodbye.
I'm going to live with Mom.
Are you really going?
Are you going to leave me?
I have to go.
You're going with Non, aren't you?
I'm going by myself.
Non isn't involved.
Don't lie to me.
You don't want to be with me.
You love him, don't you?
I'm not leaving you.
Then tell me,
that you don't love Non.
Both you
and Non
are my friends.
Do you know
that you're bad at lying, Ling?
Am I that pathetic?
Is that why you
don't want to admit it?
Just go.
Because now I'm not even sure
if I still want to
be friends with you.
Oh?
I'll help you.
It's heavy. Come on.
Thanks for dropping me off.
It's okay.
I only have a few friends left.
So, I have to take care of them.
What's up with all of us?
After Non was promoted to captain,
he and Artit stopped talking.
Things will probably get better
if I go away.
How does it have
anything to do with you?
It has nothing to do with you.
Let's change the subject.
Aren't you going to call them
and say you're leaving today?
It's better this way.
Just a quick call?
Let's hurry or I'll be
late for the flight.
Are you sure?
Let's go.
You can change your mind.
You can still call in the car.
Not enough. Dance harder!
Louder! Louder! Like that!
Do you want to come?
- Alright.
- Let's go, then.
How are you doing?
Originally, the rose was discovered
by an anonymous person
4,000 years ago.
The characteristic of the rose is...
- There she is! Paeng!
- Paeng!
Pony! Khanoon!
- Hey! It's Ran!
- Hello, Paeng.
Wow!
Did you tell Ran to come?
You're pretty feisty
under that mug, sister.
Feisty my butt.
He just came. I didn't ask him to.
I'd like to congratulate you.
Do you want to start working now?
I have some places I can recommend.
It's okay.
I'd been studying for four years.
Let me make my degree
worth the tuition.
Anyway, thank you for your advice.
Hold on, Paeng. Come here.
Paeng,
as an expression of my sincerity
towards you for the past two years,
I'd like to tell everyone
right here that
I love you, Paeng.
Can you keep recording
the live video for me?
Paeng, a bouquet for you.
It's soaking wet!
To the guys who are
watching this live video.
If you want to confess
your love to someone,
you should ask them first
whether they love you or not.
Otherwise, you'll end up like this.
- Fabulous, sister!
- Awesome!
- Let's go.
- Ran!
I'm still single!
I'm still single as well!
Come on. Hurry up.
Bye-bye!
Paeng,
aren't you going to even
give him a chance?
Everyone who has approached you
was all high-end!
If I were her, I'd take all of them!
- You're crazy!
- I'm not.
A spinster like you is
probably all dried up.
No, I'm happy being alone.
I don't want anyone.
You don't want anyone because
there's someone in your heart?
Are you crazy?
Who's going to be in my heart?
I spend all of my time with a girl
and a gay!
Come on. Let's take some photos.
Okay. Fab.
Yes!
Pokin the Princess!
Khanoon the Blue Moon!
Wanfahmai the Night Fairy!
Don't take that from me!
Whoa! Did we party
that hard last night?
Khanoon?
Pony?
Where are they?
I'm sorry for leaving early.
If Daddy knows that
I hung out with you here,
he'd beat the crap out of me.
I'm sorry I had to go home.
And who made this mess?
I have to tidy it up?
Oh, wow!
Paeng is so good at cooking!
Last time you made steak.
What are you going to make next?
I'm thinking of trying
to make steamed buns.
Should you open up a restaurant?
Hold it right there, Aueng.
I'm not that good.
I'm so proud of you.
It's been six years,
you've gotten so skillful.
You've gotten more beautiful too.
I'm sorry for not being
at your graduation.
I had to help my mom work
in the rice paddies.
No worries at all. I understand.
Have you talked to Jaem at all?
I don't know how she's doing.
She didn't reply to my texts.
Jaem doesn't know how to text.
She's probably happily raising
her grandkid.
That's great!
If you see her or talk to her,
please tell her that I miss her.
Definitely, Paeng.
I miss you.
Miss you too.
Artit, can you pass me the ball?
I'm sorry.
I decided to let Artit get
engaged to Paeng
not because of the debt.
I don't love Paeng.
I will never marry her.
Artit! I love you!
Paeng!
Even if you were the only person
left on earth,
I'd never take you as my wife!
I have nothing to lose!
My parents are dead!
I don't need to care
about anyone anymore.
Artit!
Don't you trust me, Dad?
I trust what I saw.
I couldn't fight him off.
Liar!
They're doing that on purpose.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
You haven't changed.
If you knew what I lost,
you wouldn't have
said that stupid apology.
Just atone for your sins.
You've done so much to him.
Keep your filthy hands away!
Your place is here. Eat up.
I locked her up. I'm thinking of
leaving her for a couple of days
and letting her starve.
What if she actually dies?
What are you going to do?
You're never
going to forgive me?
If you were me, would you be able to
put up with being like this?
Both my dreams and my future
are ruined.
Everything I'd accomplished was
ruined because of you!