(My Forever Sunshine)
Why don't you ask me nicely
what you want to know?
Do you know that I've waited
for the day for you to be here
with me for a very long time?
I'll try my best to be gentle.
You're as vile as your mom.
You have no right to
insult my mother.
Hey!
Restrain him!
You don't have to be
tough all the time.
Be vulnerable sometimes
so that I can take care of you.
I don't object
to accepting you as my niece
or a close relative.
But as for a daughter-in-law...
I can't have children.
If your family doesn't accept me,
then we can't love
each other anymore.
I'll explain it to Mom.
then we can't love
each other anymore.
I want you to believe in me
so that we'll be able to
get married.
Please wait for me.
I understand you.
Mom wouldn't let Non get married?
That's right. She won't allow it.
She was so happy yesterday.
She even wanted them
to get married within the year.
What happened, Kot?
Well, Ling...
can't have children.
What?
Non and I
are both hopeless romantics.
I'm also unsuccessful in love
because I loved someone
who didn't love me back.
Now Non as well?
It's not the same.
Those two are in love
and were about to get married.
What a shame.
That's true.
Non's probably going
to be devastated.
I understand the pain well.
My parents are being unreasonable.
I'll have to take matters
into my own hands.
How are you going to do that?
You don't have to know.
Nang, what on earth are you doing?
If you're going to get drunk just
because Mom said what she said,
you can resign
from being my brother.
Who told you? Kot, right?
Stay out of my business.
Get lost.
Non, don't call me nosy.
It was so painful when Artit
broke my heart.
So I don't want anyone
to feel the same pain I did.
You have some who loves you
and you love her.
Why don't you fight for each other?
This is a tiny obstacle and you
already backed down.
You're so not my brother.
You have to make a decision
whether you want
to keep going or stop.
Because if it's the former,
I'll go and pick Ling up myself.
I'll help you.
Thanks, Nang.
But let me tell you one thing.
Someone like me
never backs down.
- Hey!
You started this first!
The bed's all dirty!
- Ling! Ling!
- Keep it down, Nang.
Ling, you're here.
Ling, it's not easy for you and Non
to be in love with each other.
- You have to come with me.
- Hold on.
Let me finish up my work here first.
Why are you leaving my brother?
Do you know how sad he is?
Wait. I don't understand.
There are so many ways
to deal with infertility.
You can adopt as well.
As for Mom,
I'll deal with her myself.
You have to come with me right now.
Hold on,
where are you taking me?
To talk to my parents.
Let's go. We have to
help each other.
We have to join forces for this one!
- Let's go.
- Hey, Nang!
Right here.
- Sit down.
- Hello.
Why do you have to get in the way
of Ling and Non's love life?
You're being very mean.
You won't let Non marry Ling
just because she's infertile.
If they want children,
they can go adopt.
Parents
can only raise a child physically.
If you force them too much,
they could become delinquents.
Nang, I'm not a kid anymore.
What are you smiling about, Non?
This is your life.
Aren't you troubled at all?
You too, Mom and Dad.
What are you smiling about?
I'm being serious.
I was a little startled yesterday.
I wanted a grandchild so much,
so I said what I said.
Dad calmed me down, so I realized
that it's Non's life.
We have to let him choose
his own path.
We have no right to intervene.
That's right. I saw how much
they love each other
and how sincere their love is.
How can we possibly get in the way?
Whatever makes you happy,
will make us happy too.
Whomever you love,
we will love her too.
My son is now an adult.
I believe that you've chosen
the right person.
And the person he's chosen is you.
So you let me go
back and forth like crazy?
It's because of you, Kot.
You made it such a big deal,
saying that
you won't let them get married.
Kot, you're being overly dramatic.
I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Actually, there's
a silver lining to this.
Now I got to see
that my daughter can be smart too.
Don't take it off again.
Congratulations to you both.
Stay in love with each other.
Mutual love isn't that common.
Ling saw the goodness in Non,
unlike someone
who can't see the goodness in me.
But it's okay.
The matter of love
is not a big deal for me.
Others might not see
your goodness, but I do.
Thank you, Kot.
Nang,
you're still like a sister to me.
Artit doesn't love me
because of you.
Take care of him well.
If you didn't exist,
Artit would've laid eyes on me.
Since he's chosen you,
I'm strong enough to accept it.
Stop Press!
No need to cheer me up.
I'm much stronger than you think.
Oh, wow.
I think your sister has seen
one too many TV series.
Kot,
- take care of my sister.
- Okay.
Nang!
Artit,
when are you and Paeng...
When is it?
That's true.
Paeng,
you seem sad.
What the matter?
I...
I'm thinking
about Mark being punished
by the law.
I'm scared he might get away.
It hasn't happened yet.
Don't worry about it now.
Use the time you have to be happy.
Do you know
that you're my motivation?
Really?
Since I was young,
I begged for love from Mom.
Then I lost my parents,
the person who looked after me
and understood me
was you.
From now on,
this place is your home.
Everyone here is your family.
You're not alone anymore.
But I loved you in the wrong way.
And I made mistakes.
Back then,
I didn't understand you.
And I was very mean to you.
We've been through a lot.
I'm happy
that I have you supporting me
and always standing by me
until now.
I'll always be right beside you.
I know you well.
If you give your word,
you always keep it.
Oh, so sweet.
Aueng, you're here.
Miss Paeng,
what do you want me to do?
I have to talk to you.
Of course. Please have a seat.
Aueng,
are you happy living here?
Initially, I thought
I wouldn't like it.
But as time passed,
I became very happy.
I'm surrounded by nature.
I get to see flowers bloom
and plants bear fruit.
I'm happy that you like it here.
Why are you asking me this?
I just wanted to be sure
that you really are happy.
Miss Paeng!
Don't be worried about me.
Aueng,
can I ask you a small favor?
Small?
No need to be considerate.
Ask for more. Go ahead.
While you're here,
can you take care of Artit for me?
Take care?
Where are you going?
Promise me.
Uh...
Okay. I'll look after him.
No problem.
Look after him like you looked
after me, okay?
Of course, Miss Paeng.
Thank you, Aueng.
I love you the most.
Miss Paeng! I love you the most too!
What's up with you?
I'm having a bad feeling about this.
Are you anxious
about going to court?
No, I'm not.
Please don't cry.
I can look after him, no problem.
Promise me, Aueng.
I promise.
Miss Paeng!
Mom, Dad
it's almost the day of Mark's trial.
I will make him atone
for what he's done.
So you can finally rest in peace.
This is the only thing
that I can do for you both.
Please lead and guide me
in all that I do.
Artit.
I'm here to pick you up.
It's okay. I can go there myself.
I'm not going to let you do
what you want today.
You have to let me come with you.
Because your business
is my business.
Are you scared?
I'm not sure
if I'll be able to get him.
Mom's case was a while ago.
Even if you're not sure,
you have to try.
We'll fight together.
Oh?
Do you have a meeting somewhere?
I'm not going to a meeting.
I'm going to court
for Paeng's case.
I have to go now.
Uh... Krongprateep?
Wait.
Paeng.
Non, Ling, Kot!
It's not just Artit
who's accompanying you.
We're also here to support you.
Come on, Paeng. Let's go crush Mark!
Hey!
You're crying.
Why are you crying?
The only person who's going to cry
today is that jerk, Mark.
Don't be afraid.
You've got so much support.
Thank you so much, everyone.
- Hello.
Please follow me, Miss Wanfahmai.
We have to get ready.
Can Artit join us?
Certainly.
No need to be nervous, Paeng.
Don't worry.
Good will always triumph over evil.
I need to pee. I'm so excited.
- I'll be right back.
- Mmm.
Please.
I'll be right back.
The other party has a lawyer who's
very skilled in cases like these.
He'll frame the question
in a way to humiliate you.
You have to control yourself
and don't be nervous.
If you are nervous,
he'll pressure you
into playing his game.
Okay. I understand.
Paeng,
we didn't do anything wrong.
Just tell the truth.
Mark should be the one
who's scared, not you.
Thank you very much
for being my witnesses.
You're welcome. It's our duty.
Even though it's your duty,
we'd like to thank you anyway.
Please go and wait
in the witness room.
I'll call you once the trial starts.
Okay.
Don't worry, Mr. Mark.
You'll be able to go home
in less than an hour.
Are you sure?
I'm more than sure.
Because she came to
see you in your room.
It's also visible
in the CCTV footage.
You're not at fault here.
Paeng!
Did you bring a guard dog today?
You brought so many people.
You must be very scared of me.
I was never scared of you.
Because I didn't do anything wrong.
Artit also isn't a dog.
You're the one who's the dog.
Because you like to bite people
behind their backs.
Today,
I'll try not to be angry with you.
But I'm furious
and I hate you. You scumbag!
Paeng, calm down.
Don't feed the howling dog, Paeng.
I can sue you all, do you know that?
Go ahead. We're not afraid.
You're all insane.
That's why you get along so well.
Oh, are you asking for it?
I think
you should return to where you were.
Are you scared of me?
Do you want it? Let's rumble.
Stay away from them, Mr. Mark.
It might affect the case
if you do something.
I would've kicked him
if we weren't at court.
Don't waste your time
with someone who doesn't have
a conscience. Scumbag!
What are you smiling, Non?
The way you cursed him was on point.
He's such a scumbag.
Let's go, Paeng.
(Courtroom 403)
Paeng.
Let's go.
Hello.
All rise for the judge.
On Monday, 16 March,
at around 10:00 a.m.,
you went to the defendant's condo,
which is Mr. Mark. Is that right?
That's right.
Can you state what happened
once you've got there?
I will.
When I arrived at the condo,
I told Mr. Mark
that I'd like to wait in his room.
So he told the staff to let me in.
What's your intention for going in?
I went there to find evidence.
Did you find anything?
I did.
I found a picture of Mark
with a tattoo
on the left of his back
and I found...
Your Honor,
I object.
The prosecutor's question
is not related to today's case.
Your Honor,
I'd like you to listen to
what the witness says.
Because it's the reason
why she went there.
Proceed.
So that I can prove
that this man
was...
my mother's lover.
I object!
Miss Wanfahmai
is accusing my client.
And her statement is not
related to the case.
Please be careful with your answer.
Did you know about this?
I know
that Pimnapa
was cheating on Tharathep.
But I didn't know that it's him.
Please state
what happened afterward.
Once I found the evidence,
Mr. Mark came in.
He ordered room service
and invited me to eat with him.
He also put something
into my drink.
He tried to coax me
into drinking it.
When I refused,
he drank it himself.
So I asked him
if he murdered my mother.
And he admitted everything.
I object!
You're accusing my client again!
I have evidence.
Your Honor,
I'd like to play an audio recording
which serves as physical evidence.
Are you sure that the recording
isn't incriminating?
You're going to make me talk
and then hand over the recording
to the police.
Even if it's been recovered,
I didn't say anything
because I didn't do anything wrong.
Would you like something to drink?
No.
How come?
What?
Why do you seem so stressed?
I ordered room service
because I was hoping
that we could relax, eat, and chat.
They're all your favorites.
I'm not hungry.
Ask me
what you want to know.
That tattoo.
You know about it now?
What did you put in there?
Calm down.
Do you know that
you're too stressed?
You'll feel better if you take
something for your nerves.
Drink it. You'll feel relaxed.
I won't.
But I want you to.
I'm not going to drink it.
Why are you so stubborn?
You're just as stubborn as your mom.
You said you didn't know her mother.
You have to order them
to turn it off.
You're starting to
get scared, aren't you?
Do you really want to know?
That's right.
I'm the one who killed your mom.
I killed Pimnapa.
Your Honor,
secretly recording a video
or audio during a conversation
without the other party's consent,
it is considered
unlawfully obtained evidence
according to Section 226 of the
Criminal Procedure Code.
An exception can be made
if the admissibility of the evidence
has more advantages towards the
procedure than disadvantages
towards the standards
of the criminal code
or basic rights and freedoms
of the people.
Didn't you follow the news
about the 30 million baht lottery?
I'd like to continue to
play the recording.
Proceed.
But I didn't plan to.
But do you know why?
Because she broke up with me.
She told me
she felt guilty about
her husband and daughter.
But she never felt any guilt
towards me.
Even though I was faithful
and was so nice to her.
But she didn't love me
like I loved her.
She didn't want me
like I wanted her.
She was going to leave me,
so I...
Enough!
You wanted to know how I killed her,
so I'm explaining it in detail so
that you'll be able to imagine it.
You killed her
just because she was leaving you.
Just because she's leaving?
Do you know
how does it feel to be abandoned?
It hurts more than death.
I've been abandoned too many times.
It will never happen again.
It won't happen to me ever again.
You have to tell me.
that you won't leave me.
Why does it have to be me?
Because
you're Pimnapa's daughter.
You live a similar life.
You're an orphan like me.
So I'm the one
who understands you the most.
I want to take care of you
and protect you.
I don't need a psycho
like you taking care of me.
I guess you want to know
how I got the recording.
Artit!
Please help me!
I object!
You're accusing the defendant,
defaming him,
and causing misunderstanding.
Your Honor,
I'd like you to exclude
the recording and statement.
I'm sure that he's the one
who murdered my mother.
He's a murderer.
Please control yourself
and respect the court.
I am speaking the truth.
I wasn't lying.
He's a murderer.
You're accusing me.
You faked the recording.
I didn't know your mom.
I didn't kill her.
- You killed my mom!
- I didn't.
Stop. Or I'll hold you in contempt.
Your Honor,
I'd like to request a short recess.
So my client can calm himself down.
Then we can continue.
Recess has been granted.
Paeng! Paeng!
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay at all.
I'm scared he might get away.
If he gets away this time,
we won't be able to get him anymore.
Paeng,
I believe in one thing.
No one can escape karma.
No matter what happens today,
that man has to atone
for what he did.
But I want it to be today.
Is that recording genuine?
If you did,
if you really did kill her mother,
you have to tell me.
I didn't kill anyone.
They couldn't get to me.
So they tried to frame me.
Besides,
I don't know who her mother is.
That recording
was fabricated.
Are you telling me the truth?
I am.
This is the test result
from the beverage
that the defendant tried to coax
the plaintiff into drinking.
The results indicate
that there is GSB,
more commonly know as
the date rape drug or
or a rohypnol.
According to all the evidence,
it can be confirmed
that the defendant
deliberately tried to drug
and rape Miss Wanfahmai.
As for the weapon she brought over
that was used to harm the defendant,
it was only in self-defense.
He won't be able to get away
with evidence this tight.
He's worse than I thought.
Miss Wanfahmai,
did you go to Mr. Mark's condo
without an appointment
and on your own accord?
I have stated that I went there
because I wanted to find evidence.
I'm only asking
whether you went there or not.
That's all.
So you
went to Mr. Mark's condo
on your own,
without any coercion,
is that correct?
That's correct.
You intentionally brought a weapon
and used this knife to harm
the defendant,
is that correct?
I brought it for self-defense.
Yes, or no.
I'm going to repeat
my question again.
You arranged for a meeting
with the defendant
and you used this knife to hurt him,
is that correct?
Miss Wanfahamai,
please answer the question.
Please answer the question.
That's correct.
The recording
that you used as evidence,
did you fabricate it?
I did not. That recording
is genuine.
Deception in court is punishable
by a jail sentence.
I'm warning you.
I object.
The lawyer is threatening
the plaintiff.
Please be careful with your words.
I have a test result
which indicates that
the defendant was drugged
by Miss Wanfahmai,
who brought over the drugs.
The defendant was
coaxed into drinking.
There is no reason for
the defendant to drug himself.
Her evidence was fabricated.
No further questions.
Why was he beating around the bush?
The evidence is tight.
Would you like to cross-examine
the witness?
(Courtroom)
- Sergeant Chakrapong?
- Yes, sir.
Please come to the courtroom.
Are you alright, Tubtim?
I'm okay.
It's time for Mark's
testimony now, right?
Mmm.
Please state the history
between you and Miss Wanfahmai.
Paeng and I
met just recently.
I was interested in her.
Apart from my interest,
I empathized with her
since she's also an orphan like me.
So I told her
that I'm also an orphan.
This might be the reason
why she's so fixated on me.
It became too much.
To the point, I felt uncomfortable.
She forced me to give her lifts.
That day, she wanted to
come over so she did so.
She forced me to return even though
I had business elsewhere.
You're lying!
Please be silent
until you're permitted to speak.
Please continue
as to why you allowed her
to wait in your room.
It was what she wanted.
And I had to comply.
Just like I had always done.
The more I got to know her,
the more I felt
that she was mentally unstable.
Your Honor,
I object!
Please don't make accusations
without evidence.
It's the defendant's
feelings towards her.
I'd like you to listen
until the end.
I'd like to continue
with the questioning.
As for the food and beverage,
you were the one who ordered them.
I did.
Because I thought it would be better
if we talked
once she had calmed down.
So I thought the food might help.
The beverage didn't contain alcohol.
It was just orange juice.
What happened afterward?
After that,
I intended to clear things up and
let her know that I didn't want this
relationship.
I intended to explain to her
that it was impossible between us.
And I asked to
end our relationship.
Why didn't you talk in the lobby?
I was afraid she might have
thrown a tantrum.
I was embarrassed.
You wished to end the
relationship with Miss Wanfahmai?
I was never
in a relationship with you!
Please calm down.
He's such a liar.
Who's going to believe him?
Be quiet for now.
Your Honor,
I tried to end things with her
as politely as I could.
Can you confirm that the drug
in the beverage wasn't yours?
It wasn't mine.
The knife she used to harm me
wasn't mine either.
Why did she harm you?
We couldn't talk it out.
And she wouldn't break up with me
so she attacked me with the knife.
After she drugged me,
she tried to have sex with me.
I tried to escape
but she threw a fit
and used the knife to harm me.
What about
the plaintiff's recording?
That recording also wasn't mine.
What about her accusation
that you killed her mother?
I didn't do it.
I don't know her mother.
I deny all accusations.
No further questions.
He's coming.
It's not easy to get to me.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
What right do you have to arrest
my client in the court?
The police have a court warrant.
And it has been issued.
Why are you arresting me?
For the murder case
from eight years ago.
That's right.
For the murder of Ms. Pimnapa.
I didn't do it.
But we have a witness
who can testify against you.
It's Miss Wanfahmai.
What evidence do you have?
Did you think I went into your room
for a stroll?
The picture of your tattoo,
the picture of my mom,
and your hair,
I got them all.
The DNA on Pimnapa's fingernails
belonged to her husband.
But the DNA from your hair
that Miss Wanfahmai gave us
matches the hair
that forensics found
next to Pimnapa's body
eight years ago.
I've also taken the picture
of the woman who raised you.
Why did you take it?
You must really hate her, don't you?
Did you hate her so much
that you killed her?
The police have looked
into this as well.
You're not going to get away, Mark.
You're as vile as your mother.
Please.
It's all over, Paeng.
Paeng! Paeng!
Paeng! Whoa!
Paeng, it was so awesome!
You're were like a real detective.
You were so many steps ahead of him.
Because she's smart, Kot.
Oh, now I'm at a loss.
Hey,
he didn't show any guilt
or remorse at all.
There's probably
no humanity left in him.
Now it's all over.
Let's leave it to the police
from now on.
He said it himself,
it can be used against him.
He won't get away.
Okay. I hope
the punishment will fit the crime.
Paeng,
I'm happy for you.
I'm happy for you too.
You've been trying hard for so long.
Now I feel
like a huge weight has been
lifted off my chest.
I'm relieved that
everything ended well.
Alright.
I have to thank you all
for coming to support her.
There's no need to thank us.
Paeng is like our sister.
Everyone's had a long day.
Let's get some rest.
Especially you.
Tomorrow
I'll let you take the day off.
It's okay, Uncle.
I need to clear the backlog.
It will take a few days.
Once I've finished,
everything will be complete.
Why are you saying that?
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'd like to ask you
about what you said.
What does it mean?
I want to fulfill the promise.
What promise?
The promise that we agreed upon.
Letting me train here for two years.
I actually thought
that you would want to stay here.
Aren't you happy?
I am very happy.
But I'd like to
start doing new things by myself.
Once I've finished up my work,
I'd like to get out of here.
Thank you
for intending to fulfill the promise
that you made to me.
I won't break my word to you.
I know that Artit will be sad.
But you're doing the right thing.
Because if we keep
prolonging things,
the more pain it will cause you.
I'm worried about both of you.
Doing this
is the same as hurting you.
I'm sorry.
Please don't say that.
I told you I understand.
If there wasn't
the issue with Artit,
I'd like you to stay forever.
Thank you very much
for showing me mercy.
Time will heal everything.
I will always support you.
I hope you have a bright
and happy future.
Thank you very much.
Dad,
is Paeng gone?
You haven't gone to sleep yet?
I was waiting to talk to you.
Please talk to me.
Let's save it for later. I'm sleepy.
Tubtim,
I don't want it to be too late.
What did you talk to Paeng about
that day?
What day?
The day we went to the temple.
Well,
I apologized to Paeng
for treating her badly.
What else?
That's all.
We've been together for 30 years.
Do you think I can't
see you through?
What?
You're not going to
accept her, are you?
I have my reasons.
I'm sorry
but I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
I called you here
because I wanted to talk to you.
I wanted to talk to you too.
Did I do something wrong?
Why didn't I know
that you were leaving?
I was so busy with the case.
So I didn't get
the chance to tell you.
Maybe I'm not important to you.
That's not true.
But that's how I feel right now.
Why do you have to go?
I don't want you to go.
But I've made my decision.
Don't go, Paeng.
It doesn't matter what
your reasons are...
apart from you not loving me.
You're angry.
I'm not.
I just don't understand.
But I'm not gone for good.
We still have a chance to meet.
I must've assumed that you love me.
If you insist on going,
then I have to accept it.
Don't go, Paeng.
It doesn't matter what
your reasons are.
Can you promise me
that there's not going to be
anything between you and Artit,
other than being siblings?
I know you well.
If you give your word,
you always keep it.
If it makes you happy,
then I promise.
Thank you very much
for understanding me.
But I'm asking you
to keep this between us.
Don't let Artit know.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for Artit.
Why are you looking for him?
Tubtim?
Alright. I'm worried about him.
He's not a kid anymore.
You've got a point.
He should be alright.
I meant that he's grown up now.
He should be able
to live his own life.
He should be able to choose
his own path
and learn his own lessons
whether they're happy or sad.
But I don't want it to happen.
Are you admitting it now?
That the reason Paeng's leaving
is because of you.
I'll admit it.
I don't want history
to repeat itself.
I'm afraid that Paeng
will become like her mother.
All this time has passed.
Hasn't Paeng proven herself enough?
I'm not angry with her anymore.
But you're still scared
and have doubts about her.
That's right. I admit it.
Artit is hot-tempered.
Paeng is also headstrong.
I can't see how these two
could make it work.
Am I wrong for worrying
about my son?
There are a lot of diseases that can
affect the roses.
It's even more difficult
to take care of them
when we don't use chemicals.
We have to check on them frequently
so we can catch it in time.
Yes, Miss Paeng.
Trimming is also important.
You need to let them rest
especially with the ones
that have just blossomed.
If small buds like these appear,
you have to trim them off.
Wait until they get stronger
and until a new bud starts blooming.
Right! Just like pigs!
Pigs?
How?
When a mother pig
gives birth too often,
she'll feel unwell.
You don't know
anything at all, Saeb.
Oh, really?
That's true.
Animals and plants are similar.
But I think
you're like the mother of the roses.
They'll be very lonely if you leave.
That's why I'm letting you all
take care of them.
If they die, what are
you going to do?
That's right. Aren't you
going to miss them?
Please don't go.
Of course, I'll miss them.
I'll miss everything
and everyone here.
Because this is
my first rose garden.
It's very precious to me.
It brought me
both trouble and happiness.
I'll never forget it.
And I know
that all of you
will take good care of it for me.
Promise me.
- Okay.
You're heartbroken because of Paeng?
Pipe it down, Nang?
You blindly fell in love with her.
Now she's dumping you?
Oh, I'm so angry.
What are you laughing about?
I wasn't telling a funny story.
I don't think the heartbreak
will kill him.
That's true. I didn't die
when Artit broke my heart.
I didn't die but it hurt.
How are we going to help him?
When is Paeng leaving?
Are you still thinking of
going back to Artit?
Come on, Non.
Someone like me? No way.
Okay? That's settled.
So? When is she leaving?
Probably in two days.
Simple. Just tell Artit
to make her his.
That's all. Can't you even come up
with a simple idea like that?
Just do what Paeng did
when she was young.
Hey, Artit's here.
Watch your mouth.
I don't know why I used to like you.
You're so not the manly Artit
that I thought you were.
Honestly,
you're such a wuss.
So annoying!
Did your sister just insult me?
That's right.
Hey, Artit.
Let's do it this way. Why don't
you what Nang said?
If she won't accept your love,
then just make her yours.
Kot, you jerk.
He'll end up in jail.
Hold on. What are you talking about?
Nothing. Nonsense.
Are you okay?
What do you think?
Oh? It's all gone, Miss Paeng.
Let's go.
Hey, are you trying to pick a fight
by standing in our way?
Aueng.
Miss Paeng!
She beelined straight to you.
She must be looking for a fight.
Stay back. I'll deal with her.
I'm sorry.
I told her to come
and apologize to you.
Well? Why are you standing there?
Just say what you want to.
Just a second, Thongkhum.
It's not as easy as hurling insults.
If you're quick to insult,
then you have to
be quick to apologize too.
Alright.
When I saw you looking
after Thongkhum,
even though we were just
unimportant workers,
you still cared.
And you didn't mind
that I was mean to you.
I'm sorry for misunderstanding you
and
for framing and bullying you.
Please forgive me.
It's okay.
I stopped being angry with you
a long time ago.
But you really get on my nerves.
- Aueng.
- Let me have my moment.
I'd like to apologize to you too.
Alright. I haven't been angry
with you for ages.
Really?
Really.
Wow!
Your face was so serious.
Just a little bit.
I heard that you're leaving.
I have a lot of things to do.
And I know why.
Please don't call me nosy.
You have to stand for who you are.
You're a good
and lovely person.
Believe me. One day,
you'll be able to prove yourself.
Miss Paeng,
you're the best suited
for Mr. Artit.
Artit?
Since when did you arrive?
For a while now.
I'm sorry, Paeng.
I was acting silly yesterday.
Don't be angry with me.
I understand.
You weren't acting
silly or anything.
Do you want to go for a drive?
Come on, Paeng.
Don't be afraid.
I won't drop off you somewhere.
Hold on tight.
Please don't pull a prank on me.
I stopped pranking you
a long time ago.
Wow, just like that.
Yum!
Who made the dipping sauce?
- What should I eat first?
- The chicken looks tasty, Pong.
That's Mr. Artit and Miss Paeng.
Mr. Artit! Pull over!
Yes, Pong?
Come and eat with us.
Do you want to join them?
Miss Paeng,
have some papaya salad.
That's right. Join us.
Are you going to keep
the sticky rice for yourself?
Come on, Pong.
Miss Paeng, eat up.
Come on. Take a big bite.
Let's consider this
Paeng's farewell party.
Hey,
nobody's going to call you a mute
if you don't speak.
I shouldn't have said that,
should I?
Do you even have to ask?
I'll kick you down the hill!
Give that to me.
Eat up. Take a big bite.
Paeng, sticky rice.
The catfish is so good.
Dig in, Artit.
Here.
Mmm, so good!
The eggs have the perfect amount of
seasoning.
This one. Chicken in Isaan dialect?
What is it?
Chick'un!
Do you remember
when you came back,
this is where we met
for the first time?
I do.
You pranked me.
You lied about being handicapped.
I didn't know how to send you away,
so I decided to do that.
But now,
I don't know what to do
to convince you to stay either.
Can you tell me
what I should do?
Artit!
Paeng, you broke your promise!
Don't feign sympathies.
No matter how my life turns out,
it's none of your business.
Ever since Miss Paeng left,
Mr. Artit has become a workaholic.
He works from before
sunrise until sunset.
Who misses me?
Artit!
Who allowed an outsider
into the farm?
I'm going to deduct your salaries.
When are you going
to stop being angry with me?
This is your punishment.
I can't love anyone anymore.
I can only love you.
Please, marry me.