(My Forever Sunshine)
Songtham fooled him.
He's going to take our farm.
Go back and tell your boss.
That we will pay off the debt
Anyone, help!
Did Mr. Tharathep pay off our debt?
Why is he so nice to us?
Friends are there to listen to
your secrets and feelings,
both ups and downs.
I'll be your first friend.
It's that way.
- Ling!
- I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You meant it. I saw it.
If you're thinking of
having a girlfriend,
then I have to get over it.
Mom!
Ms. Pimnapa!
You neglect me and Dad.
Don't you yell at me!
You really don't love me anymore!
You don't love me!
Paeng!
Can I have a round of applause?
Us meeting every day
Is it coincidental
Or are we destined by heaven
To always have each other
Oh, Paeng.
Why are you so quiet?
I thought you said
you don't want to go home.
What's up with you?
Oh? Didn't you say you want to let
off some steam?
Paeng, do you want to sing?
I read an academic paper.
Singing helps
with negative emotions.
It makes you 248.75% happier.
Which academic paper?
That number seems to be made-up.
You haven't read it. Who am I?
I'm Korakot.
I'll pick the song for you.
I feel good being with you
Even if it's only you who makes
me feel this way
Paeng.
Don't lose to us. Let's compete.
How about this? You sing one song.
I'll pick the song for you.
Stop hesitating.
- I've got the song.
- Come on. Only one song.
There you go.
Just a little bit.
Here she comes.
Young and handsome
That's me
I'm so good-looking
Yesterday I rode to Pak Kret
The girls noticed me
They asked if I'm Nadech
Young and handsome
That's me
I'm so good-looking
Yesterday I rode to Bang Bon
Pretty girls asked me
if I'm Boy Pakorn
Good thing we only booked
the room for that long
or we'll probably end up
singing all night.
Actually, you're crazier
than I thought, Paeng.
Let's sing together
again next time. It's fun.
You all just go ahead.
- I'm giving her a lift home.
- Before you go,
can I borrow your phone, Paeng?
Is yours out of battery?
No, I'm going to add your contact.
I might try to hit on you later.
Whoa. No, I consider her my sister.
If you want to hit on someone,
try Non's sister.
Not my sister either.
Nang? She's too feisty.
Stop arguing.
Let's go home.
I have to go.
Take care of Ling for me too.
Sure. I'll take good care of her.
All right. Let's sing
"I Will Always Love You."
- Why?
- Because it's from "The Bodyguard!"
- Gotcha!
- You're crazy.
See you later, Paeng.
- What's so funny?
- Come on. Let's go.
Please, this way.
How was it? Do you feel better now?
Much better.
Thank you, Artit.
Next time,
you have to be calmer.
You've grown up now.
You're not a little kid anymore.
What's this? I said I feel better
and now I'm being scolded.
I'm not scolding you.
I think you're too hot-tempered
and you're very clingy
with your mom.
I'm worried about her.
I know
that you love her very much.
But one day you have to grow up
and stand on your own legs.
I can't live without Mom and Dad.
You know I don't have anyone else.
Are you that much of a loner?
Don't you have any friends?
I've just made one recently.
It's you.
Do you know I really envy you?
Your friends are so nice.
Try to be more open.
It's not that difficult
to approach other people first.
We have to start somewhere.
If you can do it,
it's your own gain.
- What?
- I'm returning this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I was really worried about you.
Don't do this again.
I was wrong too
for being emotional like that.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Thank you so much, Artit.
Artit,
be proud. You're the first and only
person who can deal with her.
Really?
That's why I have
to bother you often.
It's a bit of a trouble.
Not at all.
What I do can't even compare to
how you helped my dad.
You know about it?
If there's anything I can help you,
I'm happy to do it.
Thank you very much,
- Artit.
- You're welcome.
Okay.
- I'm going now.
- Thank you.
Try to be more open.
It's not that difficult
to approach other people first.
We have to start somewhere.
If you can do it,
it's your gain.
Let's try again one more time.
Are you smiling at me?
What's your name?
What class are you from?
What are you doing, Boy?
Are you seducing my boyfriend?
Don't.
Don't just walk away.
We have to settle this.
You're mistaken.
You were just smiling at him.
Come here.
Stop.
Hey!
Stop right now!
What's going on?
What should I do
with you, Wanfahmai?
Why are you in a fight every day?
She started it.
That's not true.
And I'm more injured too.
You're from the same school.
I'm going to call your parents.
Hello. I'm Wanfahmai's parent.
Dad, I'm sorry.
But how did you know
that I was in a fight today?
Paeng, I didn't come over
because of that.
Mom and I have
something to deal with.
You have to live somewhere else
for a while.
What's all this about?
Why can't I stay at home?
Let the adults deal with it.
You won't understand.
I've packed your clothes.
Let's go now.
Now, Dad? What happened?
Where am I going to live?
Have a seat.
Please take care of her,
Krongprateep.
I have to bother you now,
Ms. Tubtim.
Don't worry about it.
What's going on?
Is there anything else
I can help with?
No need.
I have to deal with this myself.
Dad,
do I have to stay here long?
When are you going to
come to pick me up?
Paeng,
it won't be long.
You won't be staying here long.
I'll hurry and solve
all of my problems.
And I'll pick you up.
Don't worry.
I'll look after her the best I can.
Thank you so much,
Krongprateep.
I have something to talk to you.
Drive safely, Dad.
Paeng,
behave while you're living here.
Okay?
I love you so much.
You know that, right?
I want you to be happy.
Remember that.
No matter what happens,
you have to be strong
and deal with
whatever comes your way.
Why are you saying this to me?
It's probably because
you got in a fight today.
It's nothing.
I'm just worried about you.
I'm worried about you too.
Why are you acting so strange today?
I have to go now.
Don't worry.
I'm going now, okay?
Wait, Dad.
Can I hug you?
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, Paeng.
Be a good girl, okay?
Okay?
Ouch, my back.
Oh?
Do you think this is a hotel?
What are you complaining about?
It's a Master's friend.
He dropped off his daughter here.
Who knows how long she'll be here.
Who? Which friend?
That friend who visited last week.
The one with the daughter
I don't like.
That explains the complaint.
Let me tell you something.
Master hasn't even said a word.
You're a maid. Just shut your mouth.
If someone heard it and told him,
you might get reprimanded.
If someone's going to hear it,
it's because you tell them.
I was just complaining.
You don't understand me.
You don't understand me at all.
Duang!
How are you, Paeng?
Did you sleep well?
Yes. I'm sorry for sleeping in.
It's okay. It's good you can sleep
in an unfamiliar place.
Are you hungry?
Oh, dear. Duang.
She hasn't eaten yet.
Sorry.
Go get something from the kitchen.
There's still congee left, right?
I don't feel like congee.
Do you have any sandwiches?
We don't have that.
I didn't know what you want to eat
so I didn't prepare anything.
Just have congee for today, okay?
Okay.
Go and get it.
Yes, ma'am.
Eat up.
- What's the matter?
- Mom,
I don't want to be here.
Can I come home?
What did you say?
What's up between you and Dad?
Why do I have to stay here?
Are you going to be away long?
I can live with Aueng and Jaem.
Hold on, Paeng. Slowly.
I didn't know anything about this.
Where are you?
Dad said you have some business to
deal together with you.
Aren't you with him?
Well.
Let's talk later. I'm busy.
It's not an object. But it's...
This is...
Kot, what are you doing?
Nothing.
What's this?
Ling's tutoring us.
What are you doing?
- Let me see.
- What?
- I was just...
- Give it to me.
- Hey, Ling?
- Everyone's studying hard.
But you're busy flirting with girls.
I was just taking a break.
Can't you do it after the exam?
- Who are you? My parents?
- Give it to me.
Turn it off.
Off? All right.
For us to be even, you all have to
turn yours off too.
I'll turn it off too.
All right.
Turn them all off.
And put them there.
There.
Do you know how to?
I do.
The number you have
reached is not available.
Artit's phone is also turned off.
I can't contact anyone.
What are you doing, Dad?
Whoa, whoa.
Miss Paeng's calling.
- Yes, Miss Paeng?
- Aueng!
I'm so relieved. I thought
no one's going to talk to me.
I'll talk to you.
What's the matter?
Do you know
where mom and dad are going?
I don't know. I'm not at home.
- Oh? I'll call Jaem then.
- Oh!
No need. Jaem's with me now.
Give it to me. What's going on?
What's the matter, Miss Paeng?
Where are you and Aueng going?
Why aren't you home?
Master told us to take leave.
He said you're going to a camp.
So, he let Aueng and I
take leave and return home
for two weeks.
Did Dad say that?
Why?
Oh?
- Jaem!
- She hung up.
Krongprateep,
I have a bad feeling
for some reason.
About what?
It's Mr. Tharathep.
I think he seemed different.
He was acting strange.
I think so too.
Tharathep loves Paeng very much.
But he left her in our care
all of a sudden.
Didn't he tell you what's going on?
He didn't.
You were talking to him
in your office for quite a while.
Well,
he only said that he's got
an important business.
Tubtim, listen to me.
We owe Tharathep a lot for the farm.
If there's anything
we can do for him,
then we should do it.
Just consider it a repayment to him.
I know.
But it's really strange this time.
I don't know if it's just me.
Master, Madam! Where are you?
Oh, you're here.
What's going on?
We have a problem.
Miss Paeng disappeared.
- What?
- She disappeared.
Oh? Here's her bag.
Her clothes are all here.
Did you search everywhere?
- Well.
- Is there a misunderstanding?
She might be out for a stroll.
But I found this.
(I'm going home to see Mom and Dad
Paeng)
What's going on today?
No one is answering my calls.
- What about Artit?
- Master!
Have you found her?
I looked everywhere.
I don't see her at all.
She's probably returned to Bangkok.
How could she? She's still young.
How could she do that alone?
Oh, dear.
If something bad's happened,
how are we going to tell Tharathep?
What are you doing? You're all here.
It's his friend's daughter.
We don't know where she is.
Have you seen her?
- Miss Paeng?
- Right.
Oh?
This must hers.
- Where did you find it?
- It's in the back of my truck.
This really is Paeng's.
Oh, dear.
What was she unhappy about?
Why did she go back to Bangkok?
I promised Tharathep
to take care of her well.
I'm going after her.
Huh?
Why did this have to happen?
I feel like I'm going to faint.
- Ms. Tubtim.
- Easy, ma'am.
Dad? Mom?
Dad?
Dad!
Mom!
Dad.
Dad!
Dad, why did you do this?
Dad, wake up!
Dad!
Don't leave me!
How can I live without you!
Dad, stay with me!
Dad! Dad!
Dad, don't leave me!
Dad!
Don't leave me!
Paeng!
I found Paeng.
But something's happened.
Huh?
Mr. Tharathep and Ms. Pimnapa?
Are you sure?
Both of them are dead.
Oh, dear.
What about Paeng?
How is she?
She's in very bad shape.
I'll tell you once I got back.
Let me deal with things here first.
Okay.
What's your relation
to Miss Wanfahmai?
I'm her dad's friend.
Thank you.
Miss? Miss?
What's wrong? Miss?
Paeng! Paeng!
What's wrong? Paeng! Paeng!
Calm down.
Paeng, calm down. Paeng!
We haven't found the main cause.
She might have an untreated
neurological problem.
And there might be something
like continuous physical or
mental stress that stimulated it.
We have to keep an eye on her
before giving a diagnosis.
Fire!
I'm tired enough already.
You yelled fire
and I had to run off.
Why did you trick me?
I want you to wake up
and be conscious.
I asked you to study together.
Don't be lazy.
Have you seen the time?
We've been studying
since the afternoon.
What time is it now?
I'm tired. Do you understand?
Why do we have to study so much?
- I'm sleepy. I'm going home now.
- Wait.
You sit down now.
If you don't,
I'm going to tell Cherry
that you're a womanizer.
- You're using that against me?
- That's right.
If you expose me, I'll expose you.
- What about?
- That day at Ekkamai,
- at the middle of the table...
- Enough! Enough!
Let's take a break.
Ever since I've known you,
you're the cutest today.
- Hey.
- What? What?
What are you doing?
Really.
- I'll give you 15 minutes.
- Okay.
- We can turn on our phones now?
- I got so many calls!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Whoa.
Yes, Dad.
Where are you? Why did you
turn off your phone?
I was in a study group with friends.
So, we switched off all our phones.
This late?
The final exams are getting closer.
So, we have to study hard.
There were so many calls
from you and Paeng.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Paeng visited the farm
and she wanted to talk to you
so she asked me to call you.
Right.
She must have gone home, right?
She did.
Keep studying. That's all for now.
Okay. Talk to you later, Dad.
Will she get better?
She can.
Have you heard about PTSD?
Some patients who were
extremely traumatized
will be constantly
plagued by anxiety
as if the incident
is happening repeatedly.
They'll get better
depending on many factors.
The patient themselves
and external stimulants.
The time it takes
depends on the individual.
We have to keep monitoring her.
Paeng,
why are you standing here?
I had a nightmare.
I dreamed that my parents died.
I was so shocked
I couldn't breathe.
So, I came out for some air.
And how come
I'm at the hospital?
Listen to me carefully.
That wasn't a dream.
Both your parents have passed away.
You're lying.
I don't believe you.
My parents didn't die.
Paeng.
I wasn't lying.
How can I live without my parents?
Of course you can.
You still have me, Tubtim and Artit.
Remember that.
You're not alone.
Oh?
Paeng.
How are you?
Are you tired of the journey?
A little.
I've prepared a room.
I'll take you there.
This way.
Krongprateep.
How is Paeng doing?
She said she's exhausted.
So, she went to bed.
Does Artit know about this?
I haven't told him.
He's got exams right now
so I don't want him to be stressed.
Let's look after Paeng
together for now.
Okay.
I was wondering
if she has any relatives at all.
Is that why she has
to come live with us?
That's right. She has no relatives.
Before what happened to Tharathep,
he told me to help take care of her.
Do you remember the day he took her
here all of a sudden?
I do.
Whoo!
Exams are over.
- Yay!
- Whoo!
Move over.
I'm going to take pictures.
Here. Some sunscreen.
Are you having fun watching her?
- Ling!
- What's up with you?
I have something to tell you.
What? What?
Ouch!
- You're killing me!
- It's okay, Ling.
Guys play like this.
There! There! There!
It's so breezy!
What plans do have for the break?
I'm thinking of going home.
I haven't done so for months.
You're such a mommy's boy.
What about you, Non?
I'm going home too.
You two
have a lot in common.
Artit,
what do you want to
do after graduation?
I want to be
a national rugby player.
You will be.
I'll probably work in Bangkok.
But my parents
want me to take over the business.
As for me,
I want to do anything
that makes a lot of money.
I'm going to use the money
to buy a condo,
a sports car
and eat nice things.
When I go shopping,
I'll buy anything I want.
- How much do I have to earn?
- Kot,
get a job first.
What a killjoy.
Just give me some encouragement.
What about you, Ling?
What do you want to do?
I'm thinking of getting ready.
Ready for what?
It's too soon to tell.
What is this?
Why are you being secretive?
Just tell us already.
I thinking of doing
a Master's degree.
I looking for a university.
You're so hard-working.
I thinking of doing a Master's too.
Have you decided on where to go?
So we can be at the same place.
I'm thinking of somewhere
that's close to Mom.
England?
I think there are
a lot of good universities here too.
Mom's worried
that I live here alone.
A foreign country seems nice too.
I might get
to marry a Caucasian guy.
My children will be good-looking.
Ha-ha!
That's not funny.
Hey!
Of course it's funny.
It's a Caucasian guy. Do you know
why their eyes are so big?
- Why?
Do you see
how they greet each other?
It's like "hello!"
Their eyes are so big and lopsided.
How long are you two
going to hide it?
Hide what?
What are you talking about?
You like Ling.
You like Ling too.
I know our group's rule
is no hitting on friends.
But since things have come this far,
you have to accept it.
Just tell Ling that you like her.
If she rejects either of you,
then that one has to accept it
and move on.
You heard her.
She'd like a foreign boyfriend.
She's probably
not interested in any of us.
If you already know,
then just get over her. Enough.
Don't drag it out. Understand?
Don't say it if you can't do it.
Oh? You're not going
to say anything?
I'm so irritated with you two.
If you let this feeling
overwhelm you,
in the end
you won't be able to control it.
And the person who suffers the most
will be you.
What would you do if you were us?
If it's me?
I'll tell her how I feel.
I'll tell her I like her.
If she rejects me,
I'll be happy that I've told her.
We're going to graduate
in a few years.
We'll have to go our separate ways.
Just hurry up and say it.
Time is short.
Aueng and Jaem are home!
Hold on.
I think you should stop shouting.
It seems that no one's home.
It looks like
the house is abandoned.
Oh?
It does look like
the house is abandoned.
What happened, Aueng?
What about Miss Paeng? Where is she?
Where is she?
Paeng,
have some congee. It's still warm.
I'm not hungry.
But if you don't eat anything,
you'll fall ill.
That's good.
So I'll die and I can be
with my parents.
But I don't think
your parents would want that.
They'd want you
to grow up happily.
Happiness?
My happiness was gone
the day they died.
I'll put the bowl right here.
Just eat a little bit.
Please don't make me worry, okay?
What?
Look at her!
She dumped all
the congee Madam made.
Why are you so loud?
She might hear you.
Who cares? I don't.
I understand it's hard
to get over your parents' death.
But she doesn't have to act up and
make people worry about her.
- Do you understand?
- I do.
She's having problems.
Just leave her alone.
I feel bad for Madam. She has to go
through troubles because of her.
She probably hasn't had
enough time to process it.
Have some sympathy for her.
She's just a kid.
She won't cause us any problems.
Wait and see.
Someday she'll show her true colors.
She wouldn't eat as always.
I don't think we can keep this up.
If we let this continue,
- I'm afraid she might...
- I understand.
I'm trying to find
a way to help her.
But I don't know what to do.
Hello?
Are you Mr. Krongprateep?
It's Aueng. I used to work for
Mr. Tharathep.
Paeng,
someone's here to see you.
- Little Miss!
Aueng! Jaem!
Little Miss!
I've missed you.
How are you?
I'm really sorry.
I just learned
about Master and Madam.
It's okay. I understand.
But it's really strange.
Before he passed,
he told you and me to go home.
After that, they both died
in a car crash.
A car crash?
By the way,
are you hungry?
We'll cook something for you.
No. No.
- You're so skinny.
- That's too much.
It's true.
Her arms and mine
are like chicken legs and pig legs.
You're smiling now. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy
that you both are here.
There, there. Don't cry now.
There is much less stuff
compared to Miss Paeng's house.
That's true.
And here there's only...
Hey! Who are you two?
What's this? Are you stealing?
I'm not stealing.
I'm just looking for something
to cook for Little Miss.
Little Miss?
Miss Paeng.
Isn't she a burden enough?
Now she's bringing her people too?
Aueng, don't.
We're just guests here.
You know you're just guests.
Then don't touch things
as if you own them.
How much are all of these?
I'll pay you.
I don't want money.
Then what do you want?
I want you both out of here.
I'm not going to stand
that mouth of yours anymore.
- There!
- Aueng!
You ugly toad!
- Duang! Don't!
- You're the ugly one!
Today I'm going to
cut your tongue out!
What is this? What's going on?
Good. You're here. Stop them.
Calm down! Stop!
You toad!
Master! Master!
Master!
- What's the matter, Saeb?
- We have a problem.
Hey, why are you standing there?
Stop the girl!
- And why didn't you?
- Can't you see that I can't?
If you can't, how can I?
You want it?
- You want it?
- This way, Master.
Stop! I said stop!
She started it, sir.
You started it. I was going to
cook for Miss Paeng.
But this is my kitchen.
I don't anyone to touch my stuff.
It'll get messed up.
If this is your kitchen,
then I can't come in?
I didn't mean that.
Keep this in mind.
This kitchen doesn't
belong to anyone.
Also remember that from now on,
Jaem and Aueng will be living here.
So they can take care of Paeng.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Here's some shrimp fried rice.
Aueng, what happened to your face?
Oh. She was clumsy.
She fell and hit her face.
That's right. I was clumsy.
It's nothing.
Aueng, don't lie to me.
This is a handprint
Who did this to you?
No one!
It's obviously a handprint.
Was it the maids here?
It's just nonsense.
I won't accept this.
I'm not going to let this go!
- Little Miss!
- Please don't!
Just forget it, Little Miss!
I know they don't like me.
But they have no right
to hurt my people.
Please don't go. I'm begging you.
We're just guests.
Well, I...
I didn't mean that.
It's okay. I understand.
Thank you for reminding me.
I forgot that we don't
have a home anymore.
Can you help me?
I just moved to Thailand.
And I really need help.
I can't find my classroom.
Can you help me?
Hey! Do you hear me?
Or you don't
understand what I'm saying?
Oh! I'm glad we're taking
the same class.
Oh,
really?
You understand me.
Yes, of course.
Okay. Come with me.
Ling.
Should we go on a stroll?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Ling asked me to come on a stroll.
Did she ask you too?
She didn't.
I asked her.
Kot's disappeared.
He's probably busy with some girls.
I was going to ask him on a stroll.
Did you ask everyone on a stroll?
It's fun when there's
a lot of people.
Come on.
Ling,
have you ever thought
of having a boyfriend?
I don't know.
I haven't thought about it.
Ling, what do you think
if a friend changes his status
into a boyfriend.
Hey. I don't think it's good.
You might lose a friend.
It might not turn out
that way for everyone.
It's not fair for an opportunity
to be taken away.
But I think it's good as it is now.
What do you think, Ling?
Do you agree?
What you said is true.
If you become a couple,
you might lose a friend
when you break up.
- What were you saying?
- What about you?
Ling.
RIght. You're right.
Ling, what do you think
if a friend changes his status
into a boyfriend.
Hey. I don't think it's good.
You might lose a friend.
Hello, Professor.
Chiratchaya, tell Thanon that
he can't just focus only on rugby.
He might not graduate.
He hasn't resubmitted the work
he's supposed to redo.
This is his final year.
Okay, Professor.
Thongkhum and I aren't
going to complain
if they're going to use the kitchen.
But we'd like them to be neat.
Thongkhum is very old
and she has to clean up after them.
You're telling me this.
What do you want me to do?
I'd like you to
tell Miss Paeng's people
that they have to tell us first
before they come in to do anything
so there'll be no problem.
Actually, who's the one
who got problems?
My people didn't start the fight.
But it's your people who did.
That's not true.
Aueng slapped me first.
If it wasn't because of your mouth,
Aueng wouldn't have done that.
Paeng! Why did you say that?
I'm always like this.
You just didn't know it.
I know that's what you're like.
But you have to be considerate.
Duang is older than you.
So what? Do I have to bow to her?
Wanfahmai! You've gone too far.
Who taught you to
be this ill-mannered?
Probably no one
- because her parents are dead!
- Right.
Oh, dear!
Stop, Wanfamai!
I'm standing right here!
Be considerate!
- Are you okay, Duang?
- I got it right in the face.
Paeng slapped Duang?
Isn't that a surprise?
I didn't expect her
to be this ill-behaved.
But I don't think she's going to
do anything without reasons.
That's right.
Duang said something
she doesn't like.
See?
But isn't it too far to
do it in front of me?
Whoo!
Mom, Dad, I'm home!
Oh,
aren't you glad?
I'm back.
Oh, we're glad.
Of course we are.
What now?
Artit.
What are you so angry about?
Paeng.
Hold on, Paeng.
Paeng!
You're going to
scold me, aren't you?
You're always like this.
I haven't said anything but
you're already acting out.
I just want to ask you something.
Are you ready to talk?
First of all, I just found out
about what happened to your family.
It's okay.
Your dad told me you had
to study for exams.
How are you doing now?
I'm sorry
for not being by your side
when it happened.
I'm really sorry.
Well,
is there anything else
you'd like to tell me?
I asked Paeng about yesterday.
They're both in the wrong. But
our people started it first.
As I expected,
Paeng's not someone
who starts fights first.
Fine.
How can you be sure
that she wasn't lying?
Well,
as long as I know her,
she's very direct.
She can't hide her emotions at all.
She can't lie.
If you insist,
then I have to believe you.
But for today,
she's completely at fault.
She knows that.
That's why she wants
to apologize to you.
Paeng.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry for saying things and
behaving badly in front of you.
Forgive her.
She's already apologizing.
Fine.
I forgive you.
Since this is
your first time misbehaving.
Thank you.
Non!
You're glad that I'm back?
If you're back,
then that means Artit is back too,
right?
You only think about guys.
I'm so sad.
Don't be sad.
Or you'll go bald and no one
will want to marry you.
You're going to be a spinster
because of yourself.
I'm not going to be a spinster.
Are you crazy?
What about Mom and Dad?
Dad's not here.
Mom's not here either.
Anyway, stay home for me.
Hey, hey! Where are you going?
I'm going to see Artit.
Hey! Stop!
- Let me go!
- You little...
- SIt down.
You're embarrassing me
running after guys like this.
Is she really in such bad shape?
She still needs
to see a psychiatrist.
She wouldn't eat either.
What should we do, Dad?
I try to find something
for her to do,
like books and movies.
But she doesn't want to do anything.
We're here.
Let's go.
Here.
What's this?
I brought you to dig some dirt.
Look at your face.
I forgot. Little Miss probably
doesn't know how.
I'm going to plant some new seeds.
But you don't have to help me.
I can do it myself.
What are you planting?
If you want to know,
you have to help me.
Do it like this.
Stab it like this.
Pull it up.
Mr. Artit!
Saeb's here to help! Move away, sir.
Come on, Mr. Artit.
Leave the digging to me.
- Saeb.
- I'm working.
Just tell me whatever you need, sir.
I guess you want to get fired.
What did I do wrong?
I was working.
Who ordered you to?
It might be bad timing.
Correct.
I guess you just want
to be alone together?
If Saeb knows,
the whole world knows.
Saeb!
Come on. Are you ready?
Paeng,
that's enough for now.
Go and sit over there.
Sit over there.
What are you doing?
Your hair's all messy.
I'll tie it up again.
Your hair's quite thick.
Turn around.
Okay.
Better.
Here's your reward.
What is it?
We're going to plant the seeds.
In a few months,
they'll all blossom beautifully.
What flower is this?
You have to wait and see.
It will take a long time.
It's not that long.
We have to take care
of them every day.
If you have to do that,
can you handle it?
That's all? Can we plant them now?
Hold on.
We have to keep
digging up the dirt first.
But are you hungry now?
I'm hungry too.
Pong, I was just helping.
If it's you, are you going
to shoo me away?
- I won't.
- See?
Something's going on.
A guy wants to be alone with a girl.
What does that mean?
We all know it.
You have such a big mouth.
No one's going to call you a mute
if you don't say anything.
Little Miss is only a child.
If you talk too much,
it's bad for Mr. Artit's image.
You call her a child?
See? Look at Jook.
She got married at 16, got pregnant
at 17 and gave birth at 18.
- It's not the same.
- I'm sure!
- Sure of what?
- I'm sure that they'll be together.
Oh, hey!
Where are you going?
I'm not done yet.
That's not all, Pong.
He helped tie up her hair too.
When he's done,
he bent down
so low they're almost kissing.
He bent down this low.
That low?
- Try looking up.
- What for?
I have nothing to do with him.
Is he?
- He is.
- I am.
Hold on, Saeb.
Keep eating. Finish it up.
Paeng, sit down.
Take it easy, Saeb.
You can have another serving
if you're not full yet.
You probably won't be
earning any more salaries.
I'm full already.
Saeb, no need to be so shocked.
Mr. Artit was just messing with you.
Don't be shocked.
It's only going to be
for three months maximum
or maybe six.
- What do you mean, Pong?
- You don't really know?
- I don't.
- Salary deduction.
That's a good idea.
Mr. Artit, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Please forgive me.
- Keep eating.
- I'm full.
- You're full already.
- Yes, sir.
Don't go anywhere. Just sit here.
Little Miss,
how is it going to be delicious
with those small bites?
You have to take
a huge bite like this.
Yum!
Little Miss, you have to say
"yum" too.
Paeng, take it slow.
You might choke.
Yum!
Get her some water.
- Okay, sir.
- Hey, hey, hey.
I was getting water.
- Just sit here. Aren't you eating?
- I'm full, sir.
All done.
No.
We're not done yet. You have to
take good care of them.
Because their lives
depend on you now.
You have to fertilize them,
loosening the soil, water them
and weed them.
If you take good care of them,
they'll be happy.
And they'll grow
strong and beautiful.
Here.
(Wanfahmai's flower bed)
Wanfahmai's flower bed.
I want you to be happy
and grow up beautifully.
From now on,
this is your home.
Everyone here is your family.
You're not alone anymore.
I'll put this down for you.
Wait for them to grow, okay?
Okay.
- Are they clean now?
- Yes.
Good.
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
It doesn't, but it's a bit red.
Let me have a look.
Just a little bit red.
It's okay.
But why are your wrists so small?
You're too skinny.
I have to fatten you up some more.
I'm not skinny. You're just fat
- Who are you calling fat?
- You.
- I'm fat?
- Your cheeks are so chubby.
- Look at yourself.
- No!
Artit!
I baked you something.
Have a taste. They're very good.
Of course.
- Thanks so much, Nang.
- You're welcome.
Actually, you two
are around the same age.
You could be friends.
From now on, Paeng will live
and study here.
In two days, Dad will take her to
apply at a school.
If you meet her,
please take care of her.
Sure. You can trust me
with taking care of things.
Paeng,
we'll be closer now.
If there's anything I can help,
you can tell me.
Thank you, Nang.
Please take care of me, then.
My pleasure.
Hey, hey! Nang!
Who stepped on your tail?
Are you crazy?
I'm a human, not a dog.
Why didn't you tell me that
she's moving into Artit's place?
She's going to study here too.
Did you go to see Artit again?
And who were you talking about?
That girl, Paeng.
Oh?
She moved here?
Artit didn't tell me.
- I don't want it! I don't want it!
- Hey, hey!
- What don't you want?
- Go away!
Paeng,
let's meet at around 8 p.m.
There's a meteor shower tonight.
Let's go and watch.
I'll hurry downstairs
and wait for you.
- Artit.
- Yes, Dad?
Where did you take her?
Just around our farm.
But tonight I'm taking her
to watch a meteor shower.
That's good.
Have you two eaten?
We've eaten a lot.
Paeng is so stuffed.
Do you know
since you came back
she cheered up a lot?
I'm relieved to see that.
Stay with her
during the break, okay?
Once semester starts, it'll be good
if you can come on the weekends.
Of course, Dad. Easy enough.
- I'm going to take a shower.
- Go on.
The atmosphere is so nice.
Wow! What a beautiful sight.
Missy, why are you
standing there alone?
Whoa!
You're Aueng,
the pretty girl from Bangkok.
Oh, don't say that!
Aueng, do you want to watch
the meteor shower with me?
I can't.
Jaem's very protective of me.
I have to wait for Miss Paeng too.
But she called and told me
to go ahead.
She's not free right now.
Wow!
Whoa!
Meow?
Aueng, my darling. Wait for me.
Come on.
Here. Be careful.
I see. Now I know
why I didn't see you, Aueng.
I came to prepare things for you.
Sir, I've prepared mosquito nets,
pillows and blankets for you.
SIr, do you want to drink with us?
It's okay. Feel free to relax.
But don't drink too much.
You have work tomorrow.
Aueng, would you like to drink?
I know you want me to get drunk.
Just to warm you up.
Just a little bit, then.
Miss Paeng, can I go join them
over there?
Do you even have to ask me?
She said yes.
The grilled pork smells nice.
Can I sit with you?
- This way.
- Do you want to sit over there?
I can see so many stars here.
They're so beautiful.
There's no light pollution here
so we can see so many stars.
Paeng,
try laying down.
What?
Lay down. So you won't sprain
your neck looking up.
That's true.
Let's get started with astronomy
from the ground up.
Do you see those constellations?
With the tail there, see?
That line.
That line coming down.
I see it now.
Hurray! A shooting star!
Wow!
They really are shooting stars!
Make a wish.
I wish that I can
stay with Artit forever.
I wish that Ling accepts my love.
Another one. There.
Hurray!
- So many of them, Artit!
- It'll be a while.
Why are you smiling, Miss Paeng?
You reek of alcohol.
Come on, Miss Paeng!
By the way, why are you smiling?
The corner of your lips almost
reach your ears.
Really?
Really.
Confess to me now.
It's only a meteor shower.
Why are you this gleeful?
Was it that enjoyable?
What?
See?
You're blushing?
I was just teasing you.
Oh! Or maybe
are you thinking about Mr. Artit?
I wasn't.
How can I do that?
He's like a brother to me.
A brother it is then.
But it'd be nice if you two
can get together.
If it's you,
I'll step aside.
You're laughing to cover it up.
- Aueng!
- You're all red.
Mr. Artit brought a girl to watch
the meteor shower? Who?
Who do you think? Someone familiar.
It's Miss Paeng.
It's not an ordinary relationship.
Soon enough,
we might have
a new madam of the farm.
It's not true. How is that possible?
And how is it not possible?
Why is Miss Paeng staying
here permanently
all of a sudden?
It's because Master
and Madam
want her to marry Mr. Artit.
I'm sure of it.
Bad news this early morning.
Huh? What did you say?
Saeb told me Miss Paeng moved here
to marry Mr. Artit. Is that true?
That's not true, right?
Please don't be quiet.
Say something.
Say it, Madam. Don't be quiet.
It's upsetting.
Stop!
I'm about to say it.
Okay, Madam.
You're assuming things.
There's not going to
be anything of that sort.
Are you for real, Madam?
Are you calling me a liar?
No, Madam. It's not like that.
I'm just confirming it
for everyone's sake.
I think if Mr. Artit is
going to marry someone,
he deserves someone better.
What's bad about Paeng?
I didn't mean that.
Miss Paeng is good too.
But I think she's still very young.
Hurry up and tell everyone
to stop talking about this.
Don't let me hear any more of this.
Right away, Madam.
I'll do that right now.
How did they come up with that?
Such perverts.
Miss Paeng moved here
to marry Mr. Artit. Is that true?
I know
what's my happiness now.
Dad?
The girl I love is you, Ling.
Artit is mine.
Stay away from him.
Paeng!
- I can be even crazier than this.
- Stop this right now.
It hurts! Let me go, Artit!
I decided to let Artit
get engaged to Paeng
not because of the debt.
I will never marry Paeng.
You have to be mine and only mine!
Get away!
Artit! Artit!