(My Forever Sunshine)
They're doing that on purpose.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
You haven't changed.
If you knew what I lost,
you wouldn't have
said that stupid apology.
Keep your head down
and accept your fate.
You've done a lot to them.
Get your filthy hands off me!
Your place is right there.
I locked her up.
I'm thinking of
leaving her for a couple of days.
What if she actually dies?
What are you going to do?
There's not going to be a day
that you forgive me, is there?
If you were me, would you be able to
put up with being like this?
Both my dreams and my future
are ruined.
Everything I'd accomplished was
ruined because of you!
I almost became handicapped.
Almost handicapped?
You're not handicapped?
But I almost died because of you.
What are you afraid of?
I thought you said you were going
to make amends for what you did?
You've gone crazy.
That's right.
I will get even crazier
if you stay here.
What are you doing?
You came in yourself.
You locked the door yourself.
Stay and talk then.
I'm here to officially welcome you,
Wanfahmai.
This is your last chance. Go.
Artit, you've gone too far.
How have I gone too far?
What happened to you,
I didn't mean it.
But everything you did to me
was deliberate.
It's very different.
I'm already this harsh
but you're still stubborn.
How harsh should I be
so you'll leave?
Where's your car key?
Instead of bringing a phone.
Jeez!
Paeng!
I asked you where your car key is.
Uhh...
In the storage room.
Darn it!
Should I just choke you to death?
What's going on?
So? Who's going to start?
Hello.
Saeb, you then.
Tell me what's happened
when I wasn't here.
Why me, sir?
Can I leave?
But we've made an agreement.
You heard him, Artit?
If you can change Uncle's mind,
I'll leave immediately.
What's really going on here?
Artit,
did you try to chase her out?
Artit had someone train me.
Harvesting grapes. weeding,
making wood vinegar,
burning charcoal,
cleaning the cattle pen.
I think it was too tough.
So I don't want to stay.
Artit, didn't I tell you
to just let her do her work?
Now, what did you make her do?
Even though you had to
harvest grapes or weed,
it's not in your nature to give up.
So what really happened?
I don't want her to stay.
If my return is causing problems,
please let me go.
So everyone here will be happy.
Now you're just trying to be nice.
You're just playing the victim.
If you go,
I won't be happy.
So you have to stay.
Okay.
Then I'll go.
Artit.
- Where are you going?
- Don't.
I'll handle him.
Dad!
I'm sorry.
Artit,
I'm begging you
to give Paeng a chance.
Give her a chance?
Maybe next time,
I'll end up handicapped or die?
But if you can overcome
your pride a little,
you'll see that she's not
the same person anymore.
You're probably blind.
That's why you can't see.
Then prove to me
that she hasn't changed.
But I think she has changed.
Let time prove it.
Prove who's correct.
Why should I do that?
Don't try to convince me.
If you go,
then I have to take care of
the farm like before.
I'm already old.
Aren't you worried about me?
You can let your
darling niece take care of things.
If you think so, then go.
But I don't know
what you've done either.
Because I let you be
for so many years.
Anyway,
I'll try to take care of the farm.
Are you choosing her?
Why don't you choose me?
I told you
that you're prejudiced.
You're full of pride.
Alright. Maybe if I let
you go for a few days,
you'll calm down a bit.
You'll realize it and come back.
I know you won't leave
what you've built here,
right?
But it's better
if you don't go.
Think of it as
you giving me a chance.
I asking you.
Okay, Dad.
But she and I will
go our separate ways.
Don't let her approach me.
Tubtim.
- Thongkhum.
- Yes?
There's really
one downside to Artit.
Do you know what it is?
What, Madam?
Ever since he was young,
he has never defied his parents.
I probably raised him too well.
But from now on, I have to teach him
that he doesn't have to listen
to everything his parents say.
Paeng, I'm sorry for lying to you.
It's okay, Saeb. I understand.
But don't ever let
that happen again?
I'm only joking.
My heart felt heavy
for a moment there.
Paeng,
please wait here for a bit.
I'll go and get some stuff.
Then I'll give you a lift home.
I'm already this harsh
but you're still stubborn.
How harsh should I be
so you'll leave?
Such an everlasting grudge, Artit.
Were you Chucky in your past life?
That number plate.
This is it. It's the same vehicle.
- Saeb.
- Yes, Paeng?
Whose truck is this?
It's Artit's.
Why are you asking?
Artit's car.
They're doing that on purpose.
What on earth is going on?
Apart from Artit,
who drives it?
No one.
This is Artit's most
beloved possession.
He's the only one who can drive it.
But why is it parked here
when it's his?
I saw him drove it out
three days ago.
The day you came.
He was driving so fast,
there was dust all over.
I just washed it for him.
It's all shiny now.
Then he told me to park it here.
Most importantly, he said to
keep everyone away from it.
You're so evil, Artit.
What did you say?
Oh, nothing.
Uncle?
Did you just get to shower?
Yes.
Are you really going to live here?
I think you should
go back to my house
and stay in your old room.
In the same house as Artit?
I don't think so. I don't want
to cut my life short.
Are you still angry with him?
I have no right to
be angry with him.
I have to apologize
on behalf of him and Auntie.
I shouldn't have
gone to see the client.
If I'd know I...
Uncle,
if you can see the future,
you have to open up
an astrological shop
or a live telephone hotline.
Cheeky.
I'd like everyone to get to know you
and see you as I do.
It's okay.
No one needs to see me.
Only you seeing me is fine already.
Hey!
Are you going to crack
the chopping board?
Why are you taking it out
on the pork?
I'm so annoyed.
Master sided with her again.
It's always been like this.
That's why Mr. Artit
was in an accident.
I don't understand why
he hasn't learned his lesson.
You're this angry.
Do you know how angry Madam must be?
Whatever. I'm on Madam
and Mr. Artit's side.
We have to find a way
to kick that rotten Paeng out.
Just you wait!
Hey!
All minced up!
Mom,
what are you doing?
Tonight Dad has to sleep outside
for siding with her.
Mom, calm down.
Don't do this.
I know you're angry.
I'm angry too.
But we shouldn't fight
amongst each other.
What do you want me to do?
I'm so angry!
Be patient, Mom.
I'll deal with Paeng myself.
But you must stop fighting with Dad.
We can't let Paeng
have the satisfaction
that she has successfully
created a rift between us.
Alright.
I'll try.
How much longer do I
have to keep seeing her face?
Dad told me to prove it to him.
I'll do it.
I'll make him see
who his darling niece really is.
Paeng, what do you
think if this land?
It's quite nice.
What are you planning to do?
I'm going to give it to you.
Come again?
I'd like to you plant a rose garden,
just like you wanted to.
So you can finally
follow your dreams
without having to
be involved with Artit.
Do you trust me?
What if I failed?
I thought you said you wanted me
to learn the ropes a lot first.
You can learn by doing.
I'll be your consultant.
It's better for trial and error that
you do it here, am I right?
And if you're successful
with the project,
I'll give you this
whole plot of land.
You can't do that, Uncle.
If you do that,
Artit will kill me.
- Paeng...
- Uncle,
don't talk about the debt.
It ended a long time ago.
Actually, I owe you right now.
If you didn't look after me,
who knows where I'd be.
I've survived this long
because of you.
So you don't want it?
No, it's okay.
Then you work for me.
I don't think there's
a problem with that.
Think of
what you want to do with the land.
How many farmhands you'll need,
and what's your budget.
From now on,
consider yourself my employee.
You work for me, is that okay?
Okay, then.
That's my girl.
Careful, careful.
Oh.
Pong! Saeb!
- Yes, sir?
- Yes?
Come on.
Quickly now.
From now on, Paeng's working for me.
Tell everyone
to help her with work.
- Yes, Sir.
You can go now.
Let's go.
Very good.
Miss Paeng!
I bring you over some assistants.
Thank you.
We've met but I don't
know your names yet.
I'm Kaew.
I'm Aod.
Miss Paeng,
please don't be angry about today.
I understand.
If I did anything wrong,
please don't be angry with me.
It was Artit's order,
so I had to follow it.
But you haven't done anything wrong.
By the way, what do you
want me to help?
That's right.
I'd like you to collect
some dirt samples
to be checked for minerals
and the pH value,
to see whether
it's suitable to grow roses.
Here.
- Go on.
- Okay.
- Dig it up.
- Help her.
Here you go.
- One for each of us.
- Here.
Saeb, please drop this in the mail.
Right away.
Let's go.
Oh? Whoa.
It's already 11:00 p.m.?
When did I fell asleep?
My stomach's grumbling.
So hungry.
Good thing I bought
something to eat.
What?
Where's all the food?
If I did anything wrong,
please don't be angry with me.
It was Artit's order,
so I had to follow it.
You stole it?
I'll reclaim it then.
Hungry are you?
Just die of hunger right there.
Oh, Mom.
I knew you're still working.
It's late. Have a shower and rest.
Okay.
It's all gone.
Where is it hidden?
I feel like a burglar.
I'm hungry!
Gosh! I can't take it anymore!
I'm sorry. I really don't
want to do this!
But I really can't
handle this hunger!
Excuse me, Uncle and Auntie.
I've survived!
Oh, shoot!
Oh!
Now can you tell me
why you came in here?
I asked you a question.
Are you deaf?
I was only looking
for something to eat.
If you're going to lie,
try harder then.
You're always concocting something.
Do you think that you can forget
all the evil deeds you've done
and other people
will forget them too?
I really want to know
what your face is made of.
That's why you dare
to set foot in here again.
I'm not lying.
I'm just hungry. So I'm looking
for something to eat.
Because someone's
being a snake in the grass.
They threw out all my food.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
have set foot here.
You!
Whoa.
His arms are really buff.
I'll definitely die if he chokes me.
Sicko!
You're staring at me, aren't you?
I didn't mean it.
Do you
still dare to have feelings for me?
Artit, don't flatter yourself.
A shirtless guy won't make
me feel anything.
I've seen a lot already.
That's right.
For a greedy woman like you,
I don't think it's that surprising.
Artit, if I'm such an eyesore,
I'll be gone now.
Wench.
Artit, I'm only looking
for something to eat.
Do you really have
to call me a wench?
I think it's a little too harsh.
I wasn't referring to this.
I'm talking about six years ago.
Hey,
what I've been doing to you isn't
even harsh enough.
You're lucky that I haven't
murdered you yet.
Isn't your dad's inheritance
enough for you to start a new life?
Or did you spend it all up?
Or do you want something
else from here
that isn't money?
And what is that?
Even if I don't say it,
you probably already know.
I won't make my mouth filthy
by saying it.
If you don't want to, then don't.
If there's nothing else,
I'm going now.
Whoa!
Saeb! Why did you creep up on me?
You startled me.
Miss Paeng,
you had your earphones on.
I was calling but you
didn't hear me. So I had to do this.
What's the matter?
Master told me to bring you
to go eat at the house.
It's okay. I'll eat here.
If I go,
your boss Artit
will have my head instead of food.
Miss Paeng!
My boss isn't a zombie.
Please go.
If you don't, I'll be
reprimanded for sure.
Please, Miss Paeng?
Please? Please, go?
You don't have to
eat that. I'll help you.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Oh, Paeng. Come here.
Come.
You invited her?
Tubtim,
she's only here to eat.
For you, that's all it is.
But for me,
honestly,
I have no appetite anymore.
I think I'll go back
and eat at home.
- Good.
- Don't go.
Paeng,
come here. Sit down.
Come on. Have a seat.
Quickly.
Very good.
From now on,
you have to come
and eat with me every day.
Huh? Teep!
If she comes,
I won't eat.
You can eat with your darling niece,
just the two of you.
Mom,
please don't do that.
This is our house,
why do we have to leave?
The person who should go
is the outsider.
Artit, talk nicely to her.
I'm asking you.
I've also asked you
to not let this woman
come close to me.
Last night, your darling niece
sneaked into our house.
Huh?
What were you planning to
do to my son?
You've only just arrived.
Your true colors are
already showing?
It's not like that, Auntie.
Why did you have to
come in late at night?
Don't ask for the truth from a liar.
It's easier to just kick her out.
Artit.
Last night, I came here
because I was hungry.
So I was looking
for something to eat.
Don't try to put on an act.
I know it.
It's been six years
and your tongue has gotten
sharper than a woman's.
Or maybe you are...
What am I?
Uncle,
I really came here
to find something to eat.
Maybe I was wrong
for coming in unannounced.
But there's nothing more to do.
You're the best at making excuses.
Your second-best is
minimizing your own fault.
Artit, that's enough.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm not going to eat today.
I don't have an appetite.
I don't have one either.
Oh?
See, Uncle?
It's because of me.
I'm such a killjoy.
Don't mind them.
They're just not used to it.
You have to eat with me every day
so that they'll get used to it.
Alright, let's eat.
Eat up. It's only me now.
Eat with me.
Pong!
Where is he?
Mr. Artit.
How was breakfast?
What's up with you?
Miss Paeng went to
eat breakfast with you.
So I figured that
breakfast must've been
even more delicious.
It was.
It was delicious to the point
that I want to kick you.
Calm down, sir.
It's still early.
Don't be angry yet.
Where's Pong?
Oh? You don't know?
Know what?
Your lips are quivering.
Tell me what you know.
Here I'll put some rose beds.
Over there
I'll have a nursery for seedlings.
There, it's going to be an office
and a research lab
for rose products.
Wow.
You came up with all of this
in a day?
I already had these ideas.
I just made a sketch of them.
By the way,
do you know any contractors?
So I can start with my rose garden.
What's the hurry?
You can rest a little bit.
No rest for the wicked.
I'd like to get going with it.
So you can leave?
I have to go over there now.
Artit might see me
and I'll be in trouble.
Get on with it.
Are you in a hurry to leave
because of Artit?
Partially.
But I don't want to
bother you any more.
You keep saying that.
It's like I'm a stranger to you.
I'm feeling sad now.
Uncle, please don't be upset.
If you are, I'll be dead for sure.
I only have you left.
Okay.
I'll look it over again tonight.
But at a glance,
it looks really great.
You're talented.
Thank you!
Paeng,
I'm very happy
that you came back here.
No matter what anyone says,
please think of this place
as your home.
I'll try.
I have something to give you.
You're giving this to me?
Yes.
It's for you to ride
around on the farm.
So you won't be tired from walking.
Do you know how to ride it?
I don't think it's too difficult.
Thank you.
So lovely.
Ma'am,
how long does it take before
the grapes can be harvested?
She seems promiscuous
judging from her face
- Are you talking about me?
- No.
Then why are you looking at me?
You're overthinking it.
I wasn't looking at you.
I was looking at the grapes.
Then stop looking
and get back to work.
Or do you want me to tell my uncle
that his workers are gossiping
and slacking off at work?
It's you who has to leave.
I haven't even done anything.
Those two were gossiping about me.
No one would believe
a girl who cried wolf like you.
And I'm not stupid.
Most importantly,
even if they were gossiping,
it wouldn't have been that
far from the truth.
Okay, then.
You can insult, slander, or gossip
about me as much as you like.
I don't care
because I'm not like what you said.
- Keep working.
- Yes.
How much do you want?
I asked how much you want
so that you will leave this place.
I have money.
You're very rich, aren't you?
You probably want to disappear
from here mysteriously.
I'm telling you
that I can make that happen.
If you can't contact me
for more than three days,
go and look for my corpse
here.
My corpse should be buried there
because it's the back of the farm.
What?
Scared?
If you stay,
I'll scare you even more.
Keep your guard up.
Should I cut off your arms,
your legs,
skin you,
or cut off your head first?
Go!
Oh, Dad?
Can you take a look a these plans
and see if they're okay?
Here.
From that woman?
A nursery for roses.
She drew it up herself.
If you're looking for something
for her to do to kill time,
or to keep her here,
you should keep it small.
This is too big.
It will cost a fortune.
I'd like her
to use this time to learn
and get the most out of it.
But it takes time
for a plan this big.
Or are you thinking about that?
About arranging
your marriage together?
I've stopped thinking
about that for a while already.
Do you think
I love my niece
more than my own son?
Since you're really against it, to
the point you risked your own life,
I'm not going to force you.
It's not your responsibility either,
to have to repay for someone's
gratitude in my place.
Thank you, Dad.
But I have to let Paeng stay here
no matter what.
Until there's someone who can
look after her better than me.
Tharathep
asked me two things.
I already broke one promise,
that is the one about you.
Don't make me break another.
Please help me look at it.
So I can talk to her
about the contractors tomorrow.
I don't want to be a part of this.
You don't trust me?
I trust you.
But I don't trust her.
About what?
That she wants to be my wife.
Dad, It's not funny.
I really mean it.
Artit,
humans must learn to adapt.
If Paeng
is willing to adapt, change herself,
and become a different person,
all of us should forgive her.
Forgiveness
is a great merit.
Don't you agree, Artit?
If you're afraid
of Paeng clinging to you again,
you should look for someone
and get married, no?
Who?
You saw it. I spend
my days with the trees.
Ling.
She's still single, isn't she?
Ling
is my friend.
We really are friends.
Ling is here.
- Hello.
Did everything go okay
when I wasn't here?
- Okay.
Did Korakot help with
looking after the shop?
We haven't seen him at all.
Thank you so much.
You can get back to work now.
No need to take care of me.
Okay.
Hello?
What's the matter, Ling?
I've really missed you!
How are you? I haven't seen you
since you got back from England.
Hold on. Hold on.
My ears are going to explode.
Tone it down.
The thing is, I wasn't there
to supervise the shop
because I'm working with Mahan
on a big business deal.
If I can successfully import
the goods from China this time,
you can start calling me Boss Kot.
Okay, okay.
Alright. I'll see you at the shop.
Later.
You're still the same, Ling.
If you could've come out
of the phone,
you would've done it.
What a complainer.
Kot!
Oh!
Nang, honey!
Don't you honey me.
Oh?
- Pay up.
- Do I need to pay up?
This is a resort, not a charity
where you to eat and drink for free.
Look at what you've been eating.
Those are all expensive.
Don't think because you're Non's
friend that you don't have to pay.
I won't let you do this anymore.
You want me to pay up?
Stop right there!
Don't tell me that you
forgot your wallet.
I know what you're playing at.
Nang, you're so lovely.
You know me well.
Let's do this. I've got something
to show you. I present to you the
stress-relief bra.
No, it's a stress-relieving bra.
It makes you feel refreshed like
you're standing on top of the Alps.
Kot! That's pervy!
What's pervy? It's really good.
I have a promotion for you.
Buy three get three
for only 499 baht.
I'm not buying it!
I don't want it!
Pay up!
Alright. I need to go to
the ATM first.
I'm going. I'm going.
- I'm going! I'm going!
- Kot!
Don't run away!
Oh, shoot.
Kot!
I'm not staying here anymore!
Oh, you're done with work?
Well, Mr. Artit said
we can't help you anymore.
If he sees us, he will fire us.
What about Kaew?
Him too. He left already.
I have to go now.
If he sees us, he will fire us.
If you stay,
I'll scare you even more.
Oh, oh! Mister!
- Are you okay?
- Leave me alone!
Is that how you drive?
Don't you use your brakes?
If my face gets ruined,
who's going to take responsibility?
You're such a bad driver.
- Hey?
- Kot!
Paeng!
Since got to the farm, I never
walked over to this area.
I just found out it exists.
This zone is for shops
and outdoor activities.
As for this shop, Ling and Artit
started it together.
Ling's here as well?
For almost a year now.
She came back from England.
If she sees you,
she'll be very happy.
This way. Please come back again.
Please come back again.
Ling, hello.
Ling,
I'd like to apologize for what
happened in the past.
Are you happy to see me?
I'm very happy!
Have a seat.
I'm really happy to know
that you're here.
Now I have a friend.
You've faced
Artit's wrath, haven't you?
Well, what do you think?
His wrath was so cruel
I almost couldn't handle it.
But it's understandable.
What I did is unforgivable.
But it's been a while already.
Artit should forget about it.
Ling, but you know what he's like.
It's hard to make him angry,
but once he's angry,
he never gets over it.
He's the type to
hold grudges for ages.
Don't say that.
She might feel disheartened.
Just kidding.
Let's change the subject.
Have you walked around here yet?
Not yet.
The huge expansion
is all Artit's work.
Really? I thought it was Uncle's.
Not at all.
When he had to defer his studies,
he nearly went crazy.
So he used all his time
to develop the farm
because he wanted to forget...
Oops.
I'm sorry for having a big mouth.
Don't listen to Kot.
It's okay.
I know Artit hates me.
He probably won't ever
forgive me in this lifetime.
But I'll try.
I'll try to make him see
that I really want
to atone for my sins.
Why are you applauding?
That was really touching.
If you want me or Kot to help,
you can tell us. No need to worry.
Or if you need anything else,
like a rice cooker, a sauna cabinet,
a frying pan, a fishing sieve,
tom-yum noodles, sweet palm...
Enough, already?
You can tell me. I sell everything.
By the way, do you know
where Artit is right now?
Around this time,
he's probably at the wooden shack
in the back of the farm.
Or you can call it
Artit's safe house.
It's probably this shack.
When was it built?
Saeb!
Yes, sir. I'm here.
Restrain the dog.
Dog?
Where's the dog?
It's you.
Why are you here?
To seduce me?
- No.
- Liar.
You're definitely here to do so.
Why do you have such a
one-track mind?
Wanfahmai!
That's right. Wanfahamai
doesn't want you to be
husband anymore.
Please reprogram your brain.
Remember your own words.
Okay. I'll remember it well.
I'll etch it onto
every cell in my brain.
Don't worry that I'll forget.
I came to see you
because I have a question.
Why won't you allow
Aod and Kaew to help me?
Do you have to ask me that?
It's because I hate you.
I already showed you mercy
by allowing you to be on my farm.
So you shouldn't be using my people.
Kaew and Aod have
their own work to do.
Unlike someone
who's got way too much free time.
I don't have free time.
I still have a lot of things to do.
That lame rose garden?
I've seen the plans.
I can tell you in one word,
lame.
Yes, it's lame.
But I'll improve it.
And I won't use your people anymore.
Good.
Now just get out of here.
Don't worry.
I won't come back here anymore.
Just leave the farm.
So I'll be happy.
I'm not going.
Saeb,
tell our farmhands
to remember that
this woman's dangerous.
They can kill her on sight.
Huh?
Kill her?
Is there going to be a problem
when we try to hide her body?
Who said to really kill her?
Oh?
Get back to work,
Alright, sir.
I'm all alone.
Will I make it?
Aueng!
Perfect timing. I'm hungry.
Find your own food.
This is for Artit.
Don't be so stingy.
Just one piece.
- Hey!
- Oh?
Are you angry with me?
You don't know?
About Paeng?
You're a fool.
Why are you insulting me?
Isn't it true?
I can see she's
concocting something evil.
But you keep trusting her.
You can't discipline
someone like her.
Watch out.
Your pet snake might bite you.
Tubtim, you don't have to
believe it.
But don't forget
that Paeng's an orphan.
She has no one else apart from us.
And the reason why
we didn't have to suffer
is because of her dad's help.
Do you want me to die
and be unable to face my friend?
We've helped a lot of orphans.
Can't we help the family
that helped us?
Don't be so heartless.
Don't ever think that your words
will sway me.
- Ugh.
- Alright.
Gosh! Ling,
why is the coffee so bitter?
You still have feelings.
What are you talking about?
She's trying to say
that you have a black heart,
even towards a little girl.
Oh!
So you met that brat, didn't you?
What? Did the brat tell you that
I bullied her?
Don't call her rude names!
Just a second.
Hello?
The battery's probably dead.
What's up, Non?
Right now?
I'll be right there.
Non wants me to help
carry some stuff. I'll be back.
- Look after my stuff.
- Okay.
And don't fight each other.
When I was overseas,
you called to apologize
for being rude to me.
I forgave you and gave you a chance.
- And why...
- It's not the same.
I was only being rude to you.
But as for that girl,
you know what she did to me.
If you're still fixated on the past,
how is your life supposed to
move forward?
It can.
It's going well, actually.
Don't you see how happy I am?
You're lying to yourself.
Hey,
what's in these boxes?
They're so heavy.
I took our client on a trip
to a mangosteen farm.
The owner was very kind. They
gave us heaps of mangosteens.
Ling's going to throw
a party if she knows.
She's a mangosteen lover.
Hold on.
Did they give them to you?
Or did you intentionally
bring them for her?
Wait up!
Argh.
Thanks very much.
Mmm! Now that's what
I call a coffee.
Non's coming?
Yes.
You got it?
Seriously, Ling.
How long do we have to keep
pretending to be a couple?
I don't know.
I don't understand
why you have to do this.
I have my reasons.
Just keep helping me for now.
Non,
you still can't get over her?
Why should I?
I'm actually happy
to have someone that makes
my world a special place.
Even though she doesn't love me,
seeing her be happy
with the person she loves
makes me happy too.
Don't you think, Kot?
Wise
but heartbreaking.
Wow, with this many mangosteens,
I should make
complementary ice-cream and juice.
Complementary?
Ling, you can earn a lot from those.
Why do you want to make it free?
To show our gratitude
to the customers.
Oh, right!
I agree with you, Ling.
The customers will be impressed.
Right.
Both of you are angels.
You two are so suitable,
don't you think? Non?
I'll help you carry these
over there.
Good.
They're helping each other.
You're overacting. You'd can carry
your own boxes.
Alright.
Okay.
Ling,
what's wrong?
Should you go and rest?
I'll do it myself.
Thanks.
Paeng!
Non!
Here it is.
The research lab is facing west,
you don't mind, don't you?
I don't.
But that direction is very hot.
If it's this direction,
it will in the shade and breezy.
- I have to think of the direction?
- Yes.
But your design is very detailed.
If it's about construction,
you can consult me.
That's true. You run a resort
so you must have
some knowledge about it.
Just a tad.
For this size of a building,
it should take around
four months to finish.
- Just four months?
- Yes.
How long did you
think it would take?
Non, please help me
limit the budget.
Sure. Easy enough.
I love you!
Come on. Don't flatter me.
- Here. Don't forget your pen.
- Thank you.
You couldn't seduce me
so you're seducing my friend?
You can't stand not
having a guy in your life?
Artit, that's too harsh
Non,
I have something to talk
to you about.
Follow me.
Where are we going?
Just under the tamarind tree.
Non,
why are you talking to her?
I was only helping Paeng
with her plans.
Who's your friend? Me or her?
Artit, we're not kids anymore,
fighting each other
and taking sides.
I mean well, that's why
I'm warning you.
Paeng is evil.
If you don't want her to cling
to you, stop fraternizing with her.
I'm only helping with what I can.
If I passed by but didn't help her,
isn't that a little too heartless?
You were seduced, weren't you?
Do you want to end up like me?
It might not be my problem.
What do you mean?
I think Paeng's a lovely person.
If I don't have anyone
and I'm interested in her,
then it shouldn't be a problem.
Non,
you're my friend.
And I love you.
If you get together with her,
you can sever ties with me.
Artit,
what about you getting
together with Ling?
I didn't sever ties with you.
- Non!
- Stop!
I want peace and quiet.
I'm also tired.
Your friend's been acting cheeky
with me too.
I don't want Kot coming here.
He likes to eat without paying.
He's also nosy
and acts like he owns the resort.
I'm not okay with it.
You have to be.
Kot's my friend.
And I don't think he's nosy.
You're the one causing trouble.
Did you forget I'm your sister?
It's because you're my sister
that I have to scold you.
And stop being a self-centered
spoiled girl.
Try to be mature like Paeng.
Paeng?
You mean rotten Paeng?
Why did you mention her?
Nothing. I was just saying.
How was that just a statement
when she's been gone for years?
Did she come back here?
Can you get me some water?
I'm thirsty.
Get going. Be a good sister.
Come on.
No, Paeng came back, didn't she?
- She came back, didn't she?
- Are you trying to kill me?
- I've tweaked the plans.
- Can I have a look?
What do you think?
Wow!
This is good. Much better.
Initially, I was going to say
something as well,
that it seemed a little off.
But I was too busy
so I didn't look at it in detail.
You don't have to worry anymore.
I already have a consultant
for the project.
Who? Can you tell me?
Of course. Non's my consultant.
Non? Artit's friend?
Yes. Non told me that
the building's facing the wrong way.
He said it would be too hot.
So I changed it to be south-facing.
It's still easy to go in and out of
- and it will have a nice breeze.
- Okay.
That's true.
Excellent.
Non is reliable.
If he's got time to look after you,
then I'm happy.
I was too busy worrying about
this demonstration plot
so I forgot about the direction
of the wind for the building.
If I didn't have Non's help,
I'd be stuck in a rut.
But I'm relieved now.
Non also promised me
that he'll help minimize the budget
and supervise the construction.
But Uncle,
we have to keep
this a secret from Artit.
Because if he knows,
he'll accuse me of
stealing his friend.
It's a secret.
Where is she?
I should've dropped by
to ask Auntie first.
Hey, you.
Do you know Paeng?
I do.
Have you seen her?
I haven't.
Where are you going?
I'm not finished.
- Hey, stop.
- Don't follow me. Go away.
What's this?
I said don't follow me.
Why does it stink so much?
It's bio-fermented water.
Did you play a trick on me?
Paeng!
I was asking for you.
Why did you lie to me?
Are you trying to avoid me?
When did you ask for me?
Just now, you said,
have you seen her?
I thought you were asking
about someone else.
Paeng, you still have a sharp
tongue after all these years.
Do you have anything else to say?
If you don't, I'll have
to excuse myself.
I have something else to attend to.
You're shameless.
You still dare come back after
causing all that havoc?
No one here will ever
forget your audaciousness.
Don't think you'll be
successful in getting Artit.
Did you rush over just to say this?
Nang, it's been years.
Elon Musk already sent
SpaceX to Mars.
You keep mentioning the past.
But you haven't succeeded
in winning over Arit's heart, right?
That's why you came after me.
Are you scared?
Paeng!
Artit!
Where?
Where has she gone to?
Paeng!
Oh my gosh! I'm telling Auntie!
The weather's nice today.
I hope things will
be peaceful for a day.
Auntie!
Help me!
What's that smell?
Oh, Nang!
Did you fall into a septic pond?
How old are you now?
You even had to tell Auntie?
Paeng,
apologize to her right now.
Aren't you going to listen
to my explanation?
It's not necessary.
I've told her everything.
Auntie,
I had intended to come and see you.
But I saw her on the way.
I just found out that she got back,
so I went over to greet her.
What's wrong with her? She saw me
and she insulted me right away.
She chased me away.
Look at me.
She sprinkled
this stinky water at me.
Aren't you ashamed
of yourself at all?
Paeng!
Are you saying she's lying
and started it first?
Yes.
I don't believe you.
I figured that.
But it's okay.
I'm already used to it.
Arrogant!
Did you summon me just for this?
If you're done, I'm going now.
Paeng, come back here!
Apologize to her now.
Brat!
Calm down.
She has no respect for you at all.
She probably thinks that
she has Master's support.
She's still the same.
She was evil before,
now she's still just as evil.
Even more evil than before.
I'm really sorry.
I'll deal with her later.
It's okay.
I don't want it to be a burden.
I'm only concerned about one thing.
I don't want her
to cause trouble
for you and Artit again.
Auntie,
please be careful.
It's okay.
Artit and I already
know her every move.
Artit hates her to the bone.
She can't do anything.
That's right. He detests her.
Okay. All done.
I'll get it done, Sir.
I told you
if we're alone, you don't have
to call me Sir.
It's a force of habit, buddy.
If you have some time,
take me fishing.
Can you go?
Your wife is always on to you.
She's like a security guard.
I'm never been scared of my wife.
- Krongprateep.
- Yes, dear?
You're not scared of your wife.
But I'm getting diabetes
from your sweet talk.
I'll excuse myself, Sir.
What's the matter?
Your niece is causing
troubles again.
What is it now?
She threw fermented water at Nang.
Where did this happen?
At her rose garden.
Really?
Why did Nang go there?
Well, she...
She was only there to greet her.
What are you smiling about?
Just let the girls play sometimes.
You're siding with her again.
I came to see the wrong person.
Artit!
Hey,
did you seduce my friend again?
I'm warning you now.
Don't mess around with him.
The mom scolds me in the morning.
The son throws a fit in the evening.
Will I ever get a break?
What are you muttering about?
Instead of being a watchdog,
you should spend more time working.
That's more beneficial.
Hold on.
It's because you can't be trusted.
You're always seducing guys
whenever you get the chance.
Non was just looking
at the plans for me.
There's nothing more.
Non came for that.
But I don't believe you.
You don't have to.
Snake! Snake!
- Snake! Snake!
- Paeng!
Snake! Snake!
I thought you said
you weren't seducing me.
I really saw a snake!
Just behind there!
So it's snake now?
What a cheap trick. Let me go!
Where is it? I don't see any!
If there was,
it would be on your head.
There's a snake on my head?
There's a snake on my head!
Get off! Get off!
I don't have a snake on my head.
What do you mean? I can see them.
Heaps of them.
Medusa.
Don't look into my eyes then.
I'm going to turn you into stone
for eons.
Artit,
why are you following me?
I told you I don't trust you.
Non might fall for your tricks.
I'm not meeting with him.
But if you afraid of that,
you can just call him.
We're already living
in the era of 4G.
No need to use telepathy.
Oh, Paeng.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I dropped by to see
if you're done with the plans.
All done.
I already handed it over to Uncle.
Artit, don't you have
anything to do?
I can't let you be alone
with this woman.
Was Artit this obsessive
in the past?
Or has it gotten worse with age?
I'm not sure about the past.
But it's probably gotten worse.
Have it your way.
If anything happens,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Can you handle him being this angry?
I think I can.
I'm getting used to that now.
Artit, what are you doing?
Uh...
nothing.
Oh,
are you spying on Paeng's house?
Your darling niece is trying
to win my friend over,
so I have to keep a close watch.
Which friend?
Is it Non?
Even you know about it?
So what I'm thinking
must be correct.
But if Non gets together with Paeng,
then you should be happy.
So you won't have to be worried
that she'll like you again.
She can like anyone,
just not my friend.
Tharathep,
I think I have someone
to take care of Paeng now.
Saeb, put them in the car.
Okay, sir.
Put them in the car now.
Do you have anything else
that I can help with?
No.
Saeb.
Yes, sir?
Have you seen...
Paeng?
That's right.
Oh, why are you asking about her?
You're not interested
in her anymore.
Hmm? Hmm?
Huh?
There you go!
That hurt, sir.
- Just answer my question
- Okay, okay.
My answer is
I don't know where she is.
Besides,
I'm not a gecko in her house
that would know of her movements.
Saeb, you're still being cheeky.
Feel free to relax.
Ling, come here.
Do you think there's something
more than rose garden plans?
Non is only helping her.
Wrong.
I can smell
love.
The love of red roses.
It's so obvious.
Don't you have anything else to do?
Don't you have a delivery?
That's right. I do.
Because for some things,
if you wait too long,
you might miss it.
It has to be delivered today.
Right now.
At this moment.
Because if you
don't deliver it today,
you might have to wait
for the rest of your life.
What about you?
Do you have anything to deliver?
Tell me.
I can help you.
I'll go and do my delivery now
or I might miss it.
- Aueng!
- Miss Paeng!
Uh... you don't have
to look at me like that.
I can survive.
I've survived many nights already.
I'm still alive, see?
If you're okay, then I'm okay too.
Are you ready, Aueng?
I was ready before I came over.
I've missed you!
Let's go.
Really?
We have to plant all of these?
I can't do it.
I'm not ready.
No, you have to. You are
the only person who can help.
But an area this big?
It's only the two of us.
Maybe we should
wait for the contractor?
When they level out the land,
we can ask them to plant these.
We can't, Aueng.
I don't know when
the contractor's coming.
Whatever we can do on our own,
we should do now.
If I don't do anything,
they're going to rip me to pieces.
Let's go, Aueng. Fight!
Come on. Fight!
FIght!
Okay. Fight!
Where did you get all that strength?
Oh, sorry!
I can't go on!
I'm exhausted and starving!
Let's take a break.
Then, should we go to the kitchen?
We can't, Aueng.
We can't go and mess
around with that house.
Why are they so heartless?
I don't want to get involved or be
in a fight with them anymore.
Aueng, let's find something
to eat for ourselves.
What are we going to eat?
I know!
At this farm, there should be...
And it will have everything.
Two!
Come on.
Omelet, boiled vegetables
and chili paste again?
That's right. My face is starting
to look like an omelet already.
And my face is starting to look like
a rabbit's from all the vegetables.
True. Your face really does
look like a rabbit.
Don't do that!
You know I'm scared of rabbits!
You don't look like
you're scared of anything.
Can't you cook anything else?
I can.
But I'm just lazy to do so.
Just eat it up.
You'll poop it out anyway.
I won't.
Have it your way.
What about you two?
Are you going to eat?
Let's go. I'm not eating anymore.
Come on.
Are you trying to be a ringleader?
- I won't eat it.
- You don't have to.
What about the rest of you?
Are you eating?
I am.
Then be quick about it.
Your grilled pork is so soft.
The marinade is so good!
We'll run out if you keep
eating while cooking.
Well, it's nice.
- Oh, Pong? Aod? Kaew?
- Have you eaten anything yet?
We haven't.
Would you like to join us?
Yes, please.
- Just lay out the mat!
- Hurry up.
- Hurry.
- I'm hungry.
Why did you bump into me?
Hurry! One for each of us.
Some fermented fish?
- That'd be great.
- Over here.
Make it heavenly.
Bring it over here right away.
I can't pick it up.
What?
Why are there so many
leftovers today?
Where is everyone?
How should I know?
I've been sitting here with you.
Ready? If we're ready,
then let's go.
Come on.
Here it is.
Everyone will be fed!
Here you go! Papaya salad coming up.
Just a second.
Here.
It's coming!
What are you doing?
Madam!
- Madam!
- What's the ruckus, Duang?
My ears are going to explode.
It's Paeng.
What's she doing now?
She started a mob.
Huh? A mob?
Are you sure?
I am 100 percent sure.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Where's Paeng?
Take me to her right now.
Miss Paeng!
Watch out!
Go and have a think about
how you’re going to get back to me.
Sicko!
I’m not paying.
Because these three
aren’t my employees anymore.
Stay with me. I'll look after you.
You only have money and no brain.
I'm going to show you that
I can survive without money,
If Paeng works for you,
then that means she's
my subordinate.
The recipient has
committed a grave sin,
these merits can help them, right?
Miss Paeng! Miss Paeng!
Dad!
A grave sin
is committed by murdering someone
or killing oneself, I think.