Announcer:
You're watching AMC's
"The Walking Dead."
All new episodes premiere
Sunday nights at 9:00.
And check out
these other AMC series:
"Into the Badlands,"
"Preacher,"
and "Fear the
Walking Dead."
Only on AMC.
[Breathing heavily]
Negan: What?
Was the joke
that bad?
I'm gonna kill you.
What?
I didn't quite catch that.
You're gonna have to speak up.
[Sniffles]
Not today...
...not tomorrow...
...but I'm gonna
kill you.
[Inhales sharply]
Jesus.
[Chuckles softly]
Simon...
what did he have,
a knife?
Simon:
Uh, he had a hatchet.
A hatchet?
He had an ax.
[Chuckles]
Simon's my right-hand man.
Having one of those
is important.
I mean, what do you have left
without them?
A whole lot of work.
Do you have one?
Maybe one of these fine people
still breathing?
Oh.
Or did I...
[Clicks tongue]
[Sighs]
Sure.
Yeah.
Give me his ax.
[Footsteps]
♪
[Inhales deeply]
I'll be right back.
Maybe Rick
will be with me.
And if not, well,
we can just turn these people
inside out, won't we?
I mean...
the ones that are left.
[Sobbing]
♪
[Grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
[Both grunt]
[Sighs]
Let's go for a ride.
[Engine sputtering]
Wow.
What a piece of shit.
"I'm gonna kill you."
[Chuckles]
Are you kiddin' me?
Did you see what just happened,
what I just did?
You just...
[Sighs]
[Scoffs]
Your best chance...
is to stand up,
grab that ax,
and drive it through
the back of my head.
See how you do.
Keep actin' tough.
Go ahead.
♪
Grab the damn ax.
[Chuckles]
Drop it.
[Grunts]
[Gasping]
Ohh.
[Ax clangs]
Don't make me
get up again.
Well, look at that.
Dawn is breakin'.
It's a brand-new day,
Rick.
[Chuckles]
I want you to think about
what could have happened...
...think about
what happened,
and think about
what can still happen.
[Engine starts, revs]
♪
[Walker growls]
[Laughing]
Oh! Boom!
[Laughs]
That remind you
of anybody you know?
[Laughs]
Oh, yeah.
[Growling continues]
[Thuds]
♪
[Thud, brakes squeal]
[Engine shuts off, keys jingle]
[Walkers growling]
You are mine.
The people back there --
they are mine.
This...
This is mine.
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Ax clatters]
Hey, Rick...
go get my ax.
Let's be friends.
♪
[Walker growling loudly]
Oh. [Chuckles]
[Sighs]
Get my ax.
♪
[Grunts]
[Door slams]
♪
[Walkers growling]
Aah!
♪
[Growls]
[Grunting]
[Walkers growling]
♪
Ohh!
[Grunting]
[Growling]
♪
[Grunts]
[Growling]
[Walkers growling]
♪
[Wind rushing]
[Walkers growling]
♪
Negan: Bet you thought you were
all gonna grow old together,
sittin' around the table
at Sunday dinner
and the happily ever after.
No.
Doesn't work like that, Rick.
[Walkers growling]
Not anymore.
Think about what happened.
[Walkers growling]
♪
Negan: [Echoing]
I simply cannot decide.
[Chuckles]
Negan:
I got an idea.
Eenie...
...meenie...
miney...
mo...
catch...
...a tiger...
...by...
his toe.
If...
he hollers...
...let him go.
My mother...
told me...
...to pick...
the very...
best...
one...
...and you...
are...
♪
...it.
Negan: Anybody moves,
anybody says anything,
cut the boy's other eye out
and feed it to his father,
and then we'll start.
You can breathe.
You can blink.
You can cry.
Hell, you're all
gonna be doing that.
[Thud echoes]
Oh!
Look at that!
Taking it
like a champ!
Suck...
my...
nuts.
[Thud echoes]
[Echoing blows landing]
[Walkers growling]
Negan: Did you hear that?
[Chuckles]
He said, "Suck my nuts."
Phew.
[Laughs]
[Blows landing]
[Grunting]
[Crying]
[Blows continue landing]
[Grunting continues]
[Man groans]
[Negan laughs]
Oh, my goodness!
Look at this!
[Blood splatters]
[Laughs]
You guys,
look at my dirty girl!
Sweetheart...
Lay your eyes
on this.
[Sighs heavily]
Oh, damn.
Were you --
Were you together?
That sucks.
But if you were,
you should know
there was a reason
for all this.
Red --
and hell, he was, is,
and will ever be red.
He just took one
or six or seven for the team!
So take...a damn look.
[Breathing shakily]
Take a damn look!
[Grunting]
Rick: Daryl!
No!
Oh, no.
[Chuckles]
That?
Oh, my!
That...
is a no-no.
The whole thing --
not one bit of that shit
flies here.
[Woman crying]
Do you want me
to do it?
Right here.
[Grunting]
No.
No,
you don't kill them...
not until
you try a little.
[Grunting]
And anyway...
that's not
how it works.
Now,
I already told you people --
first one's free, then --
what'd I say?
I said I would
shut that shit down!
No exceptions.
Now, I don't know
what kind of lying assholes
you've been dealing with...
...but I'm a man
of my word.
First impressions
are important.
I need you to know me.
So...
...back to it.
[All gasping]
Woman: No!
[Groaning, gasping]
[Walkers growling]
Buddy,
you still there?
[Grunting, sputtering]
I just don't know.
It seems like
you're trying to speak,
but you just took
a hell of a hit.
I just popped your skull
so hard,
your eyeball
just popped out,
and it is
gross as shit!
Maggie, I'll find you.
[Sobbing]
[Grunting]
Oh.
Oh, hell.
I can see this is hard
on you guys.
[Grunting continues]
I am sorry.
I truly am.
But I did say it.
No exceptions! [Grunts]
[Walkers growling]
[Blows landing]
[Thudding, squelching]
[All sobbing]
♪
[Walkers growling]
You bunch of pussies.
I'm just getting started.
[Grunting]
[Blows landing]
Lucille is thirsty.
[Laughs]
She is a vampire bat.
[Sobbing continues]
[Breathing shakily]
♪
Negan: What?
Was the joke
that bad?
[Thumping]
[Walkers growling]
Negan:
People died, Rick.
It's what happened.
Doesn't mean
the rest of them have to.
[Growling continues]
Get me my ax.
Get me...my...ax!
[Walkers growling]
Negan: I thought
you were the guy, Rick.
Maybe you're not.
We'll give it
one more go.
Now, I really want you
to try this time.
Last chance.
Bring me my ax!
[Gunshots]
♪
[Growling continues]
[Growling]
[Groaning]
Aah!
♪
[Growling continues]
[Gunfire]
Aah!
[Gunfire continues]
Clock is ticking, Rick!
Think about
what can still happen.
♪
[Grunts]
[Walkers growling]
♪
[Growls]
[Grunts]
[Sighs heavily]
[Growling]
♪
[Horn honking]
[Grunting]
♪
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
♪
[Walkers growling]
[Rick breathing heavily]
Attaboy!
[Walkers growling]
[Breathing heavily]
[Growling fades]
[Engine starts]
[Brakes squeal]
[Engine stops]
[Keys jingling]
[Claps hands]
We're here, prick.
[Scoffs]
This must be hard for you,
right?
I mean, you have been King Shit
for so long.
Losin' two of your own
like...
[Snaps fingers]
Gettin' 'em clipped like that,
one nut, then the other,
and in front
of your boy?
That is
some screwed-up shit!
Ah.
Oh.
Goody.
[Cap clatters]
[Sighs]
You were in charge.
Negan: [Grunts]
Hell...
...you were probably...
addicted to it.
And now, well, clip, clip --
that's over.
But...
...you can still lead...
a nice, productive life
producing for me.
I think
you're gonna need it.
I just got a feelin'.
[Sighs]
So take it.
[Breathing heavily]
Here we are.
Let me ask you something,
Rick --
do you even know
what that little trip was about?
Negan: Speak when
you're spoken to.
[Breathing heavily]
Okay. Okay.
That trip was about
the way
that you looked at me.
I wanted
to change that.
I wanted you
to understand.
But you're still looking at me
the same damn way...
...like I shit
in your scrambled eggs,
and that's not
gonna work.
So...
...do I give you
another chance?
[Breathing raggedly]
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
[Chuckling]
All right.
And here it is --
the grand-prize game.
What you do next will decide
whether your crap day
becomes everyone's
last crap day
or just
another crap day.
Get some guns
to the back of their heads.
[Guns cocking]
Good. Now...
level with their noses,
so if you have to fire...
[imitates explosion]
it'll be a real mess.
♪
Kid...
Right here.
Kid...now.
You a southpaw?
Am I a what?
You a lefty?
No.
Good.
♪
That hurt?
No.
Should.
It's supposed to.
All right.
Get down on the ground, kid,
next to Daddy.
Spread them wings.
♪
Simon...
...you got a pen?
Yeah.
[Grunts]
Sorry, kid.
This is gonna be
as cold as a warlock's ballsack,
just like he was
hanging his ballsack above you
and dragging it
right across the forearm.
There you go.
Gives you
a little leverage.
Please. Please.
Please don't.
Me?
[Chuckles]
I ain't doing shit.
Ahh.
Rick, I want you
to take your ax...
cut your son's
left arm off,
right on that line.
Now, I know --
I know.
You're gonna have to
process that for a second.
That makes sense.
Still, though,
I'm gonna need you to do it,
or all these people
are gonna die.
Then Carl dies,
then the people
back home die...
and then you,
eventually.
I'm gonna keep you breathing
for a few years,
just so
you can stew on it.
Michonne: You -- You don't
have to do this.
We understand.
You understand.
Yeah.
I'm not sure
that Rick does.
I'm gonna need
a clean cut
right there
on that line.
Now, I know this is
a screwed-up thing to ask,
but it's gonna have to be
like a salami slice --
nothing messy,
clean, 45 degrees --
give us something
to fold over.
We got
a great doctor.
The kid'll be fine.
Probably.
Rick...
...this needs
to happen now --
chop, chop --
or I will crush
the little fella's skull myself.
It can -- It can --
It can be me.
W-W-- [Sniffles]
Y-You can do it
to me.
I c-- I can go
with -- with you.
No.
This is
the only way.
Rick...
pick up the ax.
Not making a decision
is a big decision.
You really want to see
all these people die?
You will.
You will see
every ugly thing.
Oh, my God.
[Groans]
Are you
gonna make me count?
Okay, Rick.
You win.
I am counting.
3!
Please.
[Crying] Please.
[Gasping]
It can be me.
Please!
[Crying]
2!
Please, don't do --
[Sobbing]
[Dramatic music plays]
This is it.
Aaah!
1.
[Sobbing]
[Sobs]
Dad...
just do it.
Just do it.
[Sobbing]
♪
Rick.
[Breathing heavily]
You answer to me.
You provide for me.
You belong to me.
Right?
Speak when
you're spoken to!
You answer to me.
You provide for me.
Provide for you.
You belong to me,
right?!
[Breathing heavily]
Right.
That...
...is the look
I wanted to see.
We did it...
all of us,
together...
even the dead guys
on the ground.
Hell, they get
the spirit award, for sure.
[Sighs]
Today was
a productive damn day!
[Sighs]
Now, I hope,
for all your sake...
that you get it now...
...that you understand
how things work.
Things have changed.
Whatever you had
going for you...
...that is [Chuckling] over now.
Ah. Dwight...
...load him up.
[Vehicle doors close]
He's got guts --
not a little bitch
like someone I know.
I like him.
He's mine now.
But you still
want to try something?
"Not today,
not tomorrow."
not tomorrow"?
I will cut pieces
off of...
Hell's his name?
Daryl.
Wow.
[Chuckles]
That actually sounds right.
I will cut
pieces off of Daryl
and put them
on your doorstep --
or, better yet,
I will bring him to you
and have you
do it for me.
[Chuckles]
Ahh!
Welcome to a brand-new
beginning, you sorry shits!
I'm gonna leave you a truck.
Keep it.
Use it to cart all the crap
you're gonna find me.
We'll be back for
our first offering in one week.
Until then...
ta-ta.
♪
[Insects chirping]
Rick: Maggie. Maggie.
[Sobs]
Maggie...
you need to sit down.
Maggie.
No.
We need to get you
to the Hilltop.
You need to go
get ready.
For what?
To fight them.
They have Daryl.
They have an army.
[Breathing heavily]
We would die --
all of us.
Go home.
[Voice breaking]
Take everybody with you.
I can get there
by myself.
You can barely
stand up.
I need to go.
You need to go
to Alexandria.
[Breathing heavily]
You were out --
out here for me.
We still are.
[Sobbing]
I can make it now.
I need you
to go back.
I can't have you
out here.
I can't have you all
out here anymore.
I need you
to go back.
Maggie...
we're not letting
you go.
Okay?
You have to.
[Sighs]
It's not gonna happen.
[Breathing heavily]
I'm taking her.
I'm gonna get
her there.
I'm gonna keep
her safe.
I'm not giving you
a choice.
I'm taking him
with me.
[Groans]
I'm gonna take him.
[Voice breaking]
That's what I'm gonna do.
[Sniffles]
[Exhales sharply]
[Breathing heavily]
I need to do this.
Please.
We need to help you.
I got it.
No. No.
Pl-- Pl--
Please let us.
He-- He's our family, t--
He's our family, too.
♪
[Sobbing]
You're okay.
All right.
On three.
1, 2...
[Sobbing continues]
♪
Yeah.
Negan: Bet you thought you were
all gonna grow old together,
sittin' around the table
at Sunday dinner
and the happily ever after.
No.
Doesn't work like that, Rick.
Not anymore.
[Slow music plays]
[Growling]
[Engine starts]
[Music continues]
[Growling continues]
♪