(announcer) Previously, on
AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
(Eugene)
I need a search party.
See if Daryl ran home,
like the dumb animal that he is.
Daryl does turn up here,
just know there's no statute
of limitations on this.
One utterly, completely,
stone cold Negan.
How many people here can fight?
Who would train all
this cannon fodder?
I will.
Give me a week.
I memorized everything.
Daryl and Carl took Rick by
the inside of Negan's place.
There's only two of us.
Are you changing your mind?
I'm ready to kill him.
[Sighs]
[Birds chirping]
[Gate opens]
[Gate closes]
Sasha: Hi.
Are you here --
I'm here
because I need your help.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Sorry for taking over
your trailer.
Oh.
I grew up
with a lot of people around.
I'm used to it.
Big family?
Uh...group home.
This isn't like that, though.
Not the bad parts, at least.
For the first time,
I feel like I belong.
Trying to make sure you
and Sasha became a part of this
made me a part of this.
When I was first here...
I was never here.
I, um...
I always found it hard
getting close to anyone --
neighbors, friends...
boyfriends.
You should try it sometime.
Even if it doesn't last.
I'm gonna talk to our blacksmith
about making more spears.
Maybe we can trade with
the Kingdom for some body armor.
Thing is, what we really need
is riot gear.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Sighs]
[Door opens]
I was...
looking for something to read
the other day.
You can have the bullets.
I didn't know you had a gun.
I didn't.
I do now.
Sasha, don't go --
not yet.
[Sighs]
Rosita didn't come here
to train people.
You're both going after Negan.
But you can't do that
without people.
A lot of people.
We've talked about this.
I know what you think.
And I appreciate that.
But I'm not
gonna change my mind.
She's not.
Does Maggie know
Rosita's here yet?
Uh, I-I-I don't think so.
I didn't...
You should tell her.
About all of it.
No.
Not yet.
Sh--
I'm still --
I'm still getting ready.
And the thing is,
Rosita is going,
with or without me.
So it should be with me.
Then I'll go, too.
Me, too.
No.
The Hilltop has to be ready
for what happens after.
Maggie needs you.
She needs you, too.
Not anymore.
She has everyone else,
and they have her.
You can stay.
I know you can.
But I know you won't
and she won't,
but I wish you would.
'Cause it's a long life,
and then it isn't.
You can take
anything else you need.
But you and Rosita
need to talk to Maggie.
You owe her that much.
[Door closes]
Listen...
Enid...
Maggie trusts you.
You have to protect her,
no matter what.
She's the future of this place.
I know it.
So are you.
Hold on to this for me.
It's for the baby.
Maybe you can work on it
while I'm gone.
Okay.
Sasha...
Yeah.
In 10 minutes,
I'm gonna tell Maggie
what's going on.
It's up to you
what you want to do with that.
I'm doing what you asked.
[Door closes]
[Clanging]
The Saviors are coming!
[Clanging continues]
We have to get Maggie.
Where is she?
Come on!
Where do we hide?
We're not hiding.
All right, get in.
It goes to the other side.
We got to get out
before Maggie does.
[Grunts]
[Vehicles approaching]
We'll never make it in time.
Come on!
Just stay down there.
I'll keep them away.
They aren't the same ones
who came to Alexandria.
Gregory:
Simon! Hello.
Right back at you, Gregory.
Hello.
Ahh.
[Both laugh]
We weren't, uh,
expecting you back so soon.
You want to talk in my office?
I got a bottle of gin
my people found.
You're a gin man, right?
Oh, I'm a man of...
shifting specifics of tastes
in transition.
I'm into tequila now.
Añejo. Reposado.
Sipping, mixing...
Un mundo de sabor.
[Chuckles]
Gin seems like turpentine.
It happened quick with a gimlet
the other night.
I'm an unusual kind of creature.
You know what?
I respect that.
Yeah. Tequila.
Mental note.
Locked.
Great.
Oh, no need to talk.
This is hopefully a quick visit.
Oh.
Well, what can I do for you?
That's an excellent question.
Alas, the answer's
not so excellent.
You have a certain somebody
that, uh...
now needs to be
Negan's certain somebody,
so what you can do for me
is point me in their direction.
So, who is it?
You get your pointy finger up,
and I'll tells ya.
[Chuckles]
Daryl.
[Door creaks]
Did you dig that tunnel?
Maggie thought
we needed a quick way out.
So I made one.
Well, we're out.
So now what?
You know.
If this one starts,
I'll siphon some gas.
I just got to find --
There's an empty water bottle.
I thought
this was the one, but...
Like it?
I made it.
Car's dead.
[Bird squawking in distance]
[Car door creaks]
Where'd you learn
to disarm bombs?
[Car door creaks]
Were you in the Army?
[Sighs]
Someone I knew.
Not him.
Listen, I'm not here to play
"Get to Know You,"
so either we talk about
the mission or we don't.
Okay.
Jesus said
there's some buildings,
two, three, four stories,
just outside the sanctuary
to the east of it.
At least one of them
should have a line of sight
to the rear courtyard,
past the fence
with the walkers on it.
We hole up, we wait,
we take a shot from there.
If we have to get closer,
there's some weak spots
in the perimeter
we might still be able
to take advantage of,
but if we can,
I say we stay outside,
do it clean.
Maybe make it
out of there alive.
You see a problem with that?
I want to make sure we get him.
That means we go in.
If we shoot from a distance
and miss,
we don't get another chance.
I won't miss.
Even if you shoot and graze him,
he doesn't die.
I won't miss.
If we go in
and get caught --
I won't get caught.
What the hell's wrong with you?
They take us,
we don't get another try.
Because they'll kill us.
If we're out here, we're alive.
We get another go.
[Walkers growling]
Nothing is wrong with me, Sasha.
I'm gonna make sure he's dead.
Look, if this
is too much for you,
you want to bail,
now's your chance.
I'm not going anywhere.
Well, I'm done talking about it.
Good.
Maybe you'll think about it.
Maybe you'll change your mind
about what it takes
to get what you want.
Hi!
Uh, I've got
fresh veggies --
Stop.
They're vegetables.
Use the whole word.
We have time.
Uh...
Okay.
I have these vegetables
they told me to bring over,
uh, and the basket's
pretty heavy.
[Chuckles]
For me, I mean.
Probably not you.
Uh, here.
Load them in the truck,
and, uh, if you meet me
by the garden,
I can get you the rest --
Stop.
I don't know who you think I am
or who we are.
Load them yourself.
I'm busy.
Oh. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Girl, pick that shit up
right now and scram.
And I'll take that.
Now.
Don't make me
cut it off you, girl.
[Door creaks]
[Footsteps]
[Sniffs]
Dr. Harlan Carson,
correct?
Do you need a checkup?
Simon: Probably.
It's been a few years,
but I'm not here for that.
[Door closes]
We already gave you as much
medicine as we could spare
the last time you were here.
Yes, you did.
But we're not here
to take more of that.
Congratulations!
You're moving up in the world.
Negan wants you where he is.
You're an important fellow,
Harlan.
You're coming with us.
Look, I -- I have patients here
that need me.
Why does Negan need two doctors?
Well, I think my look may have
conveyed the information.
People say I have
an expressive face.
But if not,
let me repeat your question.
Why do we need two doctors?
Answer -- we don't.
So...
my brother pissed someone off,
get himself killed?
Something like that.
Very, very ugly stuff.
My condolences.
But it's time.
All of my charts are in order.
You need to make arrangements
for some kind
of medical care here,
especially for
my ongoing patients.
I will.
I need to pack.
Simon: You don't.
We have everything you need,
and what we don't, we'll get.
Hey, you like ice cream?
We have ice cream.
We have a lady
that makes cardamom gelato.
Shit you not.
Oh!
Almost forgot.
Set that down.
[Box thuds]
Well, fair is fair.
We're not leaving you
high and dry
when it comes
to medical solutions.
Go on.
[Sighs]
[Box closes]
Simon, a word?
Mm.
Look, I think I've proven
that I can work with Negan.
I'm a can-do guy,
but I got to hang on
to my peoples' trust.
Otherwise, you don't know
who might take over.
You know, someone else
might not be so cooperative.
They might have crazy ideas.
Who might take over?
What crazy ideas?
I don't know.
I'm just considering
worst-case scenarios.
You know, What I'm saying is,
I know human nature,
and it isn't inconceivable.
I hear your concern.
Mm.
I'm not insensitive to it.
Right?
If you're having problems
of that nature...
come to see me.
Anytime.
I don't know where to go.
[Chuckles]
I'll arrange it so that...
...you just tell the guard
who you are...
Mm-hmm.
...and he'll
let you right in.
Long as
there's no shenanigans afoot.
There will be none.
[Chuckles]
I just -- I just
would like you to consider --
Wonderful.
Hmm?
We'll crack open some tequila.
We'll talk.
We'll work it out.
You're a good producer for us.
I don't want you
to be so stressed.
Yeah.
I'd be a lot less stressed
if you'd leave my doctor.
Gregory...
Got it. Okay.
I won't ask again.
[Footsteps]
[Box thuds]
[Door creaks]
[Footsteps depart]
He's gone.
[Sighs]
You were gonna kill that guy.
He was gonna find us.
He wasn't, and he didn't.
He deserved to die.
Ever since you got here,
you haven't said a word to me.
Would you look at me?
Please?
[Sniffles]
Daryl...
[Voice breaking]
I'm sorry.
[Sniffles]
It wasn't your fault.
It was.
No.
It wasn't.
You're one of the good things
in this world.
That's what Glenn thought.
And he would know,
'cause he was
one of the good things, too.
[Shuddered breathing]
And, uh...
I wanted to kill that guy, too.
I wanted to string them all up
and watch them die.
But we have to win.
Help me win.
[Truck engines start]
[Walkers growling]
This'll work.
[Glass shatters]
[Growling continues]
Now.
[Grunts]
[Electricity crackles]
[Engine starts]
Get in!
[Growling continues]
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
[Walkers growling]
[Sighs]
Anything?
Negan still hasn't come out.
But Eugene's out there.
Eugene?
It looks like...
he's ordering people around.
Playing some angle.
Will you teach me those knots?
I know a bunch, but not those.
Won't matter soon.
It might.
[Sighs]
Yeah, I'll show you.
All right, here's the first one.
Cross it over your hand
like that.
Mm.
Then you take the top loop,
bring it down, up,
and back through, then...
Got it?
Let me try.
[Chuckles]
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Insects chirping]
You know...
we got lucky,
having you with us.
You know how to do everything.
[Sighs]
Johnny.
That's who taught me
about bombs.
Survivalist,
prepper-type shit.
[Both chuckle]
Marcus taught me about cars.
He was a mechanic...
and a wannabe stunt driver.
And an asshole.
Knot-tying
was from Chaser.
Yeah, that wasn't his real name.
[Both laugh]
There were others.
Were those people you lost
on the way to D.C.?
No, not them.
A lot of guys
wanted to protect me,
like there was no way
I could know
how to take care of myself.
And I didn't.
And I hated the way that felt.
So I rolled with it.
They didn't even notice
I was picking up
everything they knew how to do
and doing it better.
Then I'd outgrow them
and bounce.
The sex was just for fun.
[Both laugh]
When the world's over,
everyone should be
getting their rocks off.
Was that how it was with him?
Abraham?
No.
I fell in with him
because he saw
I could handle my shit.
And I never looked back.
Well, no, I did.
When it was over.
Yeah.
You know the thing
that killed me?
When we got to Alexandria,
I was acting like
I was all good 'cause he wasn't.
[Chuckles]
Then, the son of a bitch
was actually all good.
[Chuckles]
And I couldn't
figure this one out.
Living there,
feeling like we had made it,
I couldn't pick that up.
Then, when he bounced, I...
...I thought I hated you.
But maybe I just hated
that he figured out
his shit first.
[Scoffs]
I've never told anyone
any of that stuff.
Who I was, what I did...
I'm glad...
that you felt like...
you could.
I was stupid
to waste so much time.
Now I'll never
get to tell Abraham
I'm happy he was happy.
Were you happy?
I was.
[Sniffles]
[Sighs]
It wasn't his time.
Abraham would've wanted
to go out fighting.
And that asshole with the bat
took that away, too.
To go out
with a point to going out.
I guess we all want that.
No matter how it all goes down,
I got your back.
And I've got yours.
You think
that prick's out there yet?
Hmm.
[Vehicles approaching]
[Walkers growling]
Sasha:
Oh...shit.
Rosita: What?
Dr. Carson,
Maggie's doctor.
They brought him here.
[Walkers growling]
Negan's out.
Oh, he's too close.
Ah, I can't get a clean shot.
Turn on the walkie.
[Walkie-talkie clicks, static]
This is Dr. Eugene Porter,
Chief Engineer, speaking.
I'm gonna need
a dozen more walkers,
a.k.a. "dead ones"
in the local parlance,
for expanding
the fence protocol PDQ.
Actually, PFQ.
This is per Negan,
who I also am,
even if it takes all night
to procure them,
so I need able-bodied persons
out there
in the surrounding
blocks of buildings
snoopin' and snatchin', stat.
Negan will be indisposed
in the boudoir,
so in the meantime,
any questions should be
directed to yours truly.
Dr. Eugene Porter,
Chief Engineer,
also known as Negan, who I am.
Change of plans.
So we go in.
[Gun cocks]
I'm ready.
[Knock on door]
Come in.
Freddie said
you wanted to see me?
Yes, have a seat.
I noticed you've been slacking
on your scavenging
and recruiting lately.
And there are too many people
in your trailer.
Fire hazard.
Plenty of room here at
Barrington House for our guests.
Speaking of which,
I have job assignments
for the newcomers.
People are gonna stay,
they're gonna chip in.
No more free rides on the teat.
You let them
take Dr. Carson.
Surprised
you didn't kneel again.
You must be really worried
if you're trying
to split everyone up.
[Chuckles]
Shouldn't talk to me like that.
Who knows what might happen
with all these Saviors
coming around?
Did you just threaten me?
I was being sarcastic, okay?
No, I think
you just threatened me.
Think what you want.
You know, what I'm saying is,
I look out for my friends,
and I realized...
we're not friends.
[Knock on door]
Come in.
Ah, wonderful --
tequila.
Crack that open for me,
would you?
You may go now.
Show him out, will you, Kal?
[Sighs]
Everything okay?
Where's Sasha and Rosita?
You see that over there?
That is a half-assed attempt
at a safety protocol.
We need a full-assed,
full-court press.
That stuff out front
with the spikes
and the chains and the heads,
that's good for the optics.
It sends a message
to would-be intruders
of the "Don't Mess
with Texas" variety.
[Inhales deeply]
But we need to drill down
on actual safety protocol,
especially at points
that have proven to be janky.
Well, yeah.
That's why
I'm on guard duty now.
No offense to that last guy,
but he could hardly
handle a gun.
[Silenced gunshot]
[Body thuds]
Get up.
You're getting out.
Eugene, get up.
We're breaking you out.
Eugene!
No.
I'm not going with you.
What?
I didn't ask you to come, so go.
People got to be en route.
[Door closes]
That weak, lying sack of shit.
This is it.
I'm going in.
Hold on.
This is gonna take a second.
More could be coming back.
Keep an eye out.
[Fence clattering]
Just another second.
What the hell are you doing?
Go.
It's not your time.
There's got to be
a point to it, right?
They need you.
[Silenced gunshot]
[Groans]
[Indistinct shouting,
machine-gun fire]
[Machine-gun fire continues]
[Crying]
Damn it.
Damn it!
[Sobbing]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com