Previously on AMC's The Walking Dead...
I only want Negan.
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.
Best case, maybe you take him out.
Then make me a bullet.
Everything we have, we got from fighting.
We play by their rules,
we get some kinda life.
You led us all to the promise land,
isn't that right, Rick?
He we are!
Oh, I like it here.
Saviors can actually be quite reasonable.
Maggie.
I know people are saying things...
nice things about you and Sasha?
They are?
They are.
About the other night...
about how they're thinking
you saved the place.
Don't let it go to your head.
Well, don't let it bother you.
It seems like it bothers you.
What you doing up there?
You gonna eat that?
Yes.
Dude.
You know she's pregnant.
Against the grain, kid.
Always against the grain.
Damn, that smells good.
Want a taste?
Okay.
Here's his damn lemonade.
I had some in my kitchen.
Denise liked it.
Thank you.
Hey.
Go home.
Let me take over.
No.
I'm fine.
I told Rick I would watch Judith.
I'm gonna do that.
You should go.
We're about to sit.
We're gonna need another setting.
Today and only today, right?
Yeah.
All these bullet holes...
this'll take on water quick.
We can probably make it to the canoe.
Probably.
If you want to stay back...
I'm going to pretend you
didn't just say that.
I'm seeing this through.
We both are.
I'm not waiting for your dad anymore.
I don't know where the hell he is,
but Lucille...
...is hungry.
Carl, pass the rolls...
...Please.
Look at that, huh?
Easy as that.
It's just a transaction.
You look like shit,
which means you fought for this.
You did your jobs.
You get it, and I like that.
Negan likes that.
That's... good to hear.
You play your cards right,
maybe I'll show you where we live.
Maybe I'll buy you a sandwich.
Just tell me when.
You like watching, haircut?
Yes.
I mean...
You mean to get
the hell out of here.
Now!
Morgan.
It's just some things from
the Kingdom garden...
some nectarines, some apples.
Thank you. I am good.
You can fend for yourself, I know,
but fresh produce isn't
something you can just...
Really.
I'm good.
Ezekiel?
Apparently, some people are
having a hard time believing me
when I say I just want to be left alone.
You know, I was trying to
leave you alone, and I will.
But you called me over.
Why?
How are you?
Good.
Now you can go.
I think you're going soft.
I think you're going.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Carol, hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Morgan, I-I didn't expect
you to be here, too.
It's good you are.
I wanted to speak to you both, actually.
It's about something important.
Almost at the canoe.
We're taking on water quick, man.
I know.
Rick, on the left!
We're almost there.
No, no!
Hold on!
Stay in the canoe!
I can... Just...
Aaron!
I'm okay.
I'm all right.
Stop hugging the wall.
Watch it!
God damn it!
Go get a mop and another barrel.
We're keeping this crap?
We don't have to eat it.
Jesus. He hates pickles.
It's got hooks.
I don't know why he didn't strap it in.
Told him twice. His
stupid ass didn't listen.
Okay.
Bit of a sore loser.
Looks like the only thing
he ran out of was ammo.
We got to get this back now.
Yeah.
Well... he's got paddles.
And with the wind picking up,
it shouldn't take long
to drift back to shore.
Easy. Easy.
We got it. Take this crap back.
How 'bout, this time,
you watch where you're going?
Oh, come on. Get off his back.
You know, back there,
I didn't mean that you couldn't do it.
It's just...
going this far, risking this much
to get things for them...
people don't agree with it.
I wouldn't blame you if you didn't.
I was there.
I saw what happened on the road.
What we're doing is gonna
keep people living.
We get to do that,
it doesn't matter what happens to us.
Michonne doesn't think this is living.
Well, committing to a choice like this,
after living how we did... free...
I get it.
It's hard.
It's giving up everything,
right up until your own life.
But either your heart's
beating, or it isn't.
Your loved ones' hearts are
beating, or they aren't.
We take what they give
us so that we can live.
So, how long you been with Negan?
Why were you out there alone?
Tell me!
You think talking won't
change how this ends for you.
But you don't know me.
Let's see what happens.
I'm not gonna kill him today.
I'm gonna find the way that we win.
I'm gonna change how this ends for me.
That's why I'm out here alone.
Is that an apple pie?
How did you do that?
I could smell it from outside the door.
You baked it?
Some guy gave it to us
for what we did.
His little girl said you should
run for President of Hilltop.
"Maggie for President."
Do you want a plate?
No, I'm good.
Did Jesus give you those?
Is he still around?
There's some things I wanna
add to his list before he goes out.
The kids need something to
write with... pens, pencils.
Are you already president?
I've just been talking to people.
Jesus left this morning.
He told me to tell you, but I-I forgot.
Okay. Next time.
I'm gonna get some milk.
- Let me.
- No, I'm good.
What?
You're lying to Maggie about Jesus.
What makes you say that?
A girl who lives in the house.
She was telling me about everyone.
She said Jesus is a runner
and that he left yesterday,
not this morning.
- It's for her own good.
- Why?
Because I need to do something,
and she'll want to help me.
You want to kill Negan.
What if you have help?
If we had help... a lot of people...
then I wouldn't be afraid to tell her,
because she'd know it
wasn't on her to do it.
- But if it's just me, then.
- It isn't just you.
You and Maggie aren't the only ones
who want to take Negan out.
- There's...
- No, Enid.
That's not happening.
And if you care about her,
you don't say anything about this.
We have to keep her safe.
You have to keep her safe.
It isn't just you.
It sure looks like it.
A lot of places came
together after the world fell apart.
Maybe you're both from
one of those places.
Most of those communities
and camps are gone now.
I lost people.
I pretty much lost hope in people.
But then I found the Kingdom.
I met Ezekiel.
I saw what he built.
But now I believe what he
built is under threat.
The Saviors.
A few months back,
Ezekiel and a few guards met a
group of them in the woods.
The Saviors recognized
Ezekiel's capabilities,
and Ezekiel didn't want to fight,
so they cut a deal.
In exchange for food and supplies,
no one would get hurt,
and they'd never set
foot inside the Kingdom,
and very few of us even know.
What does any of this have to do with me?
I know Ezekiel likes you.
I also know that Ezekiel trusts you,
and that's why I'm here.
I need you to help me
convince him of something.
Right now, we have peace
with the Saviors,
but sooner or later,
sometimes's gonna go wrong.
Maybe we'll be light on a drop,
or maybe one of ours will look
at one of theirs the wrong way,
or maybe they'll just decide
to stop honoring the deal.
Things will go bad.
And when they do...
...the Kingdom will fall.
I had a family.
I lost it to this world.
I saw them die.
I'm scared that, if we
don't do something now,
that we won't only lose more people...
we'll lose everything.
I know what the Saviors are,
and I know what they do.
And I know they cannot be trusted.
And I think you know that, too.
What exactly are you asking?
I'm asking you to help convince Ezekiel
to attack the Saviors, to strike first...
and destroy them.
Is that for you...
or Negan?
It's for him.
How will you do it?
I'll pull the trigger.
They'll kill you.
As long as he goes first.
Why do you have to die?
Because he has to.
I agree.
But...
...Why do you?
There's...
...No need to lie to me if...
this is our last conversation.
If Abraham was alive, we could fight.
If Glenn was,
Maggie's kid would have a father.
Michonne and Carl can fight.
They have Rick.
Aaron has Eric.
Eugene knows things.
Daryl's strong.
What about Sasha?
Look at me, Rosita.
It shouldn't have been you.
It shouldn't have been anyone.
We'll win,
but we need to wait for the right moment
or create it...
together.
And you're a part of that together.
Don't do this.
We need you.
Okay. I know
there's a lot of them.
I'm guessing a good deal more
than we have at the Kingdom.
The element of surprise is our only hope.
We need to attack first,
and we need to do it now
while we still have the advantage.
Carol, I imagine that
violence and fighting
is something you haven't been a part of.
You're wrong.
You're very wrong.
She's probably the most
capable fighter in this room.
Then it's time to fight.
No.
This is something I am not a part of.
Then you don't have to fight.
You just have to convince Ezekiel
to bring the Kingdom to fight.
You're not understanding me.
I didn't want you.
I didn't want Ezekiel
or Morgan coming here.
And I don't want anything
to do with your lives
or your deaths.
I just want to be left alone.
People will die... a lot of them.
You killed a man.
I took a life to save a life.
It's the same goddamn thing!
We'll be taking their lives to save ours!
Only you don't know that it will!
You're gonna choose to
kill one day, Morgan,
'cause it will get that bad!
Why not choose now,
before you lose someone you care about?
There's a peace now.
I won't be a part of changing that.
And maybe we can build on that.
Not with these people!
When they turn on us... and they will...
that blood is gonna be on your hands!
But maybe you're both used to that.
You should go, too.
I should.
I don't want anyone else coming around
or even knowing where I am.
If you somehow see anyone we know,
tell them I'm gone.
Do that for me please.
Never meant for you to see me.
Hi.
Hot date?
I'm on a good momentum
with them. Gonna try to use that.
Yeah? How?
By trying to get closer,
even just to start trying.
If I can do that, after a while...
maybe months, maybe years...
maybe then we try something.
I think it's what my mom would have done,
so it's what I'm gonna do.
Okay.
Whatever it was...
I thought we had something good...
at least, the beginning
of something good.
Why'd you end it?
Why'd you even start it?
I was trying not to think about shit.
You're cute, tall.
You're sweet sometimes.
So I used you.
I'm sorry.
Would you be up for dinner later?
I really mean just dinner.
No strings.
All right.
What the hell?
It's cool, I swear.
Buddy, you can walk right
out that back gate there,
and I won't say anything to anybody.
I'm supposed to be there now,
but, listen, I'm... I'm
just trying to get by,
just like you.
Please.
Daryl.
It ain't just about gettin' by here.
It's about gettin' it all.
I got the key. Let's go.
- No.
- I just want to talk to him.
I said "no."
Don't be an asshole, Arat.
Let the man pass.
Oh, crap. Is that for me?
We haven't officially met.
I'm Spencer Monroe.
Hi.
That's Negan.
Is he down there?
Yeah.
We're all Negan.
Whatever you're trying to do, you can't.
But you still have some choices.
Go home.
Burn this car, roll it down into a lake,
make it disappear.
There's a silencer in
the glove compartment.
Where is he?
Negan?
He's in your house,
asshole, waiting for you.
Hey.
Just like that?
See, we've been waiting for hours
just to see what you gonna bring us, huh?
Why don't we have a look first?
Running water, air conditioning,
a housewarming gift?
That settles it.
I am getting myself a vacation home here.
Cheers to that.
Oh, that is good.
You know, the only thing
missing is a pool table.
Nothing better than a
good game of 8 ball.
The house across the street
has one in the garage.
Oh, Spencer,
you may just be my new best friend.
Such a nice day, though...
too nice to be cooped up
inside some garage, don't you think?
Yeah.
Oh, I got a better idea.
Not bad.
We had to go out pretty far.
What the hell's this?
"Congrats for winning.
But you still lose"?
You leave us a little love note?
No, I just...
I mean... We wouldn't, obviously...
Wait. What?
Did you just say it's obvious?
We didn't do that.
It's not about the damn note!
Hey. Don't.
Run along to Negan, Rick.
But your friend here...
he's got no place to be.
- You...
- Back up!
I could never do this with Rick.
He would just be standing
there, scowling,
giving me that annoying
side-eye he gives me.
That's actually what I
came to see you about.
I want to talk to you about Rick.
All right.
Talk to me, Spencer.
Talk to me about Rick.
I get what you're trying to do here,
what you're trying to build.
I'm not saying I agree with your methods,
but I get it.
You're building a network.
You're making people contribute
for the greater good.
It makes sense.
But you should know that Rick Grimes
has a history of not
working well with others.
Is that so?
Rick wasn't the original leader here.
My mom was.
She was doing a really good job of it.
Then she died, not long
after Rick showed up...
same with my brother, same with my dad.
So, everything was peachy here for...
what... years?
And then Rick shows up, and
suddenly, you're an orphan?
That is the saddest
story I've ever heard.
Good thing for you he's
not in charge anymore.
Doesn't matter.
His ego's out of control.
He'll find a way to screw things up,
to try and do things
his way, to take over.
That's what he did with my mom.
That's what he'll do again.
What exactly are you proposing
be done about that?
I am my mother's son.
I can be the leader she was.
That's what this place needs.
That's what you need.
So I should put you in charge...
that's what you're saying?
We'd be much better off.
You're all right. You're all right.
All right, all right, all right.
Point made.
My heart's still beating, right?
You know, I'm thinking, Spencer.
I'm thinking how Rick
threatened to kill me,
how he clearly hates my guts.
But he is out there right now,
gathering shit for me to make sure
I don't hurt any of the
fine people that live here.
He is swallowing his hate
and getting shit done.
That takes guts.
And then there's you...
...The guy who waited for Rick to be gone
so he could sneak over and talk to me
to get me to do his dirty work,
so he could take Rick's place.
So I got to ask...
if you wanna take over,
why not just kill Rick yourself
and just take over?
What? No, no.
I didn't... I don't...
You know what I'm thinking?
'Cause I have a guess.
It's because you got no guts.
How embarrassing.
There they are.
They were inside you the whole time.
You did have guts.
I've never been so wrong
in my whole life!
Now, someone oughta get up
here and clean this mess up.
Anyone want to finish the game?
C'mon.
Anybody?
I was winning!
Shit!
What the shit?!
Shit! You just... You tried to kill me?!
You shot Lucille!
She got in the way.
What is this?
This little bad boy made from scratch?
Look at those crimps.
This was homemade.
You may be stupid, darlin',
but you showed some real ingenuity here.
Arat, move that knife up
out on that girl's face.
Lucille's beautiful, smooth surface
is never gonna look the same,
so why should yours?!
Unless...
Unless you tell me who made this.
It was me.
I made it.
You see, now I just think you're lying.
And you lying to me now?!
Such a shame.
Arat's gonna have to cut
up that pretty face.
One more try.
It was me.
You are such a badass!
Fine.
Have it your way.
Arat...
Kill somebody.
No. It was me!
No!
We had an agreement.
Rick!
Look, everybody, it's Rick.
Ah, your people are
making me lose my voice
doin' all this yelling.
Rick... how about a "thank you"?
I mean, look, I know we
started this relationship
with me beating the holy
shit out of your friends,
and because of that, we're
never gonna sit around
and braid each other's hair
or share our deepest, darkest secrets,
but how about a little credit?
I just bent over backwards
to show you how reasonable I am.
Your kid...
he hid in one of my trucks
and machine-gunned a
bunch of my men down,
and I brought him home, safe and sound,
and I fed him spaghetti.
Another one of your people...
well, he wanted me to kill
you and put him in charge.
I took him out... for you.
And another one, here...
she shot Lucille, trying
to kill me just now,
so I gave you one less mouth to feed.
And by looking at her...
that mouth did some major damage.
Now, personally,
I wouldn't have picked
her to be the one to go,
but Arat...
I don't know... didn't trust her.
Your shit's waiting for you at the gate.
Just go.
Sure thing, Rick...
right after I find the guy or gal
that made this bullet.
Arat?
It was me!
No, it wasn't.
It was me.
It was only me.
You?
It required one spent casing,
one four-holed turret reloader,
powder, one funnel for the powder...
Shut up.
I believe you.
Lucille, give me strength.
I'm gonna be relieving you of
your bullet maker, Rick...
that and whatever you left
for me at the front gate.
And however much you scavenged,
it's not good enough,
because you're still in
a serious, serious hole
after today.
Let's move out!
No! No, no!
Please, just take me!
No!
Rick, I ain't gonna lie...
your kitchen is a goddamn mess.
I'll see you next time.
Carl told me you were in here.
I...
I found what I was looking for.
I wanted to go with you and Aaron,
but I couldn't.
I had to go my way.
But when I found it...
...I realized that...
I didn't want it to be my way.
I wanted it to be ours... me and you.
There are more of them,
even more than we thought.
We are outnumbered. It's not even close.
But that doesn't change
the way that I feel,
because it doesn't change
the way that things are.
We're still alive, Rick.
So much has happened,
so much that we shouldn't
have lived through.
And...
and in spite of it or
maybe because of it,
we did.
We're still here, the two of us.
We're still standing, and
we're gonna keep standing.
So, what do we do with that?
How do we make that mean something?
We're the ones who get things done.
You said that.
We're the ones who live.
That's why we have to fight...
not for us, but for Judith, for Carl,
for Alexandria, for the Hilltop...
for all of us.
We can fight them, Rick.
We can find a way to beat them.
We can do this.
But...
Only if... we do this.
Yeah, I know that now.
I know that now.
Sasha! Enid!
- You're okay?
- I'm okay.
The baby's okay...
all of us.
You were right...
right from the start.
You told us to get ready to fight.
I didn't listen, and I couldn't.
I can now.