= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 39 =
Jia Shi assigned Su Mucheng on the last round of Arena Contest.
The league's top Launcher versus the master of first generation.
It's a battle between gunpowder and magic.
How will the Arena Contest end?
We'll see in the game.
Some tactical adjustments were made on the spot.
It's normal.
Be cool about it.
Since Mucheng is wearing Jia Shi's uniform
sitting on Jia Shi's player seat,
it means that you're ready
to fight for Jia Shi.
Don't think too much.
Mr. Tao,
You're putting her in a dilemma.
You choose Mucheng to play
in such a sensitive match,
She would be suspected
even though she wants to win
but just lose the game normally.
Then play well
if she doesn't want that.
But when it comes to games like this,
if you dig out the details with preconceived,
Any operation that isn't in place
will be seemed as intentional.
She has only one option,
win.
That's just what we want.
The last Arena Contest,
Jia Shi assigned the top Launcher
Su Mucheng to challenge the veteran,
Wei Chen, the winner of last round.
Captain Yu, what do you think of this game?
Both teams' players are
experienced and mature.
They both know each other well.
And they operate long-handed professions
that are good at long-distance consumption.
This could have been
a close game.
But captain Wei lost nearly half of his blood last round,
and has consumed too much HP,
this should be a tough fight for him.
Well, we all know that
Su Mucheng didn't renew her contract with Jia Shi,
it is said that
they may not cooperate.
But Jia Shi assigned her
in such a crucial competition,
we have no idea what
the tactical arrangement of the Jia Shi Team is.
Game begins.
There seems to be a change
in the style of Dancing Rain.
Sister Su didn't start
like her style at all.
Why did Su Mucheng move
completely different from before?
She's not really going to let him win, right?
No, she won't.
Don't give up your professional honor
for helping Ye Qiu.
I'm just saying that women aren't good enough.
She's just not tough enough.
Dancing Rain keeps moving her position
to find the opponent,
Windward Formation keeps quiet,
he did not rush out.
Windward Formation's HP is in great disadvantage,
it's right to choose a more conservative way.
Dancing Rain mounted gun.
Captain Yu,
How do you evaluate the opening
of Su Mucheng's blocking.
The style of her blocking has really changed.
She no longer makes long-distance outflank,
but in a more aggressive way.
We can see that
Windward Formation begins to move his position.
He's finding Dancing Rain's position.
Su Mucheng still occupies a high place,
She has a very wide vision.
But she's easy to be discovered.
They are all long-distance professions.
It is better to
find the opponent first
and hold the upper hand.
Windward Formation seems to have found her opponent.
He starts to release Arrow of Curse.
Hasn't Dancing rain found him yet?
Found him.
The fire is too strong.
Windward Formation can't keep casting magic
and begins to find shelters.
But Dancing rain's marksmanship was too precise.
Every bullet is restricting
the position of Windward Formation.
That's too violent.
Go wild.
Su Mucheng's attack rhythm
for Launcher is almost perfect.
Her skills convergence and output cycle
are the textbook of Launcher of Glory.
But captain Wei's dodging
is just so-so.
He has to find a interval between her attacks,
releases the skills,
But Su Mucheng did not give him
such an opportunity at all.
Sure enough,
Dancing rain makes full use of
the advantages of high spot,
her attack was too wide-ranging.
Windward Formation is in danger.
Sister Su is so strong.
The series multi-skill of Mounted Gun,
Few people in the league can do it.
Using the recoil of skills and common attack
to adjust her position and dodge the skills,
She's stronger than we can imagine.
It's rare for a female player
to play so powerfully and brilliantly.
They are fighting to the limit.
Sister Su, come on!
I'm sure Wei will win.
Dancing Rain is still accurately output
in the course of positioning.
Nice.
Her skills hit the target after floating in the air.
Windward Formation's HP is empty.
The final of Arena Contest,
Su Mucheng wins.
Congratulations on Su Mucheng.
Congratulations on Jia Shi.
So as the final of Arena Contest,
We can see that Su Mucheng is
as powerful as male player,
and we also saw Wei Chen's persistence and elegance.
Thank you for bringing us
such a wonderful game,
and letting us feel
the glorious spirit behind the game.
That little girl
really grew up.
The young people are really something.
We old people have to catch up.
Su Muchueng won the game.
Congratulations on Su Mucheng. Congratulations on Jia Shi.
# You are as always #
# From adversity to glory #
# I am as always #
This is the end of
my relationship with Jia Shi.
# I am an ordinary, but more than ordinary. #
# I am at the summit, looking for another summit. #
# We will meet again when the day comes. #
Su Mucheng, Su Mucheng, Su Mucheng.
# We go through deep and down. #
# We stand at the starry summit. #
= Jia Shi Team Su Mucheng =
# Now I finally understand what I used to be. #
# I have always been my own hero. #
= Jia Shi Team Su Mucheng =
# I have seen the legend before. #
Su Mucheng, Su Mucheng, Su Mucheng.
# You are as always #
# From adversity to glory #
# I am as always #
# Remain true to original aspiration #
Stay,
and play well.
For our Jia Shi,
for our
ten years.
We can't be teammates in tomorrow's game.
We can't play together as a team
in the later game, right?
Xing Xin and Jia Shi
will eventually meet in the Challenge.
Then,
welcome to be an opponent.
I still want to be
your fifth best partner
rather than an opponent.
But,
How long will it take
to fight together again?
# We will go together and shake the world #
# We will go together to the legend #
I'm Su Mucheng.
Today, I officially returned to the team.
# I am an ordinary, but more than ordinary. #
# I am at the summit, looking for another summit. #
# We will meet again when the day comes. #
# We are stronger than we used to be. #
It seems that
I've really been away for a long time.
Leave it to me then.
# I have seen the legend before. #
The Arena Contest is over.
The score of Jia Shi to Xing Xin is 10 to 8.
The total score is 34 to 29.
Jia Shi entered the Team Competition
with a five-point lead.
Captain Yu and Shaotian, please have some rest.
Suit yourself.
OK.
I don't know
what your sponsor's thinking about,
they ask Wang Jiexi to comment on
the Team Competition.
That guy has two different eye pixels,
I really doubt if he can see
the broadcast screen clearly then.
You're here.
It's doesn't matter whether I can see it clearly,
but I saw clearly the game that
Wei Cao eliminated Lan Yu.
Of course
you can see that clearly,
because you are in good health,
you pay attention to the health care,
An old man like you
drinks such bitter things.
We young people all drink sweets.
I'm really worried about you suffer from the bitter
from the throat to the tips of your toes.
It's bitter in the mouth after drinking tea,
but it's bitter in your heart
after losing the game.
Do you think I made a good point,
anchor Pan?
I think... I have no idea.
I'm thirsty.
Well, wasn't Wei Cao
also blocked by Ambitions before the finals?
My coffee is as bitter
as your tea.
If Wei Cao play with Ambitions one more time,
they may not win.
Captain Han.
Anything to drink?
Water.
Nothing else?
The water is so ordinary,
nothing new.
It's normal for Ambitions to win,
there's no need for new ideas.
Captain Wang just said that
Ambitions doesn't necessarily win Wei Cao,
what do you think, anchor Pan?
What... what do I think...
I... I...
I've got a phone call.
You guys go on.
Hello, director Li,
when on earth will you come back?
The exciting Team Competition is about to begin.
If you think the Arena Contest is not enough,
You'll have the privilege of witnessing a brilliant confrontation
between the two great tacticians,
Xiao Shiqin and Ye Qiu.
Will the steady master of detail dominate the situation,
or the genius Freelancer with frequent tricks
control the game?
Let's see it in the game.
There's five-point difference between Xing Xin and Jia Shi,
It's not easy to comeback.
It is very likely that
Jia Shi will continue their victorious pursuit.
Every player is eager to win.
Especially those veterans
who have countless games left.
Go to the victory,
or go to the end.
Now both teams please take your place.
Lao Ye.
Lao Ye come on! Lao Ye come on!
Audience friends,
The final of Challenge of Glory,
Team Competition between Xing Xin and Jia Shi
will begin soon.
All players have entered the battle room.
After the Arena Contest,
Jia Shi is five points ahead of
Xing Xin in total points.
For Xing Xin,
if they want to win the championship,
this Team Competition...
Back to Alliance,
enjoy the game.
OK. All the characters enter the map.
The game officially starts.
Xing Xin's opening formation was well maintained
under Ye Qiu's command.
The purpose of the positioning is clear.
This is very important
in Team Competition.
Right. We can see that
after Xiao Shiqin's joining,
Tactical discipline
has also been improved.
Tactical positioning.
The formation of Jia Shi begins to change.
They don't want to get in touch with Xing Xin too early,
although they are still far away...
Plan B.
...they are still cautious about their position.
Well,
tactical positioning was adopted on both teams at the beginning.
Every detail before the two teams
meat each other is crucial
in such a game.
Jia Shi stops moving at this point.
We see that
Xing Xin also stops moving.
Master Jiexi,
what do you think of this?
Xiao Shiqin and Ye Qiu are
both experienced commanders.
They know very well that
taking the lead in discovering the opponent
will have some advantages.
Therefore, quiet approaching
and find the opportunity is preferred.
We are suddenly enlightened
after Master Jiexi's explanation.
Jun Moxiao suddenly fired a shot.
This way.
Jia Shi will judge Xing Xing's position
according to the sound of shot.
Ye Qiu deliberately sent out signals to the opponent.
This is part of the tactics.
Turn left.
Xing Xin immediately
began to move quickly.
Another shot.
Jia Shi immediately stopped moving.
They haven't met yet,
But both the tacticians
have begun to compete.
The third shot.
The three shots came from
three different directions.
It's a diversion.
They split up into two teams.
Jun Moxiao must go alone.
Let's hit it.
Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei plug in,
I bet you catch up with Jun Moxiao.
Copy that.
We see that Jia Shi has branched out into two teams.
Combat Form is with Leaf of Autumn,
the other three are together.
Xiao Shiqin found the target according to
- the time and location of the shot. - Found him.
Leaf of Autumn found
Jun Moxiao alone.
Assign two Battlemages to chase me,
what an amazing intuition.
The diversion is working.
Now it's double pin down time.
I dragged their two main players.
Those three guys are up to you four.
Copy that.
The battlefield is now divided.
Jun Moxiao confront with
Leaf of Autumn and Combat Form alone,
Xing Xin's absolute core
separated from his teammates,
Jia Shi obviously won't let go of
this opportunity easily.
On the other side, Xing Xin's playing four on three,
but it will not be difficult for Jia Shi
to have Xiao Shiqin in the battle.
Now Leaf of Autumn catches up with Jun Moxiao.
Dragon Breaks the Ranks.
Jun Moxiao is blown up.
Meanwhile, Combat Form has arrived.
Jun Moxiao is intercepted.
No way.
You've learned all I taught.
How dare you intercept me here?
I dare to do
anything to win.
It's Shadow Tactic.
Combat Form
becomes Leaf of Autumn's wingman.
Jun Moxiao was trapped
under the attack of those two.
Sun Xiang,
don't you like solo?
This is Team Competition.
I think in this era of stars,
very few teams
will use this tactic.
Today Qiu Fei's performance
makes us reconsider
what is the real Shadow Tactic.
Where's he?
Shadow Separation.
Jun Moxiao suddenly disappeared.
Leaf of Autumn and Combat Form start seeking.
The launching scope of Shadow Separation
is fifteen position unit.
He won't go too far.
Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei judged that
the location of Shadow Separation won't be too far.
They continue to seek for him.
But we can see that Master Ye Qiu's dodging
is very smart,
he hasn't been found yet.
Jun Moxiao's HP has been consumed
by 70% at present.
The whole state is quite passive.
Dragon Soaring.
Too decisive.
Mechanical Rotor, dodging in the air,
and found Combat Form at his convenience.
Cloud Seize.
Your Shadow Tactic
is not flawless at all.
This is an opportunity, Ye Qiu counterattacked.
You're the support,
why do you stand in the way of mine?
What are you dawdling behind?
Put up or shut up.
Fine.
Ye Qiu seized the opportunity to disrupt
the main attacker position and the attack rhythm of support.
Sun Xiang was forced to stand in the support Position.
Qiu Fei could not stop Ye Qiu's attack.
It's not so easy to break through.
Shadow Tacti has not just one main attacker position.
Such a pity.
Your tactic didn't work.
Xiao Shiqin told us that
you make the diversion,
we'll beat you at your own game.
Everyone else in Xing Xin is a piece of loose sand
as long as we hold you back.
Yifan. They are in danger.
Be careful of the traps.
Let's turn our attention to the other part of the battlefield.
It's bounding mine.
Most players of Xing Xin
has been ambushed by Jia Shi.
It's the bounding mine arranged by Sheng Lingmie.
They are nearby.
Be aware.
Xing Xin doesn't lack of harm face to face,
Their best choice is
to focus on fighting the Cleric Woven Shadow.
meanwhile they must pay attention
not to rush forward, or they'll be sneak attacked.
Found Woven Shadow.
Catch him up.
Han Yanrou's Dragon Breaks the Ranks
is intercepted by Successive Strike.
Woven Shadow counterattacks.
Han Yanrou, Yi Cunhui,
Bao Zi, the Invader are all consumed.
Xiao Shiqin had long anticipated that
Xing Xin will try her best to kill the Cleric...
Nice.
...and laid out a counter-attack strategy in advance.
Jia Shi is constantly accumulating advantages.
Right. Let's see.
After this fight,
Xing Xin team lost a lot of HP.
Only 70% left.
Xing Xin is at a disadvantage in both battlefields.
Someone needs to help Jun Moxiao out of trouble.
Yes.
We can see that Jun Moxiao is still
entangled by the two Battlemages of Jia Shi.
When you get back to your teammates,
they're all dead.
I'm wrong.
you won't go back.
Critical moment.
He hit Leaf of Autumn and Combat Form.
They all fell to the ground straight and stiff.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Thanks.
Wu Chen.
Xing Xin indeed holds back a trick.
It took some time to climb up.
Nice timing.
Next,
it's your turn, Lian Jin.
Copy that.
Launcher who occupies high spot without any interference,
It's horrible.
Dawn Rifle continupusly releases the skills.
The dodging of Sheng Lingmie and Woven Shadow is restricted.
They are very passive.
The Counterattack Begins.
He killed Successive Strike with a series of skills.
Jia Shi lost one person.
This is Ye Qiu's Screen Gun Tactic
founded in Jia Shi.
Today Xing Xin suppressed Jia Shi
with this classical tactic.
This is undoubtedly another
psychological strike to Jia Shi.
Now it seems that
Xing Xin is more like a former Jia Shi.
Exactly.
Now the momentum of Xing Xin
has undoubtedly reached to the top.
Long live Xing Xin!
We can't lose to them.
Jia Shi will win!
Long live Xing Xin!
Jia Shi! Jia Shi!
Jiaxing, pay attention to our HP.
Sharpshooter, prepare for support.
Copy that.
On my way.
We can see that
Jia Shi's substitute Matchstick is in.
Baozi, Tang Rou.
The coordination is 373 480.
Climb over directly,
kill the Cleric.
Understood.
Jia Shi's substitute is in,
and will arrive in half a minute.
Senior Wu Chen,
captain will arrive one and a half minutes.
Understood.
One and a half minutes.
I'll stall their Sharpshooter.
Well, in order to intercept Matchstick,
Dawn Rifle gives up the advantage of long-range,
and fight close with Matchstick.
Matchstick makes full use of
sharpshooter's flexible advantage,
Keep dodging and finding shelters.
This is what Xing Xin would like to see very much.
If Matchstick doesn't return quickly,
Xing Xin will fight one man more,
and kill Jia Shi's Cleric.
What are you doing? Come over quickly.
On the way.
The Launcher of Xing Xin
keeps following me.
It's obvious that
Matchstick is suffering from Dawn Rifle's stalling.
His teammates are also under a lot of pressure.
It has to be said that
his performance so far has been crucial.
He is the greatest contributor
to Xing Xin's advantage.
Exactly.
The Launcher operated by Wu Chen
is too aggressive,
he dares to stick close to the Sharpshooter.
We know Launchers would suffer a lot in close combat.
This is the tactic. he chose to entangle his opponent.
My god. Launcher fight me close.
Is he crazy?
It's not like
a duel between
two Launchers at all.
He's trading his own HP consumption for time
to hold his opponent back.
Is this man crazy?
Matchstick seizes the opportunity, headshot.
Dawn Rifle is in danger.
Baozi,
hold on,
Healing the low HP.
Don't worry about me.
You cover Tang.
Ten more seconds.
Be there in nine seconds.
Hang in there.
Dawn Rifle and Matchstick have turned white-hot
on the other side of the battlefield.
They both aim each other.
Nice.
Dawn Rifle is killed first.
Wait.
Dawn Rifle launched his skill at the last minute,
there's no time for Matchstick to dodge, he's killed, too.
Master Jiexi,
Can you give us an analysis of
the current situation on the battlefield?
These techniques are critical.
Dawn Rifle successfully killed Matchstick,
mission is beautifully accomplished.
Now Jia Shi's substitute has been killed,
Xing Xin's substitute Cleric, Cold Hands
will soon join the battlefield.
= You've killed by Matchstick. =
Then,
I'll leave it to you guys.
Wu Chen,
great game.
He killed Woven Shadow with a close hit.
Long live Xing Xin.
Ye Qiu is the master.
Xing Xin goes a step further,
They've killed three people, the situation is very good.
Then,
leave it to us.
So far Xing Xin still has five people left in the battlefield.
Jia Shi only has three left.
Xing Xin's Launcher gave up the long-range advantage,
took away Jia Shi's Sharpshooter
with himself,
won over lots of time for the team.
It can be said that
he is the match point in this game.
Moreover, Jun Moxiao arrived in time,
helped the team kill Jia Shi's Cleric.
Now Jia Shi lost three in row,
the situation is far from good.
But why did captain Xiao
send the two main players out?
If it weren't two main players,
Jia Shi can't hold Ye Qiu back.
But captain Xiao thought
the winning point was Ye Qiu,
He didn't expect the other players
in Xing Xin to grow up so fast.
Even the newcomer Qiao Yifan
can take the lead.
Xiao Shiqin,
you are poor of HP,
I say you just surrender.
If that makes captain Ye happy.
Sheng Lingmie stops suddenly.
Does the tactician still have any trick?
The situation is too tense.
Any operational details can make
a world-shaking change in the situation.
Sheng Lingmie is self-destructing.
Stand back.
An instantaneous explosion.
It's a self-destruction.
Xiao Shiqin let the situation reverse directly.
It's amazing.
The points before with the points of Arena Contest,
Xing Xin has to remain
three players to win.
Han Yanrou, Yi Cunhui,
Bao Zi, the Invader are all low HP,
if Sheng Lingmie's self-destruction
can kill all three,
Jia Shi will win the game in advance.
Let's see
the effect of this self-destruction.
Yi Cunhui's out.
Bao Zi, the Invader is out.
Han Yanrou's HP is only 5% left.
How did she survive?
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Han Yanrou's HP is nearly empty,
we can win in advance if we hit her.
Combat Form and Leaf of Autumn
are chasing after Han Yanrou,
Leaf of Autumn intercepts.
A Freelancer and a Battlemage
versus two other battlemages.
Jia Shi concentrates attack on Han Yanrou,
whose HP is only 5% left.
Xing Xin conducts a desperate struggle.
Tang Rou.
Two minutes and fifty-eight seconds left.
They have to be aced.
We have to remain three people.
Tang, hang in there.
Understood.
Nice.
Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. He hit Han Yanrou.
Jun Moxiao's healing
is almost at the same time.
Han Yanrou's little HP goes up again.
It remains at 1%.
Magic Shield.
Han Yanrou didn't give up the chance to attack
while she's HP is almost empty.
Keep consuming.
Let's kill her now.
As Jun Moxiao battles his opponent,
he needs to find a chance
to heal Han Yanrou.
Only Ye Qiu can do this.
But now Jun Moxiao's healing skills
are all cooling down.
He won't save Han Yanrou this time.
Now no one can save you.
Leaf of Autumn hits back Han Yanrou.
Danger.
She still has 1% HP left.
How could this happen?
It's Cold Hands.
Xing Xin's substitute Cleric arrived
at time at the critical moment.
Everyone,
sorry for the waiting.
How about it?
Even if I'm worse,
I'm Xing Xin's Cleric.
# The starry fireflies from the ordinary #
# sailing with the wind and converge into the Milky Way #
# standing on the top and claiming that #
# We will regain our glory #
# Push the clouds aside and shine the light #
The Team Competition is drawing to an end.
The last sixty seconds.
Will Xing Xin tries their best
to turn back the situation and win,
or Jia Shi makes a breakthrough and defend the Glory?
# The past overlaps the present #
# The glory we've missed #
# The pride in the future #
# Intertwined between the fingers #
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
# The only light during the long night #
# Is us from the ordinary life #
Kill Combat Form.
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
# I came from the past and will write the future #
Go for it.
Go for it, Tang.
Long live Xing Xin!
Hold out!
All of you, hold out!
Leave them to me.
Don't hold back.
Go straight up.
Do you know what you're talking about?
Our goal is to win the championship.
It's not the win or lose of the game.
Do you know that?
Tang,
run.
Now Han Yanrou's HP is only 10%.
Cold Hands' HP
is only 30%.
Hit them.
But Combat Form's last skill,
Destroying the World,
consumes too much.
Jun Moxiao wants to support,
but it's too late.
Han Yanrou, Cold Hands and Combat Form's
HP are all empty.
# We are the brightest fireflies #
So now the two teams are tied in the Team Competition.
But the totol points of Xing Xin is still
five points behind Jia Shi.
Even if Jia Shi is aced by Xing Xin and gains points,
Xing Xin will still lose by one point.
In other words,
Jia Shi has already locked in the championship.