=The King's Avatar
=Episode 7
Do you still need me to continue to ask
This is it, Captain
It's him. He said at the beginning.
Ask me to brush a Copy
I said I wouldn't go with him
Then he threatened me
And then he said
to take an unfinished thing
To bring umbrella back to life
Also said to add a little excitement
to the Glory
Wait a minute
He really said so
He actually said like this
I want to add a little excitement
to the Glory
That's what he said
It's quite serious
I swear
Sorry, Ye Qiu
There is still time to brush the copy after the match.
It seems that the training given to you by the team is not enough.
Captain, didn't you just say
we wouldn't talk about this matter
You will keep your promise, will you
Yes, I will
Unless ..
Unless what
You brush out the Smart Umbrellas.
This is stealing
Captain, is this behavior
a little shameless
You know, we Lan Yu have always been
aboveboard.
Will this
How can this be said to be shameless?
We just borrowed it to study it.
I will return it when we finish the study.
By the way, you may not be able to beat him
Captain, you are responsible for what you say.
I can't beat him
I'll tell you what
I can beat him in minutes.
Believe it or not
I'll be waiting for you for three hours.
Is it really only three hours
When can you finish
the training match with me
Mr. Ye Qiu
Quick, quick, quick
Up, up, up
All right, that's it.
Why are you so slow
Not many moves. Not many moves. Come on
Opportunity
OK
Not bad, this boy
How many have you won in a row?
You see, this Yu Wenzhou just can't do it.
Hand speed is too slow
How can I compare with you?
Be quiet.
I'd like to announce one thing to you all.
Our training camp will officially test all of you tomorrow.
with last elimination system
Is everyone clear
Don't go. Don't go
Yu Wenzhou, you are the only one I have ever seen
who have not won a formal competition.
If you lose again this time, you will be eliminated.
If you want to take this as a career
you have to work hard
Understand
All right, students
Line up and draw lots to choose your fighting teacher.
Quickly
I'll go back first.
OK
Don't be shy
Don't be shy.
Just draw lots
Quick, quick, quick, quick
Have a look
Who is it? Open it quickly
Quickly
Come on, who is it?
Who?
Don't hide it
Ye Qiu
You won the grand prize
You never won a game
There is no suspense.
Yeah
Come on
Come on, you
It's okay.
The jeers of the students
Let me inferiority to the extreme
I started an endless night
to practice like crazy
Warlock Hit battlemage
It was a bad match
The only turning point
Is whether I can release a big curse arrow
But it takes ten seconds to sing
To get the maximum energy
It is impossible not to be interrupted
The only possibility
Is to completely control him for ten seconds
Only five seconds
The singing will still be interrupted.
We must find a way to fight for another five seconds.
This is a disaster
No suspense
I'm sure I can't beat it.
There is no suspense
Here we go.
Here we go
The dragon teeth sprint leaf teacher came up so fiercely
No mercy
Sprint as soon as you get up.
Look up into the sky
Mr. Ye Qiu, Mr. Ye Qiu
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Two minutes and eighteen seconds
It became the driving force for me to move forward.
Ye Qiu also became
the opponent I most want to meet on the arena
It's done
Captain, wait a minute
What is this
Smart Umbrella
Captain
I followed your Captain's instructions strictly.
A Smart Umbrella were brought in successfully and quickly.
Mission completed
Lan Yu steal things so obviously
It's a robbery
Long time no see
You two
good friends who are very strong
It was not easy to get together
You two catch on
I'll go first. Bye-bye
You are very interested in my Smart Umbrella.
I'd like to have a try
the power of Smart Umbrella
The two minutes and eighteen seconds is what I owe you.
This is what I owe myself
Two minutes and eighteen seconds
Hide yourself to prevent interruption
Very skilled
Overpraise
Indeed as expected it is a great weapon
It seems that your singing speed has also improved
But that's it.
There's another move
Did you do your best this time
I do my best in every match.
Smart Umbrella with scattered people
Maybe it can really change the pattern of the alliance
But
Maybe you can rely on Smart Umbrella
and a variety of skills to stir the wind and cloud
How are you going to pass the challenge in the realm of God
I don't think too much as you do.
It takes too much brain cells.
With that time
I think you should think about it first
How can Huang Shaotian be prevented from running around
Ye Qiu
Hope to see you next time
You can add some excitement to Glory
Each of us is growing up
through pains
In a glorious world
We learn to reconcile with ourselves
Okay, come on, let's smile.
Three, two, one
OK
Come and hold your chest with both hands.
Good
Three, two, one
OK
Let's take a look at 45 degrees.
here
OK
Three, two, one
Still no good
This eye of yours is a little too obvious.
It's still a big one and a small one.
All right, fine. I'll adjust it again
Both eyes are bigger.
Good, good
Let me do it
Hold tightly
Look at 45 degrees
This time the picture is ok.
Eyes are the same.
Captain
Go ahead. What is it
Recently, there was a guy named Jun Moxiao in the 10th District.
The associations are not peaceful.
I doubt it.
He is a professional player of other teams.
It's a trip for us.
This is the end of today's work.
Today's task is very arduous.
Are you ready?
Ready
Forty-seven
Forty-eight
How are you doing over there
Fifty-three
This is too unfair
I can only fight one by one
You attack faster than me.
This time we're going to fight Toya
It is not too difficult to play
But the reason why it has
still not been knocked out
It is because of the steps before the fight against Tonya
are closely linked
There is a time limit besides triviality
We can't make mistakes, Tang
Mind your own business
This Tang and Ye Qiu have been playing Glory for a long time
The cooperation is quite tacit
But Tang
played with us before
Now she only play with men
in the internet cafe.
Continue
Watch your step
Front, two
Tang
Accelerate
Guoguo, wait a minute
Tang, Sky Hit
Good
Tang
We need to work harder.
A cake shop opened nearby.
I heard it was delicious
Let's go together
We will go when I have time.
Watch your back
What's the matter?
There are several questions I can't do
You must help me.
Why don't you teach me?
Of course you can. write it down first
I'll solve them later.
Continue
Play every day
Did I recruit you to play Glory?
Go to work quickly
From now on, you will practice with Tang.
Improving her skills is your job.
To the left
Smelly boy playing trick with me
Delete
Don't
What are you doing
You record it
Guoguo
Tang
Let's eat and play something together.
Do something
It's my treat. Let's go.
All right, stop it
We are now brushing copies
Can we go later?
Back off
Ultimate skill, pay attention to blood volume
Add blood
Strength and Difficulty of Team Training
is not suitable for you
Go back to training camp first.
and improve the skill level
Then come back again
My name is Qiao Yifan.
I’m an Assassin in the Wei Cao team
I am a professional player
with examination result always at the bottom.
I've never been on the arena before.
Professional player
Come on, come on.
Two, three
Yingjie
Come and take pictures together.
Quick, quick, quick
Yingjie, Yifan went to the training school.
It is estimated that it will be very difficult to come back.
Leave this position to us.
Step down, all of you
Let me take a handsome photo
with the future captain's successor
Good
Come
Watch me knock you out with a brick.
It was clearly mine
It belongs to who wins
Everyone has a ten-minute break.
The next boss, Toya
will be a tough battle.
Didn't you just say it wasn't difficult
This is designed according to the standard of ten people.
The leader of the wild map
The difficulty is not high.
But there are only three of us
Not good
This Jun Moxiao is doing
Toya's predecessors
This is the last step
There will be another first kill
Is it?
All the players
gather at the training room in ten minutes.
Emergency training
The performance of this training
Will be included in this month's assessment results
Those absent scored zero in this month's assessment.
What kind of training is so exaggerated
Absence is zero
So to put it this way
If I did well
Is it possible to be in the starting line-up?
Let's go, let's train
Go, go, go, go
Go, Yingjie
Hello
Yifan, wait
Yingjie
New opportunities
What are the new opportunities
Let's go
Where to?
Fast
Sorry
No
This is an activity led by the captain.
You do well
Maybe you won't have to go to training camp.
Are you ready
Okay
Go
Captain
Sit down
Go sit down
Yingjie, you go first
I'll find you
Starting in five minutes
I am waiting to see your results.
Encircle and suppress Jun Moxiao
Thank you
I must be in five minutes
Find a computer
In order to catch up with the examination
Stop
What's the matter, Boss
Ambush
Ying Jie directed the operation.
Received
Spread out and fight one by one
Liufei stuck position
Don't lose the target
OK
Ye Bai, be careful, not to underestimate the enemy
Xiao Yun hard, cold and soft
Pay attention to the preservation of physical strength.
Understand
Eat me a brick
Didn't you say to use the brick
I won't lose even if we end up together.
Steamed Bun, you are good.
Come back to help Tang
She's stuck
OK
Don't have to
Compared with my hand speed
I don't believe you can match me.
Send the head
I told you to wait for the Steamed Bun
You don't smile can insist on so long
Not to be outdone
I think a positive victory is almost impossible
Toya
They're going to fight Toya
You must pass through this cave.
The terrain here is complex and suitable for ambush.
Shadow copy
Yingjie, watch the back
Lose
It is no surprise.
But I didn't think of it
You lost so fast
Xiao Yun
Aggression is your greatest enemy.
No one ever started the match first.
Who will win
Yes
Liu Fei
It's good to care about your teammates.
But whenever a teammate is in danger
You lose your correct judgment of the whole situation.
This is the main problem you need to overcome at present.
All right, captain
Ye Bai
Captain, I'll practice my low-level accounts well.
Find that again tonight.
The man who told Jun not to laugh avenged himself.
Do you think today's failure
It's because you used low-level accounts.
I
Is that what you all think
A regular member of a champion team.
But want to copy inside
Encircling an ordinary player
This is not worth all your efforts at all.
Right?
Yingjie
What do you think of this Jun Moxiao's strength
Very impressive
How powerful is it
Experienced
Attacks and skills are used properly.
All judgments are accurate.
He is better than all of us.
Yes, better than all of you.
Strong enough to wipe out your entire army.
So don't despise any enemy
Today is a good lesson
After returning home
Take a good look at the video of the match.
I hope you have something to gain.
who is this Jun Moxiao exactly
You met today
is the greatest Boss in the history of Glory
Ye Qiu
Ye Qiu, Ye Qiu
Look at this
It's kind of interesting.
Hang on, Yifan.
Let him stop
I'll find him
You have a lot of ideas, but unfortunately
You didn't find your problem
What's the problem?
Master is different.
The heat is killing me.
The operation is too handsome.
What are you doing
Today's training video
This is when Yingjie lose
Yeah
Yes, this is it
It was a terrible loss, wasn't it?
Do you know what this is called
This is called the Shadow Copy
Ye Bai
Come back and watch it again.
Where is the captain?
The Captain?
The captain should left now
In fact, it's nothing
The captain is afraid that you will lose too badly.
After all, the other party is Ye Qiu.
This is it
Jun Moxiao is Ye Qiu
The Master deserves his reputation
Yeah
When do you think I can be so good
Practice well
There is no water, Yifan
If it's okay, can you pour me a glass of water.
Thank you
Pour one more cup for me
Look at you, look at you, Liu Fei
Look at you, look at you
You see, you lost first
Don't look at me. I didn't play well today.
This is not how I used to be
In fact, I think
It would be nice for Yifan to go to glory training camp.
Stay in our team
It is even worse to be a server forever.
Keep watching. Keep watching
This one lost even worse.
Work hard
Liu Fei, Ye Bai water
Thank you. Thank you
You see this operation is handsome
This is quite handsome.
Isn't that you
This is very powerful.
But then again
It’s useless
Can’t beat Wei Cao
Exactly
By the way, Yingjie
I heard
the restaurant we always go to
is renovated recently.
It may take a long time
before we can eat its takeout
So you have to help me eat more.
Why this face
I'm just going to train for a few days.
I will come back
Come back early.
Of course
When I come back
I must defeat the Jun Moxiao
I heard them say that the captain intends to train you.
to be a successor
Yingjie, come on
You too
I'm leaving
In fact, I think
it would be nice for Yifan to go to glory training camp.
Stay in our team
It is even worse to be a server forever.
Okay, thank you