= The King’s Avatar =
= Episode 37 =
You fool, you're the winner.
You finally made up your mind to surpass me.
# You are as always #
# Keep calm even though I have to leave #
Go on.
I'll wait for you at the terminal.
# writing an ending for the story. #
# I am an ordinary, but more than ordinary. #
# I am at the summit, looking for another summit. #
# We will meet again when the day comes. #
# We are stronger than we used to be. #
# We go through deep and down. #
# We stand at the starry summit. #
Team Xing Xin will fight... Mo Fan, come here.
= Team Xing Xin, Super Xing Xin defeats low Jia Shi =
- Captain. - Captain.
Captain.
Wait a moment.
Does boss dislike me?
Why I only got an exclamatory mark?
You all have a character.
The sight of your character makes me happier.
= Xing Xin Team =
= Defeats =
Captain.
= Xing Xin Team =
Come on, let's take a picture. Here.
Come on.
Let's get ready.
The adjustment of competition system for the Challenge Final.
Captain.
Cancel the Individual Event.
Turn the Arena Contest from three players to five players.
The score will be based on how many players you kill.
You will get two points for killing one player.
It means that you will lose two points for one player get killed.
The score will be enlarged if we are heedless.
I can figure out more than six ways to comeback by now.
But we only have one choice.
Smile for the camera.
= Adjustments of competition system for the Challenge Final =
Just look over there when we take pictures later.
This adjustment will not only leads to our victory,
we will also crush them by the biggest score gap in history.
Am I right?
We will get two points by killing one player.
There will be two bonus points
if we can kill them all within the prescribed time.
Do you ever think it will give the Xing Xin Team
the same chance to comeback?
Could you please shut up?
If you can't say something nice, don't say anything at all.
We won't give anyone a chance.
We can't take the risk.
Each killing counts.
- Are you with me or not? - Fine. Fine.
Let's take photos. Come on!
Here. Get ready.
Is there still one person missing?
= Jia Shi Team =
Let's have a look.
I found a very famous coach in this field.
And helped you to develop a whole training program for you.
In the next three years...
You can see that...
Three years?
Right.
Your contract with Jia Shi is about to expire.
Here. A brand new contract.
Just check and sign it.
It's just a process.
Mr. Tao, I won't sign an extension with Jia Shi.
I will leave here as long as the contract expires.
Don't you think about it?
I am sorry.
I want a fresh start.
Are you...
going to join Xing Xin Team?
I will go to take pictures first.
What's wrong?
Do you want to leave Jia Shi in such a hurry?
Can you play well in such a state?
I'm a professional eSports player.
As long as I am a member of Jia Shi,
I will try my best to win.
No one knows if you're doing your best in the match.
Who knows?
What a pity!
Since you put it that way,
I won't let you play in the final.
What a pity!
Till now...
You don't know what's the meaning of professional players.
Refine the make-up.
You! Stand there!
Just stand there!
Captain, this is your central position.
The central position is at where I stand.
Here. Get ready!
Three. Two. One.
# The starry fireflies from the ordinary #
# sailing with the wind and converge into the Milky Way #
= The Night of Champions =
= Count Down for the Challenge Final =
# standing on the top and claiming that #
# We will regain our glory #
# The glory we've missed #
# The pride in the future #
# Intertwined between the fingers #
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
# The only light during the long night #
# Is us from the ordinary life #
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
# I came from the past and will write the future #
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
# The glorious moment of coronation #
# Push the clouds aside and shine the light #
# Break the ice and cross the mountains #
# At this peak moment #
# The past overlaps the present #
# The glory we've missed #
# The pride in the future #
# Intertwined between the fingers #
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
# The only light during the long night #
# Is us from the ordinary life #
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
There is a heavy traffic jam.
We're three kilometers from the stadium.
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
# The glorious moment of coronation #
= The Night of Champions =
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
Your contract is about to expire after this match.
Are you going to have a contract extension?
Sorry, this is our internal arrangement.
It's inconvenient to disclose now.
You were the dream ticket before, but becomes opponents now.
It's a hot topic in the last three days.
What's your opinion?
Are you going to fight with Ye Qiu today?
Or you are not going to enter the field tonight?
Su Mucheng, it's said that you are going to join Xing Xin.
Are you going to avoid doing anything that may arouse suspicion?
Don't worry, everybody!
Mucheng is a professional player.
What's your feeling to against your previous employer?
Are you still communicating in private?
What's your plan in the next if you fail to join the league?
Right, what's your plan in the next?
- Master Ye, please tell us more. - Thank you.
Yeah, please tell us more.
Miss Tang.
You said you will do the one-against-three in public
before the match with Zhu Xian.
You would resign if you can't.
So are you here to cheer today?
I am here to play.
Are you going to disavow your public statement?
You broke your promise. How can you just let it go?
I am sorry.
I didn't fulfill my promise.
I let Xing Xin's fans down.
Today,
I apologize for my recklessness and impulsiveness.
But I won't quit.
I will stick with it even I have to break my promise.
There is obviously a huge gap between you and Jia Shi.
And the rules have changed in final.
- You have no chance to win so far. - Can you win?
You don't know until you try.
Let's go.
They are having huge advantages.
So they will keep it steadily.
I think they will use conventional tactics.
Tang, you take the lead in the Arena Contest.
If everything goes well, your opponent is Sun Xiang.
Just keep to play it intrepidly and to infuriate him duly.
I see.
You are the next. Play it rhythmically to consume his patience.
Yifan, you are the third one.
Beat him by using outflanking tactics.
Wei Chen and I...
will do the rest.
No problem.
And...
Where is our boss?
I've handed the list accurately.
Tonight is a night of glory for all of us.
Fighting!
Everyone, listen to me.
We can do nothing on the stage. But we can cheer up for them.
Let us practice our slogan again.
Okay.
Fans are everywhere!
Xing Xin, you are irreplaceable!
We must pay attention to the rhythm and our vigour.
And our motions also.
Just take a break.
Here. Here.
Just take this. All right.
Here. Just take it.
Here. Here. Here.
This is nice.
Come here. Take it.
This color really suits you.
Here. I help you to wear it.
Just wear it.
Has everybody got it? Here. Here.
= Block B =
Han... Han Wenqing.
Zhang Xinjie. Wang Jiexi.
It's really them.
So many masters are here.
Bro, what a blockbuster!
Hello, Zhou Zekai.
Where are you? What's wrong?
You can't put on airs to me
for you are handsome and popular.
I tell you what. The game is going to begin.
We are all waiting for you.
Just tell me if you are coming or not.
Hello?
The sponsor invited him to do the commentary.
Will Zhou Zekai come here too?
How can you ignore me?
What's wrong with your sponsor?
To invite him to do the commentary?
The cost performance is too low.
Although he is the most handsome in the league.
So what?
To do the commentary, your eloquence need to be excellent.
He is so tedious but charging too much.
It's better to put a humanoid card board here.
It's the same.
Huang Shaotian, you are careful to offend his fans.
It's okay. His fans won't know.
These microphones are already on.
Right.
Welcome to the Challenge Final of Glory.
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
Tonight, we are honor to be here
to witness the birth of a champion.
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
The victory will goes to our ever-victorious general
or will it goes to our new star?
Let's see.
We will use new rules tonight.
There will be the Arena Contest and the Team Competition.
They will dispatch six players each to play the Arena Contest.
The score will base on how many opponents they kill.
They will get two points for killing one opponent.
And all the bonus rules will be remained.
Jia Shi Team got twenty four points in the group stage.
And Xing Xin Team got twenty one points.
So Jia Shi Team has a three points advantage in the final.
Tonight, our commentators are...
The captain of Lan Yu Team, Yu Wenzhou.
Hello.
And...
I am the best Swordsman of both talent and beauty in history.
I am Huang Shaotian.
Okay. Let's cut the crap.
Let's get down to business.
Let's see.
Who are going to play in the first round?
Alright.
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
Xing Xin Team is going to appointment Tang Rou first.
Her role is Han Yanrou.
A Battlemage.
Fighting! Tang!
Even she plays the Glory less than one year,
but her style is so tough.
And she comes to the fore quickly with exceptional talent.
Let's see who will represent Jia Shi to play the first round.
It's him.
Jia Shi Team is going to appointment Xiao Shiqin first.
His role is Sheng Lingmie. A Mechanic.
Jia Shi gave up their frequently-used tactics.
Captain.
Although Sun Xiang is so reckless,
he always want to take the first formation.
But he didn't this time.
Has he become smarter?
Captain. Captain. Captain.
They must thought that I will be the first one to play.
Mistake!
Be humble.
I am telling the truth.
Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
Jia Shi Team appoints Xiao Shiqin to take the lead.
They must made some adjustments according to the new rules.
We don't know if it's in Xing Xin's plan.
What should we do now?
Our previous deployments were all messed up.
Tang Rou and Mo Fan will be restrained by Xiao Shiqin.
Tang said she will insist even she has to break her promise.
Besides, it's just Xiao Shiqin now.
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
The Challenge Final of Glory.
The first round of Arena Contest is going to begin.
Tang Rou, Han Yanrou.
Vs. Xiao Shiqin, Sheng Lingmie.
Captain Yu, what do you think about it?
Each has its advantages and disadvantages.
I think Tang Rou is likely to win.
Her APM will make Xiao Shiqin get rattled.
It's time to let newbie to show themselves.
Meets with Xiao Shiqin, the master of tactics,
can Tang Rou cover the shortage by her excellent APM?
Let's wait and see.
Okay. The game began.
We can saw that Tang Rou stick to her own style.
She rushed at the central of map at first.
The fight between Mechanic and Battlemage.
Xiao Shiqin will take the advantage of far shot.
He will choose to consume her in distant.
Sheng Lingmie found himself get discovered.
He chose to  pull away immediately.
Han Yanrou, got hit!
Han Yanrou adjusted herself quickly and fought back.
Tang Rou is so tough.
How could she fight back in such a situation?
Mechanical tracking will slow people down.
So the first choice is supposed to defend.
Or to dodge.
But Tang Rou chose to storm.
She'd rather to take the sacrifice of ultimate,
but still want to strike to approach him.
Xiao Shiqin was caught off guard.
Ladies and gentlemen, did you see that?
These masters of tactics are so cunning usually.
We need some unconventional players to teach them a lesson.
It's really exciting, right?
Sheng Lingmie throw a bounding mine.
Han Yanrou was unaware. She is in danger.
But she avoided it as well.
How could she realized?
Was it a coincidence? Or was it her intuition?
None.
She can catch the sound precisely.
As a pianist,
her hearing is much sharper than ordinary person.
Xiao Shiqin made a mistake by using Sound Trap.
Bravo!
Even Xiao Shiqin couldn't do anything about her.
Don't jump to conclusions.
He is one of the best four tacticians in Glory.
Xiao Shiqin.
Sheng Lingmie chose to use the Air Drops.
He wanted to astrict her blocking.
But Tang Rou is calm.
Han Yanrou lost track of her opponent.
Shaotian, let's guess.
As a master of tactics and a sharpie,
what will he do next?
He will use his strange weapons,
to make this fight goes into the environment that best suits him.
Whatever he do,
I hope Tang Rou can break the predicament and win.
It seems like Han Yanrou can't judge his intentions now.
She moved prudently.
Sheng Lingmie used his trick again.
Threw out two bounding mines by using Sound Trap.
Han Yanrou avoided them faultlessly.
It didn't work at all.
Why he chose to used this trick again?
He didn't want to consume her HP.
But to guide Tang Rou into his trap.
Game over.
The damage of the skill has been calculated.
It's about time.
Got hit! Han Yanrou was dead.
Sheng Lingmie led her into his own rhythm gradually.
And won the first round by 70% HP have left.
How could it be?
It's impossible.
Tang played it well all the time.
She has eluded so many attacks.
How could she lose?
Tang is quick in action and plays valiantly.
She is a talented offensive player.
Xiao Shiqin used her fortes to defeat her tactfully.
What do you mean?
Tang will get tired when she plays in high frequency.
Indeed.
She will become a fearful rival as Ye Qiu.
As a tactician,
we always look for opponents' loopholes to win the game.
But Tang Rou chose to look for opportunities to fight back
in the holes again and again.
She still chose to storm even in the most dangerous of times.
There's nothing impossible in Glory.
Although Xing Xin has lost the first round,
but Tang Rou, as a newbie,
has put lots of pressure on Jia Shi by her performance.
Although she lost the game,
but we knew that...
There's a rising Battlemage star in Glory.
She is Tang Rou.
Fighting!
It's okay.
Fighting! Fighting!
You did well!
Fighting!
How do you feel?
How about it?
I am so depressed.
Xiao Shiqin is the most horrible opponent I've met.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah.
Xiao Shiqin is so skillful.
No one has the confidence to defeat him
in the whole league.
There are always winners and losers.
I know.
But I couldn't do anything about him.
I didn't have any initiative even though I tried my best.
If this problem can be solved easily,
then I can teach you before you go to the stage.
What you're dealing with right now,
is the highest level player in Glory.
He wouldn't be where he is today
if he has some huge loopholes that can be used by others.
Keep trying!
Enrich yourself comprehensively!
There will be no shortcuts from now on.
Captain is right!
The Glory is so hard to play.
That's why it's interesting, right?
It's really interesting.
The next player from Xing Xin is Mo Fan.
= Glory Pro League =
He is a former Scrap Picker whose action is
fast, accurate and relentless and good at biding his time.
Can he break through the encirclement set by Xiao Shiqin?
And fight his way out.
Let's wait and see.
The second round of Arena Contest.
Xing Xin chose to dispatch their Ninja, Deception.
To challenge Jia Shi's Mechanic, Sheng Lingmie.
Xiao Shiqin, such an old fox...
As a master of tactics, although he won last round,
but his HP was consumed by Tang Rou.
Deception, fighting!
You still have the chance to win!
Okay. Game Started!
Deception is moving rapidly at the beginning.
He is finding the right place to hide himself.
This is a very typical opening for Ninja.
They will take the high ground first.
And to use the advantage of vision to find opportunities.
It seems like Mo Fan has the chance to break through.
Sheng Lingmie released the Electronic Eyes
to seek for Deception's position.
Xiao Shiqin knows Deception's strategy.
He is in patience.
He won't give Deception a chance to sneak attack.
Please don't hide anymore.
It's boring. Just fight!
Just fight face to face if you are real men.
You are the most famous chance taker in league.
You often use this tactic.
It means that your opponent can't find you for ages.
I just wait for chances to make no mistakes.
But they are so cheeky now.
We are different. You know?
You are so facetious.
Okay. Back to the game.
The Electronic Eyes is still seeking for Deception's position.
Deception used the shuriken.
He destroyed the Electronic Eyes.
Okay. We can see that Sheng Lingmie is taking actions.
It seems like he is heading for Deception's rear.
Sheng Lingmie has detected Deception's position.
Xiao Shiqin chose to rush at him directly.
But not to detour him from sides.
Maybe he wants to find out Deception as soon as possible.
Mo Fan knew that shuriken would expose his own position.
So when he used this skill,
he chose to move at the same time.
Deception attacked.
He used the ultimate, Moon-Slaying Sakura.
It was too close.
Sheng Lingmie couldn't avoid it but to take it.
We could see that after Sheng Lingmie got hit.
He launched a counterattack.
Mechanical Tracking. Deception got hit again.
Sheng Lingmie is still attacking.
Astrict his dodging by using bounding mine.
Body Replacement Technique.
Deception is adjusting his own position.
Disappearing Body Technique
after detonated bombs by using shuriken.
He avoided the Air Drops.
Mechanical Punch! Got hit!
Deception's HP is going to be zero.
In last moment,
all the skills of Deception are freezing.
They can figure out opponents' skills will be frozen.
This is the biggest difference
between professional players and ordinary players.
Mo Fan needs time to practice.
What should we do?
Nice!
Sheng Lingmie from Jia Shi killed Deception.
He did the one-against-two.
Sheng Lingmie's HP is 51% after two rounds.
He got four points.
Jia Shi Team got four points by killing two rivals.
Xing Xin didn't get any points.
The score on the field is four to zero now.
Xiao Shiqin hold the upper hand
in this fight between Mechanic and Ninja.
Xing Xin didn't get any points in the first two rounds.
And two of its players got killed.
The situation is not optimistic.
Sometimes, it's better to keep your skills.
I see.
If I have another match...
Sure we will.
There are nine points gap between Xing Xin and Jia Shi.
Xing Xin is going to dispatch Qiao Yifan.
If he can't win in the third round,
I think it will be hard for Xing Xin to comeback.
Yifan, fighting! Yifan, fighting!
Yifan, fighting!
Sorry. Excuse me.
You are from Wei Cao...
= The Ninth Challenge of Glory =
Qiao Yifan, fighting!
Fighting!
The third round of Arena Contest.
Yi Cunhui vs. Sheng Lingmie.
Game started.
Yi Cunhui chose tactical positioning.
But Sheng Lingmie already knew it.
He got intercepted halfway.
Sheng Lingmie hold the upper hand.
It's not good for Yi Cunhui.
Yifan, fighting!
Leaping onto the wall,  Qiao launches a counterattack...
while Xiao is alternating his skill strikes.
But Arrays of Ice and Plague may not enough to turn the tide.
He should use more Arrays of Ghosts...
and cause high damage to enemy by the Feast of Ghosts.
What happened?
Why did Xiao rush in the opposite direction?
Tell us why, Captain Yu.
Director, please replay these frames.
Yeah, it's here.
Xiao was shooting with his rifle at the same direction,
then hit the air with his Mechanical Punch.
But nobody was here, Captain Yu.
Let's see from Xiao's view.
What...
Shaotian, have you seen it?
It must be an afterimage that looks very real.
It's not surprising that Xiao mistook it for Qiao.
But I think it must be a coincidence,
because a Ghost has no skill creating an afterimage.
So Xiao was just unlucky and fell into the trap for no reason.
I don't think so.
The afterimage just appeared in a right place at a right time.
It was Visual Deception.
Visual Deception?
What the hell is it?
These frames just frightened me.