= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 35 =
Could you ever...
...compete with me for one more time?
This time...
I'd still let you win.
= Fixed Error =
What happened?
- What... What are you doing? - Give it to me...
You did this?
Don't...
How could it be me?
It was me.
It had nothing to do with him.
I'll pay you for whatever it costs.
Cool.
You do it.
Give me the money.
Fine.
Now what?
Your money was stolen?
Come here, you.
Come here!
I'm overwhelmed.
It's the first time to see someone played arcade games
when having a fever of 39℃.
By the way...
I'll go buy medicine for him.
You take care of him.
Don't touch his favorite toy.
Brother!
The Transformer's arm was broken.
It has nothing to do with me.
We clowned around together...
We kept each other warm...
We went through the chaos of our adolescence...
I still remember what you said to me.
"We shouldn't be too furious in early youth.
Because life is still long."
Are these the ones we broke last time?
Yep.
I bought both of them.
Why did you buy the broken ones?
# You cover your unwillingness with a smile. #
I bought them...
...to get your lucky coins back!
Anyways, you can fix anything.
So, fix these two machines!
Wait! Come back!
Where did you get the money?
Did you rob a bank?
What I did is much better than robbing a bank.
Look!
I earned it with my talent!
= Certificate of Awards Ye Qiu the Champion =
You won the champion?
You can't squander your money even if you are the champion!
# You are my dearest in my heart. #
Great!
I was the first one to play the game.
No one can compete with me.
How brazen!
You even dare to boast before the national champion.
You won because I wasn't in the competition.
Come look at the Ranking List.
= Ranking List No. 1: Su Muqiu; No. 2: Ye Xiu =
As long as a player can be the top of the Ranking List,
= No. 1 Su Muqiu Accept the challenge? =
his ID's profile image will be saved as an NPC automatically.
If someone surpasses me, my profile image will be deleted.
Mine is still there.
No one has surpassed me yet.
Watch me defeat you in this round!
Get on! One more round!
# You cover your unwillingness with a smile. #
= Go! =
# But you try your best not leaving regrets for me. #
# You are like my private investigator. #
# You see through every action and expression. #
= Defeat! =
# You are my dearest in my heart. #
# You will always be my support. #
= No. 1 Su Muqiu; No. 2 Ye Xiu =
# I will care about you forever. #
# You are the best in my heart. #
= Ranking List No. 1 Su Muqiu; No. 2 Ye Xiu =
Fool! You lost again!
# You make every idle moment interesting again. #
# You are my dearest in my heart. #
He didn't want to win.
Even though my big brother was an NPC,
he wanted to stay with a big brother like this for longer...
...and much longer...
# Let us stay together. #
Why are you doing this?
Fine.
You won't eat anything?
I'll throw all food away.
We'll eat, OK?
It's just breakfast.
Everyone, start eating!
Start eating.
Pass me the bread, please.
If you could turn to others in competitions, it'd be great.
Wait...
Where is Wu Chen?
Has anyone seen him?
Since the competition ended that day...
I have never seen him again.
I knew it was him.
We were right not to let him compete.
He might manage to climb the social ladder in Zhu Xian.
Don't say that, Lao Wei.
How can we blame Wu Chen for being defeated by Zhu Xian?
What I said is all true.
I myself saw him with Zhu Xian players before the competition.
Who would know if it was him who ratted us out?
He told them Lao Ye was not there.
Are you sure it was Wu Chen?
Didn't someone blunder because the mouse slipped out of his hand?
Besides...
Let me ask you...
What's wrong with your hand?
Now what?
Don't make that face.
Nobody owes you anything.
"Listen to my command and we'll win for sure"?
Listen!
What I hate most is someone gets above himself with his sciolism!
If you are really capable, win to prove yourself!
Xiao An!
Stop it!
The best commander needs a good cooperation.
Go practice and improve yourself!
Cooperation?
Who was the one that went to the front and disrupted the entire plan?
Was that me? Never!
Why did I go to the front?
There was no main attacker at all!
Don't look at me.
We need to adjust our paces when attacking!
You think you are the best and everyone else is holding you back?
But each time I do the post-game analysis,
I see you disrupt our paces by taking your own course.
Enough.
We are a team.
Could everyone just calm down?
Yifan.
When would you know your own mind?
He doesn't need to.
"Yes Man" never needs to take responsibilities for anyone!
Everyone should take responsibilities for the competition.
It doesn't make any sense to say all this when we are angry.
Why are you here validating your existence?
Have you got any score?
Why don't you make a "Losers' Team" with Luo Ji? Perfect for you!
Are you done?
You won't let it go?
No!
We are not born to build a team together!
Fine.
Let's part our ways.
Do it!
Now!
Whatever.
I don't even like it here.
Captain.
It's everyone's Xing Xin.
You should make your own decisions.
= The Eighth Glory Professional Alliance =
= Xing Xin =
Through the whole journey...
Highly intense daily training and the pressure from preparations
have been irritating all of us.
Occasional fragility and outburst...
...speak for the truest us.
I think...
= Xing Xin Team =
...we all need more time...
...to learn from experience...
= Xing Xin Team =
...to learn about responsibility...
...and to learn how to grow up.
= Xing Xin Team =
This time...
I won't...
...and I don't want to...
...make any decisions for you.
Tang.
Let's go.
Look at me!
See my APM?
As fast as before!
Look at my position.
As fancy as before!
See my reaction?
Lao Wei, any new word?
Stop it!
Look at you.
Only can show off when doing PVE.
You'll absolutely be defeated by new talents in real competitions.
We retired 5 or 6 years ago.
You're not like us. You just made your reappearance.
We'd never be the ones they wanted to rival against.
Don't even mention real competitions.
I'm afraid a boss would be a disaster for you.
Wait!
Are you provoking us?
Lao Wei, don't look down on us.
Let's show him.
I won't go home if I can't defeat several bosses.
Seriously?
Stay focused!
Good job!
Hello.
Honey...
Yes, I bought it.
I'm on my way home.
Met a traffic jam.
There is no keyboard sound.
You got it wrong.
No keyboard at all on the road.
OK, I see.
Seriously?
Come and fill!
I'm coming. Let's continue.
Lao Wei.
Let's poke?
Hello.
What?
It didn't work by increasing 2%?
OK. Wait for me.
No need.
The driver is downstairs.
Lao Wei. Let's take a rain check.
Something came up in the company. I gotta go.
See you.
What the heck?!
Next time I'll take all your phones away when you come!
Exactly!
Lao Wu, you are my good buddy.
Only you and I can also beat the boss.
Hello.
I'll be right there. I promise.
Well...
Lao Wei.
I'm sorry.
My driving buddies are rushing me.
We'll make a self-driving tour to Tibet.
I thought I could play some games before leaving.
Next time.
I'll have a blast with you.
I give you my word.
Why is it so difficult to find someone to play Glory with?
Lao Wei.
You played Glory.
And you went through a lot.
It's time to let go.
Think about your future.
You are the same.
You can let anything go but Glory.
Or you wouldn't come back.
I...
I came back for the baby diapers I bought for my kid.
Bye!
Driver, stop here, please.
Pay attention to the rhythms when you play this part.
OK.
Stop.
Tang Rou.
Let me introduce her.
This is your senior.
She is my most excellent student.
Come here.
Long time no see.
I chose to escape from here before.
But I won't do it again.
If you decide not to escape again,
would you come back?
Think about it.
Because of a mistake I made in the competition,
I have never played the piano again.
The old me...
...thought winning the competition...
...was my entire life.
But the new me...
...is not afraid of losing anymore.
I won't escape, either.
Because my passion...
...triumphs over winning or losing.
What makes me understand all this...
...is Glory.
The price...
...is listed very clearly.
If you make up your mind...
...sign here.
= Payment for Purchasing the Game Account =
Boss Wei!
You forgot to take the medicine for your hand injury.
I've brought it here.
= Signature =
You're selling your account?
Wand of Death is even more precious than your life.
Are you really selling it?
I don't want it anymore.
Don't sign it!
Get out!
Go!
Are you really leaving Glory?
Or what?
I couldn't even call up my friends together.
Where could I play Glory?
Return to Xing Xin with me.
Like our old days.
We screwed things up when rivaling against Zhu Xian.
Do you think we...
No...
Do you think I...
...should continue working on it?
Some battles you win, some battles you lose.
Moreover, it was not your own responsibility in that competition.
I'm not like any of you.
I should live like others who are in my age.
What's your age?
In my eyes...
You are in the exact age when you should strive, hang out,
and play Glory with us all!
Look at it!
It is the injury that decides I need to leave now.
Our captain has said...
Only you can make the decision...
...when you should leave the competition.
No matter if you are at your peak,
or in your trough,
or you're kicked out...
As long as you love Glory,
as long as you want to be in this arena,
you'll find a way to handle all your setbacks and failures.
It's a choice that we eSports players must face!
No matter how many times we start over...
...we'll never change.
Sign it.
Wait a sec.
I've got another pen here.
Hurry up and sign it.
= Signature: Wei Chen =
= Agreement on Selling Glory ID & Equipment =
Sir, we're about to close.
Sorry. I...
Thank you.
Why have you been sitting here?
I like this intersection.
What about the intersection?
Anything special?
If any of them comes back, I can see them from here.
So?
So I can hear the captain say:
"All team players of Xing Xin are here!"
What if...
...they would never come back?
They will.
I'm afraid we have to...
...wait for the red light to go off for too long...
...and the green light just flashes away.
The red light will be on for a long time.
But it's OK.
I'll wait longer.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
I've fixed the umbrella.
But...
I feel something is still wrong.
New rubber bands.
New hair pins.
New cloth.
The material is updated.
The quality is much better.
I think the umbrella is pretty good.
No matter how good it is...
It's not the one I used to have.
I thought...
I'd get to the end with a thousand-machine umbrella by being Jun Moxiao.
But I didn't make it.
Remember this coin?
If it had not been for it,
Your big brother would have never taken me in.
you would have never met me.
Back then, my parents were gone.
My relatives living abroad wanted to adopt me.
Should we still stick together like before?
Or should he let me leave for a promising future?
My big brother hesitated.
Head, let her go.
Tail, let her stay.
# Your old coat... #
Because of you...
our fate has been changed.
You always say you were lucky to meet us.
But your appearance...
...was the best luck the lucky coin brought to us.
Your big brother never wanted to let you go.
I was just passing by inadvertently.
And then inadvertently...
...helped him make a decision that had been in his mind.
But you always inadvertently helped us...
...to have the best choices.
# But you try your best not leaving regrets for me. #
Why are you quitting the part-time job here?
I'm looking for a full-time job...
...which will help me make money...
...and feed my family.
But...
What about the senior seminar of programming?
I quit.
Su Muqiu.
Are you really doing this?
To be a miserable brother quitting school for his little sister?
Since I've decided to stick with Mucheng,
I'll try whatever I can to give her a better life.
What is "better life"?
Mucheng's birthday wish was to go to the Sea World.
But what I can afford now is three golden fishes.
# I will care about you forever. #
Who said three little golden fishes...
...would never have their own Sea World?
The three of us...
...were like these three golden fishes.
We didn't have a big house.
We didn't have fancy decorations.
But we were still happy.
This was "better life".
Thank you.
You gave me the best birthday gift ever.
For being the best birthday gift ever...
...in my and my brother's life.
# You are like my private investigator. #
We'll have many crossings in life.
If we were not careful enough...
...we'd derail.
What I only did was to tell your brother...
...to go along one road.
There's nothing wrong with going along one road.
That was how exactly...
...I met all of you.
And my brother could go back to school.
In the end...
A thousand-machine umbrella was born.
I got it! I got it!
Look!
How about this design?
Awesome!
We made it!
But it belongs to me now.
It's mine!
Come back!
I said "it's mine"!
I said it!
Everyone said...
A thousand-machine umbrella was an unpractical fantasy.
And it was a mission that would never be accomplished.
But you said...
The difference between fantasy and reality was whether you believe it.
And the way to make the impossible possible was never give up.
So, a thousand-machine umbrella...
...has never only belonged to my brother.
You used to help him a lot.
So now...
Let him help you make a decision.
Tell us...
...what we should do.
No need to look.
I know what Muqiu would say.
"No big deal.
Start over."
Ta Yun and Xing Xin have equal points.
= Xing Xin Team =
But with the win-lose situation, Xing Xin has made their way to the final.
- Manager Chen, what's your opinion? - Talk to us.
Could we have the conversation upstairs?
OK, OK.
Share details with us later, please.
OK.
Come in, please.
We all know when rivaling against Zhu Xian,
there was something wrong with Captain Ye's ultimate weapon.
Will he show up in the final and compete?
All players are trying to fix it now.
Moreover, you care about competitions more than equipment displays.
Has your players been affected by the failure from last time?
Captain Ye has said:
"Some battles you win, some battles you lose."
Everyone is very active now.
We are actively preparing for the competition.
But according to our informant,
Wei Chen has sold his account and his silver equipment "Wand of Death".
How would you explain it?
We heard Tang Rou returned to her band and Wu Chen was in Zhu Xian.
And your other players are not with Xing Xin.
So, with everyone's leaving,
will Xing Xin be dissolved?
I've told you.
Everyone is trying to fix a thousand-machine umbrella actively.
Captain Ye has sent them to buy materials.
That's why they are not with Xing Xin now.
Could we call them from here?
We care about what's really going on.
Yes, call them.
Prove it by calling them.
Seems Xing Xin is just an empty shell. No one is here.
Who said that?
Boss.
I've got all the materials you and Captain Ye needed.
Things are going well with Yifan and others.
They'll be back soon.
It's the contract of purchasing materials.
All data are in here.
You wanna prove something?
Go ahead.
= Contract of Purchasing Equipment Materials =
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Contact us if there's any further info.
Remember it.
Keep in touch with us.
We will.
- Bye! - Bye!
So you met with Zhu Xian players to buy materials?
Yes.
Xing Xin didn't have enough silver equipment.
I wanted to surprise all of you.
Why didn't you tell us back then?
We'll listen to the chief commander no matter what happens.
Keeping you all on an even keel...
...is more important than whether I was in the competition.
Where did you go after the competition?
To save a thousand-machine umbrella.
The final was coming. Time was running out.
I visited many teams and guilds in a short time.
And I've got a batch of basic materials.
Hope they will help the captain.
Do you think if they would come back?
Boss.
All professional players will face the life crossing of choices.
I've made my choice.
It's their turn now.
What we can do now...
...is to give them more space...
...and give the captain more time.