= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 21 =
Thanks.
No problem.
Give me that.
OK.
No alcohol during the match,
this is the rule.
But since we started,
then enjoy ourselves.
One more shot.
Same as him.
With spherical ice.
Here.
Dilute with ice?
Too low.
Ice cubes suppress light taste elements in wine,
which prominent the strong elements
of heavy taste more.
One plus one
is more than two somtimes.
I am the only one.
I don't need to add up with anyone.
Sure.
Add up with talented players like you
is accomplishing others.
Unfair.
You're so prominent,
so everyone thinks that
you should win.
If you lose, it's a shame.
They'll say you're a unprofessional captain.
But we all know that
it was the Team Jia Shi that had problems.
I don't care.
If really so,
why are you sitting here
instead of Tactical Room.
Don't think you can educate me
after you won me once.
One day I'll knock you down hard.
It's supposed that
both of us will someday
knock the rest of the league down hard.
Our hardware has been upgraded.
But our enemy has also been upgraded.
Judging from the team members,
Except for the captain,
we're all new players
who haven't even played on the field.
As for weapon,
our orange equipment versus their sliver equipment,
the DPS is less than half of theirs.
Luo Ji,
How's the calculation going?
What is our winning rate against Jia Shi?
Eighty-eight.
Underling,
That's too unreliable.
It's 0.88.
Based on all the data above,
we have nothing to compare with Jia Shi.
Very wise.
It's true that
we have nothing to compare with Jia Shi.
Because there's no need to compare.
As a Captain,
I only consider the possibility of winning.
there are only two cases in my opinion.
Win,
or lose.
Our winning rate
is the same as that of Jia Shi.
Well... that's not scientific.
If we based on the data,
that should be all of us...
ESports Competition is not just about the data,
It's the person behind the account
that is the biggest variable.
Sounds like a trick,
but I have to say that
he really has a good point.
Captain,
let's begin the training now.
Fighting, fighting,
beat Jia Shi.
Oh, right.
The boss wants to tell you something.
Take good care of your appearance while signing up tomorrow.
H... How?
In her opinion, I suppose...
Just dress up to fit your professional status.
Professional status...
Do your business.
OK.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
How do I look?
Am I very professional
in this suit?
Am I look like a ranger?
Who are you?
Wait.
One more thing.
Where are you guys going?
Wait for me.
He's yours.
Bao Zi.
Tang Rou said he is more handsome than you.
Is he your friend?
I don't know him.
Boss,
am I not professional?
The eighth Glory Professional Alliance
has all finished.
Samsara guild won the championship.
It was ordinary,
but there were regrets.
Compared with my left from Jiashi,
The degradation of Jiashi
made me more grieved.
That's where I fought, after all.
But now,
I just focus on Xing Xin.
Xing Xin is a new team.
First, we must pass the selection of the Tutor Selection
to qualify for the Challenge,
and win the championship,
Only then can we get tickets to the
tenth Glory Professional Alliance.
This is a new start.
It means new hope.
Come on,
Xing Xin.
I have something else to do.
You guys sign up first.
So many people.
You say we're going to
take part in the best,
the most powerful audition?
Bao "know nothing" Rongxing,
Since it's a Tutor Selection,
It must be the most elementary competition.
Many teams come to sign up every year.
Only the top twenty teams
selected by the tutors are qualified
to participate in the Formal Selection Challenge.
So there's tutors.
Tutor team is not normal team,
Ambitions, Lan Yu, Wei Cao and Samsara guild,
Teams from the League
serve tutors every year.
It's not easy to score from them and get promoted.
It can be said that the audition is a high wall.
Sounds so complicated,
but actually so easy.
Ignore the tutor,
just focus on the rank.
Twenty teams were eventually
selected from these teams,
we are in absolutely.
Let's go.
Assassin from Zhu Xian,
APM master.
APM 410.
He used to play three combo attacks
in one second in a game.
People called him "Hurricane Hand".
APM 410.
Impressive.
This way.
Don't be nervous during the game.
Line up.
Competition is about participation.
I recall someone had
hands tremble last time.
Don't you dare say that again.
I'll spray you.
So quick.
What're you doing?
I'll be damned.
The first operator of Sharpshooter,
Cloud Piercer,
had a extremely fast reaction speed.
The reaction speed of ordinary people
is usually about 0.2 seconds.
He only needs 0.09 seconds.
Well,
let's fill out the form.
I just saw a place over there.
Let's go.
Hey, watch out.
It's lucky for you to run into me.
You'll be blackmailed
if you run into others.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
Such a silly dude,
with a dull brain,
I'll beat him easily.
That man seemed to be Wu Chen,
the captain of Team Everlasting.
Wu Chen.
Captain of at Team Everlasting.
He led the team to the game from the fifth season.
He has plenty of practical experience
and excellent management ability.
He's good at controlling the strong by weakness.
Leading Team Everlasting to win fifteen games
with a zero winning rate determined.
Many call him the Reversal God.
Seriously?
The strength of each of these teams
should not be underestimated.
If we want to get the only twenty chances from these teams,
then our chances of winning are probably...
Fine, fine, fine.
You always praise others,
enhance their spirit,
take ourselves down.
Tell you what, our boss is more talented,
he's resposible for the name "Textbook of Glory".
Tutor Selection?
It's not sure who guide whom.
You only mention your boss while comparing.
Well... where's boss?
Same venue, same people.
This scene is really
a recurrence of yesterday.
Same venue is true.
The people are not.
Sure.
You're not the captain of Thunderbolt
who lost the game and throw everything away.
You're not the captain of Jia Shi
who won the game and give a speech to me.
This page is very clever about the tactics on Ambitons.
I'll take it for reference.
Its tactical analysis of Lan Yu is also in place.
It's a pity that your Thunderbolt
can't achieve your idea at all.
Looks like you dirty guys did work hard
on these dirty tactics.
Work hard?
Doing my best?
I might consider that a compliment
If I heard such words a few years ago.
Now it's also a compliment.
Talent is a necessity
if you want to go down the eSports road.
But there is also a gap between talent and talent.
and maybe this gap
can't be bridged by hard work.
So,
"Hard work" now sounds a little ironic.
For most people, working hard is the only option.
It has nothing to do with talent.
It's too arrogant of you geniuses to say that.
There are not so many geniuses,
Those extraordinary people are just
work hard in an ordinary way
in places that you can't see.
Quantitative changes to qualitative changes.
Maybe it's just the last insistence.
It looks like I have to beat you
next time I meet you.
Or I'm unworthy of not only my own efforts,
but aslo your intentionally coming here
and said that to me.
Just finish the last pages first.
It seems that the tactics book has been written full.
Good results.
You've fulfilled your promise.
You beat Jia Shi with Thunderbolt.
But I haven't beaten you.
I heard you've made a big news recently.
Just transfered a team.
The most common news in the league.
I'm afraid your transfer
is unusual this time.
This so-called unusual
depends on who it is for.
Here.
OK.
Mu Cheng.
Mu Cheng, Mu Cheng.
Is she?
What are you doing here?
I'm asking you.
Haven't you heard?
Are you deaf?
Are you doing cosplay?
Xing Xin team can just play out here
during the auditions.
So don't hold any hope.
Any team in this hall can knock you down.
Who's that guy?
He talks so much.
So annoying.
Team member of Jia Shi Team one, Shen Jian.
What again?
Shen Jian.
So bitchy.
What did you say?
Shen Jian.
One of the main players in Jia Shi Team one.
He had joined Jiashi since the fifth season,
participated in seventy-eight games.
The highest DPS once
was 32% of the whole team.
He's the top three striker in the league.
What... What now?
Me,
the famous Glory newcomer Bao Rongxing,
have broken 1800 bricks,
have thrown more sands
than in the Sahara Desert.
If you want to compare data,
I'm not afraid of you.
Young man,
you know nothing.
Our captain, Jia Shi,
Best Newcomer, Sun Xiang,
Top Launcher of the League, Su Mucheng.
Who do you have?
You even don't have enough people.
Underling,
teach them a lesson.
Hello,
my name is Luo Ji.
My operations and skills are the worst in our team.
But I'm familiar with
everything about all of you here.
And if there's no accident,
My analysis of you
should be more thorough than yourselves.
Nice.
Very good.
Anyone?
Anyone else do you have?
Yes.
Newcomer Tang Rou,
163 days of contact with Glory,
20 days after the account has reached the full level.
68 games battle with Team Wei Cao in the arena,
the winning rate is zero.
Went to Glory Professional Alliance first time two days ago.
So what?
You are all standing at this
starting point like me.
Well said.
Anyone else?
Anyone?
Me.
You don't have to introduce yourself.
Former Wei Cao professional manager
who was beaten up cruelly
in the last All-Star Game.
Manager?
Manager of water.
Boss.
Vice Captain of Jia Shi,
Xiao Shiqin.
Vice Captain of Xing XIn,
Qiao Yifan.
Xing Xin and Jia Shi may meet again.
Let's talk on the arena.
Yifan,
the result of the Tutor Selection
is still half an hour away.
You've dragged us to look at
the empty screen for an hour.
Exactly, Yifan.
Isn't it fun to attack Dungeon?
Isn't it excited to battle others?
Isn't it enerfetic to throw the bricks?
Why waste time here?
Let's go.
Let's go back.
Move.
Unnormal behaviour,
there's only one explaination.
Fear.
Yifan.
Are you afraid?
Instead of waiting for Murphy's Law,
it's better for us to take the first lead.
What's Murphy's Law?
The fourth law of Murphy's Law is that
if you're worried about something happening,
it's more likely to happen.
How to take the first lead?
Normally speaking,
if we are not afraid anything,
there will be relatively good results.
Can I be afraid?
Do I need to be afraid?
Am...
Am I supposed to be afraid?
Yes.
Since we are all not afraid,
then the result doesn't matter,
right?
Then,
let's go back and have a rest,
let's go.
Go.
Finally.
What?
Such a coincidence.
=Nothing to worry about, right, Yifan?
Aren't you not scared, Tangrou? Luo Ji, didn't you tell us not to be afraid? =
= Shut up. =
= I second what Tangrou said.  =
= Me too. =
= Look. The Captain is offline.
He is the one who isn't afraid. He won't be affected by the opponents at all. =
= Admire the captain. =
Team Wei Cao.
= @Qiao Yifan =
All the star tutors in the Tutor Selection are familiar.
Sure.
It's much less difficult than the Alliance.
There will be no problem.
That's the reason that
there is no need
for three All-Stars to be present
at this level.
You were saying that
Sun Xiang and I don't have to play at the same time.
Exactly.
When Sun Xiang is impulsive,
I'll let him go back,
and he'll sit on the bench
and calm down.
Then it's time
for tacticians like you to play,
take over the control.
Sun Xiang and I are different types of players.
Jia Shi needs me and him at the same time.
You are new here.
You don't know much about our newcomer yet.
Young and aggressive,
doesn't know how to obey,
only know how to attack.
It's not wise to talk about compatibility
with such an impulsive person.
Impulse can also be an advantage.
Passing-line players rarely make mistakes,
meanwhile they rarely create miracles.
I have designed a set of tactics
with Sun Xiang as the core
for the Tutor Selection.
I certainly believe in your tactics.
It's just that
Sun Xiang will not make any changes
because of your joining.
He's bound to be the leak in your tactics.
What's wrong?
I want to know your next tactical arrangement.
Leaf of Autumn is the tactics.
Fine.
Then let's work together
to knock down the rest of the league.
Any leak can be remedied,
cause we are professional players.
Victory is our common goal.
Tutor Selection is different from Regular Season.
There's no Individual Event,
Arena Contest or Team Competition.
There was only one contest.
The tutor team will intercept on this map.
We need to break through their barriers,
running from one end of the map to the other.
One point for each player who crosses the line.
That's the rules.
Next, you'll talk about
how we should deal with it.
Team Wei Cao is led by Witch,
he is best at debuff,
which will greatly reduce our combat effectiveness.
Therefore,
I think we need a Cleric.
Are we that frightened?
Why do we need a Cleric to heal?
The Cleric's main project is indeedly heal,
but this time,
We need his ability to clear the debuff.
I have a video here.
Let's take a look at
how the Cleric clears the debuff.
Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie
can both release debuff,
giving us all kinds of reduced effect,
making our combat effectiveness drop sharply.
We really need a special person to disperse them.
Yifan,
Facing Weicao,
aren't you afraid?
Weicao...
is fine.
At least I'm familiar with them.
Why are you guys here?
Never judge people by their appearance.
Yifan looks dull.
But deep inside,
he's evil-minded.
I... didn't.
I'd like to see how bad you can be.
Bao Zi.
Tang, here.
Tang Rou.
Underling.
Luo Ji.
Give it back to me.
Team Wei Cao,
Some offensive skills can be used
to debuff enemy characters.
Debuff is a state of diminution
imposed on the enemy's role,
It can temporarily reduce the enemy's
role attributes, skills, etc.,
causing their decline in combat effectiveness.
Tang Rou,
Secret weapons are ready.
Yifan.
Good job.
Captain,
this is the ranking of
the whole network Cleric.
I'll do it myself.
Captain,
how about this one?
Although he's not at the top of the list,
but his power of clear the debuff is the strongest.
I think he should be very suitable for our team.
Choose not the best,
but the right.
The train of thought is clear.
Have you found him?
His name is An Wenyi.
He is a fresh graduate.
I'm thinking that he plays Cleric,
he might be easygoing,
and very likely to fit in with us.
His ID number is "Cold Hands".
Then let's take a shot.
Warm his cool hands
with our passion.
Yes, captain.
Oh right,
captain,
This is the personal data of An Wenyi.
I've highlighted all the key points.
Moreover,
this is the latest recruiting of the all teams.
Captain,
This is some interview skills
I searched yesterday,
I hope it helps.
Well prepared,
how about you go and interview?
Me?
Can I?
Sure,
you are the vice captain.
Are you really want to go to Team Xing Xin?
What else?
Well,
only two months, you can't stay long.
Then use two months to make a quick buck.
Isn't that great?
Let me tell you.
ESports is not just attacking Dungeon.
It is real.
I'm feeling that....
Are you
doubting me?
It's not that I doubt you,
You know your strengths and weaknesses, right?
Otherwise,
You won't ask me to play for you.
Thanks.
As a golden Game Leveling,
you are not that good.
Didn't we agree
you would give me five books in return?
Junior brother,
we agreed with the premise that
you have to help me reach No.1,
now I'm only No.10.
You deserves
only three books.
Although the results were not as good as expected,
it's also blessed by misfortune.
Right?
Now there's a team coming to you.
Please give me the whole set.
Sure.
Thanks a lot.
Don't you count your coffee as a book?
Then I still have one more.
This one counts on my coffee.
Hey,
These books are
no longer of any value to you.
See this as our friendship.
Let me ask you,
how much is our friendship?
You are so mean.
Why do I have a friend like you?
I want to break up with you.
Bye.
I...
Fine.
I can't believe you can be in a team.
That's none of your business.
Not only can I join the team,
but I can also raise my status.
We'll see.
These property and turnover,
just fine.
Hello.
Are you An Wenyi?
Yes, I am.
Go and tell your interviewer I'm here.
Hi.
I am...
the interviewer.
Is he
the one you are looking for?
Cold Hands.
He is An Wenyi.
Why did you let Yifan interview him?
Such an excellent vice captain,
It's such a pity that
I didn't give his the opportunity
and make him take charge of it.
Watch out.
Careful.
Interview skills No. 1,
start with greetings,
relieve the tension.
Your resume says that
your undergraduate major is
Finance.
Yes.
But it doesn't affect me
to become an excellent Cleric.
It's more than enough
to be your player with my abilities.
Not only that,
I can be your team investment advisor.
and of course,
personal finance.
Interview skills No. 2,
don't rush to the point.
Leave the problem to him,
respond quickly according to the situation.
What advantages do you think
you have as a Cleric?
Talent is not something else.
It can't be seen with one seconds.
But if you're a person of good sense,
you can see if I'm suitable or not.
Interview skills No. 3,
Go to the point directly.
So tell me about your records of Glory.
I'll be stronger
while meeting the strong one.
The records depend on whether
the team can make me play at a high level.
Your team have to rely on
a Net Cafe to support.
I'd better...
Although our team has a small scale,
but we are professional.
Let me show you our training room.
Do you have any other requirements?
Look,
Why are you so insincere?
At this juncture,
Shouldn't you talk about
the salary or something?
Never mind.
Time is money.
You...
You can request anything
as long as you can stay.
You mean that
as long as my performance is good,
the salary can be increased.
Right?
No problem.
I can grant your request.
But whether you can get the contract
depends on your performance.
Fine.
I'll play
according to your rules.
Our rules are the rules of the Tutor Selection,
which is running through the map.
You win
if you cross the finish line.
You run and
I'm in charge of interception.
I'll lose if one player crosses the line.
Let me see
what on earth your abilities are.
Boss,
you played a trick.
I'm not ready.
The opponent does not care
whether you are ready or not on the arena.
Tang Rou go forward,
suppressing captain,
I'll support you.
Bao Zi, An Wenyi,
look for opportunities to move forward.
No problem.
Got it.
It's not so easy to walk away.
An Wenyi,
Silent all captain's skills
with Sacred Fire.
Thanks.
Don't be.
Just gave you such a little.
So mean.
It's lucky that you're still alive.
Nice timing.
Of course.
Why don't you cancel my debuff?
You are too weak.
It's such a waste
cancelling your debuff.
What did you say?
Bao Zi,
more talking
and you'll lose.
Bao Zi,
use Inject Poison to break captain's Super Armor.
Tang Rou,
limit captain's range of activities
Sorry,
my bad.
It's OK, Yifan.
An Wenyi, cancel the debuff.
We're all going to die
under your command.
Why these nonsense?
There's no need cancelling the debuff.
Cause he has
unilaterally declared that game is over.
You spoke fast,
the command was right,
but you are just like reading a textbook.
You don't know how to be flexible.
You can pass if you're
dealing with an ordinary people.
But he is the "Textbook of Glory".
It's ridiculous.
Besides, captain Ye knows
so much about everybody.
There's no chance to overturn.
My teammate is weak,
bad luck for me.
Admit defeat for bet,
I have no face to ask for the contract.
Goodbye.
An Wenyi.
Please wait.
Wait.
Captain,
it's my bad.
I didn't...
Stay.
I can grant your extra request.
Happy to cooperate.
For the long-term development of our team,
we have to consciously train
new people for the second echelon.
Do you have any plans
for future development?
It seems a little early
to talk about things far away.
Let's talk about the present.
Have you thought about
An Wenyi's treatment?
I have to check the cost of the parties quickly,
and sign a contract with him as soon as possible.
I...
haven't considered it yet.
Haven't considered?
These questions
should be thought out
before the interview.
See this.
An Wenyi's Exclusive Plan.