= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 15 =
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
What are you looking for?
Since I can't stop other people,
Then I have to handle it internally.
How many locks you think I should put on the door of the attic?
What? Locks?
Or I can take down the stairs of the attic.
He is so indoorsy, anyway.
This should pose no problem for staying there for about ten days.
No. Guoguo.
What you are saying is being so weird.
I will give him the computer.
After all, it is enough to
have Glory in his world.
As long as he efface himself,
the journalists will not know.
Perfect.
That is way off base.
Even if he journalists won't come,
the police will come.
This way won't work.
That way won't work as well.
Then what should I do?
I can't think of any ways.
Guoguo, it's not that complicated
to keep him staying here.
Then what should I do?
Shall I
break his legs?
It is not that impractical.
As long as he has his hands.
Of course no.
What are you
thinking about right now?
I mean,
to keep a person staying,
you should retain his heart.
But how?
Two words.
Spoiling him.
That's strange.
Why does nobody call me?
The plan is kind of cliche,
but he is a man.
It should work.
Chu, he's coming.
Ye,
You wake up.
Why not using the vacuum cleaner?
My boss said,
the vacuum cleaner is too noisy.
It may disturb you.
By the way,
the breakfast is ready.
Eat it while it is warm.
It won't be tasty when it's cold.
What's going on?
This way. This way.
Come here. Come here.
From this one to that one,
they are all prepared for you.
What's this?
Introduce now.
These are ten kinds of nutritious porridge.
Including Eight Ingredient Porridge,
Porridge with white fungus and lotus seeds,
and porridge with red bean and corn.
They are all prepared by the boss.
Of course.
What should I do now?
There is also salty porridge.
Well, Ye,
You don't like sweet porridge, do you?
There is also salty porridge here.
Like porridge with corn and spareribs, and shrimp meat porr...
Stop. That's enough.
I have a full understanding
of her minds.
Really?
She wants to use the carbohydrate
to make me overeat to death,
So that she could inherit my Glory equipment, right?
I see.
I won't be fooled.
No.
The express.
Ye, your express.
Your express has arrived.
What else?
Hello. It's your express.
It's too hard to please him.
What's this?
This is...
This is a coffee maker the boss bought for you.
In the morning,
She can grind coffee beans for you.
At night,
She can make the cold brew coffee.
Whatever you like.
Please sign.
Suning delivers the parcel so fast.
She thinks I don't stay up late enough.
wants me to work overtime everyday.
Sir, if you don't like it,
it's refundable within 30 days.
Really?
No.
Move. Move
Boss,
So many porridge.
It's so pitiful that they're not prepared for me.
If they are prepared for me,
I must thank that person kindly.
Why do you look at me?
I love drinking juice.
But some people doesn't
buys me a juicer.
Appreciate what you are possessing.
Is there something wrong with this computer?
This...
What are you doing?
Don't. let me do it.
You such a fool...
Why bothering to do such menial work?
Let me do this. Let me do this.
Boss, What's wrong with you?
Do you think today I am
kinder to you than before?
No.
Fine. Fine.
Fine.
Since today,
You don't have to manage the net cafe.
You can play Glory whenever you want. I will still pay you.
How about that?
I think it's a trap.
It's not.
Only my sincerity.
I... let me make coffee for you.
Here.
Be careful. It's hot.
I don't want a blend of Robusta.
I want freshly roasted Arabica beans.
At least,
I want liberica.
Do you have it?
I will ask Chu to buy it.
So you don't have?
How about drinking some tea?
I have red tea, green tea, white tea...
Whatever you want.
Which one do you want.
Flower tea.
I will ask Chu to buy it too.
Then forget it.
No coffee. No tea.
Then give me a fruit tray.
OK.
It's ok.
Are you kidding me?
What?
Do you know how to peel an apple?
I have peeled it.
Have a try.
You call this peeling apples.
I need something artistic.
It's too ugly.
I won't eat it.
Artistic.
It's ok.
You are quiet deft.
The rabbit is pretty delicate.
Sure. I am telling you,
It's quiet difficult to carve the rabbit.
Look at its ears.
It would be broken
if you are not careful enough.
Unpalatable. I won't eat it.
You such a bast...
Bastard.
Say that again.
Bastard. Bastard.
Don't think that I am kind to you,
So that you can be insatiable.
Boss, keep on.
Just speak your mind and be your true self.
Otherwise, I have to act everyday.
It's too exhausting.
Acting
Yes. You want to be a fan.
Then I have to wrong myself
And act an idol.
I regard you as my idol.
But you play a trick on me.
OK. You trick me, don't you?
Don't you?
Boss, I say speak your mind.
Not beat me whenever your mind.
I'm beating you now.
So what? I…
You are so grumpy. Aren't you afraid that I will leave?
Great.
Don't come back if you leave.
I don't dare to.
Hello
This is me.
Shall we have a meeting?
It's been so many years.
I've always been a novice in Glory.
When I just met Su Muqiu and Ye Qiu,
They have been the experts in Glory.
As for me,
I was just a loser,
who couldn't do his work well,
nor play Glory.
The jungle.
The boss appears in the jungle.
Position (234 665)
Come here right now.
I'm coming.
Waiter, check out.
Your timing seems not right.
The time flies so fast.
The timing has been tampered with.
Give me the account book.
Boss.
What's this for?
It's for timing. A good thing.
It's to steal the online time of our customers.
What a shame. You study business.
You don't know what is profit maximization, do you?
But you can't be conscienceless ,
And make evil money.
The most important quality for a great businessman
Is honesty.
What a businessman needs is not qualities,
But minds.
If you want to make money, stop talking about morality.
At that moment, what I hated most was this sentence.
What's going on?
I'm going to meet an old friend.
I believe the competitive spirit we advocate
will definitely change some people's understanding
On this fields in this future.
Next, we will give vigorous support to
qualified people in this fields.
And form the esports team
as soon as possible.
= The First Glory League =
Sportsmanship, esports team.
These two strange and familiar phrases
thrilled Muqiu and me.
We wanted to hold the first Glory League,
inviting those transregional masters to compete together.
And change Glory into a real competitive sport.
Tao Xuan was fired undoubtedly
due to rise against the dishonest merchant.
and joined us.
The Poor Trio
only had broken screen and old computer host,
But expected to do a great thing.
Ye, you are the commander in chief of the whole strategy.
And our commando as well.
You are in charge of the competition schedule.
The whole level of this competition
depends on you.
Invite the players here,
and defeat them one by one. Easy.
# Unwilling to mediocrity #
# Not limited by the success #
For the competitive spirits,
for our professional careers,
we spent the poorest
but the most eventful time.
# Floating with the stream, #
# Standing at the peak of the star, #
# At that moment, I finally understand me of the past, #
# Always being my own hero. #
# I once saw  #
# the legend. #
Wei Chen and Han Wenqing, the most strangest players
in the second district, come to join the competition.
Our old  assembled computer finally had to face
- the challenges from the masters. - Let me do it.
Hello. Hello.
Come in, please.
Ready?
Go.
Go around.
The most strangest player in the second district,
is definitely worth of his name.
Let's decide the winner through one move. How about that?
That's exactly what I want.
What's wrong?
Why I can't move?
Wait a minute.
I will handle it.
You don't seize the chance to kill me?
This is competition,
Not the fight in the jungle.
Ok. I finish it.
There will be no proble...
An unfinished competition,
A broken screen,
They constituted the memories of our young age.
Ye Qiu,
Come and have a seat.
It's been a long time since I played Glory.
Cut to the chase.
Come back. Come back to Jia Shi.
Being a coach.
In fact, the position of the coach
is always being left to you.
I never consider giving you up.
I have no interest in standing aside.
I prefer to standing on the arena.
It's only temporary to be a coach.
As long as you have retired for one year,
you can come back at once.
I have come back.
In fact, we are all very clear that
the Pro-League nowadays
is quite different from that in the past.
Yes. I admit that.
Tactics and cooperation are also very important.
However, as for your high-end play,
maybe none of the audience
could understand them.
What do they want to see?
They want to see that
one can fight against many players,
or save the desperate situation on his own.
This is what they want to see,
like to see and hope to see.
I go to play games,
instead of pleasing the audience .
Your Dragon Head Raising.
You said it was just for fun.
But all the fans
regarded it as your representative skill.
Its practical value is limited.
Does it matter?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that it is irreplaceable.
Only you can use it.
Using Dragon Head Raising is necessary.
It's not for showing the virtuosity.
But you are successful in showing it this time.
When you use Dragon Head Raising
in the All-Star game,
it can rouse the crowd immediately.
I don't believe you never realize that.
Why not seizing the chance
and ascend the throne thoroughly?
You are right.
But that's not what I want.
Then what do you want?
Winning.
Do you think now you can
win back
the glory that belong to you?
Give it a try.
I...
only focus on the future,
and I'm never stuck in the past.
As for those
stumbling blocks to the future of Jia Shi,
I will throw them away without hesitation.
But...
in this regard,
we are the same.
Recently, I've been thinking that
if Muqiu was still here,
whether we wouldn't be
brought to this point.
Ye,
afterwards, you are the core of our team.
The personnel allocations
also serves for you.
You can also decide the tactics.
I don't worry your capacity.
You will definitely become the first in Glory.
Muqiu,
Here.
You are also one of our team.
After all, only you can
have the best cooperation with Ye Qiu.
But apart from the competition,
You have to offer some technical support,
Issues like the design of the equipment
are all handed over to you.
They should pose no problem
for a genius like you.
Tao, you are flattering me.
As for me, I will do odds and ends for you.
I will offer the logistical support.
I believe we will definitely
become the first team in Glory.
Come.
With Glory in your heart,
you are invincible.
Waiter,
throw these away.
Throw all of them?
Including the computer?
It has been broken, anyway.
What is the use in keeping it?
Wait.
It indeed has been broken.
See, this is my design.
Freelancer has existed in Glory.
But due to the cooldown of changing the weapons,
and the high load,
There are many shortages on the continuity of the attacking.
We can't put together the low-level skills
of different professions perfectly.
But you see,
if there is such a weapon,
it can change its forms at any time.
What do you think of it?
Then it can use all the professional
skills constantly.
Right.
I am designing a weapon like this.
I call it thousand-machine umbrella.
Great. You.
You have already thought about it.
And have it to conceal from me.
I haven't finished it.
There are still two forms left.
These two forms
can't switch between each other at random.
When I finish the design,
and find the two materials left,
you prepare to sweep away the players,
and surprise the entire Glory.
Yes.
Ye,
I heard that Muqiu and you
are designing a weapon for the freelancers.
Yes. With this weapon,
I can be
a real freelancer.
No. It should be called The King's Avatar.
But if you don't change your profession,
you can only use the skills of the twentieth levels or less.
How can you play the game?
I can.
Tao, you see,
even if I could only use the small skills of
the twentieth level or less, it can still produce
amazing transformations as long as there are enough skills.
The potential of the freelancer
is not worse than that of twenty-four professions.
He could even be better.
Fine. Forget about the skills,
What about the league?
What if the freelancer
is not allowed to use in the league?
What if the level of Glory raise its limitation?
When it raise its levels to the ninetieth level,
to the hundredth level,
Do you think playing the freelancer is still of any value?
Tao, in fact, you have been determined
not to allow me to play the freelancer.
Risk. Risk. Risk.
It's about risk.
I can't ignore the danger of it
Just for your mischief.
I have agreed to your request
of effacing yourself and not accepting any endorsement.
Do you continue to be so headstrong?
Tao, please trust me,
these problems,
I believe Muqiu and I can handle all of them.
Think it over.
Persuade Ye Qiu.
= All the rare materials have been taken down. =
= The thousand-machine umbrella is at the first level =
I think this time
we had better listen to Tao.
Why?
My research failed.
The thousand-machine umbrella. I have sealed it.
Are you kidding me? This is not joke.
Look at what you designed before.
Look at the cannon. So gorgeous.
And the weapons in the rear.
Right? And this one.
This...
Actually,
The freelancer is not a conventional profession.
Its play is very changeable.
Even if we can use it very well,
after Jia Shi recruits new members,
they can't handle so
changeable play like us.
It is a big problem
for our team composition.
In fact, it's not important.
Most importantly, one day,
we can rise to the top of Glory together
instead of depending on the weapons.
Therefore, whether using the thousand-machine umbrella or not,
whether I lie to you or not,
it's not important.
Right?
How about that?
Let's make a bet.
First, we change Jia Shi into the first team.
Then the best member of the time
will have the right to reset the thousand-machine umbrella.
What do you think? You dare to make a bet with me?
Here. This is a weapon I specially made for you.
I call this weapon
Que Xie.
How about that? Do you like it ?
Since the thousand-machine umbrella can't be finished,
then let Que Xie
accompany you and rise to the top of Glory.
Su Muqiu,
You
indeed lied to me.
This is my secret.
Ye, when you find it,
Jia Shi and you
must have reached the top of Glory.
= Statement on Retirement =
= Your article has been sent. =
My retirement
causes many related assumptions
from the media and fans.
I hereby certify that
my retirement has nothing to do with others.
It's my personal decision.
With Glory in your heart, you are invincible.
Ye Qiu.
= Statement on Retirement =
Tell them, don't need PR for now.
Ok.
The dungeon of the Field of God is a Tower of Babel.
Normally,
after the player kills all the monsters,
the gate of the tower will open,
and send the player to the Field of God.
But the thousand-machine umbrella couldn't.
Because the thousand-machine umbrella
still needs the last step.
It will be finished when the player
passes the dungeon of the Field of God.
Before that,
the thousand-machine umbrella can not be attacked
by any frost monsters in the dungeon.
Otherwise, the umbrella will be torn apart.
Thus, if you want to pass the dungeon of the Field of God
with the thousand-machine umbrella,
you can only climb from the outside of the Tower.
Transforming the form of the umbrella into a long sword,
you can use the skill of Swordsman,
Spellblade and Berserker.
Transforming the form of the umbrella into a rotor,
you can use the skill of a machinist.
I hope one day,
the thousand-machine umbrella can reach the top of Glory.
Are you so free? Especially wait for me here.
I am very busy, OK?
Watch this.
You are here to accompany your captain and try the weapon, right?
I'm here to accompany Shaotian.