= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 19 =
Bye!
-Drive. - OK.
Finally! He's left.
He's more difficult than you are!
Is my big brother really difficult?
Wait!
Are you Ye Qiu or Ye Xiu?
I'm Qiuqiu.
Qiu...
If you were Ye Qiu, I'd be Ye Xiu.
Nobody's fool!
Smart girl.
Could he buy a new one?
Always fixing this old one.
Ye Xiu...
= I'll come invest next year! By Ye Xiu =
You wanna trick me again?
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Very nice!
It's pretty!
You're more thoughtful when growing one year older.
Mucheng, do you like it?
Look good on me, right?
It's like custom-made for you.
Very pretty.
Couldn't agree more.
It must be expensive.
It's OK. Got a New Year discount.
Three for 20 yuan.
Here, Mucheng.
It's for you.
Another one is for Tang.
I'll go working.
Wait.
Come here. This is for you.
Come here.
Three for 20 yuan? Scram!
Ok. Got it.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure he'll be at the celebration in 30 minutes.
OK.
Sun Xiang!
Sun...
The celebration is about to start.
What are you doing here?
I'm busy.
Are you learning Dragon Head Raising?
I'll make it.
It's just a single move.
Is it very important?
I'll beat Ye Qiu with Dragon Head Raising.
Ye Qiu?
He's not even qualified to be your rival.
Think about it.
Nothing would happen if you beat him.
I wanna tell people I own Leaf of Autumn.
It's yours!
= Jia Shi Team =
Well...
Leaf of Autumn could be yours.
Or it could belong to others.
Whether you could use Dragon Head Raising or not isn't the key.
I am.
Understood?
In Jia Shi, it's not enough you can play Glory.
You need to understand my game rules.
The only thing you need to do is:
show me you deserve to be Leaf of Autumn.
Are you done?
May you leave?
In 20 minutes,
you'd better show up at the celebration.
= Closed =
= Open =
What a pity!
Your opening means my leaving.
See you in a year.
Welcome come back in Spring Festival.
My contract will end in a year.
Will I have a position in your Xing Xin Team?
Not sure.
If you retrogressed, we'd have to look for another Launcher.
I'm the top Launcher in Glory!
In one year, my apprentices will be riding the whirlwind of Glory.
Watch your throne.
It might be stolen.
Don't worry.
I've stuck my throne to the ground with Flex Glue.
No one could steal or rob it.
By the way, speaking of apprentices,
he's coming back today.
Who?
You know who.
Little Monster.
See you.
= Glory =
Solo! Solo! Solo!
Kick off!
Move!
Hurry up!
A new rule has been added since last year.
Players in Team 2 can't hold ranking matches without permission.
But Captain Ye said players needed to improve themselves.
It's too long if there's only one ranking match each year.
If someone wasn't convinced, they could fight.
Then we could solo.
I'll go dismiss them.
Watch your back!
Remain calm.
- Let them finish this round. - Continue!
Dodge!
Use your skill!
Beat him!
Good job!
Great!
Nailed it!
You wanna solo with me?
Not convinced by my ranking?
If I were not the best, who would be?
I beat you in less one minute.
Am I right?
I know everything.
If you didn't lose Qiu's return materials,
you'd only be the runner-up on the Ranking List!
How boisterous!
I've heard someone else is on the top spot of Team 2.
= Li Rui =
Is Li Rui here?
He finished the test ahead of schedule unexpectedly.
Captain Ye asked him to train abroad.
He was unwilling to go.
Unfortunately, Captain Ye left.
Otherwise, he'd name Qiu Fei as his successor.
Weren't you training abroad?
Why come back ahead of time?
If I didn't come back now,
things would be totally different in Jia Shi.
Would Team 2 change its position, too?
Now what?
A round of solo.
Nothing more.
I fed you with skills in the last round.
Didn't see you improve more than last year.
Shut up!
Beat me first!
Vanishing Step? Impossible!
How could you use it?
= Glory =
Yeah!
Great!
= Qiu Fei =
Prepare a feast for me today!
My treat.
Leave Team 2 if you don't show up.
= Qiu Fei =
What a good apprentice Ye Qiu has got!
Players in Team 2 have been confirmed.
You prevailed over Li Rui just now.
He'd lose face. That's all.
Nothing will change.
Not happy after being kicked out from Team 1?
Chen Yehui.
You're right.
The pot calling the kettle black.
Others had built you up for years.
Then you suffered a disastrous decline.
What' more, you are labeled with...
Traitor.
Yes, you are a traitor.
I feel awful for you.
Cut the chase.
Beating around the bush makes me sick.
You know what I'm going to say.
Ye Qiu betrayed Jia Shi.
As his apprentice, you think Jia Shi won't kick you out?
If you were crawling your way out later,
no one would ever know I beat you up.
He has built another team.
He's going to revenge on Jia Shi!
So what?
Qiu Fei.
Ye Qiu has ruined your career in Jia Shi.
You can't join Team 1 as long as you're his apprentice.
Can you accept it?
Keep talking.
I can give you a chance.
It will dissociate you from him.
As long as you help us stop Ye Qiu from returning the league,
I'll recommend you to the boss tomorrow.
He didn't take you into account when he left Jia Shi.
Think about it.
He left like that?
But he meant everything for me...
...in Jia shi.
I told you I wouldn't go back.
If they want to divorce, fine.
They think it's shameful that their son is playing eSports.
Show your big brother some respect!
You don't want to see your younger brother, either.
As an overseas returnee,
you'll be very successful.
Just wait and inherit our parents' company.
Your brother will not seize power.
Say it again when you're capable of seizing power!
I'm a loser.
I'll never achieve anything.
Consider I'm not your family anymore!
Do you still have food?
Sorry. We are about to close.
The chef is off work.
Dragon Tooth!
No bumping!
No rush. No rush.
Fight! Fight!
Go after him!
Take your time.
Steady yourself.
Follow me, fight!
Hurry up!
Wait!
No rush!
Hurry up!
Team up!
- Don't return! - Team up!
Use Dragon Tooth!
Idiot! Let me help you.
No no no.
Da Jin, Da Jin.
Where did you go?
Everything is ready.
Wait for you to start Project BBQ!
What are you doing?
It's a crucial time!
Master! What about you?
You lost?
I won!
You won! You won!
How amazing!
Amazing!
Good job!
Same time tomorrow.
OK. Thank you, Master.
Why do they call you "Master"?
- New here? - We could lose.
=Jia Shi Team =
Team 2 is on the 7th floor.
The elevator is at the door.
I'm new now. But I could be the captain next year.
You have good skills.
You should not work as a chef.
Stay with me.
You are the headwaiter here?
No wonder they all listen to you!
Wait. You did great when using Pseudo-join.
But others will dodge it when using Quick Standing.
What's your suggestion?
You're asking the right person.
Sky-strike him to the air first.
Then use Dragon Soaring.
Get the DPS first.
Let me tell you. When there's a chance, use Dragon Tooth.
Stiffness effect.
Wait. Speaking of the Circle Swing...
You used it too early.
Are you listening to me?
I'm the future captain of Jia Shi.
Fawn on me.
= The King's Team =
What do you mean?
You don't believe me?
I didn't say it.
But Jia Shi values one's competence the most.
You'll have to prove yourself.
Then you can say that to me.
Say it again when you're capable of seizing power!
You think I'm a loser, too?
We've got big guns in Team 2.
You can pick a good player to solo with.
When you are on the Ranking List,
come to me again.
= Jia Shi =
In your team,
who's the best player?
= Training Score =
Chen Yehui.
Who is it?
Why?
You are Chen Yehui?
= Jia Shi =
Let's solo.
If I win,
I'll...
...take over Team 2.
You really said that?
Chen Yehui didn't throw you out as if you were a psycho?
What a big heart he has!
Don't call me "psycho".
I have defeated Chen Yehui.
Whose idea is this?
Whoever defeats the champion will be the new champion.
Interesting!
It's said it was Jia Shi's captain, Ye Qiu, who came up with it.
It's him!
Hush!
Great minds think alike!
Agreed.
Now would you want to be my apprentice?
I'm the champion of Team 2.
Why would I do so?
You wanna be my master with your unpolished skills?
You wanna learn Pseudo-join from me last time, right?
You're just putting on an act with all your nonsense.
Who's talking nonsense now?
I've been proficient in Pseudo-join.
Then why are you here?
I'm doing well in the restaurant.
Why'd I goof off with someone from Team 2?
Whatever.
I don't care.
Peace out.
Your Vanishing Step...
Could you teach me how to do it, please?
I really want to learn Vanishing Step.
Could you... please?
No way.
Why?
If you teach me that,
I'll teach you whatever I learn in the future.
Listen to me.
Captain Ye Qiu will come to vet everyone next week.
With all my skills, I'll be selected to Team 1.
I'll learn more kills from the captain and teach you.
OK?
Sounds good?
Peace out.
Thanks for the coke.
Could you show me one more time?
Just one time.
No way. I told you no.
Wait!
I treat you as my friend!
There are many unique skills.
Are you not going to teach me?
= Jia Shi Team =
Today's breaking news.
After he left Jia Shi, the famous player Ye Qiu built his own team.
= Glory News =
According to an informant,
Ye Qiu planned to leave after Season 6
when Jia Shi suffered a revenue decline.
Building a new team is something that has been in his mind.
= Glory News =
Fans of Jia Shi say Ye Qiu is returning kindness with ingratitude.
They feel bitterly disappointed.
Coming!
Players in Team 1 are all here.
Hurry up, let's get ready!
- Where is Captain Ye Qiu? - Is he coming?
Captain Ye Qiu...
He is coming!
- Hurry up! - OK.
Qiu Fei, are you ready?
Our captain is coming.
Something came up.
You go ahead.
Are you ready?
We should sign up with the card later.
How about I sign up for you?
OK.
I've told you I had nothing to do with the school incident.
I didn't start the fight!
Dad asks you to come back to make it clear...
I have nothing to say to him.
He always thinks I'm a loser, doesn't he?
He smashed my arcade game machine.
When I told him I was going to be an eSports player,
he even said I was a shame.
Don't say it to me.
Handle things by yourself.
I'm just telling you what Dad said.
If you don't come back, Dad will go find you.
Why?
Why would all of you want to control me?
Listen.
In about 2 years,
I'll make some achievement in Jia Shi.
I'll for sure get the championship in the Glory League.
Otherwise...
I'll never go back.
= Team 2 Assessment Chart =
Where is Qiu Fei?
I'm here!
= Team 2 Assessment Chart =
Sign up now.
Your rival is Chen Yehui.
Warm up for a bit.
Let's wait for the captain.
Captain.
Where is his card?
Give it to me.
If you want me to be your apprentice,
win this round first.
I...
Start!
Go for it!
OK. Let's start now.
= Zero Breakthrough =
Using Dragon Soaring from the beginning?
He's as proud as before.
= Zero Breakthrough =
Qiu Fei is the most talented one among all.
He's tough and brave.
His style is much alike yours.
I'm not as stupid.
If it were me, I'd break Zero Breakthrough's Ground Shaking Wave.
Sorry.
I'll defeat you soon!
= Zero Breakthrough vs. Combat Form =
= Combat Form defeated Zero Breakthrough =
Wait.
In the last round, Chen Yehui hit you with Frost Wave.
Why didn't you lose any HP?
What did you mean?
Please turn over your account card.
We suspect you were using tag-in services.
It'd injure the fairness of the game.
I have to check your account card.
To rival against him...
I didn't need to cheat.
He... was using tag-on services.
It's not true!
You set me up?
Calm down!
Don't do it!
Calm down! What are you doing?
- Let go of me! - Calm down!
Now what? I was cheating, fine!
Throw me out!
Punish me!
So what? I'm a bad boy.
I haven't revenged enough.
What I want is expel Chen Yehui from Glory!
Glory is not your instrument of vengeance!
I don't care about all this.
What I do care is why you play Glory.
I want to show my dad.
I want to show you.
I want to show everyone that thinks I'd cheat and looks down on me!
If what you want is show to others,
you don't deserve to be part of Glory.
I won't throw you out.
You let yourself out.
Then tell me!
What should I do?
You could go on.
Or you could give up.
I don't even have a chance.
How could I go on?
You could because I'm your captain.
Captain...
= Jia Shi Team =
Why are you taking Glory as your instrument of vengeance?
Ye Qiu...
What you owe me is not just Glory.
Hui, Congrats! You've defeated Qiu Fei and joined Team 1.
Hui, will you live upstairs where Team 1 players live?
Yep.
I've heard they live in separate rooms.
Is it true?
Yep.
That's great!
OK. I know you'll miss me.
But we are still in the same building.
You can come visit me.
OK.
By the way, try your best.
You'll move upstairs one day.
Go for it.
Thank you!
We'll try our best.
- Better opportunities will come. - Yes!
Go for it!
= Jia Shi =
Chen Yehui...
You really hope Ye Qiu will be my enemy?
We shouldn't wait for Qiu Fei.
Maybe he's not coming.
Qiu Fei hasn't come. Cancel the plan.
It's meaningless.
You said...
...you'd give me one more chance, right?
Where is Ye Qiu?
Where is he?
In District 10.  His ID is Jun Moxiao.
Great.
You've made big progress during the half-year training.
None of your business.
Not good enough in predicting and judging the situation.
Saw me using Dragon Tooth, you shouldn't react with Chaser.
You've learned Vanishing Step, but it's not perfect.
That requires more experience.
Need more training and experience.
Good!
You've improved your Vanishing Step.
But did you miscount your Double Hit?
Are you done?
Since you have left Jia Shi,
save the crap for your new team players!
I never...
only looked you as a team player...
Then why did you desert from Jia Shi?
He gave up Jia Shi.
He also gave up everyone here, including you.
Even if we can understand what he's done,
what is he doing now?
He has betrayed Jia Shi.
Qiu Fei.
He told us one thing before.
Glory should never be anyone's instrument of vengeance.
But he is taking advantage of Glory.
By establishing his own team, he's against Jia Shi everywhere.
He's in Xing Xin Net Cafe across the road.
We can go with you.
It's between Ye Qiu and me.
None of your business.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Where is Ye Qiu?
Over there.
What are you doing here?
Don't you play Glory because you love it?
Won't you get tired for 10 more years?
You didn't mean it?
Manager, I lost connection!
- Come and check! - Coming!
Just a sec.
Hurry up! I'm fighting against Boss!
I'm talking to you!
- I dropped! - Hold it for me.
- Fixed? - Nope.
How about now?
It's OK now.
Ye Qiu.
Manager, a cup of tea, please.
-Here you are. - Thanks!
You had a good life abroad.
You've grown much taller!
I thought you were a chef before.
Now others see you as a net manager.
Same old trick.
Speaking of the net manager...
I am one now.
Haven't played it for a long time.
Want to?
One round.
It's not easy to save the ball...
If two balls in the same color are at the entrance,
you'll pot by pushing it with the ball behind.
But we have a difficult situation here.
Two balls do not belong to the same party.
If you want to pot...
you'll have to choose your own path.
I wouldn't join you if it was just pushing balls.
Look at the position.
If I can figure out my own path,
it'll be easy to save it.
You wanna try here?
Wanna stroke it with full strength?
Good plan!
They went different ways.
Everything in its place.
Good plan or bad...
Depends on where you aim.
Again.
Try here.
It's doesn't matter if you have a ball to push.
Focus on the present.
You'll see the future directions more clearly.
What...
What are your future directions?
I...
I just want to play billiards for now.
That's all I want, too.
Why are you working as a net manager in such a place?
If you want to start over,
you can pick any team.
Because there are people who love Glory.
Glory is their whole world.
What does this have to do with you?
I'm just one of them.
- We've passed! - Made it!
Great!
Good job!
Not easy!
Don't forget.
You were one of them before.
Captain...