= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 33 =
Our two players have been on the stage now.
= The Ninth Glory Challenge =
Please get into the competition room
for preparation.
Good. Yi Cunhui has detoured to the rear of Anxious Ghost.
His move and choice look more like an Assassin,
rather than a Ghostblade.
Now if Yi Cunhui sang the Ghost Array,
Anxious Ghost would be thrown into passivity.
The Ghostblade of Team Zhu Xian hasn't found that
his rival has already been in his rear.
It's a bit reckless.
Yi Cunhui is going to attack.
It seems that he's not going to sing the Ghost Array.
Move!
Yi Cunhui gave up the chance of singing the Ghost Array.
He made a melee attack using Ghost Array and Ghost-Chop.
But it appears that flaw was exposed to
Yi Cunhui on purpose by Anxious Ghost.
What a pity!
He lost some HP.
Yi Cunhui is very familiar with this arena.
He escaped successfully.
Anxious Ghost lost his goal.
Yes. Anxious Ghost is very cautious now.
He is moving slowly.
He is searching for Yi Cunhui's location.
Look, right now Yi Cunhui is still
hiding on the top of the wall.
It appears that he's still observing the surroundings.
It isn't a long distance between Anxious Ghost and Yi Cunhui.
And the former is moving toward the latter.
That's a good chance!
But I don't understand what is he waiting for?
Anxious Ghost is quite near him.
He can make a sneak attack at any time.
Oh, no!
Yi Cunhui's location is exposed by his shadow.
Anxious Ghost has discovered!
What? Anxious Ghost didn't dodge.
He got hit! What happened?
Anxious Ghost is too passive.
He got repelled again.
Yi Cunhui is catching up with him.
It's Wen Array.
Anxious Ghost has nowhere to run.
Qiao Yifan knows the map much better than his opponent.
We can see that...
Yi Cunhui is still singing the ghost array
The location and timing that he chose are perfect.
One more Dark Array.
He blocked his opponent's line of sight.
Qiao Yifan's vision of overall situation is great.
Seal off the perimeter by using the Ghost Array.
It's like the encyclopedia of Ghost Array right now.
It's going to be game over.
The Feast of Ghosts.
All of the Ghost Arrays exploded at the same time.
Anxious Ghost is going to be hurt to dead.
Nice!
Okay. Congratulations on Qiao Yifan's victory.
For winning the first victory of Individual Event.
It's so amazing.
Qiao Yifan showed his strong dominance to this game.
He is familiar with every location,
every angle and each detail of this map.
Even to an alarming degree.
Well done.
Okay. Let's watch the playback on the screen.
It was the lightning.
He has used the lightning.
He has used the irradiating position of the lightning
when he started the second attack.
He hid his attack in it.
It caught Anxious Ghost off guard.
And got hit directly.
Ruo Feng,
I have a bold idea.
Yi Cunhui just failed in a sneak attack.
Was it really a stupid mistake?
After he failed, he ran quickly down to the footpath.
Anxious Ghost was disturbed by the lightning in the next moment.
Was these all a coincidence?
It means that it's a part of the plan.
Yes.
What kind of trick did you play?
We are all Ghostblade.
Haven't you noticed that?
We remember Qiao Yifan has been mediocre since his debut.
From the first time be defeated by Xuan Qi Knight
to nosed out the Everlasting.
And finally gave us such a wonderful performance today.
He has became a mature professional from an nameless person.
He is able to stand on his own two feet now.
And he can bring infinite hopes to the team.
A perfect victory.
Xing Xin Team took the first point.
It's fine.
- It doesn't matter. - You will make it next time.
Good!
You has shown your power to Zhu Xian Team.
See?
We will win even though Ye Xiu is not here.
We have to win even though captain is not here.
Next, it's my showtime.
I will win.
Congratulations on Xing Xin Team.
They took the first point of Individual Event.
In the following,
they decided to appoint Bao Rongxing.
And how about Zhu Xian Team?
It's Zhang Jian. They will be rivals in this round.
The second round of Individual Event.
Bao Rongxing from Xing Xin vs Zhang Jian from Zhu Xian.
Bao Zi, the Invader.
Zhang Jian, the Invisible Green Hornet.
It's him.
Bao Zi.
He has gone.
So fast.
We're in trouble.
What's wrong?
Zhang Jian is not a famous player.
They are all ready.
Please get our two players into the competition room.
His opponent is a veteran in Zhu Xian Team, Zhang Jian.
We don't know that if Bao Rongxing gets fully preparation.
They have entered the map. The game is on.
We can see that they meet each other in the beginning.
But Bao Zi is not going to fight face to face.
He chooses to run away.
Altough Zhang Jian is not a first-class player,
but he is a seven years old professional player.
He is quite experienced.
His techniques are very steady.
Bai Zi...
Maybe he can scare away the ordinarily players.
But not him.
Zhang Jian is a seasoned player.
They are getting closer.
Phoenix Cut.
Bao Zi, the Invader is downed.
He is cornered.
He has nowhere to run.
But only to fight back.
Bao Zi is so passive now.
He may die if he goes on like this.
The Intimidation Skill.
It only can weaken your opponent's attack and the attack speed.
It doesn't have any real defense efficacy.
It's so puzzling.
It seems like Bao Zi is going to fight back.
It works.
How can it be?
Ranger has no sword.
What's is going on?
The situation is reversing suddenly.
Bao Zi catches the rhythm successfully.
His opponent is dead now.
An Eye For An Eye.
Bao Zi has remembered his opponent's tricks.
And fought back with the same trick.
But when did Bao Rongxing decide to use An Eye For An Eye?
I didn't notice that.
It was that Intimidation Skill.
Although it didn't stop the Invisible Green Hornet's attack.
But it bought a brief gap for Bao Zi.
But...
He didn't play his best trick vexedly.
But to reverse their position by using Knee Attack.
And got behind his back to seize the opportunity.
Turned the tables finally.
He forced the Invisible Green Hornet into blind angle
and killed him.
Congratulations on Bao Rongxing.
He won this round.
An incredible victory!
Good!
Bao Zi.
I won!
Well done!
- Incredible! - You are so tough!
You are promising now.
You know how to use tricks now.
An Intimidation Skill with An Eye For An Eye.
How did you come up with that?
Are you let him forced you into the blind angle on purpose?
The blind angle?
Was that a blind angle?
The location where you almost lost.
Don't you know that?
I didn't think about it that much.
He was chasing me at the beginning.
And I just kept running. Ran and ran.
Then I felt so humiliated.
I thought I should intimidate him a little bit.
I didn't expect that he would use a ultimate skill on me.
And then I used An Eye For An Eye without thinking.
I thought the most important thing is to be alive.
Fortune always favours fools.
Well done!
Just keep trying.
- Fighting! - Fighting!
Next is the third round of Individual Event.
- Xing Xin Team sent Mo Fan. - Fighting!
And Zhu Xian Team sent Zhang Shu.
Captain is so drawling.
We don't know when will he come back.
Just play to your strengths later.
Go and find a place to hide.
Never launch an attack unless you have to.
Do you understand?
I've not finished yet.
Okay. The third round is going to begin.
Mo Fan from Xing Xin Team vs. Zhang Shu from Zhu Xian Team.
It's a battle between Ninja and Knight.
Speaking of it,
Mo Fan did a great job in Team Competition.
This is his first time to take part in the Individual Event.
Deception is a famous Scrap Picker in the Field of God.
His individual combat capability should be good.
Actually, I'm looking forward to it.
Will he take his opponent as a prey today?
To obtain his opponent's equipment.
They are ready.
Please get into the competition room for final preparation.
Please.
Okay. They have entered the map.
The third round starts!
In the very beginning, Deception choose to hide himself.
It seems like he is looking for a sneak attack.
They are very close.
The Knight will be attacked firstly if he hasn't found out yet.
Knight vs. Ninja.
It's a tough fight for Ninja.
Knight has the most strong defensive power.
Ninja needs to be very careful to exhaust Knight's HP.
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
There is an opportunity!
Zhu Yue didn't realize Deception at all.
Deception is going to launch an attack.
What's going on?
Mo Fan didn't choose to attack.
Was it the wrong timing?
It seemed like a good timing.
Such a good chance. What a pity!
The knight has turned around.
Deception can't launch an attack momentarily.
He's still looking for opportunities.
He is getting closer to the knight.
Scrap Picker's character is to forbear.
It seems like he won't attack unless he is sure.
There's a chance!
But why did he give up again?
It's not like a Scrap Picker.
What is he doing?
Is he waiting for a better timing?
He is procrastinating.
Yellow card warning.
What?
If you don't attack in half a minute,
you will get a red card warning.
Mo Fan was penalized to be passive in game
for didn't launch attacks for a long time.
He got a yellow card warning.
It's so surprising.
I almost forgot about this rule
if the referee didn't give this penalty.
You asked him to do it.
I just asked him to delay the time a little bit.
I didn't know he didn't even know the rules of the game.
You know him well.
Okay. The game is continued.
As expected, he didn't seem like the same person at all.
But it's not a good time to attack the knight.
Is he going to fight with the knight fave to face?
Nice!
With Deception's attacks,
Zhu Yue can't fight back at all.
Zhu Yue is losing his HP.
It seems like Deception is going to win.
But he used his skills too often.
What's his plan in the following?
Why he chose to run away at this critical moment?
You can see that...
There is no ultimate skills in his skill books.
All of his skills are freezing.
Deception was caught by the Knight,
he can't use his Escape Skill yet.
If it goes on like this...
Deception is going to die before his skills get unfrozen.
He can do nothing after using the common skills.
It seems like he is still play like a Scrap Picker.
Yeah. He didn't seize the opportunity in the beginning.
And he made some mistakes.
His play wasn't very stable after the yellow card warning.
To against such a professional player,
and Knight has such a strong defensive power.
You can't expect to kill him so easy.
What a pity!
Mo Fan is still lack of experience.
He didn't seized the opportunity in the beginning.
But to be labile after he got a yellow card warning.
He was not calm enough.
Congratulations on Zhu Xian Team. They got one point.
Xing Xin hold a 2-1 lead over the Zhu Xian now.
- Well done! - It's fine.
It's fine. It's not your fault.
You just wanted to buy some time.
I will make Ye Xiu to say thank you when he is back later.
The decision has came out.
Do you want to know the result?
You're suspended.
I always thought we would meet in the final.
What a pity!
You're out early.
Maybe I am out.
But Xing Xin Team won't.
Do you know the scores of your team now?
I've known you for so long.
But I don't even know what you really want.
I could see that our friendship...
is so intriguing.
But it's good.
We won't meet in the final.
In case of our friendship gets worse.
The fame is fake.
But the feelings and experiences are true.
We've got two points.
We hold a 2-1 lead over the Zhu Xian now.
We still have a good chance to win.
We have to fight for Ye Xiu before he is back.
Tang, what do you think about the Arena Contest?
One-against-three.
I will do what I said.
That's right.
We should be overwhelming.
We should be confident.
We will not only take down the Arena Contest,
but also the Team Competition.
Come on!
We will make it!
Fighting! Fighting!
Fighting!
Don't worry.
One-against-three.
Xing Xin Team appointed Tang Rou for the first round.
- Zhu Xian Team appointed Ke Jian. - Ke Jian.
Please welcome them to come to the stage.
Ye Qiu is absent.
Here's the chance.
Fighting. Fighting. Fighting.
One-against-three.
Here comes to the Arena Contest.
Xing Xin Team appointed Tang Rou for the first round.
Zhu Xian Team appointed Ke Jian.
I heard all the fans of Xing Xin Team are yelling
One-against-three.
Okay. In the following,
Let's looking forward to the battle
between Battlemage and Assassin.
Ladies and gentlemen, the first round of Arena Contest.
Han Yanrou, a Battlemage vs. Shui Youhan, an Assassin.
Game starts!
They both good at melee attack.
Maybe they will fight hard in the beginning.
Tang Rou used her consistent strategy.
She launched onslaughts to her opponent.
It's a hard fight between Battlemage and Assassin.
You will be hard to fight back if you got attacked first.
Shui Youhan only can seek chances to consume her HP
among Han Yanrou's attacks.
The rhythm of this game is too fast.
We will see the result very soon.
Shui Youhan failed to attack her back several times.
Han Yanrou is going to win.
Now it's the time.
Shui Youhan only got five percent of HP.
Shui Youhan is running so fast. It's too fast.
Struggled to blow.
Han Yanrou reacts quickly. She stepped back.
Dragon Breaks the Ranks.
They hit each other at the same time.
They perished together.
But Han Yanrou's HP goes to empty first.
Shui Youhan is the winner.
Bravo!
I am sorry, beauty.
You took the bait.
Struggled to blow.
He reversed the huge disadvantage successfully.
Tang Rou, as a newcomer,
her APM and skills are remarkable.
But she lacks of experiences.
Her opponent took advantage of it.
She didn't anticipate his intention at all.
That led to her loss.
We believe she has learned a lesson from it.
Let's looking forward to the growth of this newcomer.
Congratulations on Zhu Xian Team
has took down the first round of Arena Contest.
Tang Rou, you have to leave now.
She can't fight anymore, so...
They have two players now.
I am sorry.
It was too fierce just now.
The second round is going to start.
Xing Xin Team appointed their manager, Chen Guo.
Zhu Xian Team appointed their captain, Lin Yi.
Boss, it's your turn.
Really?
Relax.
Just play steadily. Don't overexert.
I will get your back!
It's okay.
Fighting!
Play steadily. Don't overexert.
Boss, fighting!
Fighting!
- Fighting! - It will be okay.
Boss, fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Captain, that's their Team Manager.
She is not a professional player.
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Even the Team Manager has to play it herself.
It seems like Xing Xin got into a big trouble today.
Okay. Here comes to the second round.
The Launcher of Xing Xin Team, Cloud Chaser.
Her opponent is the Swordsman of Zhu Xian Team.
Ten Thousand Swords.
They have entered into the map.
Game starts.
Speaking of Cloud Chaser,
she is the boss of Xing Xin Team, Chen Guo.
I didn't expect she will enter the field.
Chen Guo...
Play steadily.
Maybe I should hide.
We could see that Cloud Chaser is very cautious to
choose her dodging.
She has found a cover to hide.
Where is he?
But the position she picked is so terrible.
Ten Thousand Swords has found her
and getting to her from the back.
She didn't realize.
Ten Thousand Swords didn't attack her immediately.
He chose to remind her first.
Cloud Chaser turned around. But her reaction was too slow.
Combo killed.
Cloud Chaser can't stop it at all. She is losing her HP quickly.
Silver Blade. Got it!
Cloud Chaser is dead. Ten Thousand Swords is the winner.
Ruo Feng,
Chen Guo is the Team Manager of Xing Xin Team.
Her techniques are so amateurish.
Why did they choose this kind of deploy?
But not to appoint their professional Launcher, Wu Chen?
Maybe...
She is the boss of Xing Xin Team.
And she wanted to play it for fun.
What are you talking about?
Play it for fun?
Our boss is not an irresponsible person.
What's going on?
Master is not here yet.
If there any possibles that he can't make it,
so they let...
What are you talking about?
Sorry.
I can't help at all.
It's fine. It was a little bit faster than I thought.
It's fine.
Boss, it's okay. You've tried your best.
You played well enough.
It's my show time.
- Fighting. - Fighting.
In the following,
Zhu Xian Team is going to be the defender.
Xing Xin Team appointed their veteran, Wei Chen.
Okay.
The third player of Xing Xin Team,
Wei Chen is on the stage now.
Can he turn the tables?
Let's see.
Well done!
In fact, your performance surprised me.
I thought we can defeat you easily.
But it seems like I have to work on it now.
I hope that your hands won't get hurt in this game.
Okay. They have entered into the map.
Windward Formation.
He thrown a magic missile at the very start.
He is using H&R to contain Ten Thousand Swords
by using the advantage of terrain and hand length.
Very smart.
Of course, he the master of Containment.
See?
They are getting closer.
Ten Thousand Swords used the Sword Draw.
Nice!
Windward Formation lost some HP.
Not bad!
Another Sword Draw.
Missed it!
Are you crazy?
It didn't work for me.
Five times.
He used the same...
No. He used the same skill six times.
But Wei Chen is a veteran.
He's very adept at adjusting the rhythm.
Ten Thousand Swords is in danger.
Six-light Prison! Got hit!
Ten Thousand Swords is being controlled.
Windward Formation released the Chaotic Rain.
Ten Thousand Swords can't avoid it.
He is losing his HP so quick.
He is dead.
It was too stressful.
Wei Chen is a veteran.
Such a powerful attack...
It seems like Lao Wei really can take down the Arena Contest.
Senior Wei is so great.
Okay.
Windward Formation has won this round.
Although Ten Thousand Swords' strategy is so unpredictable.
But finally,
he still lost this round.
Although Windward Formation has won...
What's wrong with him?
Only repeat those skills again and again.
Zhu Xian Team still has a good chance.
Hey! You!
Just go back to your mama if you are afraid to lose.
I hope you can say that again later.
In the following,
Xing Xin Team is going to be the defender.
Zhu Xian Team appointed Wang Luosi this round.
Please welcome Wang Luosi to the stage for preparation.
Okay!
Fighting!
Just play as what I did.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Arena Contest between Xing Xin Team and Zhu Xian Team.
Finally comes the final decider.
Zhu Xian Team appointed their Sharpshooter, Hua Nongying.
His opponent is the Warlock of Xing Xin Team,
Windward Formation.
Game starts! We can see that...
These two profession began to fight at the very start.
What's wrong with him?
Why will he play like a Swordsman?
It's so strange.
The Sharpshooter avoided Pursuit.
Just to repeat the same move.
Not only their Sharpshooter played like this,
but also their Swordsman did.
Do they have any eccentricities? They are so sick.
The same skill. Hit!
Windward Formation got hit.
No. They did it on purpose.
They made me to repeat such complicated techniques.
In order to stimulate my injured wrist.
So they can exhaust my strength.
That's right. Windward Formation can't follow up
the rhythm of attacks released by Hua Nongying.
His dodge was always one step behind.
We don't know if he can adjust his state in time.
We can see that...
Hua Nongying is still using his captain's strange strategy.
The HP on both sides is going to be zero.
It's a critical moment.
Who will die first?
Simultaneous attack!
Hua Nongying dodged it.
Windward Formation got hit.
He is dead.
Hua Nongying is the winner of this round.
Zhu Xian Team has won the Arena Contest.
What a pity!
Windward Formation almost defeated two opponents continuously.
Congratulations on Zhu Xian Team on winning the Arena Contest.
Zhu Xian Team hold a 4-2 lead over the Xing Xin Team now.
Xing Xin Team has to take down the Team Competition
if they want to win this game.
The first half ended.
Xing Xin Team is two points behind.
Let's enjoy the Team Competition after a short break.
= Chen Guo =
Captain's phone is here.
Where are they?
Captain is absent. What else can we do?
There are many other ways.
For example, Tang Rou can take captain's place.
Yifan can be a alternate.
We can put Bao Zi in...
There are many other ways.
But we haven't tried them before.
It means we have no other ways.
Lao Wei, let's drink some water.
It's okay.
We still have chance.
What's wrong?
You can't even handle a zip-top can.
You said you are going to finish one-against-three in public.
But you were a little bit cowardly today.
It's fine.
You still have chance in the Team Competition.
Don't you want to challenge three of us?
By the way,
don't make the same mistake again.
Don't worry.
I won't make the same mistake twice.
Captain is going to lay out the new tactics.
Let's go.
She's broken down.
Xing Xin still has no chance to win the Team Competition.
I've decided that we won't appoint Wu Chen.
Bao Zi will take Wu Chen's place.
Mo Fan, you will be the alternate.
We will lose.
What do you mean?
The Individual Event.
The Arena Contest.
We all listened to you.
And what's the result?
We only got two points.
I suggest that...
We should follow captain Ye's strategy
if we want to win.
We should put Wu Chen in the first formation.
Bao Zi, you are in charge of...
Wu Chen is an invincible opponent to Zhu Xian Team.
Captain has his own reason to let him enter the field.
Wu Chen is a Launcher.
He has advantages in the Team Competition.
Lao Ye is still not back yet.
Yifan, you are in the first formation.
= List =
I don't know what's your reason.
And I don't know why Wu Chen is not here at this moment.
We are a team.
I just want to tell you...
Please don't put your feelings before the benefit of our team
if you want to win.
My personal feelings?
I just want to win so much that...
I can't take our team's fate as a stake.
I have my own reason.
Please trust me.
What should we believe in you?
Stop it!
Rookie!
What are you talking about?
You thought everything I did was wrong, right?
Stop it!
Go back to your seats.
It was not Lao Wei's fault.
It was not your fault neither.
We should blame on ourselves.
We forgot our tactical training for drinking.
According to our usual practice,
let's vote for it.
= Agree and disagree =
Three vs. three now. Tie vote.
Yifan, how about you?
I abstain.
As the team manager, I will make the decision.
Listen to Lao Wei.
= Qiao Yifan =
= Alternate, Mo Fan =
= Su Mucheng =
Hello.
You only got two points in the first half.
That best newcomer has collapsed.
What's more?
Although Wei Chen is a veteran.
But his strength has reached its limit.
The most horrible thing is...
Your boss has to enter the competition herself.
What else can you do?
The game is not over.