=The King's Avatar
=Episode 8
By the way, Yingjie
I heard about the restaurant we always go to
is renovated recently.
It may take a long time.
before we can eat its takeout
So you have to help me eat more.
Why this face
I'm just going to train for a few days.
I will come back
Come back early.
Of course, when I come back
I must defeat the Jun Moxiao
I heard them say
The captain intends to train you to be a successor?
Yingjie, come on
You too
I'm leaving
In fact, I think
it would be nice for Yifan to go to glory training camp.
Stay in our team
It is even worse to be a server forever.
Okay, thank you.
Did you see the man operating yesterday
This is ridiculous
Yeah, that's funny
Can also appear that kind of mistake
Yeah
Yifan, your report card
We see that you have been working very hard.
And is also making continuous progress.
But the team competition is too intense and the quota is limited.
Go back to Wei Cao with your current results.
There was no chance to play either.
It is suggested that you continue your study here.
Waiting for the right time to go back
Then I'll go first
You have a lot of ideas, but unfortunately
You didn't find your problem
Master, I want to play again
To beat me
No, to lose
To lose again in the hands of your Master
I want to know what my problem is
Why I work so hard with few progresses
Meet me at the arena.
The combo just now
I should have escaped within ten seconds.
But I still got it
Master deliberately exposed three flaws
I couldn't catch it
Hesitated time missed the best time.
Cutting throat is not hard enough, arc flash is not fast enough.
All my skills have become chicken ribs in my hands.
I really have too many problems
Thanks for your time
But you have a good overall awareness
Overall awareness
It's a pity that overall awareness can't let me
help team kill one more person
But can let you help the team win
This is a very rare trait.
Master, can I learn from you in person
Find me here
I hope the guidance of you
can let me see the future clearly
Where to go
I know it
the last time that group of people is your Wei Cao Team
The professional lineup has sold you out
I didn't think you were still playing Glory
What’s on your mind
Retired person also are allowed to play glory
Anyway, you are also idle
Let's fight in the arena. I can pay for the materials.
Don't cry when you lose
I don't have to
I have many players who can accompany you to practice
Don't play games with me
It seems that I will not be a trainer
for Wei Cao
Haven't given up yet.
Run inside this map for a few more days.
It is estimated that novice players
will consider you as a non-player character.
Tang is angry here.
She is waiting that guy
to avenge
The loss was really a bit miserable.
But this is not necessarily a bad thing
The world of glory is big
She had to see the gap before she knew how to catch up.
What do you mean
Who let her start
to meet the peak of Glory
If you don't understand this
after losing more she would be crazy
Don't talk unless you can speak good words
Write homework
You
What if I lose
It is good to win or not
Xiao Tang is foolhardy.
which can be her advantage
Looks like Wang Dayan's material
I have to take it
It's not impossible to practice with others.
But on one condition
I have a sister on my side
If you want to fight me, you have to go through her level first.
Good
This is the cake I bought for Xiao Tang.
Why did you eat it
You spit it out for me
Boss
Xiao Tang is too busy to eat
Still fighting
It's been almost two hours.
Then why don't you persuade her
Don't go to
I said your wings are hard now
Dare to talk back to the boss, don't you
To persuade her to come and eat a cake
Okay, if you don't go
I will fire you
Okay, I'll go
It's you who wants she play Glory every day.
It is also you who do not want it.
The timing of this transition is really difficult to handle.
What are you whispering about
What do you want to say?
Isn't this very good
Go and have a rest and drink some water.
The pause is for a better victory
You are mocking me
What's good about losing ten games
Lose ten times
In the first set, you fought with the Magician
In 19 seconds, defeated by three traps in a row.
The second round is Battlemage
Twenty-two seconds
With a counterattack
In the third set, the deceitful sword lost after 26 seconds.
Lose in not seeing the situation clearly
But wear off half of the other side's blood.
The fourth set was 33 seconds.
41 seconds in the fifth set
And the 10th set just now
You persevered for a whole minute and a half.
You are improving though you are losing.
You won't eat twice for the same loss.
Do you feel this
My goal is to defeat my opponent.
Not to count the seconds
This is difficult
What do you mean?
In the last round, we will fight against the Magician
Although you supported an unprecedented one and a half minutes
But was trapped three times in succession.
The other party cheated you out of all the tricks at the beginning.
At the back of the Dragon Teeth and Sky Hit also played too early
Half blocked by the opponent
Has anyone ever told you
Chuan-style eyebrow can cause arrhythmia
What nonsense
In addition to the glory of the PK technology
Most of the time it is psychological warfare.
Strong play is your advantage.
If being led by the nose
Then you will become your soft rib
There's another showdown. Come on, champ
Xiao Tang, you have been playing for more than two hours.
Take a break and have a cake.
Xiao Tang,
Let me fight him
I especially want to fight now.
Let me fight
Just leave it to me.
Eat cake
If you have been working so hard recently
I authorize you not to study for one day, okay
Good good study day day up
I love learning.
Then
The weapon you saw last time in Kongji City
I'll buy it for you
Don't
Can I make a cake for you myself?
Don't want to eat.
Guoguo
I'm really angry.
And you can’t make me happy
Can’t
Then I will leave you alone
It seems to accompany you to go out to play
would not interest you either
This works
Finally, there is a way
That's a deal this time
No matter where you want to go, what do you want to eat
I promise you I will be on call when you call me.
I want milk tea
No problem. I'll line up to buy it for you
I want to eat cake.
I'll make it for you myself.
I want to eat hot pot
Then whenever we like
We can go to eat
Don't be angry, okay
Then you have to accompany me more in the future.
You can't keep brushing copies.
Keep your words
Sure
Then I have to think about which to eat first
Thirty-five
Thirty-six
You go left
I said, are you stupid?
If I let you go left, you go left.
Why go right?
Do you have any reaction speed?
I'm telling you, it's good that you met me.
You must be in trouble when you meet someone else.
Do you know it
Sorry to have caused you so much trouble.
Mechanical keyboard you also play electronic competition
Playing Glory? Which District and What profession
Have you ever taken a copy of the record
I'm telling you, I'm a great Ranger.
When you are free, , I will take you to brush a copy.
How about?
By the way, where are you going
I'll-I'll find an Internet cafe
All right, let's go. I'll give you a ride
I told you.
The master said that my reaction speed can be fast
Clever and savvy
It is very suitable to be a professional player.
The way I look at you
should play Glory very bad
But don't lose heart
I did the same when I first started playing.
After a period of time
The master taught me a lot
Thank you. I'll just get off at the front.
What do you take me for
Am I the kind of person who gives up halfway
I will do what I promised
Sit down
What's the name of your account? I'll add you.
Or you add me
I tell you in Glory
I am the super fierce Ranger
My account number is
Stop, stop, stop, stop
Why are you in such a hurry
This is Xingxin Internet Cafe
I am using actual actions
to teach you another trick
Too much equals less
Be careful in the future.
Good
Let's see each other
Some other day
Thank you
Hello
Excuse me, is Jun Moxiao here?
He's in there
Thank you
Jun Moxiao
Are you Jun Moxiao
Jun Moxiao, Jun Moxiao
You are the Jun Moxiao
It's me.
I am Steamed Bun.
Boss, this is called predestination
For you
This may be just a small chance encounter
But for me,
But a bitter waiting for a long time of encounter
Hello, my name is Qiao Yifan
What predecessors
This is my boss
The sky can only be ranked second.
Do you understand this relationship
Ah, what, thanks you
Hello, my name is Qiao Yifan
I am the Assassin, Grey Moon
I want to follow
You want to brush a copy with him, don't you
No, I don't think so
Do you want to see the true face of a Smart umbrella?
No
Last time you told me
What was the last time
This is not the first time you have seen each other.
When?
Which year, which month, which day, which hour, which minute, which second
Before or after knowing me
Boss
Did you admit it or not
I am your big disciple
Of course
Later, every morning to open the door
Give it to you.
Then you admit it
I am your big disciple
I just admit you to do job for me.
My big disciple Han Yanrou
Is there
Han Yanrou
No wonder you are so spirited in Glory.
Brilliant, fresh and free from vulgarity
Han Yanrou I knew it
You must be a man
You play heartbeat with a female number.
Is it right?
Who are you
I’m Steamed Bun
Steamed Bun
Steamed Bun?
Let's change places.
Master has been here since your retirement.
Yes, to be a network manager here
Why do you do network manager work
This is the closest profession to Glory
If I can't get back to Wei Cao this time
I think I don't even have the courage to log in to Glory.
Then watch the play
Relax mood
There is a very good play recently.
Have you seen it?
Escape is useful but shameful
Elder, I actually don't have much time to watch the play.
Because ..
Even if I spend all my time training
There is still a big gap between them
I am always the one who drags
So until now
I have never been to a real match before.
But I still want to play
You sure
I don't want to give up like this.
Then change your career and practice
Trickster
Find the right direction
It is much more important than working hard.
But Master
I don't even know how to be an Assassin.
And at my current level
If I practice a career from scratch, I will
Then change your career and practice
Our team has a Trickster already
There will be no need for a second one.
Find the right direction
It is much more important than working hard.
You are going to change your fate
Not to give up fate.
What do you think
Actually let the professional team to help you to brush a copy
Can you afford to lose the match?
Boss Tao, I admit it
I, Chen Yehui, am sometimes selfish.
But I swear
I have never thought of harming Jiashi.
You said such a Jiashi
Even now no one gives way to the captain.
It seems that you are really going downhill
Only those on high can go downhill.
People who have always been low
That's desperate
On my first day in Jiashi
You look down on me
Who is the boss here
Where is the boss
Thank you
Our network manager is getting more and more handsome.
What are you doing here
Be a network manager
Yeah
How about?
Accustomed to the days when others wait on you.
Are you used to serving others in turn now?
Thank you for thinking. I'm used to it
What if you are not used to it?
Who made you so low-key
Without Leaf of Autumn
no one seems to know you anymore
Yeah, unlike you
So high profile publicity
But still no one knows
Our captain
Now they have all become network manager of Internet cafes.
How can you speak so harshly?
But it doesn't matter
Those of us who are presidents
Contact with many people every day.
Top to the boss
Down to these network managers in internet cafe
We all have to take care of it
Be president
It is not enough just to deal with people.
It depends on strength.
You used to be a team member
Is too much effort to win the hearts of the people
But not good thinking to improve their own strength
To be eliminated by the team
I didn't expect you come to the guild.
still in these crooked brains
What makes you judge me
What have you done since you came to the guild?
How many copies of the records do you take
What is the increase in membership
You are not good at management.
Then drew the whole team to fight
It's no use
How do you know?
If glory is not regarded as love
I advise you to leave as early as possible.
Who do you still think you are?
You are a broken network manager
What qualifications do you have to teach me?
Turn on a machine for me.
Network management, Ye
I'm sorry.
The hospitality taught by our boss
may not be suitable for drunkards.
Please wake up and come again
Okay, then we'll see you soon
looking forward to your next visit
Okay, I'm almost there.
Nothing
Brothers from the First Canyon
was basically wiped out.
Can you brush the copy well?
For the sake of that disturbing material
is it worthy
Can you keep some order
Jun Moxiao is not asking for a little material
A lot
To invite Jun Moxiao to brush a copy
Almost sent out the elite team
And rob each boss they saw
Not just Line of Canyon
Take a trip to any copy these days.
All the same
It is shura battlefield
The Jianghu is chaotic
Xi Zhou.
Look for yourself
Copy of Record Brush by Master Brother
It really helped us a lot.
The growth of our membership
is obvious to all
But don't forget
The amount of tasks assigned by the top team
But also follow to improve
Look at this killing every day
The rhythm of being crushed
This month's results are worrying again.
This is the so-called Ju Moxiao
Brings both win and lose
Don't tell me those stupid words.
How is the feedbacks from agents
we arranged in other guilds.
It's not easy either.
All scratching their heads to find a way
Master, where are we going
Shopping
This is Kongji City
It is one of the formal main cities on the glorious continent.
All players can trade equipment here.
Buy supplies
The most important thing to do is
After the character was killed in battle
You can choose to return to the city and continue fighting after resurrection.
There is a barrier at the gate of the city.
It is equivalent to a huge protective cover.
It is forbidden to fight in the city, but it is not allowed to fight out of the city.
This empty city
Later is our stronghold
After brushing so many copies
Finally, we can enter the city.
Boss, look at this bloodsucking claw I picked
Isn't it handsome?
The weapon of 800 gold coins is different
Of course, all the gold coins have been spent for you.
Thank you, boss.
Buy things and become the boss
This is too obvious for you, isn't it?
Boss
You also buy a weapon for Tang rou's sister
She shouldn’t beat me without orange weapon.
Weapons are not that important to me.
The examination is about to begin.
I'm exhausted
Let's go. Hurry
Let's go.
Come on
You also cheer
The first training camp evaluation test is about to begin.
Let's go now
Good
Tang rou sister go so fast, why
Let me show you my new weapon.
Watch out for ambushes
Just in time
Let me try my new weapon
Team 2, firearms
and thermal missile preparation
Team 2 roger that.
Battlemage in Team 1,
flame strike preparation
The newly changed equipment has an influence on attack speed and moving speed.
Pay attention to adaptation
Got it
The attack speed improved do the timing right.
With the orange weapon
I feel that I run very fast.
Like a rocket under your feet
Boss, after my character runs out of blood
I will drop equipment, right
I have to watch out for such a good weapon.
Don't be blown away by others.
Return to Kongji City first
Another one to look for abuse
An inch of Grey, Trickster
Who is this person
Are you helping us or killing us?
Steamed Bun attack
And Tang separated by 60 degrees angle out of position
The two men staggered the attack time by 30 seconds.
Yifan watch our attack rhythm
Judging the arranging position in advance
Got it
Are you that little broth I brought with me
Not bad, you
The rhythm is well mastered.
Continue refueling
Don't waste your time in formation.
The cooling time is well controlled.
Ensure maximum efficiency
Yes
Cooperate with Han Yanrou
Miss it
Be careful
Don't panic and stabilize your hand speed.
Give up the ice array and trick array first
Moonlight array follows
Don't mess up if you make mistakes.
The more urgent the situation is
The more you can exercise your mind and judgment
Got it
A knife array blessing
Trickster
Seize the opportunity and coordinate at the same time.
Superposition Trickster
Got it
Two paradoxical array
A Trickster that has just been registered for a few days.
Can play two paradoxical array
President, the three teams of brush map back
Do you need any support
No, it's just the first dish
It worked
Younger brother Yifan
Your Trickster is awesome, isn't it
Find a time we learn from each others