= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 24 =
Just an Net Café
can be boasted to be a team.
Put this in front of Jia Shi,
how dare this boss here.
What era is this now?
How can this guy still get fans?
I'm his fan.
Also the owner of this Net Café.
Is there any problem?
This lady,
what are you thinking about?
To be a fan of Ye Qiu.
What do you mean?
In the whole Glory,
is there anyone more tragic than Ye Qiu's fans?
No one can find him after competition.
He got no resource.
No popularity.
That's no big deal.
But why did he suddenly retire?
Now he's been vanished.
His fans can't even put up a notice.
They've been his fans for more than a half of their youth,
without knowing the appearance of their idol.
A player of Glory is never free.
Ye Qiu, when would you come back?
Don't be this sad.
It has been ten years.
It's not easy for all of us.
But Ye Qiu will definitely come back.
I promise you.
Could it be said that
you know that Ye Qiu has formed a team?
I'm the boss of this team.
That means
your boss has always been in the E-sports circle
these years.
And it's the Glory circle.
That's right.
He said himself that
all his skills of making a living
are in the Glory.
Without the Glory,
90% of him would be a good-for-nothing.
I knew.
What about the remaining 10%?
It's his face.
He said his face is equal to hard currency.
It'll be easy for him to live a well-to-do life
with his face.
Forget it.
Hey, man.
Be careful!
This is the treasure of our boss.
Sorry.
This...
is silver equipment?
It's a wand reached level 60.
AD 530.
AP 777.
This is a top-level silver equipment made by our boss for years,
specially designed for warlock.
Warlock?
Is he still playing warlock?
Yes.
Since his beginning of Glory,
he has always been playing warlock.
Making a silver equipment in such conditions,
he's real something.
Our boss is stubborn.
You know, the price of silver equipment
has been driven up.
But he would never sell it.
That's right.
He would neither play a game,
nor join a team.
What this top silver equipment is made for?
That's right.
Made such effort.
What is it for?
You must be a rich second-generation.
I'm not.
Then you must have some connection with the league.
What do you mean?
No.
I don't mean that.
What I'm saying is
as a fan of Ye Qiu,
I'm a tragic myself.
You're the boss of this team.
You must have either software or hardware, right?
I do have.
I have this Net Café,
and a group of people
who follow Ye Qiu.
How many people are they?
If me included,
there are eight.
Where are they from?
Recruited from Glory.
Although they're all new faces,
they all enjoy great potential.
Even worse than a poorly-equipped troupe.
No wonder they would cheat me.
What?
I mean
you really have a good sense.
Xing xin must have a bright future.
Are you short of player in Dungeon?
Why don't you tell me the online coordinates?
My team can help you attack.
Online coordinates?
He went to search for it himself?
It's not easy to be a bounty hunter.
Besides, this is a big order.
KPI of the whole year is depended on it.
Surely he'd do it by himself.
Really?
What kind of order it is?
Follow me.
Look.
Here it is.
Our mission.
Kill Jun Moxiao.
We're not lack of player in the Glory.
But I know.
It's not easy for you to come here from afar.
I still have one.
So here you are.
What's this?
Signature of Ye Qiu.
Don't tell other fans.
Boss!
Time for meeting!
Got it!
Excuse me.
Task for this week is
to attack the following maps.
The coordinates of next Dungeon is...
Just pass by.
Pass by.
Let's continue.
Here you are, boss.
Go aside.
Boss.
The online coordinates of Jun Moxiao...
Don't even mention it.
That woman's mouth
is as close as the burglar-proof padlock.
No matter what I asked,
nothing of Jun Moxiao's whereabouts can be told.
She's so alert.
It's reasonable that
you can't find it.
Boss.
We've found it.
What?
At 4 p.m..
At Zone A in Miluo Ancient City.
- Yes. - The coordinate is
3958 2564.
You guys are bravo!
Thanks to boss's good leadership.
That's right. Boss is excellent!
Let's have a meeting.
Our mission this time
is to thoroughly intercept and kill
Jun Moxiao in Glory.
The reward is priced at 500 per time.
No upper limit of attack.
Do you know what it means?
The setting in Glory
is to decrease one level after Penta-Kill.
Then making a player reached level 70
to level zero,
the accruing amount will be
175,000 yuan.
If the Cleric brought him back to life,
the profit will be doubled.
That is 350,000 yuan.
350,000 yuan.
This is merely in the Field of God.
If we chase him into common area and kill again,
we'll gain 700,000 yuan.
700,000 yuan.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes.
Finish this order,
we'll have our year-end bonus.
What do you think?
Wanna have a try?
Yes!
Boss! Boss!
Jun Moxiao is online now.
How many people are they?
Just him alone.
Hey, man.
Here comes our God of Wealth.
Let's welcome our guest!
All right!
Team two, lift-off.
Team one, get ready for point fire.
Roger that.
Double hack.
Oh my!
How many changes does this umbrella have?
His operation is still this bravo!
Go in batches!
Run out of his Patience.
Half of our team have been killed.
Why don't you attack, boss?
Wait a sec.
Right now!
= Glory =
We got Jun Moxiao!
Boss!
Bravo, boss!
That 700,000 is ours!
Finally got this crafty piece of shit.
People who got killed today
will have a red packet!
Especially those who got Jun Moxiao's online coordinates.
You deserve a good reward!
Thanks, boss.
What I want to say is
our boss has a wide connection.
But for your friend
who helped us find the online coordinates,
we...
Wait a moment.
My friend?
What friend?
A man came here this afternoon.
He said he's your friend.
Oh, no.
That's a substitute!
My friend.
Long time no see.
You asshole!
You set me up!
How could that be set you up?
I know you're suffering from investigation.
So I sent you information on purpose.
What?
I helped you so much.
You complain for your own failure of catching me.
Cut off this shit!
Release me!
And lie down to let us have the money!
Then all will be written off!
Or else,
Lao Wei.
You even got a silver equipment.
It seems that your conditions are becoming better.
Let me have a look.
I warn you.
Don't even think about it.
Or else I'll go after you forever.
Go kill him, buddies!
He doesn't have a lot of blood.
Let's defeat him!
This is the benefit of team work.
You're here alone with little blood.
Just wait for the mass brawl and being defeated!
Who tell you that I'm alone?
Come on!
It's your turn.
Roger that.
This is the helper that you called again and again?
A Ghost to support?
Like a piece of cake.
To fight you,
it's enough.
Do you see the opposite old dog?
Don't be irresolute.
Go decidedly!
Got it!
Slow down.
You sounds young.
Why are you so irritable?
Sorry.
Hey, bro.
Good skills!
Look at your operation and mentality.
You don't like a player of Glory.
Are you a professional?
From which team?
Team Wei Cao.
Team Wei Cao is great!
I have a good relationship with Wang Jiexi.
Later I'll tell him
to let you play the first launch.
You're good.
But just lack of an opportunity.
Senior.
Sorry.
But I probably won't need it.
No, you need it.
Young lad.
= Baidu =
This is your time.
= Ghostblade of Team Wei Cao Zhou Yebo =
Don't be shy.
Don't resist.
= Ghostblade of Team Wei Cao Zhou Yebo =
Get ready for the battle!
Zhou Yebo.
= Ghostblade of Team Wei Cao Zhou Yebo =
You got wrong.
Great.
Still humbug him when facing imminent disaster.
The one you searched is not him.
He's my teammate.
Why did you search for Team Wei Cao.
Shit.
You're unreliable.
Where can I find information of your poor team?
This wand
looks like disgusting.
What kind of aesthetics does its owner have?
Cry now. Lao Wei.
Your baby wand is mine now.
You bastard!
Give my silver equipment back right now!
Boss.
Their computers are off-line.
Ye Qiu! You asshole!
We'll see!
= Xing Xin Net Café =
- Boss. - Boss.
Have a seat. Boss.
Clear the site.
Yes, sir.
Clear the people.
Or you want to book the whole Café?
I want Ye Qiu to come out
and see me.
It's none of his business if you want to book this Café.
You can talk to me directly.
You deserve?
I think,
you look familiar.
Who am I is not important.
But what I lost
must be taken back by myself.
People who pretend to be Brother Xiaoma here
will at least bring a toothpick.
Here.
It's for you.
Your label comes out.
Stop pretending.
Little fan.
Who's that?
With so many people.
Give Wand of Death back to me right now!
Or I have a hundred ways
to make you miserable!
A hundred?
You're creative.
I wander around the world,
have been known as heartless and cruel.
My buddies stand here today.
I promise you within days,
this Café will have to close.
A few days ago, boss was saying that
we need to hire several people to keep the Café.
That's all right now.
We can save the salary.
Old chap.
You know how much painstaking effort it took
for me to make this equipment?
Thousands of nights.
Dozens of versions modified.
Finally I got this top silver equipment.
It's not what I crow about.
Look at warlocks in the whole professional circle.
If I were the second,
no one dares to be the first.
You must be lonely.
Lao Wei.
What an effort is was to make this silver equipment done!
It'll be a waste to fight common players.
Unless you want to come back to the competition.
Save your shit.
Say it.
How could you return the Wand of Death?
It's rather simple.
Have a Tutor Selection for Team Xing xin.
If we win,
I'll give it back to you.
I knew it.
You want me to help.
This poor troupe can't work, right?
I have a big company.
Just a lifting of my hand
means tens of millions business.
How could I have time to kick up a row with you here?
Well,
see you then.
Listen.
Boss has already decided
to remould that wand.
For my usage.
I'll have a silver equipment from now on.
Bao Zi.
That silver equipment
cannot be owned by you alone.
What?
Shut up now.
Let me introduce this silver equipment to you.
In terms of INT,
Magic Strike,
Personal Attribute Bonus,
and Magic Singing,
this silver equipment has almost been perfect.
It's one of the best silver equipment I've seen before.
If we can dismantle it,
Its INT material can be used to
update Tang's Lance.
Its Magic Singing can transform into attack speed for Bao Zi.
Xiao An can have its Magic Strike.
- That's great! - If so,
we can form a team of violence output.
There should be no problem for that.
When you are dismantling,
you must be very careful.
In case we failed,
that silver equipment would be ruined.
We won't lose anything.
We don't need that wand after all.
Just tear it apart.
It's good that the owner of this equipment is not here.
If he was here,
stand and watch his equipment
got dismantled,
how cruel it would be!
That's heartrending.
Deal.
Wish we have a fruitful cooperation.
You can leave now, buddies.
I have to stay here.
Boss.
Don't worry.
Don't be reluctant.
I'll be back as soon as
I got my Wand of Death.
Boss.
I mean...
It's near the return deadline of our suits.
Stick it back.
See you, boss.
Let's go. Go.
Come on, go.
Let's go back to our company.
Boss said that we're going to use containment.
What is containment?
Containment
is a representative tactic of Team Lan Yu
in ancient times.
Containment means that
without conflict with the opposite side,
you can keep harassing him.
You don't even have to make any frantic effort.
It can help you achieve your goal.
Look.
This is what I found online.
The containment.
It's Tom and Jerry.
This old tactic
is from centuries ago.
It has been out of date.
Tom and Jerry is
a classic animation
produced by MGM
in 1939.
It is a bit old.
But none of us is grown up without it.
Containment?
Have you guys heard it before?
Containment has never been old-fashioned.
Only of you're not good at it.
If you can do it well,
it is classic.
Today I will let you see
what is the real containment.
Pick a map that you have the highest rate of winning.
Or else you'll find excuses,
if you lose.
Then we choose Tower of Babel.
Our win rate is 87.6%.
What do you think?
You want to win me with such a low rate?
Except the map,
I'll give you one more right.
You decide the rule of this game.
Then we climb the Tower.
The one who gets to the top of the Tower
is the winner.
Here we go.
Three.
Two.
One.
Race start.
Bao Zi.
Help me to observe
which route would he go.
He doesn't move at all.
How come?
It seems that containment
is not a big deal.
The first principle of containment
is to keep calm no matter what happened.
You can't even climb.
Cut off this shit of keeping calm.
No matter how fast you climb,
you're just my stepping-stone.
You...
What a dirty trick!
The second principle of containment
is to gain mastery by striking only after the enemy has struck.
Yi Cunhui.
Your reaction
and mentality are all not bad.
Thanks, senior.
So do you know the 36 frequently-used
combos of Ghost?
What are they?
You've gone to far!
Kill him when the game is almost finished.
That's foul.
The third principle of containment
is to play hard.
That's the best way of playing games.
I'm so kind that I'll give you the last lesson.
The so-called containment
is to play not by the conventional wisdom.
The essence of it
is the best opportunism.
Let's play again.
Young players are eager to win.
That's good.
However,
that'll be all for today.
I've got something else to do.
Got to go.
How do they prepare?
Not bad.
Then next,
I'll start to prepare for
the Challenge.
You guys busy now?
No problem.
Just do it.
By the way,
have we got enough money?
What are you looking at?
Don't worry about money.
I'll get it ready.
I want to see you smiling at me.
The coffee tastes so bitter.
But you smile,
is my sugar.
He who touches rouge will be stained with red,
but he who gets in contact with you
will feel sweet.
This woman is easy to deal with.
I didn't even try my best.
She just went away.
What do you intend to say?
And can't say it in front of the boss.
These young players,
they really can't make it.
No matter how I taught,
they can't learn it well.
Is it because they don't understand,
or they don't admit you?
In a word, don't count on them.
Just give up.
Things like competition,
are still depend on us older generation.
I'm not part of you.
When you say the word "old",
don't include me.
I'm serious.
Playing competition
needs players like you and me.
We got both competence and experience.
My Wand of Death,
is the key to success.
You must give it back to me.
Or else we'll definitely lose.
You want to get it back so eagerly.
Who are you going to fight?
I'm invincible.
Do I look like someone has any rival?
In today's Glory League,
is there no player that you regard as rival?
No matter who he is,
if fights with me,
I'll hit him hard.
There's no sugar in my coffee too.
Lao Wei.
Give me a smile.
Bao Zi, here you are.
Until now, I've realized
what is the "Return of the King",
and how intrepid it is!
Don't lag behind, King.
I'm afraid when you arrived at the competition terrain,
you can't even find the right door.
We're going to fight Team Lan Yu, will you be afraid?
Team Lan Yu?
What do you mean?
Why didn't you tell me we will fight Team Lan Yu earlier?
I know you're a bastard!
You lie to me so that I can fight Team Lan Yu for you.
Captain?
Why are you here?
Captain.
Where have you been for such a long time?
Do you know how long have we been finding you?
You should at least tell us now that you have retired.
Don't you miss our team?
Don't you miss me?
I won't let you go this time!
I finally find you.
Do you know how much I miss you?
I even write a song for you.
Named "In the World only Captain's Dear".
You little jerk.
After just several years,
you become this heavy.
Captain Wei.
Long time no see.
You've been here too.
Lao Wei.
Time to get in.
I'll go bananas right here, right now!
Come here!
Don't go there!
What are you doing?
Lao Wei said,
see you later.
See you around.
Ye Qiu, you're so shameless that you even lie to me!
Lan Yu,
is not easy to defeat.
Come on.
Give me the Wand of Death.
Right now!
Wand of Death,
weighs 3kg,
attack speed 2.
No matter how I observe,
this weapon seems to be designed for Yu Wenzhou.
Am I right?
Where's my weapon?
The competition is going to start.
Here you are.
= Purple Wand =
What can I do with a chicken claw?
Where's my Wand of Death?
Give it to me!
I promised it'll be returned after winning this game.
Why should I waste my time if you don't give it back?
For your face or your moral quality?
Aren't you clear?
I'm a retired old player.
To fight the leader of Team Lan Yu with a primary weapon?
Am I mad?
Without my silver equipment,
I won't help you fight.
My helper is you,
not your weapon.
Don't lie anymore.
In a word,
will you give it back to me?
Last round of Tutor Selection.
Team Xing Xin vs. Team Lan Yu.
Ready to start.
This is a life or death battle of Team Xing Xin.
Good.
It's you who want me to die.
Don't regret.
It means that if Team Xing Xin want to promote,
all of their teammates have to survive.
Facing Tactic Master Yu Wenzhou,
and Blade Master Huang Shaotian,
it's impossible for all of them
to pass.
Ult.
Chaotic Rain of Swoksaar.
No interruption.
Team Xing Xin must get away from the ult as soon as possible.
As we expected, Troubling Rain
is going for Jun Moxiao.
There you go!
Lao Ye.
Take that!
Dragon Cut.
Phoenix Cut.
Triple Cut.
Cut!
Finally, it's our battle!
Are you afraid?
Now I tell you,
don't cry after losing the game.
Take it!
Slow down.
It's too violent for the beginning.
I'm afraid you'll be short of momentum later.
I won't.
You'd better worry about yourself.
Don't you believe
you'll win with the help of Captain Wei.
Unfortunately, your rival is me today.
I'm a corgi if I can't hit you to near death.
Top-level confrontation at the very beginning.
That's right.
We can see at the very beginning,
it's the long-anticipated confrontation.
Troubling Rain vs. Jun Moxiao.
They keep a distance to seek for opportunity.
Jun Moxiao attacks first.
And then slip away.
I guess he doesn't want to waste time here.
Stop! You shameless.
Come fight with me!
All right. The first confrontation
between Troubling Rain and Jun Moxiao
ended up with Jun Moxiao's tactical retreat.
At another side of the map,
What is the Warlock of Team Xing Xin doing?
No one in Team Lan Yu attacks him.
They just leave
Windward Formation here alone.
At this time,
Windward Formation should finish the schedule
as soon as possible,
or go meet with his teammates.
Waste his ability?
It seems Windward Formation doesn't want to fight.
It's a good place to have a walk in the town.
But in such a serious battle,
I wonder what would players of Team Xing Xin think
when they find what he is doing.
Besides, we also noticed that
Windward Formation's weapon is a purple equipment.
He just sits down.
Doesn't worry at all.
Is this a part of
Master Ye Qiu's tactics?
I've never seen
such tactics before.
Yi Cunhui vs. Brilliant Edge.
Dodge.
Two against one can be achieved here.
But Windward Formation looks like haven't noticed.
Senior Wei.
I need your help.
Thanks, senior.
Don't get me wrong.
Well,
don't get me wrong.
Go on fighting.
That's right.
Hit him. Hit!
Captain.
There's a Warlock sitting beside me.
He doesn't attack or retreat.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
Where are you?
Coordinates:
312 662
Qi Master, cover me.
Got it.
Here comes the Qi Master of Team Lan Yu. Cloud Seize!
He successfully got Windward Formation.
Sneak attack!
You said it so loudly.
Could it be called as a sneak attack?
Do you need me to teach you?
Lao Ye.
I got caught.
What can I do?
It's good.
It's your style to be caught and hit,
and finally throw in the sponge.
You wanna be against me?
All right. I'll let you see how I lose.
Senior.
Who ever asked you to save me?
Am I wrong to save you?
Of course you are.
Waste time to make the array of ice
is not as good as leave me and run.
But you said,
the essence of containment
is to gain mastery by striking only after the enemy has struck.
If I run just now,
what if they attack you in the rear?
This lad has a good memory.
You're so despicable.
Let the Warlock lie there to attract me to attack,
and then let the Ghost attack me in the rear.
Shameless.
Haven't your leader told you
the formation of Team Lan Yu is all about containment?
Yifan.
Let's show him
what is the real containment.
Okay.
Senior.
Can you stop running?
Lao Ye.
Are you imitating Sun Xiang today?
Don't be afraid.
Let's have a confrontation if you were a man.
Troubling Rain is still chasing for Jun Moxiao.
But it seems that
he has lost his goal.
Lao Ye.
Every dog has its day.
In order to save your life,
you can't even dare to go face to face with me.
I'm gonna catch you now.
There you go.
There's no love in the corner.
But in the rear.
That's unbelievable.
Troubling Rain has been kicked by Jun Moxiao...
What are you thinking about?
Shaotian.
I'm by your side.
Why don't you turn around?
You shameless bastard!
You make me get stuck like a boss in the Dungeon.
Good, Lao Ye.
Wait for me getting out!
We'll see!
Why can't I get out?