=The King's Avatar
=Episode 4
This circle drawn by the master
is to represent that we will to fight together.
Inside the circle is the pure land, outside the circle is the battlefield.
Is that what you mean?
I mean,
Don't move out of the circle
This ..
What is he doing?
How dare he face the monster alone.
Is this he kills them
or they eat him?
I'll go and see
We need to give him a few more minutes.
A master has a master's strategy.
We must have our tolerance.
Then our tolerance is
Wait
Fifteen minutes have passed
Is our tolerance sincere enough
Enough
The master's strategy is...
Record of distance to first
is only five minutes to go.
If not go out of the circle
we could be the biggest joke in the history of Glory.
This is what we call "staying the same and responding to changes."
We are making ourselves a joke.
President
Everyone, get ready
Listen to me count down three
Then out of the circle.
Three
Two
Congratulations to Lanxi Pavilion players.
The Lanhe, Jun Moxiao, Xizhou
Thunder, and Deng Huaye
break the ice forest record.
Time 15 minutes 24 seconds 11
Breaking the record,15 points
It was five minutes faster.
What did I say
The master I invited
This is called winning all by staying still.
With Jun Moxiao
the world of District No.10
belongs to Lanxi Pavilion
Don't move, don't move, don't move
It must be the master who came to me.
Jun Moxiao quitted Lanxi Pavilion
What?
It's over.
Go, go, go, go
Go
You go get me a cup of coffee
Quick, quick, quick
You
Go water the flowers.
Go, go, go
Xiao Tang
Why don't you choose a gunner like me?
I can teach you about it.
But I like to see my opponent
fall in front of me
Fighting Magician then
My idol Leaf of Autumn is also this profession.
I, Tang Rou, will lose to nobody.
Everybody
Mu Cheng
Today is our new captain
First training after taking office
This is a new break-in
But also a mutual understanding
I believe with Sun's joining in
And the efforts of all of you here
We Jiashi will surely create another brilliant future.
My goal is to
open a New Dynasty of Jiashi
Starting today
Sun is our dynasty model
The core of the dynasty
Take the responsibility of the captain in the name of the captain.
Fulfilled the captain's destiny
Sun
Jiashi
is yours in the future.
We will fight Lan Yu in the next war.
Training starts
Everyone starts training
Congratulations to Boss Tao for getting such an excellent talent
Thank you
Ye Qiu's revenge on me was personal.
Now, fortunately, the bad guy was driven away.
Do you think I can return
Ye Qiu retired voluntarily
No one wanted to drive him away.
Ye Hui
This meal can be eaten indiscriminately.
The words can't
No, you see, I have no other intention.
I just want to go back to battlefield
When he let you go
He was still the captain.
All people on the attack
Boxer in the middle, Qigong for cover.
Guns keep up, speed
Gun attack!  Disrupt the rhythm.
gunner, what's the matter with you
It's always that slow
gunner do not rely on speed to win.
For fast speed, you have assassin and ninja
Do you mean
There is something wrong with my tactical arrangement?
You arranged tactics?
Sorry, I didn't see any cooperation
I only saw everyone following you.
Running all around
That's when you can't keep pace with me.
What era is it now?
gunner is still behind
I think it was when Ye Qiu was here.
You are too comfortable
That's why you can't get used to the new style of play.
Ye Qiu's Tactics
It's just that he plays in front and stands up
You are hiding in the blind corner behind
Attack
Over and over, just a few moves
There's nothing ornamental about it.
I'm tired of watching you play even you don't feel bored.
Not bad, it rang three times and answered
It seems that you have been living at leisure recently.
No way out
Recently, friends have called one by one.
Mocking my miserable situation
I heard the bell
It's all conditioned
you lie
Your mobile phone has always been in silent mode.
you never get a call from anyone.
Looking for you
Only run to you
Shout face to face
Then you have to shout at me again
You're not in front of me
Is it?
The curtain in your room
Why hasn't it been fixed yet?
In my room
I just want to see
Did you change the password of your room
Do you still remember the password of your room?
First, don't scold anyone at the meeting tomorrow.
Second, don't scold me if you want to scold somebody.
Third, even if you want to scold me
no more than three sentences.
What about the fourth
At the first training meeting
Don't get angry with your new teammates.
Second, don't sulk even if you are angry.
Scold when it's time to scold
Third, if you sulk
No more than three minutes
Fourth
When you are angry or sad
rushed over to Jia Shi and shout
Shout what
Shout
One, two, three, four
From now on, do not turn on the silent mode
This string of simple numbers
Is all the tacit understanding between us
But I still want to stand in front of you
Press these four numbers for you
The great god
Boss, I'll come back to you later.
In a few days, it will be Jiashi's year-end press conference.
Should we organize a
Ye Qiu assistance activity?
The time has come to support my idol.
I'll pay all the expenses. Come on
It seems that I have to send a big killer
Blow you out
Possibility in impossibility
is the Best Interpretation of Competitive Spirit
of the master, Ye Qiu,
His unique skill dragon looks up
is also a legend in the history of Glory.
First, use the strongest move of battlemage's blade level.
Fu Long Xiang Tian
Then use the invincible hand speed
And micro-operations
Forcibly change the trajectory of Fu Long Xiang Tian
This makes it impossible for the opponent to evade the attack at all.
He performed with strength
There is no strongest, only stronger
Such a fried video can't attract everyone.
What's the matter? This is
What happened, boss
It's so noisy outside.
I lost the argument.
Sorry, sorry
I-I'll go out and have a look
Come on, Chu
I'll take a look
Over there, over there
Wait a minute, tear it up
Lever it
What are you doing
Do you know who he is?
Who cares
Give money and work.
Don't look, don't look
Hurry up and tear it up here
OK
He is Leaf of Autumn who has the skill of dragon looks up.
Your old coat is like an umbrella.
Hold up my sky to shield me from the cold.
You are like my exclusive detective
You can see through every movement and expression.
You are the most amazing person in my heart.
The days together are sometimes very fast.
Sometimes it becomes very slow
In my heart the dearest you
Is my forever support
It is also my eternal stumbling block.
Always miss you
Nice win
My father is a Ye Qiu fan.
Is such a virtual role
Let this group of people of different ages and occupations
who don't even know each other
become a group of sincere
and passionate youth
Father runs this internet cafe.
It's more like running a
dreams of Glory
He told me that in one's life
There will be many impossible moments
We must learn to live in these desperate situations
Constantly break through oneself
Looking for Unlimited Possibilities
To grow
After my father died, I refused to sell the internet bar.
I firmly believe that I understand the meaning of Leaf of Autumn
I can be the real master of Xingxin
The Pride of Becoming a Father
But today
You left
Be replaced
My spiritual worship
Disappeared
It is also my eternal stumbling block.
You are the most amazing person in my heart.
Let all boring moments become
so fun
In my heart the dearest you
Dad, you helped me choose
The occupation of a gunner
You said that no matter how far the target is
Just concentrate on aiming and never give up
We can definitely win it
I will insist
Whether it's an internet cafe
or the Leaf of autumn
Xiao Tang
You've been watching the strategy all night?
A leaf does not know autumn?
Guo
Anything wrong?
This persistent spirit of yours
It's very athletic.
Stayed up all night.
But the effect is not significant
I told you.
This Ye Qiu's style of play
is not we
inexperienced can learn
He is good at creating miracles in the impossible.
This is called the brilliant tactics
I can only imagine that I can't learn.
Understand this much?
I listened to what the webmaster said.
You are telling the truth
That's a bit of a lie.
A confident truth is the truth.
What is your confidence?
confidence?
network manager
network manager, come here
Boss, wait for me
Xiao Tang, let me tell you something
My network manager imitates Ye Qiu
Imitation is excellent.
Not to mention Xiao Tang
The network manager and I have no difference.
After all, the name similar to Ye Qiu
He won
Now you look at the strategy
There is no use at all.
You need actual combat training
You can ask him to practice first.
Thank you
You network manager
I have already practiced.
He grows up spiritually and speak quickly.
The water poured so quickly that it could be kept.
I'm not talking about this training
If you don't practice, you don't need to practice
In fact what
Is this a question of not practicing?
The decisive issue of she controls me
or I control her
If she practiced with all her heart.
then won't have time to ask about your lessons.
This is a clever secret tactic.
of course
Now everything is ready, only one thing is needed.
Do you know what do we need?
You
I can't.
She is in fields beyond my knowledge.
I really don't understand her temper and thoughts.
Also can't reach
Come sit down
Sit well
First add friends to establish contact
What are you doing
Fine
boy
You see, I was rejected mercilessly.
Wait a minute.
Refusal is a woman's natural privilege.
Reserved is a woman's inherent attribute.
As a man, do you know what you need to have?
To have the determination of being shameless
Keep adding
As a man, I don't want to lose face
What?
When people are interested in me
Being shameless is called determined.
When people are not interested in me
Being shameless
That's called stupid
Really? Why do I think
you a little confusion about who is the boss.
Who is the network manager
Why don't we have the money to be calculated?
Or you can make it clear that
the faces of the two of us?
I can read and understand us.
You don't want your face?
Boy! Add!
It's like an iron wall
Did you watch the match yesterday
Yes, I did
This is amazing
Especially good
The players have all arrived.
I'll wait for your decision.
Bloody gunner Yager, are you sure?
News from inside source
The map was refreshed just a minute ago.
At present, Zhong Caotang and Che Qainzi
they have already made it
It is estimated that Ba Qixiongtu will soon be over there.
Okay, hurry up
Get on quickly.
Go, go, go
Hands on, hands on, hands on
You do it first.
I'll be back soon
Why
All of you, pay attention to me
Captain Jesse is watching you all here.
The Zhong Caotang must grab the bloody gunner this time.
Captain Jesse cannot be humiliated.
Do you understand?
Understand
Everybody, listen up
Although we ggot the first kill last time
It took half an hour
This kind of mistake
Absolutely can't happeneds again!
Yes! president!
What is your goal?
High Level, High Efficiency and High Concentration
Okay, here is the time
to show your strength
Bloody gunner Yager
We are determined to win!
Everyone! Get prepared!
Victory beckons to you.
The Batu Guild has arrived
The leader is
The shameless man who named Ye Du Hantan
The Zhong Caotang guild has also arrived
Che Qainzi guild has already arrived with people.
The two of them guild unexpectedly on hold
The bloody gunner is so fierce
Which guild went first
Which guild will die first
Let's see what the two are going to do first.
Come very fast
Not as good as you
Who will go first?
You go!
You first! We Ba Tu follows
We have the ability to go first.
Don't rob
I don't want to be the cannon fodder for Ba Tu
Shut up
You are a person who has been dumped by Jun Moxiao
Still dare to fight against us for the gunner?
shameless
Another spy in our guild, isn't it?
Old Blue, you was dumped?
So miserable
I really want to see how bad you look now.
Better than you Zhong Caotang
All right, stop talking nonsense
Soon another guild came
We won't have a chance
Why don't we do this? Let's go together
How about that?
fine
Three
Two
One
Why don't go?
We are all preparing
Why don't you go?
We are also preparing for it.
Who drives the monster there?
In face of bloody gunner's shooting in all directions
Not even a scratch.
Damn good.
This operation is too cool
Where did Bao Zi Ruqin come from?
Nice knee attack
Hit back in pursuit
This war consciousness works!
Another expert came out!
Flexibility of action, attack in place
Really good！
Is throwing sand only to the eyes
can cause a blinding effect?
What is this operation?
Beautiful, this war consciousness is equal to unconsciousness.
That's awesome.
I have never seen such a cool method of suicide before.
I thought it was a big meat bun
I didn't think it was a small white steamed bread without stuffing.
Is a super rookie eventually
So inexperienced
Why don't you two go up and help
All right, let's go.
I'll cover for you and Lao Che.
Your selfish thought
Who can't see it?
Lao Che and I are not stupid.
You also don't dream to get profit from us
There is not much blood. He is not going to last.
Are we really not going
Wait
Wait again
A master has a master's strategy.
You do it first
I'll be back soon
Why
Master Brother Yetu Blood Shooter
Are you interested?
Yes
The rule remains the same.
Send me the coordinates
Master Brother, you are here
We are all ready
Let's go together later.
We Lanxi Pavilion are under your command.
All the rare materials are yours.
Old Blue, you are not honest. Ask for foreign aid again.
Yetu bloody gunner is belongs to the person
who has the ability to rob
I have the ability to find foreign aid.
Why am I not honest?
That's right. Take the leader by his own skill
I
Master Brother, why did you form a team with others
Old Blue was dumped again
I'm sorry for the change.
What do you know? This is strategy
Finding an expert to form a wild team
This operation is really good!
Ten o'clock' direction
throwing sand at his eyes
Put the quick move and the right move
I suggest you use the latter one.
Don't stop attacking
Move to the 6 o'clock direction.
use the brick
Don't throw it
Double the damage by directly patting the back of the head
Hook
slow down the attack
We have to control the pace
Why?
Wait for them
Damn, operating with tacit cooperation and accuracy.
Why does this inexperienced one look like a different person?
He was pretending, right?
Old blue, say something
What kind of strategy is this? I can't understand it.
What does Jun Moxiao mean?
The bloody gunner was on the verge of being killed.
They are lowering the output
They're not going to make it.
At this time not on when ah
You cowards
This is the time!
No one is afraid!
Batu! follow me
Zhong Caotang follows Batu.
President
I don't care! Go!
Received
Take the bait
Full output
OK
Hook
you hide
at one o'clock direction behind the boulder
Stay safe
They ran away
It seems that they have reached the limit of attack.
You got there early, didn't you?
Who Charge Who Delivers Burial
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Want to run?
The bloody gunner broke out!
broke out?
Be careful
Full back
Full back!
Too late
Lose?
as a president?
Jun Moxiao, the bad guy!
Jun Moxiao
Don't let me meet you in the future.
What should I do in case I meet him?
Of course, must solicite him!
Start our export performance
Congratulations Jun Moxiao and Bao Zi Ruqin
Complete the first kill of the bloody gunner
This is my first first kill
You are so great
You played well, too.
Right? I also think I played well
call me next time!
Yes, no problem
My name is Bao Rongxing. I am a warehouse keeper.
My friends affectionately call me Baozi
In addition to enjoying the pleasure of my work
My hobby in leisure time is playing glory
Didn't expect today
Actually got the affirmation of the great god
My dream is to join a professional team.
Play a real match
Become a real professional player
The president lost the match just now.
What? Impossible
I heard that there was a master from the other side.
The great god is not honest
You said it yourself
Wild figure leader who have skill who rob
You defeated
Zhong Caotang and Ba Qi xiongtu this time
It is estimated that they will take revange.
Really? I just finished talking to those two
I still have invatation to play together next time.
Those two have no limit.
Actually looking for you to play together
You don't want to?
Want to!
which
Buried ground
Prepare materials
I'll let you know when I have time.
The great god was still on our side
The material I got this time.
The promotion brought to the weapon is limited.
But the rare material plus the weapon attribution
All are numerical caps
So the best weapons must all be rare materials.
The rarity of materials does not lie in the explosive rate.
But the refresh probability of the hidden leader
This is the meaning of rare
Win again?
Just a little luck.
Clearly is very strong
The time for modesty must be low-key.
The high-profile time must show off
I-I really don't have a strategy
You are really experienced
No friends, no files
What can I do? I am also very helpless
If you don't add friends, you can teach by word and deed.
If you don't receive the file, you will change your strategy.
What can I do then
I am also very irritable.
That craziness can't solve the problem either.
Are you sure you can't finish the task
I
Definitely
Under the guidance of the boss
It is an achievable task.
The deadline is 24 hours.
The bell rang
Don't become a useful person
Don't become slag