= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 20 =
Planning to
give a hard blow.
That's good.
Get separated,
and go back to their own position.
Whether is good or not.
it depends on your view.
Try again.
Hit here.
Actually, whether there exists a ball
which can push you,
It's not important.
Focus on the present,
and then the direction of the future
will be more clear.
You
What's your future direction?
Me
I just want to play billiards.
I also just want to
play billiards.
Why do you
bother to work in such a small net cafe?
If you want to restart,
you can choose whatever team you want.
Because there is a group of people who like Glory.
Glory is their world.
What does it have to do with you?
In fact, I'm just one of them.
Great.
That's hard. Let's play again.
Don't forget.
You were one of them too.
Yes.
At that time, we just once
played billiards happily.
That's good.
Why did I listen to your words at that time?
Now I can only see the bastard occupy the position.
Rather than spending the time on
finding the evidence to prove that he framed you,
It's better to focus on the training,
and keep your own ranking.
One day
you will encounter him on your way.
Dammit.
If I encounter him,
only I could be the winner.
Excellent.
We have made the deal.
After I win,
You will own me an equipment.
Talk about it after you have won.
You haven't answered
my question.
UCI offer a chance
of one -year professional E-sports training.
Will you go?
Why is me?
Members of Team One need to participate in the competition.
Such a long-term exchange program
is best for players like you
who never enter the competition before.
When I come back,
can I come into Team One?
That's rascally.
You have owned me one equipment.
When do you give it to me ?
After you come back from abroad?
I haven't said I will go abroad.
After you come back,
I will give you a silver equipment.
Silver equipment?
You mean the silver equipment that
only the members of Team One could have?
Write down the IOU.
Write it down clearly.
Don't try to escape.
You don't trust me?
I trust you.
But you still write IOU.
Write that you own Qiu Fei a silver equipment.
Wait. Write that,
You own Qiu Fei, the regular of Jia Shi, a silver equipment.
OK?
I own you this.
= I own you a glory. =
Debts that you own me,
When do you plan to pay?
You own me a glory.
You will fight the glory back on your own.
What? Want to go back on your words?
Right.
So that I have reasons to entangle you.
I will give you.
You saw him?
I guess he must
lesson you brashly.
Just like he changed PK into a competition for guidance.
Always insulting others.
Qiu Fei, amazing.
You still want to improve yourself at this moment.
Pitifully, the things you copied are useless.
The tactics of Ye Qiu are out of date.
I am very happy that
you come back from abroad.
With you joining in, it's just like adding wings to a tiger.
We are both the victims of Ye Qiu.
Why not working together?
His vulnerable team
can't last for a few days.
Jia Shi has changed the captain.
You don't deserve mentioning Ye Qiu.
This is for giving you a lesson.
Later, if I hear it again,
I will beat you again.
Tang, Yi Fan, Bao Zi, they are all not here.
I feel a little lonely.
Kinda miss them.
To them,
this is an important choice for their life.
They should be prudent.
Yi Fan, good news.
You don't have to go to the training camp.
The captain says he wants to tell you something.
Keep your training in the team.
I wan to go somewhere else.
Practicing The Array Ghost.
Manager, what are you saying?
The company plans to give you promotion.
You are in charge of this area.
Please let me calm down.
This is the last day of the invitation.
Have you decided yet?
Yes.
I have made the decision.
Let me do it.
The little devil just came, right?
Jia Shi
plans to how to arrange him?
In terms of his temper,
whatever the arrangement of the team is,
he can achieve anything
as long as it is what he wants.
Actually, no matter Qiu Fei,
or other people,
They want to follow you.
It doesn't mean you have to be responsible for their life.
They just want to
Play Glory with you.
Since they have made the choice,
each of them
has to be responsible for his own life
Right?
# The starry fireflies from the ordinary #
= the wind spear =
# sailing with the wind and converge into the Milky Way #
# standing on the top and claiming that #
# We will regain our glory #
If you love Glory,
Please love everything it brings to you.
No matter it is pain, setback, or tears.
I can't be responsible for your life.
But I'm willing to become your choice.
Because where the sword points,
Is our glory.
# The glory we've missed #
# The pride in the future #
Boss,
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
Senior,
We are back.
# Is us from the ordinary life #
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
# I came from the past and will write the furture #
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
# The glorious moment of coronation #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
Yes.
I have to say,
the weight in my mind,
is finally unloaded.
You have no confidence of me?
As for things about the team,
I can definitely take care of them. Handle them.
Won't cause any trouble at the critical moment.
It's for encouragement. Keep on.
Isn't it something cheap bought in the street?
And use it to fool me, right?
It seems so worn and old.
It's indeed second-handed.
When it is given to you,
It will be third-handed.
Master, can you be a little sincere
when you send gifts.
The badge of the first league.
Awesome.
This can be regarded as an antique.
Ordinary players
can hardly collect it.
Am I an ordinary player?
Why not saying it earlier?
I almost miss the priceless gift.
Thank you.
I like this second-handed gift very much.
By the way,
I also prepare a gift for you.
What is it?
New beginning.
The gift has been sent.
The people upstairs are also here.
Since tomorrow, the mission of the new year will also begin.
Your order.
Give me the gizzards.
Now. Now.
Here. Take it.
We met each other in Glory and got together in Xing Xin.
In the long future, please render your help.
Cheers.
Wait.
I almost forget an important thing.
Important?
Important thing?
Boss, since today,
Ye Xiu and Jun Moxiao will always be with Xing Xin.
After the team is formed,
it needs to unify the management of the account cards.
But you don't need to be so urgent.
Tang Rou, Han Yanrou will always be with Xing Xin.
Bao Zi, the Invader will always be with Xing Xin.
Qiao Yifan, Yi Cunhui will always be with Xing Xin.
# It's a long and bumpy road towards the top #
Can he find a boss?
He can.
Who?
Me.
# even if I am beat black and blue #
# there is always hope rising from desperation #
since this is what you thought,
and so did they,
then I'm out.
You always give up halfway anyway.
Since you are unwilling to do it,
then don't force yourself.
I am
the manager of Team Xing Xin.
I am the manager of Team Xing Xin.
I am willing to fight with you to the end.
Thank you.
I will not fail
your expectation.
Thank you.
Xing Xin are bound to win.
Glory will never die out.
Challenge,
we are coming!
Since the establishment of the League,
there is only one ultimate goal of all players.
That is the championship trophy of Glory.
The ultimate throne of all players,
will have a new owner today.
We take the crown. Long life Xing Xin.
Next,
please welcome my dear teammates.
Please welcome Qiao Yifan.
Thank you to the league for giving us this trophy.
We will make persistent efforts.
That is too official.
Come. Next one.
I'd better not.
Next one. Next one.
Come here now.
Actually, I have so much to say.
But the one I want to thank most
is our boss.
I think it's not an end,
but a beginning.
Next champion, next champion of the next,
will all belong to Xing Xin.
Great.
Yes.
How about this shooting?
Is it good?
Have a look.
Perfect.
Underling, what are you doing, underling?
Does it a little joggle?
Remember this feeling.
Try again, OK?
OK. Let's go.
You are so annoying.
Isn't it tiring to act so many times?
The Academy Award owns you an Oscar.
Don't be so dramatic.
Not anyone can have the championship trophy.
Right.
That trophy,
I had it three times.
Apart from the fact that it's too heavy,
it's just so-so.
Really?
I don't know.
How about joining us in the shooting?
Yes.
Come and join us.
Join us.
Come.
When we take the crown,
Let's lift the pure gold championship trophy.
Hello, everybody.
I'm Xiao Lu.
This is the twelfth game of this regular season
in the eighth season of Glory.
Jia Shi vs. Thunderbolt.
This is an epic battle.
Why?
You will know later.
When it comes to Thunderbolt,
its captain, Xiao Shiqin,
is one of the four tacticians.
Always leads his team to overcame the stronger one.
His role, the mechanic Sheng Lingmie.
is also a S-level role in Glory.
It's the core of tactics of Thunderbolt.
As for Team Jia Shi,
it is led by Sun Xiang, the Rookie.
His role Leaf of Autumn
is called God of Fights.
The contest starts now!
The players enter into the map.
The team tournament and relegation battle
between Jia Shi and Thunderbolt begins right now.
Although Thunderbolt has
Xiao Shiqin, one of the four tacticians,
members of Thunderbolt don't have enough personal ability.
They also enter into the relegation zone pitifully.
Jia Shi changed its captain,
but didn't make any progress.
It also could be relegated.
Why not being afraid of the relegation?
Come back again by killing monsters and leveling.
You think it's like playing the dungeon, don't you?
killing monsters and leveling? Shame on you.
Only twenty teams will be left in this season.
If the team is at the bottom, he can't even keep his seat.
How could they lift the level?
So...
Tonight, either Jia Shi or Thunderbolt
will be relegated.
Yes. The relegated team
will naturally
participate in the challenge of the next season.
Challenge. That is what we are going to participate.
Achieve the champion of the challenge is the only way
for the relegated team to come back to the league.
So...
The team which will be relegated tonight
will become our rival.
It's just a matter of time.
Even if we don't meet in the challenge,
we will still encounter each other in the league.
No matter which of them,
It will become our future rival.
He is indeed worth of being called Rookie.
Take away HOP of Thunderbolt.
Thunderbolt will lose if this continues.
Thunderbolt is in danger.
Jia Shi has had the game under control.
At this critical point, Sun Xiang stands out.
It's time to end.
I still can't tolerate
Sun Xiang's arrogance.
It's not good for us if Jia Shi loses the game.
Nonsense.
I hope Jia Shi will lose.
And go bankrupt right now.
According to the data,
Thunderbolt's capacity is far lower than Jia Shi's.
It's not surprising that they will lose.
If we can choose a team
as our rival,
I prefer Thunderbolt.
Thunderbolt is retreating.
Jia Shi is still chasing them. They don't want the substitution
To join the main strength of Thunderbolt.
Hi Fan, if you are Thunderbolt,
What will you do in such an unfavorable situation?
I will conserve my strength.
Wait for the chance.
Thunderbolt is running out of the time.
You have to create the chances for yourself.
Captain, you mean taking the initiative,
Containing their main force.
But that's too risky.
You are coming out yourself.
Then I don't need to chase you.
Sheng Lingmie.
He is
Xiao Shiqin, the captain of Thunderbolt.
He leads Thunderbolt, a weak team
gradually into the league.
He is the core of all the tactics of Thunderbolt.
Apart from the tactics,
even in the mental aspect,
he is absolutely the leader of Thunderbolt.
Dragon soaring. Does Sun Xiang want to expand his advantage?
Wonderful.
That's the end.
Dragon soaring begins the bonus.
It seems he will use Dragon Head Rising.
You mean Sun Xiang will use Dragon Heads Rising?
Dragon Head Rising.
Sun Xiang should use the unique skill of Ye Qiu.
What's going on?
He should escape the Dragon Head Rising.
Sheng Lingmie uses the step-back of the mechanical punch,
Escaping the damage of
Dragon soaring immediately.
What the hell is that?
Just now, we saw that
Sun Xiang used Dragon Head Rising.
But it's also the first time we saw that
Someone could break the Dragon Head Rising.
The captain of Thunderbolt.
He should break Dragon Head Rising.
How could that be possible?
Nothing is impossible.
Dragon Head Rising is not unbreakable.
You have known the solution.
This skill from the beginning to the end
constitutes seventy eight frames.
The only flaw
Is hidden in the forty-second frame.
This is unavoidable when the player uses it.
It's hard to find it.
I guess he watched the playback
for thousands of times.
And finally found this solution.
This is really his style.
Leaf of Autumn is in danger.
It takes too long to end Dragon Soaring.
Find one in about seventy frames.
His sight is too good.
It's his effort, not his sight.
This guy is too frightening.
Any skill
is meaningful only when it is used at the right time.
Otherwise,
it will become the flaw.
This time, Sun Xiang
suffers from showing his virtuosity.
Lumbricus Tactic.
From now on, fight back with all forces.
We see that Thunderbolt begins to fight back at once.
Lay siege to Leaf of Autumn.
Xiao Shiqin of Thunderbolt
Is famous for overcoming the stronger rivals.
Once he finds the flaw,
he won't let it go.
If Sun Xiang didn't use Dragon Head Rising just now,
maybe Thunderbolt would have lost the game.
Pitifully, there is no "if" in the competition.
The result has come out.
Jia Shi is in danger.
The time is running out.
Make it.
Thunderbolt successfully takes Leaf of Autumn away.
Meanwhile, team HP of Thunderbolt is higher than that of Jia Shi.
Time is up. Game over.
Thunderbolt keeps its seat.
That's splendid.
We have witnessed the history again.
Thunderbolt achieved its comeback in the desperate situation.
At the last moment, they won the game.
It's Thunderbolt that keeps its seat in the league.
Jia Shi is relegated.
So we will...
Congratulations to Thunderbolt again.
They achieve the final victory.
We also feel very pitiful to
Jia Shi, the great team in the past.
We won.
They are relegated from the league.
They will begin from the challenge
in the next season.
We also thank our audience
for your support.
We will see you again at the ninth pro-league.
Bye bye.
We won. We won.
The cooperation was great just now.
Great.
Not bad. Not bad.
Come and have a rest.
Well done.
Captain, where do we go to celebrate tonight?
I won't go tonight.
I know, among all the teams in the league,
as for which is the most diligent,
if Thunderbolt ranks second,
then there will be no team ranking first.
Tonight,
we must open a summing-up meeting,
celebrating it later.
What's going on?
The...
Since today,
I won't be your captain.
What?
Captain, this joke is not funny.
What's going on?
This is the tactics of all teams in the league
and coping strategies
that I have summarized for years.
You will use them in the future.
I also add notes to
all the tactics
You can refer to it.
After I leave,
the new captain will appear among you.
Please work hard, everyone.
Captain, captain.
What do you mean?
You want to transfer and leave Thunderbolt.
Captain. Captain.
Come out, Sun Xiang.
Members of Jia Shi,
pleas leave the competition room as soon as possible.
Come out. Come out.
What are you doing? They are fans.
You will be scolded to death.
We lost the game.
Someone has to account for this.
Then who?
It's not that simple that
we just lost the game today.
It's relegation.
Then who should be blamed?
We just followed the tactics
that has been arranged.
Now, Jia Shi believes in individualism.
Powerless people like us,
can't deicide the game
no matter we played well or not.
Today,
someone insisted on using Dragon Head Rising.
Is he ashamed ?
Enough. If you continue to
pass the buck,
suit yourself. I won't join you.
My Cheng, we don't mean that.
We just don't want to lose the game with no clear reasons.
Shut up.
Come out. Come out.
I am the captain.
I will be held accountable for this.
You think you bear all the responsibility and that's enough?
Jia Shi is relegated.
No one is innocent.
We lost the game.
We all have our own responsibility.
Including myself .
Come out. Come out.
Please calm down.
How did you play?
Su Mucheng,
The record of Jia Shi was always very stable before.
Why could it be relegated this time?
What does it have to do with the captain, Sun Xiang?
Can you explain this?
Can you explain, Su Mucheng?
Whether there is some problems?
Does the retirement of Ye Qiu
have a great influence on Jia Shi?
Order, please.
Please calm down guys.
Please calm down, guys.
This is not your fault.
You are not the captain.
Su Mucheng, don't leave.
Su Mucheng, why?
Mu Cheng. Mu Cheng. Su Mucheng.
Don't.
We don't blame you. Su Mucheng.
Mu Cheng, don't leave.
Don't leave, Mu Cheng.
Mu Cheng.
Today's performance was so good. Yes.
Jia Shi was too terrible today.
Yes.
Great.
I take you to a familiar place.
What do you want?
A cup of coffee.
OK.
Thank you.
This is the familiar place?
But we never come here before.
Really?
You think I don't have enough of the game today?
You don't dare to come?
Let me clarify,
I am furious right now.
I won't be softhearted.
This map?
You do remember it.
Of course. How could I forget it?
I don't lie to you. This is the familiar place.
I still remember
my brother created this map.
And here, I played Glory for the first time.
# You'll share with me a bowl of instant noodles #
Right. Move.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Now use the cannonball of flotation.
Throw the grenade and meanwhile change your gun.
This way. This way.
He is hiding here. OK.
That's so cruel, Ye Xiu.
You such a despicable person.
Don't misguide my little sister.
Su Muqiu,
really?
You design this map,
and now have stayed there for a while.
Shoot him. Shoot him.
You will pay for it.
I am telling you.
OK.
Send that bomb back.
# the private detective, #
# You see through every action and expression, #
Why I can't move?
I am asking you, why she can't move?
Is there any bug here?
Dammit. I have revised this map several times.
Why there is still bugs?
Entrap your own sister.
Right, Mu Cheng?
Every programmer makes progress
by fixing his bugs.
Failure is the ladder upwards success.
Right?
What ladder? Look at it yourself.
It should be called the desperate black hole.
# it's the eternal support in my heart. #
It should be here.
It has been so many years.
That bug is the only flaw
of my brother.
Now, it should have been fixed, right?
Who knows? Let's have a contest?
OK. My force is quite strong right now.
Be careful.
Do you still remember how I taught you
to handle your brother?
How dare you talk about it!
After that game,
my brother forbade me from playing Glory.
He was afraid that you would mislead me.
I misled you?
You have been self-taught.
I am stuck. The bug is still here.
Let me have a look.
Where is this?
Go down there and we'll find out.
In the past six months,
I have never given up,
although many things have happened.
Even without you by my side,
I realize that I need to rely on myself.
So I work harder than before.
But Jia Shi is
still relegated.
More desperately,
It's not the relegation itself.
Instead, no matter how harder I tried,
Jia Shi nowadays made me
feel powerless.
How to choose the future path of the following year,
I am quite confused.
We are going downhill.
As for the future path,
I don't know where to go.
Then focus on the path you're walking on right now.
Ain't I going downhill?
Actually, at many moments of life,
It's like this stairs.
You think you are going downhill.
As long as you keep going,
when you turn around,
you will find that you've stood in a higher place.
There is no absolute boundary between winning and losing.
As long as you keep going forward,
the nadir could be a high spot.
Our world is never a straight path.
There are ups and downs,
winning and losing,
and no end.
The bug at that time
has been fix by Mu Qiu.
And he left a bonus.
It is what you are seeing now.
Penrose stairs.
It still doesn't have a name.
You pick a name for it?
Then the name is
Path of Glory.
Your taste of naming has improved.
At least, it's better than Leaf of Autumn.
Your ice cream.
Thank you.
Xing Xin and Jia Shi.
They will definitely meet in the Challenge.
Then
Welcome to become my rival.
Almost all the top players live in this floor.
This is Shen Jian's room.
Next lives Zhang Jiaxing.
Sun Xiang lives there.
This is Ye Qiu's room.
One two three four.
I set the password.
It's very simple.
In case that he will sleep in the hallway at night.
Come in.
His room
belongs to me now.
Welcome our old friend to live here.
I never think we will be in one team.
By the way, this board
maybe a little loose.
The table leg is not stable.
Especially this curtain.
Don't pull it.
Otherwise, it will be worse.
Why not
fixing them?
Maybe don't know how to fix them.
It was a good place.
But with time going by,
some small problems gradually occur.
Just like this room.
After it is empty for long,
it becomes a hollow room with nobody living here.
Right?
So here I come.
The Jia Shi that remains to be fixed needs me.
You're right.
Actually, the curtain only needs to change a hook.
The table legs need to screw it up.
But the board has been totally broken.
I don't know how to fix it.
Fix it if possible.
Otherwise, replace it with a new one.
Replace?
Qiao Shiqin, you are such
a cruel guy.
You just came here.
And have thought about cleaning up.
Don't misunderstand me.
I don't misunderstand you.
But as the old saying goes,
one nation can't have two queens.
Say away. Whether you are here to
help Mr. Tao transfer the power of Sun Xiang?
Enough. Don't try to pull it out of me.
I'm not here to transfer anyone's power.
I'm here to change the broken Jia Shi
into a new look.
How to change it ?
Just like you said,
change a screw.
OK. Thank you.
It's all right.
Give it to me.
No drinking during the competition.
This is the regulation.
Since you have taken a horn,
why not enjoying yourself to the full?
Have another drink.
The same with his. With spherical ice.
Here.
Add ice to dilute it. Crowd.
The ice represses the light element in the alcohol,
while the wild and strong element
will stand out.
Sometimes,
it can reach the result that one plus one is more than two.
I'm the unique one.
I don't need to cooperate with anyone.
Of course not.
When genius players like you cooperate with others,
It's more favorable for others.
It's not fair.