= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 14 =
= Glory =
Did you try your best this time?
I spare no efforts in each competition.
Are you really going to give up like this?
Giving up does not mean admitting defeat.
Fine
Don't be a deserter then.
see you in the All-star Game next year.
Dragon Head Raising! Dragon Head Raising!
After you bottom out, you'll definitely rebound.
Never ever give up.
= Huang Shaotian =
= Han Wenqing =
= Game to Win =
= Su Cheng Huang Shaotian=
Master Ye Qiu!
- Master! - Master Ye Qiu!
Where is Master Ye Qiu?
- Tell us! - Where is he?
Just now...
He left.
Hurry up!
Each time I leave unwillingly,
what I expect is...
...the final return.
= Glory All-star Game =
Ye Qiu is back!
= Name: Ye Xiu Gender: Male =
Ye Xiu.
Your name sounds like the master's.
Know about the computer management?
No.
What do you know about?
I know about...
...how to play Glory.
I'm the one who's been with Ye Qiu in his entire Glory career.
Since the replacement failed, why did you do it?
Exactly. Why?
Ye Qiu could do it.
Why replaced him with Sun Xiang?
Why?
The answer is:
he decided to retire and replace him with Sun Xiang.
= Ye Qiu has retired. =
Those were his own decisions.
A glass has turned into a vase.
I start over on a new path.
Ye Xiu... Ye Qiu...
= Jia Shi Team Leaf of Autumn =
# You're the most amazing person in my heart. #
He really is Ye Qiu.
# Some of the days when we were together #
# fleeted in the blink of an eye, #
# while some of them were slowing down. #
# You're the dearest person in my heart. #
He really has come back.
Whether he is Ye Xiu or Ye Qiu...
It doesn't matter.
Whether he never left or he has returned,
there is no difference.
The most important is he has always been with you.
Didn't expect Ye Qiu would come back.
He's as good as he was.
- That's a 10-game win streak. - Exactly.
Our nemesis has come back.
Go on the PK.
= Glory All-star Game =
No one is scared.
See you next year.
= Glory All-star Game =
Tang.
What's up?
Guoguo, what are you doing...
I'll throw away everything from the past.
And then walk with the master to the peak.
Now we'll call ourselves "Jun Moxiao".
Then what is your plan to walk on the path to the peak?
Go back to the hotel now.
I'll get to know the master all over again.
Why don't you stay inside to enjoy the cheer for longer?
It's cold outside.
I'm worried you might catch cold.
Who said I was here to wait for you?
I'm here to see...
how you will thank me for the three tickets.
You gave me three tickets as a gift.
What do you want in return?
Same as usual .
But it's still cold.
It's the best.
I can eat slowly.
It won't melt rapidly.
Hi!
I'll have this one, this one, and this one.
= Ice Cream =
Boss.
One more thing.
= Ice Cream =
= Fresh Fruits =
Wait...
Why are you dressing like Brown Bear?
The shop assistant had to go.
She asked me to help her for a while.
A 5-minute part time job.
Thanks for coming.
Balloons are only for kids.
What about ice cream?
Ice cream is for me to heal myself.
Have a bite, please.
New life experience from your first bite of ice cream.
Run!
Running away like this after causing trouble?
Or what?
See?
Feeling good after doing something bad?
You feeling good?
I had bought all of the balloons.
Why did you buy the balloons and tease me?
I told you.
Balloons are only for kids.
Feeling good after teasing me?
You... Why you still keep the ice cream?
You want it?
If you don't want it, I'll eat it.
Come get it!
Come on!
Stop!
Guoguo, what are you doing?
The master has been in his room for a long time.
What is he doing?
If you wanna find out, go knock on his door.
It's not proper.
The boss visiting her employee.
Nothing improper.
Go.
Sounds plausible.
I'm going.
- From today, you'll do the network management. - OK.
You'll do the cleaning.
And hard labor? You'll do it, too.
Meals and accommodation are included.
But I won't pay you any money.
No money...
I was way too mean.
He's the master.
How can I just treat him like trash?
I even criticized him for he couldn't change the light bulb.
I thought he was a loser.
How could he be a loser?
Look how cute he is!
Will I never meet Ye Qiu again?
You're not eligible to say so.
The master was right.
I'm not eligible to say so.
I was closely associated with him for so long.
He cared about me so much.
But I didn't know anything.
Tang, do you think it's my blessing?
I don't think it's blessing.
It's revenge.
It's the revenge for your ignorance
when the master was there but you knew nothing.
- Boss. - Yes?
You picked a very good poster.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
It's unique and incisive.
The cardboard cut-out is great, too.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Even taller than Ye Qiu himself.
The garage kit video is amazing.
Why not be more thorough?
Let's change the password of the network.
How about "Ye Qiu is the most handsome and invincible"?
"Ye Qiu is the most handsome and invincible."
That sounds great.
I feel my net cafe has been upgraded so much.
You should have known I was using a rhetorical device.
It is called "irony".
It's "irony". The master is satirizing me.
Why would I always push him so hard?
I was baring my heart as a fan while scolding him as a boss.
Look how quickly I switched my mode!
Tang, what should I do?
What if the master leaves?
What if he doesn't leave today but departs tomorrow?
What if it's not tomorrow but the day after tomorrow?
Turn right. The second room.
Go inside and "kidnap" him now.
Or wait for him quietly at his door until he's touched.
Wait.
"Kidnapping" isn't a good option.
It'd made me look crude.
But waiting isn't a good option, either.
It'd make me look stupid.
Then what do you want?
I heard some noise.
He's throwing things.
Is he mad?
He just closed the closet.
He's coming.
Boss.
What are you doing?
Boss, move aside, please.
You are in my way.
This way, please.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Really?
Did he just smile at me?
- Did he? - Yes.
And the smile was creepy.
Is he going to part ways with me?
I may look domineering at work, but I don't mean it.
Tang! Tang!
Come back!
Tang!
Don't.
Need anything?
Could be something or nothing.
Depends on what you'll say.
Could say something or nothing.
Depends on what you'll ask.
Want something to drink?
Anything.
Then, tea.
Dragon Head Raising is so amazing.
Why is it not in the strategy guide you gave me?
If it's not there, you'll never learn about it?
I'm not saying it.
I can always steal from others.
To steal?
You'd value skills that are stolen.
Right?
So...
You'd value a name that is stolen, right?
I'd value my salary more.
Please ask the boss when the payday will be.
Didn't Guoguo tell you?
She never pays the salary each month.
It's a 10-year contract.
Salaries are paid every other 6 months.
It's a contract of selling myself.
Wanna breach it?
That contract means...
I could never leave even if I wanted to.
Have a good rest.
Did you hear everything?
Go to bed.
"He could never leave even if he wanted to."
What does it mean?
Did he mean he wanted to go?
Or he couldn't leave?
Wait.
Would he leave or not?
Put it here.
Guoguo.
What is your plan?
Holding his luggage equals to holding him in my hands.
- Beauty. - Yes?
Well, it's my seat.
- We're friends. We're just chatting. - Friends?
- Yes. - It's OK. Take my seat.
- I'm sorry. - It's OK.
Handsome, you look kinda familiar.
Do I know you?
Now I remember.
You look like someone who is playing eSports.
Really?
People say it often.
See?
Handsome, we're done chatting.
Wait a sec. You are Trou...
You can go back to your own seat.
Troubling Rain.
Exactly.
Am I right?
He does look like him.
He does.
If I didn't remember it wrong, one month has passed
since Master Ye Qiu announced his retirement.
Lots of fans are very curious about
what the master has been doing during the entire month.
If I were him, after the seven-year career of Glory,
competing in the field for such a long time,
I would take a long vacation.
Yes.
Going to a remote island, enjoying the sunshine and the beach.
- And enjoying sea waves and views. - Boss.
- The sunshine and the beach... - Boss.
- ...On the past weekend... - That's my seat belt.
Master Ye Qiu has a unique skill: "Dragon Head Raising".
It's something that many people don't expect.
Yes. We want to hear what players in other teams would say.
No comment.
Our captain means we don't know what's going on with Ye Qiu.
= All-star Game =
But if he wants to come back to the league,
we'll definitely support him.
= All-star Game =
In my opinion...
We don't know what's going on with Jia Shi and Ye Qiu.
= All-star Game =
But as his friends,
we believe there must be some reason behind what he's done.
Every profession has its best skill.
The key is the person who's performing it.
Xiao Luo, on the weekend of All-star Game,
you were invited to be the live host.
Any inside information you can share with us?
Actually, nope. I was very surprised, too.
The Samsara Team planned to invite Master Ye Qiu as our VIP
to attend the live event.
But after the master retired,
all his contact info didn't work anymore.
We couldn't reach him and invite him to join us.
But I have a concern.
Why did Mater Ye Qiu announce his retirement suddenly?
Back then, Jia Shi announced the reason why Ye Qiu retired.
It was because his mental status was decreasing.
So he decided to stay behind the scenes.
Since he still could perform "Dragon Head Raising",
the "decreased mental status" seems not true.
What you just said sent a chill down my spine.
We know nothing about any inside info.
But what I do know is:
no one in media has an access to interviewing anyone in Jia Shi.
What's going on?
Let's wait for more first-hand information.
That's bullshit.
A chill down his spine?
It's a chill in my heart.
One minute Jia Shi kicked Master Ye Qiu out,
the next minute they replaced him with the rookie Sun Xiang.
What the heck?
Sun Xiang is quite competitive.
- After all... - Wait, wait...
Was that just a total coincidence?
A rookie replaced him like that.
Jia Shi must be calculating everything covertly.
Earlier on he didn't perform well in Yue Yun Team.
Going to Jia Shi will bring him a promising future.
Damn! A new talent?
No matter how competitive he is, he's at most a rookie.
How could he ever compare to Mater Ye Qiu?
You saw that, too.
He logged in Mater Ye Qiu's account.
Could he handle it?
He was defeated by Smoke Alone.
Right?
- You are new, right? - Yes.
- Just starting interviewing? - Yes.
When you are in this for long enough, you would know.
Rookies are laughing while retirees are weeping.
The laws of nature.
I only believe in my master.
Keep doing that.
Look! Look!
They are back!
Hurry up! Follow them!
I'll protect the master!
You! Hurry up!
Don't come closer!
He's not the master they were waiting for.
= Adults only. =
Guoguo.
You were going too far.
= Adults only. =
- What happened? - Who knows?
Boss.
You ruined my hair.
Chu.
= Adults only. =
You did a good job.
Mr. Tao! Mr. Tao!
Please open the window! Please!
Mr. Tao!
Why could Ye Qiu perform Dragon Head Raising at All-star Game yesterday?
You were saying his mental status decreased.
But if it was not the story, why did he retire?
Captain Sun, as the account owner of Leaf of Autumn,
you don't have the skill of Dragon Head Raising.
Do you think you are under-qualified?
Captain Sun, any explanation?
Captain Sun, you...
Who asked the question? Step up!
Shut up!
Watch out!
Thanks for your attention.
We'll hold a press conference soon.
All of you are welcome to come.
Thank you. Thank you.
Drive.
Don't go. Answer the question.
Boss, do you still need the exercise book on the front desk?
Is it so scary?
Dragon Head Raising!
Han Yanrou successfully performed
Master Ye Qiu's unique skill "Dragon Head Raising"!
The appearance of "Dragon Head Raising" has caused a sensation.
Players in other teams say they'll support Ye Qiu to come back.
The "Dragon Head Raising" event keeps heating up.
Today, lots of media flooded into Jia Shi Building.
See?
All the media are focusing on Jia Shi.
After your three successive championships,
you haven't seen such a big crowd.
You don't have to worry about the media.
I have sent someone from the public relations arena.
The reporters waiting at the gate won't stay for long.
Once the press conference is held, everything will go away soon.
Don't tell me you knew nothing about Ye Qiu showing up at All-star.
Ye Qiu...
He didn't show up at All-star.
Really?
So what the media said was fake news?
It could be true.
It could be fake.
Ye Qiu has never showed up in public.
No media took a single photo of him this time.
No one has ever seen who performed Dragon Head Raising.
So if we say it was not Ye Qiu, it's not hard to believe.
Mr. Tao, you're really something.
Being so calm when deceiving others as well as yourself.
It's Dragon Head Raising.
Only Ye Qiu can perform it.
The fans are not blind.
About all this,
you don't have to worry.
Just spend more money.
When the PR works,
I'll send someone to lubricate relations with fans.
Things are going to be different soon.
= Jia Shi Guild Report =
I care nothing about the media or the fans.
What I'm expecting is a good market valuation of Jia Shi.
It could make it possible for the next round of financing.
Mr. Tao, we are both clear eSports is just business.
I've invested in it because I can see its commercial prospect.
But a month ago,
the market valuation went down to the bottom of two years.
You said the key was to find a new talent.
You named Sun Xiang. Fine.
What now?
No improvement in market valuation.
Instead, Jia Shi has ruined its reputation.
Sun Xiang has more commercial value than Ye Qiu.
You and I both know it clearly.
They are just having a run-in period.
We need to be patient.
I'll try my best to deal with this emergency.
Hoping for a smooth transition.
Don't worry.
Jia Shi will bounce back soon.
Mr. Tao.
I hope you are not making empty promises.
Show me something real.
Or... With all the opportunities in the market,
I still could weigh my options.
Ye Qiu is really something.
Think about Dragon Head Raising.
Really interesting.
A single move of Dragon Soaring.
If you missed, you could reverse it.
Making a bad move doesn't matter.
A timely remedy would be good.
So in my eyes,
whether it's Dragon Head "Raising" or "Lowering",
it'll be a good move if you win.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Boss, something wrong with the computer.
Go fix it.
- Boss. - Chu.
Chu, what's wrong with the computer?
Did you check it?
Boss.
The jacket needs washing.
Why is Guoguo avoiding you as she's avoiding virus?
I'd say she's encountered a big problem.
What's wrong?
She's being socially awkward.
For that reason,
we have to take "drastic" measures.
= The Best Net Cafe =
Director Cao, listen to me.
Though I didn't take any pictures of Sun Xiang,
I did get inside info.
Master Ye Qiu had left Jia Shi the day before the press conference.
Something fishy going on here.
Sun Xiang is just a small potato.
Who really matters is Master Ye Qiu.
Don't ... Director...
Why are you taking Jia Shi's side suddenly?
I'm not splitting hairs.
You've told us:
"News reporting must be true, objective and fair."
That's what I've been doing.
What about this?
Director, grant me some business trip fund.
I'll wait at Jia Shi's gate.
And I'll find Master Ye Qiu.
Then we can interview him.
Hello... Hello...
What?
Hung up on me again?
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Master Ye Qiu, where are you?
It's near Jia Shi. What if...
Hey, manager. Nice mask!
Is it? Thank you!
May I know your last name?
Ye.
Exactly!
Why?
To tell you the truth,
I... I'm a reporter.
May I ask you a few questions?
I have nothing to say.
People say you have the same style as Ye Qiu.
My boss says so.
How do you view Ye Qiu?
He's my boss' idol.
Do you know about Dragon Head Raising?
My boss does.
Why do you keep talking your boss?
Because I'm just the network manager.
If you want to interview me, you need to get her consent.
Where is your boss?
Sleeping on the second floor.
Thank you.
Boss, time to get up.
Boss.
I'll sleep more. Don't disturb me.
Boss. Boss.
What are you doing?
Boss, congrats!
Xing Xin Net Cafe will rise to fame soon.
Don't press me with your big belly.
Sure.
What the heck?
Boss, the day when the 10th district of Glory opened,
I was attacking Night Evil Cat right here.
Everything was fine just now.
Turn over the screen.
Fixed.
You're in the same trade?
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
A bottle of water, please.
I'll get it for you.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Do you make good money in your net cafe?
Is it recruiting?
I'm not in the same trade with you!
Was the day when Manager Ye first started working here?
Yes.
Exactly right!
What are you talking about?
I have an assumption.
Manager Ye could be Mater Ye Qiu.
How is it possible?
Listen to me.
According to my investigation,
the day when the 10th district of Glory opened,
Master Ye Qiu left Jia Shi.
Think about it.
When he left Jia Shi,
the master looked around.
He had nowhere to go.
So he crossed the street,
and walked in your net cafe.
He ended up being your network manager.
You're checking out?
I'm here for the job.
= Want Ad =
It's impossible.
Surprised?
I am, too.
But at one moment just now, it suddenly dawned on me.
My assumption is perfect.
How is it perfect?
Wait. Think about it.
The "lesser hermit" lives in seclusion in the country,
while the "greater hermit" does so in the city.
But unexpectedly, the master has been hidden here!
He seems to tell all:
"Look. I'll be back again.
I'm right here."
You're just hallucinating!
It's impossible.
But I do think what I said is quite plausible. Right?
You're Ye Qiu's fan, right?
I can tell it from what you do with the decorations here.
Think about it.
Look, our idol is in front of us.
Nobody else knows about it except for you and me.
Now we're kinda on the same boat.
Wait here. I'll do more investigation about him.
Don't stop me.
No way!
What?
He isn't Ye Qiu.
Look at him.
He is mean and clumsy.
He knows nothing about handling things or casting accounts.
How could he be Ye Qiu?
Right?
Really?
Yes.
If it's true, why are you willing to keep him here?
None of your business.
Do you have an agenda?
Nope.
You know it's him.
So you want to keep him here.
False.
You kidnapped, threatened and house-arrested him.
Not true.
Then let me investigate him.
Thank you.
Stop!
Bro!
Bro! Bro!
Your boss gave me the consent.
I didn't!
You did!
Bro, are you doing well here?
I...
Meals, accommodation and network are included.
He's doing very well.
Yes. My boss is right.
It's my dream job.
Bro!
Are you still doing the training regularly?
Cleaning tables, moving chairs and fixing computers.
He's doing the training every day.
- Is that right? - Yes.
I'm the best network manager.
Do you still play Glory?
In which district?
Are you performing amazingly?
A rookie in District 10.
Just as a pastime.
- Amateur. - Yes.
Very amateur.
You are in District 10, too.
What is your user name?
Are you in any guild?
That's something private.
Bro!
Boss! Boss!
It's stuck. Come fix it!
I'm Yue Zhongmian, the master of Yue Lun Guild.
It's you!
Bro, you've heard about me?
I was on the Record List!
No big deal.
You were on the Record List?
You are amazing!
Not bad.
I'm a veteran in three districts.
Making some record is no big deal.
Wasn't it because someone helped you?
That's true.
But it's not important.
Bro, what profession do you have in Glory?
The battlemage?
I'm...
- Done. Sorry for that. - Thanks!
... the Freelancer.
What? The Freelancer?
What is it?
Stop it, Little Moon.
Little... Moon...
Are you Jun...
Your benefactor.
Jun Moxiao.
I've told you.
It's not him.
It's impossible!
It's not possible at all.
Sorry. I have things to do.
I need to go.
You think about it thoroughly.
- He's definitely not Leaf of Autumn! - He's gone.
Don't you ever expose your identity easily.
You are finally talking to me.
Boss.
Talking about what?
Go on working!
Due to our internal inspection,
= Termination Notice =
we'll close the net cafe from today.
If there is any inconvenience...
= Termination Notice =
Do whatever as you see fit.
Guoguo.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Why were you walking without any sound?
The net cafe will close suddenly.
What happened?
I'm worried something bad would happen.
Have you seen the reporter coming and going every day?
If he did the same again, what should we do?
The master would expose his identity.
If he did so,
he could not stay here anymore.
If he couldn't stay here, where would he go?
He'd be homeless.
No way.
I must keep him here.
I'd rather close the net cafe.
Closing it?
But have you ever thought if you closed it,
the reporter would be more suspicious.
Right?
Yes.
- I'd make a confession without duress. - Exactly!
Canceled your plan?
Where is it?
What are you looking for?
If I can't prevent others coming in,
I need to make changes inside.
How many locks should I put on the attic?
What? Locks?
Or...
I could demolish the stairs up there.
He's indoorsy.
There should be no problem if he was up there for over 10 days.
Wait, Guoguo.
That's outrageous.
I'll deliver him his computer.
In his entire world, Glory is more than enough.
As long as he didn't show up, the reporter would never know.
Perfect.
How is it perfect?
Even though the reporter didn't come, the police would.
Seems nothing would work.
What should I do?
I'm running out options.
Guoguo.
If you really wanna keep him here,
it's not very complicated.
How should I do it?
You're not suggesting I break his legs?
It could be one option.
He would only need his hands.
Of course not.
What the heck are you thinking?
I mean...
If you want to keep someone, win his heart first.
How?
Two words.
Spoil him.
Spoil him?