= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 9 =
Team 2, firearms and thermal missiles.
Team 2 roger that.
Battlemage in Team 1, flame strike.
Retreat to Kongji City.
Another one coming to be beaten.
Missed it.
Watch out!
Be calm. Steady your hands.
Give up the array of ice. Ghost-chop first.
Then moon-slash. Attack immediately.
Don't panic even if you missed.
The more urgent the situation is,
the more you can improve your mindset and judgment.
Gotcha, my senior.
Assist with the array of knives.
Ghost array.
Wait for the perfect timing.
The same coordinate. Double the ghost array.
Gotcha, my senior.
Boss, those who attack the same dungeon in Team 3 are back.
Do we need to back up?
Nope.
Just some preparation. Testing the water.
Made it!
Yifan,
your array ghost kicked ass!
We should compare notes sometime.
How should I do it?
= Glory =
# The road to the top is rough and long. #
# But walking with you, I will have infinite power. #
The test is over.
Let's go back.
- OK. - OK.
Let's go.
Talk later.
# Youth is a forever indomitable growth. #
# We are accompanied by confidence and strength. #
# Even if we flinch and bruise all over our body, #
Just now,
I gained a complete victory.
I finished the most important test of my entire life.
# We must do our best to win a battle. #
You should improve all the skills of the array ghost.
You need to remember everything and practice.
Your reaction and judgment are not good enough.
More combat experience will help.
Your mentality is not professional enough.
Your emotion would control you.
When you missed, you'd panic.
When it comes to the situation,
thinking calmly and making supplement would avoid bigger mistakes.
You are going to change your fate,
not to give it up.
No one should ever give up easily.
Thank you, my senior.
You help me find the true self I love
in the world of Glory.
My future path...
is coming soon.
# To fight for our dream, we should win beautifully enough. #
# We are hugging, cheering, and ecstatic with joy for our victory. #
# And we spent countless shining times. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# We spent countless shining times. #
Bro, I don't beat about the bush.
Cut the chase.
Don't make any dungeon record for any other guild
except for our Ambitions Guild.
You wanna buy out?
Then you should get your cash ready.
You want to overcharge me again?
Fine. How much?
The cup is empty.
- Need me to get more water for you? - I'll do it.
You go ahead. Continue.
I'm done. I'll go get water.
The bell of #56 in District B keeps ringing and going to blast.
Would you go check?
Is it blasting?
Or is it broken?
I didn't hear anything.
Let me check.
Boss, the light...
Stop pretending.
Go get water.
Tang, what are you doing?
Have you finished your homework?
I'm on it. Still on it.
You should hurry up.
A bottle of water, please.
Thanks.
Everything is going down.
Our Yue Lun Guild is doomed.
Moon, come up something to fix it!
What should I do?
A small guild like ours,
doesn't have any master-hand.
Going down is just the normalcy.
Could you ask Master-hand to help us?
You have some personal friendship with him.
He might be willing to help.
You sure it's friendship, not grievance?
Moon,
it's about our guild, not about losing face.
You think about it.
Could you do me a favor?
Well... How have you been lately?
It's too fake.
Jun Moxiao,
have you ever heard about our Yue Lun Guild?
Actually...
I... am really embarrassed...
No... No...
Though my temperament is extraordinary,
you don't need to be so humble.
Big bro...
Say out loud.
What?
Big bro...
Go get water for me!
Stand up!
Go get water!
Big bro...
Go that way.
Please do me a favor.
I'm in Kongji City.
Come over.
Little Moon, are you showing off?
I need to apologize to you first.
Apologize?
Actually... In Green Forest,
when we first randomly team up,
I had an agenda.
I wanted all of you to be my human shields,
being killed by Night Evil Cat.
Then I could possess all the materials.
But later...
My plan fell apart.
So I broadcast in the "world",
and framed you in the "world".
Now I feel I was so childish.
Later I led you into the Spider Cave,
all I wanted was to trap you.
But I overestimated myself.
You, all by yourself,
could easily defeat a number of us.
At last,
it was you who led us to defeat the hidden boss.
And you gave me the last sword.
Why are you confessing?
I don't get it.
So...
I want to apologize to you.
Forgive me, please.
Why don't you tell me what you're up to?
Actually I want to ask you a favor.
Could you make a dungeon for my Yue Lun Guild?
As what you did for Lanxi Pavilion and Ambitions.
Just one dungeon for us.
And go to the ranking list.
You're not done with the situation in Spider Cave?
What are your tricks this time?
It's not like what you think.
Master, I'll be honest with you.
My guild is collapsing.
I... I know you make money from dungeons.
I know how much it will cost.
My guild can't afford it with all that we have got.
But don't worry.
We'll pay you back with everything we get every day,
until we pay off.
Is it ok?
Please.
It's really shabby.
All the equipments are not as valuable as the one you have.
I didn't see it clearly.
You've got the Lance of the Purple Moon?
I'll take it.
You'll... only take one lance?
Reading the strategy?
Tang has been busy with the strategy, working very hard.
Why are you asking?
= "Strategy Guide of the Place of Exile Dungeon" =
You reading dungeon strategy guide?
We're about to attack the Place of Exile Dungeon.
Grinding the spear just before a battle?
I'm just reading.
Just reading.
The living Glory master will be the captain.
You just need to know about other strategies.
The living Glory master is my idol, Ye Qiu.
Don't you just take the credit.
Tang, who wrote this strategy?
The writer is Meiguang. Why?
It's perfect.
It includes all the probability events.
It even calculates the time for each step.
- To millisecond. - Let me have a look.
Tang.
Look at this guy. Very strange.
He wrote so much for a low-grade dungeon.
Who would have the patience to read through?
Reading it is hard for a loser.
Who is a loser?
Tang, he is bullying me.
Boss.
Keep going.
When will you deliver my paper and pen?
Him again!
In all my business years,
I have never seen anyone who always order paper and pen.
Tang, is he making this place as his study room?
The same as you.
You don't have anything to do?
Go deliver for him!
Tang, send me a copy of the strategy, please.
Tang...
It's great you work in the internet café.
It's my honor that you can tutor me.
Tang, could you help me with this?
I can't figure it out. Could you help me?
Please?
Tang.
I should have a shot.
Tang...
What about this?
Leave it there and keep doing your homework.
This is some test "strategy".
Tang...
I can't do it by myself.
The pen is running out of ink. Where is the delivery?
From the storage rack on the first floor to my door,
it only takes five minutes with the average human speed.
But it took you...
six minutes and twelve seconds.
Your paper.
The paper weight is not right.
The brand I want weighs 4.09 grams.
But this one weighs 4.06 grams.
The friction that generates with my pen will slow down my calculation.
- My pen. - What?
My pen...
Sorry.
Your pen.
Wait a sec.
It's not what I want.
What I ordered was cartridge 0.48, not 0.45.
You were late for 72 seconds.
And it took me 48 seconds to explain to you.
You wasted two minutes.
I could have do more calculations in these two minutes...
Take your time.
I won't stop you from your numerous affairs.
Numerous affairs? That's what webmasters do.
You hurry up.
I need it in a short time.
OK.
There's still time to look for your expert.
What expert?
I'm going to a meeting.
Why are you having the meeting?
To find the expert who has turned the world upside down
and left everything in a mess.
Xizhou, you can't say that.
The expert really has helped our Lanxi Pavilion Guild a lot.
He did his best to help us with the Place of Bones.
You think too much.
He took the materials.
We were even.
It's just a scheme, OK?
OK, gotcha.
I'm going to the meeting, Talk to you later.
Talk about what? Everything is clear.
You just can't live without the expert.
Now the world is in a mess.
Everything is bloody.
All the guilds suffered a great loss.
It's time to call a truce.
Let's have a peace talk.
Now you want a peace talk?
It was you, Zhong Caotang Guild, who started the fight.
It was Lanxi Pavilion who asked Jun Moxiao to substitute first.
Who was the substitute?
He was an official member of Lanxi Pavilion.
He was making the dungeon record as one of us.
He then left our guild later.
- I... - Bullshit!
He was one of you whenever he was substituting.
Laoye, watch your mouth.
Lan He, you Lanxi Pavilion killed my elite brigade.
What would you do?
Stop it!
Could we just stop killing each other?
Can't we play it fairly?
Without fighting with each other?
You are such a pacifist.
Congratulations to Players Jun Moxiao, Han Yanrou and
Bao Zi, the Invader,Yi Cunhui and Yue Zhongmian
= System Annoucement =
belonging to Yue Lun guild have created
a new record for the Place of Exile Dungeon.
Time used is 22''35.
Yue Lun guild?
Have any of you
heard of this guild?
How can this kind of shady guild
try to steal the thunder?
The Palce of Exile.
Oh, my!
They even broke
the record set by our guild.
Jun Moxiao.
You are certainly not a picky one.
Xi Zhou, how can he do that?
The only thing he wants is the materials.
As long as he gets what he wants, he can help anyone.
I thought he was one of us.
You never thought like that.
You only care about yourself.
Jun Moxiao
is cruel, as blind as a bat and
disregards moral principles in pursuit of profits.
He is hypocritical.
He fails on every criterion. He is up to no good.
Everyone who plays Glory should despise him.
From now on,
Jun Moxiao, you are officially
the arch-enemy of Lanxi Pavilion
Yeah, from now on,
he is our arch-enemy.
Think about it, everyone.
Before the opening of the 10th district,
has this kind of thing ever happened?
Ever since Jun Moxiao appears,
he has been stringing us alone
from the first kill to the copy records,
from fighting against each other for the final Boss
to our infighting.
Who do you think
is the final winner?
It's that Jun Moxiao.
It seems that way.
= Brother, you better keep it low-key. =
Brother, you better keep it low-key.
= Record of Dungeons =
= Participated Players =
= Increased by =
Thanks.
All you want is this lance?
In a shady guild like yours,
this is the only disguished weapon there is.
Such a waste.
He has releaved himself for he is immdiately.
= Player Almost Young Joins Yue Lun guild =
= Player Brother Fan Ren Joins Jun Lun guild =
Awsome. Awsome.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
The new weapon is really handy.
This orange weapon suits me the most.
Sisrer Tang Rou, what's wrong with you today?
You are quite slow.
You only have a suite. Without the organe weapon,
you can't defeat me.
You can fight on your own.
I'll go offline now.
= Killed 34 Emenies =
= Lance of the Purple Moon =
= Accept Decline =
You bought it?
It's a trophy.
You played through the Place of Exile and
the only thing you want is this?
It matches the weapon
I bought you the last time.
= Mysterious Record of 16''24 of the Place of Bones =
Isn't it our record?
Let me see.
It's so detailed.
The way to play pass each checkpoint is clearly marked.
The equipments of Bao Zi Invader with pictures.
It says all my equipments
are orange.
Underling, do you think we should
follow the steps posted
= Mysterious Record of 16''24 of the Place of Bones =
and then we can create a record of
16''24?
This guy is a genius.
Indeed.
He can reproduce the full method of passing a Dungeon
only according to the record time.
He is really good at this.
What a pity.
Why?
This method requires
players to have not only high-end equipments,
but also exquisite techniques.
Normal player simple can't reach this level.
In other words,
this so-call "Strategy for the Inexperience"
is not what it claims to be.
It's only a theory.
Then why we are wasting time on this?
It's useless.
We can just go and play the dungeon directly.
It is not useless.
It's posted by someone named Mei Guang.
At least, he has a high spirit of learning.
If someone points him into the right direction,
maybe he can come up with
a really decent strategy guide.
Network manager, turn on a computure please.
Let's go.
Please show your I.D. card.
= Seats on First Floor Seats on Second Floor =
= Disctrict A  Disctrict C =
It's really crowded today here.
The business is thriving.
Here you go. No.46 in District B
Thanks.
I'm sorry but
we need to split up today.
Yifan, you are No.42 in Disrtcit B
OK.
Bao Zi.
Go upstaires to District C.
OK.
Let's go.
Why are you online now?
Didn't you mention there is a team event?
Are you going to
One Canyon Dungeon today?
Bring me on.
You surely have a lot of time, lady.
You even play the Glory.
I am sick. I took a sick leave today.
What's wrong?
Have you gone to see a doctor?
I have sever insomnia.
I can't sleep during daytime.
The doctor said,
the more I play the Glory, the better.
The most important thing is to
keep myself happy.
All right.
= All right. We are gathering in Kongzhi Forest. =
We are gathering in Kongzhi Forest.
Roger.
We have gathered the elite member from
the seven largest guilds this time
in order to take down Jun Moxiao.
Zhong Caotang guild
wins the fifth place in the league match.
Wei Cao Team, champion of Season 7,
is strong and powerful.
The Ambitions carries on
the style developed by their captain, Han Wenqing.
They are tough and hard to defeat.
Players tremble with fear on hearing of their name.
Not to mention Blossom Valley guild, Samsara guild,
Howling Heights guild and Void Walk guild.
With the buff of each guild,
the strength will double in amount
Feng Liu Yan Mu is online.
Position 375 690.
He is online now.
Bao Zi, the Invader is online.
The big fish is coming.
= Praisage =
= Jia Shi =
Everyone, Jun Moxiao and his team
are very good and experienced.
= Jia Shi =
We need to work together.
Now, Feng Shu Yan Mu, Yi Cunhui
and Bao Zi, the Invader are
in different areas in Kongzhi Forest.
They can't gather in such a such time.
We can defeat them one by one.
All teams are ready to besiege.
Move.
Strangle them.
Go.
An ambush.
Watch out the surroundings.
I also meet four enemies.
But those rookies...
they are so lame.
Tang,
are you ok?
I am killed.
Tang, I already asked them to
assemble in the Kongzhi Forrest as planned.
you can go to the Congee City to respawn.
But hide for now,
save your strengthfor later.
Solemn has no one to use now.
Position (236, 985)
target, Solemn.
The game,
is not over.
Assemble in the Kongzhi Forrest.
Got it.
No problem.
Stop them from assembling.
Wait till they are
kill them one by one.
Roger that.
Concentrate fire
on Yi Cun Hui.
What? So many enemy!
Come on! Come and get me!
Come here. Here. Here.
Oh my! Lose him again!
Go get him! Chop chop!
What are you waiting for?
Our ATT is not enough
to break through the encirclement.
Senior, what should we do?
Hide.
Hit him hard!
Don't let any of them survive!
Have you met up Yifan?
Yes.
But there are too many enemies.
We can't break through the encirclement at all.
Let him use Flame Boundaries
to give you a buff.
Baozi is kind of close to you.
I will let him support you.
Roger that.
Baozi, how about you?
Boss, so many people are chasing me.
What should I do?
Run! Run! Run!
Find a way to escape.
Go.
What happened?
Where am I?
It's so dark.
Cap, we lost Bao Zi Invader.
He may find a blind spot to hide.
Let's scatter to search for him.
They can't see me.
Seems I found a good place.
Void Walk, remain on standby outside Congee City.
After respawning,
Han Yan Rou must head to the Congee City.
Killing is not allowed in the city.
Once they step out of the city, kill them immediately.
Roger that.
None of them can survive this time.
# Normal Spear #
# Congratulations on buying Normal Spear. It costs 70 coins. #
# Normal Spear equipped #
We lost Baozi.
Things get worse than we thought.
You stay at the Congee City now.
wait for the opportunity.
Praisage Dynasty,
get ready to encircle Solemn.
Why bother to be masked on the smurf?
To give you a surprse!
Are you happy? Are you happy?
Don't let any of them go.
Kill them all.
Go.
Oh my!
So many enemy!
Ye, did you stir up a hornet's nest?
You noobs
are really brave.
Again? Why?
Want a lesson?
Alright, I will teach you a lesson.
You are freaking done.
Ye, you heartless,
run without me?
Wait for me! Wait!
Now nobody is here.
Come clean, Ye.
What have you done?
Rob their equipments,
or steal someone's girlfriend?
Let me guess.
I guess Han got upset
about you retiring from Glory.
So he decided to come after you till you come back.
No?
Then don't tell me. don't.
Let me guess again.
Ah I see.
It must be like this!
Your plot
are revealed.
That's why everyone are chasing you. Am I right?
We just break the dugeon record.
You deserve it, Ye.
What's your level?
Compete with these newbies for the dugeon?
You are more and more shameless.
Why shameful?
I am just a common player.
It's my job.
But you, haven't experienced
such a huge battle for a long time.
Scared?
Are you kidding me? I am scared?
Who am I scared of?
Then why did you run?
I come here to PK you,
not for these noobs.
Alright, without further ado,
I am going to open the PK field.
I give you one minute,
to PK me. PK. PK. PK. PK.
Shh.
Under the tree, follow me.
Fire.
The road to the top is rough and long.
But walking with you, I will have infinite power.
Failure is like the dawn of victory.
So what if we start all over again?
Youth is a forever indomitable growth.
We are accompanied by confidence and strength.
Even if we flinch and bruise all over our body,
there will always be hope in despair.
This is the most glorious battlefield.
We must do our best to win a battle.
We laugh, we cry, we feel sad for failure.
We accompany each other to bloom in the transformation.
This is the most glorious battlefield.
To fight for our dream, we should win beautifully enough.
We are hugging, cheering, and ecstatic with joy for our victory.
We spent countless shining times.
This is the most glorious battlefield.
We must do our best to win a battle.
We laugh, we cry, we feel sad for failure.
We accompany each other to bloom in the transformation.
This is the most glorious battlefield.
To fight for our dream, we should win beautifully enough.
We are hugging, cheering, and ecstatic with joy for our victory.
And we spent countless shining times.
This is the most glorious battlefield.
We spent countless shining times.