= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 40 =
= 3 killing 4 =
It's time for the decisive battle.
Kill Combat Form first.
Cheer up, Tang.
Come on, Xing Xin. Come on.
Hold on.
Leave them to me.
No need to hold on.
Fight immediately.
Do you know what you are talking about?
Our goal is to win this Challenge.
Instead of just winning this competition.
Do you know that?
Tang,
Run.
Now Han Yanrou only has
ten percent of HP.
Cold Hands only has
thirty percent of HP.
He hit them.
But Combat Form releases Destroying the World
at the very end.
Its DPS is too high.
Jun Moxiao wants to go to support them.
But it's too late.
The HP of Han Yanrou, Cold Hands and Combat Form
run out at the same time.
The two teams drew in the Team Competition.
Great. Well done.
But the total integral of Xing Xin
is still five-point lower than Jia Shi.
Even if Xing Xin gains the extra point by Ace,
They will still lose the game by one point.
That means
Jia Shi has secured the champion in advance.
The champion of this challenge has belonged to Jia Shi.
Are you sure you want to keep on?
Of course.
The competition isn't over.
But I think,
Ye Qiu won't give up in advance.
It has been more than the competition.
This battle is about glory.
Entertain the competition.
Even if...
This is the last one.
Now, Leaf of Autumn
And Jun Moxiao rush towards each other.
It is the battle between two God of fights
and also between two captains of Jia Shi of two generations.
Who can win the competition in the end?
Fight, boss.
Wipe them out. Kill them.
Fight, captain.
Wipe them out.
Fight.
Well done.
Great.
Jun Moxiao kills Leaf of Autumn.
Xiang Xin creates the miracle.
With the huge disadvantage in the team competition,
They score Ace over Jia Shi,
and win the competition
by fourteen to ten.
Xing Xin is the best,
Lao Ye is the best.
Xiang Xin, the best. Xiang Xin, the best.
What a pity.
Xiang Xin still fails in terms of the total integral.
Actually, when Han Yanrou lost the game,
Everyone in Xiang Xin clearly knows that
It is impossible to win the champion.
But they still,
show a brilliant ace.
= 24  Group Stage 21 =
= 10 Arena Contest 8 =
= 10 Team Competition 14 =
= 44 Aggregate Score 43 =
One point.
It is so close.
= 44 Aggregate Score 43 =
Xiang Xin win the competition
by twenty two to twenty.
But very pitifully,
although they score ace over Jia Shi,
they still lose to Jia Shi
by one point,
Sharing the joy if we win.
Sharing the pain if we lose.
At the worst, we will accompany Xiang Xin to restart everything,
and wait one extra year.
Little Moon,
This is the best slogan you come up with tonight.
Xing Xin,
Long life Xing Xin.
Long life Xing Xin. Long life Xing Xin.
= 10 Team Competition 15 =
= 44 Aggregate Score 44 =
Long life Xing Xin.
Xing Xin.
How could that be?
Does he break the record?
The damage of Master Ye
breaks the four-year record of the league.
So they gain extra two points.
It overturns the result of the competition.
It is too incredible.
# We must try our best to win. #
# We laugh, cry, #
# and upset for frustration. #
= 10 Team Competition 16 =
= 44 Aggregate Score 45 =
# and upset for frustration. #
# Stay with each other, we welcome the change. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
Guys,
We
win the challenge.
# Even if we're beaten back and bruised all over #
= 10 Team Competition 16 =
= 44 Aggregate Score 45 =
# Even if we're beaten back and bruised all over #
# there is always hope rising from desperation #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
# We must try our best to win. #
# We laugh, cry, and upset for frustration. #
# Stay with each other, we welcome the change. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
You chose the wrong name of the team.
It should be called Xing Xin.
# Spent countless wonderful time together. #
= A single spark of Xing Xin can start a big fire. =
I spent a pretty penny to introduce you into Jia Shi.
I let you use the account of the Master.
I gave you all the sources of the team.
And you just rewarded me in this way?
This is not a competition.
This is your last chance.
It's also the last chance of Jia Shi.
Nobody would invest money in Jia Shi
who even can't come back to the league.
The eight-year-old Jia Shi,
It is ruined by you.
Glory is not a single-player game.
Everyone is responsible for the failure.
Including you, Mr. Tao.
Let's welcome Xing Xin Team.
Lao Ye, you are the best. The best.
Xing Xin is the best.
The best.
Please lift your championship trophy.
Ye Xiu and Jun Moxiao will always be with Xingxin.
Tang Rou, Han Yanrou will always be with Xingxin.
Bao Zi, the Invader will always be with Xingxin.
Qiao Yifan, Yi Cunhui will always be with Xingxin.
Xing Xin is bound to win.
Glory will never die out.
Challenge,
we are coming!
Do you regret to come to Jia Shi?
Do you regret?
As long as I can keep joining the competition,
There is nothing to regret.
Then see you in the competition of next year.
The damage of Master Ye
breaks the four-year record of the league.
The previous record holder is
Captain Han, right?
Someone breaks you record.
Anything you want to say?
Records are there to be broken.
That's why Glory
could create so many miracles.
Now to announce
the winner of this Challenge is
Xing Xin Team.
Please welcome Mr. Feng Xianjun
to award the registration certificate of the League
to Xing Xin Team.
Welcome back.
The name in the certificate is right, isn't it?
How could it be wrong?
It is you that should be careful.
Don't write the wrong name afterwards.
Thank you.
# I am as always, #
=  Xing Xin Team, welcome to join the league. =
# Remain true to original aspiration #
At this moment,
I would like to ask you,
Master Ye,
Is there anything you want to say to everyone?
# Keep calm even though I have to leave #
# I am as always, #
Since today,
Sun Xiang will succeed you as captain.
The account of Leaf of Autumn
will also be handed over to him.
I choose to retire.
At the worst,
I will start from the beginning.
# We will meet again when the day comes. #
# We are stronger than we used to be. #
# We go through deep and down. #
# We stand at the starry summit. #
# Now I finally understand what I used to be. #
# I have always been my own hero. #
# I have seen the legend before. #
I am here to apply for a job.
Then why did you choose to retire?
Although I am a little old,
I don't want to give up.
Turn the glass into a vase.
Employ another way.
Start again.
Glory,
I can play it for another ten years without getting bored.
Xing Xin Team.
All the members are here.
# I am an ordinary, but more than ordinary. #
# I am at the summit, looking for another summit. #
Every unwilling departure
is for
the final return
I am back.
Let's congratulate Xing Xin Team
# I have always been my own hero. #
# I have seen the legend before. #
Don't stay here. Go dancing.
Go.
You don't stand here as well. Move.
Come. Have a drink.
Bye.
Living in the world,
Impossible to have no enemies.
Make you pass out with one bottle.
Make you pass out with two bottles.
Make you pass out with three bottles.
Make you pass out with one bottle.
Drink now.
Who says I will pass out with only one bottle of booze?
Can you do it?
Don't force yourself.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Are you alright? Amazing.
Three. Two. One.
This is not passing out with only one bottle of booze.
This is not passing out within three seconds.
Enjoy yourself to the full today.
I come to drink with you.
Come. Have a drink.
Mo Fan.
Come.
It is not silence that chooses you.
It is you who choose silence.
No more words.
Here.
Cheers.
I should
have a drink with you.
There is something that
I always want to tell you.
Listen to me.
I only say it once.
He can't drink much too.
All the professional players get drunk easily.
No.
Master once said before,
It is not that their capacity for liquor is poor.
In fact, they never dare to learn drinking.
Because under the influence of alcohol for long,
It will slow down their reaction speed.
It also affects the stability of the hands.
This is the real professional player.
This is so fake.
At this moment, I understand something all of a sudden.
About winning.
About champion.
About us.
I guess,
Everyone will
Meet such a group of lovable people in their life.
Our union is not to change each other.
But to become better
for each other.
The combination of you and me
creates us.
This is the thing to be proudest of.
Come here. Since the Night of Glory
when Master Ye declared to come back to the league,
every team feels that the pressure is on.
We are now going to interview
the preparations of every team.
Captain Jiexi, Captain Jiexi,
Do you have any pressure
after Master Ye comes back?
In terms of pressure,
Wei Cao doesn't feel anything.
I suggest you to interview
Lan Yu who was knocked out in the quarterfinals this summer.
Thank you.
Can you say anything else?
Yes. Please say something more.
Please say something more.
How about interviewing me?
I really cooperate with your interview.
I can tell you more than excepted.
Your satisfaction is guaranteed.
I just want to ask,
With the return of Master Ye,
Lan Ye doesn't adopt any
special solution, right?
We don't need any special training.
So definitely no.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Your satisfaction is guaranteed.
Shaotian,
Have you prepared
the featured videos for teaching?
I will send you
the secret address where Ambitions has their training.
Well, well,
Well,
I take the wrong road.
At last, let's pay attention to Jia Shi.
= Jia Shi is about to put itself up for sale. =
Since the failure of the Challenge,
Jia Shi has been keeping silent.
Just now,
Jia shi posts a message on its homepage.
Since today,
Jia Shi has put itself up for sale.
Tao Xuan said,
Years of managing Jia Shi has worn him down.
He hopes that the successor
can lead Jia Shi to create glory again.
And he will always be the fan of Jia Shi.
Jia Shi is too big.
Other teams can't buy it on its own.
It may adopt divestiture.
The team,
The team members,
The roles,
All the team sources will
go into liquidation gradually.
So,
Jia Shi will disband.
I think only the weak team will come to this end.
I never thought that Jia Shi, the strong team in the past
should be reduced to this state.
E-sports teams are just like e-sports players.
It has it own golden period.
It will get old and out of date.
Many people only see
The glamour of those e-sports players.
But they ignore the cruelty behind the glory.
So,
There is no more Jia Shi afterwards?
Will Jia Shi really end like this?
The name of Jia Shi
Will disappear forever?
Jia Shi will not disappear.
Because I believe,
People who can inherit this spirit
Will definitely occur.
Mucheng,
Do you still remember that we were here
the day when I left Jia Shi?
That was when we came back
after finishing the last competition.
Your well-known quotes.
Only by releasing the proper skill at a proper moment
can you win the game.
But,
You don't say
What I should do after winning.
What can you do after winning?
Boasting.
Saying some harsh words.
Silly girl.
First,
don't scold anyone when reflecting on the competition tomorrow.
Second,
don't scold me if you have to.
Third,
even if you want to scold me,
no more than three sentences.
What about the forth one?
Forth,
I can't attend it tomorrow.
So even if you scold me,
I can't hear it.
Saying so many words,
Aren't you thirsty?
Thank you.
You are responsible for
pulling the ring for me.
Every time I passed the corridor in the past,
I could hear the sounds of mouses and keyboards.
It is so quiet right now.
I am a bit unaccustomed to it.
In fact, the life of the e-sports players is quite simple.
They spend most time on training.
And have few entertainment.
Aside from playing the game,
they spend almost
All the time and energy here in their life.
We also spent
these years in this way.
So apart from the world of Glory,
this building
is the most familiar place to me.
In the past year, I have known that
at the end of this path,
I will leave Jia Shi.
But I never thought that
Jia Shi would be reduced into this situation,
when I am leaving.
It's so quiet.
Someone is playing Glory right now.
According to this speed of playing,
He is a little weak.
I am going to pack my stuff first.
Wait for me.
You are still so bad at playing Glory.
When did you begin to smoke cigar?
I always stayed with people smoking cigar.
After a long time,
I learn it naturally.
How about your selling?
The club is too big.
And we didn't achieve the qualification for the league.
It is the worst time
to sell this club.
But anyway,
someone has bought it.
He promises me that,
He would continue to use the name of Jia Shi.
So I've been very content.
After I sell this place,
I am about to become a poor merchant
who has nothing but money.
Things I left in Glory are
only some failures.
Nobody can erase the honor
that are possessed by Jia Shi.
When I just played Glory,
I thought of our past all of a sudden.
Then I realized that I have been wrong all the time.
Glory,
Is indeed not a single-player game.
And Jia Shi,
Never belongs only to me.
We can also create
a new age.
Turn the Glory we know
into the real sports.
We should make this thing
become the glory of our life.
Glory,
I can never play it as well as
You and Muqiu do.
So at the time i thought,
Although I could not
Participate in the competition like you guys,
I could be
A great manager of the team.
When you exerted your energy
Competed in the game,
I could provide a solid backing for you.
I always thought that
we three would be
the best partners.
Do you know that
I have had a thought for these years,
And it became increasingly stronger.
And you? You just competed in the game.
And never kept pace with me.
You refused to commercialization.
You didn't want to show in public.
So I was wondering
If you didn't hold me back,
What Jia Shi would be?
It must be better.
Maybe.
You are here to pick up Mucheng, right?
There is something.
Please help me give it to her.
Sun Xiang transfers the club
along with the account card of Leaf of Autumn.
It can't be gotten back.
I still keep the card of Dancing Rain.
Let Mucheng take it away.
If it is too expensive,
Xiang Xin can't afford it.
Senior,
What are you doing here?
Why not going to the reception room?
I go training first.
OK.
It's time for evening training.
Very punctual.
By the way,
No smoking in the training room.
OK. OK.
I see. I see.
Jia Shi,
does never only belongs to us.
Put it down. Move.
Put it a little down.
Move it to the right side a little bit.
I was once standing here,
watching the maple leaf rising high.
After another years,
maybe this place
will have a new beginning.
Right.
Luckily, somebody has prepared to take over Jia Shi.
So...
The glory of Jia Shi will not end.
# Walking to the glory from the adversity. #
Why did you want to establish the Glory league?
I knew nothing about e-sports nor Glory at that time.
But it didn't matter.
Because what touched me most was
never the Glory itself,
but young people like you
who always keep pursuing the glory.
# You are as always #
Glory,
is not that simple as you think.
# I am an ordinary, but more than ordinary. #
# I am at the summit, looking for another summit. #
= Xing Xin Team =
# We will meet again when the day comes. #
# We are stronger when we used to be. #
Samsara, the champion of the ninth league,
is about to announce that
They will bring in Sun Xiang, the former ace member of Jia Shi,
and the role of Leaf of Autumn
at the cost of 12 million.
You all see that, right?
How powerful our future rivals could be.
Yes.
It has been hard enough to
take care of Zhou Zekai in Samsara.
Now they have Sun Xiang.
What should we do?
Enhance the training.
Simulate competitions.
Strengthen the team in the shortest time.
But before that,
there is still an important thing.
What?
The prize of the challenge is issued.
Boss,
Shall we share the money first?
# The starry fireflies from the ordinary #
# sailing with the wind and converge into the Milky Way #
Hey, Dad.
I am recruiting new members.
The dungeon of the Frost Forest?
I will send you later.
I can't form the team with you.
You are in the eleventh district,
while I'm in the tenth district.
It's not about distance.
Different district means different times.
Come on.
Don't come here.
Mr. Ye,
Why not directly joining in Xing Xin
when we are recruiting new members?
Our slogan is don't worry that you can't learn it.
Don't worry about meals and accommodation.
# Intertwined between the fingers #
= Ye Xiu =
= Jun Moxiao =
# Intertwined between the fingers #
= Chen Guo =
= Zhu Yanxia =
# Intertwined between the fingers #
= Chen Guo =
= Zhu Yanxia =
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
= Su Mucheng =
= Dancing Rain =
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
= Su Mucheng =
= Dancing Rain =
# The only light during the long night #
= Tang Rou =
= Han Yanrou =
# The only light during the long night #
# Is us from the ordinary life #
= Bao Rongxing =
= Bao Zi, the Invader =
# Is us from the ordinary life #
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
= Qiao Yifan =
= Yi Cunhui =
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
= Luo Ji =
= Mei Guang =
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
= Luo Ji =
= Mei Guang =
# We are the brightest fireflies #
= An Wenyi =
= Cold Hands =
# We are the brightest fireflies #
= An Wenyi =
= Cold Hands =
# I came from the past and will write the future #
= Wei Chen =
= Windward Formation =
# I came from the past and will write the future #
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
= Mo Fan =
= Deception =
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
= Wu Chen =
= Dawn Rifle =
# The rising wave of our ten years' effort #
= Wu Chen =
= Dawn Rifle =
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
= Sun Xiang =
= Leaf of Autumn =
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
= Sun Xiang =
= Leaf of Autumn =
# The glorious moment of coronation #
= Xiao Shiqin =
= Sheng Lingmie =
# The glorious moment of coronation #
= Qiu Fei =
= Combat Form =
# The glorious moment of coronation #
= Qiu Fei =
= Combat Form =
# The glory we've missed #
= Chen Yehui =
= Total Darkness =
# The glory we've missed #
= Yu Wenzhou =
= Swoksaar =
# The glory we've missed #
= Yu Wenzhou =
= Swoksaar =
# The pride in the future #
= Huang Shaotian =
= Troubling Rain =
# The pride in the future #
= Huang Shaotian =
= Troubling Rain =
# Intertwined between the fingers #
= Xu Boyuan =
= Lan He =
# Intertwined between the fingers #
= Xu Boyuan =
= Lan He =
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
= Han Wenqing =
= Smoke Alone =
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
= Zhang Xinjie =
= Shi Buzhuan =
# Composing the great song of battlefield #
= Zhang Xinjie =
= Shi Buzhuan =
# The only light during the long night #
= Wang Jiexi =
= Wang Bu Liu Xing =
# The only light during the long night #
= Wang Jiexi =
= Wang Bu Liu Xing =
# Is us from the ordinary life #
= Gao Yingjie =
= Mu En =
# Is us from the ordinary life #
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
= Chang Xian =
= Yue Zhongmian =
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
We met in Glory.
Glory is more than a competition.
Glory is the world of us all.
We shall meet again in the world of Glory.