=The King's Avatar
=Episode 5
Win again
Just a little luck.
Clearly is very strong
The time for modesty must be low-key.
The high-profile time must show off
I-I really don't have a strategy
You are really experienced
No friends, no files
What can I do? I am also very helpless
If you don't add friends, you can teach by word and deed.
Do not receive files
You will change your strategy
What can I do then
I am also very irritable.
That craziness can't solve the problem either.
Are you sure you can't finish the task
I
Definitely
Under the guidance of the boss
It is an achievable task.
The deadline is 24 hours.
The bell rang
Become a useful person
or become a slag
This is my handwritten Glory World Rule
It's not a teaching strategy.
It's just a process introduction.
Nor is it a boast of successful experience
It's just a collection of failures and lessons.
I'm sorry
I don't read manuscripts
Bring it here
What broken manuscripts can only be thrown away
Don, take your time
Come on, come on, have fun
Smelly boy go to work quickly
Xiao Tang, you are quite good now.
Progress is very fast.
You didn't fight me for two minutes before.
Now you can't even reach 40 seconds
In fact, it can be faster
What miracle did you swallow?
Or did you take the medicine
It must be the manuscript
I just flipped through it
There is nothing worth watching
You threw it away
Where did you throw it
Throw it at the bar
Uh
Please type last month's statement.
I'll pass
Boss, you have been urging me
Do things early
So I finished it yesterday
By the way, use Microsoft spreadsheet software
A settlement was drawn up.
The computer in Area B 47 is broken
Take a look at it
Boss, you have been urging me
Internet cafes run on computers.
Head can be broken blood can flow computer must be good
So what?
The one in area b
I fixed it as soon as it broke down.
Thank you for the universal restart button.
Did the boss tell you
They should disappear when they should not appear.
What should not appear
Now
Network manager
Coming
When did you become so quick
Okay
This is a long-lost one.
The secret of Glory
Xiao Tang watched this
As if the light had been turned on
I also don't ask for light
I just look at it
What is this?
Poached Egg
This little Tang is practicing strategy？
Or a recipe.
Z-word jitter
The most important thing is that during the movement process
Hand Speed Control for Direction Change Operation
What kind of salted duck egg is it?
Falling palm
Although is not a high-level skills
it has a very strong blowing effect
The blowing distance played
can control outside the opponent's attack range
That is an extremely terrible micromanagement
Is this a teacup?
Why there is a cup?
Fancy tattoo
This must be a fancy tattoo practiced by battlemage.
This critical moment
Still have to rely on my sister's understanding
Sitting for too long is not a good combination of work and rest.
See here please get up and have a drink of tea
Let's take a break between classes.
What are we talking about
I gave you a copy.
Jun Moxiao online time statistics
If you have to wait, you should at least follow his schedule.
Otherwise, you will wait for the rabbit.
It's almost like a Waiting Stone.
I'm tired of thinking about the plan.
How to arrange it?
Uh...
You go and call a group of people together.
I have a task later
How will the big plan be arranged?
The place where the bones were buried was agreed upon by the brothers last time.
When will you get off the books?
You really miss it
Oh,no. You lied to me last time
I'll wait for you because I've arranged all the people.
You don't sway me
Your people don't have to bother
I have my own team
See you in half an hour
His own team
This is to bring a team of experts to help me
Come with me to Buried Ground
What do you think?
Can some one fight against mein the Buried Ground?
There are plenty of opponents to practice with.
Everyone is quite fierce
That's quite suitable for me
Give it a try
President, are these people all masters
Of course, is a master
You see the momentum of this female fighting method
A look at the ability is very strong
It seems that this is her first time
This year
There are fewer and fewer great gods willing to teach new people.
But copies like this
A team can only take one
You all have a chance
Later on
What about the future
Look at this ranger
This ranger is very experienced at first sight.
President
This is the gunner last time?
The inexperienced one?
No experience
It's all a lesson.
Just looks a bit like
Master, let's go
Wait for another person
See
The master said to wait for another person
It must be a peerless player
All the top players are the final ones.
It must be very strong
She just registered yesterday and buying equipment now  .
Are you sure this can be recorded
Who pressed my stool
Who?
This ..
I'm-I'm going to start
Can these two newcomers do it
This Bao Zi is too random, isn't he?
It was he who beat a monster for ten seconds.
He won in two minutes
What level is this
Han Yanrou indeed as expected
haven't made any copies at all.
She have no idea of cooperation at all.
President, this is a bit messy.
Hold on, hold on. It's all tactics.
Why is one person missing?
Where is the gunner
Why are there only four left
I lost one.
May be bought too many weapons and can't move
The gunner is also too unreliable
Zombie Bailey escaped
The keel will be drilled soon.
It is really unreliable.
Zombie Bailey has run away
Still shooting aimlessly
Oh, my God, a reaction time of 0.1 second
Hit the target
Who do you think is standing on the keel
Shooting all the way around
Accurately driving zombie Bailey
to Jun Moxiao
Broken umbrellas turn into spears.
This is a sharp stab.
What kind of gun is this?
She can use this
and play like this
Ninety percent must be professionals.
Female Gunner
Mu
Is it Su Mucheng
Of course it is Su Mucheng
to help us make a copy of Lanxi Pavilion
Must be Su Mucheng
This time, the President
President can boast around.
Even Su Mucheng has come to Lanxi Pavilion to make a copy.
Don't be ridiculous.
This time is only lucky
to shoot like this.
Focus on our mission.
It turned out to be a coincidence.
I thought she is Su Mucheng
Congratulations to Lanxi Pavilion player Jun Moxiao
Feng Shu Yanmo, Bao Zi Ruqin
Han Yanrou and Lan He break record of Buried Ground
See the new record
What did I just say
This is the strategy of my brother and I.
The president is wise
The president is wise.
Yes, yes.
Jun Moxiao is awesome
Record again
Tenth District Record Grand Slam
Jun Moxiao you are the best.
Jun Moxiao is the strongest master in history
Lanxi Pavilion Dominates the top place
Who will break this record?
I ate the keyboard
I said
If it weren't for my gun
Zombie Bailey had already run away
My lady, that's the President of Lanxi Pavilion.
He will know it is you.
If not say something
Jiashi will know it
What can you do
I'm not afraid
Professional players come to snatch the copy record.
How embarrassing is it to bully the small with the big?
Who would believe it if they said it?
Scold me
The new form is unlocked.
Help me test a thousand-machine Umbrella?
I will show no mercy
This transformation form
It's called the Pure Soul war spear
Attack speed 5
The Fastest Attack Speed in war spear
This transformation form
Called the decider's rifle.
Light weight and large recoil
Perfect Transformation of Gun Profession
This transformation is called heraldic shield
It evolved from the knight's shield.
Can easily change the priesthood skill of preventing high blood thickness.
At the same time, it also
owns high magic resistance and wide defense range
It is a close-fitting weapon for the fighting profession.
All right, stop it
Because of it
We stole her hairpin the day before yesterday.
She stole her rubber band again yesterday.
She stole her performance dress today.
You didn't use the stolen word very accurately.
This thing goes back and forth in one's own hands.
At best, it can be regarded as recycling to maximize its value.
Isn't it
Look at this hairpin and this rubber band
Especially this costume
Flexibility is just right.
Perfect
Run
Come here today.
I'm offline. I'm going to train.
On the tactics of this competition
We'd better confirm it.
I already said at the tactical meeting
You just need to be my assistant.
Leave the rest to me.
If this arrangement is absolutely necessary
There are a few points I would like to remind
Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian in Lan Yu
This is not my first match
Mucheng is there.
Captain
What's up?
Well, you just became captain
This is a new atmosphere both inside and outside Jiashi.
I think the decoration style
It must also be refreshed.
You see, this is a new rendering.
You can handle such trifles at your own discretion.
Okay, I'll get someone to arrange it right away.
But there is one thing I haven't done well
Say ..
Now Jiashi is on a upward trend.
Only this guild
With the atmosphere of the team
Drag the captain's hind legs
Is the guild's performance that bad?
The main reason is that there is an expert stirring up.
He not only robbed several big guilds' first kill
but also the record
He is a long-term occupying.
Copy record
This is simple
What kind of expert can there be in Glory
So
We will go to the team tomorrow to report a copy of the record
It is absolutely stable
No one can surpass it.
This is all the credit of everyone
But what we have to do is to make persistent efforts.
Take another copy of the record
Your enthusiasm was too high just now.
It scared the hell out of our new copy records.
Three, two, one
Start
Congratulations to Jia Dynasty players, Yi FeiXiangtian, Lin Linsha,
Meng Tianchen, Jiuyang, Jinxiang.
Breaking the Record of Buried Ground
Results: 16 minutes 56 seconds 78
What are records used for
is to let we Lanxi pavilion
to break
Everyone should be prepared
I will launch a new round soon.
Attacks on copy records
You also have to work hard to refuel
Come on
You can certainly do it
Brother, do you have a paper record?
It broke in two days without persistence.
Is it too harsh to say so?
Can't say that
Brother, the new records are all paper tigers.
You don't have to be too sad
No, in case
What if the master likes to challenge?
Brother, what did you withdraw again
Hideous news
Brother, do you need any materials recently
The guild has newly made a powerful spider silk
The more materials, the better
Then make another appointment
But this record
How do you say after-sales service
Should there be a three-guarantee policy?
What three guarantees do you want for a three-no product?
I saw the new record
16 minutes 56 seconds 78
Should be deployed professional players
And this result is already the limit.
It is almost impossible to break through again.
Is it impossible
Then our record is gone
But I like to be in the impossible
looking for possibilities
Sun led professional players to brush out
16 minutes 56 seconds 78
No matter how many times I simulate actual combat
Also can't find a way to speed up
and short the time
Since straight way is blocked
Then we have to find a  by-pass
But I still need a swordsman
Is this Internet cafe contracted by Ye Qiu
There's a match tonight. I'll help Jiashi.
So obviously you can't see it
Particularly obvious
This is the same height humanoid board I bought for tonight.
The original size is exactly the same as that of Ye Qiu.
Can you help me put this here
Give it to you.
Equal size?
Equal height?
By the way, smelly boy, I ask you
What do you think of the match tonight
Which team will win?
Boss, which team do you want to win
Anyway, I think Jiashi will lose
Jiashi would be impossible to win without Ye Qiu
This
What are you hissing about
I asked you which team would win
I didn't ask you to disarm the bomb
Forget it
You put these posters later
Give me all hung up
I want everyone who comes to the internet cafe today
All bathed in Ye Qiu's eyes
Boss
You are good at picking posters.
It's very sharp and unique. The humanoid board is well done.
Higher than Ye Qiu himself
Handmade videos are also great.
Why don't we be thorough
The Internet cafe password has also been changed
It's called Ye Qiu Unbeatable and Most Handsome.
Ye Qiu Unbeatable and Most Handsome.
That's a good one
I feel the temperament of my Internet cafe
It's all different.
You should have heard it
I just used rhetoric
This is called irony
That's it
The smelly boy has made progress
This is the Glory Professional League
The 16th round of the season
The Jiashi Team Against Lan Yu Team
Hello, everyone, audience and friends
And everyone watching live
Little friends
See you again
I am your old friend.
Xiao Luo
Please welcome the host team immediately.
Jiashi Team, please
First to enter
is the new captain of Jiashi
Sun Xiang, known as the new king
Following him closely
is the first gunner in our alliance.
Su Mucheng
Let's welcome the challenger
Lan Yu Team, please
First came to us
The first is the so-called
Yu Wenzhou, one of the alliance's four greatest tacticians
The second is our Sword master Huang Shaotian
After all, whether the new Fighting God Sun Xiang
can survive Huang Shaotian
the Sword master
The two teams have assembled
Please shake hands with each other
The elder of the little classmate came to tell you
The gap between you and your father
Listen carefully in class for a while.
Did Sister Su miss me
No
You're fat again.
Shut up
Now between the players of our two teams
All have simply said hello
I don't know
Did they make any sparks
This is incredible
Where is the webmaster beer
There
The Lan Yu team has fallen behind 0-3.
It seems that after the last victory over Wei Cao Team
With the the newcomer Sun Xiang
Jiashi is very strong
And the Sun now has Leaf of Autumn
Such a divine account number
Then his strength will be by going up one flight of stairs
There are three players from each team in the ring match.
The loser leaves the game using KOF
Change other teammates on the team
No one can go to a certain team.
The winning team scored three points.
Is it possible for Sun Xiang to defeat the three
No way
As for itself, it is very difficult to defeat the three by one
What's more, the opponent's strength is not weak
Jiashi will win
Then finally comes
the long-awaited ring match
Jiashi vs. Lan Yu Challenge Race Begins
First round
Sun Xiang Leave of Autumn
Against Yu Feng's Crazy Swordsmen
Competition Map First-Line Canyon
Start of the game
We saw Leaf of Autumn coming forward
It's just going to be positive.
The blow was dodged by Leaf of Autumn.
Backhand Dragon Teeth Floating
Then pick up the day strike Feng Mang Huijian fall on the ground
Strong dragon pressure
The attack rhythm of Yiyezhiqiu is very good.
Never excepted
Sun Xiang attacted as soon as he came up.
The pressure was too great for Yu Feng to resist.
The Leaf of Autumn suddenly launched an onslaught.
Feng Mang Huijian is dangerous.
It is very likely that they will be taken away directly.
Sun only uses 15% of the blood volume
He killed Yu Feng, Lan Yu's first player.
Great advantage
It seems that one defeat three is very promising.
Lan Yu's second player
Qigong master Tao luo Shaming came on stage.
We saw that the fallen petal palm hit and was forced by the dragon.
Great, Sun uses only 10% of the blood volume
Another player from Lan Yu was killed.
Jia Shi's fans have already started shouting
Can Sun Be the Third This Season
finish the feat of one defaet and three?
The third set will begin.
We saw that Lan Yu's champion was
Ammunition experts, Qiang lin Danyu
It's another long-distance job.
Fu Long Xiang Tian
Seckill
Sun came to Jia Shi's first show and let us see it.
His terrible personal strength
It seems that Sun did it
He really made one defeat three
I think a new fighting king has been born
What kind of luck did you run into?
Can you give me a triple crown
Boss, boss, boss
Your network manager
You came here
Boss, is this your network manager
He doesn't even know where the beer is.
Sorry, sorry
What's the matter with you?
You don't even know where the beer is
Now, immediately
Take the topographic map of this internet cafe
Draw a picture for me
The position of a screw
should be accurate to centimeter
Do you hear me
I
You take customers to get beer.
Sorry, there it is, there it is
This kind of thing will not happen again next time.
Welcome back
After the singles and challenge matches
The score is now 0-6 behind Lan Yu.
If you want to win
In the next team match
Get five points
And get two points for team elimination
What good cattle do you have?
Xiao Chu, bring me my account book
I've already calculated the account.
Do it again
All
Captain
Where shall we celebrate tonight?
Ying Chao bar
Later, all of you
All cover for me.
I have covered all the people across the street.
Understood, good captain.
Captain, let's go according to tactics.
Relax Mu Cheng
After all, we still have the captain.
We all know that the Lan Yu team has
Glory to One of Four Tactical Masters
Yu Wenzhou
It is a team with very high tactical qualities.
The cooperation between the players is very tacit
And Jia Shi clan
The new captain Sun
Can he lead his teammates?
Play a different match
We will wait and see.
Remember, be happy
Less days
Remember tactics.
Don't worry about me
When did I, the blade master,  drop the chain?
Is it right?
Come on
Players from both sides enter the competition map.
Jiashi vs. Lan Yu
The team match will begin immediately.
Of the two big teams
Sun battlemage Leaf of Autumn
Yu Wenzhou Warlock Su Ke Sa'er
Su Mucheng Gunner Mu Yu Chengfneg
Huang Shaotian, the swordsmen Ye Yu Shengfan
So these four star players
What kind of spark will they   create?
Sun has shown strong personal strength
I don't know
How will it work out?
A Leaf of Autumn Hero Pojun
The momentum is still very strong.
We saw the ammunition experts flying
After defeating Qaing Lin Danyu
Cut directly to warlock
Qaing Lin Danyu stands up
Interfering Leaf of Autumn's attack
This heat-sensitive missile repelled two people beautifully.
We saw Ye Yu Shengfan, the swordsman, on the other side
cut directly to Jiashi's sharpshooter
Yes, the choice of both sides
They all let the strikers cut to the back row.
disturb output
Sun's reaction is very fast
Yu Wenzhou's fantastic Predicts
Pull back the Qigong master
Escape the pressure of Leaf of Autumn
Yes, we see that the blood volume of both sides is now equal.
So this stalemate continues
Lan Yu is going to lose
The scene was very close
Lan Yu's Qigong Master fails to protect back row
Su Ke Sa'er is still pinned down by Leaf of Autumn.
Beautiful, Sun operates very fast.
Disengaging the ammunition expert's stiff bullet
Damn it
Leaf of Autumn hit Su Ke Sa'er.
Sun continues the momentum
Sun fierce, Sun fierce
What a fart!
Devanning
Lan Yu needs to adjust the rhythm now.
Jia Shi's Full Staff strides forward
Want to give Lan Yu continued repression
Jiashi is to lose
To lose?
Who did you say was going to lose?
This is what you said Jia Shi is going to lose?
Who are you kidding?
You see, he has taken the limelight now.
No, Jiashi is to Lose
Why?
Yu Wenzhou used his trump card tactics
Lock-one & release-four tactics