= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 16 =
= Welcome Jun Mo Xiao to the Field of God =
I hope one day
A thousand-machine umbrella could be the top weapon in Glory
Got nothing better to do?
Sit around waiting for me?
I am on a full schedule ok?
Take that! Take that! Take that!
Accompany your captain to test the weapon?
Actually it's me to accompany Shaotian.
Come on,
isn't the welcoming ceremony too solemn?
Welcome? You are overthinking.
After admitting retirement is your own choice,
how could you expect someone lined up to welcome you?
Step aside. Step aside. Step aside.
I should be the first
to fight him.
Ye, I have a question.
Is it the final form
of your thousand-change umbrella?
Any new play?
Show me.
How could I let you guys see through me?
Class is over. Gotta go.
We haven't got down to business.
So many people are waiting for your answer.
You can't leave like that.
What's the real point of your statement?
Make it clear.
There's nothing to say.
I just don't want to let my old friend down.
Thanks for coming, guys.
It's time to leave.
With so many masters crowded in the Field of God,
a riot could be caused.
Someday we will meet at the battlefield.
Ye, you will come back, right?
Right? Right? Right? Ye!
That's my opponent.
Welcome back to the Field of God.
May Glory be with you.
I will be back. Won't be long.
Why did him return good for evil?
Let me tell you,
to observe a master,
you can't just focus on his bright image.
Underneath it,
could be an ugly heart.
What does he plan to do?
After leaving the old team,
he must join a new one,
finding a better choice.
But his best choice is himself.
Baozi, time to work.
Why do you take these things out?
Haven't you seen
our boss is sad for the unethical decision
that Ye Qiu made?
He plans to build his own team!
You want to build your own team!
Betray your team! Betray your fans!
Now even build your own team!
Boss, such a scum should be broken into pieces.
What are you doing?
No need to say. I get you.
I will throw it.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Do you know who is Ye Qiu?
Ye Qiu is of course no one else but Ye Qiu.
Don't tell me he is Ye Xiu.
Cap!
To observe a master,
you can't just focus on his bright image.
Underneath it,
coule be a brighter heart.
How dare a noob like me,
curse our cap,
say bad things about our cap...
It should be me
to be broken into pieces.
What can I do for him?
To be his team member?
Ahh I can be his boss.
Boss...
I think it's quite likely.
No, it's unlikely.
How could he
allow me to be his boss?
likely...
Still unlikely.
Shakespear Bao!
Boss, my bad!
Listen,
Your salary of this month, next month,
tll the end of this year is gone!
The photo is ready.
Let me see.
Manly style, you like it?
How about elegant style?
That's not me.
Of course it's you.
The teenager version.
How about this one?
Cute style.
Any other choices?
Emm...I pick the cute one.
So this one will be submitted.
For the Challenge, it's better to use the formal one.
So can we...
dispose of the left?
Whatever floats your boat.
I have a bunch at home anyway.
Whenever I need these photos,
I can print more.
There won't be such need.
Of course there is.
For example, when I want to tease you, satirize you,
and get back at you.
To get back to the League, a team is necessary.
To build a team, a guild is necessary.
To create a guild, enough members are necessary.
Are you sure you can handle all the stuff?
Not sure.
So?
I need a boss.
Have you found one?
I think I have a choice.
What advantages does this person have?
Been a boss before.
It doesn't count.
Practice makes perfect.
Have you asked this person?
Same position, same job,
of her interst.
There is no reason to say no.
Do you know what you look like now?
Blindly optimistic.
Daydreaming.
Ye Xiu,
a new year,
means a new start for both of us.
Look!
The world agrees with me.
New year, new start.
I am worn out.
Finally, the training is over.
We can have a rest now.
How do you feel recently?
Not bad.
Two glasses of juice, please.
Wei Cao Team is recruiting.
Yi Fan, the whole training is coming to the end.
Are you going back to Wei Cao?
I want to take more practice.
Yifan didn't attent
the test of our training camp at all.
Obviously my test matters more.
What did he get?
Below zero for Assassin and zero for Ghostblade.
Just zero.
Both of us,
also started from zero.
Zero is a new start.
That's why today you come to me.
Do you want Yifan to join you?
The wild flowers are so dazzling
that exactly blind your uneven eyes.
I will never pick the wrong flowers,
or wrong team members.
But still thank you,
for helping Yifan find his way.
It's easy to know where to go but hard to get to the end.
I will take care of it.
It's hard to get back to the League.
How about joining Wei Cao Team?
No problem, as long as I take the position of captain.
No problem,
as long as you switch from freelancer to Mage.
Nah, I am not a fan of WEICAO GREEN.
Don't tell me you are still into JIASHI RED.
I want my own colour.
What's your plan?
I already told you.
I am going to be a captain.
Of which team?
I will build my own team.
A team full of newbies... It's difficult to lead.
Easy tasks are never in my list.
That's right. You are already aged.
It's time for you to train your successors.
Don't worry,
retirement is close to you, too.
Senior first.
Before that, I will nail this competition.
No need.
Someday, the newbies will surpass all of us.
Newbies are the future of Glory.
Now I am curious about yours.
Okay,
let me show you
my place.
I don't like this interview to Jessie Wang.
Too official.
No point.
He said the goal of Wei Cao is to be the winner.
But it's same to all.
You make a good point.
Right?
You two look same.
Don't tell me...
This is the captain of Wei Cao Team,
Jessie Wang.
This is our...
Hi, I am the boss of this internet cafe,
Chen Guo.
How are you?
Our boss is just too friendly.
You will get used to it.
I will reflect on
what you just mentioned.
This is Tang Rou,
the owner of Han Yan Rou.
Your techniques are close to Ye Qiu's.
I am flattered.
But I am me and nobody else.
Let's go.
Have a look.
Tang, I think we should change the name
of our internet cafe.
Change to what?
the Field of God.
Cap Jessie already drop by,
then other masters will come here soon.
It seems they are old friends.
Could our cap be dragged to
Wei Cao Team?
No way! I need to stay around.
Ready to act your part?
I'll try.
Come here.
So this is the place you mentioned.
Right.
Everything is ready except the east wind.
What east wind?
A capable boss.
It is hard to find a good one.
There is huge risk to build a new team.
I suggest you
give up this idea.
As I said,
easy tasks are never in my list.
Come on, join our Wei Cao Team.
It's impossible to be a captain,
but chances are to be placed in the starting lineups.
How about that?
I will think about it.
Your age is an issue.
Only a few years left for you.
Why do you make yourself overloaded
to build a new team?
I will think about it carefully.
Why not just hang around,
waiting for the retirement?
Wei Cao treats retiring team members
much better than Jia Shi Team.
Really?
I will think about it seriously.
What are you thinking about?
Why do you come here today?
Am I wrong?
Of course!
Isn't he old?
Isn't it too hard to build a team?
Isn't it a good choice to join Wei Cao?
Can he find a good boss?
Yes, he can.
Who?
Me!
Boss, are you kidding me?
It's not easy to build a new team.
I am not kidding.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I just afraid you don't think I am qualified.
A little bit.
To be the boss of a team, you need to have a high IQ,
and a high EQ.
Do you think you have them both?
It's not a game,
right?
Sure.
Don't make a hasty decision
just because of your sudden impulse.
Then,
there is no place to regret.
I will never give up.
Never give up.
Is she really a good choice?
We all started from zero.
Things can't get any worse.
Did I play well?
Hmm...could be an extra.
Tang,
have you taken an IQ test?
Yep.
What score did you get?
One hundred and thirty.
Hmm it could be the same to me.
Do you think I have a high EQ?
Can you see through others?
I recogized the master as a go-for before,
so maybe I can't.
Can you control yourself?
I think I can.
Are you focused, patient and thoughtful?
I think I am.
Guoguo,
What we are talking about is something serious.
You can't take it too easy.
I think I am ready to build the team.
So how?
I have money, and passion.
Money and passion are not enough.
Can you take the burden, work overnight,
and deal with frustration?
Absolutely.
I don't buy it.
Put them away. They are quite worthy.
To build a team,
it's necessary to create a guild
and achieve the certification.
These two things are the prerequisite.
I will prove myself to you!
I am waiting.
Finally my dream could come true.
I start to make careful preparation for the coming challenges.
This time, I am definitely going to prove
I am qualified enough.
Still have analysis to read?
Rewards for scaning the code.
Relly? Let's have a try.
Welcome to Strong and Stunning Guild.
Rewards for scanning the code.
Let's have a try.
301,enough to advance to the next level.
= Let's summon the Guardian to develop the guild. =
Ok, all done.
= Are you going to take the Guardian mission? =
Go ahead.
The guild is ready?
Strong and Stunning.
Registered for the test?
The clock is ticking.
That confident?
Ready for whatever coming.
After I finish the test,
and you guys knock out the Guardian,
we can hold a party
and enjoy a big dinner.
The Guardian?
After we finish this mission,
our guild can upgrade.
With the member limit reaching 1000,
we can build a team.
When did you take this mission?
Just now.
Did you know
We have to finish this mission in two hours.
What if we fail?
The guild would be disbanded.
We only have two opportunities
to challenge the Guardian.
Now it's only one and a half hour left.
Get ready?
Ready.
It's Unicorn Guardian.
We have to try our best
to defeat it within the limited time,
in order to keep our guild.
We have no choice
but to fight.
Boss,
If you want to help, just go upstairs.
I think I'd better leave it to them.
Chu, we will
get it through, right?
Sure, Ye is such a master,
so it shouldn't be a problem.
Exactly.
We still have a few good players
in our guild.
The mission is only a piece of cake.
Not to mention one and a half hour,
half an hour is enough for them.
Actually we all have confidence in Ye,
but you seem not.
Of course I trust him!
I am going to prepare food and drinks for them right now.
It's been a long time,
why does the HP remain the same?
They missed the target.
What the hell are these noobs doing?
How could it happen!
Aren't they elite?
There are too many misses!
This is intentional.
Don't bother to chase. It's no use.
Why were there so many misses?
It seems our undercover plan works.
Obviously Ye wants to build a team
after creating the guild.
In future, he will not just be the opponent of Lanxi Pavilion,
but compete with Lan Yu Team.
I understand. Don't worry.
I won't be soft.
I will crush their guild
by hook or by crook.
The Guardian
is the largest barrier of upgrading the guild.
Now it's only one hour left.
If they fail again,
their guild will be disbanded.
I didn't expect they took this mission
without any preparation.
It will only embarrass themselves.
Their guild members are all noobs.
To knock out the boss,
we are the only reliance for them.
As long as we remain undercover,
even given two more hours, they still won't get it through.
I'm back.
Baozi, is it your mistake?
Did you do something stupid again?
Boss, I...
No one made mistakes,
except you.
We've been working our ass off,
to pay the price for your impulse.
Guoguo, this time you are too impulsive.
You really should ask us
if we could finish it
before taking this mission.
If we fail,
our guild will be disbanded.
It's not a big deal.
We can creat another one
in a few days anyway.
If you want to be build a team,
I won't stop you.
But have you ever thought
if you are qualified enough?
To build a team, and create a guild,
a lot of people are better than me.
Compared with them,
I am truly unqualified.
The reason why they are better than you,
is not they are more intelligent,
or more capable.
It is simply that you forecast your failure
before taking actions.
Now that you hold this idea,
and they agree with you,
I could quit.
I give up to be the boss of this team.
Whatever... you always give up halfway.
Since you want to quit,
don't bother to push yourself,
and no need to take the coming test.
Alright!
Hurry up! Let's try again.
Although most of us don't have much experience,
we have been this dungeon once.
I think everyone is kind of familiar with it.
Just follow my lead.
I hope we could succeed this time.
Succeed? Are you kidding me?
It's all over.
Master Ye, this time I'm sorry.
Don't tell me you feel sorry for him
and are reluctant to play the tricks.
You are thinking too much. Let's get started.
Let's get started.
Feng Shu Yan Mu, shoot the Guardian at long range.
Feng Shu Yan Mu and I are in charge of crowd control.
Everybody else, fire.
And be careful when attacking at a high speed.
No wonder she is the top launcher.
Her Delivery Gun skill, is incredible.
Collective Delivery Gun!
The Guardian is under control.
Cap, you are amazing!
Fire.
Take that! Tyrannical Chain Punch!
What should we do now?
Keep attacking.
Just remember to miss the target.
There are so many people focusing this boss
that no one will find us.
Attack the wall.
Pretend we have missed attacks.
Be careful to avoid the boss.
There must be something wrong.
Why is the HP declining so slowly?
They have too many missed attacks.
What the hell are they doing?
The Guardian even stays still.
How could they miss the target!
Cap, what can we do?
Keep going.
Roger that.
No time left! No time left! No time left!
Don't stop. Keep going.
what's the point?
They are just grasping at straws.
Everybody, it's close to the end.
Let's work harder,
and act our parts.
Don't make Jun Mo Xiao figure it out.
Let's focus the wall.
Wtf!
We did it!
Congratulations to Strong and Stunning Guild
on achieving Guard Power Buff.
Many thanks to all the undercover.
I appreciate your great efforts on attacking the wall.
Do you want me to kick you guys off?
Let's go. The meeting is about to start.
Why do you still stay in their guild?
Hurry up. Our cap is waiting.
Lan He?
We did such a great job!
I really didn't expect
the boss somehow suddenly died.
What do you think?
We are bloody lucky!
We are not lucky at all.
It is just a game of plot and counterplot.
Plot? What are you saying?
First, counterplot.
Then, exploiting the enemies' force.
Counterplot?
WHat did we exploit?
At last, weak willows binding bigger wood.
All the enemies are blinded.
I have to say,
the whole process is really interesting.
What?
What? What?
If you guys keep confusing him,
I guess Baozi would rather kill himself.
What are you talking about?
Thanks.
Those noobs,
are all undercover.
Undercover?
Ahh I see.
They all wear a mask
in our team!
How dare they do this!
Well, thanks for their efforts on the wall,
we could
knock out the boss at the last second.
Cap, I guess
you figured out this way
after we failed first time.
That's why
you let them be in our second attempt.
Am I right?
A half.
The person who got this idea is not me,
is Luo Ji.
If he didn't find out
the DPS of the crushing wall is 103245.6,
much higher than the sum of the DPS of the other eight,
I wouldn't give it a go.
Excuse me,
you forgot two decimal places.
It should be 103245.618.
Shut up.
Just be a lamb.
103245.618?
Right.
Ok, I got it.
Everything is under your control,
but you still made Guoguo upset.
Cheers, for our boss.
Good luck to her!
Or... wish her a miracle!
Sounds good.
Well,
cheers!
The reason why they are better than you,
is not they are more intelligent,
or more capable.
It is simply that you forecast your failure
before taking actions.
If you want to be build a team,
I won't stop you.
But have you ever thought
if you are qualified enough?
Whatever... you always give up halfway.
Since you want to quit,
don't bother to push yourself.
# The road to the top is rough and long. #
# But walking with you, I will have infinite power. #
# Failure is like the dawn of victory. #
# So what if we start all over again? #
# Youth is a forever indomitable growth. #
# We are accompanied by confidence and strength. #
# Even if we flinch and bruise all over our body, #
# there will always be hope in despair. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# We must do our best to win a battle. #
# We laugh, we cry, we feel sad for failure. #
# We accompany each other to bloom in the transformation. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# To fight for our dream, we should win beautifully enough. #
# We are hugging, cheering, and ecstatic with joy for our victory. #
# We spent countless shining times. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# We must do our best to win a battle. #
# We laugh, we cry, we feel sad for failure. #
# We accompany each other to bloom in the transformation. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# To fight for our dream, we should win beautifully enough. #
# We are hugging, cheering, and ecstatic with joy for our victory. #
# And we spent countless shining times. #
# This is the most glorious battlefield. #
# We spent countless shining times. #