=The King's Avatar
=Episode 6
First of all, what about everyone
Don't worry.
After attracting his main force
We will surround again at this time.
The remaining four of them were left.
Su Mucheng and the four of them
Kill them together
Kill and win
come on, come on, come on
Okay, come on
Be happy. Be happy.
Remember, be happy
Less days
Remember tactics.
Don't worry about me
Players from both sides enter the competition map.
Jiashi vs. Lan Yu Team Tournament
Start right away
Of the two big teams
Sun battlemage Leaf of Autumn
Yu Wenzhou Warlock Su Ke Sa'er
Su Mucheng Gunner Mu Yu Chengfneg
Huang Shaotian, the swordsmen Ye Yu Shengfan
So these four star players
What kind of spark will they create?
A showdown between two strong teams
Often does not lie in personal strength
It's teamwork.
Sun has shown strong personal strength
I don't know
How will it work out?
A Leaf of Autumn Hero Pojun
The momentum is still very strong.
We see
After defeating Qaing Lin Danyu
Cut directly to warlock
Qaing Lin Danyu stands up
Interfering Leaf of Autumn's attack
This heat-sensitive missile repelled two people beautifully.
We saw Ye Yu Shengfan, the swordsman, on the other side
the swordsman, on the other side
cut directly to Jiashi's sharpshooter
Yes, the choice of both sides
They all let the strikers cut to the back row.
disturb output
Sun's reaction is very fast
Yu Wenzhou's fantastic Predicts
Pull back the Qigong master
Escape the pressure of Leaf of Autumn
Sun's personal strength is too strong
A pair of three unexpectedly also pressed the opposite
Such a situation
Is Lan Yu don't want to see
Yes, we saw
Now both sides have the same blood volume.
So this stalemate continues
Lan Yu is going to lose
The scene was very close
Lan Yu's Qigong Master Fails to Protect Back Row
Soxar is still pinned down by a leaf of autumn.
Beautiful fart
The autumn of stabbing a leaf hit Soxar.
Sun continues the momentum of just one pick three
Sun is fierce
What a fart!
Devanning
Lan Yu needs to adjust the rhythm now.
Jia Shi's Full Staff Strides Forward
Want to give Lan Yu continued repression
JiaShi is going to lose
To lose
Beautiful, wonderful
We saw the state of the sun
It is too brave
Who did you say was going to lose?
Maybe it'll be a lot worse.
You're right, then we saw it.
If Lan Yu does not make timely adjustments
This is what you said Jia Shi is going to lose
Who are you kidding?
You see, he has taken the limelight now.
Not Jiashi to Lose
Why?
Yu Wenzhou used his trump card tactics
Lock-one & release-four tactics
Devanning
Does Lan Yu Turn Back to Fight
Hello, classmate Xiang
Kindergarten officially opens
Ready to fight me, fight me
Did you fight
The account you are using now is a divine account number.
Autumn of a Leaf
Do you want to make a dragon look up for me
You don't know how to raise your head.
Then I'll call you a leaf of autumn
Are you not afraid to promise
Excuse me? Excuse me
So why don't you just change your name
Call it Sun Zhixiang
Three-stage Chopping Cyclone Chopping
Pick up, pick up
Or three sections
To cheat you chop chop chop chop
Sun! Sun
Do you really have no dignity
The little puss-head doesn't seem to be as dedicated as you are.
I'm sorry to say that.
My lovely little turtle
Let me tell you something secretly
Dad only uses one hand now
One hand is not enough
Dad's getting ready to kick
Shut up and stand still
See who abuse who ah
Well, if you can, you can come after me.
I'll count you winning if you can touch a hair of dad's head.
Who gave you confidence
Didn't you just finish one pick three
tell the truth
This choice of three is really our gift to you.
Look, it's swelling you up
The frog at the bottom of the well is cuter than you
Do you know your father
When winning three consecutive championships
It seems that you are still in the kindergarten class
Play with plasticine
So what is your position
Don't you have an ACDE number in your heart?
I killed you.
In fact, we all know that
In Lan Yu's tactics
Huang Shaotian has never been the core of tactics.
But you Sun an output core player
What about the top team members?
We saw Jiashi
After missing the Leaf of Autumn output point
The teammates' situation became very awkward
Captain, return
We see
The cooperation between Lan Yu players is very tacit
Under the leadership of Su Ke Sa'er
Lan Yu Four Directly Surrounded Jiashi Four
Prepare for a positional war
This is not good.
Jia Shi's players were hidden from view
Among various skills
Su Mucheng is rapidly losing blood
In Lan Yu's tactics
Ye YU Shengfan is always the role of harvesting.
Therefore, it is not the core of tactics.
What about the current situation
Lan Yu is very willing to see
Rain of Chaos
Su Ke Sa'er , Yu Wenzhou
Continue to suppress other's recovering
Except for Leaf of Autumn
The current blood volume of other Jiashi players
It has dropped below 40%
Director Li
Is this a lock-and-release strategy?
That's right
This is the tactic of locking one and releasing four.
How do you know what Lan Yu will use that
What is the strategy of locking and releasing four?
Because he is Yu Wenzhou
Heart
Sun is still too young
Up to now, we have not discovered the tactics of the other side.
That's right
Yu Wenzhou was indeed a master tactician.
At present, Lan Yu has great advantages.
Return quickly.
Jia Shi needs to hold off the competition
Wait for the captain to come back
Now Jiashi is leaderless
Go to this situation
If no one can stand up
If you take over the competition
I think Jiashi should be
The odds are against him.
Everyone pay attention to lean tactics
Therapists Cover with Shield Qigong
God gun shot strong kill treatment
Received
Indeed as expected treatment back to blood
Air reading hood
beautiful
Mu Yucheng leads teammates to Gather Fire
Directly take away the opposite one with the lowest blood volume.
Guardian angel soul speaker
Substitute into the game
At a critical moment
Su Mucheng stood out
Nice counterattack
At such a disadvantage
To bring back some situations
The substitute hastened to fill the position.
Song Xiao left and right flank
Don't let Su Mucheng break through
The rest of the people stood by to unpack.
OK
Sealing box
It's a curse arrow
Su Ke Sa'er began to sing
Jiashi's blood is already very low.
Quadra Kill
Incredible cooperation
Injury simultaneous settlement
In an instant Jia Shi was taken away with four heads
Jia Shi has played very well in the front
Without Leaf of Autumn
Su Mucheng can also lead teammates.
Kill a person
There is no problem with Su Mucheng's performance.
The front team has not been replaced yet.
Leaf of Autumn is very dangerous.
Jia Shi is very dangerous
Okay, we see
The Lan Yu Masses joined up with the Ye Yu Shengfan
At this time, Leaf of Autumn needs to defeat four
Dear classmate Xiang
You can't understand such a simple tactic.
In my opinion, under your eyebrows
Should amputation occur?
So go back to your kindergarten class.
Now you know
Is there a gap between you and your father Ye
But your yellow father
Do you mind dragging the hall for a while?
I'll give you one last lesson.
Teach you to be a human being.
Three
Two
One
Leaf of Autumn was taken away directly.
Now Jia Shi has only one replacement left.
Jia Shi's replacement has just arrived.
But it's too late
Lan Yu conveniently took the substitute away.
Good
Ace
So that we can congratulate Lan Yu
Win a team match
At the same time destroy jiashi
Yes, Lan Yu, who started badly
In the team match, he turned the game beautifully.
Due to the mass destruction points
This Round of Jiashi vs. Lan Yu
Lan Yu Victory
It is their play that is too dirty.
Next, please welcome the players from the two teams.
Shake hands and close the curtain
Little classmate, your father will always be your father.
Sue sister really should pay attention to diet
Eat less
Come on, come on, congratulations
Great, great, hard work.
Let's see each other next weekend
Bye-bye
This Yu Wenzhou is really awesome
With a team match
He turned over all the previous dishes.
Starting with Sun Xiang's Choice of Three
Is Yu Wenzhou's strategy
What?
There is also a strategy to let the opponent win.
One pick, three efforts and time consuming
Let the Sun's arrogance reach its zenith.
In the group war
As long as Huang Shaotian has a slight hook
Sun will explode
Even if Yu Wenzhou early in the morning
Waiting to be caught
Separated for a long time.
The boss looks at you with special respect.
Admire
Where is the beer?
Over there
It seems that our network manager
I really remember the map of Internet cafes
You are really enough
On purpose, you
You wait a minute
Ye Xiu, are you playing a copy now?
Did you find anyone
Not yet
You are looking for him. He is a swordsman.
Thanks, boss.
But ..
My swordsman will take the initiative to deliver himself to my door.
What is this man doing furtively?
Is he sick
Let's go.
Hello, hello
This handsome young man
Excuse me, are you here?
Is there a network manager named Ye
Yes, there is
And his name
With the captain of the Jiashi
No no no
The former captain is quite similar, isn't he
You call him out
My little brother said a few words back to me.
Can owe a passerby favor
I'm new here, not familiar
Two sentences back, two sentences
Good character
I see.
Is that Ye who made you angry?
It doesn't matter. I know him very well.
He's afraid of me. You call him out
Can I teach him a lesson for you
Teach him
Who are you?
Who am I? I am Huang Shao
What about you, little brother
I especially understand your mood.
Although said Ye
His words are poisonous and his mouth is cheap, and is stupid
In fact, he is rather miserable as he looks.
So I don't think you should meet him in general.
Huang Shao
Get on the computer first, get on the computer first for two minutes.
Ye Qiu
I'm telling you, you're not a gentleman.
You have changed, Ye Qiu
You didn't treat me like this before.
Won't you be gentle with me
Okay, you don't apologize to me, do you
I'm leaving. Bye
Lao Ye was a team leader before.
Now the situation is also quite poor
Forget it, forget it. I'm not going to see it like him.
Ye
You really changed your profession to be a network manager
This decision of yours
Is it too hasty?
Although it is the keyboard industry
But the calculator keyboard
Can it compare with our keyboard?
You don't forget
You were once a king
And I ask you
Why did you retire secretly?
Is there any hidden secret
Or do they bully you
After using it, you will be dumped.
So you have internal conflicts
You talk to me rubbish again
Believe it or not, I'll throw you into the trash can
Ye
This is your attitude towards me now.
Okay, then why did you call me here
You think me, swordman, is very free now
I am now
A full day's training schedule every day.
If it weren't for our pure friendship
Who will come and be rejected by you
Don't you feel a little warmth?
Can't you satisfy my little curiosity?
This
If you really want to know
Not completely
Ask for anything and ask for anything.
Startup password speed
Ye Qiu is unbeatable and most handsome.
Ask your password, who let you boast
This is really enough.
This kind of words only I can tolerate you
Come on, do you hear me
Shameless you are really
This is the password, believe it or not
Lao Ye, you have really fallen completely
Do you know?
I am embarrassed to say such words.
You made it the password
When did you become so childish
My face hurts with laughter.
Have you finished laughing
After that, you can get up
Isn't it just a copy
I closed my eyes for a minute.
You said just now that the record of this burial place is broken.
Be ridiculously high
Who is so boring
It's Jiashi again.
Your current relationship with Jia Shi
It has deteriorated to this point.
You're retired
Still chasing you in glory.
wrong
According to your old leaf's character
It must be hatred again, isn't it
You said you would help or not
Who got the head?
Sun
Well, it happens that I'm not having enough fun in the league.
Dad doesn't mind teaching him to be a person again.
Come here, Kolor. Come here
See how dad abused him so that he couldn't take care of himself.
No way, 27-class swordsman
Garbage from psycho garbage
How can I abuse this
If anyone finds out
I really can't mix it up
What a shame
You're guilty
You're not
There is no such word as "empty" in my dictionary.
But right
After all, the other side of the family is five
Jia Shi's professional player
Will the two of us
I said you have ways out
But how can five people be four
Who is the other person
Probably in preparation
Hello, Sister Su, guess who I am
Did you miss me
I've come to visit your Ye
When did you come to us?
By the way, interview insiders.
Why are you Jiashi performs so bad now
Step aside
Mu cheng entered the book at 3 o'clock on time.
Mu Cheng
The captain told you to go to the seminar room to hold a resumption meeting.
When?
Now
Sue sister foot process how so slow
Jiashi is only a few steps from here.
Women are really grinding
She is never late.
It is estimated that where was caught
She's not coming
What shall we do then
We are one person short.
Who?
I contacted the people at Lanxi Pavilion.
Who is in Lanxi Pavilion?
President of the 10th District of Lanxi Pavilion
President
Is this person reliable?
You're not very famous, are you okay?
I'm not very famous.
I'll tell you I'm very
I'm afraid everyone knows about Yu Wenzhou
No, I said I am very low-key
Is to avoid public panic
but
Ye, tell me the truth
The man's mouth is not strict
Will you do something for me
Can you guess?
Then I will not ask
If there is no problem, you can enter in ten seconds.
Start
Blue River Increases Output
Pay attention to cooling time when cold smoke is soft.
Bao Zi are as accurate as possible.
Liu Mu open up the pace I kill the monsters
Everybody stay close
Push ahead with all one's strength
Ye, this is how we fight
You can't take advantage of anything.
After all, the two are not skilled
Jia Shi is professional
What do I do
It is not the way to win.
What should I do? We're running out of time.
Think of a way
What time is it?
What the hell are you throwing?
Stop attack
Pick up all the monsters as fast as you can.
Stuck in a stone crevice
Each monster can at least
Reduces the strike time by 4 seconds.
Killing the monster is not the aim, winning is the truth.
Is the record this easy to break?
Jun Mo Xiao is a machine
Copy records are changing in turn.
Today, I went to Lanxi Pavilion again.
Lanxi Pavilion is really proud of and glorifies the Jianghu.
Everyone hurriedly applied to join
Lanxi Pavilion is called shameless
There is no lower limit for finding someone to play for.
Who doesn't find someone to play for
exactly
Shameless Guild get out from 10th District
Banning Lanxi Pavilion from Summoning God-beast King of Painting
It is estimated that the major trade associations now
all asking Jun Moxiao to join
With the back of a master record
Congratulations to the 10th district playerJun Mo xiao,Liu Mu
Bao Zi Ruqin, Han Yanrou and Blue river.
Breaking the Record of Buried Ground
Time 16 minutes 24 seconds 67
Yeah
Our Lanxi Pavilion has won again
What a great performance this is
Crazy again
Come and see my master brother's great performance.
The record is broken again.
Li is not severe. How did this happen?
Look
The strange card into the crevice
On average, each monster can play the new game
Reduce the time by four seconds.
Great, isn't it
Look at it this way
Weapons capable of changing forms
This is the end of all glory, isn't it?
Starting today
This person belongs to our Lanxi Pavilion
Yeah
Yesterday's Glory League Round 8
Jiashi clan was defeated by Lan Yu clan.
Please see the details below.
We have played several matches recently.
which were pretty disappointing
Should we have a good restocking?
Yes
It was you who played badly.
It has nothing to do with me.
Jiashi team and captain Jiashi
We can never evaluate them separately.
Not now
When I was in front with somebody else one-on-one hit
What are you doing back there
Should I send all Lan Yu players
All kick off
Only then can you win
If it weren't for my pick three got so few points
What can you bring to Jiashi
The four of us
Against one another
It is you who should reflect on yourself.
On what grounds
The limelight let him out
Congratulations to the 10th district players
Jun Moxiao, Liu Mu, Bao Zi Ruqin, Han Yanrou
and Blue river
Breaking the Record of Buried Ground
How is it possible
All right, look at my picture and help you brush it.
The record also helped you break
I've done so many things for you.
The inside story of you and Jiashi
Should you gossip with me?
What would you like to drink
Leave me alone. I know
Let me guess what you want to drink now
How do you like the one with the steam
No way
Is it because there is gas
So you can only give up in tears
Can I have this?
Also right, this sour taste
Not suitable for the bitter you now
Freshly Ground Coffee
You mean the Jia Shi, the gang of big bad guys
Don't want you.
Used up all your values
That's why you want to run away, right
There are many people in internet cafes.
Don't because of your voice
Exposed the identity of swordsman
But did you say I just guessed
Well, now I'm starting to abandon my identity.
I'm leaving now, you know
You don't regret it
Okay, bye
So I said
You just have a hard mouth and a soft heart.
I wouldn't be so fickle, would I
Internet access costs 10 yuan and coffee 20 yuan
Thank you for your cooperation.
I didn't even drink it.
You deserve the best money
Good, you fickle Ye
I'm really broke now.
I'll give you the money. I'll give you the money now.
Do you know that you are now realistic
To an appalling extent
In the future, our continents will be turned upside down.
Don't come with me
If I come to you again
I'll take your last name
Farewell
Three, two, one
Ye Shaotian is back
No, I'm looking for change, not for you.
Why don't you pick another seventy yuan for drinks
No, I want you
Accompany me to cross road I'll give you seventy yuan
Ye
Ye, I ask you
Do you know or not
What does retirement really means
I do not know
You know
You don't know.
Retirement means one year later
Do you want to rely on your previous fame again
When I came back
No team will want you again
When the time comes, only convenience stores will tell you
Welcome
Do you understand?
I don't know.
with reason
Go to a 24-hour convenience store
Is the only consolation
Ye Qiu, you wait
I'm talking to you very seriously now.
Do you know?
I remember you told me at the beginning.
What do you mean, an old man of honor like you
Every minute and second is precious.
But what are you doing now
You wasted a whole year's time.
When the time comes your hand speed is disabled into an old man
Every day now is more precious to me.
I want to finish one I must finish
Thing that have never been completed
What is it
I have a good friend.
If he were still alive
It must be one of the greatest gods of glory
He has a work of genius.
Are you talking about your umbrella?
Yes
I'd like to revive the a thousand-machine of umbrella.
Take it and add some excitement to the present glory.
Wait, what did you say
Add a little excitement to the present glory.
Glorious old people like me
Every day is precious
Every second
is too precious to waste
Really, really, say it again
I am a professional player.
Ye, you want to return
There is a whole set of strategies, isn't there
What do you think?
Ye Qiu
Welcome
I look forward to seeing you next time.
I'll tell you what, you won't
So easy
Wait for me
Is your battalion chief Yu Wenzhou
Did you find him
Answer it quickly. If you don't answer the phone, something big will happen.
What are you talking about? What will happen
I'll tell you, don't underestimate me
I can appear in front of you now.
I have already proved my present position.
So this time you're not
Slipped out of the hotel's fire escape.
Yeah
I came out of the staff passage.
The same
I'm trying to keep a low profile
Actually, it's a good habit to be afraid of the captain.
I'm afraid I was afraid of who
You don't believe it, do you
My unruly soul
There will be an outbreak sooner or later.
Wait
Ye, do you think
This scene looks familiar.
Take a look here
Catch that unruly guy
The courage is too big
Still dare to go out in training camp
Come and see this way
Is there anything here
No
Where is it over there
Not here either.
Come on, let's search over there
Good
We must catch that guy today.
The courage is too big
Good
Mr. Ye, why are you here
Are you here to help me
Help students
Isn't it the bounden duty of every teacher
This is awesome. Thank you
What's going on over there
Go over there and have a look.
Good
See? No me today
You're finished.
Mr. Ye, you are really a good man
I knew it all along.
You are different from other teachers in training camp.
You see how tall you are
Full of the brilliance of human nature
Especially the Korean teacher
inhuman
As ruthless as a Tyrannosaurus rex
Do you think I am
Miss Ye, do you know
From now on, I want to prevent fire, prevent burglary and the tachers.
Afraid of heaven and earth, I am not afraid of him.
You believe me.
My unruly soul
There will be an outbreak sooner or later.
But say it
You've done a really brave job in this matter.
would rather sacrifice myself to protect my students.
But if I remember correctly
Dear Teacher Ye
The next two months
All classes are held in plaster.
Do you want to try it too
The taste of bandages
don't you run
Should be faster
Shao Tian you are here?
Let's go and train.
Captain
Why did you call me so late?
You're all here.
What's the matter? I'm asleep
Let me show you a video. Blue River just sent it.
A  record of the 10th district
What's good about a record?
The captain doesn't know what happened.
Recently especially want to sleep
Why don't you watch it tomorrow?
Good night. good night.
You should not have been
Answer the phone in your room
Yes, it is
Captain, you know that
I like watching TV when I sleep.
So there may be ambient sound
Just this evening
Try turning off the TV to see if I can sleep.
It seems that tomorrow we have to
Have a good talk about this TV problem
I think today is the end of the day.
And I think in this war room
Or talk about some serious work
What copy did you just say, captain?
Buried Ground
The record time was 16 minutes 24.67 seconds
It is simply abnormal to make it so high.
It is indeed quite fast
But what happened inside
A new style of play has emerged
The cooperation between swordsmen and scattered people
Don't you feel familiar
Not familiar.
We don't seem to have scattered people here, do we?
Is there anyone playing with you
But we have swordsmen in  our team.
What about you, swordsman
Do you use it well, you crazy swordsman?
Let me worry about isn't it
At the moment to cut three segments
At the moment, it will be cut in five pieces.
You don't understand
Pig brain
You know what you eat every day.
Come on. Oh, what a worry
Captain, what did you just say
Speaking of which, look
The Time of Linking Silver Blade and Green Machine Gun
Very smooth
The cooperation between the two men is very tacit
Should belong to old acquaintance
Yes
Look at this man. His name is
Bao Zi Ruqin!
(which means bun in Chinese)
What's this name
I think
Give him another dumpling defense
The two of them can make their corperation as breakfast shop.
I am not talking about this person
I'm talking about
Han Yanrou
This name still sounds very beautiful
But I seriously suspect that
He may be a man
How do you pronounce these two words
Liu Mu, this must be an aunty
And I'm sure she must be an inexperienced one
and perform badly
On the contrary, I think that just now
the person you call dumplings
The man may be fine, you see
I don't think so
Is it?
I think this swordsman Liu Mu
Can catch every opportunity
created by scattered people very accurately
From this point of view
He should belong to an opportunist
And this characteristic
I have only seen it from one person
Don't you think it's very similar to you
Has it?
No?
Must be a fan of me.
I'm imitating my style of play again.
Captain, I finally know you're so late
What did you call me for
I will not be surpassed by them.
You don't have to worry
I will cheer myself up, too.
Believe me, okay
This fan is yourself, right
Be frank
Sit closer
Closer
Three, two
Am I so terrifying?
No
About TV
Captain, I really only have this one time
I think it is possible
I will not ask
Really
I said captain
Why are you so good-natured
I'm sorry. I don't care about it as much as I do
I'm so excited.
But what I want to know
You must tell me honestly
Of course!
Theman who played the copy with you.
The weapon in his hand is
It's an umbrella.
What's the name?
a thousand-machine umbrella
Attribute
Attack speed five absolute silver level
Although there are no special Attributes
But it almost covers all forms of occupation.
How is Ye Qiu these days?
He is now working as
I don't seem to know this very well.
Jun Moxiao is Ye Qiu
Is it?
Isn't it
Yes
Do you still need me to continue to ask
This is the thing captain
It's him. He just started to
invite me
I said I wouldn't go with him
Then he threatened and lured me
Then he said to take an unfinished item
Bring some umbrella back to life?
Also said to the Glory now
Add a little excitement
I advised him not to do this.
Wait a minute.
He really said so
He actually said so
I want to give the present Glory
Add a little excitement
That's what he said
It's quite serious
If I cheat you, I am Sun Xiang
Sorry, Ye
You still have time to the this after the match.
It seems that the training given to you by the team
Still not enough.
Captain, didn't you just say
Don't talk about this matter
What you say doesn't count, does it
Yes, I will
Unless ..
Unless what
You blew out that a thousand-machine umbrella.
This is stealing
Captain, this behavior
Is it a bit obscene?
Look at us, Lan Yu
In fact, we are always been aboveboard.
Will this
How can this be said to be obscene
We just borrow it and to study it.
I will return it when I finish my research.
By the way, you may not be able to beat him
Captain, you are responsible for what you say.
I can't beat him?
I'll tell you what
Beat his umbrella into a stick in minutes.
Believe it or not
Three hours to wait for you to come back
Is it really only three hours
When can you and I
finish that training camp match
Mr. Ye Qiu