=The King's Avatar=
=Episode 18=
You're using my scarf as a rag?!
A ragged, patched one
that should be recycled.
Isn't that the right one?
You really pissed me off!
The scarf is very expensive!
Where's the other half?
What have you even done
for this net cafe?
You couldn't change the bulb!
You had to be taught how to be a cashier!
I'm so pissed off!
You are really use...
Less.
You must win a person's heart
to keep this person.
How to win the heart?
Two words.
spoil him.
Use...ful!
Superman!
Master!
Master, having you in my Xing Xin net cafe
is a destined blessing derived from my previous eight lives!
Sorry for my bad temper. This scarf,
I don't need it anymore!
I'll buy another one next time.
In Spring Festival,
we shouldn't be fighting each other.
Right, Master?
- Are you comfortable? - So I'll continue.
What?
You shouldn't be doing this kind of
dirty work, menial work.
I'll do it!
Boss, leave the dirty work to me.
Let me do it!
We shouldn't be fighting each other.
Just let me do it!
Alright, alright.
Take this bank card.
Go buy a new set of clothing.
Wearing new clothes
will bring you the best of luck in the new year!
It dropped. Let me pick it up for you.
Take it. Go, go.
I'm not short of clothes.
Please use it to buy a scarf.
Stop there!
Go buy a new set, please.
You always switch back and forth between a few sets.
I'm so sick of it.
Take it!
This is an order.
Just go, go, go.
Shh, shh.
Go, move!
Guoguo, happy New Year!
Tang, happy New Year!
You don't look happy though. What happened?
Did Ye Xiu piss you off again?
So you've found out.
I couldn't hold back
my temper a moment ago
and said some hurtful things to him.
As a result, up to now he has not come back.
Tang, do you think that
he would leave for good?
Normal people would probably do that.
But when it comes to him...
I don't think so.
Masters are always so unpredictable.
The more out of line his behavior is,
the more like a master he seems.
So don't get mad under any circumstances
and tolerate his every action.
So you're back?
You even got your hair done!
Don't be shy.
There's no one else here.
Ye Xiu!
What brand of suit
are you wearing?
This wouldn't be
from the Italian handmade clothing brand by any chance?
I've only had the courage
to go window shopping there.
But now you just bought them and wore them home?
Considering my net worth,
wasn't it only fair that I spent so much money?
You are really driving me nuts!
Don't get mad under any circumstances
and tolerate his every action.
Never mind.
You should wear this style more often.
It makes you look really dignified.
Uh, well... The light bulb went out!
Please fix it!
Master...
I'm sorry, Master.
Do you want to change clothes?
Such expensive clothes are really difficult to clean
when they get dirty.
These are mere worldly possessions!
Please continue. Please continue.
It doesn't matter.
Awesome! Awesome!
Sure enough, changing clothes
makes you a different person.
Totally different from who you used to be!
Who I used to be?
Yep!
When you first came here,
you couldn't do anything.
You had to look up a guide
for changing a light bulb.
Customers made complaints against you three times day,
more punctual than the way I had three meals a day.
Master,
I didn't mean to disrespect you.
I was actually complimenting you!
It seems that I got too many things.
Maybe I should ask for help.
Miss,
our store provides home delivery
service within five kilometers.
Really?
Of course!
Please help me!
Okay!
Thank you!
Mucheng! We're in big trouble!
What happened?
Why are you in such a rush?
There's something wrong with Ye Xiu.
What's wrong with him?
He went out
and bought a suit in the morning.
When he came back,
he became a different person,
dressed like a rich guy
and speaking in a pretentious manner.
Do you think...
he has a second personality?
I didn't know that!
Then what happened?
Then...
Then he started to drop things!
He just kept...
breaking all kinds of things.
He kept breaking things!
Could he be thinking about flying away
now that he's full-fledged?
Boss, which of the two packs of chocolates
do you think is better?
They look the same!
How could there be any difference?
Even though the packagings look the same,
how do you know which one is liqueur chocolate
and which one is nut chocolate?
Forget it. When we go home and remove the packagings,
we will be able to know.
Boss, let's go!
Check, please.
Okay.
Maybe I should buy a watermelon for him to drop.
Boss, please help me grab another coffee.
I don't drink coffee.
Even if you don't drink it, someone else would drink it.
Alright, let's go!
Still unwilling to give up?
Did you bring
what I wanted?
You probably didn't bring
what I wanted, either.
=Citizen Identity Card=
You should thank me for letting you borrow my stuff.
You didn't abuse Little Dot, did you?
He eats better than you,
sleeps more than you.
When it's time to take him to exercise,
rain or shine, I never slack off.
When it's time for him to making friends,
I post on every platform for him.
Comparing the lives of you two,
he's been living in heaven
while you've been
living in hell.
The same examples every time.
Can you at least be a bit more creative?
In a word,
when will you come back home?
It depends.
I'll see you again when I have time.
And exactly when will that be?
At least,
give me three years.
There you go again.
It's been 10 years since you last came back home.
Why don't you try being a little bit nicer to me?
I'm your older brother, for god's sake.
You're only my brother when we're at home.
Here,
you are just a loser who looks
a lot like me.
Boss, so you were with Mucheng.
He smiled at me!
Look at him!
He even changed his clothes!
Do you think it means that he has decided not to leave?
Are you having a fever?
You are having a fever!
I'm not having a fever.
Please talk some sense into him for me.
Look at what he's like now.
He wouldn't survive going out in the world alone!
If he stayed at Xing Xin net cafe,
at least I would take care of him.
Come on, give it to me.
Go talk to him! Now!
The guy's moods are really erratic.
One second he's showing a poker face,
the next second he's smiling.
He's a grown-up man.
But he still needs me to indulge him.
The man has no conscience!
Were you just bad-mouthing me?
I wasn't!
I really wasn't bad-mouthing you!
I have this problem, I've got a stinky mouth.
But my heart is still very kind.
For real.
I liked it when you were bad-mouthing me!
Do you have more vulgar words?
Boss.
What are you doing?
Boss?
Holy cow!
What is happening here?
It wouldn't be the Shadow...
Clone Jutsu?
Ye Qiu.
As I told you,
someone else would drink this cup of coffee.
Isn't the setting of twin brothers
a bit too much?
I mean, are you really...
Are you really Ye Xiu?
I've always been.
So the one in a suit...
is Ye Qiu?
He stole my name to swindle and bluff.
It was outrageous!
I used to imagine that you must be
a kind-hearted girl.
But only when I met you
did I realize that
beauty and kindness coexist in you.
Tell me, did you come here
in another attempt to take him home?
No!
I came here to see if my brother needs my help.
Alright.
Even if he went on to use the 18 kinds of wushu weapons,
trying to tie or bind you up,
you would never leave,
right?
If he was really that powerful,
he wouldn't have needed to wait this long.
I knew that
he must have caused a lot of trouble out here.
So I came here to help him deal with it.
Confident as he sounds,
he'll be the one who gets dealt with in the end.
My brother must have suffered a lot out here.
I've been worried about him.
My brother hates to stay at home.
So he wants me to take his place.
I've been taking care of my brother since our childhood.
I've been playing tricks on my brother since our childhood.
He tried to ask a girl out in junior high school.
But a few days after the girl agreed to date him,
he broke up with her.
Then, you know what,
I was the one who saved the day!
What's with that smirk?
But the way I remember it,
it was you who tried to ask the girl out.
I pretended to be him to break up with his girlfriend.
His girlfriend couldn't tell me and my brother apart
and agreed in the end.
Just for that, my dad
rewarded me with a game console.
What else could I do?
I could only choose to forgive him!
What else could he do other than reconciling with me?
He was not as good an actor as me,
not as good a fighter as me.
Now I just hope that my brother
can live a better life.
That way I'll be relieved.
Your brother is doing very well now.
Even though he has retired,
the net cafe owner
has been helping your brother to build a new team.
A new team?
No wonder he didn't want to go home.
I mean, I need to go thank her.
Boss, what's most needed for our team?
Of course it's this(money).
So prepare to welcome the god of wealth.
Hold on.
So you're saying that you'd like to inves...
inves... what?
Invest in your net cafe.
Either acquisition or shareholding.
Choose a way you like.
Stop kidding me, President Ye!
This is just a tiny, shabby bar counter.
Not a negotiating table!
Miss,
I'm very serious about partnering with you.
Look at you!
Your president vibes are leaking out again!
You... Can't you just contain your vibes
and try to fit in with the lives of us common people?
President Ye, what's the point of an acquisition?
I don't even have valuable stuff here.
Only more than 100 shabby computers.
Come on, please drink some water.
The intangible assets
are of great value though.
Intangible assets?
Are... Are you talking about me?
As a president,
you really have a special way of complimenting people,
using all those technical terms.
I was talking about your team!
When you succeed,
the name of Xing Xin
will be of immeasurable value.
I decided to invest
because of the bright future of your net cafe,
not because of the 100 computers!
Miss Chen.
Are you really going to invest?
Of course.
But before we make the deal,
you have to promise me one small thing.
You are about to be my shareholder,
there's nothing we can't talk about.
Please go ahead.
It's about my brother.
Can you let go?
Let go?
Are you asking me to fire your brother?
This... This is a bit too much...
I'll see what I can do to give you
any compensation you want.
I don't want a huge amount of compensation.
It's just that you know your brother has stinky hands
that would break everything they touch.
I'm telling you,
in the few months since he came in here,
the value of the things he broke
could almost catch up with
the profits of the net cafe for half a year.
Okay, give me a price.
I'll pay exactly the amount.
I can't let you do that!
Is this amount enough?
=One million yuan=
Enough. More than enough!
You're being too generous.
Are you really that desperate to take your brother home?
I was acting
under my dad's order coming here.
So I really can't go home empty-handed.
I understand how you've been feeling.
But there is something
you may not know very well.
Your brother has become
kinda like a legend in Glory.
To say that he's able to rally multitudes with one call
would not be an overstatement.
Every one in the guild is his fan,
including the several super rich guys
who have been fighting to hire him.
So, President Ye,
it's not enough just to win me over.
You need to find a way to disband the guild.
Forget it, forget it.
It's not really my place to tell you these things.
I'm already your boss now.
Just tell me.
Alright! So I'm telling you,
the account card of our guild is kept in his room.
Hey...
What are you doing here?
What's up?
If you are interested in Glory,
I can help you sign up for an account.
But
that book is too difficult for you.
I have a better introductory textbook.
No need.
Alright.
After all, you've got to learn how to play Glory by yourself.
Do you know that Glory implements a one-person-one-card policy?
So,
the account card is the player's lifeline.
Some day when you really get an account,
do remember to put the account card in a safe place,
preferably a place that no one else can reach.
Gotta go.
A place that no one else can reach?
A place...
President Ye, what are you doing up there?
I've got nothing else to do.
So I'm checking the hygiene here.
Too dirty.
Alright.
There is a box of drinks under the bed.
Could you please carry it downstairs?
It's so heavy that I couldn't move it myself.
Drinks?
But I didn't see any drinks under the bed?
Just take another look, take another look.
Thank you!
There're no drinks?
Got it!
It hurts.
I didn't expect him to be so popular.
Master, you went online at last!
I have something to talk to you about.
Recently, the guild has recruited too many people.
The old members are constantly at odds with the newcomers.
So should we take some countermeasures
to reassure everyone?
The question is exactly what I needed!
Great timing!
Surely it's necessary!
From the perspective of management,
the biggest problem facing the Xing Xin Guild
is the uneven distribution of skill points among members
resulting in a tilt in the final distribution.
Master,
why are you suddenly speaking in a serious tone?
Seems that I have to use a cuter tone.
To solve this problem, you'll have to start with the root cause~
So... uh...
What do you mean exactly?
Disband the guild first.
When the opportunity comes,
recruit another batch of members
whose abilities are relatively more stable.
But...
If we disband the guild that has just been created,
we won't able to gain a foothold in the 10th District again!
I'll take responsibility for the consequences.
Anyway, disband first.
Don't keep any one.
If you have any doubt, we'll talk about it later.
But... But at least we should give out some red packets?
Otherwise, the group chat will be a mess!
Alright, give me an amount.
I will transfer the money to you now.
Okay! I'm disbanding right now!
The den has been destroyed.
You can no longer be the thief-in-chief in Glory!
=The Xing Xin Guild you were in has been disbanded.=
This time, I will definitely take you home.
From this moment on,
everything will come to an end.
What?
Have you given up?
You know I'm not that kind of person.
Who do you think will
appear on a poster here in the future?
It's really hard to say.
But I'm sure that
this would be the last time you came here.
You're right.
Even if I want to come here,
I'm afraid I won't even be able to get the opportunity.
Opportunities are always available,
as long as you are willing to contribute.
Why aren't you carrying a box?
Judging from your alcohol tolerance,
these are already enough.
This is the first time
I get to spend the New Year's Eve with others.
Cheers!
Big fortune and great profit!
Happy Spring Festival!
Peace all year round!
Go home soon!
Happy New Year!
Come on, here's to you!
Thank you for being so generous,
enabling our team to enjoy a fantastic Spring Festival!
What do you mean?
You were telling me to welcome the god of wealth.
What exactly should I do?
The easiest way to trick a rich heir
is to talk to them about money.
Your brother is really bad at finding stuff.
Didn't you tell us he's smart?
I may need to go in to drop a hint.
Okay.
Take it.
How is it going?
President Ye, there is a box of drinks under the bed.
Could you please carry it downstairs?
Got it!
So,
you guys have been playing me from the beginning.
You had delivered yourself to our doorsteps.
How could we turn you down?
You were the mastermind behind it all, right?
Ye Xiu... Ye Xiu.
You're really...
So he's...
drunk?
It would only take one glass.
He was like this ten years ago.
Still the same ten years after.
Are you okay?
Everyone's exhausted
after a day's work.
Let me carry... carry this guy away.
- You two, please rest early. - The coat!
They sure have the same genes!
Turns out he's as weak as his brother.
Happy New Year!
Childish!
You need to keep your innocence
to be happy every day!
Lunar New Year's Day! Big fortune and great profit!
Come on, ask for some good luck!
Here, a red packet for you!
Childish.
I've always been the one to give red packets to others.
That's your rule!
Now you're at my place.
I'm the one to call the shots.
There is a world of difference between you and your brother.
Your brother never hesitated to grab a red packet!
Here you are, Mucheng! This one is for you!
Thank you, Boss!
Boss, may a river of gold flow into your pocket.
Good luck with your business!
Seems that this place...
May you have today's glory forever!
...is not as bad as I thought.
What's that?
It's from your brother.
Another trick?
It's a gift that he deliberately prepared for you.
Since when has he become so cheesy?
Do you think you're the only person that has changed?
Over the years, he's changed a lot as well.
Except for his alcohol tolerance.
You were not drunk last night.
Right?
He has been away from home for so long.
Still thinking that it would only take
one glass for me to get drunk?
So you pretended to be drunk
to save him from the embarrassment
so that everybody could enjoy a happy New Year's Eve.
I'm not as noble as you thought.
You guys outnumbered me.
Those who suit their actions to the time are wise.
You're just being stubborn and reluctant to
admit you care about him!
Where is he?
Not even going to see me off?
Your brother...
is fixing the water pipes on the rooftop right now.
Are you sure you're not
making everything worse?
What the hell are you doing?
Making everything worse.
Do you need me to do more, just to "make sure"?
Alright.
An eye for eye,
a tooth for tooth.
Let's put an end to all the resentment in the past ten years.
Brat, do you think I would be afraid of you?
You threw away your comfortable life at home
and ended up here doing all the hard work.
You're really a man of integrity.
I did all that to leave Father to you.
Don't make my efforts go to waste.
Your efforts to trick me?
Thank you, you've worked hard!
I'd also like to thank you
for working so hard to fall into my tricks!
If it hadn't been for your tricks,
I wouldn't have ended up like this!
Like what? I only got your clothes wet.
There is a dryer in our net cafe.
Stop playing dumb. I was talking about that time when
you stole my opportunity to go to the summer camp!
You? Save it!
A person who decided to go to the summer camp
because of a Transformer toy
would only let the opportunity go to waste anyway.
Just stay at home and be a president.
I can't take it anymore!
If you don't let me play with the Transformer toy,
I'm not staying here any longer.
I am going to the summer camp!
What are you doing here?
Are you packing things up?
Where are you going?
To attend a school event?
Our teacher just informed us to go to the training.
Mr. Wang informed you, right?
That's right! Mr. Wang!
That doesn't make sense though.
Mr. Wang who had already resigned
informed you to go to the training?
Brother, these are all your favorite things,
and the money you saved up.
Are you really giving them to me?
Of course!
You're my only brother.
If not you, who else?
Ye Qiu, please come downstairs.
Go ahead.
I'll help you with it.
Son, come here.
Dad.
Stop being upset.
Forget about the broken Transformer toy.
Dad got you a new gift.
Thank you, Dad.
You like watching foreign movies, right?
So you've got to learn English well,
right?
That's right.
Brother?
=So you have prepared a lot of things. =
=I will go to the training for you. =
=Don't try to catch up with me. Don't miss me.=
= by Your Brother=
Oh, no.
Damn it, give my luggage back to me!
If I wanted to leave home because of the Transformer toy,
you were no better than me!
You left because you wanted to play Glory.
I'm not your average gamer.
I'm a professional. Understand?
I don't understand.
So, all a president does is count money.
You don't study at all?
But you have already retired
Retirement doesn't mean anything.
Just that I need to start all over again.
The sportsman's mentality. Understand?
But how are you going to start all over again?
By building a team?
Yes.
It's not that easy to build a team!
Is it easy to be a president?
You know what I mean.
It's not like the old days anymore.
The esports industry has been completely commercialized.
If you want to build a team,
the funds, resources, and contacts
are all indispensable.
Are you really prepared for what's coming?
Plus,
it's not only about you.
Like it or not,
it's going to impact many other people's lives.
You can't just hold onto your own dream.
You'll also have to consider a lot of problems in the real world!
I know.
For you. Remember to wear them.
Alright.
I've said all there is to be said about it.
I'll keep this from our family for now.
But I have no control
over the future.
Having played it for so many years,
who can still be so passionate about a game?
Aren't you tired of it?
Glory,
I won't ever get tired of it
even if I play it for another ten years.
Gotta go.
Bye bye!
Drive.
Okay.
Finally, he's gone.
He's even more high maintenance than you.
Is my brother really high maintenance?
Hold on!
Are you Ye Qiu or Ye Xiu?
Qiuqiu.
Qiuqiu?
If you were Ye Qiu, I'd be Xiuxiu.
Are you trying to fool me?
Your IQ just went online.
Just buy me a new one, for god's sake.
What was the point of fixing this old shabby one?
=Come back to invest more next year=
Ye Xiu, you're still trying to play a trick on me?