= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 17 =
So they were playing a spy game
in our team!
Who gave them the courage?
Thanks to their deliberate attack on the stone wall though,
we got to hit the mark by a fluke,
seckilled the guardian beast instead.
I think Master must have
thought up the play when we
failed in the first attack.
So he deliberately let them
mess up the second attack.
Master, have I guessed right?
You are half right.
It was not me who came up with the play,
but Luo Ji.
Excusing me for interrupting.
You just left out two digits
after the decimal point.
It should be 103245.618.
Stop talking. Shut up!
Whatever the master says is right.
Understand?
103245.618?
Correct.
I'll keep it in mind.
So you already had a plan in mind.
But you were letting Guoguo be that anxious.
Come on, cheers! To our boss!
Wish her good luck... on her exam.
Better wish her...
a miracle.
Great!
Come on!
Cheers!
The reason why they did better than you
was not that they were stronger than you,
better than you,
but that you showed yourself a red light
before you even got started.
You wanted to build a team.
I would not object to that.
But have you ever weighed
whether you are cut out for it?
Anyway, you've been known
to be a quitter.
If you don't want to do it,
don't push yourself too hard.
I'm sorry, Master,
for letting you go to the bother of seeing me off.
After the Spring Festival,
will you come back to Hangzhou?
The captain wanted me to come back.
Your captain's got a good eye.
The captain said that
even though my assassin scored negative points,
it was quite unexpected that my array ghost scored zero points.
He wanted me to go back to the team and start fresh.
He has set the starting point up for you.
You have to find by yourself
where you'd end up.
Master, I was so happy that
I got to play Glory with you.
Go ahead.
Hop on the bus quick!
Master, I'll work extra hard!
And I will remember
every word you said!
Good luck, and happy new year!
Thank you. Happy new year!
As always,
you're calm and composed even when you're leaving.
I'm here writing the final chapter of the story.
The ordinary is anything but ordinary.
The peak does not mark the end.
Don't give up
under any circumstances.
Wind and rain sweeping across the gloomy sky, I'm drowning...
It's so nice that I have you guys.
Only then did I realize that
I had always been my own hero.
I have witnessed... legends.
Anyway, you've been known to be a quitter.
If you don't want to do it,
just don't push yourself too hard!
But I have tried my best...
You didn't pass the qualification test.
And you collected the wrong guarding power.
You are not qualified to be a team boss at all.
Collecting... the wrong guarding power...
I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't know...
So go talk to the master now!
The master is leaving?!
Ye Xiu!
So you're back.
I happened to have something to tell you.
Hold up. Don't say anything.
Listen to me first.
Alright, you go first.
I'd like to...
show you around here all over again.
What do you think of this place?
It can serve as a lounge for your team.
It's a bit noisy.
Come with me.
This is a VIP room.
The door and windows are all soundproof.
It can serve as your tactics seminar room.
You would never be disturbed in any way.
It's pretty good.
Just a little too small.
What do you think of this room?
It has good lighting here.
We can make it the dormitory of your team.
Pretty cozy, right?
You can decorate it as you like.
It still needs to be decorated?
I can't wait that long.
Then check it out here.
It's perfect.
You guys can train here.
I will move
the two tables away.
Trust me.
I can get it done all by myself in a day.
I hope your team will thrive.
Why is it...
"your team"?
When you are looking for a partner,
don't go for someone like me.
You should get someone reliable and experienced.
Ye Xiu, you've got to return to the league.
I will root for you.
Even though I can't be your partner,
I am still your number one fan.
So this is what you call an effort?
I don't want you to leave here.
This place can serve as your base.
And they're all free, the rent and everything.
For real.
I won't take anything.
I...
All I want...
All I want is that you guys stay here.
Is that okay?
All being said,
I found that you're really stupid.
You just offered a deal that would only make you lose money.
I know that
I always screw up everything.
That's right.
You were the one to blame
when you collected the wrong guarding power.
And you were the one to blame
when you left without saying goodbye
and missed our victory.
But do you know
what's the most serious thing you should take the blame for?
The most serious thing you should take the blame for is that
you gave the guild a wrong name.
The Strong and Stunning  ?
The team should be named...
Xing Xin.
What... What does that mean?
Let's do it all over again.
I'm Ye Xiu, a professional esportsman.
I apply to be the captain of the Xing Xin Team.
Nice to meet you. I am...
the manager of the Xing Xin Team.
I look forward to working with you.
But I screwed up two things.
There is a third thing.
What is that?
If the above two things were screwed up,
we should do them again
together.
Cheer up.
By the way,
how many more points do you need to pass today's test?
10 more points.
Next time you have to pass it.
It's too difficult!
For real!
I'll have to prepare for the exam
while managing the guild.
I... I simply can't do it.
You're lucky that I'll get someone to help you.
Just wait for it.
Dad, I'm going to do something
earth-shattering.
I'm going to build a team.
Am I making the impossible
possible?
No matter how faraway the target is,
as long as you focus on your chosen one
and don't give up, you'll be able to hit the target.
By the way,
The team is named after...
Xing Xin.
So it really is a net cafe.
No customer here?
So... Assign me a computer.
Sorry.
The net cafe's boss is preparing for a test.
We're closed for half a day.
I'm going nuts.
I know every word in this book.
How come I don't understand anything
when the words are strung together?
I'm talking to you.
Show some respect, please?
If you don't assign me a computer,
I'll keep nagging you.
Just assign me one.
I'll leave in an hour.
Alright?
Alright, but can you promise that you'll be a quiet pretty boy
who won't even say a word?
Alright, District B, No. 25.
Do you know me?
No, I don't.
Are you the only person here
in the net cafe?
Why did he ask me
if I was the only person here?
He wouldn't happen to be this bad guy, would he?
Holy cow!
It really is him!
Hello?
Bro, where are you?
The captain is looking for you.
Didn't I tell you yesterday that
I would go on a business trip today?
No way!
You really went to Xing Xin to meet Jun Moxiao?
You are the guild master of the Lanxi Pavilion.
How could you be so easily
lured into meeting him?
Xi Zhou, listen to me.
The thing is,
why did the spys
we sent to the Xing Xin Guild
get caught so easily?
Because you were so bad at disguising.
You... You guys did a terrible job disguising yourselves.
So I had no choice but to
personally penetrate into the enemy's rear area.
I came here to find out
about the Xing Xin Guild.
How many members do they have?
How many coaches?
Who is the boss behind the curtain?
Could you guys figure out these?
You guys couldn't figure out these!
So don't bother me if you don't have anything important to say.
If I find anything,
I will talk to the captain myself.
Alright, gotta go.
This won't do. I have to call the police.
That's right.
Call the police, call the police.
Why did this computer crash again?
So annoying!
I need another computer. Another computer.
What's this nonsense?
Hello?
Hello, I want to...
Didn't you hear me shouting?
The computer crashed.
Assign me another one, please.
I'll do it!
Hold on a second.
What are the rooms upstairs for?
Those are the private rooms.
Can I play in a private room?
Yes, you can.
So assign me one!
You can just go straight upstairs.
Alright.
Don't go up and bother me, okay?
No, no, no, don't do it!
Professional team manager?
Are you preparing for the test?
I've taken the test before!
It was so easy!
I'm telling you,
you only need to memorize
all of the exam outlines,
and then read the industry analysis tables multiple times.
Then you'll be able to pass it with your eyes closed!
Is the esports industry
really so hot these days
that even you, a net cafe attendant,
are joining our grand Glory?
Good, good, good.
Alright, good luck!
You can do it!
No, no.
I have to talk to Ye Xiu.
I need to get Ye Xiu and Bao Zi back here.
Hello, Ye Xiu?
Listen to me,
We have a weird guy
in the net cafe now.
Hello, boss.
Master!
We just got out of the supermarket.
Let me help you.
It's alright. It's alright.
Pick them up.
Okay.
Boss,
please keep going.
I'm telling you,
we have a extremely weird guy
in our net cafe.
Boss?
Master!
The connection is bad.
I'm telling you,
I suspect that he may be a wanted criminal.
No, he is a wanted criminal.
But don't worry,
I behaved normally("ziran").
What? Cumin(also pronounced as "ziran")? Boss?
Cumin?
Is the boss preparing a barbeque?
Boss, please continue.
Come back as soon as possible, both of you.
I am worried that he will escape("tao").
Peach(also pronounced as "tao")?
Go, go, go!
Let's go!
I will come back later.
As expected, they're going to build a team.
The lineup,
time schedule,
the guarding power, dungeons,
3D maps, simulation diagrams.
I...
Alright, Jun Moxiao!
So you did know that
there were undercovers in the guild,
but you still had the audacity to use us as coolies.
I will take pictures of everything
and study them later.
Here we go!
There's a person in the room!
Why are you locking the door?!
An excellent citizen
who uses her wisdom to trap the wanted criminal.
Don't think that I wouldn't be able to recognize you
when you're wearing a wig.
This is an evil net cafe!
Who gave you the right to lock me in there?!
I'm telling you not to come over!
You... Don't come near me, you wanted criminal!
Who is a wanted criminal?
I'm warning you!
Are you calling the police?
I should be the one to call the police!
You? Calling the police?
You guys are having a jolly time, huh?
As a young, successful, handsome man
who has luxuriant hair,
do I look anything like this bald wanted criminal?
See for yourself. Any similarities?
Can't see it clearly?
Let's zoom in.
You'll be able to see it when we zoom in.
Hold on.
My name is Xu Boyuan.
Is his name Xu Boyuan?
I am a kind netizen.
First, I didn't break the law.
Second, I didn't default on the internet fee.
If you don't give me an explanation today,
I'll go to the Consumers Association to
file a complaint against you.
Speaking of the internet fee,
I'd like to check with Mr. Xu
about your bill.
Go ahead.
Two hours in the VIP room
on the second floor.
A total of 50 yuan. Is that right?
The two hours...
Alright.
I put a deposit of 100 yuan to the bar counter.
I didn't exceed the time limit. Nor did I overspend.
Right?
You damaged a door lock on the second floor
during the consumption.
It's worth 130 yuan.
Alright, I'll pay for the damage caused by me.
In Xing Xin net cafe,
all the door locks were uniformly configured.
So we'll have to change all the door locks in the whole net cafe.
There're ten doors in total,
worth 1,300 yuan.
Why do you have to change all of them?
Oh, right.
You accidentally broke the vase here
when you went down the stairs with the boss.
This vase iteself is not expensive,
but the water inside
splashed onto the socket next to it.
Now the circuits downstairs all burned out.
Nonsense!
The...
Nothing burned out!
I'm telling you...
The power outage has caused us
to be unable to do our business as usual
and the loss is quite serious.
Don't lie to me on this.
Before I came in,
I saw at the door that
you are not open today.
Now,
we're open.
I...
In fact, our net cafe
usually is very busy.
The turnover in half a day is at least
20,000, 30,000, 40,000, or even 50,000 yuan.
I'll give you a discount.
Let's make it 35,000 yuan.
After deducting the deposit...
The total is 36,550 yuan.
With the discount...
It's 35,000 yuan.
Card or cash?
What... What is this nonsense?
Don't lie to me.
However,
I'm okay if you are willing to pay the debt by labour.
I heard that you had worked as
a team manager for some time.
So you should know
how to pass the license test.
Lan He.
Why did...
You... How did you...
You... Are you Jun Moxiao?
Clever.
So it's you!
I've been looking for...
Oh, so it's... It's you...
You are Jun Moxiao!
But how did you know that I'm Lan He?
In Lan Yu, you're the second smartest guy
after Yu Wenzhou.
So I'll leave our boss in your hands.
Good luck, Lan He!
He's getting increasingly better at making deals.
No wonder he's the master I admire.
He's becoming more and more like me.
He's got such a refreshing character
that remains the same whether online or offline,
as expected of Lan He.
Master, the boss you're talking about is...
The boss is...
I fell into their trap instead.
I came here to spy.
How did I end up giving a lesson?
No way, no way.
Are you ready?
Mr. Lan, can we start the class now?
Well, Ye Qiu.
Even though you are a master,
there are some things
I have to explain to you.
I came to this city
on a business trip.
It's just a coincidence that
I came to this net cafe.
It's an even bigger coincidence that I met you.
And, I still have a very
important job of my own to do.
I understand.
There's a meeting.
I have been preparing for it for quite some time.
It's very important.
I may have to leave right now.
For how long?
One hour.
Okay, good. Go ahead.
Drop the act. Just give the lesson, okay?
Go now, quick.
Esports is the best combination
of the internet and sports.
Esports competition has now become
a recognized
sports competition worldwide
and a formal event
of the Asian Games as well.
Esports teams
are one of the pillars of the esports industry.
If we want to build a team that enjoys longevity,
a feasible and flawless
operation mechanism is essential.
So, a feasible and flawless operating mechanism
is first and foremost related to financing.
The guilds in Glory
provide essential support for the esports teams.
The teams can't thrive without the supplies the guilds provide.
Therefore,
the development of the guild
is an important foundation for a team.
For a newly established guild like yours,
the most important thing is that...
So well-behaved.
I have never seen her
studying so hard.
And I have never seen anyone
who likes to play tricks more than that guy.
You guys who are always thinking about
tricking others are really despicable.
And you guys who work as tutors are often too negligent.
Oh, right, you have to learn how to
recruit people in Glory.
Members of this type are the most loyal ones.
They are also the elite members
who will contribute most to
the later development and construction of the guild.
They are the guards of the guild.
The group admins will also play a critical role.
Instead of making the moodmakers
who are active in the group
the group admins,
we should choose those who love the guild,
have a strong sense of responsibility
and certain management skills,
especially those who are able to
coordinate the conflicts between the members of the guild,
who have become the traffic lights
and lubricants of the entire guild.
The most important thing is that
you have to learn how to set goals
and build membership systems...
So you're gonna leave without saying goodbye?
Master, my bro,
I... I am in a hurry to attend the meeting.
I've got to go now.
Have you taught the boss anything?
Master, my bro, I've really tried my best.
I told her everything I should and shouldn't.
The only thing I didn't do was
giving her the Lanxi Pavilion as a gift.
So it seems that our boss is really not cut out for it.
She really isn't.
So it seems that the license test is a great challenge for her.
She definitely will not pass it.
So it seems that I can't leave the guild in her hands.
Of course you can't.
So it seems that you're the only one able to manage our guild.
Of course I'm...
No,
I didn't mean that.
Give the position back to her
when the boss passes the exam.
Master, my bro! I didn't mean that!
Want a salary?
No... No!
I knew it!
Lan He, you're the most loyal friend!
It's not about being loyal!
I have my own job to do!
Besides, later, I'll have to...
Later, I'm going to video call Yu Wenzhou.
Join me and say hello to him?
No need, no need. I gotta go.
Have some breakfast before you leave?
I can't afford to have breakfast here. I can't afford.
So I'll leave the guild in your hands!
Good luck!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
A thief!
Stop!
Are you okay?
Get up.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I have to go now.
Thank you!
No worries, no worries.
Saying you don't need it, you deliberately left it to me...
Your backpack!
Zoning out?
Tang, look at this ornament.
Do you still remember?
Are you trying to remind me of
how stupid a mistake I had made
that you missed the most
important test of your life?
Look! I rarely have a day to
tidy up the room!
Alright, stop hiding.
These are all just props
you have been preparing,
right?
To be honest, I never wanted to
take the test.
So helping you catch the thief
and grabbing the wrong backpack
became the perfect excuse for me to
lose the exam admission ticket.
After that, every year during my vacation,
I asked you to tutor me,
just so that you would spend more time with me.
I tried so hard to prepare for tests.
I tried so hard
to make myself worthy of being your friend,
despite the fact that I never passed the tests.
Look, these, and these.
I put all my IQ points into these.
Maybe taking the professional manager test
is a better choice for me.
Alright. Actually,
I've known all your ulterior motives
since the first time I tutored you.
I didn't know you were so sharp!
Coming here to tutor you has been,
actually, an excuse for myself as well.
I come to Xing Xin
looking to escape from something.
No matter what you're trying to escape from,
please come here more often.
I probably won't be able to come here often.
Why?
The Berklee College of Music
sent me an invitation.
I'll have to leave after the Spring Festival.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
To be honest, I had been struggling to make the decision.
But I didn't want to miss
such a good opportunity.
Shouldn't you be happy for me as well?
Guoguo,
both of us should make a choice now.
Time flies.
In the blink of an eye, the Spring Festival comes.
People said goodbye and left for hometown one by one.
Only Ye Xiu didn't leave for unknown reasons.
Actually, I...
Looking forward to your next visit!
Take care of yourself.
This is the first Spring Festival
I get to spend with
Ye Xiu and Mucheng.
I have to maintain a nice image.
The coat doesn't look so good, right?
Not good, not good, not good.
No more coats.
Maybe I should settle for this one.
The color looks pretty nice.
Still less than satisfactory though.
I am the manager
of the team now.
I should at least wear fancy outfits.
It's not enough if I only have
a scarf from a luxury brand.
Fashion taste highlights your character.
People will judge your value based on your character.
Piggies, I'm counting on you!
How is it going?
Oh my goodness.
It's covered with dust.
We've run out of rags.
Please go to my room and find an old piece of clothing.
Cut a few pieces from it and use them as rags.
What would count as an "old" piece of clothing?
A ragged or patched one.
One that you know
it should be recycled at first glance.
Good job!
Stop it!
What's that in your hand?
You're using my scarf as a rag?!
A ragged, patched one
that should be recycled.
Isn't that the right one?
You really pissed me off!
The scarf is very expensive!
Where's the other half?
What have you even done
for this net cafe?
You couldn't change the bulb!
You had to be taught how to be a cashier!
I'm so pissed off!
You are really use...
Less.
You must win a person's heart
to keep this person.
How to win the heart?
Two words.
Spoil him.
Use...ful!
Superman!
Master!
Master, having you in my Xing Xin net cafe
is a destined blessing
derived from my previous eight lives!
Sorry for my bad temper.
This scarf,
I don't need it anymore!
I'll buy another one next time.
In Spring Festival
we shouldn't be fighting each other.
Right, Master?
So I'll continue.
What?
You shouldn't be doing this kind of
dirty work, menial work.
I'll do it!
Boss, leave the dirty work to me.
Let me do it!
We shouldn't be fighting each other.
Just let me do it!
Alright, alright.
Take this bank card.
Go buy a new set of clothing.
Wearing new clothes
will bring you the best of luck in the new year!
It dropped.
Let me pick it up for you.
Take it. Go, go.