= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 38 =
= Xing Xin =
Leaping onto the wall,  Qiao launches a counterattack...
while Xiao is alternating his skill strikes.
Playing a Ghost who relies on tactics,
the choice of skills and its casting time are important.
But Arrays of Ice and Plague may not enough to turn the tide.
He should use more Arrays of Ghosts...
and cause high damage to enemy by the Feast of Ghosts.
What happened?
Why did Xiao rush in the opposite direction?
Tell us why, Captain Yu.
Director, please replay these frames.
Yeah, it's here.
Xiao was shooting with his rifle at the same direction,
then hit the air with his Mechanical Punch.
But nobody was here, Captain Yu.
Let's see from Xiao's view.
What...
Shaotian, have you seen it?
It must be an afterimage that looks very real.
It's not surprising that Xiao mistook it for Qiao.
But I think it must be a coincidence,
because a Ghost has no skill creating an afterimage.
So Xiao was just unlucky and fell into the trap for no reason.
I don't think so.
The afterimage just appeared in a right place at a right time.
It was Visual Deception.
Visual Deception?
What the hell is it?
These frames just frightened me.
Why was it so weird?
I don't know.
Ask Qiao by yourself when he comes back.
You don't know it?
You know everything on Glory, don't you?
You said that these kids could easily surpass us.
Qiao just did something amazing.
He's invented a new tactic for the Ghost.
Wei,
Rookies can't be underestimated.
The cooling time for his skill attack will be over.
My last chance.
= Equipment, Rucksack =
Wait! Xiao has cast the Mechanical Tracking before dying,
which is dodged by Qiao.
But Xiao's Bounding Mines are triggered.
When did he plant them? Wonderful!
= A draw =
This was an awesome game in the Arena Contest.
Jia Shi has eliminated another opponent. Congratulations.
Meanwhile, Xing Xin finally erased Jia Shi's best player.
Xiao fought back in despair,
so they both died.
But Xiao has eliminated three opponents.
- Long Live Captain Xiao! - You said you'd be low-keyed.
Doesn't matter. It's dark here.
= A Draw =
Thank you, sir.
Yifan has changed a lot.
He used to regard everyone as his teacher,
and always asked us for help.
Now he has invented a new tactic,
and scored a key point for his team.
In Yifan's eyes,
it can't be more normal.
Every game and every tactic all make him to enjoy Glory.
Xing Xin is really a miraculous team.
I don't think it's miraculous.
Every day, he practices 3 extra hours.
In every hour, he plays 2 extra games.
In every game, he tries to use a different tactic.
So...
Yifan is making progress,
but we're marking time.
Our captain said...
in eSports, there would never be a successive winner...
but people who never stop.
Do you mean we should go back to practice?
Because of Qiao's extraordinary performance,
Xing Xin has eliminated Xiao with 3 players...
- You're great! - Awesome!
Who will be sent from both sides to next game?
Will Xing Xin show its trump card?
We're looking forward to it.
Next game will be the match point of the Arena Contest.
= Jia Shi vs Xing Xin =
Can Xing Xin turn the tide?
The 4th player from Xing Xin is Ye Qiu,
former captain of Jia Shi,
and the leader of the first champion team in Glory's history.
The fateful game is about to begin.
- Awesome! - Captain.
- You can do it! - Captain! Captain!
- We'll win!  -  We'll win!
You can do it...
Captain, there is something on your hair.
Let your hair down!
I see, let my hair down.
- Come on, Captain. - You can do it.
The player from Jia Shi is...
Qiu Fei.
- It's him. - He may be not well known by everyone here.
Qiu has been promoted from Jia Shi's second team this season.
What's interesting is that Ye used to be Qiu's teacher.
It means this will be a wonderful teacher-pupil fight.
Captain Yu, do you think whether Qiu can beat Ye today?
To beat a Freelancer, a Battlemage has to keep up with his speed.
Freelancer is very quick, but Battlemage...
Ye, I tell you this is the final.
You have to do your best to beat your pupil.
If you throw the game today, you'll cry tomorrow.
You have to beat... What?
Your advice may not be heard.
I just want to tell him.
= The 9th Challenge of Glory =
Everyone, Ye and Qiu are sitting down.
Their characters enter the map. The game is kicking off.
Both players are familiar with each other's style and details.
The game would go straight to the point without probing process.
Ye Qiu, my master.
What are you thinking?
How to defeat you.
Immodest.
Are you overjoyed to your first formal game?
Shall I let you hit me first? So you won't cry later.
Mr.Ye from Xing Xin,
your rubbish is useless for me.
Still an unpleasant kid.
As Captain Yu expected,
both of them rush directly to each other without any probing.
Because Jia Shi has 2 more players than Xing Xin,
Ye's task is very arduous.
He has to eliminate as many opponents as he could,
or Xing Xin is likely to lose the Arena Contest.
Shattering Palm-attack. Very fluent.
This is a basic connection between attacks.
But it's not easy to make a smooth connection like this.
Combat Form is launching Destroying the World,
and has precisely intercepted Ye's attack.
- Good job. - Awesome.
CF's control over the fight is beyond our imagination.
He is good at it.
Even the Master of Glory has no chance to escape now,
and has to wait passively.
...19,20,21
Qiu has given Ye 21 successive hits.
Both are attacking. Ye has disappeared.
Without target, Qiu is confused now.
But he is cautious and doesn't move around.
Where will Ye pop out from?
From the ground.
Ninja's Burrowing.
You let me see your weakness when you were hitting me.
You're not the guy who can erase me with one blow.
- Ye's Dragon Tooth repels Qiu's attack. - Too slow.
Impossible. With same DT, why could yours repel me?
Don't blink and take a good look.
Ye's DT strikes Qiao again.
Attacks are broken. Connect again.
Ye has controlled the fight completely.
Now it becomes the skill show of Freelancer.
In the air, Qiu can't escape.
Ye's Umbrella transforming and skill attacking are perfect.
= 15, 16 successive attacks =
At the middle of the DT attack,
he cancels the skill and casts it again.
The DT launched later strikes its target first.
Now, do you understand it?
20, 21...
The attacks are going on. 26, the last strike.
With 26 successive attacks, Ye has erased CF.
Congratulations to Ye. He has won the game.
Xing Xin has won another match.
Now it's 4:6 and Jia Shi is ahead for the time being.
If you love Glory,
= Training Result =
love everything it brings you.
Whether it's pain, difficulty or sadness.
I can't be responsible for your life,
but I'd like to be...
= I have owed Qiu Fei a glory =
= Ye Qiu =
one of your choices.
= Blowing Wind =
Because our glory lies...
where our swords are pointing.
Thank you.
= Combat Form: Thanks. =
Good boy.
Nothing to tell me?
It's your turn.
What did you tell Su Mucheng just now?
Come on, you have to go.
Are you afraid you'll be defeated?
I'm not you!
You were beaten by Ye and decreased half of his Hit Points.
It's not honorable for me to defeat half of him.
But can you defeat half of him?
You'll see how I eliminate your teacher.
The 3rd player from Jia Shi is Captain Sun Xiang.
This is the first duel between two captains of Jia Shi.
The fight between the old and new master could be much fiercer.
Who will win? Let's wait and see.
In the 5th game,
= The 9th Challenge of Glory =
Sun, Jia Shi's Captain, will fight against Ye, Xing Xin's leader.
This is a fight between the new and old captains.
The character, Leaf of Autumn,
which used to be played by Ye for years,
now is played by Sun, is the opponent of Ye today.
I don't know how Mr. Ye's feeling now.
To fight against his former closest comrade,
what will he do?
We needn't probe each other.
Let's fight directly in the square.
A fight without a trick?
OK.
Let's fight directly.
The game begins.
Without any tactical movement,
Sun is rushing to the center of the map.
Fighting against Ye Qiu using LOA in formal contest,
is likely something he has been yearning.
- But Ye is approaching in a roundabout way. - Where are you?
No rush. I want to increase my HP.
Now, Ye's HP is lower,
so he doesn't want to fight fiercely at first.
What is it? Is Ye Qiu healing himself?
Increasing his HP before the duel,
Ye has gone too far.
Sorry.
Freelancer only has the ability to heal himself.
Can I take some time to do it?
I'll wait for you.
Cooling time will be longer because my skill level is lower.
Then I have to tell you,
how can you fight against me...
if you use all your Mana Points to heal?
Ordinary chopping?
You're right.
I’ve got only half MP.
Increase it.
Is Ye increasing his MP? That's over the line.
- Nobody will stop him? - What is Sun doing?
- Why isn't he attacking? - Attack him.
The captain is a real freelancer.
Brilliant tactic.
Unusual.
Shameless.
He deserves to be called Master.
Come on, Jia Shi! Come on, Jia Shi...
Now!
Long live Xing Xin! Long live Xing Xin! ...
OK, let's begin.
Is 70% enough for you?
It's not appropriate to keep you waiting for a long time.
In addition, 70% is enough to beat you.
I can't beat you embarrassingly easily.
That's what I want to tell you.
Are you giving me a sneak attack?
Dragon out of Sea misses hitting Ye.
Sun launches a lethal attack,
but unfortunately, it is dodged by Ye.
Only Ye Qiu can dodge the attack with his precise Z-movement.
Chaser attack?
These Chaser attacks are not lethal. They're useless.
It's Sun's tactic.
He didn't mean to show off his lethal skill, DOOS.
He wanted to cover the tracks of Chaser with the wave effect,
so our captain can't dodge his attack.
Using the lethal skill as a cover, attack with an ordinary one.
He's really getting smarter.
After a round of attacks, nobody can get the upper hand.
Another close combat.
Debris has triggered Landslide and its attack range is extended.
Ye is hit.
It seems that Ye is still a bit strange to LOA,
which is level 75 now.
I wonder how much advantage Sun can take from here.
You'll feel worse.
The speed of Sun's spear has been greatly improved...
when the weapon reaches level 75.
LOA's attacking speed...
now can catch up with the skill speed of Freelance,
It seems, besides the character's promotion,
Sun has become stronger.
The speed of the fight is getting faster.
This is actually an Action per Minute contest .
Attacking and defending, their APMs become faster and faster.
Have they reached their peak values of APM?
Our captain's APM is so fast.
Ye has no lethal skill now.
Captain shouldn't give up his advantage...
and contest APM with the Freelancer.
He is not acting on impulse.
He believes he can beat Ye in this way.
He's just carrying out his tactic.
Once the APM reaches the peak value, you'll become slower.
If he plays too fast now, how could he cope with the next game?
What if he hasn't peaked yet?
- Hasn't peaked yet? - You don't know...
how much effort Sun has put into preparing for this game?
Shattering Palm-attack. Ye is hit.
What problem?
It was obvious Ye could dodge the Palm-attack. Why did he fail?
He could have dodged it, but he didn't expect it.
Jia Shi has upgraded the equipment of LOA for the final game.
His striking range, speed, attack and defense are all improved.
That means Ye in fact doesn't know the present LOA at all.
It's very unfortunate for Ye.
Sir, why are you so weak now?
In this way, how can you beat me embarrassingly easily?
LOA has been attacking Ye Qiu,
who seems to be a little overwhelmed by his opponent's attack.
In this way, Ye will lose the game.
Now Ye's HP is very low,
and he can't make any counterattack.
Ye is in danger.
Just like a non-player character,
you should trigger Escaping when your HP decreases to 10%.
Bleeding Escaping?
Good idea.
It's a golden opportunity, I can't let you down.
Gatling Gun is shooting and forcing Sun to dodge.
Dodging the shooting, Sun tries to approach Ye's back.
Unfortunately, he is hit by a flying shuriken.
When did Ye throw the shuriken?
A flying shuriken.
Why didn't I just notice it?
My God!
What happened? Ye has turned the tables.
Your new equipment made a lot of troubles for me.
But a trouble doesn't mean it must be a bad thing, does it?
Your moving speed has increased by 3.
Attack range has increased by 5.
Physical resistance has increased by about 200.
Stiffness time has decreased by 0.01 sec.
Pretending to be weak, you're just looking for my weakness.
I take back what I said.
It's really difficult to beat you, Sun Xiang.
But, from now on,
you'll have no chance.
Wonderful! it's a fight between gods.
Sun is launching Dragon Soaring, a decisive attack.
Ye has dodged it. Will the dragon's head raise?
Its head is turning!
Ye has been hit by the new attack from DS, Dragon Head Turning.
Jia Shi is really a top team.
It represents the highest level of Battlemage in Glory.
Captain, well done!
Game over.
Sun Xiang seized the last chance to...
= Mucheng =
- Come on! - Come on!
Ye Xiu.
What? The winner is Ye Qiu!
It's Ye who has finally won.
The result of the game was entirely unexpected.
Let's take a look at what happened.
Using the grabbing function of DS, Ye conveyed himself to Sun,
and gave Sun a Sky-strike when he was in the time of stiffness.
To be precise, just using his Blocking below level 20,
Ye took back his 0.03% HP.
With this 0.03% HP, he won the game.
It's really incredible.
It's really a wonderful game.
The 0.03% HP has determined the result of the game.
I declare that the winner of the game is Ye Qiu.
- Master! - Awesome!
Keep training, and keep breaking through your own limits.
Sun Xiang has become a real master now.
This time, I'm not only gonna beat Ye Qiu,
but tell everyone that I'm not relying on LOA.
Even if we're on the same starting line,
I'll finally win.
Jia Shi will win! Jia Shi will win! ...
I said you shouldn't be too proud.
Now LOA has lost to him.
Not LOA.
I've lost to him.
Today, I've realized...
I can't be made great by a character,
Instead, I should make the character great.
He's really awesome.
Of course.
Someday,
let's beat him.
Ye, why are you leaving? You've still got 0.03% HP.
Increase it. Anyway, you're shameless,
= Ye Qiu has given up the game. =
just do it again.
Or does it mean you want to give your rookies a chance?
Good job, Captain.
Because of his HP, Ye has given up the next game.
His substitute is Wei Chen, a newcomer.
Captain Wei!
He can't be called a newcomer. He's about over thirty, isn't he?
You were heard, bastard.
A newcomer doesn't mean a young guy.
And as far as the game is concerned, it's really new for you.
Cut your crap!
Now, give it up for Shen Jian from Jia Shi.
- Come on! - OK.
Shen Jian! Shen Jian! ...
Warm up?
For beating him?
I needn't warm up.
I'll beat him. I promise.
ASAP.
In the 6th game,
the last player from Xing Xin is Wei Chen,
the Warlock Windward Formation.
The player from Jia Shi is Shen Jian,
the Striker Successive Strikes,
Will the veteran Wei beat two players and turn the tables?
Let's wait and see.
Both characters have entered the map. The game begins.
For a Warlock, controlling and using the shooting distance...
is key to fight against a Striker.
Captain Wei knows Warlock inside out.
For a Striker, only by finding a chance to attack at close range,
can he defeat the warlock.
As expected, SS is rushing toward WF at first.
WF uses Magic Missile to interrupt him.
SS is approaching.
Jumping back quickly, WF locks him with Six-light Prison.
SS's HP is decreasing dramatically.
Though Wei is older, his attack is precise.
We all know the veteran Wei is good at draining his opponent.
But in this game, he is fighting quickly.
Bao Zi.
What happened...
with Wei's hand?
Hand? Nothing happened.
Look, his Light-prison was cast precisely and securely, right?
Though his HP is low, SS is fighting aggressively.
He's looking for the chance to decrease WF's HP.
Approaching again. WF defends with Magic Mirror.
SS's High Kicking has hit WF again.
With little HP, SS is still rushing.
WF's Magic Missile. Good.
SS is dead.
= Xing Xin =
Xing Xin has won another game.
The veteran Wei is still powerful.
He has scored two points cleanly for Xing Xin.
See? He has won, hasn't he?
Nothing is wrong with Captain Wei's hand.
He can even beat three opponents. Trust him.
I have to admire Captain Wei for his ability.
Still powerful.
Facing the healthy opponents,
can he beat two of them and narrow the scoring gap with Jia Shi?
Let Wei abandon it.
Why? He has won.
How important are the hands of a player?
You should know it.
If he doesn't stop now,
his entire career could be ruined.
OK.
You're right.
Captain Wei...
His hand is still injured.
Wei's hand has never been completely healed...
since it was hurt when fighting against Zhu Xian.
The doctor said he had to rest for a period before competing.
Ignoring it, Wei was injected with anesthetic before the game,
and told me to shut up.
Captain Wei said that Xing Xin needed his help.
So he had to compete in the game and had to win it.
Because...
it could probably be his last game.
Either living with a regret,
or making a last attempt,
he has actually made the choice...
since the day he joined Xing Xin.
Wei.
Until we take the championship,
there'll be no last game.
In the last Arena game, the player from Jia Shi is Su Mucheng.
The best Launcher in League vs. the first Master.
That'll be a fight between magic and gunpowder.
Who will win the Arena Contest? This game will tell us.
Just a provisional tactical change. It's normal.
Don't be too surprised.
Wearing Jia Shi's uniform and sitting in its bench,
it means you're ready to do your best for Jia Shi.
Relax.
Mr.Tao.
You're putting Mucheng in a dilemma.
You can't send her in the last and sensitive game.
She would be suspected of having thrown the game,
even if she hasn't.
If she doesn't want to be suspected,
she'll do her best.
But in the competition,
any mistake you make would be interpreted as throwing the game.
She has only one choice:
she has to win.
Isn't it exactly what we want?