= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 13 =
Today,
on the All-Star Game,
you defeated your own captain.
Anything you wanna say?
I... I never thought I could win.
Captain, I'm sorry, I...
Yingjie,
It's for you to shoulder the responsibility of Weicao's future.
Let's give the applause
to the two players again.
Are you satisfied with your performance today?
Gao Yingjie, do you think
Is it a fluke or strength
to win the game today?
Ying Jie did very well today.
He gave full play to his strength.
Captain Wang Jiexi,
are you really sure
you didn't intentionally lose today?
That's his strength.
Player Wang Jiexi,
When will you give away
Wang Bu Liu Xing's account card?
That's all.
Player Wang Jiexi,
Please answer the question directly. Thanks.
Captain Wang Jiexi,
you...
Do you really believe that
Gao Yingjie can be the future of Weicao?
I believe that one day
each of you will be able to defeat me.
Today, we witnessed the whole process of
the rise and blossom of an alliance new star.
Captain.
Are you all right, captain?
...on the stage of All-Star Game's history.
You are the future of Weicao.
Sit down, please.
Yingjie.
I still feel like a dream.
How could I win the captain?
Yingjie,
believe in yourself.
That's your strength.
Now let's welcome the next newcomer challenger,
Qiao Yifan, who is also from Weicao,
Let's look forward to the wonderful games he brings us.
Welcome Qiao Yifan.
Yifan.
The one who played the Dungeon with you.
He belongs to Weicao.
He is...
He wanted to prove himself.
Sorry, captain.
I was going to tell you in advance.
But I really want to play once.
If you want to play,
then play well.
This way.
Go for it, captain.
Go for it, Yebo.
Go for it. Go for it.
Go for it.
Go for it, Yingjie.
Go for it, Weicao.
Yifan.
Yingjie.
He is the jungling...
What?
Nothing.
I mean... are they rebellion together?
Another Weicao's player again.
Qiao Yifan, also from Weicao,
Let's look forward to the wonderful games he brings us.
Welcome Qiao Yifan.
Qiao Yifan's opponent to challenge today
is Xu Kong team's captain,
who is the best at Array Ghost,
Li Xuan.
He picked the wrong opponent.
Both of you are standing beside me now.
First of all, I would like to ask Yifan
What's your feeling to challenge the senior today?
Thanks for your instruction.
And how about you?
Take good care of yourself.
Two players has already sparked
before the game started.
Let's invite them to
the battle seats.
Qiao Yifan from Weicao team
is using the Array Ghost Yi Cunhui.
We know that
Array Ghost don't have much advantage in one-on-one.
His value is mainly reflected in team games.
After all, Array Ghost has a very good supporting effect.
But he's challenging
Li Xuan's Feng Shan Gui Qi from Kong Xu team.
As the best Array Ghost of the league,
He actually used Execute Ghost this time.
I don't know how Qiao Yifan would feel
if he knows about it.
OK. The game will begin soon.
Yi Cunhui, operated by Qiao Yifan from Weicao,
versus Feng Shan Gui Qi, operated by Li Xuan from Xu Kong.
The map of this game is Exile Land.
it's a regular map for Ghost Swordsman.
Right, if Yi Cunhui can use the terrain
to lay out the Ghost Array ahead of time.
There's an opportunity to take the opponent down.
The best Array Ghost of the league he againsts
would not give him such an opportunity.
Well, we see both players
are moving into the Exile Land.
Neither side attack immediately
after entering the game,
They are surveying the terrain,
which means that the dependence of Ghost Array
on terrain is very strong.
Right. Making good use of terrain to create advantages
is particularly important for Ghost Swordsmen.
Feng Shan Gui Qi takes the lead in attacking.
As the best Ghost Array,
He knows exactly where the weakness of it.
If he can get the first hand,
there will be great advantages.
The terrain Yi Cunhui chose was very open.
The blind areas are rare,
but it also exposes itself.
He's still a newcomer.
Found him.
Feng Shan Gui Qi did not choose
to rush directly, but tactical positioning.
He found Yi Cunhui's blind spot.
Waiting for the opportunity.
The veteran is surely experienced.
Feng made a sneak attack.
Facing the best Ghost Array, Li Xuan,
he seems to be suppressed.
He can barely withstand
when he is directed against.
Ghost Array was completely conquered by Execute Ghost.
We see that Qiao Yifan's HP
is dropping rapidly.
The speed of Feng Shan Gui Qi is very fast.
and gave him no chance to breathe at all.
Cross sidestep.
Unexpectedly, Qiao Yifan cut him sideways
with the skill of an assassin.
Exactly counterattack.
He wants to find the rhythm back.
It's an opportunity for Yi Cunhui.
False action.
Feng Shan Gui Qi is frozen.
Yi Cunhui released the array of ice.
He tricked the best Ghost Array.
This newcomer is really something.
Yifan will win, right?
No. He'll lose.
Where are you going?
Have some fresh air.
Let's see how Feng Shan Gui Qi will respond.
Another false action. Ghost.
Feng Shan Gui Qi is unfreeze.
He fooled Yi Cunhui,
made a counter attack when Yi Cunhui rushed up.
Yi Cunhui's in danger.
He'll be taken down.
He really did it on purpose.
All Skills are hit on him.
Yi Cunhui's HP is empty.
Feng Shan Gui Qi wins.
Let's congratulate Li Xuan of Kongxu Team
on winning the game.
The old man is a fount of wisdom.
The best Ghost Array deserves his reputation.
Newcomer is still newcomer.
I can't believe he challenged the best player in his profession.
Though Qiao Yifan has been suppressed
in this game all long,
this also shows us his potential.
Right, I think Qiao Yifan will gain a lot
from his understanding of Ghost Array and
Execute Ghost after this competition.
Li Xuan also showed the best Ghost Array of league's
superb understanding of the profession.
This game also broke the league's
fastest one-on-one winning record.
Compared with the last game of the same profession,
We can see that
Qiao Yifan has a long way to go.
Let's cheer for the newcomer.
Although Qiao Yifan lost the game,
facing such a powerful opponent,
I believe he has tried his best to
exert all his strength.
Now I still want to know how the winner,
Li Xuan, our senior,
commented on Yifan's performance.
You played well today,
but unfortunately you met me.
Thank you.
Li Xuan. Li Xuan.
Why did you play Execute Ghost today?
As the best Execute Ghost in Glory,
How do you evaluate Qiao Yifan's Ghost Array today?
Ask him more.
Listen to what he thinks.
Player Qiao Yifan,
Is your fight against Li Xuan
an individual fan behavior
or a team arrangement?
Qiao Yifan,
Your original career was assassins.
Why did you suddenly
play Ghost Array today?
Did you not consider the difference between
you and Li Xuan's strength before the competition?
How do you feel about
being the fastest loser
in the newcomer competition?
Do you think you're the right one to Ghost Array?
Do you think you're good at playing Ghost Array?
Do you think you'll continue
playing Ghost Array after losing so badly today?
Sorry.
You are too bold.
Senior.
I know what you're thinking.
You want to use this stage
to prove your ability to use Ghost Array.
But your choice of opponent is too exaggerated.
One month, and you want to challenge the best Ghost Array.
Why?
I know he's great.
If you're looking for advice,
and salute to seniors,
Li Xuan is a good choice.
But if you're trying to show off
your ability to use Ghost Array,
Li Xuan should be your last choice.
No one in the Glory circle knows
Ghost Array more than Li Xuan.
and you want to display
your technology in front of him.
No wonder you were restrained so easily.
Moreover, as the support,
Ghost Array is valuable in a team.
Team awareness and skills are hard to express
in such single-handed competitions.
You have little experience,
mistakes are a matter of time.
You're not even close to play Ghost Array.
Glory is not as simple as you think
Senior,
I just want a chance.
A chance that the captain can notice me.
Now is not the time.
Then when is?
Wait till we abandoned by the team completely?
I've done everything I can.
Maybe I should have given up.
It's not the team or the captain
who can abandon you.
It's you.
Yifan.
Don't question yourself.
You are still young.
There is plenty of time for further training.
Keep looking for opportunities.
Rebound while touching the bottom.
Never give up.
Senior, you told me not to give up,
But why did you retire?
I'm also looking for opportunities.
Though I am elder,
I never mean to give up.
After all,
No one wants to live in a shadow.
How do you feel sitting in the audience?
Great.
Do you want to experience it?
That day will not come.
I'm experiencing in advance
to avoid being unsuitable for retirement.
Lao Han,
Everyone's getting old,
Don't argue with it.
If I remember correctly,
you're one year older than me.
You're feeling slippery these days, right?
And never thought
you would quit the game one day.
I won't give up.
The confrontation between Sun Xiang
and Han Wenqing will begin right away.
I believe you all look forward to it as much as I do.
Right?
As everyone knows, Jia Shi's dream of
four quadruple crown ended by Ambitions,
Now they are enmity and resentment,
Strong versus strong,
Let's have the captain of Jiashi, Sun Xiang.
Then let's have the captain of Ambitions, Han Wenqing.
The popularity of Han Wenqing is very high.
Sun Xiang's popularity is not low either.
Sun Xiang was the newcomer king of last season.
How about this year?
First year of joining the league,
and he was elected as an All-star,
Now he inherited Ye Qiu Master's
Leaf of Autumn.
His strength goes further.
Where are Sun Xiang's fans here?
Let me see you.
Senior King of Fighter,
It's time to step aside
when you're old.
Is it?
You beat me before,
but only took advantage of the Smoke Alone.
Now I have Leaf of Autumn,
Do you think I'll lose again?
Let's see.
We saw that the two old friends
greeted each other at the beginning.
But I'm also very curious that
What did Sunxiang say
to Master Han Wenqing just now?
Nothing important.
I just want to tell senior
The purpose of my challenge is
to make a closure to the old grievances of
Jia Shi and Ambitions,
also of Leaf of Autumn and Smoke Alone.
I've smelled the strong smell of gunpowder.
War is imminent.
He is so confident.
Please enter the battle seats.
All right. Both players are logining the characters.
Entering the match map.
Sun Xiang, Leaf of Autumn,
versus Han Wenqing, Smoke Alone.
The game is about to begin.
Here we go.
We saw that there were
no tactical moves at the beginning.
Both sides rushed directly to the center of the map.
Speaking of Leaf of Autumn and Smoke Alone,
I believe you are all familiar with
these old enemies for many years.
Each match they played
from the game to the arena
was impressive.
I believe today's game
will also be a classic match
in the history of glory.
We all knew that
Han Wenqing's character is firm,
he never reteats,
The character he used,
King of Fighter Smoke Alone,
is godly character of the initial Glory.
Leaf of autumn Sun Xiang operated
is also godly character of the initial Glory,
the title of God of Fights.
Within the tough fighting Sun Xiang played,
The game is bound to be
a spectacular close-up game.
Straight Punch, Launching Kick, Soaring Tiger.
Smoke Alone starts without reservation,
constantly attacking Leaf of Autumn.
Leaf of Autumn begins to fight back.
Falling Flower Palm, Dragon Tooth, Draconic Crusher.
A series of moves, easy and smooth.
You said that Newcomer Challenge
is just a show.
Did Han Wenqing just
push himself so hard?
He's getting old.
Days are countable.
He had to.
I seem to recall that
he's only 26.
That is a veteran for professional athlets.
He just won't accept it.
Is it wrong?
Not quite.
Smoke Alone has broken through
the advantage of distance
and send himself to the side of Leaf of Autumn.
He deserves admiration.
Excellent Attack-Defense conversion.
Why don't you learn from him,
the one who's experiencing retirement ahead of time?
Leaf of Autumn made it,
and want to attack and fight back immediately.
But we can see that Smoke Alone
squatted a horse's step.
The left hand wanders in front,
The right hand is hidden in the waist.
This is the start-up of the great move, Emperor's Fist.
I accidentally heard your conversation.
I really want to know
how it feels to sit in the auditorium for the first time.
Leaf of Autumn dodged in a sudden.
Only a fist...
Nice.
Go for it, Han Wenqing.
Have you ever wondered
how you would bear Guoguo's anger
if she knows who you really are one day?
She won't refuse surprise.
We wonder if God of Fights can bring us
different surprises after changing his master.
Sun Xiang's method of operation
is very similar to Ye Qiu's.
For a moment,
I feel like I'm back in the era when the God of Fights
and the King of Fighting were at their peak.
Treasure your time, Lao Han.
I have no intention of retiring.
How about you?
My career must be one day longer than yours.
Big talk. We'll see.
We saw Han Wenqing's somewhat distracted.
He didn't escaped the Dragon Tooth of Leaf of Autumn.
It shouldn't happen.
Did he fail to keep up with his
excessive physical exertion before?
Is he really recalling the past?
Leaf of Autumn seizes the opportunity to attack Smoke Alone.
Leaf of Autumn's HP is in the lead.
It's unimaginable that
Senior Han Wenqing also had times of being suppressed.
The heyday of professional athletes
lasted that long.
Even if he doesn't talk,
he knows better than anyone.
So the captain feels anxious,
and want you to take on the future of Weicao.
The future of Weicao
isn't one person's future.
It's ours.
I know I'm not in the plan of Weicao's future.
Yifan, don't give up.
You have a lot of chances
to prove yoruself to the captain.
Yingjie,
I don't want to prove anymore.
I'm not belong in Weicao's future,
but I have the future of my own.
Professional players have such a short career,
everyone is doing their best,
how could I give up?
After all,
No one wants to disappear into the night
without a bright light.
Old fella,
are you out of breath?
Smoke Alone is now very passive,
and may be taken away with a series moves
by Leaf of Autumn any time.
I'll end him.
Here we go.
Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.
This set of skills is released very accurately.
What happened, captain?
Lao Han's really old,
Why is he so slow?
He can't lose.
That's too shameless.
Are you kidding?
Han Wenqing didn't give up.
He's defending the dignity of an veteran.
This is King of Fighter. This is Han Wenqing.
This is the spirit of Ambitions.
Never give up though at a disadvantage.
March forward courageously.
Now the game has reached a fever pitch.
It's amazing.
Impossible.
The HP advantage of Leaf of Autumn
did not continue to expand.
It is closely followed by Smoke Alone.
Smoke Alone, Soaring Tiger.
Leaf of Autumn, Dragon Strikes the Heart.
Both sides are saving power.
The one wins this blow
can seize the rhythm.
Han Wenqing and Sun Xiang are both
looking for the opportunity to launch skills.
It's just a dying struggle.
Here it comes.
Both sides launched almost at the same time.
They hit each other at the same time.
Another exchange of HP.
it's very unfavorable for Smoke Alone with the lowest HP.
King of Fighter, look out.
You're feeling slippery these days, right?
And never thought
you would quit the game one day.
Right.
I will leave one day .
I will be defeated.
I will quit Glory.
But it's not today.
Not here.
Nice.
One strike with Collapsing Fist on Leaf of Autumn.
He's still attacking
while facing such a disadvantage,
He's catching up.
At present, HP of Smoke Alone is 8%.
HP of Leaf of Autumn is 9%
The result of this climax confrontation...
I will never lose.
Dragon Soaring.
Leaf of Autumn made the great move.
If he hits,
he'll take away Smoke Alone directly.
Excellent.
Smoke Alone escaped this skill with Eagle Stamp.
Ferocious Tiger Flurry.
Smoke Alone released the great move of Fighters,
Ferocious Tiger Flurry in the end.
Nice move.
Smoke Alone killed Leaf of Autumn
at the last moment.
He's still got it.
King of Fighter Han Wenqing defeated Sun Xiang.
This climate confrontation ended
with the victory of Han Wenqing's Smoke Alone.
I'll never give up.
What's wrong with getting old?
What's wrong with the slippery?
if you can't win with one punch, then ten it is.
Or twenty.
Or a hundred.
Till I can't move.
From game to competition,
as an opponent for many years,
Han Wenqing is too familiar with Leaf of Autumn.
Eagle Stamp at last can
precisely avoid Dragon Soaring,
We saw the experience of veteran,
and the perseverance of Han Wenqing.
The strength of newcomer should not be underestimated,
But the spirit of disobedience of veteran
and his unyielding will
still impressed us.
Sun Xiang also came out.
Though he lose with one move,
He still brought us
a very exciting confrontation.
Let's give the applause to the two players again.
This time I was unlucky.
Next time,
I will never lose.
Oh, yeah?
I remember you didn't say that just now.
Thanks.
Thanks for the two players again.
Please come back to our lounge
and get some rest.
Do you think it's easy to
win the game, King of Fighter?
Sun Xiang,
What do you think of this challenge?
How do you feel about yourself?
Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang.
Sun Xiang.
What do you think of what you said just now?
Make a closure to the old grievances
of Leaf of Autumn and Smoke Alone.
Are you talking big?
Are you here for fun?
What did you say?
Say it again.
Am I wrong?
Sun Xiang did play well.
The precise Dragon Breaks the Ranks
and Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart,
few people can do it.
Master Han,
Can you comment on
Sun Xiang's performance today?
But if it was Ye Qiu,
the last move of Dragon Soaring would never miss.
Young boy,
It's too early for you
to replaced us.
Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang. Sun Xiang.
Do you think you deserve Leaf of Autumn?
Sun Xiang, let me tell you.
You can never replace Ye Qiu.
Do you like e-Sports?
If so,
Think of it as glory,
not ostentation.
Next up is the audiences'
interactive competition.
At this point, we will invite training camp players
from each team and lucky audience to compared notes.
This is an unexpected part of the All-Star Game.
It is not restricted by the rules of the game,
Mainly for communication and performance,
professional assistants would appear sometimes,
so there will be many points of view and surprises.
Let's have the first guest on stage.
Welcome Li Rui from Jia Shi.
What's wrong, captain?
Fight well.
Playing as a Professional Player.
Don't worry, captain.
I'll never let you down.
This is an opportunity to fight against professionals,
It's lucky to be selected.
Really?
Of course.
It's lucky to fight against professionals,
it's luckier to fight against Masters,
- If you wantto fight against Ye Qiu... - Lukiest.
That's not lucky.
Why?
That's dreaming.
Welcome Li Rui.
Dreams may come true
after a long time.
Who is the lucky one to be chosen?
Stop.
Me?
Let's congratulate her.
What a suprise.
You are the one lucky guy, Tang.
Play well, don't disgrace your master.
She's a girl.
When did you become my master?
Always.
Learning so much from me,
you can't turn your back on it.
I was self-taught.
Go for it, Tang.
Go for it, Go for it.
Welcome to our first lucky audience.
Hello.
Let's say hello first.
Introduce yourself, please.
Hi everyone, I'm Tang Rou.
It's Tang Rou.
Then Lao Ye must be here.
Tang Rou.
let's take a look at
their relevant information in Glory.
Let's see the big screen.
29 days.
Does that mean
you played in Glory less than a month?
Yes.
It turned out to be a rookie of Glory.
Li Rui,
You'll have to be merciful later.
Sure.
Let's invite two players into the battle seats.
a rookie girl of Glory
versus a professional-to-be player,
What do you say?
I'm looking forward to the sparks
two battle mages will make.
Game started.
We can see that
Han Yanrou rushed to her opponent at the beginning.
She's full of momentum.
Too many flaws.
Mage Fighter dodged easily.
Dragon Tooth.
Still be dodged.
It seems that Li Rui deal with it easily.
Falling Flower Palm.
Such a quick speed.
Mage Fighter made a mistake this time
and was blew up directly.
Such a quick speed for a newcomer.
Another Circle Swing.
Mage Fighter is struke down.
Mage Fighter strikes back.
She made it.
I think the audience was as surprised as I was.
After launching Dragon Tooth,
It's most likely to launch Circle Swing.
At this time, you can launch Falling Flower Palm
to blow the opponent up,
break-in the skill.
After that,
release Draconic Crusher immediately,
which will force the opponent to fall down.
you can damage three seconds.
At this time,
If he is a master,
he'll launch Falling Flower Palm to the ground
after he stands up
in order to keep your distance.
So you need to launch Dragon Breaks the Ranks
which the Attack Range is far enoough.
It's a test of foresight.
Be sure to be accurate.
Tang Rou, come on.
It seems that Tang Rou has made rapid progress.
It's only half a month before she becomes this.
And she plays just like Lao Ye.
Captain,
Sun Xiang has just be defeated by Lao Han,
Now his apprentice is being abused by Tang Rou.
This is so beatiful.
Tang Rou's uses her speed advantage
to put pressure on Li Rui continuously.
It seems that Jia Shi really has a bad luck.
So gossipy.
Tang Rou is so powerful.
Do you think this is Sun Xiang's expression now?
A Player who have just played Glory for less than a month,
this is a little embarrassing now.
Li Rui, as a professional-to-be player of Jia Shi,
will he be defeated by a newcomer like this?
Han Yanrou has completely crushed Mage Fighter,
Li Rui seems to be a newcomer.
We see that the current HP
is 60% versus 30%.
Han Yanrou is in the lead.
She is storing force.
Dragon Breaks the Ranks.
Han Yanrou wants to win the game.
If this hits,
Mage Fighter will be defeated with a series skills.
It's over.
Tang is gonna win.
Wonderful.
have you seen a professional defeated by...
Did you see it?
... a normal player?
Well, she's still a newcomer.
Right. Mage Fighter can't
dodged this blow in the air.
What?
He dodged?
What happened?
What, what, what?
Go away.
He dodged?
This operation is truely impressive.
He dodged.
It must be a coincidence.
Dragon Breaks the Ranks is exploded in front of him,
and he escaped without any injury.
This dodge can be regarded
as a professional standard.
Someone helped him.
He's just playing normally.
Who's that?
You watch him carefully.
The way he forecast, the timing he grasp.
Can you recall anyone?
Sun Xiang.
It's really him.
His self-esteem is too strong.
That's why he can't afford to lose.
Look closely.
What?
Four thorns in the air.
This battle mage is unusal.
Nice.
Four thorns in the air.
Mage Fighter's attack is so quick,
Han Yanrou has no power to fight back.
The advantage HP is gonna lose.
If it goes on like this,
She will lose the game.
It's not that easy.
She got up.
We see that Mage Fighter didn't make a concession.
He's approaching Han Yanrou.
Draconic Crusher.
What?
He cancelled it at the last moment
and change into Dragon Tooth.
Han Yanrou only drops one percent of HP.
Sky Strike. Another two percent.
What is he doing?
Han Yanrou didn't give up.
She operates the character to stand up
and rush into Mage Fighter.
She's gonna fight back.
Another Dragon Tooth?
Mage Fighter uses a micro skill again
and consumes 1% of HP of Han Yanrou.
Is he humiliating her?
How could he?
What is he doing?
He's humiliating with micro skills.
Humiliating an amateur in front of these people,
Jia Shi is not afraid of losing face.
Making fun of an amateur player,
Is he qualified for the professional league?
Are you kidding?
What are you doing?
Are you humiliating her?
Mage Fighter is still using micro skills
That's too much.
to consume Tang Rou's HP.
How could he treat a newcomer like that?
That's so humiliating.
But she didn't give up.
She's still looking for opportunities to fight back.
Han Yanrou only leaves 10% of HP.
Looks like the newcomer is going to lose.
It's over.
Storing the force.
Another Dragon Breaks the Ranks.
As a newcomer,
I'm afraid it's hard for Han Yanrou
to copy the operation and avoid it.
What? Wonderful!
She dodged.
She dodged Dragon Breaks the Ranks precisely.
Exactly.
She dodged it.
It seems that there's a mysterious person showed up.
What now?
She dodged?
Dodged.
Such a wonderful interactive spectator competition.
The operation of both sides is much faster than just now.
This rhythm feels like a professional league.
At this point, Mage Fighter's HP is still ahead.
But both players' HP are not much.
Such a deadlock situation,
Direct Li,
What do you think the players will do next?
One hit kill.
They can only take each other away
by great moves under this condition,
otherwise, nobody is sure of winning the game.
by changing with micro skills.
Dragon Soaring.
Both players are releasing Dragon Soaring.
They both want to make one hit kill.
The game is about to be won or lost.
You're right.
They launched at the same time.
This is it.
Not good.
Han Yanrou missed.
Let's congratulate Mage Fighter.
What?
Mage Fighter's HP is empty.
Han Yanrou wins.
What happened.
Mage Fighter lose first.
What happened indeed?
Everyone,
it happened just so fast,
We have no idea what happened.
Let's follow the slow-motion camera.
Good. They both launched Dragon Soaring.
They both dodged.
What?
Dragon Soaring of Han Yanrou changed direction,
Mage Fighter didn't make it.
It's Dragon Head Raising!
Han Yanrou used Dragon Head Raising!
My god, it really is Dragon Head Raising!
Impossible.
What just happened!
Han Yanrou used Dragon Head Raising as a newcomer.
Let's congratulate Han Yanrou
won this game.
Did you do your best this time?
I try my best
in every game.
# standing on the top and claiming that #
Did you really give up like this?
Giving up does not mean admitting defeat.
Fine.
Don't be a deserter then.
I'll see you in the All-Star game next year.
Dragon Head Raising, Dragon Head Raising, Dragon Head Raising.
It will rebound
while touching the bottom.
Never give up
at any time.
# Above the cloud, in the dust #
# We are the brightest fireflies #
# I came from the past and will write the furture #
Master Ye Qiu.
# This fight, we will make it memorable #
Master. Master Ye Qiu.
Where's Master Ye Qiu?
He just...
left.
Let's go.
Every unwilling departure,
is for the final return.