[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 22]
How many people did Yao kill
after she became the 16th Night?
Wang Dengcheng betrayed the Ghetto
and almost destroyed our family.
There's a conspiracy behind all this.
Someone
may hurt people I care about.
I need my life to protect them.
[Four Season Palace]
[Cultivation and Reading are Family Heirlooms]
There aren't many people who can kill
[The Spirit of Four Season Lasts Forever]
the 16th Night.
You have so many talents working for you.
Don't worry.
There are some
overly confident people
trying to get us into trouble.
[Lady of Autumn, Four Season Divine]
We lost disciples one by one.
We're having a hard time.
[Spring]
[Lord of Spring, Four Season Divine]
Why don't you
look worried at all?
Since you acted on behalf of Lord Freedom,
the Divine has been well developed.
Why waste your time
on those nobodies?
Nobodies?
We lost several of our spies
because of these nobodies.
I'm especially referring to Gao Bingzhu.
He removed the Eagle
out of the Intelligence Services.
If I do nothing about it,
I'm afraid that we'll lose more of them
in other Services as well.
The greater good will be realized soon.
They are not contributing anyway.
As for that Gao Bingzhu,
he's only
a lunatic who longs for revenge.
If you try to provoke him,
you'll not only get hurt,
but also ruin your reputation.
Do you have any brilliant ideas then?
I just think
you don't need to
waste your energy on them.
The last batch of goods
is ready to be sent to Luoyang.
Sorry I have to ask you to take care of it.
Only in this way can we make sure
that our greater good will be achieved.
I have to remind you.
Always think of the big picture.
[Gong Yan, Disciple in Four Season Divine]
-Stop here!
-Stop!
I need to see His Lordship and Her Ladyship.
No one is allowed without a good cause!
Are you crazy?
Anyone who enters here
without permission will be punished!
Have you forgotten
the rules?
I was told that the 16th Night died.
I need to confirm this with them.
[Lu Li, Disciple in Four Season Divine]
You'll be killed
for the intrusion of the main hall!
I'll forgive you this time.
It was Yao
who taught me
these rules one by one.
She is dead now.
Aren't you sad about it?
My lady.
Gong Yan,
why are you here?
My lady,
people said the 16th Night...
From this moment,
you'll be the new 16th Night.
A batch of goods
just arrived here.
Go kill
those people.
What do you mean by the new 16th Night?
The 16th Night died for the Divine.
Her sacrifice was meaningful.
What's the point of venting your anger here?
Why not find out
who killed Yao,
make them pay,
and revenge for her?
People who killed Yao
have to die.
Enjoy.
The chef's lamb soup at Tao's
is the best in Luoyang.
It reminds me that
Gao Bingzhu and I met here
for the first time.
He had this soup as well.
Any idea on what Manager Qin said yesterday?
It can't be the first time
for Kang Zhanbi and Kang Jin
to come here.
They chose Guanglin Inn
as they knew they didn't need
passports to check in.
Manager Qin said that they never went out once
after they checked in.
They seemed to be avoiding someone.
Kang Zhanbi only went out once
and was killed.
So, they were indeed in danger.
How did they make it here
without passports?
How did they get those identity documents?
These questions need to be answered.
We can be sure that
Li Ji didn't kill him.
Whoever takes the rattle poison
dies immediately.
The murderer
might have poisoned him
when those two were arguing.
Kang Jin is the key as well.
He went missing
after Kang Zhanbi died.
They must be avoiding someone.
Li Ji will be on a joint trial
by the three departments.
I'll go back to the Services
and bring him to trial.
I'll search for Kang Jin then.
All merchants from the West
need identity documents
from the Customs Office
to enter Luoyang.
I'll see if I can find clues there.
Okay, take care.
[The 16th Night, Wang Dengcheng, Yao]
Why are you being polite to me?
This is your home now.
[Victim]
Living such a life is too tiring for you.
Wait for me!
[Xiaowu and the Mouse, deceased friends of Gao]
I can't do this. Wait!
Bingzhu, wait!
I can't do this.
-Bingzhu, wait for me!
-Wait!
Bingzhu, let's go!
Life is short.
Do what you want.
Spend time with people you love.
This is the meaning of life.
[Customs Office, The South of Luoyang]
Why are you still here?
Please go through it again.
I said this before.
I can't find anyone named Kang Zhanbi
on the register.
What about Kang Jin?
Neither.
Go.
You can go.
Your turn.
Thank you.
Are there any other places
to get an identity document
apart from here?
You can get it everywhere,
such as the administrative offices.
You can even get one for 5 coins
in the black market.
Go find out yourself
if you're interested.
Sir, would you kindly
make an exception for me?
Thanks.
Liu Feng!
[Liu Feng, the Son of the Liu Family]
It's such a surprise!
It has been a long time since I left.
I just came back
and immediately met you.
You've changed a lot.
You
haven't.
I think you left Luoyang
several years ago.
I did.
I remembered the envoy from Daishan
came here at the beginning of that year.
They brought two lions
as gifts.
We went to see them together.
I never forgot
what you told me
on our way back.
Lions in the cage
are no longer intimidating.
What a disappointment!
Although I'm from a prestigious family,
I never aimed for achievements in politics.
That's why I was always told off by my family.
What you said that day
was true wisdom
and suddenly enlightened me.
Did you leave home
and do business in the West
because of what I said?
I felt like a lion in the cage
at that time.
Later on, I left Luoyang
and went to the West
like a lion going back to the mountains.
I no longer
live within those frames.
What I said
was to myself.
Hongyi,
there should be
a lot of changes here
after I left.
Indeed.
I have things to do today.
You can go to the Baili Mansion
and stay there.
Thanks a lot.
I need to go back home first
to meet my uncle and my sister.
Liu Xiang
passed away already.
Your sister
is in the Baili Mansion as well.
What do you mean?
We got married.
Yanqing.
Yes.
Find all the documents here
concerning Four Season Divine.
Bring anything related here.
Yes, sir.
Are you Li Ji?
[Li Ji, Member of the Royal Family]
I am.
Baili Hongyi sent me here.
Gao Bingzhu is back.
He immediately went to the Hall of Skills.
He is investigating Four Season Divine.
Ask him to see me.
Did he find
the real murderer?
I said this before.
I didn't kill
Kang Zhanbi.
I'm here for the truth.
Tell me,
what happened exactly
when Kang Zhanbi died?
Don't miss a single detail.
Sorry, I booked this room
a long time ago.
My guests will soon arrive.
Please let us have this room.
Get out.
If you're unhappy about this,
I can pay for
these dishes.
[Kang Zhanbi, The Ke Tribe]
Get out!
What's going on?
What happened?
Did you say a woman
was sitting next to him?
Yes, I saw her.
The manager of Tianxiang House
and some waiters
saw her as well.
What about the wine cup
she put on the table?
Where did it go?
How could anybody know that?
The 16th Night is dead.
I thought you would never come back.
The 16th Night was gone,
but Four Season Divine is not.
As long as it exists,
there will be another 16th Night.
There will be more people
losing their lives.
Four Season Divine is the real trouble.
If we don't destroy it,
there won't be any peace.
Seems that your mind remains clear.
It's never been clearer.
We already found the mole.
The Services should go back to normal.
Should I learn
the cipher used in the Services?
You don't study music.
You can't.
Have you finally decided
to take the responsibility
as the Halberdier?
Then,
I hope you can follow
our rules first.
Don't do anything
like meeting the 16th Night on your own
without authorization.
He doesn't look like
the Gao Bingzhu I know.
All he cared about was the 16th Night.
The enemy
he had been looking for all these years
suddenly died.
What would you do
if you were him?
The 16th Night died.
Somehow, he lost his purpose in life.
No,
he is looking for a new one.
Open the door!
[Baili Mansion]
Anybody?
Come out
if you're alive!
Open the door!
Baili Hongyi
got married, right?
Who is his wife?
Open the door!
Where is my sister?
[Baili Wu, Butler of the Baili Mansion]
Watch carefully.
Is my sister inside?
This is the Baili Mansion.
The Baili Mansion?
[Baili Mansion]
Do you know who I am?
I'm Liu Feng,
the son of the Liu family.
How could my sister marry Baili Hongyi?
My lord?
[Baili Mansion]
Open the door!
Yunzhi?
Sir.
Where are you going?
I still have some doubts
concerning Li Ji's case.
I'm going to Tianxiang House
to interview them again.
Li Ji, who killed the outlander?
Yes.
The outlander who died was Kang Zhanbi.
I think he died from rattle poison.
According to Li Ji,
while they were arguing,
there was an entertainer as well.
I guess Kang Zhanbi was probably killed
by that woman.
Go find out, then.
Okay.
I have something to ask you.
Several days ago,
Baili Hongyi set a trap
at Liubai Building.
What didn't you report
such an important thing to me?
It was urgent.
I didn't find time
to report it to you.
I'll explain it to you
once I come back.
Lady Liu Ran will be glad
to see you
become so tall
and so strong.
You really changed a lot.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I could say the same to you.
You still remember
what I looked like!
Then, do you remember
that we went to the riverside...
Yunzhi,
give me a break!
Where is my sister?
There.
In the kitchen?
How dare they ask her
to keep an eye on servants herself?
Liu Ran!
Liu Feng?
Liu Ran.
Liu Feng!
When did you come back?
My little brother,
you finally came back!
Why didn't you
send us a letter
all these years?
When did you become so tall?
Let me have a look.
Here.
Why does
your face look dirty?
When did you come back?
How have you been these years?
-Liu Ran.
-Yunzhi!
You can't stay in the Baili Mansion.
Come home with me.
Liu Feng.
Liu Feng,
why is it?
Why can't I stay here?
When did we ever mistreat you like this
when you were at home?
You even cook now!
Liu Feng, come here.
I'll be honest with you.
I do these
because
I'm willing to do so.
I don't have much to do
every day here.
I kind of enjoy doing this.
Yunzhi,
take him to the hall
and get his favorite food for him.
I'll be there...
Liu Ran, listen to me.
You have to come with me.
Liu Feng.
You can't stay here!
Come with me.
Liu Feng, stop it!
Stop it!
Let's go!
Stop.
Let's go.
Liu Feng!
Liu Ran!
Wait for me in the hall.
Wait outside.
Yunzhi,
here.
You go stay with Liu Feng.
Bring some food he likes
and make some tea.
Go talk to him.
I'll be there when the soup is done.
Yes.
Careful.
The black market?
My lord,
I grew up with you
in the Baili Mansion.
I don't even know
the entrance of the black market,
let alone the people inside.
I didn't ask you to find it.
Do you know where it is?
I don't,
but someone does.
Have a look!
Don't miss this opportunity!
Give it a try!
The glazed double-gourd vase for 30 coins.
The five-colored porcelain vase for 50 coins.
Also...
The most precious
Changsha red porcelain vase.
I, Bai Lang,
swear on my life that
as long as you throw an arrow into a vase,
I will give you it for free!
Good!
Go on.
Come here, sir.
Bro,
can I win any of these
as long as
I throw an arrow into it?
You can, once the arrow is in the vase.
Okay.
I'll start with 5 arrows first.
One coin for one arrow.
You have to buy at least ten.
Okay, ten arrows then.
Great!
Here you go.
Okay.
Throw an arrow in the vase,
and the vase will be yours!
Bravo!
You threw it too hard.
You need to throw harder.
Can you do it?
I can do it!
Relax.
Isn't this too difficult?
I don't think anyone can do it.
I'll give you another one for free.
No, that's enough.
Try this closer one.
You did it!
It's in!
Well done!
No!
That one doesn't count.
You said I can take it.
You...
I...
Bro!
Well done!
Here you are. Thanks.
Thank you.
Okay.
Thanks for your help.
Bai Lang,
I've been practicing that
for years!
Is this what I get?
I'll give you another one for free.
No, that's enough.
Try this closer one.
I'm done with it.
Your techniques were amazing,
but that happy expression on your face
was too much.
I can only give you these.
Take it or leave it.
I can find others next time.
Okay, I'll take it.
Good.
You're smart!
Bai Lang,
did you fool people again?
My vase!
Let's go
to the Henan Prefecture.
Bro,
destiny let us meet.
Please take this
and pretend we've never met.
Bro?
Lang,
you made a lot in such a short time.
Give it back.
Shen Fei!
Wait.
Okay.
What happened, Shen Fei?
Lord Hongyi heard that
you know someone
from the black market well.
He wants you
to find something about an outlander
named Kang Zhanbi
and his companion Kang Jin.
Please help us
and see if anyone there
made fake identity documents for them.
If anyone met them before,
please tell us the details.
Beg me!
Don't you wanna help?
Then I'll take you
to the Henan Prefecture.
You'll stay in prison
for three to five months
considering the money you've earned.
Let's go.
Shen Fei, I'll help you.
I'll do it now.
The money...
Okay.
Let's make it clear, though.
You have to pay for this vase.
It's extremely valuable.
I know this.
A red porcelain vase
made in the black market.
Am I right?
Five coins each.
Right, I'll pay.
-Here.
-It...
Bai Lang,
this is for your vase.
Good.
I'll wait for your good news then.
[Tianxiang House, Dunhua Prefecture]
[Best Steamed Bun]
See you next time!
[Tianxiang House]
Isn't Tianxiang House open today?
Since I opened my stall,
their door has been closed
for a whole day.
When did you come here?
Before dawn.
Several days ago,
a man died there
and they were still doing business.
It's quite strange.
Move!
Madam.
Sir,
did anything happen to Tianxiang House?
Last night,
their manager's house was on fire.
All seven people
perished in that fire.
What caused the fire?
We looked into it.
They didn't put out
the fire in the kitchen.
The fire then spread
to the main hall.
They were all sleeping
and were burned to death.
What about his other relatives
and the staff?
Did you talk to them?
Anyone suspicious?
It's their family business.
All people working there
were his relatives.
They all died.
Someone wanted to silence them for good.
Bai Lang confirmed that
someone in the black market
saw Kang Zhanbi.
They came here
with a caravan.
That caravan
had more than 10 people.
Any information about the caravan?
That's the strange part.
They didn't get their documents
forged in the black market.
Not in the black market?
Did they find
legal ways to do this?
The caravan
went to the black market several times,
but neither for identity documents
nor for businesses.
Nobody knew
why they were there.
If they had legal documents,
why did they
keep their whereabouts as a secret?
Why were they killed by rattle poison?
Rattle poison?
The one that killed Master Baili?
This caravan
must be hiding something.
Where are we going now?
Home.
So, our uncle's death
had something to do with Baili Hongyi!
How could you not blame him?
Liu Feng,
I've said this before.
Our uncle
did things wrong first.
Hongyi was just trying to
find out the truth.
Liu Ran,
what spell has he cast on you?
Even if he is a genius,
still, you should tell right from wrong!
He was the one
who killed our uncle!
Liu Feng,
stop this nonsense!
This isn't nonsense!
Liu Feng,
you just came back.
Don't argue with me.
Have some soup first.
If you have anything to say,
wait until you finish this.
Here.
Liu Ran,
you're no longer the person I know.
Have some soup.
What do you think?
What is this?
Beef soup.
Beef soup?
Is it good? Should I add more salt?
It's good.
Such a relief.
Wait.
You always like strong flavors.
If you find it tasty,
it must be
too salty for Hongyi.
Not good.
Yunzhi,
let's go back to the kitchen.
Liu Ran!
Welcome home, my lord.
Baili Hongyi!
Liu Feng
should be in the mansion.
Bring him here.
Liu Feng?
Did he come back?
When?
Baili Hongyi!
You're a monster!
A murderer!
I'll make you pay...
What do you want?
One of us will die today!
Don't you move!
Baili Hongyi!
Show some respect!
Shen Fei.
Baili Hongyi!
You killed my uncle
and abused my sister!
I will kill you today!
Are you crazy?
Baili Hongyi!
Liu Feng!
Shut up!
Feng, stop!
Don't you move!
Feng!
You!
What are you doing?
Liu Ran!
Hongyi,
are you alright?
Liu Ran.
I'm fine.
He just came back
and he knew nothing.
Liu Ran!
Save it!
Hongyi.
Liu Feng, stop!
What are you doing?
Liu Feng, what are you doing?
Liu Feng!
We are from a prestigious family,
a family of scholars.
How could you become
such a rascal?
You finally asked
what I've been through these years.
You're right.
I didn't read a single book.
I traveled to different places
with merchants from the West.
If you think
I am a disgrace to the Liu family,
I can leave.
I won't care about
your marriage anymore.
Liu Feng, where are you going?
Wait!
-You spent a long time in the West.
-Come back!
Have you heard about
caravans from the Ke Tribe?
Feng.
There were two outlanders
in this caravan from the Ke Tribe.
One is called Kang Zhanbi.
The other is Kang Jin.
Have you heard of them?
Why would I tell you?
Liu Feng,
please tell him if you know anything.
Liu Feng.
Kang Zhanbi died.
Kang Jin is missing as well.
It's none of my business.
I didn't do it.
We don't know where they were from
or where they had been.
If you know something
but keep it from us,
I'll report you immediately
and let the offices do the investigation.
Hongyi.
The Grand Court is known for its torture.
The Interior Guard Services is better,
but it'd be a living hell for you.
Hongyi.
And the Henan Prefecture as well.
I've heard that
no one has ever come out alive.
Baili Hongyi,
you're a monster.
Hongyi, he just came back.
He has no idea of what's going on.
Liu Ran, don't beg him.
Hongyi!
Liu Ran!
Liu Feng!
Do you see these?
I've been through everything.
Don't use this to threaten me!
I'm not afraid of torture.
Aren't you going to report me?
Go for it!
No? You are a coward!
[The Interior Guard Services]
Madam.
He was transferred to the Henan Prefecture.
Why?
Li Ji is a royal member.
That's why he was kept here.
As you said,
there are some reasonable doubts.
So, I immediately sent him there
for a reinvestigation.
When did he leave?
About two hours ago.
Anything wrong?
People who met that woman at Tianxiang House
all died mysteriously.
I think someone wants Li Ji dead, too.
Sir.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me
about what you've suffered?
I was threatening him before.
It no longer hurts.
It's fine.
Here you are.
What's this?
It removes your scars.
It's good for you.
I'm a man.
Take this!
Liu Ran,
actually, I know
the two men he asked about.
I just didn't want to tell him.
Liu Feng,
I know.
What you did just now
was not for our uncle,
but for me.
You are afraid that
they don't treat me well.
You met
Kang Zhanbi and Kang Jin?
Where?
On my way back to Luoyang,
a sand storm came
while we were in Gaochang.
More than 10 caravans stayed in an oasis
called Crescent Lake.
The caravan where Kang Zhanbi
and Kang Jin stayed was there as well.
What goods
were they carrying?
How could I know?
Liu Feng, think harder.
You said this before.
This caravan acted
secretly.
They kept a close eye
on the goods they carried.
Apart from
exchanging food or medicine,
they never talked
to other people.
What else?
Can you think of anything else?
Tell him all the details.
Don't hide anything.
Your sister's right.
Think harder.
Liu Feng, think harder.
It seemed that they need to arrive
before a certain date.
So, they had set off
before the storm ended.
A certain date?
That's it.
This is all I know.
I'll go if you don't have other questions.
Wait.
What does Kang Jin look like?
Move!
Are you sure that he fell and died?
Madam.
It is said that
he jumped out to run away
and died here.
Did you see it with your eyes?
Madam,
he was driving the carriage
and I was following behind.
I heard someone hit the door twice.
He had jumped out
and died on the road
before I realized something was wrong.
How can't you keep a man safe?
Please forgive us.
Don't get angry with them.
Li Ji is important to us.
All the clues are gone now that he's dead.
Did he run
out of fear
and die?
What a coincidence!
The whole family of the manager
of Tianxiang House died.
Now Li Ji died as well.
It seems that
he was targeted a long time ago.
They didn't find the chance
to kill him
as he was in our prison.
It's not right.
Sir Wu decided to transfer Li Ji at the last minute.
How could someone
know much about this?