♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 13=
Be careful!
Jump!
I will catch you!
Get out of the way! Watch out!
I might hurt you!
Try me.
I didn't expect this.
You must have done this a lot
when you were a kid, right?
Same to you.
This is our primary school.
The lawn in front of you
was a bike shed.
All the teachers' bikes were
parked over there.
If criticized by the teacher,
we would sneak into the shed,
and deflate all the tires of his bike.
You and Shao Zhenrong were so naughty
when you were kids.
You two
must have messed around, right?
Same to you.
What are you doing?
Treasure hunt.
Treasure hunt?
When we were at school,
it was very popular among the students
to bury the time capsule.
Zhenrong and I
also buried one here
just like they did.
You wanna give it to me?
This is the memory of Zhenrong and me.
Take a look.
We used to agree that when we were old,
we would come to this tree
and dig it out.
We'll never
be able to keep the promise.
I knew
you two were naughty boys.
Why are you laughing?
What is this?
Zhenrong won it.
I didn't know
Zhenrong could swim.
The last thing he could do was swimming.
He couldn't swim at all.
Then how did he swim
and even win a medal?
He should thank me for kicking him out.
You were so mean to him.
As long as we were back home,
he complained to Aunt Shao and my dad.
My dad gave me a very good lesson.
You didn't see that.
He was just hiding behind my dad.
You have no idea how happy he was.
Because of that kick,
he didn't talk to me for a month.
Since then he's never afraid of water.
It took him six months
to get admitted into the school team,
and won this medal.
So sorry for Zhenrong
to have you as his elder brother.
Miss Jiang,
we've been around this big mall
for two or three times.
My legs are getting thin already.
Isn't there any dress you like?
It's for the annual
convention of the group.
How can I just dress up carelessly
for attendance?
Either I don't show up,
or I shall be the focus
of the party.
Especially the attention of Yuzhen
has to lock on me and can't move away.
We haven't been to that store yet.
Hurry up!
Good for you! To be a brother.
You must've bullied
Shao Zhenrong a lot when you were kids.
We boys
fought for our relationship with fists.
Besides,
the slightest disagreement
could make us fight.
I won every time.
Are you proud of bullying
your younger brother?
"I won every time". Come on!
He was my younger brother,
and I couldn't help with it.
I was the only one who
could bully him behind doors.
In public,
nobody dared even try to touch him!
Thank you for telling me all of this.
I can have the luck
to hear so much about his past.
It's been a luxury for me.
A luxury?
I think
I should be the least qualified person
to hear about him.
If you're not qualified,
who else would care about the past.
I've always believed in that
energy is conserved in this world.
Time will make up for the pain of loss
in another way.
There is no pain that can't be healed.
And all the pains will end.
This remark.
Let's encourage each other.
Give me a hand.
Why?
Don't you want to keep it?
Just leave it here.
What if Zhenrong recollects the past
just like you,
and wanna come back
and have a look.
Let's go.
Nice dress.
Sexy, elegant, and eye-catching.
It's definitely the focus.
But Yuzheng likes demure style.
This dress is too exposed.
No.
This one. This one is nice.
High-end and classy.
I think it's dull and old-fashioned.
If I stand next to him wearing this,
people might recognize me as his mother.
Forget it.
This one is nice.
Low-profile, luxurious,
but with connotation.
Lin Xiangyuan.
Only the lady as noble as Miss Jiang,
deserves this high-end evening dress.
Don't you think so, Mr. Lin?
Yes, you're right.
Miss Jiang, to be honest,
there are only two of this dress
in our store.
I'll take it.
Lin Xiangyuan, pay the bill.
Yes, ma'am.
What a robbery! 27,500 for one dress!
Mr. Lin,
this is a high-end dress,
and the price is marked clearly.
No matter how high-end it is,
it can't be that expensive!
Can I have the invoice?
No problem.
Make the invoice to Yutian Group.
Office supplies for the content.
Lin Xiangyuan.
Miss Jiang.
Miss Jiang?
Miss Jiang!
Is everything ok?
Why are you angry suddenly?
Lin Xiangyuan,
you've worked for my dad for years.
You are the company executive after all.
No matter what,
you shouldn't violate the principle.
Miss Jiang,
if you think I did something wrong,
just tell me, and I'll fix it.
Fix it? Don't you understand me?
Stop following me!
Go back!
How about this dress?
Didn't you just request an invoice?
Only the invoice.
What if the financial personnel
asks to look at the real item?
Besides, if I accept this dress,
is it from you or by myself?
Because of this? You misunderstood me.
The invoice is to strike a balance.
It's also for the good of the company.
What? Not for rent?
Didn't we make a deal
during the daytime?
Why not?
What a bully you are!
I'm telling you! We'll see.
I will complain to Administration
for Market Regulation tomorrow!
Siqi, what happened?
Why are you packing?
The landlord came to inform us
this apartment is not for rent anymore.
The couple is going to
fake their divorce,
and sell this apartment.
So I called Qunfei,
and asked him to accompany me
to the agency for an apartment.
It went well,
and we had a deal that we could move in.
Then the agency called me
to break the deal.
What the hell!
With our budget,
where can we move, the suburbs?
Otherwise we can only
share room with others.
For God's sake!
What's wrong with all these people?
The landlord can't bully us like this!
The contract hasn't expired yet.
How can he just ask us to leave?
We're not moving!
No!
He owns the apartment.
He asks you to leave tomorrow. Can you
stay till the day after tomorrow?
Take it easy, Siqi.
Don't worry.
Let me figure it out.
I still remember
when I go to college in Shanghai,
I honestly believed that
as long as I worked hard,
I could buy a big apartment of my own
next to Huangpu River.
But now,
it's been even a luxury
to rent my own home.
I'm listening.
Mr. Lei,
the thing is...
I'm going to propose to my girlfriend
this year.
Although we have a good relationship,
the apartment isn't ready yet.
Her family has been complaining
about this a lot.
Besides,
the apartment is
more and more expensive.
I just want to ask you
whether our Yutian's property has
discount for the staff.
Have a seat.
Qunfei,
your girlfriend thinks
you won't get married
without an apartment?
It can't be put in that way.
Everyone wants to pursue
better material conditions.
When is marriage equal to an apartment?
You're such a man of integrity.
In her eyes,
aren't you even as good as an apartment?
If you marry a woman like this,
can you live a good life in the future?
I'm telling you,
love and money
don't conflict with each other.
However, as long as one party thinks
money is the decisive factor,
this relationship won't last long.
Just like the housing price now,
nobody knows when it'll change.
So I can't help you with this.
It's not because I'm inconsiderate.
It's because
I hope you go back and think about it.
Qunfei,
what happened?
Criticized by the boss?
Or in trouble at work?
Family business.
No bright future for me.
Don't be upset in the early morning.
No big deal!
Have a coffee.
Perhaps I can help you out.
Come on.
Brother,
I have to speak for you.
Lei Yuzheng has been so unfair to you.
Isn't this
simple for him?
We can't put it this way.
I'm not capable enough.
I can't blame others.
How about Xiaosu?
Mr. Lei has returned her
that apartment, hasn't he?
Xiaosu,
she refused to live in that apartment.
Fine.
Why don't you go back
and tell your girlfriend and Xiaosu
not to worry.
I'll see what I can do.
Mr. Lin. It's...
It's not good.
Brother,
you can't ask this favor of Mr. Lei.
I can understand.
As a man,
you shall keep the final bottom line
and dignity.
I have endured the pain
of no response to my call for help.
I don't care you laugh at me.
I used to be driven away
by the landlord.
Where did I sleep?
In the park.
We're on the same boat.
Take it easy.
Mr. Lin.
I... Come on.
(Zou Siqi)
Siqi.
He Qunfei, come over here right now!
Hurry up! Hurry up...
Fine, I get it.
Don't give me this.
I'm telling you.
It's no use running out of your words.
We're divorcing!
The apartment is going to be sold!
Move out in three days!
Not negotiable!
Mrs. Li,
you think it's for my own sake?
This is for the sake of you two.
I'm also doing a favor for both of you.
I've been thinking about this
for a long time.
You haven't watched
any social news now, right?
So many people have faked their divorce
to buy a department.
You two have figured this out.
Abuse the system for formality.
But as long as it is sealed
by the office,
who can make it clear?
You are not a couple
any more.
Mr. Li, Mrs. Li.
The currently valid marriage law
has clarified the prenuptial property.
It's not relevant.
Dear Mrs. Li,
you really have to think about it.
What if at the end,
you lose both your husband and money,
who are you turning to?
He?
He wouldn't dare even if I allow him.
Darling.
I think we should think it over.
She has made the point.
We've been living such a good life.
Why make a fuss
for an apartment? Don't you think so?
Who are you with?
Look at yourself!
Can't you stare blankly
as long as there is beauty?
Don't you know what to do?
Who's the boss of this family?
I am!
We're divorcing!
Fuck off!
So disgraceful!
I've been used to you for so many years.
You're getting more and more ungrateful!
Don't you really think
I am a coward?
Look at this apartment!
It has become like a refugee camp.
Our son can't come back.
I have to cooperate with you to play.
The neighbours are all laughing at us.
For an apartment,
you campus belle has turned into
a domineering woman!
You want a divorce?
Fine!
Divorce!
Go to the office now!
If you're not coming,
you are
the domineering woman!
How dare you swear at me!
How dare you direct your anger at me!
How dare you get mad at me?
Divorce!
I can't live this anymore!
Oh, my!
Who's this for?
What's going on, baby?
What's going on? Baby. Let's go.
Go divorce! Who cares!
Well, well...
She's gone.
The lady has gone.
I thought
you really wanted to divorce me.
I was freaked out!
Have been acting with you, holy.
My husband is the best!
Shanghai's housing price
has been rising like looting.
I've checked around.
The one we're living now
is the best choice.
However,
we have to move out in three days.
Today I went to
the landlord to beg.
I saw Mr. Li
having a big fight with Mrs. Li.
Their fake divorce
may probably become true.
There is always a way.
It's not the third day yet.
There will be a way.
Right, Du Xiaosu has a good attitude.
Leave the well-furnished apartment there
as a decoration.
Live in the basement with others.
And play bitterness.
Awesome!
Fine. I know you have principles.
I know you have principles.
Who is it?
Siqi, where are you?
Why? Just say it, I'm upset!
I'm also asking the people I know
about the apartment.
Just now Mr. Lin told me
his friend's apartment is available.
And he is looking for the tenant.
Where is that apartment?
It's in the city center,
where you can see the
whole Huangpu River.
The location is pretty good.
Fine, I got it.
I'm leaving.
Qunfei needs me. Something emergent.
What? Is everything ok?
Everything is fine. Don't worry.
I'm leaving.
Be careful!
I will!
-Siqi, here you are.
-Lin Xiangyuan?
What are you doing here?
Show you around the apartment.
Come on.
Don't you rush to make the call.
Listen to me, please.
One of my very good friends.
He is abroad all the year round.
This apartment has been not occupied.
He Qunfei is eager to rent an apartment,
right?
I just asked about it.
On the one hand, I'm wondering
whether I can help.
On the other hand,
I want to find a tenant
for this apartment.
You know.
If the apartment isn't
occupied for long,
it will be aging.
What?
The apartment will be aging?
It's the first time
I've ever heard about it.
The most important is that
my friend is very rich.
This apartment is free for you to live.
Free?
Free.
Lin Xiangyuan.
What are you up to?
What do you have in your mind?
Siqi, you misunderstood me.
I, Lin Xiangyuan,
swear to the God,
I'm really just doing a favor.
Absolutely no other purpose or thoughts.
How about this?
Since we're here already,
let's go and have a look.
If you don't like it,
I won't force you.
Fine, let's go. Just take a look.
OK, get in the car.
Come in, I'll show you around.
How do you like it?
Do you like it?
It's too luxurious!
Your friend is so rich!
You provide us with such
a luxurious apartment
for free.
Are you sure?
Because we're friends.
Lin Xiangyuan,
I know you help us out of good will.
But I'm really sorry.
I don't know your friend.
I can't accept it.
In this case,
I should go.
No, no. Siqi,
don't get me wrong.
I swear to God,
this apartment really
belongs to my friend.
I'm just offering you a favor
incidentally.
I absolutely have nothing in my mind.
You've made the swear your mantra.
As far as I can see, the God
has been drown by your vows.
It'll be much easier for you to
go to the street,
and beguile those ignorant girls.
Fine, I know
in your mind, I am
a person to sail with the wind,
and sacrifice principle for profit.
Yes, you're right.
I wanna be a good person too.
I also wanna be a great person.
I'm fighting every day.
We came to live in this city.
If I don't work hard like this,
don't fight like this,
what can I do about it?
Do I have a choice?
Am I qualified to make the choice?
I'm just like you.
We are the people who come to
this city to work hard.
No connections.
Have no one to rely on.
We can only rely on ourselves.
Since we're all in the same dilemma,
we're in the same boat.
Siqi,
sometimes I'm wondering
what we're fighting for in this city.
Why are we working so hard?
When is the end of all of these?
Sometimes I'm too lonely.
I don't even have someone to talk to.
Can you understand?
You're right.
But I wanna ask you,
this apartment,
why don't you just give it to Xiaosu?
Siqi, do you think I don't want to?
You know what she's like.
It's impossible for her
to accept any help from me.
That's why I'm asking you.
Siqi,
please.
Will you?
Thank you.
Why are young and beautiful girls
like you so shameless?
Didn't you get me?
I'll give you another half a month.
I'll call police if you are still here.
Mrs. Li, it's not we don't wanna move.
It's just...
we haven't found a good apartment yet.
We'll move as soon as we find one.
Could you please excuse us?
Who are shameless?
Who are you scolding?
Siqi,
what's wrong with you?
You're begging me!
You cannot take advantage of us.
Besides,
the contract we assigned,
it clearly states that
if there is any change,
it is required to give one-month notice.
Are you able to read the contract?
Are you being unreasonable?
I'm unreasonable?
How?
This house is mine.
I told you last time
to move out within three days.
You didn't.
Now I'm giving you another half a month.
Am I unreasonable?
Who is unreasonable?
I'm not asking you to move right away,
considering it is nice to you.
Mrs. Li, calm down, please.
I'm not moving! I won't!
You wanna call the police? Go ahead!
Let's see if police help you
or us, the vulnerable group!
Siqi, save your words.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Li. My friend,
she's shot-tempered.
All right, I get it.
Half a month.
We will move out in half a month.
Hard day for you.
Don't be so angry!
This young lady is so sharp-tongued.
We got it. We'll move in half a month.
Bye.
I'm not done yet!
I'm having a headache,
and you really gave me a headache.
Why did you stop me?
Is there anyone like her?
Just come in and ask us to move out.
But it is her house after all.
That's why
we have to have our own apartment.
If you rent someone else's apartment,
you'll always have to
look at other people's face.
Half a month, what can we do?
Come on.
Don't be so sad.
I have a good news for you.
I went to see an apartment today,
and it was very good.
One staircase for one apartment,
with two bathrooms and two rooms.
Really?
Where is it?
City center.
We could just move there
for the time being.
And then we could spend more time
on apartment-hunting.
You got rich?
No, it's rent for free.
For free？
How is it possible?
It belongs to one of my relatives.
He just wants someone to look after it.
Come on.
Xiaosu, think no more.
I'm on it!
Just follow me!
We'll move there tomorrow.
OK, stop.
Three, two, one.
You can open your eyes.
Do you like it?
This is the place
we're going to move in.
Isn't it luxurious?
Look!
The french window with a full view.
The kitchen.
How is it?
From now on,
you can make breakfast for me here.
You're so mean.
Look over here.
Look, the chandelier! How beautiful!
It's beautiful.
Isn't the place we've been dreamt of?
Here is the bathroom.
I finally have my own bathroom!
What about it? Do you like it?
I've made up my mind.
This is for you.
This apartment is great. But...
We two
diligent and beautiful girls
help him look after the apartment.
He can't be happier, can he?
But we live in such a great apartment.
What a big favor it is!
Don't worry too much.
He's rich,
and money can be spent for years.
You mentioned it belongs to
your relative,
who's that?
It's...It's my...
It's my little aunt.
Her cousin,
and her colleague's friend
who works as engineer in Huawei.
You have no idea about his job.
He won't come back for years
when he's away for business.
Come on, think no more.
There's some place for you to live,
why do you care so much?
How about this?
You and Qunfei move in together.
It's your relative, not mine.
I'd better go back.
No, don't. Xiaosu.
It doesn't suit me.
Come on, he can't live here!
You cannot feed wolf
with lamb?
You're my friend.
If he lives here with me,
he'll try to take advantage of me.
I haven't made up my mind
to live with him.
I don't think it is right.
Cone on, Xiaosu.
I agree with Siqi.
I can't live here.
If Siqi lives here alone,
I'll be worried, right?
Stop thinking! Stop talking!
Bring in your luggage!
That's it. Hurry up!
Is it here?
Yes! Hurry!
I promise you.
There is absolutely no problem
with this apartment.
Make yourself at home.
How about this?
If the landlord
is unhappy,
we'll move out right away.
Great! Let's go!
Mr. Lei asks for our advice,
I'll make one point.
I still believe
the Global Entertainment Center
is a project with high risk.
As a real estate enterprise,
I admit that we can only accept it
with a certain reluctance.
But if we're going to launch
such a big project
of the Global Entertainment Center,
where does the money come from?
I hereby earnestly assure the board
the capital of this project
does not need additional investment
from shareholders.
After the project starts,
it will not be fully carried out
at one time.
If so,
there won't be
a large amount of money required.
The risk is also controllable.
Mr. Lei, are you saying
the project will be carried out
in stages?
Open the ones when they are ready.
If the profit is good,
we'll carry on the next stage,
aren't you?
Yes, that's more or less what I mean.
But I wanna blame myself for
not planning enough for this.
The staging plan of the project
is not completed yet.
I apologize for this.
But I also would like to ask
all the directors present today.
The Global Entertainment Center project
has been approved through voting
by the Board of Directors.
I wanna show my respect to you
to ask for your opinions again today.
So, I hope all of you can respect
the decision made by
the Board of Directors.
Anyway,
Uncle Li, thank you again.
I
grew up
under the watch of all of you.
I can benefit from
each of your suggestions and reminders.
Therefore,
I hope all of us can work together,
just like before,
lead Yutian to a next level.
Thank you all.
Is it Xiao Zhang
from the Financial Department?
Yes, it's me.
You're pretty efficient in
the reimbursement of
office supplies last time.
I'm gonna give you a like.
OK, I'll come over when I'm available.
Who is there?
Lin Xiangyuan?
What are you doing here?
What? I can't come, can I?
Not afraid to run into Du Xiaosu?
I know Xiaosu is at work today.
Siqi, who's that?
Qunfei, you are here too.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Siqi, I wanna talk to you.
Qunfei, stop cooking
and prepare some fruit.
Mr. Lin and I have something to discuss.
OK.
Come in, Mr. Lin.
Siqi,
I know
I'm a little bit rude this time.
Yutian's annual convention is tomorrow,
I know
Xiaosu is too busy to prepare
the clothes for the annual convention.
I, according to her figure,
help her make the choice of clothes.
You know that
if it's me to give it to her,
she will say no.
So
I wanna ask you for a favor,
please give it to her.
Don't tell her it's from me.
Xiaosu is my junior fellow
in the school.
She has a character.
She will say no if I give it to her,
Siqi, please, give it to her for me.
Dad, are you sure you're not going?
Yes.
You represent me with full authority.
Have you picked your dancing partner?
Not yet.
I think Fanlv is a good choice.
Is it Manager Zhu?
Few days ago, I tried on
an evening dress, do you remember?
That'll be great!
I'll have it picked up now.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪