[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 23]
Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I think you've all heard that.
The princess will set off two days later.
Give me an idea.
The craftsmen who could make the super bow
were all killed on the way to Kaifeng.
What do you think
we should do?
Your Majesty, are you going to
send the design drawing again?
Otherwise, why did I come to you?
I'm willing to set for Kaifeng immediately
with all staff in Wood Feather House
to make the super bows and defend the country.
That’s what I’m waiting for.
Luo, go get ready.
But what about the princess?
If she doesn't leave in two days,
the Northern Zhou will not give up that easily.
Before we reach Kaifeng,
the situation may become more tricky.
Since Your Majesty decided to send us to Kaifeng,
Your Majesty must have made a plan in mind.
Li Qingfeng,
you are indeed exceptionally smart.
So what's the plan?
Li Qingfeng, don't keep us guessing.
Tell us.
Sir,
do you remember
the plan you told me before?
My plan?
To take the princess away by force.
Now I remember.
So this is what you mean, Your Majesty.
Go. Go to take her.
Take the bride away?
Wang Sheng, listen up.
Yes.
I order you to follow Li Qingfeng
to leave the city together,
and secretly prepare an ambush in the Northern Zhou's escorting procession,
to save the princess.
Then you must escort the princess
and people of Wood Feather House
to Kaifeng city.
Without fail.
Yes, Your Majesty.
This plan is feasible.
It seems good.
We should have decided it earlier.
I didn't expect His Majesty and I have the same idea.
This trip is dangerous.
Miss Zhao, you have business and family concerns.
You'd better stay in Lin'an
and wait for our successful return.
No way.
I must go.
It is different from last time.
This time,
we have cut off all means of retreat.
It concerns Miss Chen's fate,
Wood Feather's fate,
and even your fate.
As a member of Wood Feather House
and your friend,
I must go.
But Mr. Zhao...
I will explain it to my father.
Don't worry.
Niaoniao, don't worry.
I will protect you.
With you by my side,
I'm not afraid to go
anywhere dangerous.
Luo, you…
I’ll leave you alone.
I’m leaving.
I'm sorry.
Pretty good.
Sir.
You really came at the right time.
I'm sorry this time.
I owe you a favor.
I don't need your favor.
Come on.
I'm talking about
your romantic opportunity to be alone with Miss Han.
Sir, what brings you here?
I have to go home.
If I don't come back in two hours,
come to my aid at the back door of my mansion.
Understand?
Got it.
Sir,
you should talk to your parents
in a serious way.
How can I not understand this?
Don't worry.
Just do as I say.
I know what to do with the rest.
Yining, do you have to go?
Yes.
Yining,
you are my only,
my only precious daughter.
What you are going to do
is like killing me.
Dad, you know that.
Fine.
I can't say that I allow you to go.
I only hope you to come back safely.
Don't say anything.
My dear daughter,
I don't care about anything in my life.
However,
the only one I can't let go
is you, my daughter.
Dad.
I promise you
I will come back safely.
Get up, my dear.
You must come back safely.
Come back safely.
Yuanxu,
you fetched us here all of a sudden.
I think you may have something important to tell me.
Mon and Dad,
have some tea.
There's no reason for you to show us excessive attention.
Tell me. What's the matter?
Have you and Luo decided
to get married?
No, no.
Luo.
Luo is going to the Northern Zhou.
Don't mention it.
I'm sad enough as it is.
Right.
According to the plan,
Princess Zhaohe will set off two days later.
That’s right.
Poor kid.
But Yuanxu,
don't be sad.
I will find a better girl
for you.
What are you talking about, Mom?
Don't you like Luo very much?
No other girl in the world
is better than Luo.
I know you are infatuated with her.
But you have to
move on, right?
Mom, don't worry about this.
He's right.
Tell us.
Why did you call us here?
Right. Why?
I have to inform you that
I am going to Kaifeng.
OK. Kaifeng.
Where did you say?
Dad, calm down.
Are you kidding?
This time, we just followed...
Follow? Follow who?
I think you're crazy.
Anyway, we're not trying to provoke the Northern Zhou.
Everything will be fine.
What do you mean by it?
You think I don't know that?
A few days ago,
the arrow-making craftsmen of the Ministry of War
were killed by secret agents from the Northern Zhou
just on their way to Kaifeng.
Aren't you now going to Kaifeng
for the same thing?
People of the Arrow-making House were officials,
so the secret agents from Northern Zhou would come.
But we are just a few craftsmen.
Besides, apart from the Arrow-making House,
Wood Feather House is the only one
that is able to make super bows.
Who else can go if we don't go?
But you
can't risk your life.
What will risk your life?
What are you two talking about?
What's going on?
Mom, Dad will tell you the details.
Today I came home to inform you that
I will come back from Kaifeng
in two months at best.
At worst,
I don't know how long it will take.
Anyway, don't worry about me.
No way.
I said I came to inform you,
not asking for permission.
What if you happen to meet the secret agents
of the Northern Zhou?
If we meet them,
we will be sure to die.
No way. I won't allow it either.
Dad, Mom, why can't you expect something good?
I've been blessed since I was young.
I will be fine.
My kid, don't scare me.
Just stay in Lin'an.
And leave alone Wood Feather House.
Mom. Dad.
I'm really not a good son.
In the past,
I was the most merry-making idler in Lin'an.
Until I entered Wood Feather,
and followed the princess, my master,
I gradually became serious about life.
Now I want to do something good
to the country and the people.
Please allow me.
It's also a good thing to build houses.
You don't have to risk your life.
Your dad is right.
But if Lin'an is no longer Lin'an,
Xiao Dynasty no longer exists,
and people become homeless,
whom can we build houses for?
But it's not up to us
whether Xiao Dynasty continues to exist.
Dad,
you always wanted me to get admission
and become an official.
I always dreamed of being a hero
to uphold the justice.
Actually, I'm not that capable.
I can't be
either an official or a hero.
I have let you down.
It may be that Mom often burns incense
to pray for me before gods.
Even if I didn't become an official,
I've understood the meaning of being loyal to the country and the people.
Dad, I promise you
that I will be back safe and sound after two months.
In the future,
I’ll be the son who makes you proud.
Mom, take it as my trip to Kaifeng
to bring back
your daughter-in-law Luo.
This is my only chance.
I won't let it go.
Please forgive your unfilial son.
[Wood Feather House]
Sir, why are you in such a good mood?
He is certainly very happy
to have his family's approval.
This will be my first time to take someone else's bride,
and the bride is my master.
I can not only bring back my master
but also defeat that bastard, He Zhigu.
How can I not be in a good mood?
Right.
Taking the bride on imperial orders,
I'm afraid, is the only chance in the world.
Miss Zhao is here.
Of course I should be here.
Every single one in Wood Feather House is needed.
Miss Zhao.
[Wood Feather House]
Miss Zhao, Mr. Zhang is here.
Mr. Zhang is well informed.
Why are you here?
I was told you’re going to Kaifeng.
Why didn’t you tell me in advance?
It’s so urgent.
I can't even prepare something for you.
Mr. Zhang, I've told you before.
Alright.
I knew it. I know.
Here are some cakes and pastries made by my baker.
[Wood Feather House]
Take it on the way.
As long as the food box is not open wide,
it will taste the same even after 7 or 8 days.
[Wood Feather House]
It's much better than solid food.
Take it.
It's good.
Thank you.
[Wood Feather House]
Architect Li, I heard a few days ago
a troop of our soldiers was killed outside the city.
You must be careful this time.
We are not officials,
but just a small team of craftsmen.
We won't be discovered by the Northern Zhou.
Don't worry, Mr. Zhang.
Miss Zhao, promise me
you must come back safely.
I will.
Architect Li.
I can tell the bad news from your face.
What happened?
The ministers who advocate peace were against His Majesty,
kneeling down in front of the palace
and unwilling to get up.
His Majesty was furious.
And then?
The Minister of Revenue would rather be beheaded than appropriate funds,
claiming that he doesn't want to be a sinner.
Then behead him.
If you want to behead him,
you have to kill half of the six ministries.
[Wood Feather House]
Are we not going there?
It's useless for us to go now.
If it's just us who
make all the super bows
and complete the city defense,
we can't complete it until next life.
Come on. I told my parents.
I was almost crying.
It's embarrassing for me to go back now.
Unload the carriage.
Unload it.
Are you serious?
Qingfeng.
I
don't want you to leave.
I know.
You've understood me the best since we were little.
I always think that
how good it would be
if we didn't grow up.
I still remember, in our childhood,
Father was reading in the study,
and we had fun outside the study,
being so carefree
and happy.
You even taught me to catch crickets
and taught me archery.
My arrow
accidentally hit Father's window.
Then he rushed out and scolded us.
He was so angry and fierce.
But he still asked the imperial kitchen
to cook a lot of delicious food for us.
In the whole palace,
you were the most naughty kid,
behaving like a hoyden.
Father asked me to read The Great Learning and The Doctrine of the Mean,
while you were reading anecdotes for me.
Father asked you to learn music, chess, calligraphy and painting,
while you went to the Ministry of Works
to create those mechanisms and woodware.
Even so,
I was still high in favor with Father and Brother.
Yes.
In the palace,
everyone wanted to win Father's favor.
They tried their best and racked their brains,
leaving no peace place in the palace.
Only you
who dared to
act recklessly,
but still kept the innocence of children.
But Brother,
I'm not a child
any more.
Before Father died,
he asked me
to take good care of you
to protect your childish heart all your life.
I
feel guilty for Father.
I know very well
your love for me.
But in the end,
I had to grow up.
Langyue.
Do you think
I am a good emperor?
I've known two good emperors.
One is my father,
and the other is my brother.
But I have to send my own sister
to the barbarian Northern Zhou,
making her not only suffer from homesickness,
but also
become the meat on the enemy's chopping block.
But Brother,
it's for the prosperity of Xiao Dynasty.
That's what a good emperor should do.
But Li Qingfeng
would certainly not think so.
Why did you mention him?
Because he is the one you care about.
I know
what happened between you two.
When he came to me with the drawing of super bow,
I saw in his eyes
the same thing as that in your eyes.
He also begged me
to keep you here.
Are you sure
not to see him again?
Rest early.
If I see him again,
I’m afraid, even if I die,
I won’t leave him any more.
Mom, we are back.
Greetings, Mrs. Meng.
Don't stand on ceremony, Luo.
Sir,
can I talk to Mrs. Meng alone?
Why do you have to avoid me?
It's nothing to worry about.
But there's something
I can't speak in front of you.
Please wait for me at the door.
OK?
Just leave as she says.
OK.
Luo, if you have anything to say,
come and sit down.
Mrs. Meng,
he must have told you.
Tomorrow I will
accompany the princess to the Northern Zhou.
I know.
But what do you mean?
I have been wearing it for so long.
It’s God’s gift
and my blessing.
Now
it's time to return it to its owner.
Since Yuanxu gave it to you,
he's sure to want you to his wife.
I'm also sure that you should be my daughter-in-law.
But why are you leaving?
Are you
not willing to accept us?
I am willing to.
Nothing can make me more willing than that.
But I clearly know
I can't be your daughter-in-law.
Please
find a good match for him.
There must be someone
who is more suitable to wear the bracelet than me.
Luo.
Do you know how much Yuanxu loves you?
I know.
He treats me very well.
But I owe the princess a debt of gratitude.
How can I let the princess
face the ferocity of foreign country alone?
Therefore,
I can only repay
his love in the next life.
I understand your feelings as master and maid.
But I know Yuanxu well.
He may look careless,
but once he is determined,
he will devote everything to that person.
If you leave,
he will be overwhelmed with sorrow.
Please help him forget me.
Take a look.
How is it?
It's utterly natural,
poetic imagery beauty.
I don't know if you're praising me
or yourself.
Most importantly,
this painting
was drawn by us together.
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
It's not that I don't want to let you go,
♫I feel so safe♫
but I
♫My dreams are all about you♫
can't let go
all the people in this country.
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
♫Just want to meet you again♫
♫I am so lucky♫
♫You did not give up♫
After this drink,
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
I’ll go back to the palace.
♫You'll show me the world♫
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
♫Ask your heart♫
♫Even if only a drop♫
♫A drop of love is left♫
♫I would love to♫
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you're still up?
I'll get you some hot water.
You can wash your face and rest.
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
♫I feel so safe♫
♫My dreams are all about you♫
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
♫Just want to meet you again♫
♫I am so lucky♫
♫You did not give up♫
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
Your Highness, I brought you some hot water.
♫You'll show me the world♫
Your Highness, what are you doing?
♫Put on a wedding dress for you♫
It's useless to keep them.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
♫Ask your heart♫
♫Even if only a drop♫
No.
♫A drop, a drop♫
♫A drop of love is left♫
♫I would love to♫
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
In doing so,
♫Fly round and round♫
I can no longer have longings.
My lady.
♫Fly into your arms♫
Do you still like to call me lady?
♫Ask your heart♫
It's my mistake.
♫Even if only a drop♫
♫A drop, a drop♫
♫A drop of love is left♫
♫I would love to♫
Qingfeng.
Langyue.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, I deserve to die.
What happened?
I failed to keep an eye on Luo.
Luo is missing.
Luo is missing?
Have you searched everywhere?
I've searched every place
but still can't find her.
Silly Luo.
Where did you hide?
Your Highness.
20 maids of the palace
are waiting in the yard.
Would you like to take a look?
Let’s go.
[Zhaohe Palace]
Luo.
Your Highness.
Wang Xi.
Don't come over.
What are you doing?
Your Highness.
I know what you think.
But even if I die here today,
I'll go north with you.
Don't do silly things.
Your Highness.
I'm silly.
Even if the sun were to rise in the west,
I'll go to the Northern Zhou with you.
If you want to abandon me,
I’d rather die.
[Hanyuan Hall]
Your Majesty, it’s time.
Summon her.
Welcome, Princess Zhaohe.
[Hanyuan Hall]
His Majesty's command.
Here I issue an emperor's command.
By admiring the late emperor's virtues,
for the peace of the country,
for the security of the land,
I granted a marriage between the two states of Xiao and Zhou.
The couple are destined to be together.
Since Xiao and Zhou unite by marriage,
I confer a title of Princess Nanping on Princess Zhaohe,
with an imperial edict and official costumes.
The command is accompanied by documentation.
May you behave yourself,
with self-esteem and self-discipline,
to promote the country's civilization
and make peace between the two states.
Show your respect to the country,
and your loyalty to me.
That's all.
Thank you.
Your Majesty.
Langyue, take care.
Brother, take care.
Farewell, Princess Nanping.
Brother.
[Xiangrui Cloth Store]
It's the princess.
Your Highness! Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Farewell, Your Highness.
[Lin'an]
Coming.
Your Highness!
Luo.
Your Highness.
Your Highness. Luo.
Li Qingfeng.
The birds in hometown were still chirping.
[Lin'an]
The Princess left home in sorrowful melody.
The soul buried in grassy tomb would never return.
Who was the handprint on the lush cliff left for?
Please.
How is he?
He's full of depression and anxiety.
Does he have something worried in his mind?
Don't mention it, old man.
Boss,
fill the prescription I wrote down.
Take it twice in the morning and at night.
He will get better in seven days.
But...
But what?
If what he worries can't be solved,
his melancholy can't be dispelled and relieved.
As time goes on, it may hurt his liver and gall,
further turning into a chronic disease,
and even risking his life.
OK.
Got it, doctor.
Thank you.
See you.
Well, now,
some left, and some got sick.
Boss Luo,
I would like to invest more to Wood Feather.
You can go back.
Don't worry too much.
If Mr. Zhao refuses to lend you money,
come to the Zhang's Mansion to find me.
Have you ever thought about how much is needed
to build the city defense?
I'll give it to you as long as you ask.
The number doesn't matter.
I think I need to make it clear to you.
I have only
friendship for you,
never affection.
But affection
is the only requirement for me to choose a husband.
I know you like me.
Just like I liked Li Qingfeng before.
But he never liked me.
And I
have never liked you.
Mr. Zhang,
we can't force our feelings.
I'm a straightforward person.
I hope you can forgive me.
So go back.
I see.
Mr. Zhang,
thank you for sending me back.
Five million taels.
If
one of your seven brothers dares to say that,
I will scold him severely.
But Yining, you said it.
It's quite another matter.
But you must tell me the truth.
You want to borrow so much money from me.
What for?
Invest Wood Feather House.
What a joke!
Such a small team of craftsmen.
If you just invest it,
how can you spend so much money?
Go to Kaifeng to make super bows
and rebuild the city defense.
What did I say?
I knew it.
Last time,
you risked your own safety
and went to Kaifeng.
Are you going to bet
the whole Zhao family's life this time?
Yining, if you were me,
what will you do?
Alright.
Listen to me.
Don't mention it again.
I've heard about it.
Mr. Sun, the Minister of Revenue,
openly opposed the imperial edict in the court.
His purpose was not to appropriate the funds.
Think about it.
Even the emperor couldn't do this.
Why should our Zhao family do it?
Zhao family won't be involved.
Zhao family won't be involved?
If we do this,
our family is involved.
Think about it.
How important it is to rebuild the city defense.
If people with evil intentions investigate it,
they will know
Wood Feather House is invested by our Zhao family.
Can you say
it has nothing to do with our family?
Isn't it a kind of involvement?
Even if we're involved,
is this something to be ashamed of?
It's not something to be ashamed of.
It's something to get beheaded.