''A Girl With A Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Could it be that I am really Hua Xiaolei?
Tomorrow, go with me to visit your father.
From now on, I'm Hua Que.
When will you stop acting this scene?
Now that you've reunited, naturally it would be more appropriate for you to stay at your home.
Not to mention the birthmark but every part of your body, I know it all.
I don't care if you believe me or not, but I'm not Hua Xiaolei.
When will Chun Hua and Qiu Yue come to an end? The feeling is quite good.
You can still continue to be my brother, Qiu Yue.
[Episode 10]
[Hua Residence]
The one who had a love affair with Shangguan Qiu Yue is Hua Xiaolei.
It's really not me.
Little Chun Hua.
Are you sleeping?
I'm sleeping. I'm already sleeping. You can't come in.
It's not good for us to stay in the same room.
I urge you! You should give up on this idea. All right?
Did you hear me?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
I know! I know you definitely came in.
Don't scare me all the time like this!
I'm telling you, I'm so good at kicking people's butts.
So good! See! Don't come over here.
I still remember what you promised me today.
What on earth do you want?
"As long as you don't tell Xiao Bai,"
"I can do whatever you want."
Young Master.
I just passed by a small stall on the road,
and I learned some tricks and methods to read someone's fortune from their face.
Watch closely!
I see this Young Master's space
between your eyebrows with happy eyes is glossy and smooth.
Today's matters must be good.
The Hua family has finally reunited.
I also have a clear conscience about my father's last words.
In addition, I've sorted things with Uncle Hua.
After Uncle Hua saw Miss Xiaolei, what reaction did he have?
He was happy, of course! Brother Hua even rushed a special trip to return.
As long as you don't tell Xiao Bai,
I can do whatever you want.
So, is this what you want me to do?
The one whose ice silk pearl stops glowing first,
has to agree to a condition of the other person.
You're so childish.
Ice silk, Baby, fighting!
Little Chun Hua, wait for your punishment.
Idiot!
You cheated.
You didn't say I couldn't cheat.
In this game, you weren't supposed to lose.
- Why not?
- Have you forgotten what I told you?
These two pearls interact with and care for each other.
If one of them dies, it will be difficult for the other to survive.
- So?
- As long as mine still glows,
yours won't stop.
However, after hearing what you said, I think
this Brother Hua is a bit suspicious.
- What do you mean?
- It's normal to express family affection after a long separation.
But at least, they should have some scruples about etiquette.
Brother Hua can't make Miss Hua Xiaolei lose face in front of guests.
Maybe Uncle Hua was a little too excited, so Brother Hua just spoke up for him.
You think too much.
Why were you making that sound?
Can't I say it? I can't express any opinion about Miss Xiaolei.
Anyway, how is Miss Xiaolei's memory loss?
Is there any progress?
There was nothing strange about the reunion of Uncle Hua and Xiaolei.
I think... we must think of another way.
Miss Chun Hua.
Xiao Bai.
Why don't you return to Fengming Mountain Manor with me?
Not good!
Why not good?
Unless...
Unless you marry me.
Doesn't Little Chun Hua need your brother?
Oh! Brother!
What's wrong?
Everything I said just now was
only talking in my sleep.
So in Little Chun Hua's heart, I'm such a mean person then?
How could that be? Of course, not!
How could that be possible? That's impossible.
If you're mean or not, in your heart, don't you know the answer?
Good to know! Then quickly change your clothes and go with me to see father.
Come with me to pay our respects to father.
You are still so immersed in your act, aren't you?
I need to change my clothes so do you think you should...
Go ahead and change! I'm your brother so what are you afraid of?
My own brother also can't...
Why don't... you turn around?
All right.
If you don't hurry more, Xiao Bai will leave soon.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
What did you say? Is Xiao Bai here?
Really? Where is he?
Xiao Bai! Xiao Bai, you've come.
Father, I'd like to pay my respects to you.
Greetings, Hero Xiao.
Brother Hua, thanks for your hospitality to allow my early morning visit.
Please forgive me.
Hero Xiao, there's no need for formalities.
Hero Xiao, if you have something to say, please don't hesitate.
Please sit!
My father is ill so I can't stay for too long.
Since the matter regarding Xiaolei has been resolved,
I plan to set out and return home immediately.
Such being the case, I also won't demand that you stay longer.
Remember to go back and greet your dad on our behalf.
Finally, I can get rid of this ill-fated relationship and return to the main story.
Goodbye, Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Wait!
About the marriage contract...
I was just about to mention the marriage contract.
Our Xiao family will keep our words.
We've found Xiaolei so we can fulfill the marriage contract.
I will once more select an auspicious day for Xiaolei and I to get married.
Yes! Yes! That's how it should proceed.
Hero Xiao, you truly don't bear in mind the Hua family.
Brother Hua, why would you say such a thing?
Though the Hua family can't equal the Fengming Mountain Manor,
our family is still considered one of the very best influential families.
How can you casually remark and muddle through our previous agreement?
I was being thoughtless.
Brother Hua, if you worry the Xiao family will treat Xiaolei unfairly,
I will dispatch someone first to bring betrothal gifts.
There will be many more gifts than before.
Master Hua, what do you think?
Regardless how many betrothal gifts you send, I have only one little sister.
Then, Brother Hua, what do you mean exactly?
Call off the marriage.
-  What?
- What!
Xiaolei, don't get agitated.
I also agree with this statement.
If I was careless in any point, please instruct and tell me my mistakes.
It's only that, if you want to suddenly cancel
without reason, it cannot be justified.
All right! Since Hero Xiao has mentioned the reason,
then I'll take the time and explain to you.
Regarding reason,
the Hua family sent our most treasured jewel to the Fengming Mountain Manor,
but she fled for her life almost dying in a large fire.
Although she returned with her life and survived,
she has changed, been in a daze, and been acting foolish.
She can't remember even the slightest bit of the past.
There is no shirking this responsibility.
I truly apologize to Xiaolei.
Don't apologize so quickly.
Let me ask you! Fengming Mountain Manor is known as martial arts of Bei Dou,
but you cannot protect even a young girl.
If she was your younger sister,
would you entrust her to someone like you?
This... this...
We still don't clearly know about this matter but you simply place all the responsibilities on Xiao Bai's shoulders.
Regarding affection,
Sister is still young.
I would hate to see her married off having a rough time.
She should wait a few more years to keep me company at home.
Father! Father, please reconsider.
Then I'll hand responsibility for this matter over to father and brother.
This is a matter of great importance.
Since Uncle Hua and Brother Hua already have other plans,
I need to report to my father, then I will give you an answer.
I'll take my leave.
No, Xiao Bai! Xiao Bai!
Xiao Bai...
I give this back to you!
Sister, why are you so angry?
You still have the nerve to ask me that?
There are so many people in this world.
Why do you insist on making things difficult for me alone?
It was you, Little Chun Hua, who personally told me
I can do whatever I want.
Yes.
But I already played with these ice silk pearls with you.
Little Chun Hua acted shamelessly and cheated, so that doesn't count.
Then tell me, what on earth do you want to get me out of this?
Sister, you are very silly.
I think Xiao Bai doesn't have sincere feelings for you.
Xiao Bai already said he wants to marry me.
- If you didn't put obstacles in his way, I could already be...
- Mistress Xiao, right?
Xiao Bai and I,
we originally had an engagement agreement, hadn't we?
We have an affinity for each other.
We were innocent playmates and childhood sweethearts.
If it weren't for you causing every kind of trouble,
how else could I be subject to so much suffering?
But now, as luck would have it,
Xiao Bai has left.
My engagement is gone.
You should compensate me!
You are still terrible to me.
You say that you're my brother,
then you should act like a brother.
- Why do you...
- Sister, enough!
Don't cry!
You are so ugly when you cry.
Even more so, you are saying I'm ugly!
You said I'm ugly!
Forget it! You can leave.
You're lying to me again.
You're keeping an eye on me here so how can I leave?
You have your own legs.
You are free to go anywhere.
I know! If I leave,
- then you'll just...
- Where's the fun in killing you?
Then you...
won't tell Xiao Bai
about that matter, right?
That is exactly to say,
this matter is something that only Hua Xiaolei did.
I don't have anything to do with that so why should I clean up her awful mess?
Has it nothing to do with you?
At any rate, I have lost my memory, haven't I?
This argument is so peculiar.
I don't know whether Xiao Bai will think the same way or not.
Then... I am really going.
You will be back.
You big obstacle, where does your confidence come from?
Brother are right! Everything Brother says is right.
This is my home, isn't it?
You should wait for me here. I'll certainly come back to see Older Brother.
[Hua Residence]
Little Chun Hua already left.
What method should I use to make her come back obediently of her own accord?
I have an idea you can try.
Say it.
If Xiao Bai comes back, then so will Miss Chun Hua.
Interesting, keep talking!
Everyone knows the thing Young Master Xiao cares about the most
is the longevity fruit.
Now that you mention it, I didn't hear any news of the longevity fruit in a while.
I understand. I will get to work.
Longevity fruit?
Sisi, recently, it's rumored that
the longevity fruit flows out of the healer's hands,
and it can bring the dead back to life.
Where on earth could there be such a wonderful thing?
Husband, I don't believe in it.
As long as I'm able to cure your illness,
even if there's just a sliver of hope,
I still believe in it.
What is this?
Take a look, Wife.
[A prize for guessing correctly]
It's a lantern riddle.
The red string is a lantern riddle. The string!
It is related to me.
Let me think about it.
A colored string...
means the character for "cut off."
Cut...
A dead end?
A hopeless situation?
My husband,
why does it sound a bit unlucky?
Sisi, you always love to think too much.
It's actually a compliment.
It means "a remarkably beautiful woman."
Master, I have news about Mr. Shi.
Brother Xiao, have you really decided to return like this?
The Hua family unexpectedly called off the engagement.
I did not foresee this.
I plan to make a decision after discussing it with my father.
- Too bad! Marriage arrangement has separated so many lovers.
- I heard the longevity fruit surfaced again.
Quick, go and take a look.
The longevity fruit?
Chief.
Chief Leng.
Chief Leng is on our side, so there's no need to be secretive.
According to my scouts, clues to the longevity fruit have resurfaced.
Where is it?
Yetan City, with the Hua family.
[Official Notice: Longevity fruit calmly waits for the man who is destined. If interested, see the Hua family.]
- The Hua family?
- Who is the destined man?
Yes! "The destined man..." What's going on?
To the Hua! Excuse me.
I wondered why Xiao Bai suddenly planned to go to Yetan City to see the festival lanterns.
Now I see that he made these plans ahead of time.
He wants to grab the longevity fruit first before others.
Since you trust me,
then I will act according to your plan.
The guest you're talking about has already left.
Left? When did he leave?
He's been gone for a while now.
I don't know any martial arts.
If I want to chase after Xiao Bai,
I'll never catch up with him.
Don't worry! It'll be done soon.
Now, be careful!
- Eat while it's hot.
- Buns! Hot steamed buns!
Sir, I'll have two orders of steamed buns.
Miss Caicai?
Miss Chun Hua?
Miss Chun Hua, what are you doing here?
I still want to elope with you.
Steamed meat buns!
Why did you all leave so quickly?
Just now when I returned to the inn, the young innkeeper said you all left.
But why have you returned?
There's an important matter so I must return to the Hua family.
I... I finally got away from the Hua family after so much trouble. What?
And now are you saying you want to return?
Xiao Bai, let me tell you this,
our marriage doesn't need my brother's and father's approvals. Truly!
- If we return to Fengming Mountain Manor, we can...
- It's not about that.
Listen! You truly don't need to be afraid of my brother or father.
- I'm being serious. You just need to...
- Miss Chun Hua.
Right now, the longevity fruit appeared at the Hua residence.
The chief of the martial arts circles has been waiting for it to save his life.
Therefore, this matter is of the greatest urgency.
So he's not returning for my sake.
This time, I think only we three should go.
Miss Feng and Miss Leng, just return to the inn and wait for my news.
[Hua Residence]
My Sister! My Sweet Sister, where have you been?
Father and I were so worried about you.
It's fine! What matters is you've returned home. Let's go!
Brother Hua.
When did you two get here?
Thank you, Hero Xiao, for personally escorting Xiaolei home.
But there's nothing for you here, you should leave now.
Wait a moment, Brother Hua!
Haven't we said that Xiaolei is not marrying you?
Hero Xiao, how can you have no sense of shame?
Brother Hua, you're crossing the line.
Regardless if Xiaolei marries him or not, the Xiao and Hua families all are old friends.
- Brother Hua, you should not lose your sense of propriety.
- And who might you be?
So what if I lost my sense of propriety?
Brother Hua, please listen to my brief remarks.
The reason I'm here is absolutely not due to the engagement matter, but for a much more critical issue.
May I have a word with you in private?
Why can't you say it here?
I'm afraid that this place is not quite suitable.
Hero Xiao, if you're unable to speak clearly,
then forgive me for being unable to accompany you.
- Butler! Send them away.
- Brother Hua, to be honest,
I want to ask you about the matter of the longevity fruit.
Well, regarding that, it's really not appropriate to speak here.
Please come in!
Thank you.
I said you will hate to part with me but I didn't expect you to return so quickly.
When Xiao Bai finishes tending to his affairs, he'll take me away with him. You'll see!
I hope so.
You all may take your time but I'm taking my leave now.
Hero Xiao, could it be that you'd like to question us separately?
Brother Hua, why would you say such a thing?
The one whom my sister fell in love with is indeed smart.
If I'm guessing correctly, just now, that young master
is going to looking for my father.
Am I right?
Xiao Bai is definitely not the complicated man that you say he is.
Brother Hua, since you get straight to the point,
there's no need for me to hold back.
Brother Hua, I hope you can understand how I need the longevity fruit to save my father.
Of course, I understand your difficulties, Hero Xiao.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have let you all in.
Come to speak of it,
does Brother Hua know the location of the longevity fruit?
This...
Sister,
do you think we should tell Hero Xiao
our Hua family secret?
Does our family have a secret?
You're joking around again! Have you forgotten what happened yesterday?
Y-Yesterday?
Yesterday... y-yesterday?
Xiao Bai, what is he talking about? I truly have no idea.
Since you don't want to talk about it,
then I must become an unfilial son.
To tell you the truth, the longevity fruit is at our manor,
but as to where it is exactly, I'm also not sure.
I only remember very late last night,
my father told me to prepare paper and ink.
He said he wanted to write an official notice.
So Master Hua wrote the notice?
I never wrote any kind of notice.
Moreover, I don't even know what the longevity fruit is.
Someone must be purposely framing me.
Uncle Hua, if you don't feel at ease,
I can give you my guarantee.
If you have any terms or conditions, please do not hesitate to tell me.
This is truly preposterous!
I have urged my father before,
since the longevity fruit is in our hands,
why don't we just give it to Sect Master Xiao?
It would be a great contribution to the martial arts circles.
Moreover, our families are longtime friends.
However, he didn't think so.
Contrary to expectations, Father simply did not understand this logic.
He still insisted on announcing this to the whole world.
He said he wants to sell it for a good price.
Oh, that's right! Hero Xiao, speaking of my sister's wedding,
Actually, I've been in awe and admiring you this entire time.
It's just that my father fears affection will grow in Sister's heart,
and she will steal the fruit for the Xiao family in partiality.
Therefore, we decided to break off the engagement.
No, no, no! Not that.
I truly did not know anything about this matter. Truly!
Brother Hua, you must tell me all you know for me to come to my own conclusion.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫