''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominating the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique, secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Qianyue Sect kills the innocent and endangers the pugilist world.
This demon sect is so vicious.
I need to draw a clear distinction with them.
Xiao Chun Hua doesn't remember that she is my sister.
Cave Master, why did you pretend to be her older brother?
Since you have lost your memories, then let us start over again.
I dote on you so much, shouldn't you help me?
Brother, why do you always make it difficult for them?
We are the opponents with the upright track.
Since Older Brother really needs the Xin Fa,
I will go back to the Fengming Manor to get it.
We, Fengming Mountain Manor, will definitely stop Qianyue Sect's crime.
[Episode 3]
Senior, you know me too well.
This time, I need you to do me a favor.
This time, is it the filial debt?
Or is it the affair debt?
Both kinds of debt.
My dad believes that family comes first and career comes the second.
So he is pushing me to get married.
You also know that I don't have a place for anyone in my heart.
Avoidance is just a temporary measure.
Spring flowers bloom in Fengming Manor.
Beautiful scenery is pleasant to the eyes.
Xiao family is the heavenly place to be free from sorrows.
Brother Qin, you can directly say it if you have anything.
Senior Xiao, when there is a beautiful girl around you,
why do you have such a long face?
The girl you saw just now,
is indeed the one I brought back from Baxian residence.
She doesn't know kungfu at all,
but she was there when the healer was killed and
she also lost her memory.
Her identity and background, both are suspicious.
I had no results after talking to her. So I hope—
As long as you take me in,
I will do everything I can.
What can you do?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Miss, you are here idling.
It took me ages to find you.
I even thought about going to find Young Master Qin myself,
unexpectedly he has come here in person.
After all, I am considerate toward a beauty.
What a playboy!
Just now you said you wanted to see me, I guess that something has troubled you.
Little Chun, I'm right, am I not?
If you guess it wrong, then you really don't live up to the title of your narcissism.
Young Master Qin, how smart you are!
Actually, I wanted to ask you.
What on earth does Xiao Bai like?
This is a good question! He likes weapons, kungfu, musical instruments, and similar things.
As a disciple from an influential family, you could say he has knowledge in a wide range of subjects, and is too profound to be understood.
Then what does he dislike?
This is also a good question. Young Master is broad-minded
and never gossips about others.
That's not helpful at all!
I think you care less about the things he likes
but more about the people he likes.
Am I right?
I didn't expect Young Master Qin to be such an honest man.
Oh right,
I heard that Xiao Bai had a marriage arrangement before?
You're referring to the daughter of the Hua family?
The Hua family is rich.
Miss Hua is beautiful and smart.
It just that fate messes with people.
She passed away before she could meet in the matrimony with young master.
But...
- But what?
- But Miss Hua's death was very strange.
The fire burnt down the bridal chamber,
but her corpse was never found.
Don't you think that's strange?
Disappearing from the face of the earth, that means
Xiao Bai and I are destined to be together.
Miss, where did that confidence come from?
I'm not telling you.
Originally, I was going to invite Young Master on the morrow
to do lunch together but now, under this circumstance...
I might have thought too much into it.
Wait! Have lunch together?
Where? Just me and Xiao Bai?
11:45 in Qian Hua Xuan.
As for the participants, sorry, I will also be there.
That's fine! Just eat more and talk less.
Thank you. I'll go find some nice clothes.
Master, here is Hengshan Sect’s Xin Fa.
Sell it on the market.
This...
Just say what's on your mind.
I am slow-witted.
I don't understand why you want to sell what we worked so hard to get.
Why would I care about such shoddy kungfu?
What is the foundation of each group?
Movement and mantra.
Their movements are not rare but their mantra is precious to them.
I want what they treasure to become worthless.
The impartial justice of the martial arts world is just like this, isn't it?
I will do what they won't do.
I understand.
This kind of task should be done by the hard-hearted Master Shi.
Yes.
Three books is not enough.
I don't know how well my silly sister
is stealing the Xiao family's Xin Fa.
What is it, Brother Qin?
If Miss Chun Hua isn't a master of disguise to the extent where even I can’t see through her,
then she really lost her memory.
It seems her identity still cannot be confirmed.
Brother Qin, I also have a favor to ask.
Go ahead and ask.
Brother Xiao, what's the meaning of this?
- That's not right.
- What is it that's not right?
The sword is wrong.
After the incident, I inspected the corpse of the healer.
That sword had directly stabbed the heart.
It didn’t miss by any tiny deviation.
Now that I think about it, it was from a chisel.
Brother Qin, I apologize for offending you.
Is there anything else that’s suspicious?
There’s something else that’s even more suspicious. That palm print!
The healer's death wasn’t caused by a stab from the chisel?
When I was inspecting the corpse of the healer,
there was a faint palm print.
This palm had stopped the beating of his heart.
To have easily injured him to this extent, I'm really not sure who is capable of this in the pugilist world.
Besides, to be killed in such condition,
the healer's character isn’t that bad to the extent of suffering the wrath of Heaven, is he?
What do you think?
In my opinion, the healer's death
was probably caused due to being caught off-guard by a surprise attack.
I concur.
Xiao Bai?
Miss Chun Hua’s clothes are extremely exquisite today.
One look and you know that it was put together at the tailor shop.
What do you know?
This is specially tailored for the date between Xiao Bai and I.
Each stitch represents my sincere feelings towards Xiao Bai.
You wear your affections for him on your body,
- but Xiao Bai–
- Qin Liufeng, shut up!
It’s your fault for talking too much. Even Xiao Bai is standing up for me.
What is this?
This is the ginseng soup I made for Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai has to practice martial arts every day. It’s very tiring,
so he must drink more.
Since this feast is prepared for Brother Qin,
it still would be better if he eats more.
How can I enjoy this delicious food alone? Come! Let’s enjoy it together.
Thank you, Miss Chun Hua.
Miss Chun Hua.
If an attack is from an acquaintance,
this is how the expression in the eyes and the state of the limbs would be.
Xiao Bai, you are finally beginning to understand.
I only pushed her and it naturally left no trace.
Your analysis is correct.
Thus, we can pinpoint the murderer as someone whom the healer was familiar with.
Thank you, Brother Qin.
It hurts so much.
Come! Let’s set aside work-related matters for now.
Please forgive my rash action.
Have a seat!
Then let me toast this cup of light wine to Brother Qin’s arrival.
Also, thank you, Miss Chun Hua, for dressing up for this feast.
You’re welcome!
Miss Chun Hua, this is our hometown’s specialty.
You must definitely try it and see if it is to your taste.
Then I won’t… stand on ceremony.
Using fish as an example,  a person who likes eating the fishtail is probably from a poor family.
A person who likes eating the fish belly is probably the youngest in the family.
And a person who likes eating the fish gill
is bound to be from a wealthy family.
Young Master Qin is really skillful!
- You flatter me.
- When eating fish, the most delicious part
is at the fish… belly!
What else does the fish belly mean?
Fish belly has much meat and is a favorite for children in poor families.
Could it be that her family is in dire circumstances?
This fish is a little spicy.
But… I like it.
The Southerners like sweet, Northerners like salty, Easterners like spicy, and Westerners like sour.
According to her taste, we can find out the location of her hometown.
She likes spicy? Is she really from Sangtian Village?
This beancurd, its taste is fine and smooth.
It's sweet but not too rich. So delicious!
Here, Young Master. Let’s toast. Cheers!
There are rumors in the pugilist world that the healer found the longevity fruit but was unexpectedly murdered.
The whereabouts of the longevity fruit are also unknown.
According to the medical records, Miss Chun Hua was revived from the dead.
I’m speculating that she ate the longevity fruit.
However, she has completely lost her memories and doesn’t even know who she, herself, is.
As I see it, she isn’t a crafty person.
Thus, I have already ordered for the news to not be spread.
Are you sympathetic towards Miss Chun Hua,
and therefore, keeping her by your side?
It is extremely easy for an evil person to murder her.
How can I leave her wandering out there?
Right, right, right.
Until she finds her family, she can stay in Fengming Mountain Manor.
As for the longevity fruit,
my father is critically ill so I still need to quicken my search.
According to my recent investigation, news of the longevity fruit
was first released by a Master Shi in the pugilist world.
He does things extremely discreet and secretive.
Nobody in the pugilist world has seen his actual face before.
A person who has never been seen before, spreading news of a thing that has never been seen before.
Seems like none of the news of the longevity fruit and its genuineness can be believed as of yet.
[Chuanqi Sect]
Don’t wake her up.
Have a good look, and see if she has anything else that’s suspicious on her.
Gorge Master, her hidden weapon.
Qianyue Sect?
They’re so used to secretly sending spies
that they’re sending spies to my sect?
Gorge Master Fu,
for jobs like the appreciation of hidden weapons, you should be looking for a blacksmith instead.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, you have been sending people to sneak into Chuanqi Sect many times.
What exactly are your motives?
If we were to trace back by a hundred years, both of us would be from the same sect.
Am I wrong to be concerned about you and send people to check up on you?
I’m afraid that killing within the sect is indeed a tradition of your Qianyue Sect, isn’t it?
Gorge Master Fu, you must be joking.
But it is truly a pity.
We have been busy with our internal conflicts all these years,
and have allowed Fengming Mountain Manor to strengthen its Wulin sects.
It turns out that you want to unify the pugilist world.
Don’t worry! I have no interest in your great ambitions.
It looks like you have taken an interest in the woman who was revived from the dead.
Because of the longevity fruit?
It’s a pity that she’s protected by Fengming Mountain Manor.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, don’t think I won’t dare lead people to attack Qianyue Sect today.
Gorge Master Fu, you are now at the edge of Qianyue Sect’s territory.
You even had to beg me to come to meet you.
If you really have the skills, why didn't you go straight into the cave to look for me?
Who is there?
- Miss Chun Hua?
- Xiao Bai?
You should get out!
Young Master!
What are you doing here?
Don't you know this is the private bath place for Young Master?
How could I know? No one told me.
You still don't want to get out?
Hurry up and leave!
You... you are still looking?
If this is your private bath, why don't you put up a sign?
Let's go!
[Private Bath]
It definitely says "private bath" here.
Xiao Lei.
I want to drink water.
Water.
Is nobody here?
No one is here.
You caught a cold from the pool. There's nothing to be afraid of.
Silly Sister, let go. Lie down!
I am not going to let go.
Unless...
Older Brother, you let me take advantage of you, then I will recover.
All right. You lay down first,
then you can take advantage of me.
You will really let me take advantage of you?
You can take advantage any time.
Older Brother, there is no need to worry about me. I am almost fully recovered.
How could it be so fast?
I want some water.
What now? You no longer want to take advantage of me?
Are we really siblings?
Of course.
Am I not treating you nice enough?
Then, were we like this before?
Before? No.
Ever since our parents passed away, we have been eating and sleeping together.
Back then, Xiao Chun Hua is much braver than now.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
[Qian Hua Xuan]
How could he be such rigid
in the way he talks, walks, and does things?
Miss Chun Hua, what are you doing?
I saw you standing upright so firmly.
I wanted to see if I could push you.
Xiao Bai, cleary you're a young man,
why are you acting like an old man?
Xiao Bai, I didn't take a bath in your hot spring on purpose!
I didn't see the words, "private bath"!
I even thought you were a gentleman and didn't have an interest in those things.
I didn't think you would be this shy!
Miss Chun Hua, why are you—
You're talking about how you saw me taking a bath, aren't you?
It's okay, you're my husband anyways.
Xiao Bai, you are a man of honor.
What do you want to do?
Miss Chun Hua, the weather is nice today.
I wonder if you know how to fly a kite?
What?
Xiao Bai.
The kite won't fly high with you holding it so tightly.
The thread spool...
- What's wrong with it?
- It's old and small. Why don't you throw it away?
Do you remember the first time we met?
I remember.
It's Xiao Bai who saved me.
I remember you called me,
husband.
Did I? I have forgotten already.
I remember.
It can't be wrong.
That's what you called me.
Then maybe it's because
I felt really close to you.
It's like I'd seen you before.
What is the earliest thing you can remember?
I don't remember. I don't remember anything.
You don't even remember who you are?
I really don't remember!
You are an important guest of our Fengming Mountain Manor.
I will do my best to protect you.
Xiao Bai, do you care this much about me?
Miss, if there is something you are afraid to express.
Don't be afraid, you can tell me.
As long as you are here, I won't be afraid.
Xiao Bai is finally starting to get the idea.
Get what idea?
Older Brother, why did you come here?
There is a huge and luxurious mirror here, I can't take a look?
Did you get a new hairpin?
You could tell? Does it look good?
What's so good about a crudely made product?
It's already broken!
Why do you care about useless things?
Have a chat with me!
Look! You look like a bun when you're mad.
I will gift you another one.
It looks a lot better than that.
I'm giving this to you, take it!
This is too precious! I can't accept it.
Then, what do you want?
I want you to make me happy.
All right.
Then, what do you want me to do?
I will definitely satisfy you.
Really?
The Master of Qianyue Sect does not go against his words.
Older Brother...
should bark like a dog. No!
Bark until I am happy.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a  pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even the admiring for the freshness and the beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have, is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even the admiring for the freshness and the beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have, is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I've left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet, how can you still not see it  ♫