''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Just now, I didn't completely trust you.
I only know that you wouldn't hurt Miss Feng.
Although the origins are unclear, they say the antidote was made from Longevity leaves.
People will act as if the Devil is in their hearts as long as we cannot find the Longevity fruit.
We'll just find something that no one has ever seen before,
and fake it as the Longevity fruit.
We must destroy it in the presence of all, and we still need to find a good excuse
to gather the chiefs of all the sects together.
I thought it over and over again, so I decided to make up for it by giving you a big wedding.
You actually dare to marry him, without my approval!
[Episode 20]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Sisi,
the ghosts and gods in the afterlife
are not in our control.
The only thing I can do
is to save you.
I must save you.
You must hold on and live well.
[Full of Noble Daring Aspiration]
Miss Leng, why does your face have a little bit of blush today?
It's just the reflection of the "happiness" characters.
If you said these words were prepared for us,
that would be much better.
Forget it! I dare accept your words.
The wedding will be soon, and our efforts in the past few days
will eventually pay off.
The closer the wedding, the more we cannot slack off.
Miss Leng, do you think the Longevity fruit that all the world is scrambling for,
is really worth it?
I'm still young so why should I think about that?
Miss Leng, we are like-minded, no doubt.
I also think that living a life with the one you love
is better than immortality without love.
Boring!
Boring?
Well, then I insist on saying something today.
Miss Leng, I boldly ask, on life's long, winding road,
are you willing to let my beaming bright self join you?
I think you are just too beaming and bright.
You get in the way and become a hindrance between Caicai and me.
Xiao Bai, what are you doing here?
You can't look!
In the past, you wouldn't even come when I invited you.
And now you just came over without my asking.
Your customs here
for new brides are so difficult.
Originally, I thought I could just wait for my new bridal clothes.
Who knew that I still need to embroider my own handkerchief?
Oh, right! Look, do you think this pearl resembles the Longevity fruit?
Speaking of that,
we actually became acquainted because of the Longevity fruit.
Chun Hua,
if the Longevity fruit is real,
what would you do with it?
I think...
I would send it to Madam Yousi.
- Madam Yousi? She's Fu Lou's...
- So what?
She's such a nice person.
Madam Yousi is so lovely and pitiful.
I really like her.
If the Longevity fruit was snatched by the Demon Sects,
I don't know what kinds of storm or chaos that would ensue.
However, she's not like that.
Madam Yousi is just like this pearl,
extremely innocent and kind.
Fu Lou is very protective of her, just like a clam with its pearl.
If this pearl were plucked away one day,
then the clam's heart would be empty.
Right now, I don't know whether Fu Lou is evil or not.
I only know that if someone's heart is empty,
then he will truly be afflicted and tormented.
Chun Hua, I...
It's you again!
Why have I always been in awkward, troublesome situations lately?
Brother Qin!
- Brother Qin.
- Young Chief Master, why are you so unenthusiastic and half-hearted?
You were just being attentive with Miss Chun Hua, and now you're here to sway me through pillow talk.
Fortunately, I am a man of fervent righteousness.
- I can't stand your fickleness.
- Stop making a fuss!
I'm very remorseful and uneasy.
Remorseful?
Toward me?
Do you really think it's okay to hide this from Miss Chun Hua?
Well, then I'll take you to own up to it.
I just tried to admit it to her but I couldn't get it out.
She earnestly wants to marry me but if I confess to her now,
she will surely think I don't sincerely want to marry her.
As long as your conscience is clear, it's all right.
You have never been in love so what do you know?
I...
Why am I always the one who gets hurt?
This is broken ice stone.
It wasn't Qin Liufeng just now but Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Chun Hua, you need to be clear-minded (lit your heart has to be clear).
You're about to marry soon so how can your mind and heart be full of that big devil?
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Xiao Bai, you were the very first one I saw.
You must be the one for me, aren't you?
The red is so tasteless.
Tell me, when common people get married,
must they decorate with lanterns and be festive?
Red paper and red cloth blots out the sky over the earth.
Yes. Red is the color for joyous events.
If the women in this world were able to marry whom they love,
naturally, that would be joyous.
Well, you've been covered in black all day.
Does that mean you were never happy?
It is my honor to serve you, Master.
As such, I consider to already be very lucky.
I certainly don't need any common or worldly joy.
You're also a woman.
Do you have someone you adore?
I am merely a subordinate.
- I do not think about love.
- You're lying!
I have allowed you to serve and support me for your entire life.
So you must bear
this small injury.
Yes.
In regards to Xiao Chun Hua's wedding,
you must report to me every detail, no matter how big or small.
When you act, you're ruthless, relentless, and merciless.
You are worthy of being Master's most trusted aid.
You didn't manage to dodge my dart! Gu Xingzhu, practice more until you get it right.
What happened with that injury on your face?
I was busy and got injured, all in the line of work.
Xiao Yan, you smell like you've been drinking for three nights.
Has Master been drinking often lately?
If you really want to know, Gu Xingzhu, you should ask him yourself.
Xiao Yan, it's already so late, where are you going?
I can't be daydreaming, can I?
Of course, not.
Miss Caicai, what are you doing here?
Miss Caicai, do you blame me?
Miss Chun Hua, you saved me twice.
You are a nice girl.
You and Young Chief Master are finally able to get married.
I simply wish you the very best.
That's all!
You will definitely be the prettiest bride in the world.
Thank you.
It's a pity that Young Chief Master can't feast his eyes on you sooner.
Chun Hua.
Xiao Bai?
Miss Feng.
Well then, I won't disturb both of you any longer.
Xiao Bai, come and sit here.
If you don't come over here, I'll be angry.
So great!
Tell me that you like me.
I like Chun Hua.
Why have you changed and become so obedient?
You've never been like this in the past.
When you looked at me before, you would blush.
You even use the Fengming Saber to separate us and to keep me at a distance.
- Chun Hua, I—
- I know!
You'll be good to me for my entire life, won't you?
Miss Chun Hua,
I hope you won't be angry at me for keeping the truth from you.
I hope that this grand wedding
can stop all the problems.
I hope that Young Chief Master and you
can be happy forever.
- Congratulations, Young Chief Master!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
I am fortunate to have all of the heroes and outstanding people
here to attend my wedding.
This magnificent scene is a rare sight.
- That’s right.
- That’s true.
However, the announcement that I will make
has nothing to do with this wedding.
My Lady, what do you think of this flower?
Don’t always cut those flowers in full bloom.
My Lady, you are very strange! Flowers for flower arrangements should be beautiful.
Why do you always pick those that are withering?
Flower arrangement
is for those flowers with a short life span to have a second life.
If we cut a flower that's in bloom
just because of its beauty,
aren’t we placing the importance on the wrong thing?
Now, Miss Chun Hua
and Young Chief Master are having their wedding.
I wonder if they have received my congratulatory gift yet.
My Lady, don't you worry!
The weather does not look good.
My Lady, I will go to fetch an umbrella.
What’s going on?
Because of the Longevity fruit, the pugilist world is in chaos with murders happening everywhere.
As part of the Righteous Wulin Sects, how can Fengming Mountain Manor be indifferent?
Right! This is right.
It’s truly been too long.
- Our ways to handle the situation were wrong.
- We should have done something.
However, days ago, I was fortunate enough
to obtain the Longevity fruit.
- What?
- Young Chief Master, are you speaking the truth?
- Is the Longevity fruit in your hands?
- Really?
- This is a blessing for the righteous sects.
- I have never seen it before.
Everyone, be quiet! Let Young Chief Master finish his speech.
I have really never seen it before.
There is no end to troubles if this fruit remains in this world.
Therefore, today, I will destroy the Longevity fruit
in front of everyone.
- You cannot do that!
- That’s right. You should not do that.
No way! How can he do that? He shouldn't do that!
Xiao Bai,
the grand wedding you promised me,
is it just a cover for the Longevity fruit?
A wedding was organized with such great pains.
[Double Happiness]
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Could it be you're also here for the Longevity fruit?
You have such a one-track mind. How laughable!
But seeing you make a fool of yourself, is much more interesting.
Shangguang Qiu Yue, let go of her immediately!
Fengming Saber’s last technique is a crushing blow.
Young Chief Master, I'm unsure of the result if you attack us.
However, your Miss Chun Hua will be mutilated.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, are you insane?
Immediately let go of her!
Let go of her?
I am here today to inform you
that this wedding cannot proceed.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Shangguan Qiu Yue, she is my wife.
What rights do you have?
What rights do I have?
Miss Chun Hua has a birthmark on her collarbone,
a shape of a flower bud.
Young Chief Master, you don't know that, do you?
That scar…
It turns out that you do know.
Then I might as well let you know.
Miss Chun Hua, with her original name of Hua Xiaolei,
had an engagement with you before.
It's just that we have already been husband and wife.
What? What is going on?
He cannot really say so! Right, he can't! Exactly! How can he say that?
How outrageous!
Exactly!
Xiao Bai, it is not like that.
I am not Hua Xiaolei. Chun Hua is just Chun Hua.
Xiao Chun Hua,
without my permission, you are not allowed to marry others.
But that is all right! I have already decided to take you back to Qianyue Cave.
Xiao Bai wants to take advantage of the wedding to destroy the Longevity fruit
while I just want to be with you.
Xiao Bai!
You can destroy your Longevity fruit
and I will have my Xiao Chun Hua.
Young Chief Master, hand over the Longevity fruit!
Hand it over! Hand over the Longevity fruit!
The Longevity fruit will be discussed at a later date.
No! Hand over the Longevity fruit now!
Hand it over now!
Move aside!
What are you doing? Young Chief Master, what are you doing?
That’s right! We must make him hand it over!
- You must hand it over!
This is not good! I have never seen Young Chief Master so angry.
Who else would like to taste the real whistling wind of the Fengming Saber?
Xiao Bai, you are so vicious. Let's go!
Go, let's go.
A phoenix must
go back to its hometown.
Travel the four seas to seek its phoenix.
Words are worthy of virtue and go hand in hand with each other.
Not being able to fly
brings me to ruins.
It was such nice weather.
Why does it suddenly rain so heavily?
My  Lady, My Lady.
Welcome home, Xiao Chun Hua!
Qianyue Cave is not my home.
Brother will help you live in the cliff.
You dishonored me
and humiliated Xiao Bai.
- You are pushing me down the cliff.
- Then that's indeed a good thing.
From now on, you have nothing to do with Fengming Mountain Manor.
Why do you have to separate us?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫