''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
However, I was obviously lead through this way previously.
How is it that I cannot find the route now?
You tried to poison my food and arranged someone to come and kill me.
Xiao Bai, do you really want me to die so badly?
I need to return to Fengming Mountain Manor to get to the bottom of this.
As much as I want to give you freedom, I also want to protect you.
By keeping someone locked beside you and only allowing them to do what you want them to do.
is that really still considered as freedom?
Xiao Chun Hua, rest assured! I will never harm you.
Qianyue Cave is constantly going against Fengming Mountain Manor. Why is this so?
I fear that it could be the difficulty of staying away from feelings.
We need to quickly find Miss Chun Hua.
[Episode 23]
If others saw the master of Qianyue Cave combing my hair, they will laugh at me.
Whoever dares to joke about this, I will kill him.
Then why don't you just kill me?
Could it be...
that I still possess something that you can use to your advantage?
You're not an exceptional martial art master, nor are you in any important position.
What possible use do I have for you?
Previously, I just wanted you to help me steal the Xin Fa.
I mistook you for Hua Xiaolei.
Later, Xiao Bai mastered the last stage of the Fengming Saber skill.
Then the Xin Fa has long become unimportant to me.
Now, I just want to protect you for life.
I don't want you to protect me for life.
I just wish you would graciously lift your hands and let me go.
Let you go back to Fengming Mountain Manor?
Little Sister, Xiao Bai wants to kill you.
Even in my Qianyue Cave, he dared to have murderous intentions.
If I let you go back,
won't you be heading towards your death?
I believe in Xiao Bai.
What exactly is so good about Xiao Bai
to allow you to be so loyal to him?
I want true love.
Xiao Bai is the first person I've chosen to love.
Little Sister,
you are too stubborn.
There are so many well-paved paths for you to walk upon in this world.
Why must you go down the wrong path?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Older Brother, you gave this ice silk pearl to me,
using it to tie me up.
Now I will
return it to you.
Please, Older Brother,
give me a path to live.
Look!
How have you been calling me?
In your normal daily life, how often do you rely on me?
This pearl has seen it all.
I thank you for your protection.
It is just that we are no longer children.
It is time
for us to look for our own paths and homes.
My little sister has grown up.
Escort her out!
Miss Chun Hua, since you have already decided,
then please leave.
Master.
Did you send her off?
Yes.
Is Yousi of Chuanqi Gorge not going to make it soon?
The matter of Gorge Master Fu loving his wife to death has been hidden well.
Spread the news of You Si's illness to the public.
Young Chief Master!
Miss Chun Hua is back.
Young Chief Master, please enter.
Chun Hua.
Let go!
Are you and Shangguan Qiu Yue...?
The first thing you do when you see me is to doubt me?
You...
Are you okay?
You are right! He asked me to come to steal the Xin Fa.
Shangguan Qiu Yue has seen the birthmark of Hua Xiaolei before.
It was also he who let me go on his own accord.
What is it? You think that I've sullied the name of Fengming Mountain Manor, thus you want to kill me?
Why would I?
I really went to Qianyue Sect to look for you but–
So because you couldn't find me you sent a spy to kill me?
What?
Why would I want to kill you?
I have always believed you and wanted to save you.
You have heard everything Shangguan Qiu Yue had to say.
How can you still believe me?
Do not lie to me!
I am not lying. I do believe you. Honestly!
Maybe Hua Xiaolei showed him the scars,
but it definitely isn't Chun Hua who has amnesia now, is it?
It was  Shangguan Qiu Yue who threatened you.
He made you come and steal the Xin Fa.
He made you believe him, didn't he?
I am willingly to give you the Xin Fa
but Shangguan Qiu Yue did not get the Xin Fa.
Isn't that right?
I gave him a fake one.
So how could I not believe you?
It is I who has wronged you
because earlier I did not know that you were being threatened by him.
I allowed you to bear the burden alone.
Then before this,
did you think that I've sullied the name of the Fengming Mountain Manor.
You sent Ling Yang to kill me.
I most definitely did not send Ling Yang to kill you.
I was waiting all this time for your return. Anxiously awaiting!
I waited for you to come back and tell me the truth
but suddenly, all the communication from there ceased.
Was it really not you?
I never gave such a command.
Caicai, just think,
how do you think Chun Hua came back?
The spy is dead.
If that big demon didn't let her go, how could she come back?
Then the relationship between them can't be so simple.
Maybe, this time she's back with crafty schemes.
In the future, when it comes to Miss Chun Hua,
we should just let the Young Chief Master deal with it.
Then do you believe that they have a secret affair between them?
We are outsiders.
The last time you were poisoned, everyone was at a loss.
Only Miss Chun Hua actually brought the antidote
and the antidote appeared everywhere afterward.
No matter what, she saved me.
In the future, anything that are relating to her,
only the Young Chief Master should deal with them.
How did it go? Did you have a good talk?
Chun Hua was truly used by  Shangguan Qiu Yue.
She did not betray Fengming Mountain Manor.
However, you still cannot be sure if Chun Hua and Shangguan Qiu Yue...
Is there really a secret affair?
I dare not probe into it,
but I do not believe there is.
Speaking of this, the antidote for the Dandelion
suddenly became common everywhere.
The leaf of the Longevity fruit, the antidote for the Dandelion,
if these all came from Qianyue Sect,
then Shangguan Qiu Yue might not be uninterested in the Longevity fruit.
Speaking of this,
Ling Yang wanted to harm her in Qianyue Cave.
Chun Hua would not lie about this.
The complications in between...
I'm not sure about what happened between Ling Yang and Chief Leng.
You had more interactions with Chief Leng before.
Brother Qin, please explain it to me.
Ling Yang only obeys Chief Leng.
Apart from this, if Ling Yang has other thoughts,
that could be a possibility.
No wonder Miss Chun Hua's return this time is much different from before.
Why don't you go and comfort her?
It seems like we still need to discuss this further.
I apologize for the disturbance, I will come back another time.
Chun Hua?
Please come and sit here.
Miss Chun Hua, we are discussing the news relating to the Longevity fruit.
I just wanted to come to see how everyone is.
Now I know.
I will be on my way.
Miss Chun Hua!
Miss Chun Hua, please wait a second.
Do not misunderstand!
I've become an awkward existence now.
Of course not! You are still the Young Chief Master's wife.
Young Master Qin, don't forget!
We have never had a wedding ceremony.
The wedding will happen sooner or later, but
the Young Chief Master's wife is different from other wives.
There are more responsibilities and sacrifices.
[Chuanqi Gorge]
Husband, you needn't worry about me.
It's only because I didn't put on any makeup,
thus my complexion is not so great.
Your complexion is not bad.
Sisi, you are still so pretty.
Longevity fruit!
You have to be real.
You have to let a person long plagued with sickness
become healthy again.
I don't care for longevity,
but the limited interactions,
you should grant this.
Ever since Xiao Chun Hua returned to the Fengming Mountain Manor,
has she been well?
From my investigations,
Miss Chun Hua's return to the Fengming Mountain Manor has not been widely known.
Is she so well protected or have you been manipulated?
I was careless.
Stand up!
I told you to get up!
Yes.
How is Lady Fu's condition?
She does not have long to live.
What should we do about this?
Fu Lou cherishes his wife like one cherishes their eyes.
This news is pretty widespread now, am I right?
It can be seen that there has been chatters in the streets.
Those who chatter about this aren't good people, either.
They're all waiting to compete with Lady Fu for the Longevity fruit.
I will arrange for this immediately.
Wait a minute!
It's not fun to simply strike with force.
I am really interested in seeing what these people who want to steal the Longevity fruit are willing to trade for it.
What do you think, Ye Yan?
The honorable sects all care about their reputation.
Those that are in danger are in dire need of power.
That sounds logical,
Then let them all speak their mind.
I will arrange for this immediately.
How about we call it 'Book of One's Crimes'?
That name sounds good. Go on!
Book of One's Crimes? Longevity fruit? What do you mean?
After the failure of burning the Longevity fruit at the wedding last time,
it was difficult to make everyone believe
that Miss Chun Hua took the Longevity fruit to Qianyue Sect.
We had a few days of peace at Fengming Mountain Manor.
However, from early this morning, many people from the pugilist world have come about this again.
Master Shi started something again?
Yes. He announced that the auction failed last time,
thus allowing Fengming Mountain Manor to freely gain the Longevity fruit.
He doesn't want to be involved in these matters.
He asked for Fengming Mountain Manor to burn the fruit in front of everyone,
to halt the thoughts of greed.
This explanation sounds very glorified but there is more.
He suggested that in order to uphold principles of goodwill,
the people should be open to confessing their crimes.
This Master Shi,
his schemes really are endless.
The promise of the Book of One's Crimes, those who confess
will get the Longevity fruit.
He hopes that someone will repent and absolve their sins in order to set a good example.
Supporting that path will open up to sinners who repent.
Why do I feel that he does not have such good intentions?
Yes, for sure he doesn't have these good intentions.
He mentioned on multiple occasions that the Longevity fruit is in the hands of Miss Chun Hua.
If we don't burn the fruit, then doubt will persist.
Also, he mentions that Fengming Mountain Manor follows through with their promises.
A place of leadership dating back to 100 years.
Fengming Mountain Manor is the best choice for this kind of procedural justice.
Burning the fruit in front of the public.
There was already much bloodshed at the auction.
Now, doubt is spreading to more people.
I don't want to cause more trouble.
How about... I go to clear up this misunderstanding?
No, the idea of the Book of One's Crimes is not bad.
I hope that those big demons do come out
and repent for their sins.
They can get the Longevity fruit and follow the path of goodness once and for all.
But who would be the best person for this role?
Burn the Longevity fruit!
Such a bewitching item should have been burned long ago.
Book of One's Crimes.
In the pugilist world, there are two big demons.
Shangguang Qiu Yue of Qianyue Sect and Fu Lou of Chuanqi Sect.
If Fu Lou can really repent for his crimes,
then it can also settle things regarding my father's death.
But once he admits it,
wouldn't my father have died for nothing?
The righteousness of the pugilist world, compared with personal grievances,
I will choose righteousness, of course.
I do not agree to this.
Book of One's Crimes?
The one who wants the Longevity fruit the most is Fu Lou.
He would do this without a second thought even if he thinks it is fake
but this is a trap.
Miss Chun Hua, how can you be so sure that
Fu Lou would fall for this without a second of doubt?
The most precious thing to Fu Lou is his wife.
His wife is currently very ill and needs this Longevity fruit the most,
but this Longevity fruit is fake.
Miss Chun Hua,
I once heard you say this before.
That's true! According to the rumors, Fu Lou's wife, You Si, is gravely ill.
Fu Lou has been worried over this.
This rumor coincidently matches with the existence of the Book of One's Crimes.
Could it be too good to be true?
I'm afraid his feelings... can't be compared to the absolute sincerity for Miss Leng.
Were you happy to return to Fengming Mountain Manor?
Is it because of Xiao Bai that you don't act flirtatiously with your brother?
Based on your reaction, does that mean you admit to it?
- Older Brother!
- I thought you never wanted to see me again, based on our last encounter.
Today, I passed by coincidently and found out that you were looking for the ice silkworm pearl.
- Older Brother, I was just really desperate!
- Look!
The one you think of when you're desperate is also your older brother.
If you return it to me again, you will never see me again.
Older Brother, can you take me to Chuanqi Gorge?
The Cave Master of Qianyue Sect committed so many crimes.
He never does anything out of goodwill.
But since it is your request,
then I must fulfill your request.
Do you really like Lady Fu?
She is a very nice lady.
No wonder you wanted me to ask her for help last time.
What good is it to have a weak heart?
Fu Lou was ultimately brought down by her.
If it was not for her,
Qianyua Sect, Chuanqi Sect, and Fengming Mountain Manor;
the situation of the three pillars wouldn't have persisted until now.
I've met Fu Lou.
Although he acted decisively and cruelly,
he definitely is not a brute nor an unconscionable person.
If he could find a woman to stay by his side at an earlier time,
he wouldn't be in this chaotic martial art world now.
However, he has found Madame You Si
who is soft-hearted and kind.
She is even in such a fragile health.
Fu Lou knows it,
that's why he doesn't let her go out of the valley to be seen easily.
However, Xiao Chun Hua is very special.
You were the first to notice Fu Lou's weakness.
Perhaps...
This is what made me give up immortality
and this is the love that I also want to find.
Don't hurt Fu Lou and Madam You Si.
If I wanted to do that, they wouldn't still be alive now.
You don't want to kill Fu Lou?
I don't want to.
Fu Lou must not die by my hands.
You are so right.
After all, Chuanqi Gorge is not that easy to deal with.
If you kill him, wouldn't you have another group of enemies?
I'm never afraid of too many enemies.
Besides, it is not that difficult to kill Fu Lou.
Older Brother, comparing you with Fu Lou, whose martial arts is better?
Xiao Chun Hua, you don't need martial arts to kill Fu Lou.
The key is to know a person's weakness.
If you know his weakness,
he will be much easier to deal with.
Right! You have no weakness.
Older Brother has a weakness.
My weakness is you.
Be careful in the future!
This Yousi is easy to deal with,
but can Xiao Chun Hua deal with Fu Lou?
Master Fu Lou came very quickly.
Shangguan Qiu Yue,
did you spread the news about the Longevity fruit in Fengming Mountain Manor?
Making fun of others must be amusing?
I see Master Fu Lou is concerned about the chaos.
So you came to Chuanqi Gorge to make fun of me?
That is where you are wrong.
This time, I came here to help Master Fu Lou.
I've asked you to join forces before.
At that time, you flatly refused.
I don't believe that you can be so kind now.
I indeed don't have much kindness.
However, for my younger sister,
this time, I managed to squeeze out a little (kindness).
Your internal strength.
I already said it, Master Fu Lou.
It's more troublesome to make me to be an opponent than a helper.
The helper you mean... is her right?
It's me!
Since she hasn't the Longevity fruit, she is useless.
My younger sister is quite useful.
Gorge Master Fu, Fengming Mountain Manor is about to hold a Longevity fruit conference in these two days.
My younger sister happens to be Xiao's Bai fiancée.
Gorge Master Fu can use my younger sister in exchange for the Longevity fruit.
You are even so supportive.
Older Brother doesn't act for your consideration.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫