''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
This book records all the activities of Baxian Residence.
Why don't we take a look at Baxian City?
Say, the two of us are just out in broad daylight, won't we be seen by Xiao Bai and the rest?
You forgot? Your brother knows the art of disguise.
Something big has happened at Qianyue Cave.
This will be your punishment for leaving me!
[Seeing willows by the river and spring flowers deepen my sadness. Even as our hair turns grey, will we ever meet again?]
Just what did he tell you?
He only told me about everything you have done to me from the start till the end.
The person who told me these was not Xiao Bai or Qin Liufeng, but Gu Wan.
[Episode 33]
Have you asked Chun Hua when she will return?
It should be quite soon.
Will she really be unscathed?
Miss Leng and I can confirm that.
Since this is the case, why can't we just get her back?
- Young Chief Master, we must not do that!
- Is Shangguan Qiuyue still alive and by her side?
I can confirm that there is only Chun Hua by herself.
- Miss Feng, even you are lying to me?
- I am not.
You need not say more! I will look for her now.
Xiao Bai, stop making a scene!
Right now, you should focus on healing your body.
I promise you, in three days, just three more days,
I will definitely bring Miss Chun Hua back to your side.
Move away!
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
This is so strange!
I was originally really worried about her, but now that I know she is unscathed,
I only want to kill her.
If we can't be together alive,
we will be together in death!
Chun Hua, you should be buried amongst the Xiao family ancestors!
The drug test for sedative soup is out.
What happened?
He has already crossed over to the demonic path.
Being purely heartbroken should not cause him to become like this.
He seems to have become a different person.
Just like that day in the bamboo forest, when he killed the assassin.
This is definitely not just a result of the heartbreak.
There is something wrong with the medicine.
[Thousand Moon Pavilion]
Gu Wan is still alive?
Gu Wan said Ye Yan thought she killed him, but luckily heaven has eyes.
When he woke up from the brink of death, it didn't let him continue to be fooled.
You would still believe his nonsensical words?
Ye Yan... she has disappointed me greatly.
Older Brother, are you now pushing the blame?
Yes. It's Xiao Bai's fault; it's Qin Liufeng's fault;
it's Gu Wan's fault; it's Ye Yan's fault; it's my fault!
It is the fault of the entire world.
Ultimately, it has nothing to do with you, hasn't it?
Xiao Chun Hua, you have to believe me.
Gu Wan's motive for looking for you is not that simple.
Older Brother, you are wrong again.
I do not believe him.
I believe myself.
I believe the experiences that I have been through.
The first person you saw was me.
Everything you have been through, I understand it all.
Older Brother, since you knew about my dream of seeing you at first sight,
you thought you could use that to hold onto me.
That is not the same.
Then is it because the previous me was still of use to you?
Putting it that way isn't wrong, either.
Xiao Chun Hua, you've taught me a lot.
For example, mid-autumn. For example, mooncakes.
Does my usefulness mount to a small amount?
Xiao Chun Hua is very cute.
You always make me smile.
Xiao Chun Hua also has a lot of little ideas that I can never think of.
When I was sick, Xiao Chun Hua even looked after me.
Also...
Also what?
Let me!
I will slowly bring back your memories.
I went to check the sedative soup at the medicine shop.
This medicine has an extra ingredient.
Aconite.
It helps to restore depleted Zhen Qi, and get rid of cold and pain.
Hearing about it like this, it doesn't seem to have a problem.
No! There is a big problem.
Young Chief Master's Fengming Saber is practiced with pure Zhen Qi.
This medicine, for an ordinary person, would naturally be good medicine.
But for Young Chief Master... now, his Zhen Qi is now out of control.
If he continues to use it,
it is like adding oil to a fire.
It must be Master Pu'er.
No. Li Yu is not free from suspicion.
Right now, Young Chief Master's mental state is chaotic, yet he seems to be extremely lucid at times.
However, there is something he said that is right.
What is it?
Shangguan Qiuyue must have kidnapped Chun Hua.
The first thing,
is when Older Brother asked me to enter Fengming Mountain Manor to help steal the Xin Fa for you.
I have stopped asking you to do such things long ago.
That is because Xiao Bai already mastered the Fengming Saber.
Naturally, the Xin Fa has lost its value.
The second thing,
was when I was kidnapped into Chuanqi Gorge.
You wanted me to test if Fu Lou's weakness was indeed Yousi.
- You like Yousi.
- Like?
Thanks to your plans,
I got to know You Si.
The third thing,
was during the Longevity Fruit auction.
You caught me and brought me to Qianyue Cave to distract Xiao Bai.
Then naturally the event at the auction was
out of control.
I just wanted to help you test Xiao Bai's feelings.
A simple description of testing him,
caused the deaths of so many people.
The fourth thing,
was when you used the Dandelion poison to kill Feng Qianwei.
You also almost caused the death of Miss Feng.
I was still curious about why you would be so kindhearted to give me the antidote.
Younger Sister,
the poison was not done by me.
You did not poison them?
But the antidote is in your Qianyue Cave.
Other than you, who else would be able to prepare this medicine?
Fine!
Let's not talk about the truth or falseness of this matter.
Then the fifth thing.
The book of sins that you asked Master Shi to announce.
That should have been done by you.
- That was just a public letter.
- A public letter?
One letter decided the life and death of Fu Lou and Yousi!
You already knew it, didn't you?
However, you were still not satisfied.
You used their deaths
to make me leave Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai has a stubborn personality.
I simply returned the Ice Silk Pearl to you.
This should have also been in your plans,
but what about him now?
He crossed over to the demonic side and is unable to get up from sickness.
Older Brother, the control over anyone that you want
will soon be all yours.
Xiao Chun Hua,
it is only because I like you that I planned to make you leave Xiao Bai.
So, you are able to admit this now.
Older Brother, previously you said it is easy to tell the truth but difficult to lie.
Right now, to you, I am just a good for nothing.
You can't even be bothered to use lies to placate me.
It's because those are all in the past.
I already said that I want to be with you,
so I will stop lying to you.
Right.
I do not know martial arts.
I also have no family.
Before I knew you, I never realized that I was so useful.
Ultimately, I still need to thank you.
I would never harm you.
I will treat you well.
That is because I am merely one of your pawns.
Now, you want to put away the chessboard.
Shouldn't you let me go now?
Xiao Chun Hua is not a pawn.
Have you forgotten?
Wasn't it because I was injured by Gu Wan?
A ruse of harming yourself.
All of your actions
make it difficult for me to believe you.
Since this is the case,
let me bring you to see something.
Why did you bring me here?
You want me to think about those skeletons and scare me?
So that I will become obedient?
Xiao Chun Hua has started to use the worst way of thinking to speculate about me.
I also learned that from you.
Do you remember when I told you that you're not the first person who come here?
This ice valley
was accidentally discovered by sect leader Nanxing He back then.
He personally made a secret passage.
Other than the leader of Qianyue Cave, no one else knew about it.
Why are you telling me this?
I want to tell you the story of this ice valley.
Today, I have heard too many stories so I don't want to hear anymore.
Even if it is related to Fengming Mountain Manor?
After the secret passage was built,
the ice valley welcomed its first visitor.
He was Nanxing He's sworn brother.
Guess, who was he?
This is erected by my ancestor, Xiao Min.
It's a long story.
Back then, he annihilated the Xingyue Sect causing innumerable causalities.
He felt the killings were too heavy, so he erected this memorial tablet,
wanting us, descendants, to keep paying respects.
Xiao Min, the first martial arts leader.
That's right.
They are here to learn from each other and to drink and chat merrily.
So Qianyue Cave's hatred for Fengming Mountain
started since that time.
Xiao Min is only an insider,
but after Nan Xinghe found out about it, he still didn't kill him.
Such a moral character isn't far better than today's Righteous Path?
Such a pure internal strength that
only Nan Xinghe had in those days.
What a pity...
A trap...
A fierce battle ruined Xingyue sect.
Killed hundreds of thousands of Xingyue sect brothers.
So what did Xiao Min do in the end?
He fooled Nan Xinghe to negotiate with the Righteous Path.
Finally, he brought down a vicious attack.
Nan Xinghe was only 33 years old when he died.
Even his youngest son tragically died in the hands of the Righteous Path.
Xiao Chun Hua.
What do you...
think is right?
What is evil?
Helping the common people of the world is right.
That Xingyue sect taught hundreds of thousands of lives to be slaughtered.
It's the right way,
yet the evil way.
Xingyue sect is the evil path because it has made many evil things.
Evil path?
Evil path, but it's the martial arts circle oath
for those who are not willing to obey their self doctrine.
In those years Nan Xinghe just wanted to live happily,
but the Righteous Path
said that was the evil way.
He was too powerful.
Powerful enough to control the situation in the pugilist world.
That kind of person, if unable to restrain,
will let the safety of martial arts only between his thoughts.
For Xiao Chun Hua, a hint is all that is needed.
[Baxian Residence]
- A prescription precisely?
- Yes.
The Young Chief Master went back for the past two days and he is either talking nonsense or beating up.
So the two ladies are terrified.
I thought about it and it would still be better to ask you to prescribe a dose of soothing soup.
It's hard to say, the mind of this young man really changes unpredictably.
Fortunately, I have seen a lot of people.
I think you might back out.
Just a moment ago, I specially made one with my own hands.
Come!
I can't thank you enough. I can't thank you enough for that!
The Young Chief Master should be quiet, avoid movement, and shouldn't go out these days.
Okay. Actually, the purpose of my visit today,
is to personally request a prescription for a sedative soup from you.
I have been negligent again.
Not a problem.
They are all common medicines and shouldn't be too difficult to find.
Thank you, Master Pu'er.
- This... Young Master is still waiting for me, so I shall not disturb you further.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
- Please.
At the ancestral hall of the Xiao residence,
there is hidden a poem of remembrance.
This shows Xiao Ming has not forgotten about his sworn brother.
He doesn't even dare to write out his name!
However, this has been the education of the Xiao family since long ago!
It has been destined for this kind of guilt to be hidden in his heart.
Education?
Their so-called education
is not the true difference between good and evil,
but it is to prevent the status of the leader of the martial arts circle from crumbling.
So is Xiao Bai.
However, at least, they consider
not harming innocent people when unnecessary.
What about You Si and the youngest son of Nan Xinghe?
Aren't they innocent or did they deserve to die?
We have a chance to become an established sect,
but they won't give us that chance.
Shangguan Qiuyue,
but your methods
are even more cruel and merciless.
You hate my methods,
hate the fact that I have used you before,
but Brother is doing this to make the pugilist world more organized.
Xiao Chun Hua, you have said before
that you wanted to live in carefreeness and stability,
but in this martial arts circle that filled with conflicts,
is there any true stability?
So, you mean,
designing a ploy to take advantage of me was all for my own good?
When I finally rule all of the pugilist world,
you will understand my intentions.
You're not even able to make people believe you now,
why are you talking about the future?
I will listen to your words.
I will also correct myself slowly in the future.
I am no longer of any use to you.
You also don't have to listen to me.
If you still hate me,
you can also take advantage of me.
Take advantage of me to protect you for your whole life.
In the future, any of Xiao Chun Hua's requests,
I will fulfill them.
Really?
I have said before.
I will be good to you for your whole life.
Okay.
Older Brother, just let me go.
This is my only request for you.
Young Chief Master still cares for Miss Chun Hua.
His illness immediately recurred when he heard about her crisis.
Shangguan Qiuyue is scheming and unscrupulous, but we never would have thought.
We never would have thought that Shangguan Qiuyue would make trouble at this time!
He might just be afraid that our relationship with Master Shi has deepened by one step,
so he let out the news of him being injured to confuse us.
In the end, it gave Young Chief Master a heavy blow.
But how has he guessed that Young Chief Master would go crazy?
That might not be the case! The last time when Fu Lou went to get the Longevity fruit,
Shangguan Qiuyue openly sowed discord between Young Chief Master and Miss Chun Hua.
It is evident that this person is very manipulative.
He has done many deals for others before,
so he should know Young Chief Master like the back of his hand.
This devil is always hiding in darkness,
watching how we fall into his trap.
When the time is ripe, he will slowly reveal himself,
and tease mercilessly.
- Thus, it's the more that we must not fall into his trap.
- Yes.
The immediate matter now is to find Master Shi and let the truth come to light.
How about this? I will visit the Baxian Residence again.
Xiao Chun Hua, you will regret this.
Are you threatening me?
From now on, no one will be there to protect you.
I don't need anyone to.
I can live well on my own.
This world is very dangerous,
the kinder you are, the worse an outcome you will have.
After leaving Qianyue Cave, I will have no ties to Qianyue Cave from now on.
I will not frame you,
and I hope in the future you also will not use me for your ploys.
Okay.
I promise you.
Little Yan!
Gu Wan? Why are you here?
Did you forget what I told you?
Every word you said, I remember it all very clearly.
It's good if you remember it well.
-  Do you think I will show you mercy?
- You won't!
Hence, I specially came to see you.
It's because I already have finished the matter I should do.
A matter you should do?
I removed a thorny eye for you.
What have you done?
Answer me! What have you done?
You will know very soon.
Little Yan, you will thank me
because I won't let you be like me,
who can’t get a response from my loved ones.
Little Yan...
I still remember the first time I saw you.
Right next to this lotus pond...
Bright-colored lotus flower...
Your face is even more...
more...
Ye Yan?
She dares to come back.
Don't hurt her!
Xiao Chun Hua, you are leaving Qianyue Cave.
You can't raise any more conditions to me.
However, it's not impossible to consider,
with a condition that you stay here and keep me company.
This trick is no longer useful to me.
Master!
Gu Wan? Is he worthy to die in here?
- It's my fault, I—
- You don't have find an excuse.
Shangguan Qiuyue!
You have only one follower.
Only one follower?
I've always been by myself.
I used to have Xiao Chun Hua.
Now Xiao Chun Hua is leaving.
Older Brother...
The last time that I hear you calling me "Older Brother,"
it seems as if it was a lifetime ago.
Isn't it, Leader Ye?
Last time, when Gu Wan rebelled,
you seemed to have come late.
During the last rebellion, it was me who harmed and push you into a dangerous situation.
It has nothing to do with Ye Yan.
If Older Brother is suspicious, why don't you suspect me?
Yes.
Why am I unable to suspect you?
Xiao Chun Hua always said I'm good at manipulating people's feelings,
but Xiao Chun Hua is confident in your calculations and use them extremely well.
Is it because you rely on the fact that I love you so much?
Ye Yan, thanks to Gu Wan,
I'm sending Xiao Chun Hua out of Qianyue Cave today.
What exactly did Gu Wan do after all?
You can ask this dead man.
You are running out of time.
Think carefully on the words you'll use to persuade me.
Before I come back, you are not allowed to die.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫