''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique, secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
The Sky Thunder System can satisfy your wish,
but you must give up immortality.
The very first man you see is your Mr. Right.
Husband!
I'm Xiao Bai.
My father is a leader in martial arts circles.
For now, come with me to the Fengming Mountain Manor.
Take me back?
[Fengming Mountain Manor]
Then there will be many opportunities. Who is Shangguan Qiu Yue?
- It's Qianyue Sect's Master.
- What is Qianyue Sect?
- A Demon Sect.
- It's great to have the Demon Sect leader as my relative.
So great!
[Episode 2]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
It seems that he really is Shangguan Qiu Yue but he doesn't resemble whom Lu Xiu described.
Has no one seen him before?
Well, we could have just chatted. Why did you bother fussing while someone else is watching?
Who else is watching us?
Well, she won't see us if I gouge her eyes out.
Wait! Wait...
Older Brother, you have too much bloodlust.
She just attacked you.
And she even disturbed our family reunion.
Our established rule is don't frighten or let my family's little Chun Hua see blood.
Wait!
We only have one life, don't we?
This, just let her keep both eyes, please.
Just now, were you talking about...
Xin Fa?
I can help you steal it.
You should spare her.
How is that possible? It's obvious you don't know martial arts.
And before, you nearly lost your life.
You had better return to Qianyue Cave with me.
Older Brother!
Might as well! My little Chun Hua is so kindhearted.
This time, I will show mercy and spare her.
You may keep your eyes.
Thank you, Master. Thank you, Miss.
You simply must be very careful.
You must not let Xiao Bai discover your identity.
Otherwise...
What will happen if he finds out?
Then, you cannot blame me for being merciless.
Where did they go?
Hello! How do I find you all?
What on Earth is the Xin Fa?
Hello?
Miss Chun Hua.
Who were you talking to just now?
I was just training my voice.
It's my daily hobby. Would you like to hear some more?
Do you want to give it a try?
Miss Chun Hua, you should quickly return to the manor with me now.
All right.
At that moment, it seems that you know a bit of martial arts.
Ye Xingzhu, are you satisfied with your new helper?
Congratulations, Master! You can once again rope in Hua Xiaolei.
It's just that... I don't understand.
Why did you pretend to be her older brother?
Since she lost her memory, we can start over.
Now, if you pull Xiao Bai and their relationship into this again... that would be interesting.
Forgive my stupidity.
If she believes and treats me as her brother, then she can help me continue to steal the Xin Fa.
You are wise, Master.
Now, what is Xin Fa? It's the treasure of all sects.
Members of martial arts circles shouldn't be so narrow-minded.
Good things ought to be brought out and shared with everyone,
without hindrance.
I will instruct Gu Xingzhu and He Xingzhu
to hurriedly acquire the other sects' Xin Fa.
What about the Xiao family's Xin Fa?
Just leave that to Hua Xiaolei.
Hua Xiaolei, Xiao Chun Hua.
Xiao Chun Hua, Hua Xiaolei.
I think I gave her a better name.
The leader has a fierce, cruel temperament, with vicious means, and anyone who has seen...
What will happen if someone finds out?
You cannot distinguish right from wrong.
It'll mean death, either way.
No, I have to find Xiao Bai and clearly clarify about it.
Miss Chun Hua.
Xiao Bai, I have something I want to ask you.
- Your Xin—
- Young Master!
Young Master, something bad happened. The Hengshan Sect's Xin Fa was stolen by the Qianyue Sect.
Chief Mo is seriously ill from the incident.
The Qianyue Sect again! The Kuishan Sect's and the Mangshan Sect's.
This is the third Xin Fa that has been stolen.
Go back to tell Chief Mo to rest and regain strength.
Fengming Mountain Manor will stop the Qianyue Sect's crimes.
Yes.
Miss, is something the matter?
I just wanted to ask...
does your heart...
- treasure someone?
- You...
Me?
You're such a shameless, young woman.
Do you think this is shameless?
What a big blockhead! He's so stubborn.
- Seventh Junior Brother, meanwhile, go to the Hengshan Sect to see Chief Mo.
- Yes.
- Eleventh Junior Brother, go to the Kuishan Sect.
- Fourth Junior Brother, go to the Mangshan Sect.
- Yes.
- Miss, you...
- Actually, you don't need to be concerned about me.
After all, I already know that business affairs are important.
People's health and safety are also important.
I'll wait to talk after you care for all these issues.
Miss Chun Hua, wherever is your mind?
Why do you think our young master is very concerned about you?
Anyhow, I'm not preoccupied with anything.
Xiao Bai, do you need a maid?
A personal maid?
Young Master, I think Miss Chun Hua
resembles someone.
Is it Xiao Bai's fiancee?
Or some other beautiful woman?
I think Miss Chun Hua resembles
our kitchen's apprentice, Qishiliu.
Is that so?
Are you serious?
Come here, hurry!
If you have nothing to do, then chop some wood.
What, chop firewood?
Just like this! Pile it up against the entire wall.
They should be evenly cut
and piled up neatly.
Everyone in your Fengming Mountain Manor knows martial arts.
Why ask a weak and feeble girl like me to do such things?
It's dangerous to approach a person when he is practicing martial arts.
Xiao Bai, you should start getting familiar with
the sound of my breathing and footsteps.
This is where I practice martial arts. Outsiders can not come here.
How am I an outsider?
How about I keep you company?
Please keep your distance, Young Miss.
If I go farther, I can't see clearly.
If anything happens, don't say I didn't warn you.
Xiao Bai, your swordsmanship is amazing.
What are you doing?
There are six logs of firewood here.
You should cut them into eight pieces
They should be cut evenly
and piled up neatly.
Also...
that's all for now.
Can you do that?
I'll try.
Xiao Bai, you're so amazing!
This one is not even.
This one has a different length.
My skills are not good enough.
None so! It's already very good.
What are you doing?
I'm collecting the firewood.
The environment for practicing martial arts is very important.
It has been hard on you, Miss.
No problem! Look, you even know to reflect on yourself now.
That's very good! You have to keep practicing.
You're right.
Thank you for keeping me company for so long.
No problem! No problem at all.
Xiao Bai's performance was very good.
How about it? Practice like this every day.
You will definitely improve.
- Let me help you.
- No, no, no.
I can handle it myself. Don't I also need to practice?
It's getting late. Don't you need to see the master?
Thanks a lot for your understanding. I will get going now.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Xiao Bai, you have to come tomorrow. You must come.
I'll keep you company while you chop...
practice martial arts.
I just have to thaw the ice in warm water to deal with you.
Take it slow!
[Thousand Moon Cave]
Is this the Qianyue Cave?
Yes.
I didn't expect it to be so warm and elegant.
How has Xiao Chun Hua been after arriving at the Fengming Mountain Manor?
The people at Fengming Mountain Manor make me chop firewood.
I'm exhausted after all that manual labor.
Only Big Brother is good to me.
Big Brother, it's so cold here. Aren't you cold?
Xiao Chun Hua learned how to behave.
You even know to care for me.
Big Brother knows how to create a romantic atmosphere more than Xiao Bai.
Big Brother, due to a flower petal birthmark on my body
so I'm called Chun Hua; Big Brother is named Qiu Yue...
Does that mean you also have a birthmark?
If Xiao Chun Hua is so curious, why don't you see for yourself?
Such a calm attitude!
Can I really look for it myself?
Look, then (I'll) look!
It's okay. You can be frivolous.
You are my Big Brother. That wouldn't be right.
It's your own Big Brother. What do you fear?
I should know the limit since it's my own Big Brother.
Big Brother loves you so much. Shouldn't Xiao Chun Hua help Big Brother?
Xiao Bai is a good person and he's good to me.
After I lost my memory, it's Xiao Bai who took me in.
Isn't stealing Xin Fa quite indecent?
Is he a good person?
If Xiao Bai finds out that Chun Hua is Shangguan Qiu Yue's little sister,
do you think he'll continue to treat you well?
Older Brother, why are you so hostile to them?
Little Sister,
we have never seen eye to eye in every way.
It is dangerous to steal Xin Fa.
If Little Sister doesn't want to do it, that's okay.
Just stay with me at Qianyue Cave.
Xiao Bai is my Mr. Right.
If we can't meet, I can't even get him to like me over time.
Since Older Brother needs this Xin Fa so much,
I must return to Fengming Mountain Manor to try. But...
I can't guarantee that I'll be able to steal it.
This is my good little sister.
Xiao Chun Hua, rest assured! Older Brother will secretly protect you.
Then I'll return now.
Gu Xingzhu, escort Chun Hua back to Fengming Mountain Manor.
Yes.
Put me down! I want to get down.
Let go!
Gu Xingzhu, can we choose a more civilized mode of transportation?
You carry me like a sack. It's not comfortable at all.
Miss Chun Hua, you probably forgot your own identity.
What identity?
I'm your Cave Master Shangguan's little sister!
I am just following the rules.
Then let me ask you.
Did Cave Master Shangguan and I
- really have the same mother and father?
- It's getting late.
Find a horse carriage for my little sister.
Yes, Cave Master.
Am I really your biological sister?
My request isn't too much to ask. Is it that hard to fulfill?
Indeed, you are not.
It's possible that Mom and Dad misremembered.
Chun Hua could be Qiu Yue's older sister.
I, Shangguan Chun Hua,
am Shangguan Qiu Yue's older sister!
What are you doing?
Aren't you suspicious?
Then, how about I'll take off my clothes
and show you my birthmark?
I wasn't serious!
I am your older brother.  What are you afraid of?
Xiao Bai!
I didn't think even Older Brother would fall for it.
Older Brother, do you resemble Father or Mother?
- Why?
- Although we are siblings,
I can't find any similarities between us.
Did you inherit all of Father and Mother's good traits?
How does Older Brother compare with Xiao Bai?
Compare Brother and Husband? Of course, they're different.
To me, you two are different.
How are we different?
Older Brother Qiu Yue is a close relative.
If I had merely half of Older Brother's good looks,
the Xin Fa would come easily to me.
If you say it like that, Xiao Chun Hua wants to use the beauty trap.
He is a gentleman.
I don't know if the beauty trap will work.
It's entirely Older Brother Qiu Yue's fault for stealing all the good looks.
If not, the beauty trap would work, wouldn't it?
Xiao Chun Hua is right so we have to find another way.
Also,
you aren't allowed to use the beauty trap.
You'll make a spectacle of yourself.
I don't need Older Brother's reminder.
[Thousand Moon Cave]
Master, I wonder if Miss Chun Hua is Hua Xiaolei.
Whether she is Hua Xiaolei or not, why are you so nervous?
I have absolutely no intention of prying. It just that...
I'm guessing, letting Miss Chun Hua go and steal the Xin Fa.
But it's related to the matter of Xiao Bai not mastering the Fengming Saber.
You're quick to listen and observe.
- For the sake of Cave Master's safety.
- Is it for my safety?
People without eyes and ears are the safest.
I am wrong!  Please have mercy, Cave Master!
I told Gu Xingzhu.
Other than him, no one else knows.
I'm willing to guarantee with my life.
- There's one more thing.
- Say it!
Qin Liufeng is heading toward Fengming Mountain Village.
However, he has not met Hua Xiaolei.
Go! Watch closely.
Yes.
Miss, what's wrong?
If you encounter someone from the Demon Sect, what will you do?
What do you do?
Good and evil are irreconcilable!
Getting rid of the evil is my family's duty.  Why bother asking?
What if this person is your friend?
Friend?  Who?
Then what if... I'm just saying what if...
Don't speak nonsense! I do not conspire with those who are of different beliefs.
I will not have such a friend.
One side is my moody older brother.
The other side is the persistent Xiao Bai.
What should I do?
Forget it, forget it! Stop thinking about it.
What's wrong?
The sunset today is quite beautiful.
It is indeed very beautiful.
I never noticed it before.
Have you never noticed?
All four seasons, rain or shine,
Father always tells me to practice swordsmanship.
Xiao Bai, your life is too boring.
Actually, what I mean is...
do you want to put down the sword in your hand
and watch the sunset glow with me?
If you are bored, then go back now.
Xiao Bai, you are really an unromantic block of wood!
How did that happen?
I changed to a new move. I feel it's not bad.
Why didn't you do it according to the requirements?
If you cut them like this, how can they become firewood?
Firewood?
Anyway, you've done blade work before.
Not burning it, will be a waste, won't it?
Are you asking me to use the Fengming Saber to gather firewood?
I'm not! Isn't this a chance to practice your swordsmanship?
Once you're done practicing,
you can bring the wood to the kitchen to burn.
The Xiao clan's Fengming Saber punishes evil and rewards good.
It has a good reputation everywhere but is tarnished by you.
How can you refer to it like that?
If you don't gather firewood, you must gather bamboo. Isn't that the same?
How is it the same?
Are you scared that the Fengming Saber will become blunt?
- Then I'll just find you a normal blade some other day.
- You...
Also, why are you learning martial arts?
- Shouldn't it be practical?
- Martial arts isn't used for gathering firewood.
I know!
But... really, don't you think that
using martial arts to cut firewood
can save time while practicing swordsmanship?
Xiao Bai! Xiao Bai!
Your swordsmanship is so good.
Can you teach me a few tricks?
Swordsmanship is a steady skill, and requires strength.
Women are naturally weaker. Using a saber proves to be difficult.
If Miss really wants to learn, I'll teach you the sword.
No need, no need! I don't need to learn much.
- I just want to learn a few tricks.
- A few tricks?
Yes, it's just for gathering firewood.
Don't understanding human natures,
and inflexible thinking.
Why is my male lead like this?
Miss Chun Hua.
The kitchen doesn't need any more firewood.
Master Xiao also doesn't need anyone.
You don't have to make the effort next time.
Did Xiao Bai make you say that?
This brainless, wooden man.
Are you also mocking me?
Bow down!
- Bow down.
- Is Miss training the flowers?
This way of practicing martial arts is interesting.
May I ask whom Miss learns from?
I...
Why do you care?
If I didn't guess wrong, Miss would be
whom Young Master saved at Yisheng's house...
the weak lady.
Do you know Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai?
You two are so close.
It seems that your relationship with Young Master is not ordinary.
I was disrespectful. Sorry!
My surname is Qin, called Liufeng.
My father is the Dongshan Sect leader, Qin Daoxian.
- May I ask for your beautiful name?
- Chun Hua.
Chun Hua.
The romantic flowers in spring.
It seems that Miss lives up to this name.
You, too.
Young Master Qin also lives up to
your name's meaning of flirtatious.
Junior Brother Qin.
Young Master.
Xiao Bai, you're here!
It's been a while, yet Senior Brother Xiao still looks so grand.
You will be a good leader of the Wulin Sect.
Junior Brother Qin, there are no outsiders in this house.
Say it! Why have you come?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a  pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and the beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and the beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫