''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique, secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
- Brother!
- Little Chun Hua is going to get me killed.
Chuanqi Gorge.
If you want to kill her, then just kill me first.
Go to the flower field to look for Fu Lou’s wife and she will save you.
The most beautiful woman in the world. Indeed!
Sure enough, she lives up to her reputation.
Prepare a carriage for these two ladies to send them off.
When will Chun Hua and Qiu Yue come to an end?
Now, do you know the reason why I want to get the Xiao family's Xin Fa so much?
Miss Feng, Miss Chun Hua, it's good to see you both come back safe and sound.
[Episode 8]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
It seems that the identity of Miss Chun Hua is really bothering you.
However, what bothers you most is the truth about Miss Chun Hua's identity
or the marriage contract with the Hua family?
Brother Qin, I racked my brain but I still can't figure it out clearly.
Are you even making fun of me?
I, exactly, am your brain.
And the brain knows how it works.
Why are you unhappy?
I recently heard many rumors about Miss Chun Hua.
I still can't know what is true and what is false.
But right now, I have an idea.
Brother Xiao will go to the Hua family to find out the truth.
You're insightful!
However, I fear beating the grass will startle the snake (act rashly and alert the enemy).
This is simple.
What day is it half a month later?
August 15th.
The lantern festival of Yetan City is so well known.
At Mid-Autumn Festival, people enjoy the moon with beautiful women. Wouldn't it be lovely?
If you have time, I will accompany you
to check out the Hua family near Yetan City.
Miss Chun Hua must go with us.
What do you think about the others?
Miss Feng will go, too.
After all, she is the one who points out Miss Chun Hua.
Is that so?
Too many people behave badly.
Although it's just putting on a show, we should still do a good job.
I'm the dignified young master of Dongshan Sect.
How can I enjoy the moon and flowers without beautiful girls?
[Yingzhen Inn]
I'll be objective. I am really sorry.
During Mid-Autumn Festival, many people come to enjoy the flowers and lanterns in Yetan City.
Currently, there are only two rooms left.
Please take it...
So... This is too unfortunate.
How do you think we should divide the two rooms?
How can this be divided? Of course, you men share a room and we girls share the other.
- No!
Really, no more rooms? I can give you...
No, I can't. He can pay double the price.
I'm so sorry. I'm afraid you have to bear with it.
In fact, some people will leave later.
Until then, I will save it for you.
Since that is the case, then let's arrange it like this.
During the Mid-Autumn Festival, the moon will be beautiful before the flowers.
But right now, we have things to do.
Thank you, Brother Qin, for your care.
After the truth emerges, you'll find your fiancée.
Then you will live a happy life.
I will be suffering as my lonely self.
Brotherhood is for life.
With your words, I think you deserve my help.
However, I still don't understand one thing.
Since you are so impatient to know the truth,
why don't you go with Miss Chun Hua?
Before, Hua family's attitude was strange, and Miss Chun Hua is so suspicious.
I want to find more clues before they meet each other.
Then... when will you stop keeping the secret from them?
After I'm sure Chun Hua will be safe
when I announce her identity.
You are so thoughtful.
When Miss Chun Hua knows your good intentions for her,
she will surely feel so grateful.
I really envy them for being lighthearted.
Now, they must have been enjoying the flowers together.
[The Flower in the Mirror, the Moon on the Water]
Why does Miss Leng look at me like this?
Could it be that she also suspects my identity?
Darn my older brother! That's how Feng Caicai heard the imitation voice.
That is... You must be hungry, right? I’ll go to buy some mooncakes.
Great! I'll go to see if there's a room available.
Big Sister, I can't find my older brother. Can you help me find him?
Where did you and your brother go?
And what color clothes is he wearing?
Older Brother is wearing white clothes.
He took my bamboo dragonfly (pinwheel) and ran.
Why is your brother doing this?
Never mind! Big Sister will help you get back the bamboo dragonfly, okay?
- Yes.
- Let's go!
Big Sister, that is my older brother,
and my dragonfly. It's indeed him!
You—
Give it back! It's my bamboo dragonfly.
It's yours if you can get it.
I heard someone was looking for her older brother.
Even a little girl would believe you.
I even thought you had me as your only younger sister.
Little Chun Hua, are you jealous?
Of course, I have only you as my younger sister.
Just that... do you know who's that girl from before?
Back then, you killed her parents.
I saw that she was pitiful so I took her in.
As an older brother, I did so much for my younger sister, but you don't remember anything.
I've actually done such a heartless thing before?
Father, Mother, that’s the weird older brother who stole my bamboo dragonfly.
All right, all right.
Your father will get you another one. Let's go!
Shangguan Qiu Yue, can you stop playing jokes on me?
Are they Kongming lanterns?
I gave up immortality to find my love!
I hope I can have a good ending with my Mr. Right.
Also, I hope that all this trouble can disappear soon.
Younger Sister, what are you doing?
Making a wish!
What's "making a wish?"
Making a wish is like... asking for your family to have good health,
and the world to be at peace.
Then as your wish flies to the sky with the Kongming lantern, it will be fulfilled.
These people actually look for their happiness through these rotten lanterns.
And they even hope it will come true. How absurd!
Little Chun Hua, why do you also perform these foolish things?
Just tell me what wishes you have, I will surely make them come true for you.
If I tell you, am I just courting my own death?
A wish can't be said aloud. Once I tell, it won't come true.
Boring!
Oh, mooncakes?
- Mooncakes.
- Each year at Mid-Autumn, families share mooncakes together.
They admire the moon together. It means the family will remain together in harmony.
Older Brother, did you ever have mooncakes before?
Of course, I've eaten it before.
Then what flavor do you like?
Brother must not have eaten flower-flavored mooncakes.
I want to eat it now. Let's go!
[Hua Residence]
This really is an influential family, living here so isolated.
Xiao'er, you must remember that without Uncle Hua,
there wouldn't be a Fengming Mountain Manor today.<
[Wind Listening Pavilion]
Now, Uncle Hua’s family moved to Yetan City.
Hence, your Uncle Hua and I
decided on a marriage between you and Hua Xiaolei.
Brother Xiao!
Brother Xiao.
Xiao Bai.
Are you recalling the old times, aren't you?
Now, we have only one wall separating us from the truth.
I suddenly feel so confused now.
Don't worry! You're such an affectionate, loyal person,
the heavens will certainly send help to you.
Don't be nervous! Let's go.
[Hua Residence]
- Greetings, Young Lords.
- Visiting in the middle of the night is disrespectful on our part.
Please tell your master that Fengming Mountain Manor's young master, Xiao Bai,
has an important matter to discuss.
Little Chun Hua, you're so clumsy.
Can you make mooncakes properly?
Older Brother, if you don't want to help then forget it, but stop saying nonsense here.
Then you tell me, how should I help you?
I want to make this flour into dough.
That's amazing!
I'm doomed. I'm doomed!
Master...
- Look!
- Look at what?
There's something moving inside.
- Look carefully!
- Where is it?
- Lower!
- I don't see anything!
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever. It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
[Hua Residence]
Fengming Mountain Manor, Xiao Bai.
Dongshan Sect, Qin Liufeng.
- Greetings, Master Hua.
-  Greetings, Master Hua.
Your junior has not visited you in a long time.
May I ask if everything is fine with you?
Just a few months ago,
I could have called you “Son-in-law.”
But now, you've become my nephew.
How is Xiao Mengzhu's health?
Thanks to Uncle, he is so-so.
After he was poisoned by the Demon Sect many years ago,
we still couldn't find the antidote for him.
Demon Sect again!
They are really powerful.
I'm here unexpected,
because I have something urgent to report to you.
What is it?
Older Brother, didn't I already tell you?
Mooncakes must be shared with family.
It only tastes good when you share it.
Ye Yan, come here!
Master.
- Try it.
- I dare not.
If I want you to try it, then try it.
Does it taste good?
Since it tastes good,
why have I never eaten it before?
I made a mistake.
I thought you dislike the festival atmosphere.
- so... I didn't—
- Then that means
you did it on purpose.
I know it's my fault.
Older Brother.
Little Chun Hua, tell me!
Should I gouge her eyes out
or kill her?
Older Brother, while eating mooncakes, we should enjoy the moon.
Besides, during the Mid-Autumn Festival,
why do something so bloody? Right?
Instead, why don't we go for a walk?
Do you remember the taste?
I remember it.
Prepare more next time.
Little Chun Hua likes to eat it.
Then let's go.
The lantern show is already over.
Why do they still not return?
Really strange!
Young Master Qin loves to play.
He likely went to watch the lanterns.
Who cares how Master Qin plays around?
I'm worried about Young Master Xiao.
After he entered Yetan City,
his behavior is so suspicious.
What makes you say this?
According to Young Master Xiao's personality,
he wouldn't come here just to enjoy the lantern show.
Young Master Xiao must have another purpose for coming here.
I think you know this better than me.
This place is near the Hua family’s home.
Compared to watching the lantern show,  based on Young Master Xiao's personality,
visiting Old Master Hua is the most important matter.
It's Mid-Autumn Festival so it's normal to drop by and visit an elder.
It's just that... How can he visit
the elder late at night?
Even more odd is Miss Chun Hua.
She said she was going to buy mooncakes.
I think at this time,
all of the shops are likely closed.
My young daughter died recently.
Why do you bring her painting here
to cause pain to a grey-haired person? (Idiom: an elder's pain when a younger loved one dies.)
Uncle (term of respect),
Xiaolei is still alive.
Xiaolei did not die.
I already found her.  It's just that... she has lost her memory.
Where is she now?
She came with me to Yetan City but it's just inconvenient for you to meet her right now.
What do you mean?
Forgive me for speaking bluntly.
After finding Xiaolei,
her suspicious aspects have been increasing.
I know I shouldn't speculate, but I worry the Demon Sect will take advantage of her.
Thus, I came to confirm with Uncle Hua.
Before Xiaolei's marriage, did she...
Utter nonsense!
Not only did you cause my daughter's death,
right now you even want to destroy her innocent reputation.
Xiao Bai,
my Hua family and your Fengming Mountain Manor have had a relationship for generations.
What kind of person I am, your father clearly knows the best.
The daughter that I taught and raised, even after becoming ashes,
I will not allow you to insult or slander her.
- Uncle Hua, please don't get agitated! Brother Xiao didn't mean that—
- Shut up!
You should tell me.
Where is the arsonist who set fire to Fengming Mountain Manor that day?
These matters... We have yet to ascertain what happened.
I see that you came to Hua family to convict.
That my Hua family colluded with the Demon Sect.
We are too shameful and inferior to associate with Fengming Mountain Manor!
Butler, escort the guests out!
Uncle Hua.
Uncle, please be understanding of today's situation.
After we figure out the truth, we will definitely visit again to apologize.
The Old Master is interesting. He was so enraged.
To know his biological daughter is still alive...
Is his reputation more important?
You can't blame Old Master Hua.
Involvement with the Demon Sect has always been an unforgivable crime.
I acted too impulsively.
What plans do you have?
No matter what, Xiaolei has the right to know the truth.
Let's go!
You, young masters, watched the lanterns until late at night.
How wonderful!
Why isn't Miss Chun Hua here?
Miss Feng didn't get to see the lanterns and eat mooncakes, just waiting for you.
But now, you only ask where Miss Chun Hua is.
I am very sorry for making Miss Leng wait for this long.
Who is waiting for you? Fancy yourself!
I just knew that Miss Leng would be angry so I brought you a small gift.
I hope you will like it.
Casually picking wild flowers
is Master Qin's style of doing things.
Yetan City is full of good and bad people.
Miss Chun Hua also doesn't know martial arts.
I think I should go and find her.
Did Miss Chun Hua say where she went?
She went to buy mooncakes so she should be back soon.
- How long has she gone?
- It's been three hours.
Young Master Xiao, I'll go with you.
Hold on! I'll go as well.
Count me in!
During the Mid-Autumn Festival,
family should eat mooncakes together.
Together and complete!
Our parents are all dead.
It has been so long.
I don't even remember what they look like.
Brother is so pitiable.
However, I'm destined to be with Xiao Bai.
Then Big Brother will be lonely in the future.
From now on, I'm your only family.
I will find more time to keep you company.
What you said...
do you mean it?
Of course!
Brother believes you.
Excuse me! Have you seen this girl?
- Excuse me! Have you seen this girl?
- She's this tall. Have you seen her?
You really haven't?
No.
Brother Qin, how's it going?
Let's continue looking.
How beautiful!
How can this place exist in Qianyue Cave?
How can there be so many lotuses here?
Big Brother, were you born during Mid-Autumn festival? You must be!
Otherwise, how would you be as beautiful as the moon in the sky?
Why don't you beg me? I'll pick it for you.
Then I'm begging you to help me pick one.
Thank you, Big Brother.
What's wrong?
The curtains are not good. I don't like them.
In your heart, everything's not that good.
In my heart, Little Chun Hua is the best.
Big Brother, I really have to go back now.
Didn't Chun Hua say you have to be with family during Mid-Autumn Festival?
Is Xiao Bai more important than me?
That's surely not what I meant.
If I don't go back, Xiao Bai will be worried.
Are you sure that he would be worried?
You know Xiao Bai considers himself a hero.
I'm just a weak woman in his eyes.
Of course, he will be worried.
Might as well! Since you're so worried,
get the Xin Fa within ten days.
So be it! I'll worry about that later.
Then...
wait until after I get the Xin Fa, I'll come back to play with you.
- You can play however you want to.
- Okay.
Then I'll give you something precious.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫