''A Girl With A Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
As for this meal, we shouldn't eat this meal.
The Longevity fruit is fake but this Soft Muscle Powder is real.
I tell you the truth, this is the Snake Saliva Incense.
It was indeed the Longevity fruit produced by this Master Shi,
that set the sects of the Righteous Path and the Demon Sects against each other.
If it weren't for you
and the Longevity fruit auction,
how would there be so much bloodshed?
It seems that in Xiao Chun Hua's heart,
I'm also only a heinous evildoer.
[Episode 40]
What did you all make her eat?
Why does the Hundred Flower Tribulation turn out to be like this?
I only fed her the Snow Lotus Seed.
You guys gave her the Snow Lotus Seed.
I only know that Team Leader Gu has won this game.
No matter whether it's the Soft Muscle Powder or the Snake Saliva Incense,
as long as it got mixed with the Snow Lotus Seed,
then it will trigger
the attack of the Hundred Flower Tribulation poison.
Bu'er, where is the antidote?
I am most familiar with the Hundred Flower Tribulation poison.
There is no antidote.
I was planning to cure you after the great fight.
I never imagined—
We'll just have to see, between the Young Chief Master and the Cave Master Shangguan,
who is going to save her?
I really don't know which figurehead of the Righteous Path or the Demon Sect
will sacrifice himself to save a mere girl.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
If we do not get rid of the poison,
Xiao Chun Hua will die after half of an hour.
Older Brother Qiu Yue, don't kill the innocent anymore.
The Qianyue Sect is skilled at manufacturing poison.
Since this poison originated from Qianyue Sect, there must be an antidote.
There's no antidote for the Hundred Flower Tribulation poison.
There is still one more method to save her.
It's by using only the Zhen Qi (internal force).
The average normal Qi won't do.
It has to be the purest Qi from Yang,
(TN: In Chinese philosophy, Yang is characterized as male associating with heaven, light, and heat in oppose to Yin which is characterized as female associating with earth, dark, and cold.)
or the purest Qi of the three Yin.
(TN: Xiao Bai has the purest Yang Zhen Qi; whereas, Qiu Yue has the three times the Yin Zhen Qi of any other.)
Young Chief Master seems to have been practicing the purest Yang Zhen Qi .
Could it be that...
Shangguan Qiu Yue has been practicing the purest Zhen Qi of three Yin?
About the Hundred Flower Tribulation poison, even with the strongest martial arts masters,
it still takes three days to detoxify and cure her.
Team Leader Gu and I were originally planning
to poison the girl during the great fight between Qianyue Sect and the Fengming Mountain Manor.
Then it doesn't matter whoever doesn't sacrifice himself,
I can still gain power and elevate my status.
Such an important thing, Team Leader Gu and I
have planned a long time for this.
But who knew you'd feed her the Snow Lotus Seed
and quicken the attack of the poison?
No matter who decides to cure her,
that person has to use up all his purest Zhen Qi.
The pugilist world will lose yet another top level martial arts master.
However, who would be so foolish
to become so vulnerable in front of the other?
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
Whose ice silk pearl glows first has to promise the other person one thing.
So childish!
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
Little Pearl, do your best, okay?
So as long as my pearl is still glowing, yours won't fade, either.
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
You have to kiss here.
I did a lot of things behind your back.
However, you still didn't know.
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
Chun Hua, Qiu Yue (spring flowers, autumn moon), when will it end?
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
It's good now.
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫
Why do you want to save me?
Chun Hua?
I already told you...
I will treat you well.
Shangguan Qiu Yue had used the fake Longevity fruit
that led to so many deaths.
He has to be punished.
Young Chief Master,
why don't... we kill him now?
Then use your Zhen Qi to cure Miss Chun Hua's poison.
Young Chief Master cannot kill him.
He is saving someone.
Wouldn't that be taking advantage of the situation?
Husband!
I clearly remember...
your face.
In your heart,
is there anyone you like?
There's no right or wrong for love.
Although Elder Master Xiao failed Shuangguan Hui,
he didn't stain his name as a martial arts master.
Chun Hua said,
use kindheartedness to heal the world,
then you won't fail to love others or get to know others.
I like you.
I have never loved anyone other than you.
You said that you like me.
Xiao Bai likes Chun Hua.
You'll be good to me my whole life, won't you?
I was wrong to be with the great villain of the Qianyue Sect.
I...
am, therefore, also a demoness.
You should kill me for the greater good.
wouldn't that be even better?
Miss Chun Hua.
Young Master Qin.
I was thinking about when I first met you until now.
Did you sense the change with time?
I'm no longer a cockroach that never dies.
The truth of the Longevity fruit is now known to the world.
Bu'er has also been executed.
Yes.
I still have to congratulate you, Young Master Qin.
You achieved what you wanted, having an engagement to Miss Leng.
In the final fight, the Qianyue Sect had everything within their grasp.
They could have benefited from it.
However, I never thought that suddenly
Shangguan Qiu Yue was taken by Ye Yan.
The martial arts world has also calmed down.
It ended without even a fight.
Your poison from the Hundred Flower Tribulation has also been cured.
You were unconscious for two days.
We moved you from Baxian Residence back to the Fengming Mountain Manor.
Yes.
You... Are you still blaming the Young Chief Master for not making a decision?
Not at all.
He should have done it that way.
If he saved me and sacrificed all of you,
I would feel guilty forever.
Shangguan Qiu Yue
used up his purest Zhen Qi.
This news has spread all over.
Originally the Righteous Path and the Demon Sect would spare no effort to win,
but due to his illness, everyone dispersed in no time.
After that, there was some inner turmoil within the Qianyue Sect.
People from all over the pugilist were against Qianyue Sect.
He had started the issue of the Longevity fruit
so all the sects deeply resented him.
But don't you worry!
The Young Chief Master has ordered that no one can harm him.
Three days ago, Ye Yan settled the rebellion
and had Qianyyue Sect under control.
Then what about Shangguan Qiu Yue?
He... stayed out of the conflict.
Actually, this incident would be to his ultimate benefit.
To think about it again, he was a very calculating person.
He caused us to fight each other from within.
However, before the great fight, he had already used up all of his purest Zhen Qi;
and thus, ultimately prevented this fight.
It is also better this way.
The pugilist world can be peaceful for a while yet.
If his will to protect himself were a bit stronger,
that would have been great.
You... must really love him.
Shangguan Qiu Yue likes to play with people's emotions.
He treated you just like a pawn but he always protected you.
Who would expect that right before the great fight,
he could give up his prospects to choose you?
He, actually,
is too naïve.
Who would dare to disagree?
However, no one can firmly say that he is naive.
I have always wondered what he really wants.
It's as if all he ever wanted is you.
When facing Bu'er's final plot,
he and the Young Chief Master had the same decision to make.
The Young Chief Master chose the greater good, as for him...
he chose you as his final move on the chessboard.
No matter what,
he has won.
With a girl like you by his side,
our worry against him will also lessen
and the peace in the pugilist world
will be maintained a little longer.
Miss Chun Hua,
I now, bid you
a "Goodbye."
The days are getting colder.
Please remember to close the doors and windows.
I am well and strong right now.
You have lost a lot of weight after dealing with this illness.
Xiao Bai, I really do not blame you.
Is that so? I would prefer that you blame me.
I also want to go and see him.
When will it be?
Just right now.
I will tell someone to take you.
Are you still angry at me?
If you stay with me, there will come a day when I will sacrifice you.
Only being with him,
you will be cared for under all circumstances.
Xiao Bai,
you must live on well.
Don't worry! There will be a lot of girls who will fall in love you in the future.
I will get someone to take you.
Thank you.
♫  In a trance, seeing you for the first time  ♫
♫  Tugging on my heartstrings  ♫
♫  Just one glance  ♫
♫  That I will cherish for all of my life  ♫
♫  In love and inseparable, year after year  ♫
♫  There are many volumes of the book of gratitude and grudges  ♫
♫  Looking out into the distance, I long for nowhere and nothing  ♫
♫  One's path in life is boundless and goes as far as one can see  ♫
♫  The wind carries and sends promises  ♫
♫  People coming together and separating squander this life's destiny  ♫
♫  Dreams are numerous and disorderly like thousands of fallen petals  ♫
♫  Looking after each other yet having nothing to say  ♫
♫  Spirits of my dreams lead me along, telling me to carry out my ideas  ♫
Xiao Bai,
thank you for all the care you have given me.
In the past, I believed in love at first sight.
Love means fated to be together.
To love someone is to become like the person of your dreams.
But now, I realize
love is unconditional,
requires no effort, and cannot be resisted.
Xiao Bai.
A person will die.
A love-filled life will always be too short
and destined to taste of joys and sorrows.
It's unavoidable that you must make choices and sacrifices.
You are a hero.
One day, you will meet someone
whom you will be unable to resist.
Chun Hua.
♫  Do you wish to spend forever with me?  ♫
♫  Who will you tell? Who will you cry with?  ♫
♫  A song filled with parting sorrow is difficult to score  ♫
♫  I'll accompany you on this road of hardship and strife  ♫
♫  Who will you look after? Who will you miss?  ♫
♫  For the rest of our lives, we will commit to each other for good times and bad  ♫
♫  Do you wish to  ♫
I came!
♫  Spend forever with me?  ♫
Xiao Chun Hua, are you here to see me?
Yes.
Are you waiting for me?
Xiao Chun Hua, please go back.
I no longer need you.
I don't agree with your previous tactics.
I know!
Can't you control yourself a bit?
Sure!
Then why are you still not coming to me?
I never saw you dress yourself like this.
It is too ugly.
Don't touch! Just ignore it.
You are still so cold.
I do not like people who are cold.
You have to wear more clothes in the future.
Okay.
A while ago, they pursued to kill you.
Are you hurt?
It is all in the past.
Might as well! I know you can't die easily.
Did you also hope I wouldn't die?
Of course!
I only want you to live on well
just like now.
You fool, Older Brother!
I am also leaving.
Will you hug me?
Two people embracing each other,
isn't this warmer?
Yes.
Then I'm going to be flirtatious with you.
I'll do as you please and let you flirt.
Didn't your Purest Zhen Qi return?
Not really.
Will your hair ever turn back?
It is very ugly, isn't it?
A little bit.
But it's not a problem.
I will get used to it after a while.
Let's go!
Let's go home.
This is not pitying.
It's also not gratitude.
It is because Xiao Chun Hua
want to be with you.
Chun Hua is always supposed to be with Qiu Yue originally.
However, I am
unable to take Xiao Chun Hua flying anymore.
How can that be matter, anyway?
We can start a new life.
Then, you have to live well
and love me well.
The past cannot be erased.
Xiao Chun Hua, you also have seen Fu Lou's demise.
Are you scared?
I'm not.
However, you will be.
I have a lot more courage now.
In addition,
you are not Fu Lou and I'm also not Yousi.
I will not let us meet the same ending.
Xiao Chun Hua,
I will ask you seriously one more time.
Do you really have no regrets?
I really don't have any regrets.
However...
in the future, when we fight, I might say some things.
Do not take it to heart!
Sure!
Then...
Older Brother, you once said
you will always treat me well.
Is that still true?
Of course, it's true.
Every word I have said to you is true.
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
Fu Lou died
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
so Yousi was unable to live on; hence, you must promise me
that you must die after me.
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
- I will try.
- Moreover,
I won't allow you to love someone else, or tell me you hate me
and be in a cold war with me.
- Also, you can't—
- I will not permit Xiao Chun Hua to leave me.
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
Okay?
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
Yes.
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
Xiao Chun Hua, let's go.
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
Channel Manager: sweetsunnyday
Chief Segmenter: karasu_006
Segmenters: nicefly09, chemellelott, aanya1_515
dasfl49, nmelova, alessandrina, deval_chloe, kkikikaa, nanaosaki81, jedelande, marisol_inf, adenike
Chief Editor: nicefly09
General Editors: sunset_vermont, worthyromance
Translation Editors: trangxklnguyen_197, laurapuente
[In Sang Tian Village, a female awoke with amnesia after death.]
[In Sang Tian Village, Chun Hua awoke with amnesia after death.]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫