''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
After the longevity fruit auction, Master Shi should have earned millions.
Baxian Residence doesn't have so much money.
Bo, zhong, shu? Bu'er?
Three days later, Bu'er will invite you to a banquet.
There will be lots of Soft Muscle Powder in all the dishes.
Xiao Chun Hua, you shouldn't engorge it.
Li Yu isn't Master Shi.
Now, every piece of evidence all point to Master Bu'er.
I believe that people like Bu'er
will definitely think the more visible the place is, the safer it is.
Find Shangguan Qiuyue and force him to detoxify Chun Hua.
- This poison has no cure.
[Episode 37]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Are you crazy?
This place is full of people loyal to Fengming Mountain Manor.
- Don't you want your life anymore?
- No problem.
If someone sees me, then I'll just kill him
and use his clothes to leave.
Is it fun to you?
I only missed you.
Lady, you finally came!
Please hurry to take this man home.
He is so handsome but is so dumb.
If he continues to wander, he will likely lose all of your family's fortune.
Xiao Chun Hua, you must save me.
What is wrong?
I came here to pick the jade pendant that I ordered for you.
I gave him money but he won't let me leave.
I have an upright business so I don't want to take advantage of you.
- This much money, how am I supposed to give back your change?
- I told you to keep the change.
Look! This one is yours.
It is engraved with your name on it.  [Spring Flower (green)] [Autumn Moon (white)]
This one with my name on it is mine.
Is it you who told him to engrave these?
I didn't tell you? Oh right! I think you were mad at me at the time.
I must have forgotten to mention it.
Please talk later! We need to clear this transaction first.
If you insist giving me this,
I will not take it and you will have to leave those jade ornaments here with me.
We don't want them anymore.
You have been wandering around just for this?
Wait a minute! You can't do this because these jade ornaments have your names engraved on them.
- Who would I resell it to?
- That's right!
What to do?
I bought it for you so why would you pay for it?
Then your money will be given to me?
This man indeed has a strange mind.
Let me tell you, Miss! You must look after him in the future.
He is an older brother and I'm his younger sister.
How can I look after him?
You can. You can!
You two really get along very well, fighting in jest for fun.
I really like you both.
This young man should understand the hardship of making money.
In the future, you won't feel bad after spending it.
You are the younger sister but you are steadier than your older brother.
Please educate him! He will listen to you.
Of course, I will listen to her.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Please. Take care!
Flowers for sale!
Flowers for sale! Miss, come and take a look.
You like it?
-Take one.
- Flowers!
Kites!
Can you please not make trouble for me anymore?
The jade pendant Xiao Chun Hua had chosen,
if he sold to others, what would we do?
So you caused him trouble.
It's lucky that I stopped by or else I do not know what will happen.
Even if you had not intervened, I would have only scared him a little.
I doubt it would cause much trouble.
He doesn't want to take the money.
He is still smarter than you.
He is honest and kind.
I am not like you who has no conscience. Take it!
My money is yours.
Xiao Chun Hua should take it.
However, how do you have so much money?
Where did you steal it from?
I have tons of money so there's no need to rob anyone.
I have a friend so I just went to see him to borrow some money.
He just gave me 10,000 Liang casually.
He is really scared and afraid I won't help him.
What friend?
Master Shi?
Might as well! He sold a fake Longevity fruit and did make a lot from it.
Master Shi is indeed Bu'er.
You came to Baxian City this time.
It is not as simple as you just need to borrow some money, am I right?
The fact that you are staying.
Is it really to just wait for me?
Then why must we leave in three days?
Xiao Chun Hua, you sure are silly.
It has already been two days.
When everything finishes,
I will take you back to Qianyue Cave.
Finish? How would you like to finish it?
Killing people?
Get me to go back to Qianyue Cave with my hands stained with blood?
Xiao Chun Hua, if you want to see me, you can go to that meadow to find me.
Remember this! As long as I am alive,
I surely won't let you die.
I want you to take me back now.
Did you go out to relieve boredom?
The poison in your body
was used as a tactic for Shangguan Qiu Yue to force you into something?
If you do not want to tell me, I will not pursue it, either.
However, I will find a solution for you.
The poison in my body is just a small matter.
You are the master of the martial arts circle and the successor of the Fengming Saber.
You should take care of the whole pugilist world,
and not me.
You are afraid that I will be busy with the matters of pugilist world and can't take care of you?
The Xiao Family takes care of the pugilist world generation after generation.
It's our responsibility.
However, I will definitely save you.
Shangguan Qiu Yue will not let me go.
Besides, the poison I am inflicted with is connected to him.
So I cannot help you to fight against him.
I just want to live well.
I know that my attitude and standpoint make other people
feel that I bring shame upon the Fengming Mountain Manor.
I do not want to burden you.
You once told me
you liked me.
- In the past, I did and I wasn't lying to you but now—
- No need to say anything further.
Chun Hua, I won't let the pugilist world down.
I will not let you down, either.
Xiao Bai,
sometimes, people are forced to choose.
The path that Shangguan Qiu Yue has chosen to take
should not force us to make the same choice.
Chun Hua, don't you worry.
I definitely won't let the poison in your body to spread.
Xiao Bai must really hate Shangguan Qiu Yue right now.
He might just kill him.
Not good! I can't go out alone right now.
It will definitely draw their attention.
Miss Chun Hua, do you need something?
Miss Caicai, I have been in conflict recently.
Why don't we go out to get some afternoon tea and chat?
- Sure! Let me get Young Chief Master—
- No, no, no!
Why are we bringing such a big man like him?
Let's just keep it among us, girls.
Sure!
It is so hard for us to get some time alone together.
Yeah. The three of us can't just follow the men wherever they go.
It's still better if girls are more independent.
That is right. Qin Liufeng is too clingy.
I have been wanting to come out with you girls.
My stomach is bothering me so I need to relieve myself.
- Do you have any food poisoning? Or—
- No, no.
I am just feeling unwell.
I just want to go and relieve myself.
I have no money right now so you both should wait for me.
Lady Boss, where is the restroom?
When you go out the door, head North.
How do you get to the restroom?
It is a bit far! Once you exit, you must go North.
Miss, what do you need?
Do you see those two young misses?
They are all my frenemies.
They want to take my man.
I need to meet with him but they are so clingy and I cannot meet him.
I just told them that my stomach hurts and needs to go to the restroom.
However, that won't delay them for long.
I must burden you with the task of delaying them.
Sure! I know those two well.
You know them well?
Then you must be extra careful.
You just go! I can watch them.
Take the back door.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks, Madam.
Have you really been here?
I was worried that you couldn't find me.
Oh right! They are all trying to look for you; you should leave quickly.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, I've looked for you for long time.
Xiao Chun Hua, you brought people here.
Do you want to kill me?
In you mind, everyone wants to kill you.
Since you don't trust me, you shouldn't have told me your hiding place.
It is not that I do not trust you.
However, because you are too stupid, I am disappointed in you.
Did Miss Chun Hua really go to see Shangguan Qiu Yue?
Yes. This morning, Lady Chun Hua went to invite the two girls out.
They thought it was weird so they told me about it.
So I followed the girls to the restaurant and stayed nearby.
Then I saw Miss Chun Hua sneaked into the meadows alone.
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
I have been working day and night to find you.
God helps those who help themselves.
Tell me where the real Longevity Fruit is.
Your first words to me is the Longevity Fruit.
You sure are blunt.
The Longevity Fruit must belong to the legit circle of the martial arts circle.
I naturally must know where is it for sure.
Chief Leng, you are full of flaws when you are anxious.
When you fought with Feng Qianwei for the Longevity Fruit back then,
was it with this same attitude?
You... What are you talking about?
You and Fengqian Wei both want this longevity fruit,
it's a fair competition.
However, you only want to take a shortcut.
You promised Master Shi to help him in the auction.
You had gotten the Poison of  Dandelion from him.
Then you killed your biggest competitor, Feng Qianwei.
Nonsense!
All the people who claimed that I talked nonsense were all attested to the truth in the end.
Everything I've said is the truth.
Leng Ying, when you discard Feng Qianwei's body in the wilds at the time,
did you really not know how potent the Poison of Dandelion is？
Shangguan Qiu Yue,
Feng Qianwei's body was obviously in the coffin,
but you slander me that I discarded it.
Your lie is so untenable.
It seems that Chief Leng still doesn't know that it's I who sent in the coffin.
You!
Master Shi originally wanted to use that coffin to punish you
but he didn't expect that you were wicked and merciless.
You led Qin Liufeng and his companion to a secret room.
You had wanted to get rid of them
but your biological daughter was also there.
Leng Ying, you were in such a hurry to kill Fu Lou,
wasn't it because he also had discovered everything?
Do you think that since Fu Lou spared you, you can do whatever you wanted?
Leng Ying,
the people who you killed, Fu Lou, You Si and Feng Qianwei are all watching you now.
Accidentally, Xiao Bai opened the secret room and you didn't get punished.
On the contrary, you made Feng Caicai get the Poison of Dandelion.
It was not me. It wasn't me...
It was not me!
What a pity!
Leng Ying,
go and explain to those you have killed.
Let go  of Chief Leng!
Be careful!
Chief Leng?
Miss Chun Hua, did he hurt you?
How many people did you bring?
It wasn't me.
It was not me. I didn't do anything.
Miss Chun Hua, don't be afraid!
I am here.
Fengming Mountain Manor
are full of people who concentrate on making profits.
You also associate with them?
Shangguan Qiu Yue, if you allow yourself to be seized without putting up a fight,
I will give you a chance to live on for the moment as the master of martial arts circle.
Live on?
I'm not sure if the Sect Chief Nan Xinghe
will laugh if he heard this in Heaven.
Chief Leng.
Chief Leng is going to die.
Shangguan Qiu Yue,
you have committed another major crime.
Chief Leng,
how about you ask Chun Hua, who is next to you,
if he deserved to die.
You have the nerve to mention Chun Hua?
Cave Master.
Ye Yan?
- Oh no! It's not good.
- What is the matter?
Miss Chun Hua's poison flower has bloomed.
This is love poison.
When the inflicted is enamored, it will become fatal.
What?
Oh right! Let's not telling Miss Feng and Miss Leng about Chief Leng.
Miss Chun Hua, Miss Feng and Miss Leng are both waiting for you.
Do you want to explain to them?
Should it be time for me to explain anything right now?
For your Fengming Mountain Manor's responsibility,
can you just treat others' trust as rubbish?
Don't be mad!
I told him to say it.
Do you think I still don't know what kind of person you are?
You came here to confess that this was all done under your command.
What would that solve?
Of course, I know this was done under your command.
The fact is
in order to eliminate Demon Sect,
you can do anything.
I want to kill Shangguan Qiu Yue.
However, if I have to be in a battle to the death with him,
I certainly will do it above board.
Really?
Has your father ever told you
Where is the spirit tablet without any characters in the study from?
Do you want me to tell you a name?
Nan Singhe.
I heard about it before.
My ancestors and Nan Xinghe are sworn brothers indeed.
But later my father didn't bring this up.
So I didn't question closely as well.
Xiao Min feels guilty for Nan Xinghe.
Xiao Yuan feels guilty for Shangguan Hui.
The spirit tablet without characters
shows the self-accusation of Fengming Mountain Manor which can't be told to anyone.
It's also Fengming Mountain Manor's ridiculous pride.
Last time,
you made use of "acknowledging one's sin" to scheme against Fu Lou.
This time, you used me to find Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Sometimes, I was thinking if there is one day I was also among the spirit tablets without characters.
To become one of your underserved victims
who bear your secret self-accusation.
My ancestor was also helpless.
However, Nan Xinghe originally killed countless people.
How can you compare yourself with them?
If Nan Xinghe gives up evil and return to the righteous path, then we won't have Qianyue Cave today.
I didn't expect anything new under the sun.
In the end,
I will become a pawn for you to manipulate Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Miss Chun Hua,
not anyone can give up evil and return to good.
There can only be one person walking in front of you.
Otherwise, there will be cause of a disaster for sure.
Sometimes for the sake of pugilist world,
you must choose one.
So in reality, you are very clear about your grudge.
It's nothing to do with good or evil.
No matter it's Shangguan Qiu Yue or Nan Xinghe,
They must both die.
No.
I have no intention to kill Shangguan Qiu Yue.
You have injured him to that point and you still say...
Chief Leng arrived before us.
I didn't expect that.
I was forced to injure Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Unfortunately, Chief Leng still died.
I cannot kill Shangguan Qiu Yue.
It's because the antidote for your poison is with him.
Are you really doing this only to get the antidote?
Miss Chun Hua, I like you.
I just want you to live well.
Xiao Bai,
thank you.
- But—
- There is no buts.
I will promise you that I will use any method
to help you get rid of your poison.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫