''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Please, Older Brother, let me go.
My younger sister has grown.
When you see me, is your first response to doubt me?
I actually believe you and wanted to save you.
Chun Hua has been used by Shangguan Qiu Yue.
She did not betray Fengming Mountain Manor.
Book of One's Crimes? Longevity fruit? What do you mean?
Those who openly repent will receive the Longevity fruit.
Fu Lou cherishes his wife the most in his life.
His wife is extremely sick and desperately needs this Longevity fruit.
But this Longevity fruit is fake.
Older Brother, can you take me to Chuanqi Gorge?
Gorge Master Fu can use my sister to exchange for the Longevity fruit.
[Episode 24]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Miss Chun Hua?
Madam Yousi.
Why did you come?
Gorge Master Fu,
my younger sister is very kind.
You have to treat her well.
If you really care that much for your younger sister,
would you really let me know that fact?
What is your purpose?
Toward this younger sister,
I do have genuine love.
However, it could not be compared to the love you have for your wife.
Thus, you do not need to worry about anything.
I just don't accept being threatened.
I also do not permit anyone I care about to get hurt.
What plans do you have?
Of course, I plan to visit Fengming Mountain Manor with a message.
I will tell them
the Young Chief Master's future wife is here as a guest.
Do you think they will bring the Longevity fruit to trade?
Come out!
Shouldn't you be secretly monitoring the people in the sects of the Righteous Path?
Did you dispatch the Book of One's Crimes?
Of course, the Book of One's Crimes is not a bad idea.
In order to get the Longevity fruit, they must openly repent of their sins.
Those people hope that only one person
ends up as the sacrifice.
Fu Lou is desperate for the medicine.
He is, therefore, the most suitable sacrifice.
Now, Fengming Mountain Manor is under criticism.
There is no escape for them.
If Fu Lou were to be eliminated this time,
that will not only greatly sully the name of Fengming Mountain Manor,
but they will also lose the hearts of some supporters.
It's the first rule of Qianyue Sect.
Do not guess what the Master is thinking! Have you forgotten?
Moreover...
it's to allow Xiao Bai to lose the heart of Chun Hua.
Shut up!
Okay, okay. I won't continue speaking of this topic.
I also won't say that because of this, Chuanqi Sect will fall apart.
The days of Qianyue Sect taking over Xingyue Sect are looming.
Why are you so faithful to the Cave Master?
I heard that at your wedding ceremony,
you were kidnapped by the Cave Master of Qianyue Sect.
At the time, I even thought it was due to the fighting between the sects.
Looking at your expression now,
it seems feelings were involved.
Madam, do you care for longevity?
My husband has killed many people.
So you know?
He promised me he wouldn't kill anymore.
So I believe he will not kill another person.
It's just that I have also seen the martial arts world,
especially Chuanqi Sect and Qianyue Sect.
They completely adhere to the survival of the fittest.
Because of me, my husband
went to Chuanqi Gorge.
He started as the lowest disciple and rose all the way to the Gorge Master.
The hardships in between...
you would understand without thinking too hard.
I never thought of it like that.
He did all this for me.
So I must think of him.
I told him,
couples who aren't in love with one another,
even if they were together for a lifetime, remain an unhappy couple.
The days of a couple who love each other,
even if it is a few years, those are still happy days.
However...
I think he really wants me to be by his side forever.
I gave up eternal life and gave my all in search of love.
However, can Xiao Bai give me this kind of love?
Older Brother's care for me, I don't know if it's real or fake.
Is it a test on the path of love?
Or is love too complicated in itself?
Why can't I get an all-consuming love
without any reservations like Yousi?
Hero Xiao is upright and righteous.
He's a hero with whom women want to marry.
The way that he loves you makes me think you are lucky.
But the one who kidnapped you at the wedding,
he is also extremely charming.
Homme fatal (handsome devil)! It's only skin-deep.
Love can make a person's heart flutter to pursue what they want,
while it makes another person's heart flutter to accept someone.
Then Madam Yousi,
you really are happy.
After all, love is not something anyone can get.
I can tell that you really have a dilemma.
What kind of love is the best in your opinion?
I think,
I don't care how others perceive him in their eyes.
In my eyes, he is the most precious.
It doesn't matter how I appear to anyone else.
I just want to be special only in his eyes.
Love is not something that can be defined.
When you look back at
what choices you have made,
what you gave up,
and what he chose and gave up,
everything will become clear.
Why has my husband not returned?
Where did he go?
I do not want him to lose his life in exchange for mine.
I have left a note in Miss Chun Hua's room.
Very good!
However, with Xiao Bai's personality,
he most likely won't make any moves on Chuanqi Sect that allows us to gain the upper hand.
He knows what must be done.
Yousi's body is weakening and Miss Chun Hua is with her.
Fu Lou is frantic like a cat on hot bricks.
That's why there's no need for us to worry.
A Book of One's Crimes; a love that transcends life and death;
a friendship between Chun Hua and Yousi!
It's enough to make this story play out more interestingly.
Go for now! Just sit back and watch the show.
Brother Xiao, Miss Feng just knocked on my door saying that you can't seem to sleep.
She told me to wake up and keep you company. What a cruel life I lead!
Young Master Xiao,
Miss Chun Hua is gone.
- What?
- She left a note.
Exchange Longevity fruit for Chun Hua at Chuanqi Gorge.
What is wrong?
Chuanqi Gorge.
Miss Chun Hua really is a burden.
First she's kidnapped by Qianyue Sect and now by Chuanqi Sect.
Leng Ning!
It's already been four hours.
Haven't you decided still?
I must care for the overall situation.
I am sorry to treat Miss Chun Hua like this.
If you trade the Longevity fruit for Miss Chun Hua, the result will be the same.
But this is about the reputation of Fengming Mountain Manor.
Exchanging the Longevity fruit for Miss Chun Hua would be out of personal feelings.
Fu Lou using the Book of One's Crimes to get the Longevity fruit is out of martial arts justice.
I already made Fengming Mountain Manor lose face once.
It's hard to be the Young Chief Master.
Miss Chun Hua said that Fu Lou has a genuine heart for his wife.
Chun Hua and his wife have a good relationship.
That's why Chun Hua would be safe at Chuanqi Gorge.
But right now, they have a hostage in their hands.
We still need to find another way.
Young Chief Master Xiao, Chief Leng wants to see you.
It's already very late. Why is Chief Leng here?
He also brought a girl.
- This is....
- The wife of Gorge Master Fu, Yousi.
Simply keeping a hostage
can make Fu Lou willingly fall into the trap.
Yousi is a lady, who cannot fight back.
She is also gravely ill.
- Kidnapping her here–
- Daughter, the pugilist world is dangerous.
You don't understand.
Those who are with demons
can't be any good themselves.
- But–
- Yousi is the wife of my father's murderer.
It seems we can't fully believe the rumors of them being in love.
Fu Lou is cruel and heartless, but Yousi is weak.
It looks like she has suffered torment to survive until now.
There is some truth in what these two girls have said.
Husband...
Where am I?
Madam Yousi.
This is Fengming Mountain Manor.
We ask for the company of you and your husband.
Today, why don't you rest in the guest room?
Gorge Master Fu, he...
will be here shortly.
I have not been able to notify you in advance.
It is a lack of propriety on the part of Fengming Mountain Manor.
I'm counting on you then, Young Chief Master Xiao.
Did Miss Chun Hua bring me here?
Yesterday, we had a pleasant conversation.
My gifts...
Miss Chun Hua is presently out.
She really likes your gifts for her.
That is good.
Since Madam Yousi has decided to stay here,
then I will take my leave.
Then let us take Madam Yousi to the guest room.
Who would think the head demon's wife is so out of touch with the outside world?
However, to use a weak lady as a means for an exchange,
this will also be criticized by others.
Since it has come to this,
let's craft a divorce letter to be sent to Fu Lou.
Are you still thinking about today's events?
My father's actions today
have really shocked me.
Chief Leng was accounted for the overall situation.
It's just too extreme!
The pugilist world is dirty.
There are things that you can't avoid.
Regarding this, hearing Yousi speak,
it sounds like their love is very deep.
Fu Lou has protected her well.
[Chuanqi Gorge]
Brother Qiu Yue?
Where is Madam Yousi?
Why haven't you returned to Qianyue Cave?
You used me to come to Chuanqi Gorge.
Now, you want to force me to go back home?
You're too cruel.
Not at all! I am just worried you won't get a restful sleep.
I have some interesting news.
I came in a hurry to tell you.
What news?
Do you sleep well in here? Tell me!
Do you feel more comfortable at Chuanqi Gorge than at Fengming Mountain Manor or Qianyue Cave?
That's true.
It's because Madam Yousi is the one I admire the most.
When she's by my side, I feel at ease.
Yousi is prone to illness, what is there for you to admire?
What do you understand?
All right.
I'm all ears.
Madam Yousi has the thing that I want the most.
What's that?
Previously, I always heard, "Give your meager resources to help others in time of need."
Now, when I see Madam Yousi and Fu Lou,
they depend on each other for survival and cherish each other.
I feel that if one is able to obtain this kind of love, your life will not go to waste.
In that case, have you yourself experienced this kind of feeling before?
Before,
I even thought...
I don't know.
I think you miss Xiao Bai.
What do you think?
Do you want to gamble once more with me?
Bloody Fengming Mountain Manor!
Gorge Master Fu.
Last night, you had a very happy chat with Yousi.
I thought since she is ill and weak, her friends are few and far between.
So I allowed you to sleep here!
I never expected that in one night,
Yousi would be kidnapped by Fengming Mountain Manor!
What?
How pity!
Master Fu Lou unexpectedly shared such interesting news first.
I really didn't expect Fengming Mountain Manor dares seek personal gain using this shameless way.
I also truly did not expect until yesterday that
Gorge Master Fu would naively think Fengming Mountain Manor wouldn't dare such a shameless act.
As long as the outcome is "justice,"
they can go as far as 10,000 excuses to cover their evildoing.
Xiao Chun Hua should be even more familiar with their routine.
So you already knew that Madam Yousi...
You suddenly came here yesterday, was that to help outside forces from within?
Gorge Master Fu,
my younger sister lacks courage and confidence.
I hope you won't frighten her.
Gorge Master Fu,
the Longevity fruit is fake.
The Book of One's Crimes and destruction of the Longevity fruit are both hoaxes.
I came here to prevent you all from falling into their traps.
Fake?
It is indeed fake.
Sisi still needs it to survive.
Madam Yousi is at Fengming Mountain Manor now.
And you have so many personal enemies.
She is now in imminent danger.
Fengming Mountain Manor!
Wait!
You can take me along.
They kidnapped Madam Yousi.
You can kidnap me.
Well, I won't keep you two company any longer.
Gorge Master Fu, my young sister is rather tough.
If you want to pretend to kidnap her, you must act that it's real.
That's right! We should make our acts seem real, but
you can't disfigure or disable me.
You have free rein to do anything else.
I see that what my younger sister cares the most, is about her face.
Ice silk and the hidden chamber are nothing compared to this.
Why don't we make a bet?
If I win, you must return to Qianyue Cave with me.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, what kind of game are you playing at now?
Young Chief Master, something bad has happened!
There's no use kidnapping me!
If you kidnap me, I'll make Xiao Bai deal with you later!
Goodness!
Gorge Master Fu, how about you use your weapon and put it on my neck?
That way, it'll seem more realistic.
Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
Like that, like that!
Help! Rescue me!
Xiao Chun Hua is actually quite good at acting.
However, she shouldn't use this trick with me next time.
Fu Lou is the only one who came from Chuanqi Gorge this time.
The martial arts sects assembled at Fengming Mountain Manor this time solely to
watch the grand ceremony of the Book of One's Crimes, dominating by sheer force of numbers.
Gorge Master Fu also brought many Chuanqi disciples
and assembled them outside Fengming Mountain Manor.
Pick an excellent one.
Yes. Regarding that, Gu Wan already went to make contact.
Once the Chuanqi Sect completely collapses,
Xiao Bai and I will be the only ones left to fight to the finish.
Interesting!
- Xiao Bai, quickly save me!
- Chun Hua.
Fu Lou, a life-and-death struggle is not the outcome that you want.
I am urging you to let Miss Chun Hua go.
I'll exchange your wife for mine.
If you don't bring Sisi out immediately, then I'll kill her!
Fu Lou, you already made a terrible mistake by slaughtering innocent people.
Don't commit any more crimes!
Crime? You all kidnapped Sisi first.
Have you nerve to brazenly judge others' crimes?
Gorge Master Fu forgot he is unscrupulous himself.
He betrayed his own master and married his wife by force.
Xiao Bai! Xiao Bai, save me quickly! Xiao Bai!
Such a cowardly woman who fears death!
Do you think you are qualified to be the Young Chief Master's wife?
- Using the Young Chief Master's wife to threaten us won't work—
- Chief Leng,
Chun Hua is my fiancée.
Bring Sisi out and I'll let her go.
My husband!
Didn't you all
invite me and my husband here as guests?
My husband, Miss Chun Hua is a good person.
Don't hurt her!
If you let Miss Chun Hua go,
I'll return your wife to you.
You all...
It is so hard for you all to become capable.
Madam, please!
My wife.
- My husband.
- Are you all right?
All right, let's go!
I didn't think that Xiao Bai still has some empathy.
If that's the case,
Xiao Chun Hua,
will you be happier if you go to Fengming Mountain Manor?
Master Fu Lou, wait a minute!
Tomorrow noon, Fengming Mountain will hold a Longevity fruit conference.
Then Madame Yousi's illness may be cured.
Xiao Bai.
You know the Longevity fruit is fake, don't you?
Xiao Bai, you...
I, Xiao Bai, guarantee by Fengming Manor's hundred years reputation
that the Longevity fruit is not fake.
Tomorrow, my Fengming Moutain Manor will protect
you and Madame Yousi's safety.
Miss Chun Hua,
the Longevity fruit should be left for those in need.
It should not be kept in Fengming Mountain Manor.
nor should it be used to make fake public disclosure all around.
Xiao Chun Hua hasn't agreed with my bet yet.
You can come and go freely everywhere.
Wherever my Young Sister is, no mater if there are mountains of daggers and seas of flames (grave danger),
I still can come and go freely.
You are more comfortable with pestering people than anyone else.
You can see, at tomorrow's Longevity fruit conference,
whether your Xiao Bai can protect them both or not.
- As long as you don't interfere—
- I promise not to interfere.
As long as he can protect them and I believe that he can protect you
you can stay at Fengming Mountain.
But if he can't protect them,
then you should follow me back to Qianyue Cave.
I won't gamble with you.
You don't want to gamble, or you dare not gamble?
Martial arts justice or personal morality, which one is more important?
Between you and martial arts justice,
which one will Xiao Bai choose?
When you gave him a chess piece back then,
did Xiao Bai tell you which one he would choose?
Indeed, he didn't.
Xiao Chun Hua, ten thousand beautiful words
aren't worth one word of truth.
Older Brother, what word of truth will you tell me?
Older Brother has no true word to say.
Older Brother only do it.
Stop!
I was so embarrassed in Fengming Mountain Manor all because of you!
Now, do you want to swagger out of the room?
Is that so?
Older Brother thinks when I'm with my younger sister
it's like being in Qianyue Cave.
Okay, I can gamble with you!
Xiao Chun Hua finally made up her mind.
Tomorrow is the Longevity fruit conference.
The night of the full moon may be more interesting.
The full moon
looks like a trap.
Young Sister's words seem to be scolding Older Brother.
Sisi, don't you worry!
Wait for me to get the Longevity fruit tomorrow.
We can be happy together after then.
Husband, because of my illness, you run around day and night.
It was inevitable to offend people.
When my health gets better,
I will explain clearly to each and everyone.
Then we can be together for a long time.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫