''A Girl With A Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Actually, this is Miss Leng Ning. This is Miss Feng Caicai.
We didn't meet for a while so this time, I specially prepared a gift.
- Remember you're a demon, not a fairy. Don't use the beauty trap! It's embarrassing.
You must be here for tomorrow's poem meeting.
Today's poetry theme will discuss the ways of the right.
I even thought poem meeting would be so romantic, but it's just this. How boring!
How did the legendary dignified Gorge Master Fu become as weak-willed as a woman?
Right now, I just want to achieve longevity, then talk about death.
[Episode 6]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Sentiment and righteousness don't get along.
If you must choose only one, you should choose righteousness.
Then is Miss Caicai really saying that
the martial arts world is teaching people to be heartless?
If it's for the people, I'd rather be heartless.
This way, you will be on the right path.
Great! Then I would also like to recite a poem.
Please, Miss!
"They hoe weeds at noon. Their sweat drips on the soil. Who knew each grain of rice is the fruit of hard toil?"
Good poem! Good poem! Such a very good poem!
Miss Chun Hua, you're indeed so talented.
- Yes.
- Good poem!
I still have another one.
"Geese... geese... geese...
Necks curve as they sing to the sky.
White feathers float on the green water.
Red feet paddle through clear streams."
What's wrong?
This is the poem Brother Qin wrote when he was seven.
- Didn't you know?
- Is this Qin Liufeng's original?
- System, are you kidding me?
- I wrote it as a joke in childhood.
Miss Chun Hua is so thoughtful.
Who has the time to recite your poem?
It was just on the spur of the moment.
I still have another one.
Two golden orioles—
No...
A red plum tree—
Too ominous (red plum tree symbolizes a woman's affair).
When will spring flowers and the autumn moon end?
"When will spring flowers and the autumn moon end?"
How much of the past do you remember?
Someone told me before
this was a sad poem.
She was calm every time she recited it.
Right now, Gorge Master Fu,you are at the exact same time as when she was here.
So even Master Shangguan also has someone you miss.
No,
she died a long time ago.
But it seems the person whom Gorge Master Fu misses, is dying
and needing longevity fruit to stay alive.
Is it the wife of your master whom you stole?
Fu Lou, I didn't know you also seek the longevity fruit.
Are only the Right Path people allowed to know about the longevity fruit?
Have you seen the longevity fruit?
Fool! Do you try to get information out of me?
Chief Feng killed the healer.
That's not a problem but I am not as easy to handle.
Gorge Master Fu, don't falsely accuse me.
The dignified Xisha Sect Master impudently killed the healer for the sake of the longevity fruit.
If your so-called Right Path martial arts friends knew...
Gorge Master, if you have something to say, do so.
Fine! Bring the girl who died and came back to life here.
When will spring flowers and the autumn moon en—
I messed up. I forgot that I can't mention Qiu Yue.
Miss Chun Hua.
Everyone, calm down!
I learned some medical techniques and skills.
We can make a decision after I examine her.
How is it?
It's not urgent.
I learned acupuncture before.
After I give her a few needles, she will wake up.
I never heard that Young Master Qin knows about medicine.
Miss Chun Hua, you're finally awake.
My head hurts.
I want to go back and sleep.
Miss Chun Hua drank some wine just now.
She also caught the cold breeze. I'll ask Miss Feng to take you back to your room.
No need! I can go on my own.
- She is pretending, right?
- I don't know.
Young Warriors, what's the meaning of all this?
Today is the distinguished meeting of our Right Path martial arts circle.
This girl's tongue wagged too freely and willfully said those two words.
Is it possible she's a Demon Sect enchantress?
I was too negligent.
I forgot to tell Miss Chun Hua about this taboo.
However, she really didn't do it on purpose.
Young Master, you are chivalrous.
But what exactly is her identity?
How does Young Master relate to her?
Why have you unexpectedly absolved her this way?
I'm really not absolving Miss Chun Hua.
I simply think that Miss Chun Hua did nothing wrong
but for these two words of Qiu Yue.
What?
These mere two words put you all into such a panic.
We should all make a concerted effort to eradicate the Demon Sect.
We shouldn't put excessive attention on such words to fear a mere word.
Could it be that
you all truly fear them?
Naturally, we aren't scared of them.
There's just no need to bring up these topics.
Since you're unafraid, in the future when we eradicate the Demon Sect
and uphold justice, we will need all of your help.
Today is our elegant, illustrious gathering.
Don't let unsheathed weapons
and their frosty, icy glitter ruin the mood.
I especially invited some girls
to play music for your enjoyment.
What do you think?
Two Misses, please!
Thank you, Elder Brother Qin, for your righteousness.
Later, there will be a better opportunity to thank me.
Luckily, I'm clever and quick-witted. Otherwise...
Why is he here again?
You can't hold your liquor,
but you had to show off.
What is Older Brother trying to do?
He wouldn't, would he?
Since little Chun Hua doesn't want to take her medicine,
Older Brother can only use his own methods now.
Older Brother, stop teasing me!
When I was trying to steal the Xin Fa for you, I nearly lost my life.
Big Brother cares for you a lot to even come here to help sober you.
When did I bring up Xin Fa?
Oh right, Older Brother! You should probably go now.
If someone finds out, we'll be done for.
What do you fear? Wouldn't it be fine if we just killed them all?
You're here?
- Take it out!
- What?
You know but you still ask.
Hasty men don't get to eat hot tofu.
Stop!
My dad suddenly found in his investigations that Hua Xiaolei of the Hua family died.
Died from what?
The Hua family doesn't reveal much about this matter.
However, once you see a painting of Hua Xiaolei,
you might form your own judgment.
Have you seen this painting before?
How could I have seen it before?
I'm such an amicable person, yet you still don't believe me?
I don't believe you.
Older Brother, I want to ask you about a matter.
What matter?
Did Xiao Bai's fiancée, Hua Xiaolei,
die in a sea of flames?
Indeed!
Did they never find her corpse?
Correct!
Then who started the fire?
The one who set the fire is you.
How is that possible?
Little Chun Hua, don't forget!
When the Xiao family's house burned, you were there, too.
Was I there, too?
You're lying to me. I don't believe you!
LiChun Hua is forgetful as expected.
You had many devilish ideas so you snuck into the Fengming Mountain Manor.
You said you wanted to steal Xin Fa for your Older Brother.
Older Brother, are you really speaking truth?
I... Am I really the one who started the fire?
Absolutely true!
You only started a fire and killed someone.
Why are you nervous?
Brother Xiao, if you keep going like this, how will we ever see Miss Hua's real face?
Are those Lisheng's shoes?
Xingyun's necklace?
Senior Brother, it would still be better if you leave.
Go.
So mysterious! Who cares?
I still don't believe it.
Little Sister doubt Big Brother.
I wouldn't dare.
How do I dare doubt Big Brother?
Is Miss Chun Hua here?
I'm here, Miss Feng. What did you find me for?
For the poem society, I especially brought over new tea.
I wonder, would you want to try it with me?
Sure, I'm coming to open the door. Go then!
Miss Chun Hua?
Miss Feng, I'm still getting over my hangover. It's better not to meet you now.
Well, drinking the new tea with me can help you overcome your hangover.
Miss Feng, I still discuss important matters with Miss Chun Hua.
Can you wait for some other time?
Since Young Master Xiao and Miss Chun Hua are still talking,
I won't bother you anymore.
Young Master Xiao?
How are you...
I'm coming to find Miss Chun Hua to discuss important matters.
But I clearly just heard your voice from inside her room.
I'm afraid Miss Feng heard incorrectly.
I was just in Senior Brother Qin's room.
Then, could it be...
voice imitation?
Miss Chun Hua, are you okay?
We are going to come in.
Miss Feng must be anxious because of the poem society.
But I clearly heard two people.
I suppose Miss is just too tired. Go back and rest early!
Since Young Master Xiao needs to discuss important matters with Miss Chun Hua,
I will not bother you any longer.
Miss, are you better now?
I'm not good, not good at all.
My head feels dizzy, my chest is stuffy, and I want to throw up.
Xiao Bai, can you check if I have a fever?
I'll tell the server to bring you hangover soup.
No need, no need!
Xiao Bai, it's better to just keep me company.
Miss Chun Hua,
I actually have important matters to discuss with you.
As you have not sobered up yet,
I shall talk with you at a later date.
Xiao Bai!
Miss, have you sobered?
Xiao Bai, can you take me outside for some the fresh air?
- Xiao Bai.
- Chun Hua.
- Please speak first, Miss.
Tonight, the autumn breeze is blowing gently. The moon...
The moon is bright and the stars are few.
You also think it's not bad, don't you?
Miss, you may speak plainly. Say whatever you want.
Was I not allowed to bring it up? I even pretended to be drunk.
What did you say?
I was saying
going out for fresh air indeed helps sober me.
All is good if Miss feels well.
Xiao Bai, I really didn't mean to do that in the poem society today.
I couldn't think of more poems so I was a little muddleheaded—
Miss is not at fault.
If Demon Sect didn't stir up havoc, how could the martial arts circle be so anxious?
It's just...
Do you really remember nothing from before?
I'm  Shangguan Qiu Yue's younger sister.
I even set afire Fengming Mountain Manor.
I don't remember! However, Xiao Bai, you just ask straightforwardly,
I'll tell you anything I know.
I want to know everything about you, Miss.
Since Young Master Qin is so absent-minded, I won't waste your time anymore.
Miss Leng, please don't go anywhere. I want to make it up to you.
My thoughts really were not wandering.
It's just tha...
There are some matters that are so unimaginable.
- Is it related to Miss Chun Hua?
- Why do you say that?
At the poem meeting, Miss Chun Hua was amazing.
Her name is now famous in the land.
Miss Chun Hua surely isn't of the martial arts circle.
It's logical she defies trivial conventions.
You take her side as if I was purposely blaming her.
- I didn't mean it that way.
- I don't care what you meant.
Young Master Qin keeps mentioning Miss Chun Hua.
Why don't you tell Miss Chun Hua the incredible event?
But I don't remember... I only remember what happened after I woke up.
Then what happened before you awoke?
Was Miss hurt by someone? Or—
I only remember that
the first person I saw after awaking was you.
Young Master, whether practicing martial arts or doing anything else,
you are very focus in all.
I only remember that
whenever I am in danger,
Young Master always rescue me.
I also remember that
I-I dishonored Young Master in his private pool.
Pardon me! I was rash.
Please don't remember such incidents, Miss.
I-I-I forgot already!
Miss, you haven't eaten anything properly all day.
Right now, do you still have an appetite for anything?
Xiao Bai is still the most considerate.
I do!
I have something to say to Young Master Xiao.
Miss Feng, what do you wish to say?
It concerns the martial arts circles.
I'm afraid Miss Chun Hua would be disinterested.
Miss Chun Hua, you've just sobered.
Why don't you go to your room and rest?
All right.
Miss, please speak.
- Today's poem society—
- Miss Feng.
Today, Miss Chun Hua didn't do it intentionally.
It's best to forget these matters.
Why does Young Master easily trust Miss Chun Hua?
As a righteous martial arts sect, we must be fair.
We shouldn't suspect anyone without good reason.
Furthermore, Miss Chun Hua is a weak girl without martial arts skill and with no family.
Her heart is innocent but she just approaches some matters recklessly.
She certainly has no ill will.
I clearly heard another voice from inside her room but when we entered, there was only her.
- This kind of explanation...
- Miss Feng,
I have my own reasons.
It's simply that now is not a suitable time to tell you.
Young Master, you only hear what you want.
Thanks for your reminder.
It's getting late. Miss Feng, please go back and rest.
There is still another matter.
Is the garmentthat I gifted you
suitable for you?
I didn't have enough time to try it on yet.
If the garment is not suitable, please tell me
so I can alter it for you.
I didn't expect Young Master Qin would be such a gifted scholar with practical martial arts skills.
It's "jack of all trades kung fu," nothing compared to Brother Xiao's.
Miss Chun Hua, did you have a nice chat with Brother Xiao last night?
Very good We also had a small midnight snack.
Oh, that's right! Young Master Qin, I recommend a wonton shop that is very good.
- We—
- Miss, you are concealing some of your identity.
Do you have any trouble that you're reluctant to discuss?
Concealing?
I have a lying devil brother or I am an arsonist?
If it were me, I wouldn't be so stupid.
If the Young Master knows, it will just...
Young Master Qin, what are you saying? I truly don't understand.
Yesterday at the poem meeting, Brother Xiao didn't blame Miss Chun Hua.
If you intentionally fool him, Brother Xiao will become suspicious.
By then, your Xiao Bai will be quickly stolen by others.
Just don't blame me for not warning you.
Young Master Qin, you're must be kidding.
I'm someone who lost my memory.
How could I conceal something? Right?
Miss Chun Hua, have you packed up everything?
This afternoon we'll prepare to return.
Thanks for your reminder, Miss Leng. I'll go and pack now...
Father, what are you doing here?
I heard something about yesterday's poem meeting.
Sure enough, as you said, this girl cannot be trusted.
Moreover, not only that, but
Miss Chun Hua gave herself away yesterday.
She imitated Young Master Xiao's voice to fool me behind the door.
Just as expected, only the Demon Sect has the skill to imitate voices.
How could an ordinary person easily learn that?
But yesterday, I talked to Young Master Xiao about it to no avail.
I was unable to convince him without evidence.
The Chief of the Alliance is seriously ill and powerless.
But we can't just sit by and watch.
Take her to the woods outside town.
I'll also wait there for you.
You and I will interrogate her.
We will surely obtain detailed, accurate evidence.
After I return to Fengming Mountain Manor, I can be alone with Xiao Bai.
Miss Chun Hua, no need for you to return today.
I've told the Young Master that you'll take a stroll with me.
What do you mean?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it  ♫