''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
I was fifteen when I finally escaped.
That woman forced me to become literate and to practice martial arts.
Sister Ye Yan said the rebellion outside has been handled.
When your injuries heal, you can leave.
But my injuries have not healed yet.
- Brother can also heal at Qianyue Cave.
- Brother trusts only you.
If I knew the Longevity fruit is related to the puppet silver needle, I must certainly obey his orders.
The trail has gone cold again.
Young Chief Master.
Young Chief Master?
[Episode 30]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
This hairpin! It seems I have seen it somewhere.
Never mind! I must have remembered it wrong.
Does Younger Sister want to flirt with me?
Don't you forget
that you have been severely injured.
It's flirting or hurting.
You can't be the one who makes the decision..
For example, I can kill you now.
If Younger Sister wants to kill me,
I'll be happy to oblige.
Or do you still reluctant to do it?
You cannot take the next step to kill me,
nor can you step back and let me go.
Therefore, I will have to make the decision for you.
What are you doing?
Xiao Chun Hua, you do not have the heart to kill me.
In that case, you must like me.
If that is the case, can I be flirtatious with you?
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
The wall is too cold,
I'll warm you.
[Culture Prospers]
Are you saying that Chief Feng
is the one who killed the healer?
I never imagined that the Chief Feng whom I admired all my life,
destroyed himself.
I have yet another suspicion.
Although Chief Feng had deep internal strength and excellent martial arts,
he and the Healer were still evenly matched in skills.
Chief Feng would not be able to kill with one stroke.
There must be something odd about it.
Doubtful indeed!
We shouldn't make it public before we completely investigate this matter.
And the more not to let Miss Feng know.
Got it!
Xiao Chun Hua,
you have flirted with me and hugged me.
Why are you still so cold towards me?
Why are you asking me like I was the one who initiated it?
When I was injured, who let Xiao Chun Hua set her mind on
taking advantage of my poor health?
However, since I now know you have feelings for me,
I will not hold it against you.
What nonsense! Who said I liked you?
Xiao Chun Hua,
there are many benefits to liking me.
What benefits?
For example, I will let you flirt with me for the rest of your life.
[Culture Prospers]
Puppet... Silver Needle... Healer...
Li Yu...
- Young Master Qin.
- Miss Feng?
It is already so late, is there anthing I can help you with?
Can I speak with you inside?
Yesterday, Young Chief Master and I visited the Healer's former residence.
Just as we reached the front door, his expression changed for the worse.
Miss Feng, don't be suspicious!
- You have to believe—
- How can this be?
I feel very nervous when I think of this matter just now.
However, I can't make up my mind
so I came to you to verify.
This issue needs to be investigated thoroughly.
We can't jump to conclusions so quickly.
However, I can't sleep well, which is why I came to talk to you about it.
Miss Feng, I can't solely believe in Fu Lou's words.
You have to believe in Uncle Feng's conduct and character.
- And today Young Chief Master specifically talked to me about this—
- Master Qin.
I'm not talking about this matter.
It's... it's about the Young Chief Master.
Lately, there seems to be something off about him.
Normally, you are closer to him.
I wanted to ask for your opinion.
[Culture Prospers]
Young Chief Master and I visited the Healer's former home yesterday.
As soon as we reached the front, his expression turned sour.
That place was where Chun Hua and Young Chief Master first met.
Now everything changed, it's hard not to be emotionally affected by it all.
That's right! It's the reason why I left first.
I wanted to let him be alone with his thoughts.
However, I didn't expect to encounter
a surprise attack by masked men in the bamboo grove.
A surprise attack?
Thank goodness! Young Chief Master caught up to me and saved me.
However, I didn't expect him to use the last move of the Fengming saber,
and immediately kill the attackers in a split second.
That is not his style.
The Young Chief Master is usually careful and deliberate.
He's chivalrous and wouldn't kill them without finding out the truth first.
He simply hurt them without any deliberate thought.
Didn't he tell you that we were attacked by surprise?
Not at all.
If Young Chief Master was affected emotionally by his separation from Miss Chun Hua,
and became muddle-headed and unthinking,
that could be understandable.
But when he came back, he never once mentioned this incident.
He couldn't be that scatter-brained, could he?
Moreover, I believe
his swordsmanship was extremely ferocious and frightening.
It absolutely did not merely come from his emotions.
That is so strange!
A word like "forever"
is easier said than done.
It's because "forever"
is not easily achieved.
Xiao Chun Hua, the emotional and sorrowful expression on your face
reminds me of the first time that we met.
You lied to me the first time we met.
You now have the audacity to mention "forever" to me.
At that time, you were lying in Baxian Residence.
Xiao Bai was furious when he got there.
I could only watch you from afar.
How could I lie to you?
Baxian Residence?
Not true! The first time we met was on a hill behind Fengming Mountain Manor.
I remember it so clearly.
Are you trying to mess with me again?
I would never mess with you about the first time we met.
Back then, Hua Xiaolei left me.
Ye Yan persistently hunted her down to kill her
so she ended up dying at Baxian Residence's entrance.
At the time, I was even thinking
how she could escape death.
I never thought that when she awoke, she became Xiao Chun Hua.
Were you there that day?
I watched over you until you finally came about.
One look at you and I instantly knew you were a different person.
Your expression at that time was extremely innocent.
We're only reminiscing about our chance encounter, what are you thinking about?
Were you wearing this hairpin that day?
That is correct!
I can see that this hairpin seems to have fate with Xiao Chun Hua.
So...
it was you.
It was me.
What is wrong with Little Sister?
The very first person I saw...
was you?
Xiao Chun Hua, you are acting strange again.
Who else would it be?
The first man you meet will be your true love.
♫  In a trance, seeing you for the first time  ♫
♫  Tugging on my heartstrings  ♫
♫  One glance  ♫
♫  That I will cherish for all my life  ♫
♫  In love and inseparable, year after year  ♫
♫  There are many volumes of the book of gratitude and grudges  ♫
♫  Looking out into the distance  ♫
♫  I long for nowhere and nothing  ♫
♫  One's path in life is boundless and goes as far as one can see  ♫
♫  The wind carries and sends promises. People coming together and separating  ♫
♫  Squanders this life's destiny  ♫
♫  Dreams are numerous and disorderly like three thousand fallen petals  ♫
♫  Looking after each other yet having nothing to say  ♫
Why? Why is it you?
It's my fault.
I wasn't good.
Please do not cry anymore.
♫  I'll accompany you on this road of hardship and strife  ♫
♫  Who will you look after? Who will you miss?  ♫
♫  For the rest of our lives, we will commit to each other for good times and bad  ♫
♫  Do you wish to  ♫
♫  Spend forever with me?  ♫
♫  One's path in life is boundless and goes as far as one can see  ♫
♫  The wind carries and sends promises  ♫
♫   People coming together and separating squanders this life's destiny  ♫
♫  Dreams are numerous and disorderly like three thousand fallen petals  ♫
♫  Looking after each other yet having nothing to say  ♫
♫  Spirits of my dreams lead me along, telling me to carry out my ideas  ♫
♫  Who will you tell? Who will you cry with?  ♫
♫  A song filled with parting sorrow is difficult to score  ♫
♫  I'll accompany you on this road of hardship and strife  ♫
♫  Who will you look after? Who will you miss?  ♫
♫  For the rest of our lives, we will commit to each other for good times and bad  ♫
♫  Do you wish to spend forever with me?  ♫
Team Leader Ye, you've been guarding this place without eating or sleeping for three days.
Do you want me to call someone to switch shift with you?
No need! Just do what you were assigned to do.
Yes.
No matter what, I'm still your older brother.
When will Chun Hua (spring flower) and Qiu Yue (autumn moon) end?
That is not the same.
Xiao Chun Hua, aren't you happy?
I am happy.
Very happy.
It's good as long as you are happy.
Did you know?
When I was at Baxian Residence, I had a dream.
In the dream, the person said
that the first person I saw when I opened my eyes
is my one true love.
I always thought, that person was Xiao Bai.
He was not wrong.
It's just that Xiao Chun Hua mistook me for someone else.
Thank goodness all is not lost.
Will you really treat me well?
Of course!
I will be good to you forever.
The Longevity fruit auction made a stir in the martial arts circle.
Countless deaths and injuries,
and Li Yu is only a normal disciple from Baxian Residence.
If he was allowed to participate earlier in the planning of the conspiracy,
he would be lured out by others or perhaps be killed quickly in order to prevent secrets from being disclosed.
However, Li Yu is still living well.
There is nothing suspicious.
So I believe his words.
When I think about it, the assassin that night
is not like Li Yu.
Speaking of that, after Miss Feng and you were at Baxian Residence,
were you also attacked?
Yes.
Yesterday, we went to Baxian Residence.
At that time, my thoughts were numerous and confused.
Upon return, I actually forgot about this incident.
No problem! Young Chief Master, I think you have been too tired these days.
But even until now,
someone still hinders our investigation of the Healer's death.
This means that the possibility of Chief Feng being the killer
is not high.
After all, Chief Feng is already...
If we can really find the mastermind behind these assassins,
that would count as a way to prove my father's innocence.
Since the owner of the silver needles on the puppets is the Healer,
after his death his medical skills were inherited by the Baxians.
We shouldn't just focus on the Healer's disciple, Li Yu.
We should thoroughly search the Baxian Residence.
That's right! Why didn't I think of that?
I was led by Li Yu.
You are not stupid! You just think you are too smart.
[Baxian Residence]
[Excellent Medical Skills]
Last time, I lacked medical experience.
So I was unable to help you get rid of your poison.
Fortunately, with a quick glimpse today
I can see that Miss Feng is ruddy and have strong pulse.
This allows me to not be too guilty.
Thank you, Master Bu'er, for your concern.
You don't need to check her pulse
and already know Miss Feng's health situation.
How about this? Please examine me!
It can't be renal weakness, right?
Young Master Qin, I need to remind you
to really worry about your health.
Master Bu'er, do I really have a severe illness?
This will not do.
My happiness has only started to sprout so I cannot die now.
Young Master Qin.
Young Master Qin, you keep a love affair
in repeated hesitation so it's hard to say by your appearance.
However, it seems you were ecstatic and restless these days.
It is a fire from the five elements (metal, wood, water, fire and earth).
I advise you to be careful in not getting angry.
[Excellent Medical Skills]
Speaking of it, why did Young Chief Master come to my manor today?
Do you have some important matter?
Recently, incident after incident happened in the martial arts world.
They have caused countless causalities.
I have heard of these matters.
It's just that I'm not a member of this martial arts world.
I can only do things to make up for it.
So I'm also worried about the outbreak of chaos afterward,
and I thought of you
who told me a technique of controlling puppets.
If we can understand this,
maybe it can help the Righteous Path to reduce some losses.
Technique of using puppets?
That's right! A physician described it before where
a silver needle is used to...
- You're talking about the guarded technique.
- Exactly!
Although this puppet silver needle was sealed up by Healer for a long time,
it still is a special, unique skill.
If you know it,
then can you pass it on to me?
Young Master Qin, this is black magic.
Black magic, if used reasonably, is also the righteous path.
Unfortunately, I practice medicine and do my commercial activities everyday.
When could I think to study this black magic?
This technique of using silver needles to control puppets, I really don't know about it.
Since Master Bu doesn't know about the technique of using silver needles to control puppets,
then please don't pester him further, Brother Qin.
Actually, Young Master Qin did not need to go through the trouble of coming here.
What do you mean by that?
Almost a year ago,
all the Xin Fas of martial art sects were stolen.
Although we, the Baxian Residence, paid no attention to mundane affairs,
yet we weren't able to escape.
My older brother's life work
up to now is in the hand of a hawk, taken by little petty thieves.
Inside it, there is a detailed record
of the whole process of making this puppet silver needle.
The selling price is only eight Wen coins.
[Baxian Residence]
Is that the end of it then?
Isn't that Baxian Residence's...
Stop!
[Baxian Residence]
Everyone, let me introduce someone.
Baxian Residence's disciple, Li Yu.
Are you the Healer's disciple?
Why are you at Baxian Residence to serve us tea?
You do not know.
Although Master Bo'er and old Master Bu'er were biological brothers,
their personalities were as different as sky and earth.
Healer was benevolent and magnanimous.
But, in fact, Master Bu'er is a complete penny-pincher.
It's nothing! I was just carelessly venting.
Everyone, I should go back; otherwise, Master Bu'er will probably censure me.
- Take care.
Let's just go with the original plan.
Miss Leng and I will continue to search for clues of the puppets.
Young Chief Master and Miss Feng, you should stay around Baxian Residence,
to observe Master Bu'er some more.
[Loyal Heart on Medical Skills]
Why has the ice silk pearl's glow become weaker?
I have not taken it under the moonlight for a long time.
That's also good.
Good?
If Xiao Chun Hua is too good to the ice silk pearl,
I will be jealous.
How can you be jealous of a pearl?
Xiao Chun Hua, open your hand.
No matter what you say or do,
I will treat you well forever.
How will you prove that to me?
Look me in the eyes!
This is the man I
first laid eyes on ever.
My true love!
However, the system never said
that my true love and I
would have a happy ending.
What's wrong?
I am a little worried.
Worried about what?
Nothing much!
Let's play a game called Truth or Dare.
Truth or dare?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫