''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Why did you make such vicious remarks to slander my late father and all the Chiefs here?
So what exactly is your relationship with Chief Xiao?
Xiao Chun Hua, just watch the show unfold and you’ll find out.
My father was open and honest his entire life
so how could he have a love affair with a Demon Sect temptress?
This Xiao Bai cultivates the Fengming Saber,
and still needs to rely on the "Enchantress of Qianyue Cave."
Has Xiao Bai's Fengming Saber made a sound for you?
If I were to be in these circumstances, we have to depend on each other, surviving and dying together.
[Episode 14]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Xiao Bai, as human everyone...
has to go through birth, aging, sickness, and death.
Everyone
must taste sadness, joy, division, and reconciliation.
has to face many difficult choices or giving up.
Young Master Xiao—
My father has been extremely strict with me since I was young,
practicing the art of Fengming Saber every single day,
continuously non-stop.
Father wanted me to be a righteous gentleman,
able to discern between right and wrong.
Father was busy with pugilist matters.
He was distant but polite to Mother, respecting her like a guest.
Who would ever think that
Father had loved another person so much?
And it was even more unbelievable
that he would have such entanglements
with a woman from the Demon Sect.
Father was always my role model in my heart.
Although Li Jian Ling's words were extreme in nature, Father's dignity in his whole life
was actually built on the disappointment of a female demon.
It was even from betrayal and taking advantage of.
Xiao Bai,
there is no right or wrong in love.
Master Xiao might have disappointed Shangguan Hui
but he has lived up to his reputation of a great warrior.
Your father is still a hero.
I was just comforting you.
I have been comforted already.
Then...
why don't I perform a magic trick for you?
You see, over there!
Look at that brightest star.
Do you see it?
Then why don't I retrieve it and give it to you?
The stars are unreachable
so don't tell jokes.
What are you doing?
Reaching for the stars.
Look!
I think,
Master Xiao might have caused Shangguan Hui grief,
but he didn't disappoint the pugilist world.
His life had been morally upright and blessed.
We can only hope that our generation
won't be stuck between a rock and a hard place.
Just like a pawn,
we also should not forget to persist in love's intentions
and don't get caught up in confusion.
Wasn't that spectacular?
Yes.
Thank you.
We also don't know which choice Young Master will take.
Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Shangguan Hui.
They are both lonely people.
Older Brother. Older Brother!
I also want a pawn.
Older Brother.
Master.
Have you ever seen a lady who has the surname Shangguan?
No, I haven't.
Of course, you haven't seen her before.
Before, I had thought I understood her so well.
But only now, I have realized that
I truly did not know her at all.
Master, are you thinking of a former family member of your?
Passionate feelings court disaster.
Naivety is on the verge of stupidity.
Who is that similar to?
Tell me, who do you think is like that?
I dare not answer.
It's not that you dare not but you simply don't know.
If only you were like Xiao Chun Hua, it would be so good.
She dares say and do whatever she wants.
Just like the girl whom Li Jian Ling described today.
It's exactly because they are so similar,
they both gave their passionate feelings to the wrong persons.
Ye Yan, you haven't seen her before
because she had met a terrible fate.
My condolences, Master.
Condolences?
I merely do not wish to see my younger sister
to follow in her footsteps.
Silly Little Sister,
you gave him a chess piece,
and watched the stars with him.
In reality, the space you take up in his heart
is no more important than the Fengming Saber itself.
Do all sisters of the Demon Sect
have this kind of endings?
Brother certainly won't let that happen.
Have you heard any news about the Longevity fruit?
Gorge Master, we still haven't made any progress.
You good-for-nothings!
My deepest apologies.
Since Xiao Yuan died, everyone has been ready to make trouble.
Perhaps the Longevity Fruit will appear as a result.
I will go to investigate again and certainly won't let you down.
That year,
Master Nan Xinghe made a solemn promise
regarding the Chuanqi Sect and the Qianyue Cave.
Whoever killed the leader of the martial arts circle
would become the unified leader of Xingyue School.
It's a pity that I've been anxious and in a desperate hurry for the Longevity fruit.
So that Xiao Yuan, an irrelevant person, could steal that opportunity from me first.
Do you really think a living person will
keep a dead man's solemn promise?
Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Every time I see you, Gorge Master Fu, I feel restless.
I just feel funny for no reason.
At the moment, Xiao Bai still doesn't have a strong foothold.
This is precisely the right time for Chuanqi Sect and Qianyue Sect to unite.
If we work together, we can take advantage of this weakness to sneak in and
take down all people of the Righteous Path in one swoop.
Your great plans of domination are just around the corner.
How can the trivial Longevity fruit be even worth?
I'm carefree and have no interest in the Longevity fruit at all.
However, you drag around a chronic invalid with you.
If it continues like this, I'm afraid you'll need to ask a celestial being or become a Buddhist taoist.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, do you think you're worthy to mention Sisi?
It's all but just a Longevity fruit.
Despite your best efforts, you still haven't found it.
I think that's far more interesting than the Longevity fruit itself.
Don't push your luck!
However, you amuse me and make me laugh every time.
I, Shangguan Qiu Yue, should recognize your kindness to give you something in return.
I present to you, Gorge Master Fu, the latest news about the Longevity fruit.
Let's leave!
[Chuanqi Gorge]
Sisi.
Husband.
Isn't my complexion especially nice today?
Yes, you look so wonderful.
You will get better and better each day.
I might have found a way to cure your illness.
[Wind Listening Pavilion]
[Grieving]
Everyone, take a look at this!
"On the 15th day of this month, at noon,
in the ancient tea alley of Bishui City, the Longevity fruit
will be auctioned to all who wish."
- The Longevity fruit?
Yes, rumor has it that
this Longevity fruit auction will be extensive.
The price to enter will be one million liang.
The seller will be Master Shi himself.
Master Shi again!
This Master Shi sold the Xin Fa last time.
This time, he's selling the Longevity fruit.
Although very little is known about him, the things he sells
are all coveted by the entire martial arts circle.
Nowadays, every Xin Fa is already incredibly precious.
The Longevity fruit is even more rare.
The Qianyue and Chuanqi Sects surely won't stand by idly.
They will likely assert themselves into this situation.
You all are too naive!
It's not just members of the Demon Sects,
do you think your upright, well-known families won't want the Longevity fruit?
Don't forget! When Master Xiao was severely ill,
- Fengming Mountain Manor—
- Miss Chun Hua.
My father has always laughed off the Longevity fruit.
In addition, he warned me not to strive for fame and wealth, but be more of a calm, positive person.
Exactly! The Feng family also advocates adherence to true, right principles.
They certainly won't get involved in such an illicit affair.
Miss Chun Hua is right.
Early this morning, families from each sect came to bid me farewell.
I even thought they had an important matter
and didn't think that it was related to the Longevity fruit.
Bishui City will surely be welcoming a rain of terror this time.
In my opinion, this is certainly a trap.
Now, who know? Master Shi is probably profiting from others' conflict.
Indeed! This could be a trap.
We must be extremely careful.
This Master Shi! He surely knows that even if this is a trap,
the Fengming Mountain Manor clearly can't remain indifferent.
"He has staked himself on the edge of his sword.
How can he treasure his own life?"
In his lifetime, my father thought the same.
Chief Xiao.
Young Master, did you receive the notice about the Longevity fruit auction?
Indeed! Chief Leng, what's your opinion?
After this information gets out, Bishui City will become chaos.
As of now, Master Xiao still hasn't been laid to rest.
Of course, Young Master, you should focus more on family matters.
I can go to Bishui City first, on your behalf,
and take some men with me to prevent civil strife.
I don't know what you think of this idea, Young Master.
Thank you for your trouble, Chief Leng.
After I bury my father, I will join you there as quickly as humanly possible.
Father, if you can help the Young Master, naturally, it couldn't be any better.
Then I'll be going now.
[Wind Listening Pavilion]
[Grieving]
Xiao Bai!
Miss Chun Hua,
it's so late but you still haven't gone to bed.
I see that you take great pains to keep night watch
and now, it's also added the Longevity fruit matter.
I'm worried about you.
Father said,
"Martial arts cultivation is like rowing upstream.
Stop moving forward, then one will fall back."
I say
that emotions are like this as well.
Father said, "If one cherishes the people under Heaven,
he will be able to bring peace to the world.
Otherwise, one's words would be empty."
I say,
if you cannot even hold one girl in your heart,
then what can be said for the whole world?
- Miss Chun Hua—
- Xiao Bai,
I also have many, many great principles.
If you carefully listen to my words,
you could also recite them in this way.
However, if you don't listen closely,
that's also fine.
At the very least, when you think of me, I'll still be that lively, vivacious Chun Hua.
Miss Chun Hua, if there's something you want to say, just say it!
I will earnestly remember everything.
Good!
Then I'll say it.
Master Xiao, the son you raised
has a loyal heart, and is supremely honorable and righteous.
He's also very cute.
However, I want to say,
to set an example of benevolent righteousness to the world,
one must love and know others.
Yes.
Chun Hua says,
"To set an example of benevolent righteousness to the world,
one must love and know others."
Thus,
do I have a point?
Then give me a high five!
Xiao Bai, in future, don't repeat what your father said all the time.
You should think more about what I said. Okay?
Young Master, do you really want to take Miss Chun Hua with you?
Miss Chun Hua doesn't know any martial arts at all.
If we run into any trouble, wouldn't she hinder everyone and endanger our important plans?
That's exacty why I want to take her. With Miss Chun Hua by my side, she will be much safer.
Young Master, you are still the one who is so considerate.
Caicai, love is a battlefield.
This opportunity is fleeting and will disappear quickly.
Miss Leng, you think so much for me, I'm deeply grateful.
If you are, then do something about it.
You two need not worry.
With me and Young Master present,
what can happen to Miss Chun Hua?
Miss Chun Hua is Young Master’s fiancee.
What does she have to do with you?
Miss Leng, what I mean is...
- What I mean—
- If Young Master wants to bring Miss Chun Hua along,
I think it’s best you ask her if she’s willing.
I’ll go! I’ll go, I'll go.
I must go together with Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai, do you think I'm right?
Why do I feel that Young Master’s demeanor today is a little different than normal?
Before, when Brother Xiao encountered a girl, I would be the one
responsible for lowering the temperature of his ears.
To think that a pure person like Brother Xiao,
can still remains composed even with a beautiful lady in his embrace...
I wonder when I will have a gentle and warm lady
in my embrace.
Leng Ning.
Xiao Bai, did I just overreact?
I'm sorry! It's just that I'm really so happy.
You've done something more extreme before.
How is that possible?
After all, I'm educated and reasonable.
Do you remember the first time we met?
You even called me, Husband.
This is the wooden-headed Xiao Bai.
Taciturn (reserved).
A modest gentleman.
Refined.
That's right! This is the Xiao Bai I know.
Husband?
How... how long ago was it?
I already forgot that I did this.
Might as well! When you called me that again,
I feel as if it was a lifetime ago.
Who made you always so unenthusiastic?
Then I don't want to court a rebuff.
Feelings are like rowing upstream,
advance or be left behind.
Just like my stupid ship!
Before, I only knew how to work hard on the water's surface.
I didn't expect to be able to go forward on other lakes.
I don't want to be a lake.
What I want to be... is a big sea,
a tsunami that can engulf you.
Miss Leng, Miss Leng.
I asked the Xiyu Embroidery Lady to meticulously sew this sachet.
It has rose fragrance, orchid, and borneol (tree powder).
It was even sewn with pure gold thread, you will definitely love it.
I'm afraid there is no gold and jade among them.
If you don't like it, there are still more.
Miss Leng, Young Master Qin treats you
with deep affection.
I don't know how many deceived playboys used this cheap trick.
I'm tired of it.
Young Master Qin is more nonconformist on the surface.
He is still different from those other ones.
This time, the late Master Xiao
and Shangguan's affairs
make me feel obtuse (slow to understand).
What would you do if it were you?
I think everyone's fate is different.
My choice would be the same as Master Xiao's.
I would rather save the common people than choose a personal relationship.
I've probably been like this my whole life.
But Miss Leng has a fine nature and clever mind.
There will be a beautiful marriage for you.
I think no one can compare to you, Miss Feng.
Miss Leng mocked me again.
If I were so wonderful,
how would I be caught between you and Young Master Qin,
let alone Miss Chun Hua and Young Master?
Certainly not! It's just that Xiao Bai doesn't know how to treasure you.
You have done well enough.
If it were me,
I don't know how to leave with my dignity intact.
You! No peeking.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫