''A Girl With A Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
What if you have to sacrifice me in exchange for the peace you wish to obtain?
What will you choose?
I will not let that happen.
According to the rules, the Longevity fruit belongs to Gorge Master Fu.
I just hope that you can protect Sisi.
In a major incident involving the Book of One's Crimes,
how can you not invite me from Qianyue Sect?
Fu Lou, you have to follow through with your promises.
There is nothing I cannot reveal in the Book of One's Crimes.
Why is my father not on this list?
As for the person who killed Feng Qianwei, I know who it is.
[Episode 26]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Husband!
Husband.
Husband...
Xiao Bai,
Xiao Bai, I am begging you. I beg you to please let him go, won't you?
However, he has killed so many people.
On the contrary, he didn't want to kill them.
That day at the doctor's home,
he is the one who saved me.
He is now already an arrow at the end of its flight.
Even if today, by luck, he can escape,
he may still be unable to return to Chuanqi Gorge.
- Xiao Bai... you—
- He's not wrong!
I am the one who's in the wrong.
- Why don't you all just kill me first?
- Wishing to die is still not easy.
Back then the noble warrior Yuan was murdered.
If you aren't afraid to follow him, I won't take responsibility.
Take it easy! I came only to attend the celebration.
Xiao Chun Hua, Fu Lou has a mortal heart.
Even better, two monsters came so that I can catch both in a dragnet.
I knew you had an affair with this demon.
How can Young Chief Master be misled by you?
I already told you that I won't intervene but just be here to observe.
And what right do you have to quarrel with me?
Master Leng, there are so many people here.
Please behave yourself.
Xiao Chun Hua, since they all think this way,
then why don't...
- Will you just recklessly annoy even more?
- Okay.
I will not lift a finger or intervene.
Husband!
Sisi,
wait till the full moon...
Husband.
Husband!
My husband!
- Fu Lou is dead.
- Fu Lou has died.
- My husband!
- He just died like that?
We should cut him into pieces.
Yes! He deserved to die.
It should have happened earlier.
That's not even enough.
Are you all human?
He is already dead and you still won't even want to release his body?
Chun Hua, how can you say that?
If it was not for Lady Sisi,
do you think you can really kill him?
Fu Lou committed the crime of killing a teacher.
This woman not only didn't avenge her first husband,
but she even developed relations with a horrible person.
She should be hacked to pieces!
The person who should die is not him.
It's Yuan Zhihai.
It is Yuan Zhihai who was vicious and merciless.
He forced the two of us down this path.
All the scars on my body
were caused by Yuan Zhihai who beat me.
Look at them carefully!
All of you...
All of these were Yuan Zhihai's doing.
Scars like this
are all over my body.
Do you want me to take off all my clothes for you to look at them?
Yuan Zhihai
forced me to marry him after his first wife's death.
Fu Lou and I were originally childhood sweethearts.
He framed Fu Lou.
He made Fu Lou leave the mountain.
I was afraid something would happen to Fu Lou,
so I accepted his deal.
However, Yuan Zhihai was very narrow-minded.
He constantly thought Fu Lou and I were having affairs.
He frequently hit me and tormented me.
He also made me take medicine for abortion.
Even the three children I had with him
were also aborted.
What a joke!
How could you prove that those injuries were caused by Chief Yuan?
Maybe it's the result of Fu Lou abusing you.
Fu Lou?
If it was not for me,
how could he be in the state that he is in now?
Yuan Zhihai disfigured his face and forced him to drink poison.
I grabbed it from him,
and that's why my body is sickly and disabled now.
So do you think
that Yuan Zhihai shouldn't have died?
Chief Qin,
all these events,
you should well know it all.
Ten years ago, I did indeed pay a visit to Chief Yuan.
Chief Yuan snatched you from Fu Lou, that's true.
However, Fu Lou did murder his teacher. That's also true.
Within our martial arts circle,
people regard murdering one's teacher as the worst offense.
As an outsider, it was inappropriate for me to meddle in Chief Yuan's family affairs.
So are you all the ones who uphold justice?
Fu Lou is sorry to you all,
but he always treated me right.
Do you want to cut his body into 1000 pieces? Fine!
When you cut his body in 1000 pieces,
then let me join him.
Chief Qin, you obviously knew the inside information.
However, in spite of all, you didn't lend a helping hand.
As for the rest of you,
you confuse what is right and wrong, and constantly fight.
This is simply the most ridiculous thing ever!
Everyone, to act ruthlessly sparing no one is not proper for the Righteous Path.
A innocent lady like her, who did nothing wrong in her life,
if she was truly abused by Chief Yuan,
then it's not too late for her to turn over a new leaf now.
I promised Fu Lou that after he dies,
I will let his wife go.
Chief Xiao, you really have the nerve to say that.
If you didn't hand over the Longevity fruit to the Demon Sects,
how could we have lost so many brothers?
- Yes!
- Yes! Yes!
- Yes! They all died because of him!
So, are you all still heartbroken over the Longevity fruit?
Let me tell all of you!
The Longevity fruit is fake.
- Fake?
- Is it fake?
- Chief Xiao, is what she says true?
So was the large meeting convened for the Longevity fruit
all just a fake?
Xiao Chun Hua is truly straightforward and outspoken.
You are so lovable.
Miss Chun Hua is tired these days and suffered shocking events.
That's why she is speaking nonsense.
Xiao Bai,
Fu Lou is already dead.
- You should tell the truth to Madam Yousi now.
- Chun Hua!
How can you destroy my reputation and Fengming Mountain Manor's with everyone watching?
What about me?
How much do I mean to you?
I am no match for your Righteous Path martial arts.
I am no match for your persistent desire to root out the Demon Sects.
Can't I even measure up to a fake Longevity fruit?
I am just a
- chess piece you sacrifice anytime for the sake of righteousness!
- Shut up!
If everyone is uneasy,
I can take Madam Yousi back to Fengming Mountain Manor.
We can deal with this at later time.
Wait!
My husband is already dead.
Whether the Longevity fruit is fake or not,
it does not matter anymore.
Longevity fruit...
Open it!
Aren't you all curious?
Since she does't care anymore, I'll honor her wishes and destroy it.
Did you really destroy it?
Hypocrites!
My husband.
You must be so tired.
We will never be apart again.
My husband.
Let me accompany you.
Madam.
Xiao Bai, you apologize.
- Miss Chun Hua.
- You apologize!
The energy between these two opposing forces cannot coexist.
In regards to this matter, I was not unfair to them.
Fu Lou has only himself to blame.
In the case of Lady Yousi,
I... there was also nothing I could do.
Then kill me.
- What nonsense are you saying? How can I kill you?
- I had a love affair with Shangguan Qiu Yue.
You heard about it clearly on the day of the wedding.
I colluded with the great Devil of Qianyue Cave.
I myself am
an enchantress, naturally.
If you kill me, then you'll get rid of an evil for the Righteous Path.
Isn't that better?
Miss Chun Hua, the Young Chief Master has never doubted you.
- Please don't—
- This is none of your business.
This involves the important matter of the Righteous Path and martial arts circle's peace.
Chun Hua, you are my wife.
We can write off the past events with one stroke.
So is this you "never suspecting me?"
Since you already firmly believe the events of the past,
as long as you're the Young Chief Master,
you should place righteousness above loyalty to one's family.
Set an example!
Righteous Path places the righteousness above the loyalty to one's family, but Demon Sects do not.
Xiao Chun Hua, I was right.
These people are all hypocrites.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, it is you who is stirring up trouble.
You wreaked havoc at my wedding and kidnapped my wife.
You've even tried to confuse her.
You've made it so she can't tell right from wrong.
Is what he is saying, true?
Yes.
But what does it matter?
Brother Qiu Yue.
I have been misled by you.
Can you take me back to Qianyue Cave?
Wait!
Since you are taking her away,
then take this thing that belongs to Qianyue Cave.
If you won't let her go, take it with you.
- Young Chief Master!
Thank you so much, Young Chief Master, for returning this to its rightful owner.
They are all gone.
Xiao Bai?
Fu Lou did save Miss Chun Hua.
Chun Hua really developed a relationship with Madam Yousi.
When she witnessed them both die in front of her,
she naturally could not handle it.
Brother Qin, you were right.
Miss Chun Hua doesn't have the quality to be a Chief's wife.
Since childhood, my father told me that possessing utmost wisdom surely brings hurt, and
that deep love comes with a short lifespan.
My father taught me that one must restrain yourself and observe propriety,
don't make a fool of yourself, remain quiet,
and make the righteousness of the martial arts circle one's duty.
One's duty cannot be love affairs.
Therefore,
before I met Miss Chun Hua,
I saw the people of the martial arts circle as brothers.
There is no difference between men and women.
In life,
there are only responsibilities and not love.
After my father assumed the role of martial arts circle Chief,
he looked after their matters day and night.
My mother was the daughter of a well-known, respected family,
but she was so unhappy her entire life.
When I was ten, she passed away.
I always thought
Miss Chun Hua
was cute and lively,
warm-hearted, brave,
and naturally kind.
She loves to play coy and be jealous.
She's selfish, afraid of death, and hates to part with delicious food.
I colluded with the great Devil of Qianyue Cave.
I myself am
an enchantress, naturally.
If you kill me, then you'll get rid of an evil for the Righteous Path.
Isn't that better?
She truly is not suitable to become a Chief's wife.
She is really not suited for it.
She does not know martial arts.
She is naive and impulsive.
If she isn't taken away by Qianyue Sect, then she is taken by Chuanqi Sect.
She is really unsuited for this.
She is truly unsuited.
I am very sad.
No one thought it would come to this.
Do not be sad any longer.
Fu Lou never thought he would become a villain.
However, he was forced to be one.
He and Yousi,
I never thought about
how we targeted him.
Did we really do wrong?
None of us wanted Fu Lou to die.
The Chuanqi Sect was able to keep Qianyue Sect in check.
The Longevity fruit is something fabricated to exist in this world.
If we don't get rid of it, then the entire martial arts circle will become unstable.
I suddenly remembered the poem that you wrote at the poem meeting.
"The martial arts world is in rain and darkness for ten years before seeing the light."
In this martial arts world,
small warmth would have been better.
I want to be together with you, Miss Leng,
and be a couple of free, unfettered heroes in this world.
[Thousand Moon Pavilion]
Where am I?
What was I going to do?
What do I want?
I am suffering so much.
Xiao Chun Hua,
you have suffered.
Master.
- The excellent disciples of the Chuanqi Sect are all here.
- Yes.
Gu Wan's actions are quite swift.
It's just that the number of people
- is a bit small.
- Most of Fu Lou's former people comply with his final order to seek refuge with Qianyue Cave.
However, some still can't agree to submit allegiance
because we don't have the Chuanqi Sect's command seal.
It came to a deadlock so Gu Wan finished off the diehard supporters.
We took over the Chuanqi Gorge smoothly and easily.
Gu Wan has been with Qianyue Cave for many years,
so his skills and tricks are becoming more seasoned.
Master, will you personally appear to console the remnant of defeated troops?
No need!
We should make them tremble with fear for a few days.
We will trust luck and wait for any windfall.
Then I will go and notify Gu Wan.
You should watch out and be careful of Gu Wan.
I will obey your command.
[Wind Listening Pavilion]
I never saw him use this kind of force and imposing manner before,
but now I have the opportunity.
This force and energy is a bit too aggressive.
My father used to say in genuine, traditional Kung Fu, strive to perform it with great ease.
But now...
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely ♫
♫  As it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever. It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time. The loneliness that I’m fated to have  ♫
♫  Is difficult to put into words. How I wish that you could see it  ♫
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed. Yet this insatiable longing   ♫,
♫  Seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I've left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫