''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
The more that someone likes to distinguish between good and evil, the more careful you need to be.
His heart may have a layer of dust.
There's a poison called 'Dandelion'.
Do you have the antidote? It would be better for me to use this drug to
get Shangguan Qiu Yue drunk, and take advantage of the opportunity to coax it out of him.
However, there wasn't any 'Three Day Drunk' in that vial.
I exchanged it with an aphrodisiac.
- I meant to take the arsenic!
- Little Sister, do you really hate me so much?
I must get the antidote for the 'Dandelion' poison.
People at Fengming Mountain Manor poisoned me.
Fine! I'll give you the antidote.
[Episode 19]
It's because I must get the antidote for the 'Dandelion' poison.
For Xiao Bai?
For myself.
People at Fengming Mountain Manor poisoned me.
- I must—
- It's fine.
I'll give you the antidote.
It's the Xiao family's secret poison.
If someone is flirtatious with me,
not only will the poison's toxicity break out, but it will also infect others.
Really? I don't believe that.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Keep this in mind!
I'm the only one who can be flirtatious with you.
Actually, that 'Three Day Drunk' vial was filled with 'Three Day Drunk'. Of course, it's the 'Three Day Drunk'.
Then what is 'Three Day Drunk'?
It simply makes the wine taste better, nothing more.
Fengming Mountain Manor poisoned you, as your brother,
how can I sit still and do nothing to save you?
Take it!
[Qianyue Cave]
Xiao Chun Hua, you were right.
I should change my way of life.
And find a girl that you adore.
What would it be like if I experienced that?
What do you mean?
Of course, you'll be happy,
excited, and you'll have butterflies in your stomach.
You'll have your blood run fast. You'll—
Anyhow,
Anyh...
it'll be very beautiful and joyful.
Is that so?
Is that what you think?
You should leave.
But in that kind of life,
will I have Xiao Chun Hua?
She's still breathing.
Stop!
Miss Chun Hua, what are you doing?
- Young Master!
Miss Chun Hua, is this really the antidote?
Do you also not trust me?
Even Dr. Bu can't do anything, and you're going to save Cai Cai?
Are you sure you don't harm her?
Miss Leng, I trust Miss Chun Hua.
Miss Chun Hua, you should quickly give Miss Feng the antidote.
Miss Leng, I greatly offended you just now,
please forgive me.
I trust Miss Chun Hua.
You trust Miss Chun Hua because she's your fiancée.
However, no one knows where this antidote came from so how can you ask me to trust
the person who is giving the antidote, sincerely wants to save her?
It's not that I don't trust you, it's just that you are so confident about where this medicine came from.
True! Why did I trust that Devil so much?
Cai Cai?
Cai Cai is awake!
That's great!
That's great...
I'll go and look for the physician to see if there is residual poison.
I'll accompany you.
Master, what orders do you have?
Give the antidote for the 'Dandelion' poison to Master Shi.
Tell him to distribute it to the various pharmacies.
Yes!
Hold on!
Remember to tell those shop owners
how this antidote came about.
Xiao Bai, thank you for trusting me.
Actually...
Just now, I did not entirely trust you.
I just trust that you would not harm Miss Feng.
As for the medicine, Miss Chun Hua, where did this medicine come from?
If I say that I bought it from outside, would you believe me?
I found the antidote!
I found the antidote. Quickly look at it and see if there are any problems.
Where did you get this medicine from?
I bought it at the pharmacy.
Why are the two of you still standing here?
Hurry and give it to Physician Bu.
Here!
Is it hot?
Young Master.
It is good that this medicine is effective.
Miss Feng, you have suffered.
Regarding Leader Feng's death and your poisoning,
these two situations,
I will surely investigate the truth for you.
So for now you should stay in Fengming Mountain Manor to recover.
This time, we must really thank Miss Chun Hua.
Yes.
For this situation,
I am truly grateful to everyone, especially Miss Chun Hua.
She is just a weak girl with no knowledge of martial arts,
yet she ran around outside to help me find the antidote.
Actually,
this antidote was bought on the streets by Miss Chun Hua.
Bought?
Are you saying that all the pharmacies
are currently selling the antidote for 'Dandelion' poison?
I interrogated the pharmacy owner.
He said that the origin of this antidote is unclear. Just that...
Just that what?
The owner said that although its origins are unclear,
it is rumored that the antidote is made using the leaves of the Longevity fruit.
It seems that it must also be related to Master Shi.
Even the leaves are so miraculous.
Could this Longevity fruit really grant immortality?
Miss Chun Hua.
Miss Chun Hua?
I never thought that all the alleys and streets of this city would be selling the antidote.
Using the leaves to make the antidote...
Being sold in all the streets and alleys?
Yet there is no news of the fruit itself?
How can this be?
Master, please forgive me. I have already done my best to search for it.
It is truly...
Useless!
Shangguan Qiu Yue?
How could I dream about marrying Shangguan Qiu Yue?
The one I love is Xiao Bai.
Right!
The first person I saw is Xiao Bai.
So the one I love is him.
Maybe there has just been too much happening recently.
There's also the matter of me being muddled when stealing the medicine from Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Maybe once I marry Xiao Bai, everything will be all right.
Right!
Miss Feng has been getting better day by day.
Once she is fully recovered, why don't we all head to Mount Ling to play?
Play what?
Right now Xiao Bai has important things to settle, how can he have the time to play?
Then why don't you say,
what is the situation that is making our adorable Xiao Bai the most frustrated?
Wait!
Looking at the chemistry of the two of you, you should say it together.
Then so be it!
- The marriage process.
- Longevity fruit.
My meaning is...
carrying out the wedding is not as important as looking for the Longevity fruit.
Right?
However, as of now, the Longevity fruit's location is unknown.
At this moment, we still don't know how to investigate it.
For every day we cannot find the Longevity fruit,
the martial arts world will continue to have this demon in their hearts.
Miss Chun Hua, what do you think?
Whether it is a heart demon, I do not know.
However, I know that everyone is interested in this Longevity fruit.
Everyone is being led by the nose.
Yet everyone wants it but cannot get it.
Every time news about the Longevity fruit is leaked, there will always be someone who dies.
For such a thing to continue existing in the world,
there will definitely be even bigger repercussions.
Once we get rid of the Longevity fruit,
then there will no longer be any trouble in the future.
Wait! We don't even know what the Longevity fruit looks like.
How can we even talk about eliminating it?
Are you a fool?
To look for something that no one has seen before,
just display a fake Longevity fruit, then wouldn't it all be over?
Miss Chun Hua,
it is easy to draw a dragon while looking at a cat, but difficult to draw a dragon based on nothing.
Where did you get the confidence
to look for something we have never seen before?
Young Master Qin,
you look down on me too much.
[Treasured Delicacies]
Look! What is this?
- Fried chicken!
- Fried chichen!
You may not know what this is, do you?
- Sushi!
I can guarantee that
you definitely do not know what this is!
- This is called—
- Shui Mantou!
(steamed bun or steamed bread with water)
This scene created by the system is too advanced!
Miss Chun Hua, as a matter of fact, you are quite amazing.
After all, we've only seen this on the maps and records of the coastal country.
We have never seen it in person.
You even read that book?
What are you all doing?
Miss Feng, Miss Leng, you are here. Please sit!
- What are you all doing?
- Miss Leng, this is the new fried chicken that Miss Chun Hua has come up with.
It's delicious! You should give it a try.
You're quite the expert at eating, drinking and idling away your time.
I think the Longevity fruit is a harmful object to others, so we must destroy it.
Moreover, we all haven't seen the Longevity fruit, and we still have no idea what on earth it looks like.
So that's why Miss Chun Hua made this.
Miss Chun Hua is very thoughtful.
Miss Chun Hua is indeed learned and versatile.
However, you must also consider the reality.
The Longevity fruit has wandered around the world for many years.
This is something that should be easily preserved.
What Miss Chun Hua made...
is very delicious.
Easily preserved?
Easily preserved...
That's it!
Is this the Longevity fruit?
The walnut does indeed nourish the mind and is beneficial to one's intellectual power.
It's just that this Longevity fruit...
A game of smoke and mirrors?
It looks like it!
Don't move!
Miss Chun Hua!
Miss Chun Hua.
Although I haven't had the glory of being the leading role these past few days,
it's simple and nice that they could end up liking me this way.
I am not bad!
- I am sorry!
- Chun Hua, are you okay?
That was my fault.
It's not your fault at all!
If I bump into Xiao Bai, I should be so happy.
Chun Hua.
[Prospering Humanities]
Such a fine treasure
I can't find a good place to hide it.
What?
Marriage?
Where is the ring?
Are you stupid? This!
I...
Fortunately Xiao Bai is so naive. Otherwise, he wouldn't have fallen into my hands.
The last time you mentioned the matter of marriage, I was indeed slow-witted.
I didn't promptly give you an answer.
I've thought it over and over again.
Hence, I've decided to make up for it by giving you a large wedding.
Miss Chun Hua!
Qin Liufeng, you came just the right time.
What is it?
We are
getting married!
Young Master, we have been intimate and so close for 20 years.
I can't believe you chose someone else.
Let go of my hand!
Miss Chun Hua!
Miss Chun Hua, I was uneasy and fidgety before.
Weren't you burning with jealousy, just now?
Come!
Take this!
I've decided to give this to you after much thought and consideration.
There are many eyes and ears around the Young Master and me.
Miss Leng has an innocent state of mind and Miss Feng is just beginning to recover from her illness.
Besides, you're about to get married to the Young Master soon.
If I give this to you, how else will I have to be worried about?
Young Master,
congratulations!
Great news!
Pretty!
Great news! Xiao Bai is getting married!
Are you drawing on my eyebrows or disfiguring me?
My little husband, I want to file for divorce and have you leave.
Don't worry!
I've let go the matter of the heart a long time ago.
Yes, Xiao Bai is not that great.
Cai Cai, I will always protect you.
I will protect you until the day you have a nice home to return to.
Miss Leng, you're so conscientious and good to me.
Don't forget!
I'm your little husband!
Chief!
[Tianxiong Sect]
[Invitation]
Chief, an invitation sent by Fengming Mountain Manor.
[Banquet at Fengming Mountain Manor
Time: Early Afternoon]
[Xiao Bai, Chun Hua.
You are cordially invited by Xiao Bai.]
Chief, an invitation sent by Fengming Mountain Manor.
[Invitation to Banquet at Fengming Mountain Manor]
Wonderful! You'll be married in ten days.
I must congratulate you, Young Master.
Thank you so much, Chief Leng.
I have no son.
I've watched you grow up.
You're like my half-son.
Recently, I have had many matters to tend to.
I completely forgot to bring a few gifts.
The world has been chaotic because of the matter of the Longevity fruit.
I'm sorry for your trouble, Chief Leng.
Young Master, you're at ease and getting married now.
Is it because you have news about the Longevity fruit?
Today, Chief Leng inadvertently mentioned the Longevity fruit.
Which reminded me,
I must destroy it in the presence of all. I still need to find a good excuse to
gather the chiefs of all the sects together.
Just tell them that we have the Longevity fruit, then it'll be all done,  won't it?
Idiot! Wouldn't that be acting rashly and alerting the enemy?
At the moment,
we have a good opportunity.
Marriage.
Ye Xingzhu!
Do you know what I found today?
I'm not your master, you also don't need to report everything to me.
If you report to the Master.
I don't know if my fate will be dead or alive.
Feelings. They may seem simple but hold deep meanings.
Ye Yan, you are more ruthless than the Master.
You don't need to walk in circles to say something, I will report to the Master.
Xiao Chun Hua?
Sister...
Master!
Why is it you?
Master, please forgive my mistake.
What is your mistake?
Go.
The subordinate has something to report.
In ten days, Fengming Manor will hold...
Xiao Bai and Chun Hua's wedding ceremony.
[Chuanqi Gorge]
Subordinate intercepted an invitation.
[Invitation to Banquet at Fengming Mountain Manor]
Xiao Bai's wedding?
Is it with Miss Chun Hua?
Yes.
I like Miss Chun Hua very much.
Young Master is an excellent
place to return to.
It's a pity that I am in Chuanqi Gorge
and can't send presents in person.
Although I am in Chuanqi Gorge,
I don't regret even one day.
Sisi, since you want to congratulate,
then I will send someone to send the gift.
Husband, you are so kind! It's good to be by your side.
You are a gift from heaven to me.
I don't want to make a much extravagant request.
You...
Can you stop looking for the Longevity fruit?
Sisi, you deserve longer
and better days.
But you run around for the Longevity fruit.
How can I have a good life like this?
Husband,
I want you to promise me.
Let's spend this life together,
continuing to live.
These are the good days I want.
I promise you.
Like drunk?
[Hehuan Medicine]
(The Chinese characters can also mean a couple being together happily)
[Three day drunk]
Aphrodisiac.
Silly sister.
Good sister.
Without my consent,
you actually dare to get married?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫