''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique, secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
This girl does not know any martial arts.
Her background and origin are all suspicious.
What does Xiao Bai actually like?
I would assume you're not interested in what he likes but whom he likes.
Miss Chun Hua revived because she ate the longevity fruit but she completely lost her memory.
Based on my observation, she isn't someone tactful.
Miss is our Fengming Mountain Manor's precious guest. I strive to protect you.
As long as you are here with me, Chun Hua won't be afraid.
[Episode 4]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
[The white, delicate skin has a spot of red.]
"The white, delicate skin has a spot of red." Such a good poem! Good poem!
I should not have told you about the private bath situation.
You tested her for so long. Did Miss Chun Hua have no reaction to the kite?
Is that why you let her stay in Miss Hua's room?
It's such a pity that it was renovated after the big fire.
I don't know if she can remember it.
You really put a lot of thought into this. However...
Does Brother Qin have a good idea?
Tell me how you will thank me first.
I'll repay your great kindness with heartfelt thanks.
I just want a few jars of aged wine. Don’t be so stingy!
Hurry up and tell me.
First, you think Miss Chun Hua is Miss Hua.
Second, Miss Hua never left her room. No one ever saw her.
You two only met once in childhood.
Third, Miss Chun Hua already lost her memory and your research had no result.
So...
I can't help you.
Calm down! What I mean is...
the Hua  Family can help you, not me.
Why the Hua Family?
We can go ask the Hua Family for her portrait.
Wouldn't it be all clear then?
You can still fly the kite.
Miss Chun Hua.
Are you satisfied with your new place?
I am satisfied, very satisfied.
Older Brother, quickly leave! If he enters—
Don't worry!
He won't break into a girl's room.
What if there's an exception?
Xiao Bai, what are you here for?
Why don't you come in to talk?
I don't need to enter your room.
We should just talk from the outside.
Xiao Bai, do you have something important to say?
I forgot to tell you just then that
the annual poem meeting will be in half a month.
Are you interested in attending?
Then I—
Will you also go?
This year, I host this meeting so I will be there.
Then you should take me there.
My pleasure, I will. Get some rest. I'll leave now.
Xiao Bai, there's something I don't know if I should ask.
Please do.
Why are you so good to me?
You changed my room and even want to take me to the poetry meeting.
You don't need to worry.
You just need to remember that I mean no harm.
Older Brother, do you try to scare me to death?
What's there to fear? I think it's quite fun.
You just have to believe that I mean no harm.
How did you make Xiao Bai trust you so much?
Aren't they just some little tricks?
I did all this to help Older Brother get the Xin Fa.
Oh, right! Older Brother,
how do you imitate others' voices?
You can, too.
Me?
Older Brother, I can't.
You used to know how before.
Unfortunately, I already lost my memory.
Why don't you teach me again?
Come here!
Turn around!
Now, try again.
Just like this...
Miss Chun Hua.
Why are you laughing? Is it funny?
It's fun. Of course, what Older Brother taught is fun.
Are you done playing?
If I don't get the Xin Fa in three days,
I will kill you.
Older Brother wouldn't dare kill me.
I remember now.
Three days later, get the Xin Fa.
I guarantee it.
This Older Brother with sudden mood changes from joy to anger is too dangerous.
Gu Xingzhu, why are you back?
Where's Master? He's not in Thousand Moon Cave.
Master went to look for his little sister.
Little sister?
It’s Hua... his younger sister.
Things underwent huge changes in this world.
Yet he still insists that one person steal the Xin Fa.
I advise you to mind your words.
Xiao Yan, you still draw such a clear line between your personal and work affairs.
We are all Master’s subordinates.
It is much more convenient this way.
This surely is funny.
I previously heard an old rumor.
Master wants Xiao Yan to be as good as dead
because it’s his mother’s dying wish.
It's no wonder he is especially interested
in the Xiao family’s Xin Fa.
It’s time to make the medicine.
[Chuanqi Sect]
My Dear, when I left the gorge yesterday,
I got information of a rare medicine.
Your illness finally has a cure.
There was a rather long holdup that caused you worry.
I will be worried…
Gorge Master, someone from Qianyue Sect is here.
My Dear, wait for my return.
Gorge Master, do you want me to act now?
Why are you suddenly so anxious?
You already attained a leader rank for three years.
After this, you’ll either be murdered by a disciple,
or you must murder Shangguan Qiu Yue to become the Cave Master.
It seems that you only have these two choices.
The Cave Master of Qianyue Sect is the most respected.
Among his nine leaders,
the strongest will emerge victorious.
Plotting a rebellion is not a serious offence.
Losing (a serious "crime") leads to a death penalty.
Back then, you also had murdered your leader.
Being a leader is much more comfortable
than being a disciple, isn’t it?
Shangguan Qiu Yue’s capabilities are fathomless.
Are you worried about this?
I have a plan to help you…
take over Qianyue Sect.
Take action as soon as possible.
Gorge Master Fu, do not look down on me.
Cave Master, I earnestly request a personal meeting.
Come in!
Qianyue Sect has countless Xin Fa in martial arts
but is still unable to perfect the only Su family’s swordsmanship.
Do you know why?
The last move of the Su family’s swordsmanship wasn't passed down.
Recently, I learned this last move was drawn into a painting.
I fortunately obtained this painting so I respectfully offer it to you.
Bring it here for me to see.
You held Qianyue Cave Master position far too long now, didn't you?
It’s time for a new master.
You were intelligent all your life.
In the end, you still fell for my trick.
Men!
Kill him!
Master.
I'm willing to deal with these traitors on your behalf.
Ye Yan, you can’t betray me.
We agreed that whoever kills him will become the next master.
It seems that you aren't injured, but just want to draw the snake out of its hole.
If you had the ability to kill me,
cultivating you would not be in vain.
It’s a pity you only depended on Fu Lou
to boost your own courage.
If you aren’t serving Qianyue Sect,
then you serve Chuanqi Sect.
What’s the point of you living then?
I was momentarily deluded, irrational, and my sin is inexcusable.
Please kill me.
You always mention “dying.”
Am I that scary?
We only have one life, don't we?
This, just let her keep both eyes, please.
Master.
He Xingzhu overestimated himself and attempted to plot against Master.
Have you all seen their fates?
We will always be loyal to Master.
It looks like I’ll have to treat him more kindly in the future.
I’ll act according to your wishes.
Master.
Ye Xingzhu,
tell me, should I or shouldn't I take this?
Presently, you are the best poison master in this world.
If I had wanted to play any tricks, I would have died just now.
That’s a good reply. Where is Leader He?
He lost all his martial arts skill, and seeks death.
We must persuade him otherwise.
We must not let him die.
Yes.
Master, this painting…
A low quality item is unsuitable for me.
As usual, send it over to Mister Shi.
Master, if you only want Fengming Saber Xin Fa,
shall I send a few more people there?
Just from hearing it, one can see that Xiao Yan is already beyond cure.
One foolish girl at Fengming Mountain Manor is enough.
When the time comes, just do as I say.
Stealing the Xin Fa while flying the kite.
Will Xiao Bai be carrying the Xin Fa?
But how do I steal the Xin Fa?
Let me first try it on Qin Liufeng.
So clumsy! Next time be faster and
don't have shaky hands.
I failed again!
I don't know martial arts. Of course, I'm clumsy.
What happened?
Miss Chun Hua seems especially interested in my silver.
Miss Chun Hua, what did you steal Qin Liufeng's money for?
I need to have some money to walk around with.
Also, Qin Liufeng is a playboy.
He's full of tricks. If I don't steal his,
should I steal yours, instead?
This is my first time hearing about stealing in such a dignified manner.
Yes!
Xiao Bai?
Please be forgiving, Brother Qin.
Okay.
Miss Chun Hua steals my things and Xiao Bai apologizes to me.
How interesting!
How is it interesting?
Only this place in Fengming Mountain Manor is sealed tightly.
[Bright Moon and Bright Heart]
The Xin Fa must be there.
Miss Chun Hua.
What's wrong?
I was just taking a walk but twisted my ankle.
[Bright Moon and Bright Heart]
Let's go.
There is nothing here.
Xiao Bai, what is this?
This is set up by my ancestor, Xiao Min.
It’s a long story.
Back then, he wiped out Xingyue Sect.
Countless deaths and injuries made him feel he sinned greatly.
Thus, he set up this memorial tablet
for descendants to make offerings.
Later, my father changed this into a study room.
Here incense is continuously burned.
Actually, upholding justice is a given.
Sacrifice is also unavoidable.
Yes, you're right.
[How can this be endured? Down in Nine Springs (after death) waking in pain.]
This isn't Xin—
Does the writer seem to be in a bad mood?
What is this?
Nothing, it's only my ancestor’s past.
Chun Hua.
What are you looking for?
It's a study room. I was just...
looking for a brush to practice.
What should I write?
You should write what you are good at writing.
What am I good at? Good at everything.
[World]
[The most beautiful man in the world.]
Excellent! How could I be so excellent?
As excellent as my husband.
So compatible!
Fine! I'll change it for you.
[Second]
Xiao Bai.
Will you write a word to describe me?
Xiao Bai, don't leave.
Are you unwilling?
He probably saw how excellent my calligraphy is,
and fears he can't surpass me.
Excellent! It's so excellent, Chun Hua.
Gosh, you wrote so wonderfully.
[Written by Xiao Bai]
Such a nicely put-together phrase,
with such a great artistic conception.
It’s boastful but not lacking in modesty.
But Xiao Bai didn't want it.
Older Brother, why are you here again?
It's a surprise here every day with Xiao Chun Hua.
Brother didn't want to miss it.
I suppose... Older Brother thinks I live among the enemy,
being scared and on edge daily, so you came to see me.
Yes, I'm worried about you.
Did you write this for Xiao Bai?
Why is it the second in the world?
it's because you're the first.
Liar!
I guess Xiao Bai didn't accept it so you took it back, didn't you?
Older Brother knows even this.
Don't waste time saying sweet things.
Be serious in your mission.
I didn't forget. I even looked in the study room today.
But there was nothing in there except for books
and a memorial tablet with no words.
Ancestral hall?
It looks like Xiao Bai treats you rather well.
What does that mean?
Did he tell you the story of the memorial tablet?
He did.
He said it was set up after his ancestor had eliminated the Xingyue Sect,
and felt he committed great sin.
Is Xingyue the Qianyue Sect’s predecessor?
That’s right.
Our blood feud with Fengming Mountain Manor formed hundreds of years ago.
Do you mean blood feud?
Didn't Older Brother say
you just wanted to learn Xin Fa so you wanted me to steal it?
Doesn’t Xiao Chun Hua also want to learn the Fengming Saber Technique?
How do you know that, too?
But I just want to learn it to chop firewood.
My little sister is so smart and learns how to imitate voices very quickly.
Fengming Saber Technique is nothing.
When you get the Xin Fa, Older Brother will teach you personally.
Hand-in-hand?
At that time, whatever way you want me to teach you,
I'll be willingly to teach you.
This... is not good?
Hand-in-hand is too intimate. After all, we are siblings.
It's your brother. What is there to fear?
Not good! This brother has an unhealthy tendency.
I need to stay away from him.
The poem meeting is just a few days away.
Xiao Chun Hua must obtain Xin Fa quickly.
I promise, I will have Xin Fa and Xiao Bai
all settled in one go.
You just need to get the Xin Fa.
No need to worry about Xiao Bai.
[Qian Hua Xuan]
Xiao Bai!
Xiao Bai, don't wear that. Wear this!
Get out!
I found someone to make this especially for you.
If you wear this to the poetry meeting, you'll really look good.
Hurry and leave!
I searched everywhere in Fengming Mountain Manor.
It looks like the Xin Fa has to be on Xiao Bai's body.
Miss Chun Hua, what are you doing?
Either you don't wear anything or you wear what I got you.
Stop!
Put it down!
I said so!
What are you standing there for?
I wait for you to come out to try on the clothes. Hurry!
Miss Chun Hua, come here.
What are you doing?
No, Xiao Bai.
Okay, Xiao Bai. Just wear it once, Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai.
[Plum and Willow Inn]
Ye Xingzhu, how could you be this careless handling matters?
I didn't do my duties well to make proper arrangements for the inn.
It's the first time my younger sister leaves Fengming Mountain Manor.
You must be cautious and ensure her safety.
Even the waiters and staff must be extremely obedient.
I have already changed all the inn staff,
and I left a rather smart underling to be on staff.
The extra people were already brought back.
I chose a few underlings who know no martial arts as waiters,
- lest our plan be found out.
- What about the innkeeper?
I'm still waiting for your instructions.
Keep him! It would attract too much attention if we suddenly change the innkeeper.
- Get up.
- Yes.
You actually didn't have to come.
This plan to make a person suffer from his own scheme can be left to me.
What?
Can’t I even join in the fun?
Do you worry about me?
You are extremely skilled in martial arts. Mine is far beneath yours.
Staying in Thousand Moon Cave every day,
how would one knows the developments or disputes in the pugilist world?
Anyway, if I only knew earlier.
Ye Yan,
you should also go out more and see the world.
People say that a group of horrible-looking people control Qianyue Sect.
We should find an opportunity to clear this stigma.
All right.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫