''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
I am fortunate to have all of you heroes and outstanding people attending my wedding.
Therefore, today, I will destroy the Longevity fruit in front of everyone.
A wedding that is organized with such great fanfare.
Miss Chun Hua with the original name of Hua Xiao Lei, had a marriage engagement with you before.
However, she is already wedded to me.
You destroy your Longevity fruit
and I will have my Xiao Chun Hua!
The Longevity fruit will be discussed at a later date.
From now on, you will cut off all ties with Fengming Mountain Manor.
Why do you always have to break us up?
[Episode 21]
That is just great! From now on, you will cut off all ties with Fengming Mountain Manor
and have no association with them.
Why do you always have to break us up?
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Xiao Chun Hua, you would rather believe in destiny
than trust your own judgement.
Forget it! Your clothes are wet.
I will get Ye Yan to bring you a change of clothes.
My Lord!
Do you only have clothes in this color?
I am responsible for protecting you.
I cannot be too flashy.
Forget it!
Bring some of my clothes over.
By the way,
- make some fitting clothes for Xiao Chun Hua.
- Yes.
Also, you make a few for yourself, too.
I cannot stand seeing you wearing such lifeless clothes.
Thank you, My Lord.
It is too big.
You also know it doesn't suit me.
We will just make the necessary alternations.
Besides, there is nobody more suitable than I am.
You are so dismissive of love.
How will you change?
How much can you change?
That is not important.
But I am very compatible with Xiao Bai.
If you really love him so much,
you would have threatened me with death.
Xiao Chun Hua...
just likes to constantly talk about love,
but the more you anxiously looking forward to it,
the more mistakes you'll make.
We must always cherish ourselves.
Love is where both parties adjust for each other and put each other through trials.
If there is no confidence from the beginning,
how will one achieve results?
Since that is the case,
why don't you let me go through your trials?
Impossible!
In any case, to Xiao Chun Hua,
Shangguan Qiu Ye only has two identities.
One is a wretched devilish older brother,
and the other one is a person who eloped with you.
- Shangguan Qiu Yue—
- I got it.
Let me help you
throw these clothes which are an eyesore, away.
Ye Yan!
Xiao Chun Hua, have a seat!
It looks like you are mad at me again.
Xiao Chun Hua, you are always shaking your head at me.
It seems that you really dislike me now.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, are you done?
- Call me, “Older Brother."
- Shangguan Qiu Yue!
I can turn you into a puppet that will only call, “Older Brother." Do you believe I can do that?
That is enough!
Actually, I know everything.
As long as you obediently stay in Qianyue Cave,
I will do anything you say.
Then, can I ask you to die?
That is also possible when it's called for.
Chun Hua
should I trust you?
[Qian Hua Xuan]
Even you cannot find him.
Me? Why should it be certain for me to find the Young Chief?
Today during the wedding, based on the expression on your face,
it looked like you knew perfectly well about the scar on the young chief's fiancée.
Miss Leng just reminded me!
Young Master Qin, how did you know about that?
So,
is your relationship with Miss Chun Hua really that intimate?
- Or you and the Young Chief—
- Miss Leng, I was wrong. I'm certainly on good terms with the young chief.
The young chief and I are like brothers, we know each other so well and our love is more solid than gold.
Then, what are you doing in following us? Let's go!
Don't make a fuss! It's critical that we find the young chief.
Where is Sisi?
Sisi.
Just lie down, Wife!
Sisi, rest well and take good care of yourself, you'll be better tomorrow.
That would be wonderful.
Gorge Master, Xiao Bai's wedding ceremony was not successfully completed.
[Happiness]
- Miss Chun Hua and Shangguan Qiu Yue.
- It must be that Devil's doing.
Maybe he wanted to drive a wedge between them.
However, Shangguan Qiu Yue even knew all about the scar on her body.
The young chief said that Miss Chun Hua had been coerced to leave by Shangguan Qiu Yue before.
Perhaps, he saw it at that time.
Cai Cai,
if this had been your wedding,
it most certainly would not be like this right now.
Actually, the young chief and I had already anticipated that the wedding would erupt into chaos.
After all, we had to destroy the Longevity fruit. We just didn't expect—
Speaking of which, where is the Longevity fruit?
What's this?
It's the Longevity fruit.
The Longevity fruit?
Well, then Little Sister, you have to take good care of it.
How about I give the Longevity fruit to you,
then you'll let me go to Xiao Bai? Could I?
Xiao Chun Hua,
have you stayed with Xiao Bai for too long that you've become stupid?
This fake Longevity fruit is enough to only fool those old fellows,
do you still want to lie to me?
How do you know this is a fake Longevity fruit?
You haven't behaved well, so you're not allowed to sleep here tonight.
[Qianyue Cave]
I have something to ask you.
What's the matter?
You do know.
I don't know.
Give me a break!
I truly don't know.
You... did you really have a relationship with Hua Xiao Lei or not?
I can't remember that far back.
When you came to see me that night, you told me that you didn't want to marry Xiao Bai.
Then, you took off your clothes on your own accord.
I can't remember what happened after.
Or maybe you could repeat that one more time, then perhaps I'll be able to remember.
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
I remember now! You were the one who went to bed first.
I only liked that birthmark
but I didn't like Hua Xiao Lei.
Thus, after she took off her clothes, I just left.
Chun Hua is Chun Hua. Hua Xiao Lei is Hua Xiao Lei.
I don't remember what happened between us before, so you must not sow discord.
I'll be good to you, I swear.
If you really cared for Hua Xiao Lei,
you shouldn't have made her marry Xiao Bai in order to steal the Xin Fa.
Your feelings toward me are like those of a cat or a dog.
Furthermore, I don't like you.
I want to marry Xiao Bai and I don't want to marry you.
Hence, did you bring me here...
just to kill me?
I just don't want to see you marry Xiao Bai.
[Qian Hua Xuan]
Who's there?
Brother Leng, you're here, too.
Yes, what a coincidence!
Are you here for the Longevity fruit as well?
Are you not?
Fu Lou is here, too.
Forget it!
I have Fu Lou to take care of him for me.
[Humanities Propitious Prosperity]
- I—
- You—
You go first!
I just realized that I was extremely anxious today,
which caused my mind to be in a state of chaos and delay our main matter.
You held up two main matters today.
Destroying the Longevity fruit is our main priority.
Then, what about Miss Chun Hua?
Today, Fengming Mountain Manor was indeed not peaceful.
How about I'll gather the chiefs of all the sects together again tomorrow
to give all of them an explanation.
However, she's just a young girl,
we should think of a way to save Miss Chun Hua first.
I am the Young Chief.
I should set aside affairs of personal love
and resolve the issues of the Longevity fruit first.
However, the Longevity fruit
has never been in our hands in the first place.
[Qian Hua Xuan]
The Ice Stone.
Why has the Xiao family been
involved with the Qianyue Sect for so many generations?
Miss Feng.
Miss Feng, it's very late, and you're here...
Since childhood, I've grown up with you.
You are deeply conscious of and clear on matters of principles.
You are kind-hearted to others and very skilled at martial arts.
Hence, for the past ten years,
I've completely
adored you.
Afterwards, Miss Chun Hua appeared.
I was jealous and envious of her, so much that I even loathed her.
And even more so, I just did not understand.
But afterwards, I realized
she is the one that you've always wanted to find.
But she...
and Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Do you trust Miss Chun Hua or Shangguan Qiu Yue?
In your heart, is the Longevity fruit more important
or is Miss Chun Hua more important?
Xiao Bai,
you are the Young Chief.
There is no doubt that the Longevity fruit is important,
but you must cherish both your family and the country.
You must first have affection and trust in your family,
then you will be able to have a great love for the world.
I'm worried about Chun Hua.
So have you thought about how to rescue her?
[Stay calm and don't be impatient. Wait quietly for the opportune moment. Xiao Bai.]
Xiao Bai? You're not angry at me because of the nonsense that Shangguan Qiu Yue was spewing.
That's great!
The location of Qianyue Cave's entrance is mysterious and unpredictable.
How could Xiao Bai have sent someone to sneak in here?
Xiao Chun Hua, I was afraid that you wouldn't feel like eating, so I came to keep you company.
Do you have the ability to stimulate my appetite?
I want to have my meal peacefully and happily.
It looks like the food is not bad today,
since it's given you a silver tongue.
So I should thank you then?
It would be better to give me a taste.
This is the food of Qianyue Cave;
of course, the master of Qianyue Cave can have it.
Xiao Chun Hua, have you forgotten what I taught you?
Stop dreaming!
Xiao Chun Hua, what I've taught you is
that you must remember to give me the chopsticks first.
Otherwise, what were you thinking about?
I see! That wasn't what he meant.
That scared me to death.
At any rate, it didn't have anything to do with you.
It's not bad to have mutual respect between husband and wife.
- Where are you going?
-I'm going to Qianyue Cave!
Calm down! The spy just passed on some information.
- She's already received the secret letter and the token.
- Really?
It's absolutely true! We'll need to wait until the opportune moment arrives.
In a few days' time, we should be able to save Miss Chun Hua.
This Shangguan Qiu Yue is careful and meticulous.
Are you certain that the secret letter was sent and received without any mishap?
He's Uncle Leng's informant and has been remaining undercover in Qianyue Cave for many years.
Why haven't I heard about this before?
This man's name is Antelope.
Uncle Leng saved his life before.
So he'll receive the call of Uncle Leng's flute.
In order to save Chun Hua this time, Uncle Leng has put to use this
chess piece that has been remaining undercover for many years.
Well, I'm sorry to bother Uncle Leng.
That's well played.
It's able to move many more people than 'Three Day Drunk'.
But... how does Qianyue Cave have a flute that's able to move people this way?
Carefully investigate the flute player!
The flute sound is pleasant to hear. I'm so happy for Xiao Chun Hua.
Master.
Stop there!
There are footstep watermarks all over on the ground.
Is this what Gu Wan normally teaches you?
I recognize my mistake.
I never expected you to be blindly subservient in front of your senior,
reprimanding subordinates with strictness.
I'm afraid that the ground being wet is inconvenient for you.
It's just an unreasonable worry.
Seven days have passed.
Why is there still no news yet?
Xiao Bai,
you said you would come to save me.
Don't lie to me!
What are you doing?
Recently, you have been quite boring.
Come and let me take a look!
What are you talking about? I really don't understand.
Although the map of Qianyue Cave is not very detailed,
I still can't let Xiao Bai take it.
Xiao Chun Hua's drawing is too ugly.
You are free to draw your paintings beautifully.
I remember it so I don't need it.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫