''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominating the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
When will the spring flower and autumn moon end?
Today is the distinguished gathering for our martial arts circle of the Right Path but this girl let her tongue wag too freely.
Is it possible that she's an enchantress of a demon sect?
Miss is not at fault. Were it not for the havoc stirred up by the Demon Sect,
how could the martial arts circle be in such a state of anxiety?
As a righteous sect of the martial arts circle, we do things fairly.
We shouldn't suspect anyone without good reason.
Brother Xiao is not blaming Miss Chun Hua.
However, if you intentionally fool him,
Brother Xiao's will become suspicious.
By then, your Xiao Bai will be quickly stolen by others.
Just don't blame me for not warning you.
[Episode 7]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Feng Caicai, Feng Caicai!
To think that you would go as far as to use such a dirty,
underhand, and shameless method.
What exactly do you want to do?
Implementing moral governance for the good of people and thoroughly exterminating evil.
- What did you say?
- I am doing my duty as someone who’s righteous.
Feng Caicai!  Feng Caicai, you—
Good!
Daughter, you can indeed undertake a task alone now.
Father, you flatter me. I still have to interrogate her.
You should stay out of it.
- But there isn’t enough evidences, Father.
- Wait a minute. Where are we going?
No!  Where are we going? Feng Caicai?
Feng Caicai!
I say, aren't you—
All of you, listen up! The person I’m meeting this time
is the Demon Sect, Chuanqi Sect’s Fu Lou.
You don't need to know the reason.
- Understand?
- Yes.
- Watch this young enchantress carefully!
Let's go!
Older Brother, what are you guys trying to do?
Our Chief Feng said that he would give you to me
to be my concubine.
I...
You even dare marry me? Do you know who I am?
Do you know who my older brother is?
My older brother...
is Shangguan Qiu Yue.
I'm telling you, if my brother finds out about this,
he will definitely kill all of you.
You dare glare at me? Glare again!
I'm telling you! My brother likes gouging people's eyes.
He'll surely gouge your eyes out and play ball with them.
Okay, I get it! Let's go.
You even dare carry me like this?
I'm telling you, if my older brother finds out,
he'll certainly chop off your hands.
Gorge Master Fu!
Gorge Master Fu,
I have fulfilled my promise.
Gorge Master, please keep yours.
Sure enough, Chief Feng do things resolutely and swiftly.
If you are such a capable person, how can I let you go that easily.
In the future, if I have anything,
I must ask Chief Feng for help.
I brought the person.
Gorge Master, you shouldn't break your promise.
Who gave you the guts to speak like that to me?
Gorge Master Fu, if you don't keep your promise,
I'd rather kill this girl
and never hand her over to you.
I knew it was you from the get-go.
Then that's just boring.
Older Brother!
Xiao Chun Hua is going to get me killed.
Shangguan Qiu Yue actually has a younger sister.
I didn't expect that you are Shangguan Qiu Yue's younger sister.
I didn't expect it, either.
But... But... I am indeed a treasured girl.
Please be magnanimous and don’t stoop down to my level.
Friend, which sect are you from?
Why have you followed me this entire way and still don't show yourself.
Xisha Sect, Feng Caicai.
Miss Caicai.
Since you came yourself,
- Go quickly.
- then I will do the honors
to keep you at the gorge as a guest.
Miss Chun Hua and Miss Feng left together?
Impossible!  Miss Chun Hua is hostile to Miss Feng.
You know her very well?
I don't dare. Young Master certainly knows Miss Chun Hua the best.
Also, even the scar on her chest, Young Master...
Don't talk nonsense!
As young master's wife, she must be generous and tolerant.
But outside the door, I heard the voice imitation technique.
When I opened the door, I found only Miss Chun Hua. How to explain this?
Young Master, you only hear what you want to hear.
Perhaps Miss Feng dropped in and wanted to have a chat with Miss Chun Hua?
However, we still should think about some countermeasures.
Is it regarding Young Master's future wife?
- Have you tracked down Shangguan Qiu Yue yet?
- My weak kung fu is too inferior to his.
So I couldn't keep up with him.
Chuanqi Gorge.
You, good-for-nothing! There's no use in keeping you around.
I even have to kill you.
You want to run?
You are Shangguan Qiu Yue's younger sister
and even have an unclear relationship with Xiao Bai.
Interesting!
What kind of relationship do you have with Xiao Bai?
I'm... I'm his relative.
Relative?
Xiao Bai really attaches great importance to a relative of unknown origins.
He even told the healer to give you the Longevity Fruit.
I... I'm his wife.
His... his future wife.
We have had an agreement.
Because he saved me, I pledged to marry him.
It wasn't your older brother who saved you?
What kind of relationship do you have with Fu Lou?
If you have nothing to do with him, then why did he save you?
You're the one who saved me.
My Older brother wouldn't allow me to marry Xiao Bai, so he left me.
Surely you don't want me to pledge to marry you, too?
You have proven yourself to be someone who has eaten the Longevity Fruit.
You have truly dragged so many people into this.
Make proper arrangements.
Do not neglect our distinguished guest.
Yes.
Then, how about that one?
Useless! Just kill her.
Don't!
If you want to kill her, then just kill me first.
Gorge Master, your wife wants to see you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Keep her alive, for now.
I am really a saint.
you are not only my rival in love but you are also doubting me in all respects.
But I just cannot bear to see you harmed.
What do I do? Who will come to save us?
Last night, the wind blew and lots of the forget-me-nots fell off.
I told Yanhong to gather some and bring them back.
I made some nail polish because I think it's pretty,
so I called you here to take a look.
Where is the rest? I'll apply some for you.
Xiao Chun Hua, how can you be so careless?
Why did you leave me behind?
You called me 'Older Brother' in front of Fu Lou.
Of course, you're my brother.
Foolish Little Sister!
If he were to know that, he would certainly take advantage of you to deal with me.
So, of course, I could not let him know how important you are in my heart.
I just considered it for your safety.
My hand is already broken.
Let me take a look.
Hurts! It hurts.
Silly Sister, it's not broken but dislocated.
I'll treat you.
Initially, you left me behind
and now, you're using this method to buy me over.
Then, Xiao Chun Hua, what do you want from me?
After I'm better, I'm going to act frivolously with you.
There's no need for that long, you can do it now.
See! I not only acted frivolously with you,
but I could also treat your wound as well.
You... just now...
What were you doing?
Xiao Chun Hua, didn't you ask me to act frivolously with you?
I was afraid again that you would shout or make a sound to attract others.
Unfortunately, both of my hands are not free
so I could only treat your wound with this method.
I'm your older brother, what are you afraid of?
Xiao Chun Hua, did Xiao Bai act frivolously with you?
- You—
- Oh, right!
He is a decent person and a man of integrity.
Naturally, he wouldn't be like this with you.
I should ask, have you acted frivolously with Xiao Bai?
Fu Lou thought that Xiao Bai, for my sake,
begged for the Longevity Fruit from the healer.
If he thinks like this, that's also good.
What "good" is it?
All right, I'll be going now. Be a good girl, Younger Sister.
No, no, no!
Aren't you taking me along?
What kind of place do you think this is?
The outside is closely guarded so how could I get a person out of this gorge?
So you're going to leave me behind again?
How could I leave you behind?
It's not too difficult if you want to get out of here.
Come! I will tell you a way.
Go to the flower garden and look for Fu Lou’s wife.
She will definitely save you.
- Really?
- When have I lied to you?
Oh right! Can you quickly...
Isn't this so beautiful?
Sure enough! the most beautiful person needs to live in the most beautiful place.
Save me!
Madam, save me! Hurry!
Miss, are you all right?
No wonder Fu Lou married his teacher’s wife by force.
The most beautiful woman in the world.
Sure enough! She lives up to her reputation.
You are…?
- I am–
- My Lady, she is the Gorge Master’s guest.
She is unaware of the customs and crashed into you. I will take her away now.
He wants to kill me.
Miss, don’t be afraid! He won’t dare to kill anyone.
But Fu Lou wants to kill people.
I was fortunate enough to be able to escape.
My husband won’t kill anyone.
Then why did he capture us for?
My Lady, don’t listen to her nonsense.
The friend of this girl is constantly causing trouble for Chuanqi Sect.
Gorge Master is simply inviting them over as guests to chat with them.
I knew it! My husband is a good person.
He’s not speaking the truth. It wasn't like that.
Madam, my friend is also a weak lady.
She is currently locked in the dungeon, close to dying.
I heard that Gorge Master Fu had committed the serious crime
of killing his teacher to marry you and even kept you trapped in this place.
Let alone the fact that you don’t hate him, but how can you say that he’s a good person?
It’s not his fault.
He’s a good person.
He isn't in the wrong.
- Madam, you–
- Scoundrel!
Wait!
Let her go! About that lady in the dungeon,
let go of her also.
Madam, I misspoke.
Gorge Master Fu is a good person.
It was just a misunderstanding earlier. Don’t take it to heart!
However, Madam, we can only look for you to rescue us now.
Let’s do this.
Prepare a carriage for these two ladies to send them off.
My Lady, should we wait for Gorge Master to come back?
It is not logical of us to force the guests to stay.
Madam, the scenery here is really great.
I presume that it’s even better outside the gorge so why don't you go out with us and have a look?
While you’re there, you can also send us off, lest they don’t let us go.
Besides, this is my first time at Chuanqi Gorge.
I even would like to get to know you better.
I promised my husband before that I won’t leave this place.
Then…
Then you can just send us to the carriage.
All right.
That is inappropriate.
I am just sending them to the carriage,
and not outside of the gorge.
That is already very impolite of me.
Then I will excuse myself.
When my husband returns, I will definitely talk with him.
Miss, what’s your name?
I’m Chun Hua. Madam, what’s yours?
Chun Hua?
- I’m You Si.
- Madam You Si.
Gorge Master Fu indeed treats you really well.
My husband treats me very well.
This time, both of you, ladies, have been frightened.
Please don’t blame him!
- My Lady, we should–
- Si Si.
Husband, I am just sending these two ladies off.
How could you force your guests to stay?
I originally wanted to send them off.
However, one of them had accidentally injured herself,
so I kept them to allow her to recuperate.
That’s good! I even thought that you were trying to make things difficult for them.
That’s what happened! Gorge Master Fu is a very nice person.
How could he make things difficult for us? Right! That could never happen.
Then… we can take our leave first, can't we?
It’s so cold, yet you came out.
Be careful! Don’t catch a cold. Go back in then.
Husband, don’t you be angry! I’ll go back in a minute.
This horse doesn’t seem easy to rein.
Why don't you send them back?
No need, no need! We can go back on our own.
- Don’t worry! They can go back on their own.
- You must be joking.
If your husband sends us back, we’d be done for.
Horse! Horse, why are you not moving?
Quickly move!
Quickly move. Go! Go!
Miss Feng. Miss Feng!
What should I do now?
Why are you squatting on the ground?
Older Brother, this horse refuses to move and Miss Feng is unconscious.
I really don’t know what to do.
What are you afraid of? Aren’t you alive and well?
Older Brother, I beg you! Please save her.
She had previously plotted against you but you still want me to save her?
But if she’s not saved soon, she will lose her life.
Then just let her die! Accompanying me is more important.
Let’s go! I’ll take you for a stroll.
I’m not going! If you want to go, you go yourself.
In any case, I have to save her.
Miss Caicai. Miss Caicai.
Miss Caicai, please wake up.
Miss Caicai.
Older Brother, I beg you! Please save her.
Could it be that you did something to her?
What are you thinking of? She suffered from Fu Lou’s blow originally, and thus, will not be able to live long.
You don't need to bother about her and I won’t need to do anything to her, either.
Older Brother!
As a matter of fact, I still need to thank Xiao Chun Hua.
Otherwise, I won’t even know that Fu Lou has such a kindhearted wife.
That's true! Lady You Si is beautiful and warmhearted,
but unfortunately, she is in poor health.
If such a frail lady is lost in some unknown place.
I think Gorge Master Fu will be so vexed.
Xiao Chun Hua, you shouldn't relay Lady You Si's matter to anyone.
Just like how you don't want anyone to know that I am your younger sister, right?
I just want to protect you better.
Older Brother.
Why does your body feel so cold every time I touch you?
It's because I grew up on ice.
Then am I the same when I was a child?
Not really! I held you in my arms when you grow up.
Then, what about our mother?
She's dead!
She died because of Fengming Mountain Manor's people.
Before she passed away, she called out both of our names.
She wants us to avenge her.
Really?
When will spring flowers and the autumn moon end?
Now, you should probably know the reason why I want the Xiao family's Xing Fa.
Let her take this pill and then after an hour, she should be fine.
Thank you for saving me.
Of course, you should thank me.
In Chuanqi Gorge, I competed with Fu Lou in wit and bravery.
It's not easy for us to escape but you still need to apology to me.
If you and your dad hadn't kidnapped me, none of this would've happened.
I was wrong in this matter.
- But...
- Forget it, forget it! All because I'm beautiful and kind, I won't argue with you.
Moreover, I don't want Xiao Bai to worry about me.
Miss Chun Hua, these are two separate matters.
Today's matter is rather suspicious.
- How could you—
- Your father and Fu Lou's relationship is the most suspicious.
Your father wanted to kill me to start with.
Now, he even wants to sent me to Fu Lou.
Tell me, why would he do this?
This matter I will definitely ask my father for a clear answer.
If father is really colluding with the Chuanqi Sect, I won't practice favoritism.
However, this matter will require solid evidence.
If not...
If not, I will think you are intentionally creating discord between me and Xiao Bai.
Miss Feng, Miss Chun Hua, it's good to see both of you come back safe and sound.
By the way, where did both of you go?
Miss Feng and I had a bit of a misunderstanding.
So we went out for a walk.
We walked and talked, and lost track of time.
However, we've cleared the misunderstanding.
- Is that right, Miss Caicai?
- But I am still suspicious of Miss Chun Hua's identity.
- Young Master.
- How could you still...
Miss Chun Hua has a lively personality.
The voice imitation technique, I think she was joking around while drunk.
I heard wrong.
Its all good now that the misunderstanding is cleared.
Sorry that we've made you worried all day.
If there is any misunderstanding, it's good to talk it out.
Xiao Bai.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even the admiring for the freshness and the beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have, is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫