Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Miss Chun Hua, I like you.
This confession, I'll accept it.
Everyone came for the Longevity fruit.
It's good that when you were in danger, you know to call me.
Having a passionate, unforgettable love is much better than immortality.
What's more important to Xiao Bai, you or the Fengming Saber? He still didn't decide yet.
Are you really certain of that?
I must test the Young Master of the martial arts circle for you.
[Episode 16]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
This is my first time in Bishui City.
I have the pleasure of gathering together with all chiefs.
Indeed, I consider myself most fortunate.
Here! Let me take this opportunity to make a toast
and show my respect to you all.
Chief Qin, you are too modest.
Thank you so much, Chief Qin! I also got a blessing in disguise.
If it's not for my daughter...
It's best not to mention it. Never mind!
Everyone, here! Let's all have a drink.
- Here, cheers!
- Cheers!
A thousand cups of wine still isn't too much when best friends meet.
No need to fear good wine!
- The third cup, I—
- Chief Qin.
Is the Young Chief Master still inside?
Did you not invite him to come give a few words?
Fine! Everyone, wait here for a moment.
Young Chief Master, please be calm.
We put missing person posters all over Bishui City.
Perhaps, Miss Chun Hua will return very soon.
I have troubled you, Miss Feng.
Young Chief Master, quickly come.
We, old fellows, all wait for you.
- Young Chief Master.
For most of you here today,
we saw each other at Fengming Mountain Manor just a few days ago.
Today, we presumably gather here in Bishui City for many different reasons.
We still have two more hours before the great Longevity fruit auction.
Evil and righteous martial arts paths wait for the opportune moment to take action.
As the Righteous Path, we should make law and order our top priority.
- I hope you all can—
- Well said.
Young Chief Master, what you said is quite reasonable.
If anyone has an interest in the Longevity fruit, please prepare your money.
- Let's compete fairly by the rules, all right?
- All right.
[Yingzhen Inn]
The auction will start soon. Be careful! That wine might be poisoned.
Many chiefs are here.
Did you inquire about Miss Chun Hua's whereabouts?
We won't be able to get anything out of these people.
Besides, I'm the Young Chief Master.
I should give priority to the bigger situation at hand.
How could I ask them to go and look for Miss Chun Hua
because of my personal romantic relationship?
Come, everyone!
We still have some time before the Longevity fruit auction.
Shall we eat and drink first?
- Come, come, come.
- Chief Tang, cheers!
- Come, everyone!
- Chief Qin.
It seems my father drank a lot. so he might tell me to go and drink with him.
Why don't I accompany you to go out for some fresh air?
It's noon now.
Chun... Miss Chun Hua.
- Naughty!
- Jewelry!
- Miss Chun Hua has good lucks. She will be fine. Don't worry!
- Young Master.
I have lots of fashionable jewelry here.
Will you buy one to give to your beloved?
We have many beautiful women.
Choose some nice ones for me.
Young Master, I only sell my jewelry to those who are destined.
You and I do not have a bond of destiny.
However, this Young Master seems very kind.
Your jewelry is truly first class.
You even seek those who are destined.
Here! I have a bracelet passed down through generations.
Young Master, are you interested?
Let's go!
Young Master, this jade bracelet is for a beautiful woman.
Hand over the bracelet!
"Come to Qianyue Cave today at noon. Exchange the Fengming Saber for Chun Hua."
- Shangguan Qiu Yue.
- Why did you tie me up?
- I told Xiao Bai that I kidnapped you.
So I have to tie you up, of course.
Now he pays excessive attention to his wording.
Xiao Bai is currently on the road hurrying to the auction.
Xiao Bai and the others are going to prevent the chaos at the auction.
What is it? Did I disappoint you?
Do you think the righteous sects and the Chuanqi Sect will fight?
You are really abnormal.
You mention this conspiracy so casually.
I'm just curious.
Let's make a bet!
I don't want to.
I bet that Xiao Bai won't make it to the auction on time today.
I made him come and rescue you today.
Do you think that I hold such a special place in his heart?
Well, it depends whether or not you're more valuable than the Fengming Saber.
What do you think?
The auction is from eleven to one o’clock, it's same time as saving Miss Chun Hua.
If the auction is carried out, saving Chun Hua will have to be pushed back.
Why don't we go to save Chun Hua first and return before one o’clock?
Okay, I will meet up with you soon.
- But what if Shangguan Qiu Yue tries—
- Young Chief Master, rest assured.
The three of us will take control of the auction situation,
and wait for you and Miss Chun Hua to return together.
Young Chief Master.
Be careful on the way!
Oh My, I just drank too much wine.
I need to use the toilet urgently.
Brother Suifeng,
I'll accompany you.
Master Shi has not arrived yet.
It is not appropriate for anyone to leave now.
Chief Suifeng...
What do you say?
Chief Qin,
have a seat!
This group of old men,
why are they not killing each other yet?
Or did they already drink the poisonous wine
and all died?
There is a quarter of an hour left.
Xiao Chun Hua, it seems you aren't worth as much as the Fengming Saber.
Do you really believe that someone
will give up all for love?
For love, there are people
who will give up everything.
Later, her wish came true
and she met her Mr. Right.
Then later, she was dumped by Mr. Right.
My Lord.
[Longevity Fruit Auction]
Everybody,
Young Chief Master will be here soon.
Please wait silently.
Chief Leng, you worry too much. We are established, dignified sects.
How could we stir up trouble before the auction even starts?
If word gets out, won’t we be a laughing stock?
As agreed, Fengming Mountain Manor, Xiao Bai, has arrived.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, where are you?
A quarter to noon, it's time for Longevity fruit auction.
Chief Leng, what are you hesitating for?
After you!
- It is now a quarter to noon. The auction will start soon.
- Hold on!
- It's already time near eleven.
- It's all your fault for dawdling.
I didn't think the righteous sects would secretly station many guards.
If you flirted less, we could have moved faster today.
We are near the auction venue. Be careful!
Feng’er!
Father?
Son, you are impressive! You did not let Xiao Bai have a head start.
Father, Father.
- W-what are you doing?
- What are you all doing here?
We are going to the auction. What about you?
Right, right, right! Speaking of the auction, have you ever thought about this?
The Longevity fruit at the auction,
so many sects arrived just to fight for it.
I have always found it strange.
You are always very intelligent so for this, I've decided to stand on the sidelines
and not commit evil deeds with them.
When they have stopped fighting,
we will then take advantage of the situation, won't we?
I wonder, how is it going at Young Master’s side? Is it going smoothly?
Although Xiao Bai didn't attend the auction but came to save you,
he may not be able to rescue you.
Are you going back on your words?
If he is able to rescue you, I will do anything you want me to do.
Do you want to go and watch the show with me?
I didn't think Xiao Bai
would really put the auction aside to come and save you.
I knew that Xiao Bai would come to save me.
Congratulations, Young Mistress Xiao.
Why is Xiao Bai not using the Fengming Saber?
Fengming Mountain Manor has a rule.
No woman can be killed by the Fengming Saber.
He is indeed a man I admire.
Young Sister, your perception of Xiao Bai is very partial.
If you don't step aside, don't blame me for being merciless.
"Xiao Xiao Fengming Saber!" He did not disappoint me.
Younger Sister, cooperate with me to put on a show later.
- What kind of show?
- The hostage cries for help and is strangled to death by me.
My Fengming Saber has said it will not kill women,
but it hasn't said it won't injure them.
- All you hopeless fighters, withdraw!
- Yes.
Xiao Bai!
Young Master Xiao. Oh, that's not right.
Young Chief Xiao, I trust you've been well since we last parted?
Your Qianyue Sect has done all kinds of evil and killed people like killing flies.
Today, I will kill you!
Well said!
I'm your enemy. Release Miss Chun Hua!
He really cares about you.
My Husband!
- Husband?
- Shangguan Qiu Yue!
You said I could exchange the Fengming Saber for Miss Chun Hua.
I am here as you've wanted.
I really want to choke you to death.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, let go of Miss Chun Hua!
This saber... I can give you!
On second thought, I go back on my word.
Wouldn't it be better if you  just choked me to death?
You can go now.
Miss Chun Hua, are you all right?
Xiao Bai, your Fengming Saber!
Ice silk.
I didn't think that the dignified Young Master of Fengming Mountain Manor,
whom all in the martial arts circle praise as a man of honor,
would rely on the Qianyue Sect's ice silk, in order to save face.
The Longevity fruit will be auctioned at 11:30 a.m.
- Where is the Longevity fruit?
- Where is Master Shi?
At 11:30 a.m., Longevity fruit auction. 11:30 a.m., Longevity fruit auction.
- Where is the Longevity fruit? Tell me!
- Where is Mr. Shi? Tell me now!
- Where is Mr. Shi?
The Longevity fruit will be auctioned at 11:30 a.m.
What's the meaning of this? What's going on? Exactly
The Longevity fruit auction has an entrance fee of one million liang.
You all have this.
However, there is only one Longevity fruit.
So among all of you right here,
- only the survivor can obtain the Longevity fruit.
- How can you prove the Longevity fruit is real?
I'm already getting close to death!
Regardless if it's true or not, I want the Longevity fruit!
The one who can live to tell the tale,
will be able to take the world's treasure, the Longevity fruit.
Gorge Master.
How is it going?
All people from the Righteous Path are swept away in a scene of violence, killing each other.
When I returned, it was already a bloodbath.
- A taste of their own medicine.
- They're all fools.
They didn't see the Longevity fruit or Master Shi.
They just fight all those who are close by.
Well, that's because
I still haven't shown up at the homicidal auction.
It's time I should make my appearance.
Wait!
- It's not right. This wasn't here before. Son, my two daughters-in—
- Father!
R-Right! Ladies, e better not go inside right now.
This scene is quite bizarre, and we don't know what's inside.
We should be a little cautious.
Chief Qin is right.
Chief Suifeng!
The Longevity fruit is mine!
You, and you all!
Do you want to vie with me for the Longevity fruit?
Son! The way I see it, we must be careful.
We should get out of here.
Oh, no! My father is still in there.
- Take good care of yourself, Old Man.
- What are you doing, Son?
Be careful! Take care of yourself! I'll go find Young Chief Xiao to uphold justice!
Uncle Leng!
Xiao Bai,
I have something to ask you.
Miss, please say it.
Did Shangguan Qiu Yue tell you to exchange the Fengming Saber for me?
Well, what if... I'm just saying what if,
what if I had returned,
but not your sword, what would you do?
Rest assured! I won't lose you or the sword.
- You are truly so confident.
- Yes, truly.
No one knows that there's ice silk on my Fengming Saber.
I also had no idea it was a relic left by my father.
This relationship between ice silk and the Qianyue Sect,
I only discovered this when I learned of Shangguan Hui.
Rest assured,
I will handle these matters as quickly as possible.
Let's go!
Don't worry! Uncle Leng will be all right.
Uncle Leng isn't here!
This...
It's the silver needle the Healer used to control puppets many years ago.
Allegedly, this technique is very evil.
The Healer has stopped using this needle for a long time, not to mention...
the Healer is already dead!
Be it a success or a failure,
let me try it one last time.
Xiao Chun Hua has left.
It suddenly became so boring.
My Lord, please ease your anger.
I just remembered Xiao Chun Hua and you are about the same age.
Come,
say something I would like to hear.
I dare not.
You ate the mooncakes that Xiao Chun Hua made.
We are now a family.
What is there to fear among family members?
I…
only want to serve you my entire life.
I don't dare harbor other thoughts toward you.
You already said “entire life.”
Yet you say you harbor no other thoughts.
If you…
want to kill me now…
I will have served you my entire life.
I like what you said. It’s not bad!
I wonder where Xiao Chun Hua and Young Chief Master are now.
Are they able to make it for the grand show?
Miss Chun Hua.
Do not look over there!
Where are Qin Liufeng and the rest?
This is all my fault.
Turn around now.
Miss Chun Hua, don’t be afraid! I'm here.
Qin Liufeng and the rest are not here.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫