''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
[Episode 1]
In the year 2169, mankind already achieved immortality.
People can undergo the process of physiologically reducing emotional responses and
wearing the helmet of virtual love.
By launching the micro-current stimulus program,
- one can experience the climax of love.
- Stop!
I don't want the physiological stimulation!
I want to experience an actual love.
The Sky Thunder System can satisfy your wish
- but you must give up immortality.
- I'm willing!
Without love, what is the point of immortality?
I'll give up immortality.
Do you have any requirements for your love journey?
I want my Mr. Right to be exceptionally handsome, devoted,
very powerful, and spoils me with a lot and a lot of sweets.
He can handle some bugs. He should be charismatic and decisive.
He can be a Mary Sue, but he should be aloof and not too old fashioned.
Your theme of self-destruction is,
"When will the spring flower and autumn moon end?"
("spring flower' is Chun Hua and "autumn moon" is Qiu Yue in Chinese - this question implies a never-ending relationship)
Hold hands, hug,
kiss!
Bear in mind, the rule of the first one who comes into your sight!
The first man you shall see is your Mr. Right.
- The count-down is now starting! Three.
- What does that mean?
- If I don't like Mr. Right,
- Two.
- can I switch?
- One.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Can it be that... he is...
Bear in mind the rule of the first one who comes into your sight!
The first man whom you see is your Mr. Right.
Husband!
Where is the agreed-upon Mr. Right?
He's just the grim reaper!
I didn't expect to encounter such a thrilling beginning.
But I do like it.
We can talk in a civil manner.
- Why pull out the sword?
- How dare you!
You dare to disobey our young master?
Young Master?
Does that mean I'm the future young master's wife?
You have eaten the longevity fruit and killed the healer!
Who is the healer?
What's the longevity fruit?
If you say that I killed someone, then I really killed him?
Then I say that you killed someone and framed me.
Young Master, he is still alive.
- It's indeed her.
- It's her.
Just tell them that, "I'm not the killer."
It has nothing to do with me.
- Me?
- As the matter stands, I am unable to tolerate your continuous quibbling.
Give me your life!
Fu Lou?
Young Master, I'll go after him!
What is your relationship with Fu Lou?
Fu Lou?
Then, what kind of relationship should I have with him?
You said, "there is none," so why did he rescue you?
He rescued me?
That's not right.
Clearly, Husband saved me.
You're frightening me to death.
Don't kill me!
Miss, what is your name?  Why are you here?
Can you withdraw the sword first? I'm scared.
Miss, there is no need for you to be scared. I'm Xiao Bai. (Xiao means little or young. Bai means white)
My father is a leader in martial arts circles.
The son of a martial arts leader?
They must have vast and fertile lands and countless disciples!
I came to find a cure for my father.
I came to find and beg for the longevity fruit from the healer.
But I unexpectedly came across this crime.
Miss, if you know anything, just tell me.
What can I know?
The system didn't tell me anything.
Let me tell you
I... am your...
future... wife.
Full of nonsense!  Who exactly are you?
Young Master!
Chief Feng, did you discover any clues at Fu Lou's place?
Fu Luo indeed came for the longevity fruit, but it's just that...
I'm incapable, thus, I allowed him to escape.
Young Master.
We found this petition in the healer's drawer.
[Chunhua, female, found in Sangtian Village, memories lost after being revived from death]
Chun Hua? (A name that means "spring flower")
Are you calling me?
Such an old fashioned name!
She really lost her memory?
Lost memory?
This set-up is not bad.
Since all of the disciples from the Baxian Residence identified her,
she certainly must have killed the healer.
I observed her hands, it doesn't look like she practices martial arts.
My husband is amazing.
For the time being, you should come along with me to the Fengming Mountain Manor.
Take me back?
Then there will be a lot of opportunities.
[Thousand Moon Pavilion]
My Lord, we have news.
After Hua Xiaolei betrayed you, she died.
I heard, she ate the longevity fruit the day before yesterday and came back to life.
However, she has even lost her memory.
Now, she was saved by the Fengming Mountain Manor.
Do you want me to drag her back and question her about the longevity fruit?
Ye Xingzhu, you are too naïve.
What is the longevity fruit if not just a rebel?
Just let the ignorant be.
However, she is following Xiao Bai again.
This is very interesting.
I already fell down.
In order to get up, I need a  hug from Xiao Bai.
So boring!
[Fengming Mountain Manor]
"Chivalry lasts long for centuries."
"Chirping herald the Halcyon days."
Such great assurance!
This is my future husband's house.
Really great!
[Blooming Spirit, Lasting Glory]
Young Master.
Xiao Bai, all of these houses are yours?
- Young Master.
- Then are all of these people at your service?
They will do whatever you say?
- Young Master.
- Lu Xiu, this is Miss Chun Hua.
- Hi.
- Take good care of her.
After I tell my father, I will make arrangements.
Yes.
Miss Chun Hua.
Xiao Bai.  Xiao Bai!
Xiao Bai!
Miss Chun Hua, this way, please.
Father, this time I went to Baxion residence
to meet a healer for the longevity fruit.
To cure the poison in your body.
However, someone had killed the healer.
Currently, we don't know the location of the longevity fruit.
Xiao'er, the longevity fruit is very strange.
I am afraid it will lead to a catastrophe of bloodlust.
I brought back a girl from the healer's residence.
She came back to life after she ate the longevity fruit.
Life and death are dictated by fate.
You should give importance to the martial arts world.
Stick to the right track.
The identity of that miss is unknown.
You should investigate her identity carefully.
I understand.
Xiao Bai? Xiao Bai.
Miss Chun Hua, that is not your seat.
Since the seat across is not mine,
then I can only sit next to Xiao Bai.
How can you be so impolite?
Forget it!  Let her be.
Xiao Bai, I heard that there is something called...
longevity fruit.
Eating it can bring someone back to life.
- True or false?
- Young Master, the longevity fruit,
is it just Shangguan Qiu Yue's trick?
The self-destruction theme is when Chun Hua and Qiu Yue will come to an end.
Shangguan Qiu Yue?
Who is Shangguan Qiu Yue?
What do you mean who, it's Qianyue Sect's leader
What is Qianyue Sect?
A Demon Sect.
Since I am Chun Hua, would Qiu Yue be my relative?
Sister?
Chun Hua, Qiu Yue, such vulgar names!
It's great to have the leader of the Demon Sect as my relative.
So great. Really great, so great!
People of Qianyue Sect kill innocent people, such bloodlusts, you dare...
You can't tell right from wrong.
The demon sect is so vicious.
We need to draw a clear distinction with them.
Miss Chun Hua,
medical records say that you rose from the dead.
Do you still remember how you came back to life?
The system planned it.
You mean...
[Spring Welcoming Pavilion]
Come closer!
Come closer and I will tell you.
What do you mean by this?
Miss, just stand right there and tell me.  I can hear you.
Don't want me to come closer?
Then I'll let you come to me.
Just ask whatever you want to ask.
Miss, what is the first thing that you remember?
Miss, louder please.
Come over here!
Say that one more time.
Actually, just now I couldn't hear you clearly. What did you ask?
I just asked, what is the first thing that you remember?
It's you.
Then since you had consumed the longevity fruit,
do you remember how it looks like?
I remember…
how you look like.
I also remember calling you “husband”.
Step aside!
You brought me back, yet you don’t care about me.
Now that we are finally able to see each other, you’re still asking all sorts of questions.
Aren’t you afraid that someone might want to murder me?
Lu Xiu will protect you.
What if that person is so skilled in martial arts that even Lu Xiu can’t win against him?
Personally, I think that you should–
You need not worry. This is Fengming Mountain Manor, after all.
He does not understand a woman's heart!
Young Master.
How is it?
Is there anything unusual about Miss Chun Hua?
Other than being ignorant of etiquettes,
there is nothing unusual about her.
However…
However, what?
She directly addresses you by name.
It seems she believes that both of you have a very close relationship.
This might have been caused by the loss of her memory.
However, it seems that she truly doesn’t know about etiquette.
Don’t listen to her nonsense! Continue observing her secretly.
Yes.
Miss Chun Hua, where are you going?
I want to have a look at what Xiao Bai is currently doing.
Does Miss Chun Hua really not remember anything?
I really do not remember anything.
Fengming Mountain Manor, also known as martial arts of Bei Dou, the leader of of all sects in the martial arts circles.
It’s because of this Xiao Xiao Fengming Saber (the name of a martial art skill)
that the Demon Sect is afraid of committing evil deeds,
allowing peace in our land.
Then…
What’s the story behind the Demon Sect?
One hundred years ago, the head of the demon sect, Nan Xinghe, went on a rampage in the pugilist world.
Later, the Xiao family ancestors joined forces with several huge sects to eliminate him.
After Nan Xinghe’s death, the demon sect suffered a huge blow.
They later split into two different sects: Qianyue Sect and Chuanqi Sect.
The pugilist world now consists of the Wulin sects,
Qianyue Sect and Chuanqi Sect,
forming a tripartite confrontation situation.
Tell me more about Qianyue Sect?
Qianyue Sect is vicious in its ways.
It is rumored that the leader, Shangguan Qiu Yue,
is extremely ugly.
But I heard that anyone who has seen her…
Why are we bringing her up for?
If you put it this way…
Shangguan Qiu Yue and Xiao Bai are unable to coexist with one another.
Miss Chun Hua. Miss Chun Hua!
Miss Chun Hua.
Miss Chun Hua!
Miss Chun Hua, quickly wake up to go up the mountain with me.
Why do I need to go up the mountain? I’m not going.
Just go by yourself!
The weather is fine and the air is fresh.
Miss Lu Xiu, let’s set out now!
I can’t take it anymore! I can’t walk anymore!
Just go by yourself! In any case, I’m not going.
Miss Chun Hua, why do you not use your lightness skill?
Lightness skill?
People in Fengming Mountain Manor all know martial arts?
Of course!  Especially our Xiao family’s Xiao Xiao Fengming Saber.
It is said to no longer be passed down.
Lu Xiu, could it be that you like Xiao Bai?
Young Master already has a marriage engagement since young.
I won’t dare to have such feelings.
Miss Chun Hua must be joking.
What did you say? Marriage engagement? Who does he have a marriage engagement with?
Tell me!
Back then, Leader Xiao and Old Master Hua became relatives by marriage.
However, before they got married, Young Master’s bride, Hua Xiao Lei,
passed away.
The bride died before she could move into the groom’s household?
In that case, Xiao Bai is still single.
I see that it's getting late.
Miss, hurry up and follow after me.
Forget it! Then stay here and wait for me.
Remember, you must not go anywhere.
Don’t go anywhere, okay?
Xiao Bai, I’m sorry.
Allow me to be infatuated for a minute.
Don’t be afraid! Open your eyes.
Thank you, Young Master, for helping me out. I have nothing to repay you with, except for–
Your body?
Such a smooth talker! I’m going to be tricked by an expert.
Such a pity, my supporting male lead.
Without a doubt, I only have money to repay you with.
Then how much do you think you’re worth?
Then… how much do you think I am worth?
A thousand gold? Ten thousand gold?
D*mn! I've met a scammer.
All of these aren’t enough in exchange for your life.
I think that you are priceless.
Since that’s the case, I’ll take my leave.
In the future, I will definitely repay your great kindness. Bye!
Wait a minute!
Since you are priceless,
I think you can only marry me in return.
I am Xiao Bai's young wife of the famous Fengming Mountain Manor.
If you want money, then you can go to the Fengming Mountain Manor. But if you want me,
let me tell you, you must be tired of living.
Really?
Indeed.
Would it be possible for me to ask the young wife of the manor for a favor?
How about solving my tiredness?
You...
It's you? Hua...
Do you know me?
Yes, I'm Chun Hua.
Where are you from?
Qianyue Sect.
Oh, so we're family, aren't we?
Since that's the case, take me to see Shangguan Qiu Yue. Let's go.
That's right.
You guessed correctly.
I am Shangguan Chun Hua.
Shangguan Qiu Yue's older sister. Let's go.
Let's go, quickly take me to see my younger sister. Let's go.
Let's go! Let's go!
Since when does my family's little Chun Hua have a younger sister?
Shangguan Qiu Yue is my younger sister.
If she were here, she would have already recognized me.
At any rate, you all don't need to care about this so much,
just take me to my younger sister, that's fine. Let's go.
You've already seen him.
You?
Shangguan Qiu Yue is...
a man?
Who told you I was a woman?
Is he really Shangguan Qiu Yue?
Didn't Lu Xiu say she was a hideous and evil woman?
How do I know you're not lying to me?
Sure enough, Xiao Chun Hua does not remember,
you are my younger sister.
Since I woke up with the healer, I haven't remembered anything.
Since you've lost your memory, why did you still want to find me?
Because when will Chun Hua and Qiu Yue come to an end?
Interesting!
If I had known, I wouldn't have let you go on this mission.
Now, it turns out to be like this.
What mission?
You rarely went out in the past.
This time, you decided to go to Fengming Mountain Manor, saying you will steal the Xin Fa.
(Xin Fa = a cultivation method of the heart)
Not only did you fail to steal it,
you also ended up being wounded like this.
You are really my older brother?
What are you doing?
Weren't you suspicious that I am lying to you?
On your body, you have a pink birthmark
that is in the shape of a flower bud. That's why you were named Chun Hua.
It looks like he really is Shangguan Qiu Yue.
But he doesn't fit Lu Xiu's description.
Has no one seen him before?
I can tell you, no need to make a move.
It's not good if someone sees it.
Who can see?
Then I will gouge out her eyes so she can't see.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫