''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man,
someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Drown my sorrows in liquor...
But I didn't think that drinking makes people happy either.
Miss Feng has good character, courage, determination, dedication to sacrifice for my righteousness.
As for Miss Chun Hua,  you two have met.
Wouldn't it be natural if you could say things openly?
Miss Chun Hua, you can't go back.
I just want to be with someone.
I'll be with you.
I'll save him, and he will kill me.
Big Brother, I beg you. Please save him.
[Episode 28]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Your subordinate is incompetent.
Thank you, Master, for your life-saving grace.
Please, Master, regulate to replenish your Zhen Qi as soon as possible.
Your subordinate is willing to support you.
There is no need.
The Master's inner strength is greatly damaged at this moment;
thus, it's still better to regulate it as soon as possible.
How do you know that your Senior's Zhen Qi (internal force) is damaged?
It's just that... when I awoke,
I felt that Master's breathing wasn't as even as before.
Hence, I dared to guess.
You are right.
I need a few hours to adjust my Zhen Qi (internal force).
You should close your Acupoints (acupuncture points).
Gu Wan, aren't you closing your acupoints still?
Gu Wan, you're an ingrate!
[Treasure Pavilion]
Please!
Greetings, Masters.
Shopkeeper, have you ever seen such a handsome master?
I see what you say!
Oh, My! Two handsome masters like you two young masters,
should need, at least, a pair of custom-made jade pendants to show your extravagance.
How can you compare us in the same breath?
Also, why should I have a pair of jade pendants with him?
You two are, in a manner of speaking, so intimate that you must be sworn brothers.
- Certainly, you are a match, aren't you?
- You...
I-I...
Shopkeeper, think again!
- Where is there such a pretty man?
- He is in fact,...
So,that's how it is...
Since you are married, that's another reason to customize a pair.
Shopkeeper!
What nonsense are you spouting?
In that case, we will listen to you.
We won't buy it.
That won't do! If that's the case, why should I come with you?
[Qianyue Cave]
Did you ever think of this end, Shangguan Qiu Yue?
Is it rebellion in Qianyue Cave?
You guys have bold daring.
Gu Wan, didn't you say that Shangguan Qiu Yue was seriously injured?
What are you afraid of?
No matter how strong Shangguan Qiu Yue is,
right now, his power is only 30-40%.
Besides, the hidden weapon I used just now may have injured him.
We have so many people here, why are you so afraid of him?
Did you forget who saved your life?
This is his own fault!
But today, I'm lucky that you're here.
Unexpectedly, even wise Shangguan Qiu Yue can have a momentary judgment lapse.
He actually listened to a silly girl like you and took our bait.
I was right to escort this treasure.
[Order]
This is the Gorge Master's seal that you all know.
Everything means nothing after death. Fu Lou is dead.
- Why would we still care about his nonsense token?
-You!
I'm late! Please forgive me, Master.
You certainly came at the right time.
I wounded him yesterday.
I thought he wouldn't take any actions at this time.
I didn't expect he would take advantage of his wound's condition...
Wong is wrong! No need to find an excuse.
Xiao Yan, look for yourself!
You are loyal and devoted to him, but what is he considerate of you?
Shut up! Stop being so rude to Master.
Okay. Since you love Young Lord so much,
then I will take his position.
Why are you still standing around? You know all Shangguan Qiu Yue's tricks, don't you?
Do you think he will let you all go?
All of you, stop being foolish!
Now, Gu Wan can't even fend for himself, what can he do for you all?
Don't be led astray by him and be led to your downfall!
Let me tell you all, although Shangguan Qiu Yue suffered a damage to his Zhen Qi,
he's still more than capable of dealing with you all.
People who have nothing to do with this matter, should leave immediately.
Perhaps, he will show you mercy to spare your lives.
You all should die.
Just now, you purposely pretended your vital energy was low.
to lure us out, didn't you?
What did you think will happen?
Should I still keep those who will betray me anytime?
Shangguan Qiu Yue, we, Chuanqi Sect brothers, came to you with a good intention to seek refuge.
However, you put on an appearance and even took away our power.
You detained so many of our brothers and you simply so deceiving.
Since you surrendered and pledged your allegiance to Qianyue Sect, is there any more Chuanqi Sect?
If I didn't lock them in the dungeon,
more people than you guys would have come today.
I suspect Gu Wan had promised you, after finishing this matter, you would be in charge of the Chuanqi Gorge,
and he would take control of Qianyue Cave.
- Actually, Gu Wan instigated this whole matter. We—
- You!
I even thought you all could accomplish great feats,
but if you want to beg him for mercy now, that's also fine.
At most, you should just waste your Kung Fu and chop off your legs.
Those who practice martial arts
but waste their Kung Fu, are no worse than death!
Do you want him to let us go?
In your dreams!
Even if he says he will let us off,
would you really trust his words?
Kill him!
I never thought I would underestimate you.
Do not pursue a fallen enemy!
Clean up this place!
I need to spend time to regulate and replenish my vital energy.
You should stand guard so that no one can be allowed to enter.
Yes.
Xiao Chun Hua, let's go!
[Baxian Restaurant]
What would you like to order, my fellow patrons?
An order of "Buddha Jumps Over the Wall," braised shark fin, Wanfu meat,
Beijing roasted duck, chicken with mixed vegetables,
soft-shell turtle stew, and eight-treasure mushroom soup.
Bring us all your signature dishes.
Sure! Please wait.
Miss Leng, can you finish all those dishes?
Who told you I was going to stuff myself with all this food?
I'm very particular about my food.
We just need to have
a taste of genuine flavor, that's all!
[Something is happening]
Young Master Leng.
Do you remember the Longevity fruit auction
and those two silver needles that could manipulate puppets?
If you didn't mention it, I would have completely forgotten.
Well, what happened to those silver needles?
Earlier, on the back of the puppets' heads,
I discovered two silver needles that could manipulate them.
Is that so?
Those two silver needles were the Healer's special, hidden weapon.
They can manipulate corpses of the recent dead to revive them.
Waiter!
Let's follow him.
Sir, may I help you?
Add a jug of wine.
Okay.
Young Master Leng, our bill has not been settled.
Why are you in a hurry to leave?
Sit down!
Young Master Qin, you're so rich.
Why can't you afford one meal for me?
Of course, I'm not as money is a worldly possession.
- Now, that is correct.
- Money is a worldly possession.
Therefore, my pocket is completely empty right now.
You—
This is not your style.
I spent all the money I carried buying the jade pendants.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
If Miss Leng wants to eat in a restaurant, how dare I decline?
I will pay for it.
The total is 37 silver and six copper coins.
Do you have enough?
So much?
Before you ordered these dishes,
I already knew all the prices by heart.
Why didn't you tell me then?
You were in such a good mood, I did not want to spoil it.
Hence, what should we do?
- Put it on outstanding credit.
- No, I can't.
You and I are both honorable people.
Waiter!
Miss Leng, have you dined-and-dashed before?
Sir.
Why is there a fly in the soup?
That's impossible, Sir!
This—
Patron, how about I exchange it for you?
[Baxian Restaurant]
Someone was terribly despicable today.
Someone was a partner in crime today.
Let's take care of the official business first.
[Baxian Restaurant]
Are you all right?
Didn't you say you needed to go and regulate your Zhen Qi?
Shangguan Qiu Yue! What is wrong, Shangguan Qiu Yue?
Are you injured?
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Shangguan Qiu Yue! Shangguan Qiu Yue, wake up!
Why are you so cold? You are even colder than before.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, say something to me!
Call me Brother!
Come! I will take you to your bed.
Shangguan Qiu Yue, you are indeed injured!
[Full of Noble Daring Aspiration]
It seems that this trip was not a waste.
Miss Leng. Master Qin.
Caicai, you're finally back! Did all go well?
It was okay. I just wasn't accustomed to not having you by my side.
Yes. I regretted not being with you as well.
Why did I go out with Qin Liufeng in the first place?
Brother Qin, are there any solutions to this matter of the Longevity fruit?
- Let's go inside to discuss.
- Sure.
Watch out!
Gu Wan won't chase after us into here, will he?
He can't.
If you lock it from inside, they cannot open it from the outside.
Are you doing okay?
XIao Chun Hua can easily kill me now.
Do you think I dare not?
My little sister is a good person but you can also choose
to grab the command token and leave.
Gu Wan knows you are injured and he's there, so how can I leave?
I'll arrange for Ye Yan to escort you.
Gu Wan won't harm her.
This tunnel is too dark so I wouldn't dare to leave.
Are you not only scared of death, but also the dark?
Do you still have strength to make fun of me?
You clearly knew that Gu Wan set a trap to make you expend your Zhen Qi.
You fool! It would have been really easy to lure them out, so why did you invest your Zhen Qi?
Because
Xiao Chun Hua wanted me to save him.
Why are you so cold?
Zhen Qi devours me from the inside out.
Does Zhen Qi affect you from inside out?
Is it because you saved me?
Xiao Chun Hua, you caused me to end up in such a state.
Shouldn't you pay me back with something?
Tell me! What would you like me to do for you?
Gather yin and nourish yang!
Nonsense!
I am not lying to you.
Xiao Chun Hua, are you willing to save me?
I can't, I...
Are you still not willing to take me into the ice gorge?
Collect the world's cold yin energy.
What did you think I meant, Xiao Chun Hua?
We can get there if we walk straight down.
Were you messing with me?
I would never do that.
I'm simply flirting with you.
Come back, Xiao Chun Hua!
I am really leaving.
Shangguan Qiu Yue. Shangguan Qiu Yue! Wake up! Shangguan Qiu Yue!
I knew it!
Xiao Chun Hua, you would not leave your brother without care.
Besides playing tricks on me, what else can you be proud of?
Now, you are injured so severely with no one you can trust around you.
I do
I still have you.
Miss Leng and I spread the message, but we didn't expect to catch such a big fish.
- What do you mean?
- In the restaurant, we mentioned the silver needles publicly.
As a result, before we left the restaurant, there was someone behind who wanted to kill us.
But luckily, we already took necessary precautions.
That person didn't succeed and we could even subdue him.
Then that person hastily used a powder that blinded us.
And there is this...
These are those silver needles again.
Correct! Before he nearly blinded me, I had pulled this out of his cuff.
Afterward, we asked after the man we noticed in the restaurant.
He's called Li Yu, the Healer's disciple, and he lives in Baxian Residence.
I investigated his identity and found out that this Li Yu was originally a gambler.
Debt collectors beat him nearly to death.
People from Baxian Residence saved him.
We still don't know the location of the Longevity fruit and the Healer's case still remains unresolved.
Now, this is truly complex and difficult to solve with many moving parts.
It seems that we must make another trip to the scene of the Healer's death.
Xiao Chun Hua, we are here!
Be careful!
Put me down over there.
Why is it so cold here?
This is an ice cave.
I never like it here.
I was locked in here for decades.
Only Cave Masters ever knew about this such place through inheritance.
Can only Cave Masters come here?
I am not even a member of Qianyue Sect.
You are not the first.
Who else?
Shangguan Qiu Yue! Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Blood? This can't be good! I should stop the bleeding first.
Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Brother Qiu Yue.
Hurry and wake up.
What wish do you have? I will make it come true for you.
Didn't you tell me that you will make my wishes come true?
I'm begging you, I'm begging you!
Will yourself to wake up. Quick!
I am begging you.
Did you awaken? How are you?
I already heard you.
I heard Xiao Chun Hua's wish.
I have decided to grant your wish.
Xiao Chun Hua, your new outfit is very pretty.
What is the situation we are in now for you to still talk about that.
Do you think I will die?
Can you stop talking?
It is only a small injury so I can heal myself.
Then hurry and heal yourself!
Since Zhen Qi consumes me from inside out,
I can't use my Kung Fu right now.
Then what should we do?
Do not worry, Xiao Chun Hua!
I will be fine in a few days.
A few days?
How can we stay here for a few days?
Are you cold?
I am not afraid of the cold.
Little Sister, you sure do care a great deal for me.
I'm not caring for you.
I am just afraid of you dying in front of me.
There is nothing here.
Aren't you afraid of starving to death?
However, it is the safest here.
If you
do not want to stay here,
there is a secret passageway to exist.
You can escape through there.
What do you like to eat?
As long as it is prepared by you,
I will eat it.
It sure is peaceful here.
It won't be good is we just barge in there, will it?
What are you afraid of? Fengming Mountain Manor leads the martial arts circle.
Right now, we came to investigate the Healer's death, so it's perfectly justifiable.
Isn't that right, Young Chief Master?
Young Chief Master?
Xiao Bai?
Husband!
Can you take the sword away first? I am scared.
[Chun Hua: A girl who had died in Sangtian village, was revived but lost her memory]
Chun Hua?
Young Master?
I remember the first time you met Miss Chun Hua,
it was at this place.
So everything that has happened, related to the key link in the death of the Healer,
the Healer, my father, and Miss Chun Hua.
They all have countless ties with the Longevity fruit.
If we make use of this opportunity and solve this riddle,
then the misunderstanding between you and Miss Chun Hua
will surely disappear.
Those who abandoned and left me,
I can't keep them anyway.
Right now, I would rather much cherish you all,
especially you.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' - Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫