''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
The Chuanqi Sect wants to exchange Miss Chun Hua for the Longevity Fruit.
Up until yesterday,
Gorge Master Fu still naively thought Fengming Mountain Manor wouldn't dare to do
such a shameless thing.
The Longevity fruit is fake.
I came here to stop you guys from falling into their trap.
They kidnapped Madam Yousi, you can kidnap me.
If you do not bring out Sisi, I will kill her!
The Longevity fruit should be left for those who truly need it.
We cannot tell everyone it is fake in order to keep it at Fengming Mountain Manor.
Between you and the martial arts circle, which one will Xiao Bai choose?
[Episode 25]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
I longingly remember that time in the very beginning, when you would always want to act flirtatiously with me.
I won't let go.
Unless...
you flirt with me, then my illness will be better.
I do not remember such a thing.
It is better to be a sister,
memories that you do not want to remember or past feelings that you do not want to feel,
can all be willed away.
You can choose to not remember everything, but I cannot.
I must be responsible for helping you remember.
The Longevity fruit was something we initially concocted.
It's simply because we wanted to destroy it in front of everyone.
Did you already know about this?
If you do not want me to know, then I won't.
If you think I knew, then I must pretend that I knew.
You haven't uttered a single sentence with sincere words.
The Longevity fruit is everywhere.
Everyone is trying to get it.
So, besides the trap for Fengming Mountain Manor,
do you have any other traps?
Are you here to protect me or are you here to see the commotion that the Longevity fruit is creating?
Or are you here to see how many people are willing to die or kill for this fruit?
Or to see how many idiots you can fool?
Xiao Chun Hua, you no longer believe me.
So it does not matter if I confirm or deny it, I will always be in the wrong.
Then just tell me the truth.
Xiao Chun Hua is becoming obsessive again.
Actually, the whole world has these thrilling sights
because the greed of man makes it so.
However, my desire to protect you is real.
Well then, is Fu Lou's intent to protect Yousi, greed as well?
Or shall I say,
you have no feelings of greed?
Xiao Chun Hua have changed.
You are no longer like your past self.
The previous Xiao Chun Hua would every day only think about how to act flirtatiously with Xiao Bai and me.
Well, I suppose that you were warm-hearted, good, and kind, like a fool.
How is it that now, you do not believe anything?
In all actuality,
I came to this world as passionate as fire.
I wanted to find true love.
Regardless, in spite of everything, I wildly ran all the way toward my goal.
When I achieved my goal,
my heart,
I don't know how it has become cold.
It seems like you have also discovered that you are not like before.
I guess this is also a good thing.
The simple and pure Xiao Chun Hua is nice.
The deep and thinking Xiao Chun Hua is also nice.
Both are cute! I like them both.
Tomorrow, everything should come to light.
I encourage you to open your eyes wide to watch carefully.
Chun Hua, you...
Are you feeling better?
Let's elope.
In the past,
I was undoubtedly suspected of killing the Healer.
Why did you still take me into the Fengming Mountain Manor?
Since I was young, my father always taught me
that the Fengming Mountain Manor has the responsibility to the whole world's martial arts circle.
We must punish wicked people, get rid of evil, and support those small and weak.
Miss Chun Hua, you do not know martial arts.
Therefore, you would not possess murderous intent.
I even indiscriminately called you, Husband.
I brazenly and without reason returned to Fengming Mountain Manor with you.
You never kicked me out or found me to be a burden.
Miss Chun Hua, you are different from any of the girls I had met.
Although you may not have known any manners,
your heart was pure.
You were cute and warm-hearted.
I really liked you.
Moreover, you are still Hua Xiao Lei,
my fiancée.
I knew the skill of fake voices.
No one knew where I came from and I loved to make trouble.
You were constantly partial toward me.
You tolerated me.
At that time,
I really thought I obtained true love.
Chun Hua,
I will always accept you and protect you.
I really do not know what is wrong with me.
I didn't get what I wanted.
I got what I didn't want.
Xiao Bai,
Fu Luo trusts you so much.
You must promise to keep them safe tomorrow.
My father taught me that
it is my mission to maintain peace and justice in the martial arts world.
Father said...
Father taugh...
Father said,
"Those who think for the greater good will be granted the strength of the four seas;
otherwise, it is just speaking empty words."
Chun Hua says,
"If you cannot even hold a girl in your heart, how can you take care of the greater good?"
Nothing has changed.
You are still the Chun Hua I love.
This is such an obvious trap.
Only Fu Lou who is desperate for a cure would believe it,
but he still trusts and believes in you.
So Xiao Bai,
you must make sure they are safe tomorrow.
I want to hear you give me your words.
That is ignoring that the two of them are of the demon sects.
If they can be exchanged for peace in the pugilist world,
then their death will be worth it.
But what if...
What if it is not the Longevity fruit or Luosi,
but me whom you must be sacrificed to get the peace you want.
What would you choose?
I will not let that happen.
You always sound so confident about success.
Will he really come?
I am also not sure.
Young Chief Master Xiao.
Gorge Master Fu indeed came as planned.
A man honors his words.
I am the same.
Wait!
Young Chief Master Xiao.
Gorge Master Fu's Book of One's Crimes really is sincere.
According to the rules, the Longevity fruit
should belong to Gorge Master Fu.
Fu Lou! Don't you dare leave like this.
Stop! Fengming Mountain Manor
should honor the deal we have with Fu Lou.
Don't you dare think you will obtain the Longevity Fruit!
Don't you dare leave! Take the Longevity fruit!
Masters, please rest assured!
Fu Lou personally promised,
after this, he will offer his life as penance.
Thank you, Miss Chun Hua, for staying with me while I wait for my husband.
Madam Fu,
You are... Cave Master Shangguan?
This demeanor,
you must be Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Cave Master Shangguan,
why don't you have a nice chat with Miss Chun Hua?
I still need to check for why my husband is not back yet.
Why are you here?
I know that you are nervous, so I rushed here as soon as I could.
You are here only to see the commotion.
Of course, if there is commotion to be seen, that would be better.
But it would still be the best if I can take you back to  Qianyue Cave.
I really hate all of you who are so full of yourselves.
It sounds like Xiao Bai angered you once again.
Xiao Bai is like this because he wants to help the greater good.
Even if I am unhappy,
I must endure it alone.
- What about you?
- Me?
I can promise to not let you suffer.
So what are you here for?
Rest assured, Xiao Chun Hua! I will surely not intervene.
In order to ensure that Xiao Bai won't mess up when he sees me,
I will only observe from afar.
However, my Xiao Chun Hua,
just don't forget our bet!
Husband!
Sisi!
Here! Come and sit down.
You are home?
Look what I brought!
The Longevity fruit.
Did you go to the Longevity fruit meeting?
Did they make things hard for you?
They are willing to use the Longevity Fruit to save your life.
I know that Miss Chun Hua and Young Master Xiao
are both good people.
In the past, you always complained about how boring it was to be trapped in the gorge.
Once we cure the poison in your body,
we can go explore all the beautiful sights of the world.
We can also learn about all the food all over the world
and make it for you to eat. How does that sound?
I was just saying that casually.
Do you remember that?
Anything you say,
I remember them all.
Sisi, once I have talked things over with them,
I will come back to see you.
Fu Lou, your promise must be fulfilled.
When the night of the full moon comes,
after Sisi has consumed the Longevity fruit,
I will offer myself.
There is nothing to hide in my Book of One's Crimes.
Good!
All the names on this list
are people you have killed.
[Names of those killed by Fu Lou]
Fu Lou,
you petty man!
Why is my father's name not on this list?
I don't have a heart to repent for crimes,
but I would never lie.
You purposefully left out Feng Qian Wei.
- I did not kill him.
- You are lying.
As for you, it seems like you still don't know
that your good father was the one who
killed the Healer.
How can that be?
He slipped into Baxian Residence but failed to locate the Longevity fruit.
He was worried that his motives would be revealed,
so he killed the healer.
Unfortunately, I bore witness to this by chance.
I do not believe you.
Gorge Master, I
don't really care whether you believe it.
As for the person who killed Feng Qian Wei,
I also know his identity.
Fu Lou, do you dare continue to shamefully boast?
Even if you didn't kill Feng Qian Wei, the number of deaths written on paper,
how many can you truly face?
There is someone who can support my claim that I am not lying.
This time, I will do what you ask.
However, you must promise me that you won't harm any additional person.
I agree.
Don't!
Do not make any sudden movements.
We don't want Miss Chun Hua to get hurt.
Speak!
Feng Chen Wei,
did he once lie to his daughter and kidnapped you only to bring you to me?
Fu Lou has committed innumerable murders all his life,
but since I earnestly obtained the Longevity fruit to protect Sisi,
I will most definitely not lie or miss a single person.
In a few hours, my wife will consume the Longevity fruit.
After Fengming Mountain Manor agrees to her protection,
I will naturally come and face my crimes!
Miss Chun Hua, I have something to ask of you.
As a man, I must take responsibility for my actions.
I beg of you to protect my Sisi.
Take her away!
All right. I promise you.
This is the token of the Chuanqi Sect.
You can pass this on to Shangguan Qiu Yue, or you can give it...
give it to Xiao Bai
as long as it can protect Sisi.
[Order] (Chuanqi Sect's command seal)
But didn't you also promise your wife to protect her?
I am begging you,
please be by my wife's side always.
A major incident like the Book of One's Crimes,
how can you not invite Qianyue Sect to observe?
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
Young Chief Master Xiao, the perpetrator is in front of us.
Be careful of those who secretly try to reap the benefits.
Fu Lou has repented for his sins in exchange for the Longevity fruit.
He is heading toward the path of goodness.
I hope Cave Master Shangguan
will observe without interruption.
Young Chief Master Xiao, I was disrespectful.
Fengming Mountain Sect had honorable intentions.
I, Shangguan Qiu Yue, admire that.
Gorge Master Fu is really open and honest about his crimes.
I almost thought you were also a member of Fengming Mountain Manor.
Of course, Gorge Master Fu is also open about killing people,
so there shouldn't be any innocent people who died for nothing.
What do you think Chief Leng?
I am also curious about the names on the Book of One's Crimes.
Then tell me, who killed my father?
Miss Feng is very expressive.
The person who killed your father is definitely not me amongst the people here.
You are all too impatient.
This takes place under the full moon, yet the sun is still out.
I will not stay here to play with you guys anymore.
When the full moon is out, I will come to observe.
Gorge Master Fu,
can you tell me
who killed my father?
Miss Feng, what more can you discuss with this murderer?
Fu Lou, you committed so many crimes.
I have so many disciples who died at your hands.
Your life is forfeited. Go!
Someone once begged me not to harm any additional person
but if you all want to die,
I won't stop you.
Miss Chun Hua,
I heard my husband's voice.
They are...
They are just negotiating.
When the full moon comes—
I know.
It isn't a negotiation.
They are out to kill.
Miss Chun Hua.
I want to be by his side.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking it's eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through the fickleness of love  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on, there's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of the spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫