''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless, treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
Xiao Bai, there is no right or wrong in love.
Persist in love's intention, don't get caught up in confusion.
Feelings are like rowing upstream. Advance or be left behind.
I want to be a big sea, a tsunami that can engulf you.
You gave him a chess piece, and watched the stars with him.
In reality, the space you take up in his heart
is no more important than the Fengming Saber itself.
The Longevity fruit will be auctioned to all who wish.
Bishui City is surely welcoming a rain of terror this time.
[Episode 15]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Xiao Bai's heartbeat is so erratic.
Why is mine so stable?
When the owner meets with the one that he loves,
the Fengming Saber will emit the sound of heartbeats.
Miss Chun Hua,
I like you.
In my lifetime, my heart was never touched by any girl other than you.
I was thinking
that in the future, I want to hear you call me "Husband."
I finally accomplished it.
However, why don't I feel excited?
Is love like this?
It could be I'm not fully prepared.
It also seems a little cliché.
This confession... I accept it.
However, I order you
to earnestly abide by these words.
Husband.
Future Young Mistress Xiao, only a few days until the Longevity Fruit can be obtained.
You must be so excited that you can't sleep.
You must be the one who wants it.
I'm not interested in this sort of common object.
However, since there's something lively to look at,
I can't miss it for no reason.
Then aren't you interested in immortality?
What about you? Are you interested?
What's the meaning of immortality?
To me, having an unforgettable romance that is etched into your soul
is much better than living without dying.
It's pitiful that this thing called love,
has a hundred ways in which it can fall apart.
In the end, the only thing left in your hands is emptiness.
The only use it has, is to allow bystanders to see
a ridiculous performance.
What do you understand about love?
Then why did you come to Fengming Mountain Manor?
I came because I wanted to come.
After little Chun Hua stopped calling me Older Brother, she really became more impudent.
Aren't you afraid of me getting into a rage and immediately killing Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai already achieved Fengming Saber's last move.
Being able to kill him or not still can't be determined.
You seem to care so much about him.
Unfortunately, Xiao Chun Hua doesn't know where she is in his heart.
She is incomparable to the nation's great causes and justice in the martial arts circles.
Now, she is even incomparable to that hereditary Fengming Saber.
If Xiao Chun Hua doesn't believe it,
then we'll wait and see who's right.
Chief Leng, I haven't seen you for quite a while.
Same here!
I heard Chief Leng presides over martial arts circles on behalf of the young sect master.
Why would you appear here?
Isn't it all because of some hypocrites?
They keep saying to be chivalrous but each harbors evil thoughts.
I have no choice but to do some housecleaning
in order to stabilize the general conditions for the young sect master.
It's a joke! You operate under the false pretext of the young sect master's behalf to murder allies.
Does the young sect master know this?
As long as you don't speak,
how would the young master know?
Chief Leng wants to kill to silence people.
- Let's see if you have this capability!
- I'm honored.
Old friends meet each other, it's inevitable to have some exchanges with each other.
Chief Feng, farewell!
Old Friend, Old Friend, we've known each other since childhood.
Such a pity that there's only one Longevity fruit.
Master, Feng Qianwei died from being poisoned by dandelion.
Go and let Mister Shi
prepare a first-rate coffin.
Understood.
[Hibiscus Pastry]
[Bishui City]
Chief Suifeng.
Elder Brother Guo.
Chief Tao Ran, nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you! Let's go inside.
Let's go inside.
[Tea]
[Bishui City]
Valued Customer, please have a look at our new tea leaves.
They all came for the Longevity fruit.
Keep following the movements of these people.
This time, I will certainly obtain the Longevity fruit.
Yes.
Shangguan Qiu Yue.
Longevity fruit.
I noticed you didn't find it after searching everywhere.
It certainly is more interesting than the Longevity fruit itself.
I'm a carefree soul so I'm simply uninterested in these things.
Are you truly uninterested in the Longevity fruit?
It looks like
I have to find your weakness.
[Bishui Inn]
Customers, it's not a coincidence. There is only one room left.
Look! It's all because you're being difficult.
You wouldn't travel together with Young Lord Qin, then just let them take advantage.
First come, first serve. Willing to gamble, then should accept loss.
From appearance, you don't seem like siblings.
You must be a young married couple.
Then you don't need two rooms.
Room number five.  Help yourselves!
Miss Caicai, we should stay in the same room.
However, I recall you're a light sleeper.
I'm afraid you can't have someone with you.
I have to learn to be considerate.
No matter what, I am your husband now.
Miss Chun Hua, this is the room for me and Brother Qin.
The journey was long.
I'm so worn out that I can cry.
It's a good thing that we traveled together.
Brother Xiao, "fragrance always stays in the hand that gives the rose." (helping others makes you happy).
Do not waste my sacrifice!
I don't know where Brother Qin learned these little tricks.
He can actually make a real flower appear.
Xiao Bai, why don't you put it on my hair? (lit. my head)
Isn't this the one that I gave you?
This trip is extremely dangerous; thus, I decided it was better if I keep it with me.
Do you want to use this as a talisman?
Then you didn't protect it very well.
It is my fault for not treasuring Miss Chun Hua's sincerity.
In the future, I will surely be more careful.
Wait!
Watch!
Does this look like Yue Lao's (Chinese god of love and  marriage) red string?
Yes.
Xiao Bai, put your chess piece in the middle.
Look! I formed only one star.
This white chess piece is also a star.
These two stars together
will be called, "one heart, one goal."
It's late.
Why don't we go and check out our surroundings?
Might as well! Anyway, we will have plenty of time to rest later.
Miss Chun Hua.
Brother Qin will also be in this room.
Chief Suifeng.
Young Master Xiao. Miss Chun Hua.
Have you settled the matters regarding your daughter?
Do you have time to stroll around Bishui City?
Miss Chun Hua, you don't know.
My young daughter and Tianxiong Sect's disciples quarreled on the way to Bishui City.
Chief Suifeng, if you need someone to mediate between the two sects,
I am certainly willing.
I don't want to cause problems for Leader Xiao. Don't dare, don't dare!
I will go end this matter.
- Goodbye.
- Chief Suifeng, please stay.
Master Suifeng,
do you know why Leader Xiao came to Bishui City?
Leader Xiao is a busy man.
I wouldn't dare to guess.
Okay, then I will tell Chief Suifeng the truth.
This time, Leader Xiao came to Bishui City himself.
Not for anything else,
but solely for the Longevity fruit auction.
I think... Chief Suifeng
also came because of this news, didn't you?
People like you call yourselves a righteous sect of the martial arts circle.
Clearly you all want the Longevity fruit, but you are full of lies and hypocrisy!
Chief Suifeng, no one is a saint and faultless.
Accepting criticism and making amends is better than making excuses for your mistakes.
Rather than interrogating me, you should worry about yourselves.
In the last few days, Chief Leng was hiding during the day and going out late at night.
He behaves suspiciously.
Maybe he covets the Longevity fruit more than anyone else.
Nonsense!  My dad came to assist Leader Xiao.
How dare you slander!
Also,
Eldest Miss Feng, I fear you may not know yet.
Yesterday, I coincidentally ran into your dad.
Did you already meet my dad?
I wonder why he is staying in Bishui City.
Don't mind that old guy.
We know both your fathers very well.
They are definitely not evil people.
[Bishui Inn]
Since Xiao Bai gave me a flower,
I will return the gesture with an even prettier one.
Miss, take a look at the flowers.
- The flowers look pretty good! I'll take all of them.
- Wait a moment!
I saw this one first.
- How presumptuous of you!
- Stop!
This is Her Ladyship's friend.
Why is she outside Chuanqi Gorge?
- Miss Chun Hua.
- Lady Yousi.
Madam,
I chose that flower first.
Thank you.
If Miss Chun Hua wants to enjoy flowers,
you can come to Chuanqi Gorge.
You don't need to buy already plucked ones.
Who dares to casually go to your Chuanqi Gorge?
Thank you, Madam, for your invitation.
- But...
- I plan to go back soon.
You do not need to worry.
My husband is not there.
Then...
Okay.
[Chuanqi Gorge]
This is the newly brewed rose tea that is good for complexion.
Miss, give it a try.
After you left the gorge, Her Ladyship often talks about you.
She said she worries that you and Gorge Master will have another misunderstanding.
How is that possible? Gorge Master Fu is such a good person.
It's good you're willing to forgive him.
I heard,
there is a Longevity fruit auction.
Is this true?
This Longevity fruit created too much turmoil.
Gorge Master Fu treats you this well.
Why do you still seek immortality?
My husband must have done a lot of wrong things to you.
I apologize to you on his behalf.
These things are all because of me.
My body cannot endure much longer.
He wants to obtain the Longevity fruit
to help cure my sickness.
I tried persuading him.
However, he said that if there is a tiny bit of hope,
he will not give up.
I am going out for a walk.
Who is it?
Before, I could not figure out
why Fu Lou planted beside Chuanqi Gorge
this sea of flowers.
Thanks to Xiao Chun Hua, I now know.
It turns out that it was for Yousi.
I don't know if Xiao Bai would do this for you.
Xiao Bai may not understand romance
but it's enough to have me in his heart.
Have you in his heart?
You and Fengming Saber, which is more important?
He has yet to choose.
Are you this certain?
You're not even my biological brother so why are you bothering with all this?
Besides, you no longer need Fengming Saber's Xin Fa.
Now, I am useless to you.
I indeed have nothing for you to do.
Yet I still want you to stay,
but I don't know a good way to do this.
Or do you want me to directly kill you?
Just let me go!
After I am wed to Xiao Bai,
I will be at ease to settle down as a virtuous wife.
I'll really, truly know my place and not cause any trouble.
- Shangguan Qiu Yue, have you gone crazy?
- You only care about getting married.
Miss Chun Hua!
Quietly wait for her to come over.
- Did she come again?
- What do you want to do?
Her Ladyship personally invited Miss Chun Hua.
Don’t think of doing anything to her.
This young girl holds a secret about the Longevity fruit.
Our doing this is all for Her Ladyship's sake.
We should take her to Gorge Master Fu thoroughly interrogate her.
- But,... how about Her Ladyship?
- That's easy to handle.
Just tell Her Ladyship that she was tired of enjoying flowers.
Tell her that she left the gorge.
Then you must proceed with extreme caution.
You must not let Her Ladyship find out.
We searched the entire city but found no clue where Miss Chun Hua is.
- Were there any signs of a struggle?
- None.
I said earlier that we shouldn't take her here.
This is only asking for trouble. Moreover, she...
Miss Chun Hua must be lost again.
Why don't we search outside the city?
She is over there! Catch her!
When will Chun Hua and Qiu Yue end?
You know to look for me when you encounter danger.
Not bad!
So it is Chief Leng.
So it is Chief Qin.
Why do you have the leisure and interest to come to Bishui City?
To tell you the truth, I have received news
of the Longevity fruit’s auction here in Bishui City.
Therefore, I would like to have a try.
This auction is attended by both bad and good people.
It is rare that people from the righteous sects are participating.
It was also only after young sect master’s word of caution
that I was on guard against those lawless people.
Chief Qin, you should be extra careful.
This Longevity fruit isn’t an evil object.
You, yourself, know of its advantages.
So do I and everyone else.
I have honestly and scrupulously prepared the silver,
and honestly and scrupulously came for the auction.
I haven’t done anything that will give me a guilty conscience.
What do I have to be afraid of?
Then I wish Chief Qin all the best in your great ambition.
I hope they’ll be realized.
Gorge Master.
Last night, I followed Leng Ying’s tracks
and found him…
- He really is bold!
- However, after he murdered Feng Qianwei,
he unexpectedly vanished.
Soon afterwards, Shangguan Qiu Yue arrived.
I am incompetent and was forced to leave first.
This old, useless trash.
Someone must support him in the background.
[Qianyue Cave]
You’re very quiet.
It's so unlike you.
Xiao Bai.
Older Brother, you saved me?
“When will Chun Hua and Qiu Yue end?”
When you meet danger, you know to call brother.
But after you awake, you call Xiao Bai.
It seems that you still don’t consider brother very important.
How can't I take Older Brother to heart?
Whenever I am in trouble, Older Brother will always save me.
Words can't express how grateful I am to you.
Is that so?
Brother only worries that Younger Sister
is wrong about him.
Thank you, Older Brother! But you don’t have to worry about me.
Xiao Bai is full of righteousness, straightforward, and upright.
From when I lost my memory till now, he always protects me.
I'm definitely not wrong about him.
I didn't know that your Xiao Bai
is a better person
compared to his father.
He will at least be better than you.
I was missing a long time. Xiao Bai and the rest must be very anxious at the inn.
Older Brother, why don't you let me return to Bishui City first?
Don't you want to watch the spectacle caused by the Longevity fruit?
- Why don't we go together, all right?
- No.
"Immortality is not as important as love."
This is what Little Sister said.
Even though I have never had
a taste of love before,
However,
the relationship between you and Xiao Bai
isn’t as you described, passionate
and forever remembered, is it?
Where’s my bracelet?
Therefore, I have to properly test that
young master of the martial arts circle on your behalf.
What are you planning to do to Xiao Bai?
Don’t you worry, Little Sister!
It’s only a small game.
You just have to accompany me
and watch the show.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a  pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness that I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫