''A Girl with a Head full of Love'' by Singer: Zhao Lusi
♫  Chivalry feelings are everywhere  ♫
♫  Throughout the ages, the sun and moon shine brightly  ♫
♫  The phoenix's whistling cry rises, one sword can dominate the mundane world  ♫
♫  Oh my, what a flamboyant way of speaking  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫   This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  I have a head full of love  ♫
♫  Even the winds and frost over a thousand miles are all romantic  ♫
♫  I only want my life's one true love  ♫
♫  I want a male lead to hold a peerless treasured sword in his hand  ♫
♫  The story I want is very sweet, very sweet  ♫
♫  The storyline I want must be atypical  ♫
♫  I've always been simple-minded  ♫
♫  Young Disciples, the secular world is touching and unrestrained  ♫
♫  Joining hands with the hero in white, standing shoulder-to-shoulder, from north to south, all wars will cease  ♫
♫  Swords and sabers are like a dream  ♫
♫  I'm meeting a lover after dusk under a willow tree  ♫
♫  Right or wrong, anyone can determine his own fate  ♫
♫  This is the world, I'm rushing into  ♫
♫  Jack Sue, male chauvinist, Mama's boy, go away, go away  ♫
♫  Someone self-restrained, a scheming man, someone evil, want them, want them all  ♫
♫  Longevity fruit, calamity of a hundred flowers, right and wrong are entangled, very good  ♫
♫  Phoenix's sword, silk of affection, the sect's unique secret skill, proud, proud  ♫
[Love Better Than Immortality]
According to what they said, this shopkeeper's wife had a peculiar smell on her.
However, contrary to expectations, it was not the smell of perfume but of food.
I said I would protect you, Xiao Chun Hua.
So you weren't injured at all. Have you been lying to me this whole time?
- It's simply that I already recovered.
- So you've been lying to me for three days.
Spread the news of Qianyue Cave's armed rebellion and
that Shangguan Qiu Yue has been seriously wounded,
to throw them into disorder.
- So did you do this to make them fear you?
- Yes.
Older Brother, but
what I really want is stability, rather than safety.
[Episode 32]
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
Men's clothes are much better! I don't need to change to become beautiful.
It's so annoying that there are so many frivolous women.
Miss Leng.
Wait! You come here now.
Is this a special trip just to get hit?
I provoked and angered Miss Leng yesterday.
I'm guilty of a crime for which death can't even atone.
Did you think that I'd forgive you after one small sentence of an apology?
No, no! For this reason, I specially prepared a gift for you
to ask for your forgiveness.
It's not much but I hope that we can be of one heart.
Please kindly accept my small gift, Miss Leng!
Do you like it?
Who wants your raggedy clothes? Get out!
Miss Leng—
[Wind Listening Pavilion]
- Miss Feng.
Young Chief Master.
How was your investigation of the restaurant?
I broke through a door and a window at the back.
I found this. Take a look!
You broke in through a window? That's quite unexpected.
Before, you would regard entering through the back door is beneath you.
Since things reached this stage, desperate times call for desperate measures.
This...
This is an account book with records for all Baxian Residence's visitors.
You have fallen short of expectations.
Previously, Shangguan Qiu Yue told me to kill you but I didn't have the heart to do it.
As a result, you have provoked and attracted this kind of disaster.
I... I left in such a hurry so I couldn't check carefully.
In addition, I thought all people from Fengming Mountain Manor were decent and upright.
- How could they enter by breaking a window?
- You saw the ways of the world and became accustomed to it.
However, you still hold a pipe dream that good people won't be too hard on you.
Originally, I took a fancy to you in the brothel, but to no avail.
Master! I won't do this again.
Finally, we can emerge and bask in the sun.
I'm so happy.
It seems that we also have done this before.
Last time, you were so happy rolling around in the meadow.
Were you maybe a loach in your previous life?
Then, let's say I were a loach (river bottom fish),
then what were you?
Well, with you, Xiao Chun Hua, entwined so closely with me right now,
if you were a loach, then I was a white loach.
What kind of loaches are white?
Although we are both loach spirits,
I need to attract people's attention a bit more.
This way, the flirty loaches will take the initiative and flirt with me.
Since everything has been meticulously designed by you,
then I'll just do and enjoy everything as I like.
Such a beautiful day
and such a handsome brother!
In the future, I hope we'll be able to spend every day like this.
We will!
Then Big Bther, that's settled!
I remember that you like dandelions the most.
I still remember you said,
dandelions have the most exuberant spirit.
But now, I don't like dandelions.
Why not?
Because now, I like the lotus flower.
It's beautiful when it blooms, and it lives so happily.
It opens and closes broadly.
It has a brilliant life!
You are becoming more and more brave.
You actually dare to make fun of me.
Brother, I recently felt very suffocated on the mountain.
Why don't we go down the mountain for a walk?
All right.
I hope she won't cut the clothes into pieces but just throw them out.
Qin Liufeng, one should have a goal in life.
Just in case... I haven't prepared anything just in case.
Miss Leng, although these clothes are simple,
when you wear them, it seems one's heart and soul were poured into them.
That's too erotic.
What? Do I look bad?
Beautiful!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
That's right! You're not in a dream.
Miss Leng!
Now, shouldn't we reverse our roles
to have you call me "Little Husband"?
Don't poke fun at me!
We must tend to important matters. Look at this first!
[Baxian City Restaurant Account Book]
Account book?
It would be the best to return to Baxian City and observe for a bit.
Then I will go with you.
Miss Feng and the Young Chief Master seem truly happy for you.
I am as well.
Brother, what if we're on the street without any careful consideration, and Xiao Bai and the rest see us?
Have you forgotten? I know how to change my appearance.
- This child is really cute.
- Father!
- Father?
- Good boy!
Where did you go just now?
Why did you leave me over there all on my own?
Who did you disguise yourself as?
A person I bumped into on the street not too long ago.
Let's go!
That little boy just now really looked like you as if he were your son.
My son will certainly be handsomer than him.
Father!
Father, why didn't you wait for me?
Why did you come over here?
Mother said you're not allowed to go out again and meet women.
Who is she?
If you dare to say that I went out,
I'll cut off your tongue.
Dare you? I'm going to tell mother.
How can you tell Mother without a tongue?
You're not my father!
B*stard, wait until I return and tell my father about this!
He'll come and beat you!
You see? My son just ran away.
- What did you want to do with him?
- You liked him, didn't you?
I was going to take him back to Qianyue Cave to become our son
and give him some medicine for him to fully forget the past.
You psycho! How can you steal someone's son?
Fine! I shouldn't steal a son.
Then in the future, we should have many sons.
We should go over to that street.
Also, get rid of your mustache.
[Baxian Residence]
Young Chief Master, all is safe and sound.
- There's nothing unusual.
- Let's wait and observe a bit more.
Everyone, be careful!
Watch out!
Li Yu?
[Baxian Residence]
Could I have a word with you in private?
You all can go first.
Li Yu, Baxian Residence already has so much medicine.
- Why are you still carrying in these?
- The Longevity fruit isn't inside these trunks.
I was just casually asking but if you don't want to tell me, then forget it.
Miss, it isn't that I don't want to tell you.
I just feel angry when it's brought up.
We were relayed some news today, a major issue occurred in Qianyue Cave.
The cave leaders caused an armed rebellion
along with Fu Lou's Chuanqi Gorge disciples.
They severely wounded Shangguan Qiu Yue.
What?
Can you explain more about what you just said?
I heard that Shangguan Qiu Yue has disappeared now.
For the remnants of the troops, both sides suffered heavy casualties.
However, after Master Bu'er heard this, he was extremely happy.
He even said, this would be a good business opportunity.
He instructed me to purchase all medicinal materials in the entire city.
He said when it's time, he can sell them at a higher price.
He'll even rip off the Devil himself.
Really!
Is this news conclusive?
If Master Bu'er said it from his own mouth, then it is certainly beyond doubt.
After this news, the one by Shangguan Qiu Yue's side,
how was Miss Chun Hua doing then?
I heard no news of her; however, I think if Shangguan Qiu Yue is missing,
then the others are not that much better off.
Young Chief Master.
I must go inside now.
I will wrap it for you.
Surely it's safer being in the store than on the street.
I shouldn't run into Xiao Bai here.
What are the two of you looking for?
Shopkeeper, do you have any jade pendants?
Have you any pendants for lovers?
A pair!
I have some that come in pairs. Follow me!
Please take a look.
Brother, look! This one has your name engraved on the front.
Xiao Chun Hua has great eyesight.
All right, I'll take this one.
Let's go!
Wait, wait!
You haven't paid me yet.
Pay him!
I... didn't bring any money.
Why don't you sell it to me now, and I'll send you money later?
Small shops cannot sell on credit, you should just come back later.
I just want this one.
Young Master, if you really want this one, then I can save it for you half a day.
I want it now.
You have no money. Do you want just to rob it?
- That works, too.
- Would you really dare steal in broad daylight?
Do you want to kill me and steal my money?
Shopkeeper, calm down!
I won't sell it anymore!
Shopkeeper, my brother's head is not quite right.
Don't argue with him. I'll pay, I'll pay!
Oh, no! Oh no!
I...
- I also don't have any money.
- You just said my head is not quite right.
Your ears are even better than a rabbit's.
Well, your head isn't quite right, either.
Otherwise, why would you be with me?
Fine, fine! You're always right.
- Let's go!
- No way.
I must buy the jade pendant that you picked out for me today.
Well, all right! I'll go back to grab some money.
You must be a good boy.
I'll go now.
[Baxian Residence]
If even Shangguan Qiu Yue has disappeared without a trace,
then others won't be that much better off.
Do you see? This is your sorry fate for leaving me!
Young Chief Master!
Might as well!
Since you chose to follow and be with the Devil,
this serves you right!
Seeing willows by the river and spring flowers deepen my sadness.
Even as our hair turns grey, will we ever meet again?
Chun Hua, if you're lucky enough to survive,
after I kill Shangguan Qiu Yue with my own hands,
I will get even with you.
[Seeing willows by the river and spring flowers deepen my sadness. Even as our hair turns grey, will we ever meet again?]
Is everything you said really all true?
Although I was lucky enough to escape death, I've lost all martial arts skill.
Now, I'm just a good-for-nothing.
If you don't believe me, you can call Shangguan Qiu Yue
here to kill me.
I also have no way to fight back.
Miss Chun Hua, we are cut from the same cloth.
So the last time you fled from Qianyue Cave, I purposely let you go.
Presumably, you know about this.
That was because you had other reasons.
I'm absolutely not some type of daredevil
but I fought desperately in Qianyue Cave just because I wanted Ye Yan to understand my feelings for her.
If you're suspicious of my behavior, then you can go now.
I believe what you've said.
Yes, I hate Shangguan Qiu Yue; however, no matter how much I hate him,
there's nothing I can do to him.
There's no way I can take advantage of him as you can,
because he'll achieve his goal of uniting the martial arts world very soon.
If he leaves you, he will not suffer any loss.
Miss Chun Hua,
actually, you are very similar to me.
Your love for Shangguan Qiu Yue is just like mine for Ye Yan.
So I really don't want you to become like me
to trust the wrong person
to finally end up with a tragic of sorry fate.
Then is Master Bu'er diagnosing and treating him now?
Today, Li Yu called for Master Bu'er to come and I wasn't able to decline.
However, the clues we found before all point to Baxian Residence.
If Master Shi is truly a member of Baxian Residence,
then he might want to further hurt the Young Chief Master.
We should go there right now then.
Wait!
Isn't that Miss Chun Hua?
It's her!
Hold on! How about this?
You two go to Baxian Residence and I'll go to find out how she feels now.
That also works!
Miss Chun Hua!
Qin Liufeng?
What are you doing here?
We've been investigating the case of the Healer and Longevity fruit in Baxian City.
However, our results fell short of our expectations.
Miss Chun Hua,
how have you been lately? I heard that Shangguan Qiu Yue—
Don't bring him up!
With the rebellion in Qianyue Cave, you must be homeless, don't you?
Indeed, I don't know where I should go.
The Young Chief Master, he...
misses you all the time.
I already broke up with Xiao Bai.
If I return and see everyone, it'll be so embarrassing.
Miss Chun Hua, what if I told you
that the Young Chief Master has fallen sick and bedridden from missing you so much?
He's such a calm, cool-headed person.
I don't believe you!
Miss Chun Hua, it's absolutely true.
After the Young Chief Master heard of the Qianyue Cave rebellion,
he was so worried about you that he threw up blood and fainted.
He's in a coma now.
How could that happen?
He misses you day and night, and longs for your return.
Miss Chun Hua, you are the only one
who can save the Young Chief Master from his extreme misery now.
Please do me a favor! Return and take a quick look at him.
Please trust me!
What are you two doing?
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
He was plotting something horrible for you just now.
That's none of your business.
Xiao Chun Hua, it seems that you're suddenly in an awful mood.
Still all thanks to you.
It seems that he wasn't plotting something horrible for you.
It's that you two fall in love with each other.
It seems I ruined a good thing for you.
Yes, you have. So what?
Return with me!
Shangguan Qiu Yue!
[Baxian Residence]
There's no need for you two to panic.
The Young Chief Master's pulse is stable now.
Master Bu'er, did you discover why the Young Chief Master threw up blood and fainted?
He has no injuries to his internal organs.
Presumably, he's simply anxious about his wife.
For a while, he was in an alarmed, bewildered state of mind because his internal energy was diverted.
Consequently, his energy is upsurging.
He just needs to rest more.
After his internal energy returns to normal, then he'll wake up.
That's good. Thank you.
I asked Li Yu to make this calming soup just now.
- I'll feed it to him.
- No need, Master Bu'er.
What do you mean by this, Miss Feng?
This calming soup is a medication that makes people calm, foolish, and ignorant.
However, Young Chief Master only needs rest right now.
No one neglected him.
- I'll give him some now.
- Young Chief Master is a martial arts person.
I think he will wake soon on his own.
We won't inconvenience you any longer.
Miss, although it's just a love-sickness,
yet if anything else happens,
he will suffer real harm and fall seriously ill.
I cannot afford to bear this burden.
Wouldn't you agree, Miss Feng?
The Young Chief Master is awaken.
I am sorry. I did not mean to.
Are you feeling okay, Young Chief Master?
I am fine.
This is Baxian Residence.
Thank you for your care of my health but I still have important things to do.
I need to talk to you guys about something.
Are you awake?
- Why are you here? Where is Miss Chun Hua?
- Leng Ning!
What is going on with Miss Chun Hua?
I...
I indeed saw her.
She is safe.
Do not worry!
That's good.
Li Yu, that boy, definitely cooked and burnt the medicine again.
I will check on it. I'll go and check.
Since you're awake, let's return to  Fengming Mountain Manor first.
Sure!
[Qianyue Cave]
Shangguan Qiu Yue, let me go!
What do you want?
I should be asking you, shouldn't I?
Xiao Chun Hua made her big brother wait at the jewelry shop.
I told the manager to engrave your name on the jade pendant.
I just wanted to make you happy.
However, after coming out,
I saw you fooling around with the  people from Fengming Mountain.
Then I truly disappointed my brother.
Xiao Bai has gone,
and Qin Liufeng came.
What medication did he give you that you'd treat me this way?
Treat you this way?
Every day I smile and look only at you.
But you just play around with my mind every day, is this what you wanted?
Shangguan Qiu Yue, what you want is someone you can control
- but I am a living being!
- What did he say to you?
He just told me everything you have done,
from start to finish.
Silly Sister, you have been manipulated by him.
Qin Liufeng is from Fengming Mountain.
He certainly has a lot of resentment toward me.
Big Brother, you sure are confident.
It's Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai still misses you.
So he used such a low tactic to come between us.
He doesn't have any tolerance,
unlike a martial arts leader, let alone deserving you.
So are the tactics you used any better?
I am not like him.
I just want to be good to you and Xiao Bai will only hurt you.
Brother, even at a time like this,
you still worry about my relationship with the people of Fengming Mountain Manor.
It is such a shame!
I wasn't told these things by Xiao Bai or Qin Liufeng.
It was Gu Wan.
Timing & subtitles brought to you by the L∞Ve Team @ Viki.com
''The Unfinished Moment'' by Singer: Li Hongyi
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  It's a time for accidental appearances  ♫
♫  It's a broken promise of spring, summer, autumn and winter  ♫
♫  It's the full moon reflected on water, blinking its eye  ♫
♫  Seeing through love's fickleness  ♫
♫  It's the touching melody of a fast-beating heart  ♫
♫  It's such a pity for not stepping forward  ♫
♫  The peach blossom valley without you  ♫
♫  Is not as lovely as it used to be  ♫
♫  Even admiring the freshness and beauty of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  Can't compare to seeing you for just a fleeting moment  ♫
♫  A brief instance determined forever  ♫
♫  It's hard to walk on. There's even no one to argue with  ♫
♫  Sealing up half of my memories in this place  ♫
♫  Leaving another half to be changed by time  ♫
♫  The loneliness I’m fated to have is difficult to put into words  ♫
♫  How I wish that you could see it  ♫
♫  Trying my best to pick up all the shattered fragments of spring flowers and autumn moon  ♫
♫  For you, I pieced together the predetermined storyline  ♫
♫  That passing moment that we missed  ♫
♫  Yet this insatiable longing seems like it will go on for years  ♫
♫  The falling snow and blossoming flowers carpeted the ground  ♫
♫  I left behind distinct traces from loving you  ♫
♫  The brightness of the moon changes as the years press on  ♫
♫  Yet how can you still not see it?  ♫