♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 9=
Well done, Xiao Mei.
The hot spring is a perfect idea.
Since the spring can wash away
our memory,
it should work for him, too.
Anyway,
Rongrong looks like a man,
a real one.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing but some funny things.
What have you done, Jiang Mengmeng?
I don't know.
(Secret Passage Next to Spa)
What is it?
It's a secret passage!
Your high...
Mengmeng, good job!
Maybe, it's because I'm the protagonist.
Wait.
It doesn't make sense.
Why did Sang Luo build a secret passage
next to her spa?
If anyone who comes here finds it,
it will be the way out?
I guess maybe even Sang Luo herself
doesn't know the existence of it.
Why?
Let me tell you a story.
Listen up.
Thirty years ago,
the world was in chaos,
and people lived in danger.
So,
many families would build
a secret passage like this,
to meet the need of emergency.
If I'm right,
this passage was built thirty years ago
when Sang Luo was just a kid.
This passage
must be built by its former owner.
But you are a prin...
I mean, Rongrong,
how did you know what happened
thirty years ago?
I...
That's not the point.
The point is that
we can escape
through this secret passage.
Alright.
Tomorrow evening,
most of the servants will go to help for
the Blood Moon Tactics.
Rongrong,
you distract them.
And the three of us
will bring the girls here.
Be careful.
You too.
- Where was I last night?
- Hey, you!
Give us a hand.
Coming.
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry.
This one, nail this on.
Alright.
Wrong position.
To the left.
The left.
Why are you two just standing there?
We are short of men there.
Get over there.
This way, move, move.
Xiao Ai,
if you had said you were afraid of the
dark earlier,
we would have brought you to the hot
spring before dark,
and you wouldn't have cried alone for
so long.
I‘m sorry. I'm too self-willed.
You have to waste your time on me.
Don't mention it.
We are friends.
Girls,
Let's go for the spa.
Come on.
Hurry.
Follow me.
- Wait for me.
- Hurry up.
What's this?
No time for explanation.
Let's go out first.
Go.
Go, go, go.
Mengmeng, aren't you leaving yet?
You go ahead.
I'll wait for her.
Let's go.
(Murong Chen.)
(Don't get spotted.)
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
Jiang Mengmeng
Let's get out of here.
Everyone else is gone. Let's go.
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
(Yi Chun Tavern)
I went everywhere,
acted tough talk soft.
It didn't work.
The officials said,
it's a cold case.
Of course, they have nothing to do with
what happened in the underworld.
Underworld?
So, what have you got?
Follow me.
We need to see someone.
Xiao Ai.
What's…
going on?
(Back hill of Sang's house)
Good word, Xiao Mei.
Xiao Mei, you betrayed us.
You are so naive, little girl.
Xiao Mei didn't betray you.
She worked for me from the beginning.
Yesterday came a girl
who had been crying.
She was placed in a small room.
I know where Sang Luo is.
I found Sang Luo's room last night.
Since the spring can wash away
our memory,
it should work for him, too.
So, Xiao Mei revealed Xiao Ai's location
on purpose,
and took us to Sang Luo's room
to listen to all her plans.
So, the purpose of taking the servant
into the hot spring
was to lead me to find this secret
passage?
The Blood Moon Tactics in the house
was also fake?
Of course.
I have to make it real.
If you didn't find the fake Blood Moon
Tactics in the house,
how could you believe all of these,
and come to this real one?
To be honest,
I admire you.
Although you were in danger,
you were not terrified,
and you planned to escape.
Brave girl.
But, that's it.
It's not over!
Don't you want 18 girls?
You know what?
There are only 17 girls here.
This one isn't a girl
disguised as a man.
He is a man.
Why are you selling me out at this time?
What's so funny?
Do you really think
I didn't know?
I lied about the number of girls needed,
little fool.
I only need 17 girls
in my tactics.
You're the only one I want
from beginning to end.
Look at your face.
Soft and smooth,
without any wrinkles.
Get your hand off me!
You sick old witch!
Go on.
I'll cut you first.
Why not start with another one,
beautiful lady?
She's so fickle.
Take her.
How about drawing lots?
Draw lots, draw lots.
I know.
You are stalling for time,
so you can live longer.
But
the moon doesn't wait.
Stop joking, Mr. System.
How can a protagonist die in a Dungeon?
Don't you usually like thunder and rain?
Why is there no cloud in the sky now?
Cut me first.
Leave her alone.
Yun Ya, help me.
Help.
Don't worry.
After you die,
your beauty will, through me,
exist in this world forever.
Considering short youth and rapid aging,
this is another kind of immortality.
Isn't it?
Stop it.
Sang Luo.
Go away.
Xi Qing.
Aren't you training?
Why are you here?
It's nothing.
I have to come
to stop you from making mistakes.
Sang Luo,
how can you be so vicious?
Me vicious?
I did all this for you.
Look at yourself,
and look at me.
When people see us,
they would think we are mother and son.
Never mind what others think.
We love each other. That's enough.
Not enough.
Oh, so,
Sang Luo did all of these
just to pick up a pretty boy.
This view of love is wrong.
I read a lot about cradle-snatcher love.
I know this.
Excuse me.
Listen up.
Miss Jiang's free love class.
Sang Luo,
I have to say it's your fault.
This boy loves you
despite age gap,
which proves that
youth and beauty mean nothing to him.
What did you call me?
Boy.
You should be about my age.
Little girl,
I'm about your father's age.
You should call me uncle.
What?
You don't look like
an uncle.
You look…
I'm forty-six.
Forty six?
Here is the thing.
I learned a skill
when I was young.
This skill
can make me look young forever.
I'm sorry. You two go on.
Sang Luo,
I told you that
I love you,
not your youthful face.
No matter you look young or not,
I'll keep loving you.
Don't you believe me?
Of course I believe you.
But I'm still afraid.
Everyone knows
getting old means
being hard to be loved.
When I see myself
getting old in the mirror,
while you
are still a teenager,
I really have no self-confidence.
Xi Qing,
please give me more time.
I have missed this chance.
I can wait for the next full moon.
It doesn't have to be in Qing Luo Town.
I can get other girls somewhere else.
Alright?
Sang Luo,
stop it.
Please be clear-headed.
My head is clear now,
never clearer.
Xi Qing,
you go for training.
One more time.
I only need  a training session.
When next time you finish your training,
I'll succeed.
Xi Qing,
what are you doing?
What have you done?
Since
you don't believe me,
I dug
my eyes out.
From this moment on,
I can never see you again,
and you will be beautiful forever in
my mind.
Never growing old.
No, I'm sorry.
Xi Qing,
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's so moving.
I wish I could meet such a man
in the future.
Xi Qing.
Are you still thinking about tonight?
Have all the girls gone home?
Yeah.
I've asked Song Che and Chang Kong
to walk them back.
Don't worry.
What is still bothering you?
I 'm thinking about
Sang Luo and Xi Qing.
So, it is true
that there are people who don't
care about appearance.
He just can't see anymore.
Murong Chen.
That's not funny.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
I mean,
true love can transcend all external,
such as appearance, money
and status.
But it doesn't have to be proved
in this extreme way.
But if not in this way,
how can you know that
you have love someone from the outside
to the inside?
Feel with your heart.
How?
If you really like a person,
even if you can't see her clearly,
you will be deeply attracted.
Just like I was unconsciously
attracted to you
before I recognized
you as Xiaomeng.
If one really loves a person,
he doesn't want to get anything
from her,
but to give anything to her
without reservation.
Even if you have something that
you don't want to do,
you will change
for her,
and make her things your own.
You will bind yourself to her,
and share her motions.
Laugh when she's happy,
and wipe when she's sad.
I get it.
Thank you, Murong Chen.
I didn't expect,
you are the master of love.
(I didn't even know
what Yun Ya looked like,)
(but I was attracted to him.)
(Knowing that he was ill,)
(I wanted to cure him.)
(For him, I gave up my identity as
a princess,)
(and escaped from the palace.)
(Even if he missed the appointment,)
I still...
(That's right.)
(That's true love.)
The moonlight is so beautiful tonight.
Right, it's beautiful.
But it doesn't know your admiration,
as the way you ignore my affection.
What did you say?
Nothing.
(Jiang Mengmeng,)
(when will you know
my affection to you?)
I'm sorry.
I've done so many bad things
to you.
It's okay.
We know you didn't mean it.
That's right, Xiao Mei.
We've already forgiven you.
Fortunately, you stopped me,
so there were no irreparable
consequences.
Thank you very much.
You don't have to thank me.
I think it's all Xi Qing's credit.
I wish you happiness and long life
together.
Do you have any plans for the future?
We've sealed the secret passage,
and decided to move out of the house
and retire.
I'm sorry
to have you retire with me.
Actually,
I'm tired, too.
Only if you are with me,
it doesn't matter where I live.
But I'm blind now.
I can't do many things
that even ordinary people can do.
From now on, I will be your eyes.
Ah right.
I have a parting gift for you.
This is...
the blood night-blooming cereus.
You are giving it to us?
It almost became a murder weapon
in my hands.
But still,
I don't want to destroy it.
So, I decide
to give it to a kind person
who can use it in a right way.
With all due respect,
this blood night-blooming cereus
maybe...
We accept it.
Thank you.
It's about time
we should go.
Right.
So, we are leaving.
See you.
Let's go, Xiao Ai.
Childe, it's so lively here.
Yeah.
Why didn't you let me tell Sang Luo
that the blood night-blooming cereus
might be fake?
Think about it.
She just experienced too much.
She kidnapped so many girls,
and almost became a murderer.
Her husband lost his eyes.
At this moment, you tell her
that all these were a fraud.
Guess if she would collapse?
You are right.
Lies are not necessarily bad.
Sometimes,
white lies can also make things better.
Besides,
her thanks and wishes to you are true,
which is more important than
whether the flower is true or false.
These two are happy now.
If I hadn't brought Xi Qing,
how could you two be like this?
Didn't I take you to Xi Qing?
We both did it.
You are right.
Murong Chen.
I usually see you fooling around,
I didn't expect you are so considerate.
Of course I am.
You don't know me very well.
I have many advantages.
Alright, alright.
You are the best.
I mean it.
So do I.
It's a long journey.
Why don't we ride horses?
Mengmeng, come to ride my horse.
Your horse is as stupid
as you.
Mengmeng,
ride my horse.
My Da Huang is a war horse.
Mine is a royal one.
Your horse is as delicate
as you.
Flashy but weak.
I bet he doesn't know the way.
Your horse is as rough as you.
You can insult me,
but not my Da Huang.
Stop it.
I'll handle this.
Childe,
can you do it?
There is a first time for everything.
Don't worry.
We have to sleep here.
Luckily, it's summer now.
It's not that cold at night.
But it's may be hard for Mengmeng.
A  noble princess
has to sleep in the open with us.
I'm not that delicate.
She is a princess, and I'm a prince.
Why don't you sympathize with me?
If you can't bear this,
you can just write a letter
to Cang Yun Kingdom
and let your people take you back.
Why are you bothering to stay with us?
I just let Mengmeng see me off,
not you.
If you hadn't force Mengmeng,
how could we be together now?
I'd say you don't have a pure motive.
What motive?
You
know it.
- Say it.
- Mengmeng.
Mengmeng, which of us is right?
Mengmeng.
I'm sleepy.
Then go to sleep, childe.
Go to sleep.
I have Chang Kong, what do you get?
Song Che.
What?
Look.
There.
Right, there.
Did you see it?
What?
Nothing.
You idiot.
What?
What's wrong with you?
I've got Da Huang.
Humph.
A real man would sleep here.
Good night, Da Huang.
Mr. System.
I have completed the mission.
Why don't you
give me some rewards
and let me see Yun Ya?
Did I do it wrong?
Mengmeng.
Yun Ya,
you are here.
This is the right use of full moon.
Are you disappointed
that I didn't come
to get you last night?
You already know?
Right.
The great hero
knows everything.
Actually,
you can send the signal earlier,
without putting yourself in danger.
Or,
it's because I missed the appointment
last time,
and you are still blaming me?
I know
heroes are busy.
If you don't show up,
there must be something holding you.
And you always have to travel all over
the world
to help others.
It's hard to take care of me alone.
If you ask for me,
I will come.
I mean,
helping people is what I do,
and I'll help you if you are in danger.
I knew it.
Speaking of which,
this time I also experienced
the happiness of punishing the evil
and helping others.
I used to be surrounded
by a crowd in the palace.
I thought,
as long as they can protect me
and love me, it's fine.
But after I left the palace,
those people around me were not there
anymore.
I found that
there are also things I can do,
such as saving my companions,
the girls,
and temporarily lost Sang Luo.
It turns out that
there are so many things
that make people feel happy
except being loved.
Have this!
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
This plot...
Is the climax coming?
Are you alright?
I'm okay.
Oh.
Last time you said you would help me
find the blood night-blooming cereus.
Don't bother.
Why?
I was detained last time,
and failed to get you
out of palace.
I broke the promise.
So, let's end our cooperation.
You fool.
What?
I said you are a fool
who doesn't know a girl's mind at all.
Those agreements
are to cure you.
You mean,
you want to cure me?
Don't you understand?
Both the blood night-blooming cereus
and the agreements
are my excuses.
I just want you to be healthy
and happy.
I hope you can do what you want
without worry.
There is no trade between you and me,
only love.
What kind of man
would run away every time I hit on him?
You should have put me down
before you leave.
What now?
Help!
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪