♪Waking up to a sunny day every day,
my dreams are sweet♪
♪I reply to your gaze by holding hands,
without having to say a word♪
♪Even when we part for a short while,
we're still thinking of each other♪
♪No matter how long has passed,
I'm sure you're still waiting there♪
♪Please forgive my willfulness
and let's clear all misunderstandings♪
♪The deep feelings for you
that have never changed♪
♪I want you to listen to it♪
♪At this moment, you and I fall in love♪
♪I just want you to be with me♪
♪Every day, I grow fonder of you♪
♪For you, I'll take that risk♪
♪I fell in love with you♪
♪My wishes about you♪
♪Capture all the happy moments♪
♪I believe in forever,
because this is love♪
=About is Love S2=
=Episode 14=
Why is she so fond of both of us?
I have further studied
her articles.
I noticed
that she only admired Wei Qing at first.
Later on, she was rescued by you.
She probably developed
an adoration of you.
She has been hoping
for you two to get together
to fulfill her greatest fantasy of love.
She even learned about your history.
From how you two met, fell in love,
to the events that happened later on.
She knows almost everything.
If that's the case,
I'm against meeting her.
Why not?
I don't want to use Wu Xiao.
Whether it's using her admiration
or if she thinks she owes me,
I don't want something good
to become a burden she has to carry.
How are you going to meet Wu Zheng then?
We acted too rashly today.
I want to be well-prepared
and meet him with sincerity.
There are millions of paths to take.
Must you pick the toughest one?
We were in the wrong first.
If he finds out
that we got to meet him
by taking a shortcut,
he would definitely think
that we are people
who would do anything
to get what we want.
How are you going to meet him then?
By waiting forever?
We should at least
show that we are sincere.
I still believe
that if you put your heart into it,
there's nothing you can't achieve.
How long do you plan to wait?
I'll just keep waiting
until he is willing to meet me.
I won't let you.
On what grounds?
The fact that I am the CEO of Yunma
and this incident
happened in my company.
I will take care of it.
I won't let you grovel to others.
You have your way of doing things.
I have my own principles.
You don't have to agree with me,
but you can't stop me.
Where are you going?
Relax.
You don't want to use Wu Xiao.
So I won't go to her.
He's just concerned about you.
He can't bear to see you suffer.
You don't have to defend him.
He's just a domineering maniac.
Isn't it a good thing
that he's a wife-protecting maniac?
I don't need his protection.
I just wish
that he could understand me.
But understanding goes both ways.
He thinks that love means protecting you
in a domineering way.
You don't have to accept it,
but don't neglect his love.
I wish to neglect it,
but I can't stop myself from failing to.
(Zheng House)
What are you looking at?
It's Zhou Shi.
She came and asked to see you.
I didn't let her in.
So she's been standing outside waiting.
Waiting under the sun?
She's even using
such an old-fashioned tactic.
I guess she's really desperate.
I think
Zhou Shi seems pretty sincere.
Perhaps there's truly a misunderstanding
with the contract incident.
Why don't you...
Zhou Shi might be all right,
but it's hard to say for Wei Qing.
I've heard of his methods.
Let's wait and see.
All right.
The weather is so hot.
Tell her to leave.
I've told her.
She refused to leave.
I don't think she will give up
unless she meets you today.
Give her a bottle of water.
Yes, sir.
(Zheng House)
♪Waking up to a sunny day every day♪
Where did you get the clothes?
And these items?
Where else did you think I'd gone to?
I knew
that with your mulish personality,
you would come here to wait.
That's why I went to get these things.
So that you won't get a heatstroke.
You didn't have to come.
I can stand the heat anyway.
You may not feel sorry for yourself,
but I do.
Besides,
if one marries a dog,
they must stay loyal to the dog.
Who are you calling a dog?
What's the matter?
My legs are numb.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hold this.
♪The deep feelings for you♪
♪That have never changed♪
Sit.
It's so small. I'm not sitting on it.
Be careful.
♪At this moment, you and I fall in love♪
♪I just want you to be with me♪
Take the fan.
♪Every day, I grow fonder of you♪
♪For you, I'll take that risk♪
You've got everything.
Of course.
I'm your boyfriend.
♪My wishes about you♪
Where did you get the water?
Mr. Wu's secretary gave it to me.
I think he's starting to yield.
If I keep this up for two more days,
I'm sure he'll be willing to meet me.
See? I told you the most important thing
is to show sincerity.
Okay.
In that case, I will stay here with you
until he's moved by your sincerity.
You should leave.
Mr. Wu.
Mr. Wu, please give me another chance.
Mr. Wu! Mr...
Stop the car.
Did you get hurt?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
♪There's only myself♪
♪And my nervous breathing♪
Did you lose your mind under the sun?
Are you even
risking your life for the sake of work?
I...
♪Keeping a distance♪
♪The so-called mystery
is just a pathetic animosity♪
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just feeling a bit dizzy.
I...
♪How can you get swayed?♪
♪It pierces through the armor
I cast with my sadness♪
How are you feeling?
Still feeling dizzy?
You've gotten a heatstroke.
You must get some rest.
♪Would you notice the meteor
if it wasn't for the shower?♪
♪My heartache is just an impact crater♪
It might hurt a little.
Bear with it for a while.
♪Would you notice the meteor
if it wasn't for the shower?♪
It's all right.
♪He's just trying
to bind you with wishes♪
♪There's only myself♪
♪And my nervous breathing♪
Be good.
Get some rest today.
Remember to keep your wounds
from getting wet.
If you're still feeling unwell tomorrow,
then go to the hospital. Do you hear me?
I will.
You silly.
♪How can you get swayed?♪
Where are you going?
To guard your door.
♪It pierces through the armor
I cast with my sadness♪
Hi, Feifei.
- Good morning, Feifei.
- Good morning.
Good morning, Feifei.
I didn't know you are so popular.
That's for sure. I'm a godd...
Is it because you're old?
You rascal. I'm warning you.
Don't you bring up my age again.
I'm still young.
Fine. You're the youngest here.
You're a pretty and adorable young lady.
Obviously.
Talk to you later.
I have to get my makeup done.
By the way, stay here
and don't try anything funny.
Don't go anywhere. Do you hear me?
Got it. You're such a nag.
What scene are you shooting later?
A kissing scene.
You can't.
Why not?
I don't allow other men to kiss you.
This is my job.
Then pick another job.
Pick another job?
Are you going to support me financially?
Besides, who are you to tell me that?
What if it were my past self
telling you that?
You wouldn't have minded then.
I don't believe you.
If that was the case,
why did I keep
declaring dominance?
What are you talking about?
Did you remember something?
Feifei, you're here.
The director is asking for you.
Quickly get changed. Okay?
Where do you girls
usually go and have fun
around here?
There's a hot spring.
Yes, it's just nearby.
It looks exquisite.
So sorry.
Really? Where is it?
- How do I get there?
- Just nearby.
What's the name?
I'll search for it online.
- Jiang.
- Dajiang?
You get to wear a kimono.
Let's connect on WeChat.
We can hang out together next time.
- Sure.
- Here.
Feifei.
Here you are.
Let's hang out next time.
What were you doing?
Having a chat.
Why? Am I not even allowed to chat?
You can chat, but why connect on WeChat?
We got along quite well.
What's wrong? Are you jealous?
You wish.
I just don't want you
flirting with girls
with Fei's body.
What do you mean by Fei's body?
It's my body too. Okay?
You stole it.
Fine. I don't want to argue with you.
If you don't want me
to flirt with girls,
then I won't.
That easy?
But you must agree to one condition.
Stop scolding me.
Okay. Deal.
You said something about
declaring dominance.
Did you remember something?
Once in a while,
I do recall some bits and pieces.
Then did you recall
memories of us?
I'll tell you if you come closer.
You ras...
You promised that you wouldn't hit me.
Then why did you kiss me?
Didn't you ask me what I remembered?
The most I managed to remember
was the two of us kissing.
You're so annoying.
Do well at your shoot,
Superstar.
Stop.
You've fallen into it
and you're only falling in deeper.
But...
he's still Ning Fei.
Even if I can't have his soul,
I can still see him every day, right?
What you're doing is drinking poison
to quench your thirst.
If I get to see him every day,
I don't mind drinking poison.
Didn't you say that you don't miss him?
Why have you changed your mind?
Previously, I thought I was dumped...
Betrayed.
Now that I'm aware of his condition,
I can't just leave him like this, right?
Even if I want to break up,
I should wait until he has recovered.
That's very selfless of you.
You go, girl.
Enough about me.
Shouldn't you
be changing your image right now
to make things fresh and exciting
for Li Mingcheng?
Why are you here again?
I came up with a lot of plans,
but I'm not good at this aspect.
I was afraid that there might be
mistakes in my judgment.
After thinking it over,
I thought you have the best taste
among the people I know.
That's why I was hoping
you could help me change my image.
Really?
Am I that important to you?
Just you wait.
You gave me your trust.
I now repay you with a surprise.
The moment you step out of this door,
I will make sure Li Mingcheng
becomes crazy about you all over again.
Slow down.
Won't this be a little too much?
No, no. Absolutely not.
You look stunning.
I didn't know
that our Miss Brainiac here
has been hiding her curves.
Are you sure that Li Mingcheng
will like this?
I am absolutely sure and certain.
First, let's be clear about one thing.
Women dress up
for themselves, not others.
Men are indeed
interesting living creatures.
Miss Brainiac.
The dress is fire. You look amazing.
What does that have to do with you?
She is taken.
Go back to your den.
I will hang around wherever I want to.
This is my house.
Fine.
Let's leave.
We're almost done with the outfit.
As for the hairstyle...
How should I style it?
Goodness gracious.
Your glasses look hideous.
Wear contact lenses, okay?
I also have to give you
a full skin-treatment
so that you get
an inside-out transformation.
I recently found a domestic product.
It's really effective.
Try it.
I can accept all of these.
But this lingerie
feels weird.
Weird?
Come here.
Listen. this lingerie
is the true essence.
It's a gift specially for Li Mingcheng.
To let him truly feel
what inner beauty is.
Inner beauty.
But there's nothing much under this.
Trust me. I won't be wrong.
We're almost done with your appearance.
Now we need to work on
your inner transformation.
So that you become
more feminine.
How?
(Cheer him on.)
(And then?)
(Can I give him a hug?)
(What you did for Tony Leung earlier
was the same...)
You want me to be like her?
It's Lin Chiling. Baby.
We only have one night.
So we must
do our best!
Do our best.
You're home.
So? Did you manage to meet Mr. Wu?
Why is your face red?
You got sunburned.
Why didn't you use the umbrella?
That would make me look insincere.
You taught me that.
(He's just concerned about you.)
(He can't bear to see you suffer.)
Stay right here. I'll be right back.
Here.
It might hurt a little.
Bear with it for a while.
Don't look at me
with those pitiful eyes.
Look to the side.
It doesn't hurt if I look at you.
All right. Look at me.
You're such a kid.
It was so sunny outside.
You must have had a hard time.
It wasn't so bad.
It's more effective for me
to get a sunburn than you.
Speaking of which,
Wu Zheng is really mean.
I stood outside for so long,
but I didn't even get a bottle of water.
What choice do you have
when you're notorious
for being a gentlemen killer?
All done.
What did you
apply to my face?
Will it get better tomorrow?
If I go there again,
will I still get sunburned?
You plan to go again tomorrow?
He hasn't yielded.
What else can I do?
Maybe
we could try a different way.
You've changed your mind?
If this way doesn't work,
we should try another one.
It's not like I insist on
sticking to this path.
But let me be clear.
We mustn't force her.
We must at least explain everything.
It's only okay
if she is willing to help us.
Sure thing.
Let me apply some more on your nose.
Where is she?
Over there.
She just got here.
She will probably be here for a while.
Can you do this alone?
Have some faith. Get rid of your doubt.
I forgot that you are
a skilled businessman.
Zhang Shuai, watch and learn.
You need it to end your single life.
Sure.
Thank you.
Wei Qing?
You're Wei Qing. Wei...
Keep it low-key.
I'm just here to have a meal.
You... I...
May I?
Yes, of course. Please have a seat.
Are you hungry?
The beefsteak here tastes delicious.
Try it.
Thanks for the courtesy,
but I'm not hungry.
I see.
Are you waiting for someone?
Is it Zhou Shi?
She rescued me before.
She's my savior.
Isn't it a small world?
Did she tell you about it?
Sure enough, he's still got it.
I was worried
that his skills had turned rusty.
He has you now.
He couldn't be bothered making an effort
in front of other women.
Isn't that a good thing?
All right.
Wait here. I'll go over.
Be on standby to assist us.
Go on.
Has she returned to the country?
Are you two together?
Are you two in a relationship?
We are indeed...
We are just colleagues.
Zhou Shi.
Don't tell me
you two are here on a date.
Calm down.
We are actually here for business.
We've been hoping to meet your father,
but he refused to meet us.
So you two were the ones
who kept looking for him
the past few days.
What happened to your face?
Did you get sunburned?
Don't tell me
he made you wait under the sun.
How could he do that?
I can't believe this.
I will talk to him when I get home.
It has nothing to do with Mr. Wu.
We did it of our own accord.
Could you put in a word for us
with your father
so that he meets us?
All it takes is just for me
to say the word. Let's go.
Wait a minute.
You two aren't in a fight, are you?
How does this have anything to do
with meeting Mr. Wu?
Of course it does.
You see. I've always thought of you two
as my role models in love.
I told my dad
not to stop me from dating.
But if you two aren't even together,
then I'll no longer believe in love.
I've embarrassed myself
in front of my dad.
But...
The truth is
we've been in a relationship
a long time ago,
but we kept it a secret.
Really?
Yes.
Why else did you think I got sunburned?
What a sweet couple.
I dropped my phone. Let me get it.
Let me help you.
We agreed not to lie.
Who says I'm lying?
We're going to be a couple eventually.
It's just a matter of time.
But we shouldn't lie. What if she...
What are you two doing?
You're not
talking behind my back, are you?
I've got my phone. Here it is.
I have one small request.
Name it.
I really wish to see how you two
truly interact with each other.
That's not a problem.
Let's go then.
Let's go.
The view looks nice over there.
Let me take a picture of you two.
Stand closer to each other.
That's right. A little closer.
Can you two
smile more naturally?
It looks a bit like a staged photo.
It is staged.
Show your professionalism.
Yes, that's the feeling.
All right, why don't you two
take a break
while I pick out some photos?
You keep her company.
I'm going to take a break.
You two continue.
♪And face all obstacles in despair♪
Mr. Wei.
You two are actually
not in a relationship yet, right?
♪Keep holding on to the illusion
and I'm burned by the past♪
You
noticed?
I'm not stupid.
But I can also tell
that you really like her
and so does she.
I don't know what's the reason
you're still not together.
That's pretty spot on.
Do you need my help?
It's fine.
♪You changed me
and an upturn occurred in my life♪
♪I look forward to the day
the world gains its colors♪
♪Love has arrived,
and I've made my choice♪
♪We are so lucky♪
What are you doing?
Capturing a beautiful moment.
That's cheesy.
Stop taking pictures.
Seriously,
I have fear of taking photos now.
♪Our fate♪
Where is Wu Xiao? How was the chat?
We're done chatting.
She agreed to take us to meet Wu Zheng.
For real? Let's hurry then.
Slow down.
She wants to take a stroll first.
She'll take us there when she's back.
I said I wouldn't use her,
but I ended up lying to her.
You really think
she only agreed to help us
because she fell for it?
She saw right through us,
but kept quiet.
How did she find out?
Your acting was so stiff.
Wasn't that obvious?
She even said
that she could tell that you like me.
That's nonsense.
I think you made that up.
She said
that when you're in love with someone,
your eyes won't lie.
When you look at me,
your eyes are filled with love.
♪I thought I had to go through
the entire journey alone♪
♪And face all obstacles in despair♪
♪Keep holding on to the illusion
and I'm burned by the past♪
♪I quietly endure
this endless loneliness♪
♪You showed up and I paused my memory♪
♪You changed me
and an upturn occurred in my life♪
Sorry.
The sight of it was too beautiful.
I couldn't help myself.
Carry on. Just carry on.
Well...
We've taken pictures and looked around.
How about meeting your dad now?
Okay. Let's go.
♪We are so lucky♪
♪That we don't have to keep looking♪
♪However broken my heart was♪
♪One kiss from you can heal it♪
♪Our fate♪
♪Has brought us together♪
♪Sorry that I'm so slow♪
♪I almost missed you♪
Do you think Wu Xiao will succeed?
We have
stood guard and acted sweetly.
We've done everything we had to.
We just have to leave the rest to her.
♪There's no more doubt♪
♪It needs no approval♪
♪My heart beats fast and I feel warm♪
♪I treasure every moment
when my heart flutters for you♪
You've been working here
for quite some time.
Why are you so dense?
Is this painting usually hung here?
Why are you so forgetful?
I'm sorry. I'll take this away.
Dad, I'm home.
Here you are, my baby girl.
Come on, sit.
Why were you out eating for so long?
Have you drunk the soup
I made you?
Dad, I don't like soup.
What do you like then? Tell me.
I'll have someone get it.
Dad, I had my meal before I came back.
I'm still too full to eat.
You're right.
You can skip the meal.
How about some fruits then?
Look at you, baby girl.
You didn't listen to me.
That's why you've lost weight,
baby girl.
Dad.
Stop calling me baby girl.
I'm a senior student now.
So what?
You're still my baby girl.
Even when you've reached menopause,
you are still my baby girl.
My little sweetheart.
Dad, you see.
My friend wants to meet you.
Friend?
What kind of friend?
Is it a guy or a girl?
Baby girl, listen to me.
You should be studying at this age.
You mustn't be dating.
I'm not mentally prepared for it yet.
- If you get married...
- Dad.
Dad, it's nothing like that.
They are a couple.
Oh, a couple.
That wouldn't be a problem.
Wait a minute.
You never let me
mix with your friends.
How come you thought of
introducing your friends to me now?
That's because you're so charming
and handsome.
Everyone is eager to meet you.
Yes, you're right. Where are they?
I'll go get them.
Hang on.
What are their names?
Wei Qing and Zhou Shi.
Baby girl, you have laid
a trap for me.
Daddy.
I know you're the best dad in the world.
I think I'm a pretty good judge
of character.
Why don't you give them a chance
and hear them out?
Baby girl, you're a kid.
You should stay out of adults' matters.
Listen.
They see that you're kind and naive.
So they're using you.
Do you know that, silly baby girl?
Fine.
You're always on about adult matters.
Then when I date someone
and get a boyfriend in the future,
you must stay out of it too.
Not on my life.
You are my one and only baby girl.
How can I let a guy
take you away so easily?
I don't care.
It's the same thing.
Look at you.
You and your bad temper.
You're breaking your old man's heart.
Daddy.
I know you're the best.
Just do me a favor.
If you're not happy with them,
I won't talk to them ever again, okay?
Please, Daddy.
All right, all right.
I can never say no when you do this.
Go get them.
I'll go right now.
That's what happened.
We will get to the bottom of this
as soon as we can
and give you an explanation.
I know this explanation
sounds weak.
But please believe me.
Compared to profit,
I value reputation even more.
Besides asking for your understanding,
the reason we're here
is to also discuss the compensation.
We wish to minimize your loss
as much as we can.
Daddy.
Give them a chance.
I really like them. Besides,
they are also victims of this.
Since you're being so upfront,
and you even got yourself
such a tenacious lobbyist,
I won't hold
Yunma and Shangjue accountable.
I won't ask for compensation.
However, my partnership with both of you
ends here.
Mr. Wu.
Miss Zhou, this is my bottom line.
We respect your decision.
Once everything comes to light,
I will personally
make an official apology to you
in front of the public and media.
I hope we still have a chance
to work together in the future.
What's the matter?
We walked all day with Wu Xiao.
Now my feet hurt.
Let me have a look.
It's all bruised.
I just don't understand girls.
Why do you girls
like wearing high heels so much?
It's not that we want to.
We just don't have a choice.
I don't mind it.
Don't wear high heels
when you're with me
from now on.
Okay.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Giving you a piggyback.
It's fine.
Get on my back.
Three, two...
You're too light.
Make sure you eat more, okay?
Got it. You're such a nag.
Luckily,
we managed to meet Mr. Wu in the end.
But it's also a shame
that we failed to get a partnership.
It's all right.
I'm happy
as long as we got to meet him
and explain everything.
You got yourself covered in bruises
just for the sake of an apology.
Was it worth it?
It was.
You're trying so hard.
Are you that eager to be a career woman?
I'm not trying to be a career woman.
I want to become
a better version of myself.
Why?
(I can only be by your side)
(if I become better.)
Come in.
What's with the clink-clanks?
It's hard to unscrew a lid
with one hand.
Don't you know how to ask for my help
with your hand like this?
I'm applying skincare.
How could I ask you for help?
Let me help you.
Place a few drops on my hand.
Do you know how to do it?
I just have to try and see.
You seem like a professional
with your massage.
Then make sure
you give me a five-star rating.
Sure.
I'll tip you later.
Thanks.
By the way,
we also have a deluxe package.
Full-body wash and treatment.
If you continue harassing your customer,
I'm calling the police.
I was just making a suggestion
since you couldn't use your hand.
All right. Fine. You're so annoying.
Get out since you're done.
I need to take a shower.
Hang on.
Wait a minute.
Your face.
What's wrong?
How can it be so pretty?
♪You showed up and I paused my memory♪
♪You changed me
and an upturn occurred in my life♪
♪I look forward to the day
the world gains its colors♪
♪Love has arrived,
and I've made my choice♪
♪We are so lucky
that we don't have to keep looking♪
♪However broken my heart was,
one kiss from you can heal it♪
♪Our fate has brought us together♪
♪Sorry that I'm so slow♪
♪I almost missed you♪
♪We're so lucky
that our eyes were locked on each other♪
♪God has custom made this person for me♪
♪There's no more doubt,
and it needs no approval♪
♪My heart beats fast and I feel warm♪
♪I treasure♪
♪Every moment
when my heart flutters for you♪