DANI: There's an old Native
American proverb that says...
inside every person,
there are two bears...
forever locked in combat
for your soul.
- ( WIND WHISTLING )
- One bear is all things good.
Compassion, love, trust.
The other is all things evil.
Fear, shame,
and self-destruction.
- ( LOUD CRASHING )
- ( GASPING )
- What's happening?
- We have to run...
as fast as we can!
DANI: Wait!
- ( GRUNTING )
- ( DANI PANTING )
( RUMBLING AND CRASHING )
Don't let go of my hand!
( GRUNTS )
( WIND HOWLING )
( CAR HORN BLARES )
( MAN SCREAMING )
DANI: What's happening?
DANI'S FATHER: Here! Hide here!
I have to go help them.
- No! No, Dad, please!
- Dani!
- Please don't leave me alone!
- ( EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE )
Dani,
I have to go back.
Stay here.
( WHIMPERS )
DANI'S FATHER: Hey!
- ( CRYING )
- ( DEEP GROWLING )
- Run! No! Get away!
- ( WHIMPERING )
Run!
- ( CRASHING )
- ( DANI'S FATHER GROANS )
No!
- ( WHIMPERS )
- ( INHUMAN GROWLING )
( CRYING )
( TREES RUSTLING )
- ( PANTING )
- ( DEEP GROWLING )
( GROWLING CONTINUES )
( GRUNTING )
( GASPS )
( MUFFLED THUMPING )
( GROANS )
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
Hello?
( GRUNTING )
Hello? Let me out of here!
WOMAN: ( ON PA ) Relax, Dani.
I'm on my way to you.
( MUFFLED THUD )
Where am I?
Where is my family?
I know you're scared,
but you're safe now.
If I could come in,
I'll explain.
Would that be all right?
- Doors. Infirmary.
- ( LOCK BEEPS )
Hi, Dani.
I'm Dr. Reyes.
If you take a seat,
I'll free your hand.
Dani, what I'm about to tell you...
is going to be very difficult.
An F5 tornado touched down
on your reservation.
No.
You're the sole survivor
of a terrible tragedy.
No, no.
- ( DEEP GROWLING )
- ( PANTING )
It was growling!
Something was chasing us!
What?
Sometimes trauma makes us
remember things...
that aren't real.
Here.
I think this may be yours.
I'm really sorry.
( GASPING )
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
Why didn't I just die with them?
Why me?
Survivor's guilt is
a common reaction to trauma.
We look for reasons.
Most of the time,
we find none.
But the reason you survived...
is because you're
a very uncommon girl.
Your reservation was wiped
off the face of the earth.
But you made it out
with barely a scratch.
Do you know
what mutants are?
Mutation most often
occurs in puberty.
You might spend the first
13 years of your life...
relatively normal.
Then, just like that...
you come of age and
discover your true nature.
What's my true nature?
We'll have to figure
that out together.
( HESITATES )
Then how do you know
I'm a mutant?
The man I work for
has a way of recognizing
new mutants...
the moment their condition
reveals itself.
That's how we discovered you
and your fellow patients.
You're not alone, Dani.
This is a facility for
young mutants like yourself.
Teens who need
some extra care...
before they can go on to
live healthy adult lives.
There's some warm clothes.
Toiletries.
How long do I have to stay here?
Until I decide
you're not a danger.
Danger to who?
Yourself.
You have been through a lot.
Get some rest, okay?
We'll talk more in the morning.
Dr. Reyes.
There's really no one left?
But you're in a safe place now.
Nothing can hurt you in here, Dani.
Good night.
- ( DOOR CLOSES )
- ( LOCK CLICKS )
Yesterday, I asked you
to think about...
the first time
your mutation manifested.
Would anyone like to share?
Sam?
Illyana?
Roberto?
Rahne?
Look, we can't help each other
unless we talk to each other.
I've said this
a hundred times.
This program can't help you
if you refuse to participate.
So, Rahne,
why don't you start?
- I...
- ( DOOR SQUEAKS )
Please join us, Dani.
This is our new patient,
Danielle Moonstar.
( LAUGHS )
Oh, it's serious.
DR. REYES: Let's do our best
to make her feel at home.
Go ahead, Rahne.
Right.
I was 13.
I remember running
through the woods.
( PANTING )
DR. REYES: How did you feel?
Free.
Like, the most free
I'd felt my whole life.
But guilty, too.
DR. REYES: Why guilty?
Because I knew it was bad.
I went to Reverend Craig...
to see if he could
pray it out of me.
He asked me to show him,
so I changed.
And what did Reverend Craig do?
Beat me about half to death.
Said I was a witch...
that I was going to hell.
( SIGHING )
Would anyone else like
to share their first time?
New girl.
How fucked up are you?
- DR. REYES: Illyana.
- ROBERTO: Drugs, I bet.
Or a nympho, maybe.
Hopefully.
DR. REYES: Keep behaving...
exactly like you are right now...
and we can all just spend
the day in solitary.
I want all of you
to think very carefully...
about how you'd like to use
your time here.
And how long
you want that time to be.
Illyana,
since you're already up...
why don't you show Dani around?
And why do I have to?
Because I'm asking you.
DANI: How long
have you been here?
Are there any other doctors?
- Why aren't you...
- Shh.
What's that, Lockheed?
Oh, I know.
I hate her, too.
Dr. Reyes! ( SNAPPING FINGERS )
( LOCK CLICKS )
Main building. Dorms.
Chapel, if you believe in that shit.
And garden.
You don't know how
to grow weed, do you?
No.
( SIGHS ) What kind of
Indian are you?
Cheyenne.
I wasn't actually asking.
( SPRAY CAN RATTLING )
You're my lookout.
( DANI SCOFFS )
Where are we?
ILLYANA: Who knows?
Dr. Reyes always says...
the closest town
is 20 miles away.
But she could be lying...
to keep us from trying to escape.
There's no fence.
Nope.
No fence.
Nothing between you and freedom.
Run, new girl, run!
( WOLF GROWLS )
Faster!
( CHUCKLES )
( GROANS )
( LAUGHING )
Aw. This isn't a hospital, Pocahontas.
It's a cage.
And now you're trapped in it forever.
Man, I really should have warned you.
( GRUNTS )
( SCREAMS WITH FRUSTRATION )
( PANTING )
( BELL TOLLING )
- I have to go to help them.
- No! No, Dad, please!
- DANI'S FATHER: Dani!
- Please don't leave me alone!
DR. REYES: Survivor's guilt is
a common reaction to trauma.
Stay here!
DR. REYES: You're the sole survivor.
( GRUNTING )
RAHNE: What are you doing
out here?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
- ( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
- ( WIND WHISTLING )
Wow, this is really high up.
A fall from here
would mess you up.
It would kill me.
Instantly.
I wouldn't feel a thing.
I want to get out of here, too...
but not like this.
My home is gone.
My dad's dead.
Where I'm from, we believe
suicides go straight to hell.
Always kinda scared me
out of giving it a go.
I don't wanna be here.
I wanna be with my family.
If they're gone
and you're here...
maybe it's for a reason.
Maybe it's not time
to be with them just yet.
But I'm all alone.
There's two people up here.
You calling me a nobody?
Please.
It's going to get better.
I promise.
( SIGHS )
( BOTH GASP )
( DANI GASPING )
Let's live a little longer,
Dani Moonstar.
Dani, where were you?
- Uh...
- I was just...
showing her the chapel.
No one is ever to be
unaccounted for, Rahne.
You know that.
I'm sorry,
Dr. Reyes.
Okay.
DANI: Did I just
get you in trouble?
RAHNE: It's okay.
She likes me.
I'm one of the good ones.
Me and Sam.
( WHIRRING )
( SAM YELLING )
Holy shit,
I thought he just exploded.
RAHNE: No.
That's his thing.
He can blast off.
Zero to 100 like a cannonball.
( SAM GRUNTING )
Not so good at landing, though.
DANI: Is this,
like, practice?
I don't know.
Sometimes it seems
like he's out here...
just trying to hurt himself.
( SAM GROANS )
He grew up in a small town in Kentucky.
Did really well in school...
but had to drop out to work
in the mines with his dad.
Help the family and all.
DANI: Poor guy.
RAHNE: Right? Poor guy.
- And then there's Roberto.
- ( MUSIC PLAYS ON HEADPHONES )
His family's, like,
the richest family in Brazil.
( THANKING IN PORTUGUESE )
Thanks, doggy.
Probably living the sweet
life before he got here.
Something must have
gone really wrong.
What's his power?
He won't tell,
but he's got something.
Parents sent him here
to be cured.
Is there a cure
for being an asshole?
Maybe he's just
the crazy one.
RAHNE: No.
That spot's taken.
Well, I really
enjoyed spending...
the day with you, Dani,
but I should go.
We're not supposed to be
in each other's rooms and...
Why is she always watching us?
For our own good.
She means well.
She's trying to help us.
If you follow the treatment,
you'll get out of here, Dani.
Probably before
the rest of us cuckoos.
Well, night.
Rahne?
Thank you for helping me.
What do I know?
Maybe we both
should have jumped.
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
( COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY ON SPEAKERS )
ROBERTO: Dish duty is really
trimming down the wardrobe.
Every time
your shirt gets dirty...
you just throw it away?
Here. It's all yours.
Cool.
ROBERTO: Was it scary?
Working in the mines?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
DANI'S FATHER: No!
- ( DEEP GROWLING )
- ( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( SWITCH CLICKS )
SAM: Oh, Jesus.
ROBERTO: I got it.
You couldn't pay me
a million dollars...
to go in one of those things.
I couldn't pay you
a million dollars anyway.
When we get out of here,
I'll spot ya.
My folks are good for it.
Night, Kentucky.
Night, man.
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
- ( DANI WHIMPERING )
- ( DEEP GROWLING )
- ( HEAVY FOOTFALL )
- ( DANI PANTING )
( GASPS )
( MUFFLED THUDDING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( MUFFLED WHIRRING )
( SAM GRUNTS )
SAM: Hello? ( ECHOING )
Somebody!
( METALLIC CLANKING )
( MEN GRUNTING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( MAN GRUNTING )
Dad?
Samuel.
What did you do?
( MUFFLED WHIRRING )
- ( MAN SCREAMING )
- ( SAM GASPS )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANING )
( GLASS SHATTERS )
( WHEEZES )
( GASPING )
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
( SHOWER RUNNING )
Oops.
There aren't any cameras
in here, are there?
Only safe place
in the building.
But there could still be mics, so...
Shh.
Wow, that's, um...
That's some serious body art.
Tattoo wasn't
painful enough?
It wasn't my idea.
What's it stand for?
I'm sorry. I don't want
to talk about it.
( INHALES SHARPLY )
( SOBBING QUIETLY )
( RUMBLING )
( GROWLS )
( GRUNTING )
DR. REYES: Control.
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
Control.
( MUTANTS CONTINUE BREATHING DEEPLY )
And...
control.
- TARA: ( ON TV ) Darling.
- I can't do this.
SAM: I have one arm.
It takes two.
TARA: ( ON TV ) We can do this.
ILLYANA: Hey, Standing Rock.
You want a buffalo wing?
You people love buffalo,
don't you?
Jeez, Illya,
will you just...
- leave her alone?
- No.
It's okay.
"Standing Rock."
That's a good one.
More original than "Pocahontas."
That was huge
in fifth grade.
You don't scare me.
My dad told me
about bitches like you.
Oh.
Well, here.
Why don't you show us
on the puppet...
where Daddy touched you?
- Lockheed!
- SAM: Hey, guys, come on!
You keep my father's name
out of your mouth, bitch!
( ILLYANA GRUNTS )
You don't know
anything about me.
ILLYANA: Do you know anything?
Sixteen years old and
doesn't even know her power.
Seems like that mutant period
should've kicked in by now.
- Leave her alone.
- SAM: Yo. Hold up.
I'm helping her.
This is therapy!
- Get your hands off me.
- Or you'll what?
Let's find out.
What are you gonna do, huh?
- ( BOTH GRUNT )
- Fuck! Bitch!
- RAHNE: Illyana, don't!
- ( ILLYANA GRUNTS )
You know the rules.
No powers in here.
And definitely no fighting.
( ILLYANA SCOFFS )
Sorry, Doctor.
I thought maybe Dani was invincible.
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
Just wanted to see
if I was right.
Solitary. Both of you.
But it wasn't Dani's...
Everyone else,
lights out in 10.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- ILLYANA: Mmm.
I'll see you in hell.
Come on.
( LOCK ENGAGES )
ILLYANA: What's that, Lockheed?
( SYSTEM BEEPING )
ILLYANA: ( ON SPEAKERS ) Don't be scared.
We'll go to our special place, okay?
The Smiling Men can't get us
in our special place.
( DISTANT ETHEREAL SINGING )
- ( THUD )
- ( WOMAN SINGING LULLABY )
- ( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
- ( EERIE CROAKING )
( SNARLS )
( SOFT RUSTLING )
- ( WIND WHISTLING )
- ( GRUNTS SOFTLY )
- ( STATIC BUZZING )
- ( SYSTEM BEEPING )
- ( INHUMAN GROWLING )
- ( HEAVY FOOTFALLS )
- ( GROWLING )
- ( DANI SCREAMING )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
Dani?
DANI: What's happening to me?
( BEEPING )
DR. REYES: You're clearly
manifesting something...
but we need to do more tests
to find out what it is.
It's okay.
I'm a doctor.
Actually, I come from
a family of doctors.
My mother was a vet.
A lot of pets came in
with rattlesnake bites.
Did you know baby rattlesnakes
are more dangerous...
than adult ones?
They haven't learned
how to control...
how much venom
they secrete.
Even the mutants
we call heroes today...
when they first got their powers...
chances are
they hurt someone.
That's why new mutants
are dangerous.
- And they need to be...
- Locked up?
Sequestered...
from average humans,
for their safety and ours.
Put pressure.
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
It's been a week
since my last confession.
DR. REYES: My superior runs
a facility for gifted mutants.
You could move there after
this, if you wanted to.
Rahne said I could even
get out of here faster...
if I follow your program.
I've noticed
you and Rahne...
have taken a liking to each other.
That's good.
She's a good influence.
And she's right.
It's important we find out
exactly what your power is...
so we can help you control it.
RAHNE: I masturbated twice.
I lied to Dr. Reyes.
And I was up in the vents again.
( MUFFLED DOOR CLANGING )
( SOFT THUD )
Hello?
I'm gonna say one Our Father
and two Hail Marys, okay?
( DOOR CREAKING )
Hello?
( GASPING QUIETLY )
( SOFTLY ) Who's there?
MAN: Witch!
( LOUDLY ) You witch!
I'll flay the flesh
- from your bones!
- ( DOORS THUDDING )
( WHISPERING ) Demons can't
come in churches.
Demons can't come in churches.
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
- Hey.
DANI: Where have you been?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just needed some time
to myself.
ILLYANA: Come on.
Where are you guys going?
Reyes is asleep,
so we're going up to the...
To the "never mind,
you're not invited."
Come on, Illy.
Come on,
we'll show you.
Whatever.
So, you guys hang out
in an attic?
Yeah.
It's one of the only places
Reyes can't watch us.
ROBERTO: It's full of cool shit...
from back before this was even
a place for mutants.
ILLYANA: Let's play
a little game.
Dare.
You can't say dare.
Fine. Jesus.
Truth.
How many girls have you been with?
Like I can even remember.
ILLYANA: Rahne?
He's lying.
It's a lie detector.
We know.
Fine. Three.
That's not bad.
ILLYANA: No, look.
- I told you.
- SAM: What?
Why not?
I get too hot.
( SAM LAUGHS )
Yeah, you think it's funny?
Your turn, asshole.
( VELCRO RIPS OPEN )
What's the coal for?
My dad gave it to me.
Right before...
he passed.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I belong here, so...
I'm not sure
any of us belong here.
I think I do.
Why?
ILLYANA: New girl,
he already had his question.
It's your turn.
Aren't you gonna
hook me up?
I don't need a polygraph
to tell if you're lying.
What's your power?
I don't know.
I thought you were
going to say that.
How about another question?
What's with the stupid bear?
Same as Sam.
My dad made it for me.
( SCOFFS )
Why?
When I was little,
I was...
I was really afraid
of the dark.
Like, so afraid,
it was impossible...
to get me to go to bed.
So my dad, he told me
a legend of a bear.
A Demon Bear...
that lives inside of us
and feeds off of our fear.
That'll help a kid sleep.
Shut up, Berto.
So, when you're born...
the bear is tiny and weak.
And the older you get...
the more afraid
we become...
the bigger and the stronger
the bear gets.
My dad, he...
he made this for me so that
I would always remember...
how small it was
when I was born.
So that I would remember
to never be afraid.
Enough.
Let's do this.
Well, come on.
Truth.
Why are you here?
Because I killed 18 men.
One by one.
With my sword.
( ON SPEAKERS ) And Lockheed.
DANI: You're lying.
SAM: No, she's not.
ILLYANA: You don't believe me?
I'm the most powerful
mutant here.
Today, I'd like to talk
about obedience.
If you want any hope
of moving on...
to my superior's facility...
it's crucial that I know
you can be trusted.
Yes?
What if we don't wanna move on
to your boss's facility?
You know, what if
I just wanna go home?
Sam, you remember
what happened.
You think they stopped
looking for you?
If you weren't here,
you'd be in prison or worse.
I was...
It was an accident.
You think anyone outside
this room would believe that?
I would.
Sam is a good guy.
SAM: Even if I'm not...
do I really have to spend...
my whole life in here
for one mistake?
Once you're better...
When am I better?
What's gotten into you, Sam?
SAM: Look,
something's not right.
I'm seeing things,
terrible nightmares.
Uh...
When will I ever get better?
You're better
when I say so.
No, forget it.
It's bullshit.
You're not listening to me.
( DOOR THUDS )
( SNORING )
RAHNE: What did you do to her?
ILLYANA: I may have spiked her tea.
( ILLYANA CHUCKLES )
( PUNK ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
( EXCLAIMING )
( SAM LAUGHING )
( PUNK MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING )
Hold those bag of bones together, man!
SAM: Whoa!
( LAUGHING )
( BOTH LAUGHING )
( RAHNE GIGGLES )
Whoo! ( CHUCKLES )
Indubitably,
it's indisputable...
that you are the absolute
worst mutants I've ever seen.
Ergo, my superior will be
very, very disappointed in me.
I surmise I may even
receive a spanking...
for being so, so bad.
Oh. Oh, my superior!
( GIRLS GIGGLING )
Yeah, who is this superior
she's always talking about?
Isn't it obvious?
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
You know who the X-Men are, right?
Yeah. It's just,
why would we wanna be X-Men?
Right. I ain't wearing no suit
and fighting people. I'm rich.
What, they pay you
to be X-Men now?
I wouldn't mind being an X-Man.
And why would they need a dog?
( SIGHS ) Children.
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
RAHNE: Come with me.
I want to show you something.
DANI: Where?
It's a surprise.
What are those two
up to?
Cheers.
( CHUCKLES )
DANI: Rahne, wait.
Are you sure you know
where you're going?
Yeah. I can see in the dark.
Just follow me.
ROBERTO: You know
how much trouble...
we're gonna get in for this?
( LAUGHING )
What's she gonna do?
Kick us out?
I don't wanna be here anyway.
Yeah.
But as long as Dr. Phil
has her magic bubble...
over the grounds...
you don't have a choice.
SAM: Yeah.
I never did
have a choice.
What do you mean?
( SIGHS SOFTLY )
You know, I had to go and
work in the mines with my dad.
I was still new
to the job.
And this one day,
I just...
I just got claustrophobic.
Like I couldn't breathe.
It was...
And he blasted.
Yeah.
I killed my dad.
Most of his crew.
I just... I just couldn't
forgive myself.
I'm sorry, man.
I didn't...
Just kept thinking...
I would do anything
to change that.
( SIGHS SOFTLY )
What about you?
What did you do?
Nothing.
Wait, so you could get out
of the building...
this whole time?
I can get anywhere
in the hospital...
through the vents.
This is the only way out, though.
I'm always paranoid
Reyes is gonna find it.
Yeah, she's gonna
find out a lot tomorrow.
RAHNE: ( CHUCKLES )
Trust me. This is worth it.
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
RAHNE: Come on, lay down.
( THUNDER CRASHING )
DANI: Oh, my God.
Isn't that beautiful?
Yeah.
It is.
It's our beautiful cage.
That's what my father called it.
You had a dome
over your reservation?
( LAUGHING )
No.
( RAHNE CHUCKLES )
He meant our bodies.
Like...
how we're trapped in them.
And at death,
our souls are free.
Free to be
with the ones you love.
Sounds pretty nice, honestly.
( MUFFLED WOMAN VOCALIZING )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( VOCALIZING CONTINUES )
Sorry, I thought
I heard you...
Want company?
Fine.
But you have to turn off
the lights.
ROBERTO: Sure.
Ooh, scary.
Are you scared?
No.
I think you are.
Virgin.
You have to catch me.
ROBERTO: Hey, wait.
( DISTANT RUMBLING )
RAHNE: Doesn't feel like it's real.
Sometimes it doesn't feel
like you're real.
What do you mean?
( DANI SIGHS )
It's just that...
you're just so nice to me.
Too nice.
Sometimes I feel like
I made you up.
You didn't make me up.
I promise you, I'm real.
Your eyes.
Oh. ( SIGHS )
I'm sorry.
DANI: Don't.
They're beautiful.
( CHUCKLES SOFTLY )
I've never
done this before.
With a girl?
With anyone.
( SIZZLING )
What's wrong?
I can't. I just need
a second to cool down.
Isn't this what you want?
Yeah. It's...
I can't get too hot.
If I get too hot, I...
( SIGHS )
You can tell me.
I was with my girlfriend.
I tried to hold her...
but I burned her with my...
- I killed her with my hands.
- Hey.
- I burned her.
Look at me.
You can't burn me.
You won't hurt me.
But...
you do need to
catch me again.
ROBERTO: ( ON SPEAKERS ) Illy?
Illy?
- ( SNARLING )
- ( ROBERTO SCREAMING )
( GRUNTING )
Mariella! No!
- ( ROBERTO SPEAKING PORTUGUESE )
- ( GROWLING )
( CONTINUES SPEAKING PORTUGUESE )
( SIREN WAILING )
What is it?
It's Berto.
( ALARM CONTINUES WAILING )
- Control room, unlock.
- ( DOOR UNLOCKS )
( ALARM CONTINUES WAILING )
- SAM: What's going on?
- Go back to your room.
( ROBERTO SCREAMING )
( CONTINUES SCREAMING )
( STEAM HISSING )
( ILLYANA COUGHING )
Damn. What happened here?
What?
What's the code, huh?
DR. REYES: Give me my phone back.
I am in charge here.
You're not in charge of shit.
Did you not see what happened?
Huh? Illyana tried to kill me.
It wasn't me.
Roberto, Illyana was in her room.
Bullshit!
There was nobody
in the pool but you.
Did you see what I saw?
Huh?
We're trapped in here
with demons...
and you want us
to stay trapped!
- Give it back.
- What's the code?
- Hey! Berto, chill.
- Chill nothing.
I'm calling the cops
and getting out of here.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Yeah? Says who?
Says your doctor.
( SCOFFS ) Bullshit.
You're not a doctor.
I've known men like you.
Men who like to keep children
trapped in cages.
I've known them...
and I've killed them.
She wasn't in the pool.
But I know
what you did to me.
You're gonna help the others
clean this mess.
In your dreams.
( ILLYANA SCREAMS )
Let me out of here!
Damn it!
I am not dying in here!
Do you understand me?
( BANGING ON DOOR )
Let me out!
DR. REYES: Initiate lockdown.
Today, Dani,
we're going to go a little deeper.
Clench your fist.
This will relax you.
( WINCES )
( RECORDER WHIRRING )
I'm gonna ask you
a series of questions.
I want you to respond truthfully.
What's the last thing
you remember...
before coming here?
( MACHINE TRILLING SOFTLY )
( DANI GROANS SOFTLY )
DANI: My dad woke me up.
He said we had to run.
And everything was shaking.
What were you
running from?
He said it was a tornado.
We both know
it wasn't a tornado, Dani.
What were you running from?
( INHUMAN GROWLING )
It was snowing.
In the summertime?
DANI: It brings the snow.
What does?
( HEAVY FOOTFALLS )
( DANI WHIMPERS )
The Demon Bear.
( DANI GASPS )
( ECHOING ) Where are you?
( ECHOING )
I'm right here, Dani.
( CHILDREN SCREAMING )
What is this place?
What are you doing?
Dani?
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
No! No! No!
( VOCALIZING )
( DOOR UNLOCKS )
( DOOR CREAKS )
( MUFFLED THUD )
Hello?
Dani?
Who's there?
( METALLIC JINGLING )
You're not real.
I killed you.
( IN DEMONIC VOICE )
And like Christ, I rise again.
Stay away from me!
Lockheed, what's going on?
( AS LOCKHEED ) It's her.
DR. REYES: Focus, Dani!
Can you control it?
Nobody can.
( GASPING )
( SCREAMING )
( SNARLING )
- ( BONES CRUNCH )
- ( SCREAMING )
RAHNE: No!
- ( FLESH SEARING )
- ( RAHNE SCREAMING )
( WOLF HOWLING )
( PANTING )
Stay back!
( GASPS )
DANI: Rahne!
( WHIMPERING )
SAM: Oh, my God.
ROBERTO: Is that real?
That's real.
See, I told you.
This shit's real.
What happened to her?
ILLYANA: You happened.
It's Dani.
( RAHNE CONTINUES WHIMPERING )
It's all Dani.
I didn't do anything.
You brought this evil here!
I now know your power,
new girl.
Let me show you mine.
DR. REYES: Illyana, no powers!
( CHOKING )
- ( SCREAMING )
- ( EERIE CROAKING )
( SCREAMING )
ILLYANA: Don't!
( ILLYANA YELPS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( GASPS )
She's in our heads.
She'll kill us all.
( GASPING )
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( DOOR OPENS )
DANI: Something's happening
to me, and I can't control it.
That place you took me...
Was it hell?
Limbo. It's a place
we made up.
"We"?
Me and Lockheed.
I brought someone for you.
At first, it was just
our special place.
We went there in our minds...
whenever something bad
was about to happen.
But we went there
so much...
stayed there so long...
it became real.
DANI: I saw a memory.
It wasn't mine.
Who were they?
ILLYANA: I never knew
their names.
They were all the same.
They made us cry.
And it made them smile.
( KEYBOARD CLACKING )
( SYSTEM BEEPS )
( BEEPING )
DANI: How's the pain?
RAHNE: Drugs are helping.
Was it really him?
Preacher?
If he wasn't real,
he could've fooled me.
( SIGHS )
Why won't you come in?
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of what I saw.
Of him.
But what if he only came
because of me?
Even if you are the one
making these things happen...
you had no choice.
It's not your fault.
I saw something when
Dr. Reyes was testing me.
I saw kids like us.
Mutants, being forced to do things.
Horrible things.
( IN HUSHED VOICE ) I don't
think this is a hospital.
The place that I saw,
I think that's where we go...
when we leave.
If we leave.
( DOOR OPENS )
I'm ready for you, Dani.
- RAHNE: Wait.
- I have to go.
What if you're right?
Are you just gonna let her
pump you full of drugs again?
Last time,
I saw things, secrets.
( WHISPERING )
Maybe I will again.
Maybe those secrets will help
us find a way out of here.
How?
I don't know yet.
But let's live a bit longer,
Rahne Sinclair.
RAHNE: Dani wanted me
to stay with her.
I need you to wait outside, Rahne.
I know, but...
DR. REYES: You can come back for recovery.
Doors. Hallway H.
SAM: Hey.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
It's just...
Well, Reyes was...
SAM: Reyes was what?
( ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE )
You guys hear that?
SAM: Is that music?
I know that song.
Wait.
What are we testing this time?
This is more a test of me.
I told you
my mother was a vet, right?
One day
our family dog went feral...
mauled the neighbor's boy.
Lift your head.
Down.
It was rabies.
( ETHEREAL MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING )
It's coming from my room.
RAHNE: I'm going to get Dr. Reyes.
Illyana, don't!
( WOMAN SINGING LULLABY )
SAM: What the hell
is this place?
- ( MUFFLED CHATTER )
- ( EERIE CROAKING )
ILLYANA: No.
( BREATHING SHARPLY )
No, I buried this.
( SMILING MAN SCREECHING )
Stay away from her,
you pig!
( SNARLING )
( ILLYANA SHOUTING )
SAM: Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Look. Look at me.
Listen to me.
He cannot hurt you.
No! Don't!
Look, see? He's not real.
All right?
( ILLYANA CRYING )
( SCREECHING )
Go! Run!
Run!
DR. REYES: My mother tried everything.
It was too far along.
I can't tell you
how hard it is...
for a doctor to face that, Dani.
That powerlessness.
( WHIMPERING )
You can do your best
to save a patient...
but sometimes
the most humane thing to do...
is put it to sleep.
( GAS HISSING )
DANI: ( MUFFLED ) Help!
Help!
( PANTING )
( MUFFLED ) Help me!
Help me!
SAM: All right. It's okay.
( CONTINUES CRYING )
Oh, Jesus!
( SNARLING )
ILLYANA: Get away! Stop!
Get off me! Let me go!
No! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
( SAM GRUNTING )
( UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES )
- ( SCREECHING )
- ( ROBERTO SCREAMING )
DR. REYES: You're
the most powerful mutant...
we've ever had.
But my superiors believe your
powers cannot be controlled.
It's almost over, Dani.
( MUFFLED CLANGING )
( SCREAMING )
( RAHNE SCREAMS )
( DR. REYES GROANING )
( GASPING )
Dani?
Dani, wake up.
( GROANING )
SAM: Hey, Dr. Reyes!
Thank God.
You gotta help us!
Hey!
Dr. Reyes!
( SHOUTS )
( SMILING MAN GROWLING )
( EERIE CROAKING )
I love you, Lockheed.
We're gonna die.
Come on, Illyana.
You gotta do something.
- I can't.
- Use your powers.
I can't!
Illyana, do something!
Oh, seriously?
( SMILING MAN SNARLING )
( GROWLING )
( WHIRRING )
SAM: Hey, Berto! Berto!
( PANTING )
Bitch put force fields
over all the exits.
SAM: Is she trying
to kill us?
Don't know. Did she make
those smiley things?
No. They're Illyana's.
Of course they are.
Have you seen the girls?
No.
All right. Upstairs.
( GROWLING AND SNARLING )
( ILLYANA SHOUTING SPELL
IN LATIN )
( YELLING )
( PANTING )
Where the hell
did you go?
Our special place.
That was so hot.
( PANTING WEAKLY )
( GROANING )
( RAHNE GASPING )
What the hell's going on?
Where's Dr. Reyes?
RAHNE: She tried to kill Dani.
What?
That test?
It wasn't a test.
She tried to kill her.
ILLYANA: My file.
"Patient reviles authority.
"But her fragmented psyche
and base hatred for humans...
"makes her a prime
candidate for the program.
"Conclusion...
"A killer...
"with limitless potential.
"Recommend continued investment."
Essex Corporation.
That must have been
the place I saw.
RAHNE: She wasn't
prepping us to be X-Men.
She was prepping us
to be killers.
We don't have much time.
Reyes wants me dead.
And it won't be long...
before she comes back
to finish the job.
How? This place is designed
to keep us inside.
All our powers, it won't work.
It's hopeless.
No. It isn't.
We got each other
out of our cages.
We can get out of this.
SAM: That's all
well and good.
But she's still got force fields...
around the building.
The windows, everything.
How you gonna get past that?
By taking out the source.
Then let's kill the bitch.
( MIC FEEDBACK WHINES )
DR. REYES: ( ON PA ) Tonight...
I'd like to talk
about responsibility.
( DR. REYES COUGHING )
You have a responsibility
to your treatment.
I want all of you to go
to your rooms right now.
If you disobey,
or if you try to leave this facility...
I have a responsibility
to stop you.
No matter what it takes.
DANI: How do you know
she's still in here?
I'm a good smeller.
DR. REYES: You're a good killer.
SAM: What's going on?
What's Essex Corp?
( DR. REYES GROANING )
( PANTING )
It's a scientific organization
founded by my superiors.
Founded to do what?
Screw with our heads?
( LOUDLY ) To save you!
( GROANS )
If it wasn't for me...
you all would've been dead
a long time ago!
( SHOUTING )
It's okay. Hey.
( GRUNTING )
DR. REYES: Calm down.
Like I said...
I want all of you
to calm down.
( GIRLS GASPING )
All right?
Promise to do that.
And I'll let you go.
Except Dani.
Dani needs to be put down.
- No!
- Let us out! Let us out!
DR. REYES: It's okay.
It's for her own good.
And yours.
I'm sure you've figured out
her power by now.
So special.
She takes
your greatest fear...
your darkest secret...
and makes you
live through it.
No! ( CRYING )
DR. REYES: Over and over.
Over and over.
Until it kills you.
( STIFLED GROANING )
That's it.
That's it. Breathe.
- ( MUTANTS WHIMPERING )
- ( DR. REYES GRUNTS )
( MUTANTS GRUNTING )
That's it.
( STIFLED GROANING )
You're about to see
your father again.
In the spirit world.
( GASPING )
( BEEPING )
( HEAVY THUMP )
( GASPS )
( HEAVY FOOTFALLS )
What are you doing, Dani?
( FOOTFALLS APPROACHING )
( YELPS )
- ( GROWLING )
- ( SCREAMING )
( CONTINUES SCREAMING )
( GROWLING )
Dani.
Guys, she won't wake up.
Help me.
- SAM: Hey! Wake up!
- RAHNE: Dani!
RAHNE: Dani! Guys! Dani.
SAM: It's coming back!
( GROWLING )
It's hunting us.
No. It's hunting Dani.
Why Dani?
Because that's what
she fears.
Come on. Help me.
SAM: All right.
One, two, three.
( BOTH GRUNTING )
- ( MUFFLED CLANGING )
- ( GRUNTING )
ILLYANA: Take Dani
to a safe place...
and I'll take care
of this bear.
( CHANTS SPELL IN LATIN )
( ELECTRICAL BUZZING )
What are you going to do?
ILLYANA: I'm going to
play with it.
Get her out of here.
Are you crazy?
That thing'll kill you!
He's right.
It's magic.
So am I.
No! Illy!
- Hey, Yogi!
- ( LOCKHEED CHITTERS )
Lions and tigers
and bears. Oh, my.
- Right, Lockheed?
- ( CHITTERS )
( ROARING )
SAM: Holy shit!
ROBERTO: I'm gonna
marry that girl.
( LOCKHEED CHITTERS )
You okay, Lockheed?
( ROARING )
SAM: Come on!
Let's go. Let's go.
Berto, you have to run
with her.
I can't. I'm not ready.
RAHNE: You won't hurt her.
You can do this.
( ILLYANA GRUNTING IN DISTANCE )
Come on! This way.
( GRUNTING )
( ILLYANA SHOUTING )
You guys go.
I'm going back for Illy.
ROBERTO: Sam!
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Gotta get better someday.
RAHNE: Give her to me.
Hide.
Demons can't come in churches.
( PANTING )
Dani, I really need you
to wake up.
ILLYANA: Come back,
you coward!
RAHNE: Hail Mary,
full of grace...
blessed art thou
amongst women.
Pray for us sinners now
and in the hour of our death.
- Amen.
- ( LOUD CRASH )
( GROWLING )
( WHIMPERING )
Aah! No!
( ROARING )
( SCREAMING )
( CONTINUES SCREAMING )
Ahh!
( GROANS )
( RAHNE GASPING )
( ROARING )
( SAM SCREAMING )
( GRUNTS )
Demon Bear!
( GROWLS )
Nowhere to run now.
( ROARS )
I know you're in there.
Please. You're not alone.
I'm here.
We're all here...
fighting for you.
Rahne, where are you?
( WOLF PANTING )
Rahne!
Dani, I know
you can hear me in there.
( ILLYANA GRUNTING )
What are you doing?
I'm hiding, the same thing
you're doing.
- ( HEAVY FOOTFALL )
- ( GROWLING )
( ILLYANA GRUNTING )
SAM: Watch out!
( ILLYANA YELLING )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANING )
ILLYANA: Lockheed!
( YELPS, SOBBING )
( GROWLS )
SAM: Berto!
Nut up!
( ROARS )
- ( RAHNE YELPS )
- ( DEMON BEAR GROWLING )
( YELLS )
( GRUNTING )
( YELLING )
( ROARS )
( ECHOING ) Rahne!
RAHNE: You have to wake up...
or we're all going to die.
( GROANING )
Berto!
No! Berto!
( GROANING )
Only you can stop this.
DANI: I can't.
( ROARING )
( YELLING )
( GROWLS )
( SCREAMING MANIACALLY )
- ( YELPING )
- ( GROWLS )
( GASPING AND GRUNTING )
SAM: Dani!
Dad!
I'm so sorry.
DANI'S FATHER:
It wasn't your fault.
But now you need
to wake up.
But the bear,
it's too big.
You're bigger.
( ECHOING )
RAHNE: ( GRUNTS ) Dani!
( WHIMPERING )
No! Dani! Help!
Dani!
( RAHNE GASPING )
No!
Dani! ( SCREAMS )
Stop.
( ROARING )
No.
( DEMON BEAR PANTING )
( DEMON BEAR GRUNTING )
No.
( ROARS )
I'm in charge now.
Control.
( ROARS )
( DEMON BEAR PANTING )
Good.
( GROWLING )
( SHUSHING )
( DEMON BEAR GROWLING SOFTLY )
( SHUSHES )
( DEMON BEAR GRUNTING SOFTLY )
Everything is gonna be okay.
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore.
But it's time
to go to sleep now.
( DEMON BEAR GRUNTS QUIETLY )
( GRUNTS )
( SNIFFS )
( SIGHS )
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
( BLOWS )
( SIGHS )
Thank you.
Thanks, all of you.
For saving me.
Are you kidding?
You saved us.
( CHUCKLES SOFTLY )
Hey, guys. The dome's gone.
So we're free?
Reyes always said
the nearest town...
is 20 miles away.
She could be lying.
Shall we find out?
DANI: My father
used to tell me that...
inside every person,
there are two bears.
One bear is all things good.
Compassion, love, trust.
The other is all things evil.
Fear, shame,
and self-destruction.
I asked him, "Which one wins?"
He answered,
"The one you feed."