♪Wander in the darkness and listen♪
♪To the sadness of the rain secretly♪
♪The sudden sound of tears♪
♪Gather the past slowly♪
♪A quiet shimmer in the night♪
♪May not yet be able to shine♪
♪The desolation of anticipation
burns with abandon♪
♪The miracle ahead♪
♪Let me go wandering♪
♪Forget about the ordinary♪
♪Forget about sighs and confusion♪
♪Just see the direction of your heart♪
♪Don’t be sad♪
♪Dreams set sail♪
♪Let me fly♪
♪My hope♪
♪My freedom and power♪
♪Will all turn into a light♪
♪Writing the music of life♪
♪Blooming on the center stage♪
♪My dream makes me shine♪
=Shining Like You=
=Episode 15=
On a stormy night,
in a downtown theatre,
a spectacular musical is on.
The lead actress, Ruoyu,
wins a big round of applause.
But right at this moment,
a mysterious woman
shows up at the backdoor of the theatre.
She sneaks into the theatre
to recover what Ruoyu took from her.
Yes.
It’s a story
about two actresses fighting
for the lead.
What do you think?
It’s so real.
I like it.
Mm-hmm.
Not bad.
No objection.
So who’s the scriptwriter?
It’s me.
If you think it’s OK,
then let’s talk about the characters.
There are five characters in the play,
the mysterious woman, Rufeng,
the lead actress of the play, Ruoyu,
the lead actor of the play, Tianzong,
the patron of the theatre,
Mr. Three Million,
and a waiter
who appears as a clown.
I think Fang Yan is the best candidate
for Tianzong.
He’s noble and handsome,
but sort of eye candy.
Sanshang should play Mr. Three Million.
What about the clown?
It requires high flexibility
to play a clown.
I think Du Ang is our man.
I don’t play clowns.
You’re the most flexible among us.
No one can play it except you.
Shut up.
Am I funny?
Who said clowns must be funny?
They can be cool.
Right?
Yeah.
Well, I’ll rewrite the script.
As for the girls,
Kaixin is good for...
I want to play the lead actress.
Please, my dearest Qiyi.
Qiyi,
who would remember roles
other than the lead ones?
The lead actors are whom we watch on TV.
Kaixin,
I have an idea.
We both give it a try.
The better one gets the role,
OK?
Alright.
You’re such an affectionate man.
You’re buried in my soil,
where you take root,
and tie me up with your roots.
Your thick canopy
shades every inch of me.
In the abyss of darkness,
I’ve already fallen completely.
Look at me.
I don’t know when I started
to get used to living so humbly,
and wishing you could set your eyes
on me.
Forget it.
None of that matters anymore.
You’re the one
and only.
I love you
with all my heart.
I think Qiyi is better.
Qiyi did great,
but I’ll go with Kaixin.
Huh?
Sorry, Kaixin.
I think Qiyi is better.
What do you want?
Du!
If you’re angry,
take it out on me.
Why do you think I’m angry?
If you’re not happy,
punch me.
Do you have the guts to fight me?
What kind of man are you
to embarrass a girl in the rehearsal?
Listen, Fang Yan.
I’ll do my part in the play.
But our brotherhood
is over.
I wonder how Hao Kaixin
got admitted to Performing Arts.
I hear she has a special talent,
martial arts.
So she can only work as a stand-in
like a sandbag
in a crew.
In Showbiz,
plain girls have no future.
Shadowing Lu Qiyi doesn’t give her
any privileges.
Kaixin,
check it out for me.
Is the schedule OK?
Isn’t it always your call?
So, rehearsal at 9:00 AM tomorrow.
Don’t forget.
I want to play the lead actress.
Okay, my dearest Qiyi?
Like I said,
it’s difficult to be an actress.
Who would remember roles
other than the lead ones?
The lead actors are
whom we watch on TV.
Late for the first rehearsal.
Are we gonna rehearse or not?
Fang Yan said he couldn’t make it
and would come in the afternoon.
How can we rehearse with someone absent?
Let’s do it another time.
Kaixin,
let’s read the lines today.
Sanshang,
can you read Fang Yan’s lines?
I don’t mind.
But most of my parts are with Fang Yan.
I’m not good at
filling in for others.
Du.
Can we work a little hard on it?
The tryout is in two days.
If I were the lead actress,
I’d do my best.
How about this?
I’ll fill in for him.
OK.
Du Ang,
start with you.
Prologue.
I’ll start with this.
Du Ang.
Yeah.
You’re playing a clown.
Can you add more exaggerating
or funny moves?
I think it’d be better.
Oh.
Got it.
Well...
Hey!
Du Ang, where are you going?
I think we’re all in great shape.
However, we need to pay attention
to details,
especially the lines.
We need more practice.
Let’s go over it again.
OK.
Alright.
I’ll read it.
Act one,
date…
- Excuse me.
- March...
I have to take a call.
You guys go on.
You always interrupt me.
25th.
Hello? Hai.
Did you consider it?
Yes, I did.
I have so much homework.
So I probably can’t go this time.
Then I won’t be able
to get you a role in the film, Jujiu.
OK.
Maybe this is destined.
But do call me next time
when you need me.
Alright.
So be it.
Thank you.
Bye.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
How did it go with the rehearsal?
Not bad.
OK.
What’s it about?
It’s about two actresses
fighting for the lead.
You wrote the script?
Mm-hmm.
It’s a good theme.
Better be the head of a dog
than the tail of a lion.
The actors who don’t want to be the lead
are not good actors.
But Qiyi,
do you know
why everyone wants
to be the protagonist?
Because only they can be
remembered by the audience.
Have you watched Crazy Stone?
Yes.
Is Huang Bo the lead actor?
No.
But everyone remembers him.
And this supporting role
is the start of his career.
Do you know why?
Because he cherishes
every chance to perform.
His motto is
“There are no minor roles,
only blinkered actors.”
Qiyi,
do you know what to do now?
Hey,
hey, what is this different
from the real one?
It looks real,
which means it’s not real.
Then let’s do a swap.
Let’s just switch it over, right?
What?
Kaixin,
I want to talk to you.
A swap?
That’s right.
You can play Rufeng.
(Fang Yan as Tianzong)
Mr. Three Million,
Miss Ruoyu has been
very popular recently.
Shall we
give her a chance to audition
for the lead actress of the new play?
No.
(Li Sanshang as Mr. Three Million)
If Miss Rufeng finds out
someone is shaking her up
as the lead actress,
she’ll go crazy.
That’s true.
But a theatre has to
embrace new actors and actresses
to keep the audience’s attention.
Among all actresses,
who else is
more impressive than Ruoyu?
Not only does she have a good voice,
but she’s also tender
and modest.
Do you think we should...?
I advise you
to keep some distance from Ruoyu.
I heard
someone saw you
and her discussing script alone
in the park last night.
If Miss Rufeng finds out
that her boyfriend
is so kind to another woman,
she’ll probably be astonished.
We were discussing the script
last night.
She didn’t understand some of it.
The show is about to start.
Let’s watch
Miss Rufeng’s performance first.
(Lu Qiyi as Ruoyu)
(Hao Kaixin as Rufeng)
♪The stage is my kingdom♪
♪All bow to me♪
♪Be my prisoner♪
♪Make sure your heartbeat and passion
echo my steps♪
♪Keep spinning, make everyone jealous♪
♪Between heaven and earth♪
♪I’m the only one
who’s beautiful and kind♪
♪Everyone is crazy for me♪
(Du Ang as the Clown)
♪I do everything for your applause♪
♪Let me light the area in front of you♪
♪Tear your heart apart
and light up your eyes♪
♪Whose favorite are you
in the center of the stage♪
♪I will not be defeated♪
♪You’re nobody’s lead actress♪
Dean.
Yeah.
Would you like to say a few words?
After you. Please.
OK.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I can see that
you’ve put a lot of thought
into this assignment.
Good job.
We’ve discussed it
and agreed
that the play by Lu Qiyi’s team
is more fascinating
in both the storyline
and the performance.
And I admire their courage
to make it a musical.
So we decided
that Lu Qiyi’s team
should participate in the show
on behalf of the freshmen.
Yeah!
However,
there are some problems with it.
The stage effect is rather dull.
So we decided
some of you will perform
and the others work behind the scenes.
Let’s try our best
to present the best work
on the stage.
I hope everyone will work hard.
Dean?
Mm-hmm.
Your comments, please.
Sure.
Mr. Sun is right.
No more compliments.
It’s true that there are
still some problems.
The prominent one I think
is that we need to reconsider the cast.
I watched
the other three groups perform.
I think
Bai Qiao is a better candidate
for the homeless girl, Rufeng.
Also,
the clown.
It requires the high flexibility
of the actor.
It seems you can
barely manage it.
I think the most flexible boy
in your class
is a better candidate.
Sir,
so you’re saying
I’m no longer needed.
We should avoid our weaknesses.
Sir,
we have been practicing for a long time
and we perform better as a team.
It’s settled.
This musical
is meant to be the best by the freshmen.
So the cast has to be the best.
I’m fine.
Qiyi,
maybe I’ll never be
the lead actress in my life.
Hello?
Qiao,
when is this month’s money coming in?
Don’t worry.
I’ll transfer it in a few days.
Look,
your tuition is over 10,000 a year.
But till now,
you haven’t acted in any works.
What a waste of money!
Alright,
I’ll transfer the money tomorrow, OK?
Why do you want to sell your bag?
I don’t like it anymore.
This bag is worn out.
What?
How?
I only carried it twice.
Once it’s used, its value drops.
You name a price then.
3,000.
3,000?
I bought it for over 10,000.
Then inquire elsewhere.
That’s my offer.
Hello? Hai.
It’s about the thing you said last time.
Yeah, I’ve considered it.
800 soldiers rushed to the north slope.
For the next pose,
I’d like you to form some kind of
communication
with your partners.
Ready?
Go.
Nicely done, Qiyi.
You’re great, too.
What is this?
I’m Rose.
I’m Jack.
What a lame pose!
No wonder the ship sank.
OK, resume your positions!
The girls did great.
What’s wrong with the boys
in your class?
You’re so lifeless.
Can you practice a little harder?
Show me your muscles
and your strength!
Ma’am,
here comes the strength.
may I have a dance with you?
(Southern University of the Arts)
Hello? Aunt.
Hi, Qiyi.
Aunt, do you remember
the end-term show I told you about?
The date is set.
And I got the lead role.
Congratulations, Qiyi.
Good luck!
Thank you, Aunt.
And Dad said
he’d come to watch it
with my grandparents.
If you’re available,
I’d like to invite you, too.
Great. When?
It’s next weekend.
Make sure you do your best.
Don’t let us down.
Most of all,
don’t let your grandpa down.
Understood?
Don’t worry, Aunt.
I’ll do my best.
Good. Is that all?
I have to go.
Yes, that’s all.
By the way, Aunt,
I wrote the...
Hello?
Kaixin,
are you going out?
Mm-hmm.
How did you do
on the Marxist Philosophy test last week?
Not bad.
I can speak in a hoarse voice.
That would be better.
Bai Qiao,
finally.
Sorry.
I’m late.
It’s OK.
We just started.
I read the lines for you.
Thank you.
Hey,
you OK?
Yeah, I’m fine.
Let’s do it.
OK.
What the heck is going on?
Tianzong,
someone drugged my coffee.
I...
Help me, Tianzong.
What were you thinking?
You screwed up an important show.
It wasn’t my intention.
Someone set me up.
It’s like this.
It wasn’t my intention.
Someone set me up.
With emotion.
Look at him in the eyes.
What’s the difference?
Go on, go on.
Forget it. Don’t fight.
Help me, Tianzong.
Someone set you up?
Who can prove it?
I can testify to Miss Rufeng.
I saw it.
Someone did set her up.
Tianzong,
please believe me.
you have to believe me.
Tianzong,
I think you can grab him at this point.
Are you Rufeng or am I?
But every line I wrote
serves a purpose.
Calm down. It’s OK.
Qiyi is right.
Let’s do as she said.
Bai Qiao improvised it great.
It’s the same.
It means pretty much the same thing.
But...
I think we should call it a day.
No one’s in the best shape.
Hey,
Bai Qiao is definitely drunk.
Also,
why is Qiyi so irritable today?
She isn’t usually like this.
Why don’t we rehearse in the afternoon?
More?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Fang Yan,
was I bad-tempered
during the rehearsal?
I know you’re under a lot of pressure.
I invited my family to watch the show,
so I have to do my best.
Silly girl.
Don’t put so much pressure on yourself.
Thank you.
Well,
do you think the script is lame?
Let me put it this way.
Many scripts
are being revised
until the shooting.
Recently,
- Well…
- the famous actor, Su Wen...
Can you read the script
- after the evening rehearsal?
- According to an insider,
Su Wen is suspected of tax evasion.
And his previous investment in films
is thought to be money laundering.
Fang Yan.
Su Wen’s image as a good man
- Fang Yan.
- is questioned.
Huh?
Next, a quick look at the latest films.
Fang Yan,
- help me improve the script
- The shooting of The Undercover
- after the rehearsal.
- by a famous director, Wang Liang,
- I have other plans.
- kicks off at Hengdian.
- Maybe you have to do it on your own.
- We’re informed that this film
- I have to go.
- that features martial arts
takes 7 years in the planning.
Director Wang, with his talent,
gathers Li Kun, Zhao Ying
and other leading actors in his cast.
This film is expected
to be released next year.
You haven’t eaten, have you?
No.
I ordered some for you.
Here.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Mm-hmm.
It’s great.
I came over last night
and waited for you until 11:00 PM.
Is something wrong?
No.
My friend broke up with her boyfriend.
I went to stay with her.
Oh.
(Glamor Body Contouring)
Hi,
would you care to learn more?
Our hospital offers a discount now.
The price is low.
We have doctors from abroad.
The consultation is free.
Look at my face.
I had surgery there.
How do I look?
It’s completely natural.
Take it.
Hello, miss.
Take a look. Here.
(Glamor Body Contouring)
We offer a discount now.
Favorable price for face shaping
and whitening.
(Micro-plastic Surgery)
No, thanks.
It’s true. Take a look.
Go consult the doctor.
I was told that the doctor
came from abroad.
I did come back from abroad.
Generally speaking,
your face
is featureless.
Your facial organs
don’t look bad.
But on the whole…
How should I put it?
I think it’s unattractive.
Really unattractive.
Well,
what do you suggest?
Miss,
don’t worry.
Well,
we can get your chin
reduced a bit.
Here.
Check this out.
We have several packages.
Yeah, this one.
And this.
Doctor,
do I have to do all these?
Don’t you want to be a star?
Yeah.
Then tell me this.
Which actor or actress
hasn’t had plastic surgery?
I’ll be honest with you.
I’m not exaggerating.
Our hospital
is basically their first choice.
Well, for our business’s sake,
we have to keep it confidential.
I promise
you’ll become prettier and more elegant
than those actresses.
Because you’re not bad all over.
And you’re young.
Right?
Rest assured.
We won’t mislead you.
We have professional ethics.
It’s your call.
OK.
I don’t have the key.
Dude,
my dorm is locked.
I can’t get in.
Can I use your phone?
Do you have Uzhda’s number?
How about Luo Xiuwen’s?
You don’t have their numbers?
I don’t know them.
Alright. Forget it.
I’ll sit and wait.
How many times have I told you
not to turn around when filming?
You wanna steal the spotlight?
From the lead actress?
I’m talking about you.
Don’t laugh.
Fame or job? Your choice.
Let me tell you.
I can find as many extras
like you as I wish.
Do you want to keep this job or not?
Ox.
Get out of here.
I’m Hao Kaixin.
I’m good at martial arts.
Hao Kaixin.
Yeah.
What can I do for you?
I want
to make money.
To make money?
Yeah.
Is there anything I can do?
I’m counting on you, Ox.
Come with me.
(Chiba Restaurant)
You’re good.
What a waste
if you don’t act!
Come to me when you need money.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Ox.
However, I have to give you
a small tip.
As a stunt double,
your face can’t appear on camera.
If necessary,
you take the beating.
Don’t fight back.
Got it.
Yeah.
(Casablanca)
Hey, Sun.
What are you doing tonight?
It’s your birthday.
Don’t you remember?
It doesn’t matter how I found out.
Clear your schedule for tonight.
Alright, say no more.
It’s settled.
Why did Lu Qiyi choose Fang Yan?
Why didn’t she choose you?
Me?
It doesn’t matter.
But look at me.
I’m good-looking,
hot,
humorous,
and charming.
And I’m rich.
I can’t even find a flaw in myself.
You and Lu Qiyi were
childhood sweethearts
and you’ve known each other
for ten years.
I would understand if she chose you.
But how was she bewitched by Fang Yan?
I think you’re good
in every way,
except for the long face.
But you’re kind under the cool demeanor,
a better man than Fang Yan.
And you’re more handsome.
You’re not bad.
Oh, I’m flattered.
Hey,
you’re always playing others’ songs.
Why don’t you write one yourself?
I haven’t written songs in a long time.
Your inspiration has dried up.
That’s a shame.
It’s a shame.
(Xiaoshi
I’m already here.)
(Xun)
Hello?
Shall we begin?
I’d like to apologize to you.
I was bad-tempered.
It’s OK.
We understand.
Let’s do it.
OK.
By the way, Qiyi.
Let’s practice the part in the center.
I think…
You and Sanshang should come up first.
Hello? Kaixin.
Don’t panic.
I’ll be right there.
What’s wrong?
It’s Kaixin!
Hey!
Calm down.
Tell us what happened.
Kaixin hurt an actor in the crew.
She’s detained by Ox.
He’s gonna break her leg
if we don’t compensate.
I have to go save her.
I know Ox.
I’ll go with you.
♪I hide all my thoughts in my heart♪
♪Don’t dare to reveal the trace of love♪
♪I’ve been ignorant about love♪
♪I’ve never felt the world beating♪
♪If I come closer♪
♪It will be a crush this time♪
♪Even if it’s the last time♪
♪To prove that I can be brave enough
to hold your hand♪
♪Look, we’ll bloom
in the middle of the stage♪
♪Our steps are dreams of love♪
♪Every note♪
♪Every beat exists because of you♪
♪Listen, we’re singing the most♪
♪Beautiful song in every moment♪
♪I’ll always remember the touching♪
♪Moments in life that won’t fade♪
♪The touching moments in life
that won’t fade♪
(Behind the clouds is the sun.
After every rain, there is a rainbow.)
(Many thanks to your company.
Pursuit your dreams and shine!)