(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Episode 10)
My money.
My money. It's mine.
- Chief. Chief! - There are people inside!
- There are people inside! - Stop it!
- Let us out! - No!
Chief!
- Kang Yo Han! - Don't do it!
Stop it!
I'm only trying to give him an opportunity.
- Don't do it. - Save them.
- Don't do it. - Don't do it!
No!
Hey.
Don't do it.
Honey! Get us out of here!
Save us! Help!
Let me go. Let go!
Calm down and look at him.
My money!
My money.
- My money! - Honey! Save us!
My money!
No!
What is this? It's all fake!
It's not my money.
It's not mine!
- I must save them! - Relax.
Relax and watch.
This is... What happened is... So... This is...
He lied to his family too.
That he'd lost all the money.
Seo Jin.
Seo Jin. Daddy didn't have a choice.
Honey, I'll explain everything. I'll...
Darn you!
Don't go! Stay!
Don't go!
Here. Get your revenge if you want.
Don't hesitate.
Don't hurt me.
I'm sorry. Let me live. I'm sorry for what I did.
Please don't kill me.
I'm really sorry.
My money.
My money! My money...
He's our only bait to get Cha Kyung Hee.
Let's not waste him.
Are you having fun?
Not really.
I don't know what else to do with cards.
- You don't know? - No.
- Haven't you played cards? - Who would I play with?
Well, with your family I guess.
Or with your friends.
I'm sorry. I'm saying useless things again.
Are you trying to meddle in my life again?
Don't make an assumption about me.
I don't like hanging out with people.
Anyway.
I want to thank you...
for catching Doh Young Choon.
You don't have to.
We've only built the second floor so far.
The second floor?
Through Cha Kyung Hee's secretary, we caught Doh Young Choon.
Now we should work on the third floor.
When we're done with Cha Kyung Hee, will we deal with Heo Joong Se?
Who's at the end?
I don't know how tall the building will be.
But what I'm more interested in is...
bringing down the building at once.
You thought I'd bring it down, didn't you?
So did you look into Juk Chang?
It seemed you were digging up his back.
Yes.
Juk Chang and his gang started assaulting people on the street...
when Heo Joong Se started instigating his followers...
to take to the streets.
We can't just depend on the police.
We should take the initiative to make this country safe.
Tonight, we will become the real heroes.
What else did you find out?
- Well, Secretary? - Yes, sir.
Can you turn on episode 86 of Heo Joong Se's show?
The second week in September four years ago.
Yes, sir.
You two are close friends now.
Korea's Total Change. I'm Heo Joong Se.
- How refreshing! - How refreshing!
Hello, I'm Do Yeon Jung.
Hi! I'm Heo Joong Se.
Kids I love and respect.
Do you know why you're unemployed losers?
Do you know why you've never gone out...
with a pretty lady like my wife...
and lead a low life?
I'll tell you the reason.
It's because of the higher-ups. The privileged ones.
It's because they abandoned you.
There's a cheap labor force that would do anything for them.
They are cheap foreigners.
The privileged people are replacing you guys...
with these cheap foreigners.
Do you understand me?
- Do you? - I understand.
I mentioned Seo Jeong Hak many times.
It's only 19 dollars. 19 dollars.
You have to read this.
People with pure Korean blood will disappear in this country.
People of mixed race will dominate.
Soon we won't have any genuine Koreans left...
in this country.
So you have to come to your senses.
You should protest holding a bamboo spear or something.
You should protect this nation!
Young people should organize a patriotic society.
Show them you can form an army...
- and you can... - Honey.
I think that's enough.
Everyone, you should always listen to a pretty lady like her.
I guess you admit that she is a pretty lady.
Was that why you were laughing?
You like to play the field, right? What a loser.
Can you turn and shoot him?
Shoot the loser's face.
Stop.
He worked for him as a video editor.
He was the president of Heo Joong Se's fan club at first...
and was selected as his staff member.
He also helps his presidential election campaign.
It's very interesting.
He wants young people to organize a patriotic society.
Heo Joong Se had an absurd dream from the beginning.
Should we put him on trial?
Obviously, I think we should.
If we let him go wild like this, he'll cause so much trouble.
They're like the president's soldiers.
Cheers.
I think it's hilarious how you made Kang Yo Han pose for the shoot.
You held him back for a while, Ms. Jung.
Well, I should call you Chairwoman Jung now.
Don't worry about him. I'll hold him back tight.
That guy nosed around to dig dirt on the Dream Home project.
And that wasted so much of our time.
Wasting time means wasting money. Darn it.
So let's not walk on eggshells now and push ahead.
Let's gather the poor and the people protesting against us in Seoul.
Then we can put them in jail and plan a reality show.
The title of the show could be "Clean Korea".
We should also put illegal migrants in jail.
Your approval rating will go up.
Just wait for now.
There are people who are waiting to stab me in the back.
The police and the prosecution. I can't trust them with my plans.
I should empower the organization that is more loyal to me...
and have them take care of things.
I'm nearly ready.
(2nd branch, Ministry of Justice, Juvenile Education Center)
(HMBN Chairman Park Du Man)
(Recording Report)
How is the fact-checking going on Jung Sun Ah's story?
It's quite difficult because they happened a long time ago.
Stop working on everything else.
Put everyone on it.
Why can't you work faster?
Yes, ma'am.
The team leader is concerned about one thing.
What is it?
The number of unprovoked attacks increased recently.
They're mostly targeting foreign workers and women.
So? What do you want me to do about it?
People are asking...
why the Ministry of Justice isn't doing anything about it.
Did people die or something?
Not really but...
They're attacking people on the street in broad daylight.
This phenomenon goes exactly against the slogan, "Safe Korea".
But that's Heo Joong Se's slogan.
It's his presidential election pledge.
Why do I have to be concerned about it?
I apologize, ma'am.
Heo Joong Se, that jerk...
is instigating silly kids to create a climate of fear.
Maybe he thinks it's going to empower him.
But he's wrong.
If we just let them be, someone will cross the line.
Maybe they'll kill someone.
And when the people get sick and tired of them,
we'll take matters into our hands.
I'm the Minister of Justice, Cha Kyung Hee.
As a presidential candidate,
I dream of a unified country...
by embracing everyone in Korea.
Certainly, ma'am.
So you deal with Jung Sun Ah.
We should stop her before she gets more powerful.
It's strange that Seo Jeong Hak suddenly died.
There's a bigger picture.
The picture that Jung Sun Ah drew.
I understand, ma'am.
And one more thing.
Yes, ma'am.
You're checking on him regularly, right?
Who are you talking about, ma'am?
Doh Young Choon.
Yes, I am checking on him regularly, ma'am.
He must have money hidden somewhere.
That sneaky little jerk.
He'd do anything for money.
Why are you standing there?
- You may leave. - Yes, ma'am.
You're the most talked-about person these days.
We have Judge Oh Jin Joo of the live court show with us.
Hello, Your Honor.
Hello.
I saw pictures from your photo shoot.
And you looked amazing.
- Thank you. - People are raving about it.
They say you should quit your job and become an actress.
Not everyone can become an actress.
Everyone, I was born to be a civil servant.
Plus, I get to work until an older age.
You're so funny.
How do you handle it though?
The entire nation is watching you.
It must be pretty tiring.
No, I don't have the time to feel tired.
So many people are supporting me.
- Really? - Yes.
They send a ton of letters to my office.
- Do you want to have a look? - Sure.
You're keeping all of them?
Knowing that there are people who trust and support me...
really motivates me and makes me happy.
I hope Judge Oh's sincerity gets through to our viewers.
You're the best.
Gosh. It's finally over.
You did an amazing job, Judge Oh.
I'm always amazing.
Why didn't you join the interview?
I felt awkward doing it alone.
I'm camera-shy.
That's not okay. We live in a media age.
We need to communicate with the public.
This would've been the perfect time to hold our next trial.
I wonder what Chief Kang is up to.
I have something to show you.
What is it?
- Stop! - No!
Stop it!
- Hey! - Are they crazy?
My goodness. Oh, no.
What were the police doing?
(The Jukchang troops are cleaning up Busan.)
Nice! Way to go, Busan.
- Hold on. - Are you guys going to help me?
We are...
power.
How about...
we put him on trial?
On our live court show?
Judge Oh has agreed. The problem is...
How are we going to arrest and put him on trial...
when the police are protecting him?
Exactly. For him to be tried, he needs to be prosecuted first.
But he's practically being protected by the president.
How are we going to...
But you know,
there's someone who would love to help us out.
Who do you mean?
Someone who would hate to see...
things go Heo Joong Se's way.
Cha Kyung Hee?
I doubt she'll agree to help you.
Of course, she won't listen to me.
That's why Lawyer Ko is leaking information to her...
through his connections in the prosecution.
That Juk Chang and his gang works for Heo Joong Se.
Once we arrest the guy, he can be prosecuted, I guess.
But she'll still feel uncomfortable putting him on trial.
I do know one officer...
who might be up to the task.
An officer?
Do you mean Soo Hyun?
Since the commissioner has the guy's back,
she'll have to do the job by herself.
That's impossible.
I'm sure she's already on the move.
Okay. Busan is done now.
After Busan, we'll go to Daegu...
What next?
Daejeon it is.
All patriots in Daejeon, show me what you've got.
You want to beat these guys, don't you?
Show me how patriotic you all are.
What are you thinking about?
- Gosh, you startled me. - Let's do this.
Don't sneak up on me like that.
You want to get him?
Well...
Yes, I do.
Since he got caught last time,
he's been hiding, just broadcasting alone.
I see.
Then track him down.
Do you need my help?
You?
Let me see.
Give that to me.
Are you sure?
Here.
Well...
Let's see here.
I doubt it's going to be this easy,
but first...
I knew it. The security is pretty tight.
That's impressive.
I can see you're a computer major.
(Thug)
Excuse me.
- Hi, Soo Hyun. - Hi, Ga On.
You haven't been home in a while.
Well, I've been busy.
Anyway, are you okay?
Juk Chang posted a video of you pointing a gun at him,
and it could give people the wrong idea.
You have no idea. I had to hand in my gun for that.
The jerk really needs to be caught,
but the higher-ups won't cooperate.
I can't get any help from the Cyber Bureau.
At least I should try to stop him.
Otherwise, no one knows how far the jerk will go.
Are you already on it?
Oh, I'm just playing some games.
- Games? - Yes.
Do you think you hack...
by pounding away at the keyboard?
Is that what you imagine?
You're clueless.
I'm running a program in the background.
Just give it some time.
It'll take a while.
A day, a week, or longer.
Thanks, Elijah.
Wait.
What is it?
He just clicked the link I included in my comment.
I didn't expect him to fall for such a simple trick.
What link is it?
It's a link to some pictures of female singers.
Female singers?
Hi, Ga On.
What? You've tracked down Juk Chang? Where is he?
I'll head over there right now.
Soo Hyun, calm down.
It's dangerous. Request an official investigation.
No one will help me.
Also, catching one moron is no big deal.
You don't even have a gun. It's too dangerous.
Don't worry. Just send me the address.
I'm serious.
Do as I say.
Soo Hyun...
(Jung Sun Ah, who is suspected of having murdered Seo Jeong Hak...)
The story is there.
But there's not enough evidence.
To bring her down at once,
I at least need more circumstantial evidence.
- Minister. - What is it?
The foundation has cut down on subsidies for the ministry.
- What? - They just decided it on their own.
We won't have enough funds to run the unofficial organizations.
I can't believe that woman.
Minister, you didn't make an appointment.
I'm sorry. She just barged in.
Gosh.
It's okay. I slept well.
Don't do that. She works for our country.
It's been a while.
Has it?
I've been a little distant, right?
Please forgive me.
Being the board chairman is not easy.
Why did you cut back on the subsidies?
Is that why you're here?
You must've been very disappointed.
Please understand us.
There are many organizations that need our help,
but with people becoming more selfish, we get fewer donations.
But you're giving more money to the Blue House now.
Well...
That must've been decided by the working-level employees.
I don't remember it well.
Do you want me to refresh your memory?
Do you smell something?
Like what?
For some reason, I smell blood around you.
What could it be?
What are you talking about?
How long has it been since Mr. Seo's suicide?
Wait.
It must be a touchy subject.
I apologize.
You served him for a long time.
It must've been a shock. You must be in grief.
What is it you're trying to say, Minister?
Being that I'm in the position that I'm in,
I hear a lot of things, you see.
For example?
An elder who had received national respect committed suicide.
A national funeral wouldn't have been enough,
but you rushed to get his body cremated.
Why was his suicide note...
written on the computer instead of by hand?
Especially since he always wrote things in calligraphy.
Do you not have a lot of work these days?
Do you want me to give you more work?
What did you say?
Come back when you have concrete evidence, and we'll talk then.
I'm busy...
working for our country.
- Jae Hee? - Yes?
My guest is leaving.
Oh, and Minister Cha.
I'm sorry,
but the cost of fuel for your official car is quite high.
The national finances aren't doing so well,
so can we change it to something a bit smaller?
The citizens will be moved.
They'll say that...
the eldest person running our nation is different from others.
You must be crazy.
(Your precious vote. A safe Korea will be realized now.)
What on earth are you doing?
What's taking so long to find something on Jung Sun Ah?
I'm sorry, ma'am. Please give us more time.
My gosh, you are all so incompetent.
I should go meet Kang Yo Han.
Pardon? You want to see Kang Yo Han?
What is it? Why are you so surprised?
It was just so sudden.
Jung Sun Ah's file said that she was a maid in Kang Yo Han's house.
I'm sure Kang Yo Han will know something...
to help us look into that woman's past.
Set up a meeting with him.
Choose a quiet Japanese restaurant.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you sure that this is the place?
(Goryeo Real Estate)
How did you find out about it?
By the way, why are you here?
I thought you'd be bored if you came alone.
Were you worried about sending me here alone?
Yes, I was worried.
- What? - Not you, Juk Chang.
I was worried you might end up beating him half to death.
It's a power shutter.
I think this is the only entrance.
- Hey, Elijah. - Elijah?
The entrance is closed with a shutter.
Oh, okay.
Why did Elijah call?
Elijah's the one who traced the IP address to this building.
Really?
She's a genius who was admitted to Stanford early for computer science.
She's incredible.
I still think this will be hard to open.
Let's look for another entrance.
(Goryeo Real Estate)
Be careful.
(Best Math Academy)
(King of Dance Academy)
(KU Security)
Soo Hyun. Come up.
- Why? - It's open.
What?
(Goryeo Real Estate)
Hey, Elijah.
You're incredible.
How did you manage to hack into this too?
That's enough. Just be careful. Both of you.
Thank you.
Hacking? They're such ordinary people.
(KU Security, Business: Security)
Okay.
Hello?
I'm inside Jinheung Building right now.
Oh, really? How are you in there at this hour?
I attend Best Math Academy,
and I stayed to study for a test, and...
Mister, I'm so scared.
What should I do?
Okay. I'll open up for you.
Really? Thank you. Thank you so much.
Do you think we'll be okay?
What if someone is here standing guard?
Do you think a loser who does internet broadcasts has bodyguards?
I looked it up, and he records his broadcasts in a small venue.
Hey.
(Chang Speech Academy)
(Jukchang)
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
Stop lying. We have 40 minutes left!
I'm starving right now!
Where are you?
I'll go get it!
Hi.
It's been a while.
Are you here alone?
Let go.
That hurts.
Let's go.
I'm going to go.
Darn it. What took you so long?
Hey.
Go back.
Gosh. That hurts!
Come help me!
(Chang Speech Academy)
Hey, you punk!
Are you okay?
Go check it out.
Kang Yo Han?
Just focus on getting Juk Chang.
Is it a fair fight now?
Darn it.
Darn it!
[VIU Ver] tvN E10 'The Devil Judge'
"The Revolutionist"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Shoot. My arm hurts.
This is for real, you loser.
How are you all?
Wow, the youth, law, education. You're doing great work.
It's fine. Don't mind me.
It's fine. Keep doing what you were doing.
If there's something fun, show me too.
Minbo Group?
Gosh, the audio is so darn clear.
I can even hear Min Yong Shik's breathing.
What do you think you're doing here?
Is this your Inwang-dong Team that's better than...
the National Intelligence Service?
Let's go inside.
Let's talk out here.
They're all on your team.
How did you find this place?
I'm very interested in the youth, law, and education.
Forget that and get to the point.
How do you know Jung Sun Ah?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I heard she used to work as your servant.
- Is that true? - I can't say.
I can't speak of another person's private life.
There's talk that she killed her own parents.
Is there? That's shocking.
"Nothing's for free."
That's what your look says.
What is it you want?
Juk Chang.
"Juk Chang"?
Cooperate with me so I can put him on trial.
The prosecution just has to indict him,
then sit and watch the show.
Heo Joong Se will make a fuss.
Why are you being so timid?
I'm the one who must deal with the aftermath.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, by the way.
I found this on the way here.
Shall I give it to you? Or to him?
Here you go.
(Unnatural Death Case Report Statement: Jung Sun Ah)
(Statement: Jung Sun Ah)
(Autopsy Report)
An internet broadcaster...
Isn't this...
too menial a case for the live court show?
He instigated violence and caused unrest.
Wouldn't it please the Blue House too?
I believe it goes very well with the president's wish...
to strengthen law and order.
That does make sense.
Very well. Make this work.
How did it go?
It's a pass.
Let me set up this one.
You?
I know people like Juk Chang very well.
This is a blatant challenge to...
the beloved and respected people of Korea.
A patriotic young man took action...
to protect his country, and he's being put on trial?
Are judges that great?
Are they above the people?
This is clearly a coup planned by the judiciary!
(What is Kang Yo Han's plan?)
This isn't what I thought.
Either way, didn't this happen because of...
a young man's pure patriotism to protect his country?
Right?
Whether this trial is carried out fair and lawfully,
I will keep a watchful eye until the very end.
(President voices displeasure)
Darn it.
Kang Yo Han, I want to rip you apart.
This is insane.
Mr. Lawyer.
I'm a political offender.
A revolutionary leader.
I'm not like the common criminal. Do you get that?
Then shall I not submit anything that shows mitigating circumstances?
Like your unhappy upbringing?
Hang on.
Wouldn't it be an advantage to submit that?
Write something up. With as much detail as possible.
Okay, I'll do that.
Since we're on the topic,
Kang Yo Han and the younger judge came at me...
and threatened me with a wooden pole.
How about we leak that to the media?
To plea insanity,
you need a doctor's diagnosis.
I saw it.
Would I lie to you about that?
You saw it?
Then can you give me a list of names of people who witnessed it?
I need objective evidence.
No, forget it.
I was alone.
Are you sure you can win?
I can't go to prison.
Yes, don't worry.
I'll get you out on probation.
You're putting in too much effort.
You care for the plants here...
and a gruff guy and weird girl in a weird mansion.
I'm pretty sure I'm just as weird.
Yes, you have been a bit weird.
Why? Did Professor Min say something?
Why would he?
I haven't seen him since we met here last time.
Oh, really?
I wondered if he nagged again.
You suddenly show up outside my workplace...
and ask what I'd do if you did something bad.
Then Kang Yo Han shows up when we're trying to get Juk Chang.
Are you up to no good?
Do you think so?
No, well...
I just feel a bit jealous.
My childhood best friend's hanging out with a rich guy...
and it feels weird.
Like you're living in a different world.
I see.
He's not rich.
If you get to know him,
Kang Yo Han's really poor.
I'm way richer.
I have fond memories of my mom and dad...
and a pretty home I kept.
And...
I have a fan club.
They root for me.
I'm going home.
Already?
I'm busy.
Being a police officer keeps you busy.
Get home safe.
I have you,
Soo Hyun.
Hi, Master Yo Han.
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
Just because you're the head of the Operation Support Committee...
doesn't mean you can barge in like this.
Why do you keep making me barge in?
Are you doing this on purpose to see me?
What brings you here today?
The live court show.
Why did you choose such a high-profile case again?
The defendant is neither a politician nor a conglomerate.
What's high-profile about it?
Isn't he just a petty offender?
He works for Heo Joong Se.
He was throwing a fit, saying he'd get rid of the live court show,
but I managed to calm him down.
I told you to wait just two years.
Why do you keep complicating things?
Wow, that psycho works for the president?
That's interesting.
The thing is, he attacked my niece.
He did?
It's still not okay.
You'll have to give in this time.
Just scold him a little in court and let him go.
What if I can't?
That would put me in a difficult situation.
And that would mean...
you'll be in a difficult situation too.
All right.
I'll think about it.
Master Yo Han, you're being a good boy these days.
So please stop barging in like this.
Exactly. Instead of making me barge in like this,
you should invite me sometimes.
Is your house still beautiful?
Like in the old days?
Do you miss the place where you used to work as a maid?
Never...
Never say that again.
I was just a guest who stayed there for a while.
Don't you dare insult me.
Fine. I'll keep that in mind.
We are...
- Juk Chang! - Juk Chang!
- We are power! - We are power!
Guys, quiet.
- Juk Chang! - Juk Chang!
As you can see, the Supreme Court is...
filled with excitement about today's trial.
The supporters of the defendant...
are continuing their protest inside the Supreme Court.
Worrying that the excessive enthusiasm...
will lead to accidents,
the court has decided to hold the trial behind closed doors.
(Live Court Show)
Let's start the trial.
Defendant Kim Choong Sik?
My name is Kim Ju Won. Please call me Kim Ju Won.
The court must use your registered name,
Defendant Kim Choong Sik.
Let me ask you again.
Defendant Kim Choong Sik?
Yes, Your Honor.
You're on trial for organizing and instigating...
random attacks against...
foreign workers, women, and sexual minorities...
throughout the country.
Your Honor.
Do you have something to say?
- Yes. - Go ahead.
(Live Court Show)
(Defendant)
Before the trial, let me make a solemn declaration...
before history and our people.
My brave deed...
cannot be tried in a worldly court.
Therefore, I'd like to read aloud my declaration of national salvation.
The court is not a place for incitement.
The Japanese judges who tried independence activists...
would've said that too.
What are you so afraid of?
Why are you hiding the truth, Judge Kang?
Fine, I get it.
You can go ahead.
(Live Court Show)
(Counsel)
(Declaration of National Salvation)
"One faithful man is worth..."
"a million selfish men."
"I, Kim Ju Won,"
"am ready to become a devil for my beloved country."
"Compatriots,"
"stop being hypocrites and protect our people first."
"The three-year-long epidemic left us with no jobs."
"Foreigners invade our country and commit all kinds of crimes."
"Our women laugh and talk with foreigners on the street,"
"linking arms with them."
"Foreign young men are taking our jobs away,"
"taking our women away,"
"and taking even our souls away."
"Making things right in the country..."
"means..."
"becoming the true owners of the country again."
"As someone who loves this country, I'm convinced."
"We must drive all foreigners out."
"We must kick all mongrels out of this country."
"A pure Korea. A safe Korea."
"Together, we'll achieve it again."
"That's what patriotism means."
"We are power."
Yes, we are. Well said.
He is the person we're serving.
Guys, vote right now.
How's it going? 55, 56, 57...
(National Vote Status)
What's going on? What happened?
His supporters must be taking action as a group.
(Hourly Graph)
(In Opposition To, In Favor Of)
Are you done?
I'll stop here for now.
- Defendant. - Yes?
Do you know the occupation of the foreign workers...
who were attacked by your group?
I'm not sure.
Is that really something a revolutionary should know?
They lost two colleagues...
in a gas leak during sewer repair.
The repair had been put off because no one wanted to work on it.
Defendant, whose jobs do you think they took away?
During times of war, there are bound to be innocent victims.
You shouldn't disparage the people's legitimate anger.
The people?
Did you say, "legitimate anger"?
Here we go!
- What are you doing? - Stop it!
That sure looks very legitimate.
Right? It really does, doesn't it?
That's what happens to a foreigner when he takes away one of our women.
Your Honor, have you heard of the purity of a single-race nation?
Did you say, "our women"?
Women are citizens of this country as well.
We don't belong to men.
Our people, my foot.
I apologize for my inappropriate language.
I just felt a surge of some legitimate anger...
that's hard to control.
It sounded like you swore.
But your voice is too low. Can you come closer?
- Defendant. - Should I come to you?
(National Vote Status)
Defendant.
Please focus.
(In Opposition To, In Favor Of)
- Defendant. - Yes?
Try to calm down.
Okay.
We've never met before,
but seeing you makes me feel sorry.
You must've led a difficult life.
We've met before. Don't you remember it?
- Your Honor. - Yes?
Is it okay if I go down to the defendant...
and talk to him?
Sure, go ahead.
Thank you.
(Live Court Show)
(Counsel)
There...
is a young man here.
He might be acting tough, but on the inside,
there is a child who has been hurt.
What are you doing right now?
I'm talking about the documents your lawyer sent us...
asking us to grant you an extenuation.
What?
(Counsel)
I was told that ever since you were young,
you were obsessed with gaining the attention of others. Is this true?
- What did you say? - Your grandmother was very worried.
Let's watch the footage.
Choong Sik hasn't always been a bad kid.
- Grandma. - I heard...
he instigated some type of demonstration,
- but he would never do that. - What is that?
He's just acting up because he's immature.
- Did you agree to this? - So please forgive him.
Hey, Choong Sik. About what you took last time...
- Hurry up and turn that off. - That...
- Turn it off right now! - Your grandma...
- was saving up for her funeral. - Don't turn it off.
You don't need to do anything else.
Just make sure you return that money to her.
Please do that.
Are you crazy? Why would you say that?
That's the only way you can have a proper funeral.
My goodness. You're crazy. You've lost your mind.
Counsel. How was the defendant during his school days?
His homeroom teacher took some time to speak with us.
- Let's watch this together. - What is this? What...
He incited violence for political reasons?
He would never do such a thing.
He acted like a bully when he was a student,
but in reality, he idolized them and copied what they did.
He wasn't accepted as one of them.
My gosh. What a waste of time and money?
A loser who copied the bullies?
Choong Sik went to school with me.
Do you know what he did when he was a student?
He got caught planting hidden cameras in the girls' bathroom,
and he got expelled.
He says he wants to start a revolution,
but he's not someone who's capable of doing that.
Please have mercy on him.
You're going to make him into a loser instead of a devil?
This will ruin things.
The people around the defendant say this about him,
but there's one thing that bothers me.
The defendant...
continuously asked for donations through his channel.
He said that he needs funds to create a revolution in our nation.
He managed to collect a significant amount of money.
What did you do with that money?
Why are you avoiding eye contact, Defendant?
Did you purchase bombs and guns in the black market?
What exactly are funds for a revolution?
No. I don't know what you're talking about.
- I plead the fifth. - Defendant, if this is the truth,
this is treason.
The main culprit behind treason can be sentenced to death,
life imprisonment, or life imprisonment without labor.
Were you aware of this, Defendant?
No.
Do you have something to say, Counsel?
Yes. The defendant didn't use that money to plot treason.
This is a part of the defendant's privacy,
so I was hesitant to reveal it,
but in this situation, I have no choice. Let's watch it together.
(Counsel)
- Let's watch it. - I work as a content creator.
One day, Kim Choong Sik and another fan got into a battle,
and they started sending me a lot of donations.
It was a couple of thousand dollars every single day.
- No! I don't know her! - It's not like he's rich.
- I wish he would stop. - What are you doing?
- He keeps asking to meet me. - Please calm down.
He keeps begging me.
He makes me feel uncomfortable.
- I really wish he would stop. - No way.
Did you use your grandmother's funeral funds to send her donations?
You went too far.
(National Vote Status)
Hold on. It's okay.
It's okay. I told you I'd make sure you got off with a reprieve.
Go back to your seat.
Go ahead.
It's okay.
Your Honors.
As you can see, the defendant isn't a revolutionary.
And he's not a dangerous person who's plotting treason.
To be honest, he's not even worth being on trial right now.
- Lawyer Ko. - Of course,
the defendant's crimes aren't small,
but I will be grateful if you gave him a chance to redeem himself.
What could be the best punishment for the defendant?
Is it flogging? Or is it imprisonment?
I racked my brains for an answer.
I received the suggestion that...
we give this young defendant another chance,
so I sentence the defendant to three years in prison...
with a five-year stay of execution.
However,
the defendant's crimes were terrible...
and the chance of recidivism is quite high,
so the defendant must wear an electronic anklet...
and be placed on probation.
Through the electronic anklet signal, the defendant's location...
will be traceable on the DIKE app.
(DIKE)
(Kim Choong Sik, Date of Birth: September 23, 1993, Age: 33)
An electronic anklet? What an embarrassment.
What are you going to do in the summer? You can't wear shorts now.
As of today, I'm creating a squad to go after Juk Chang.
Hey, Juk Chang. Come out. I'll go after you.
To all the citizens watching this trial,
can you all be...
(The defendant's location)
the defendant's probation officer?
Keep an eye on what he's doing and where he is.
Don't take your eyes off of him for one second.
The defendant needs your attention.
Don't you agree, Defendant?
My gosh. I brought him up, and he ruined it all!
My gosh! Kang Yo Han!
Just scold him a little in court and let him go.
All right.
I'll think about it.
(Defendant Kim Choong Sik sentenced to probation.)
(The entire nation can trace him via an electronic anklet.)
Darn it.
Did he fool me?
Do you see Juk Chang behind me?
I will show you how I punish Juk Chang live.
Don't forget to subscribe, leave comments, and like.
(Why is Juk Chang so fast?)
(Where did he go? Let's get him!)
- Get him! - The Kim Choong Sik Case...
is a national embarrassment,
and it should never happen again.
This kind of behavior is like spitting on the faces...
of everyone across the country who has volunteered...
to help provide relief, and our beloved citizens...
with their pure patriotism.
It's a case that just reeks.
It smells. It smells terribly...
like a conspiracy.
Where did he go?
Let's keep going. Hurry.
But that man, Kim Choong Sik. Is he really Korean?
Is he a real Korean, like us?
Not a fake Korean, but a real Korean with citizenship?
One nation, pureblood.
A descendant of Dangun would never do something so idiotic...
I'm sorry. I meant, they would never do...
something so embarrassing.
That's all.
There you are.
You should hide, so we can't come find you.
Are you going to let them do that to Choong Sik?
Hey, are you crazy?
Don't you dare bring up his name ever again.
Yeon Jung, this is really hard on me.
My goodness.
Gosh, darn it.
Hey! Why do you keep running away?
Your location can be traced with this app.
Everyone. We will punish Juk Chang!
- Hey, get over here. - Come on.
Let's get started.
Hey, are you guys having fun?
Why wouldn't we be having fun?
Okay. Get him!
(Let's Get Juk Chang! Juk Chang is Dead Today.)
- That's right! - Get him!
- Hit him harder! - Go for it!
Hey, Secretary. Can you turn that off?
Yes, sir.
Why? Does it make you feel uncomfortable?
It feels like we created another monster.
Monsters aren't made.
The monster within is just awoken.
Whenever there's a good excuse.
You're pretty focused.
Minister Cha, how did you get in?
Why are you so surprised?
That's very unlike you.
Are you carrying out a search and seizure?
You're quite an interesting person.
Are you that great a person?
That the Minister of Justice...
should carry out a search and seizure?
Then are you here to ask for a favor?
I think you're mistaken.
I came here to remind you of your place.
- "My place"? - You know,
you look best...
when you're standing behind someone...
in utter silence, hands politely folded.
If one fails to know their place,
their end is not pretty.
Minister Cha.
Perhaps you're the one who fails to realize your place.
Do you still think you're most likely to become president...
after what happened to your son?
Aren't you a little too confident?
Do you think you deleted your past completely?
My past?
What is it you're trying to say?
Why do people around you keep dying?
When you were 12, it was your mom.
When you were 20, your dad who had abandoned you and your mom.
And most recently,
Mr. Seo whom you had been serving as secretary.
I had no idea you enjoyed writing novels.
You have a great imagination.
Do what suits you best.
You used to be a servant?
What a lowlife.
See you around.
Hi, Sun Ah.
Kang Yo Han told Cha Kyung Hee about me.
- What? - Look into it.
Why would he...
Shut your mouth and look into it!
You'll have to pay for interfering with my plans.
It seems you worked hard to get here.
Would that be okay?
I will kill you,
Kang Yo Han.
I will tear you to shreds.
(The Devil Judge)
We have no choice but to make them turn their blades at each other?
Hello, Young Master.
I think it would be fun to play with you.
Will she join you?
I'll give you one week.
Bring me what I want.
Cha Kyung Hee doesn't know yet, right?
The first step.
She'll testify that Kang Yo Han made her lie in court.
Isn't it too risky?
You said you never know what she'll do.
We risk it all and it's still life and death.
Do I scare you?
That's too bad.