Durian flavor.
I like this too.
I don't know if Zixin likes it or not.
Hi.
Take two for me, too.
Okay.
Here you are.
Get me two more.
Strawberry, please.
Thanks.
Okay.
Well,
You are...
Since I said
I like strawberry cake,
lawyer Tang bought me
everything with strawberry flavor.
I have to pretend to be
a law school innocent girl,
all the time.
How much?
Twenty, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Wait.
Well,
If Lawyer Tang finds out
that my tenderness and sweetness
are fake in the future,
will he think I cheated on marriage?
My coach said
not to fight unprepared battles.
This camouflage is also one of the tactics.
Besides,
you also have
your own charm.
After you get along for a long time,
he will definitely like
your other advantages.
Unlike me and Zixin,
I was so embarrassed today.
It's fine.
Aren't we all ready?
Don't girls like
shiny things,
either diamonds
or fireflies.
The firefly forest tonight
will surely impress her.
Are you sure?
Definitely.
I don't think
you like these things.
I...
Isn't my beer
shiny?
It's gonna be a double blessing
for the love League
tonight.
Believe me or not?
Yes.
Deciding set tonight.
=Episode 8=
=Cursed Sorority=
=Legally Romance=
Go, go, go.
Nice over there.
- Take a photo.
- Okay.
This way?
Well,
it seems this way.
Stop shooting. We'll do it later.
Do we live here?
Huh, the one in front, right?
Look.
Yeah, that's it.
Hurry in and have a look.
Is this where you
planned to take me last time?
- Hurry.
- Go up and take a seat.
Yes, it's really good.
Come on, come on.
Sorry,
I will take the initiative
to tell the teacher of the student union
about this matter,
because I caused you to fall into the water
and your computer is broken,
so these bills
are not available.
It's not that serious.
Just hand it in
before go back to school tomorrow.
Just fill in
the report again
before we go back.
Yes,
it's not that serious.
Everything will be fine.
I can do that.
Isn't it just some
car rental fees, tolls
and tickets,
as well as meals?
No,
but even if I can think of
these names,
I can't think of
these specific figures.
Let me do it.
Come on,
Our food bills
are too trivial.
If I remember correctly,
there is money
for two meals in the morning and evening,
and then
there is money for a night barbecue,
drinks
and so on.
And...
It's okay.
I have a backup here.
For these expenses,
as long as they are ordered in advance,
I'll back them up
to the mailbox.
Just copy them.
For breakfast,
I ordered
a total of 150 pancakes
(2012 Law School fellowship)
and 30 sandwiches at the snack bar.
Because we bought a lot,
the boss cut a dollar of each.
Beverages are one hundred and fifty
bottles of carbonated drinks
and thirty bottles of dairy products.
Three of them said
they were lactose intolerant,
so they replaced them with soybean milk.
That's about
one hundred and fifty.
Really?
Even numbers can be right!
No, I used to know
that you have a good memory,
but I didn't expect it to be so good
that you can even remember
someone who is lactose intolerant.
I've done this before,
so I have experience with it.
And this time
I cooperate with you,
I know you want to join the presidium,
and I don't want to hold you back,
so I'll remember it in advance.
It's me who's holding back.
That problem solved,
the invoice is ready.
It's all here,
here.
If there is no invoice,
do I have to
use my own money?
How much did we pay for chartering a boat?
Five thousand and three hundred.
I won't enter the student union.
I can't afford it,
really.
I won't.
Don't worry.
Wait and let me see.
Otherwise,
I'll go back now.
They shouldn't be closed yet.
I'll go back and make up the invoice.
Can the invoice be made up?
Then I'll go,
Let me go.
I've dealt with them before.
I'm more experienced.
And in the future, Guanghua School
will cooperate with them in activities,
and he will definitely make it up for me.
Wait for me,
I'll be back in a while.
Thanks.
Where did Qian Chuan go?
He was eating here just now.
He doesn't come back either.
How's it going?
I got the invoice
and put it together
with other bills.
Come here.
I dried your clothes.
Take it.
Thank you.
Well,
if you need my help
in the future,
just tell me directly.
Come on,
save you from saying
I'm selfish and mercenary.
Did I say that?
I'm not sure.
I'm kidding you.
Don't you like
this traitor on you?
Put your clothes on now.
One servant does not serve two masters,
unless it is a traitor.
(Zhu Gong)
Senior Chongwen, Qian Wei,
Do you want to come down and play Werewolves?
Come on, come on.
I'm down.
I'll go down first.
Okay.
Fine, I'm here
trying to find
your rival,
while you're so weird here.
Let me tell you,
I have already asked,
there is a sea of flowers over there,
and there will be fireflies
in the sea of flowers at night.
You can take Zixin there,
and I will hold Qian Chuan, okay?
I have paid
for your help.
That's good.
Where's Qian Chuan?
Don't worry, I'll find him now.
Stop it.
Look.
Qian Wei, Lu Xun.
- It's all waiting for us to go down.
- Come down and play together.
Just get down!
Play together!
Just play with Zixin.
Yeah
Okay, sure.
It's getting dark, close your eyes.
Werewolf, please open your eyes.
Prophet, please open your eyes.
It's dawn.
Open your eyes.
Lu Xun was killed by the werewolf
last night.
Does the first good man
who dies have the right to pour wine?
We can punish the first werewolf.
Yes.
Drink it.
I'm a hunter.
I take Qian Wei and die together.
Why did you take me?
I'm a good guy!
I'm not a wolf.
It's no use taking me away.
It doesn't matter whether you are a good man
or a werewolf.
As a hunter,
if I go,
I can take you away.
You don't have to take me.
I'll take you. Hurry!
No, you're taking revenge for yourself.
Drink it.
- Come on.
- Drink it, Qian Wei.
Come on.
- Drink it.
- Hurry.
What's the use of
taking me?
If you agree that Qian Wei is a werewolf,
please vote.
She must be.
Follow me and vote with me.
Believe me, and raise your hand.
She must be.
You know it, why don't raise your hand?
- It's not your business.
- I...
He doesn't raise his hand,
so I need to call him.
I'm canvassing.
I won't raise my hand.
OK, don't raise your hand.
Qian Wei,
You've covered
all the fine drinks this afternoon.
Drink it now.
Finish in one gulp.
What the hell, what bad luck am I.
Why am I always a werewolf?
Because your emotions are written on your face.
You can't be a wolf like this.
Otherwise,
You'll be a judge in the next game.
No,
I'll be lucky when I finish this glass of wine.
I'm sure I can win.
Come on.
Come on, I'll pour you wine.
Senior, this is not wine.
This is mineral water.
You cheat.
What's wrong with you?
Take water as wine?
You are so interesting, senior.
Cheat.
Wait, wait,
let me explain,
I just saw that Qian Wei drank too much,
so I just wanted her
to drink some water to relax.
Or
I'll drink it for her, okay?
This game punished me for drinking.
No way,
Qian Wei is the monitor.
The monitor should look like a monitor.
Admit defeat for bet.
You both have to drink.
Yes.
We law students
must obey the rules.
Drink!
Drink it.
- Finish.
- Hurry.
Drink.
Fine, she can't drink any more.
I'll drink it for her,
or she'll get sick.
Good.
You guys,
You play first.
I... I...
I'll take a break.
I can't.
Come and play Werewolf.
Two more people.
Are you okay?
Here I'm.
Go, go, go.
Hurry.
Finally let us play.
Come on, and sit down here.
Come and Have a bite of watermelon to sober up.
Come on, deal.
Don't always care about winning or losing.
Win or lose doesn't matter.
The most important thing
is to have fun
with friends.
You drank a lot.
Eat it yourself.
It used to be the same.
Every time you eat watermelon,
you always leave the sweetest piece
in the middle to me.
When I am sad and frustrated,
you comfort me that it doesn't matter
whether I win or lose.
But then I found out
that it didn't matter whether I won or lost.
Li Chongwen,
you always want to win.
Then let's continue.
What's up?
Do you have a stomach trouble?
You shouldn't have drunk that wine just now.
How do you know I had stomach trouble?
Prophet, please close your eyes.
Huh...
Good.
You're covering your stomach.
It's obvious.
Open your eyes.
There are no pharmacies
or hospitals on this mountain.
Well,
I will borrow a kitchen from the boss
and cook you some soup
with red dates and peanuts.
You would feel better.
Fine,
Let me go.
He can't drink the soup you made.
Drink slowly and don't choke.
Don't look at me.
Okay,
thanks.
Much better.
Wait,
how did you know
I need to drink red dates and peanut soup
with a stomachache?
Your stomach is not good,
so you're not supposed to attend
this kind of social engagement frequently.
Slow down.
Don't worry.
My stomach feel better
after drinking the peanut soup you cooked.
I'm sorry
for your suffering.
I must buy you
an air conditioner this year.
Small law firms like ours
still have to rely on contacts
to stand out.
It's all right,
I'll treat
those big bosses well.
Then take some cases from them
that they don't want,
and throw a sprat to catch a herring,
maybe we can stand out.
Then
you won't have to suffer any more.
I don't feel hard.
Isn't that good?
Let me tell you,
It's said that
don't blow the air conditioner all the time.
Blowing air conditioners is
not good for the body,
while the natural wind
of electric fans is the best.
Besides,
although it's leaking,
we can save money
and water the flowers,
right?
I am a prophet.
When I play werewolf killing later,
I will secretly change a card with you
to help you win.
Thanks.
But didn't you say
the process is also important?
I also want to win,
but it's not
in this way of cheating.
The weather is fine today.
Yep.
Look,
I didn't expect
such a beautiful place around here.
Really,
look at the flowers there.
Sit down.
Here you are.
What's this?
Acupuncture needle.
Acupuncture needle?
You come out with a needle?
What's wrong with you?
Or shall I help you with acupuncture?
No, no.
This is my gift
to you.
I hope your exam goes well.
Thank you.
Well,
Actually, I have something else to say.
Go ahead.
I've never seen
a guy so handsome
in a white coat
since the first time
I saw you in the infirmary.
I've always been reluctant
to eat the chocolate you gave me.
I just want to ask you,
will you always let me
be your acupuncture mouse?
Shiyun,
it's not girl's business
to confess.
I like you, too
Really?
Yes.
Fool.
From now on,
I'll buy you
strawberry cake.
Don't touch me,
Mr. Liu.
Am I allergic to dog hair?
Stop it,
Stop!
Qian Chuan!
Wake up,
I can't. Come on!
Wake up!
God, wake...
What? What's up?
How could you be here?
Fine,
I'm allergic to dog.
I don't know why.
I've taken allergy medicine,
but it's still very itchy.
I don't know why.
I can't find
Lawyer Tang either.
Isn't Qian Chuan there?
At this time last time,
I was allergic to dog hair,
so Qian Chuan took advantage of it
and confessed in advance.
This time,
he must have colluded
with Liu Shiyun.
She must be
in a tiger's mouth now.
Come on, no matter
how hard I try,
in the end, I was always responsible
for his lonely life.
He and Liu Shiyun
are not here.
They must have made an appointment to confess.
No, let's go.
Listen,
we must not let him succeed.
Hurry,
hurry up.
No, no, no,
why do you care about them now?
You are hurt,
is it painful and itchy?
- Can you stand it?
- No,
Listen,
I won't die.
But I tell you,
you'll regret
missing tonight.
I know where they are.
They are in the
flower field,
where
fireflies gather.
Let's take the insecticide
to the flower field now.
All right, stop talking nonsense.
Hurry.
See a doctor first.
Go to the hospital.
No, I don't need to go to hospital.
But I tell you
fireflies are important.
You can't just
leave them alone.
I saw so many fireflies
for the first time.
Me, too.
What a coincidence.
It's small,
but it's really bright.
Your eyes
are brighter than it.
Zixin,
You always wear this.
You must like crystal very much.
In fact, you are
as pure and beautiful
as crystal in my eyes.
Zixin,
I like you.
I want to protect you
and accompany you all the time.
Would you like to be my girlfriend?
To be honest,
the crystal is very beautiful,
But it is easy to break.
It's easy to hurt others
when it's broken.
Qian Chuan,
Thank you for your like,
but I can't promise you.
I know,
I know many girls like you,
and I'm not the best one.
If you think something is wrong with me,
I can change.
I am willing to work hard for you.
Is it because
I'm so embarrassed during the day?
I'm really afraid of heights,
but I'm not afraid of anything else.
Not today, of course.
Loving someone
has nothing to do with effort.
Qian Chuan,
You're really good.
You don't need to
change anything for me.
Just because of me,
because my own heart
has been broken.
I can't fall in love with others
until it heals.
Qian Wei is my good friend,
I don't want to hurt you either.
So,
I'm so sorry.
Why don't you stay with your boy
but come to help me?
I was busy in vain.
Sorry.
Stop it.
Just drink.
I thought
I might be rejected in fact.
But I'm still not reconciled,
I want to try.
I'm not the best.
I really don't deserve her.
She said
she refused you
because she had been hurt.
Lu Xun, the first in the grade,
was also rejected,
right?
So,
don't belittle yourself.
She said she didn't want to hurt you.
What does it mean?
It means she doesn't hate you.
I think you still have a chance.
Really?
Sure.
As a girl,
I certainly know
what girls think.
What the world would be
if fairies
are so easy to chase?
The Seventh Fairy and Dong Yong
were married,
but there is still a galaxy between them.
It's nothing.
For my view,
Just give her
a little more time,
Let's make persistent efforts
when she is no longer sad for others.
Yes,
you're right.
At least you have succeeded,
and our love alliance
has not ended in vain.
Correct.
That's good.
Great bro.
- Let's go and drink.
- Go.
Have a drink!
Drink and have fun.
Have fun.
Go.
Be happy.
Hurry.
Wait for me.
Have fun.
Go.
Don't...don't hold me.
(Outpatient)
(Qian Chuan: Finally, I failed)
Look,
Qian Chuan failed.
Great!
The fireflies in the sea of flowers
won't die.
Be careful.
Don't look at your smart phone.
I've seen the Olympic Games in odd years,
the postponement of college entrance examination
and judicial examination,
and thousands of years of iron trees bloom,
But I never seen
Lu Xun fall in a sweet love.
I think he deserved it.
It's not an allergy,
but just a flea bite.
I'll prescribe
some topical medicine for you first.
If your skin is still itchy,
take some medicine orally.
Remember not to scratch it.
I'm glad it's all right.
How about we put the dog
in someone else's house
before taking a bath
and taking medicine?
It seems that this little dog
has no fate with us.
(Prescription of Qingshan Hospital)
Thanks.
You'd better take the topical medicine
as soon as possible.
Well, doctor,
we live far away,
the places where the medicine can't be applied,
the back or something,
can you help me
apply it now?
Ask your boyfriend to help you.
- No.
- No, no, doctor.
Huh,
I'll pay
for her medicine now.
Please do her a favor.
Your boyfriend is
so handsome and careful.
He was the only one
of the accompanying family members
who didn't play
with his mobile phone all the way.
It's rare to be so innocent.
Cherish him.
He is not my boyfriend,
but my classmate.
Then he must like you.
Well,
Don't tell the student union
that I went to the emergency tonight.
I'm afraid it will affect my participation
in the presidium.
No problem.
I'm not so free.
Am I gossip man?
Okay,
Your cold image
has finally played
a positive role for me.
Don't scratch.
Itchy.
It's okay to scratch across clothes.
Hold on.
What...what are you doing?
You don't have one more hand
to scratch in this way.
If you fall,
I won't have the strength
to carry you to the hospital again.
No matter how hard I tried,
I still failed to help Lu Xun
succeed in chasing love.
Is love
really bound long time ago?
Can't ordinary people change?
Lu Xun is arrogant
and annoying,
But he is still very loyal
at the critical moment.
Hmm,
Thank you for accompanying me
to the hospital so late today.
There is...
there is no taxi-hailing app.
They didn't take our orders
as soon as they heard
we were going up the mountain.
What taxi-hailing app?
What's that?
Just take a taxi on your mobile phone.
You can increase the price
when there are many people and few cars.
Very convenient.
Those are all unlicensed taxi.
Don't think about it.
What do you know?
Look,
ten years later,
you will know
how stupid you are.
Don't scratch.
Hold me tight.
Hold on, come on.
Listen me?
Hold!
Am I heavy?
For me,
just fine.
Why does Lu Xun
suddenly treat me so well?
No, no way.
It's not possible.
It must have been a rare occasion
for my former boss
to treat me well,
and I suffered a Stockholm Syndrome attack.
Illusion, it must be an illusion.
Your boyfriend is
so handsome and careful.
He was the only one
of the accompanying family members
who didn't play
with his mobile phone all the way.
It's rare to be so innocent.
Cherish him.
You...
You, do you
like me a little?
College love is not a puppy love.
But don't worry,
I'm not going to report you.
What the hell?
I only have
career and money
on my mind.
I don't have
these worldly wishes.
None
is good.
What are you doing?
One good deed a day.
Do you have
anything you like?
I mean something within 50 RMB.
I'll repay you
for doing good every day.
Stars.
Zixin
What Lu Xun really wants most
is Zixin.
Sure enough.
Don't worry,
I'll help you.
I promise you.
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feelings♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪
(Guanghua Law School)
We Guanghua law school
(Law popularization activities into the community!)
has always had a tradition
of going into the community
to provide free legal education to the people.
You can take this opportunity
to accumulate
practical experience.
After the activity,
students who are willing
can submit a paper.
If the quality is good,
I can recommend it
to the Legal Expo magazine.
Only Lu Xun
wrote the paper in the class at that time.
I also despise his false positivity.
Who knows,
it was because of his published papers
that he got an internship
at the top law firms.
I'll write it carefully
this time.
Little Lu Xun,
I'm sorry.
The visiting professor leading the team
in this activity
is Mr. Wang Ruogu,
a well-known lawyer.
Let's welcome Professor Wang.
(Seize the opportunity to publish papers)
Hello everyone,
I'm also glad
(Fair competition for publication opportunities)
to bring the law
into the community this time
with you guys.
It's also my first time.
I'm not alone
Today.
It is exactly him.
And I brought
a Qingyun plan
- I know.
-that can help
- I just heard it before.
-more students.
The name is humbling called Ruogu,
but he is a hypocrite.
Just at this moment,
I was a little in a trance.
I really seem to see myself
among them.
So this time,
I'm not only here to tutor you,
but also to find
promising,
ambitious
and capable students among you.
Qingyun will always support them.
Qingyun will offer you opportunities to learn,
practice
and even work.
And in the near future,
I can't make
the same mistake this time.
I have to stay away from him.
I cannot repeat the mistakes.
until they set up
their own law firm.
In this activity,
two classes teamed together,
twelve people in a group,
and take turns to enter each community.
The communities of this event
are written
on the form sent to you.
In the first choice,
write one for who wants to enter the community.
In the second choice,
write two.
After filling in,
each monitor collect the statistics
and counts it.
Let's start
by grouping
according to your vote.
If there is another conflict,
then we can coordinate.
Well,
was there a delicious barbecue shop
in Anda,
Anda community last time?
Let's choose this.
We can go to dinner
together
after that.
Right?
Yeah.
Choose Anda community.
(Anda community 1)
(Lotus community 1)
(Popularize legal knowledge)
(Popularizing and learning the law,)
(The meaning of popularizing law)
(Brochure)
Qian Wei,
What are you doing here?
The senior in charge of your group
has something to do,
so I'm here for him.
I brought you breakfast.
By the way,
I have
a very important thing
to show you.
This is a classic case
of law popularization activities last year.
You can have a look at it later
when you eat,
which is a little helpful
for today's consultation.
Come here,
I have
a classic case here,
let's pass it around
and have a look.
I hope our group will be rated
as an excellent team this year.
Okay.
- Thanks, senior.
Fighting.
(we are on the way)
(Legal Advisory Desk)
Protect yourself, right?
Look, uncle,
It's clearly
written on it.
Have a look.
Okay.
So, the reason
we take this activity
is...
Uncles and aunts,
There are too many people
in line here.
I can't solve each of you
for a while.
Look over there.
This classmate here is also very good.
You can go there,
right?
The little girl is
quite silent.
What does she know?
I agree.
Can she do it?
The barristers on TV
are such boys.
Yes.
Good-looking and eloquent.
We all want to ask you,
and we don't believe others.
Aunt,
ability is not divided between men and women.
Look at this girl,
she is Qian Wei.
She is our class monitor.
She not only has excellent academic performance,
but also
has great social practice experience.
The most important thing is
that she has a delicate mind
and can often find another way
to spend the least time
and do the most things.
Isn't that good?
Right.
Okay.
Let's go over there.
Yes, yes.
Let's split up.
Okay.
- Come on.
- Go.
Come here.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm here.
Yeah.
to ask about women's rights.
My daughter...
She is...
(Guanghua University)
Thanks.
Qian Wei,
You've been talking for two hours.
Take a drink and have a rest.
Thanks.
I want to make a will.
I'll help you.
Uncle,
we can help you
make a will here.
However, if you want
Higher legal force,
it is recommended
that you go to a notary office
for a notarized testament.
We may
need your ID card
and household register to make a will.
A witness is also needed
in the process.
Why don't you discuss it
with your family first?
I have no family,
and I don't need it.
My son knows.
I will donate my house
and all my inheritance
to the country.
Can you help me find
what organization needs money?
I donated it all.
Uncle,
We still have to
go in this process.
I just want to donate all the money.
I'm waiting.
Let me see.
Uncle, please drink some water
to moisten your throat, and don't get angry.
I don't need you.
His purpose is
not to make a will.
You are doing good deeds and charity.
How can you
not let your son know?
I told you, the kid isn't here.
I mean,
you can't make a will.
We can't waste a good opportunity
to educate him, can we?
My son doesn't come back
for half a year.
How do you educate him?
I'll donate all my property
to charity
and didn't leave him a penny.
Don't angry.
Isn't that a boy?
I'm sure it's not as sweet as a girl.
He's not so...
so cute, is he?
But look at your watch,
He bought it for you!
I don't want his money.
He just buys things,
but doesn't go home.
This is false filial piety.
You're right.
But you said
you would donate
all your money to others
without giving him a penny.
But in fact,
you still love him.
Although he doesn't come back,
he satisfies you materially.
That's
how he love you.
It's not a legal problem,
but an emotional problem.
Just solve it.
But in this world,
only the father is angry with his son.
How could a son be angry with his father?
I won't say nice words.
You don't need to say.
Fine,
you tell me your phone number,
And I'll call him.
Let me educate him.
You also need a good conversation,
so many things will be solved.
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪