(Guanghua University)
(Guanghua University 2011 Debate Team Recruitment
Competition List)
(Does Happy Farm affect people's moral values)
(Positive)
This question
seems to be about games,
but it is actually torturing people's
attitude towards stealing.
Although stealing vegetables at Happy Farm
will not bring
substantial economic losses,
it weakens
(Does Happy Farm affect people's moral values)
people's concept
of stealing.
If such games
persist,
such cases are bound to grow rapidly.
And games that
spread bad practice
will definitely be banned
within two years.
The online virtual economy
will also be included in the scope
of legal protection in the future.
Whether it is online or offline,
theft should
all be punished.
(Debate team)
(Negative)
(If the husband owes a debt,)
Except for a few specific circumstances,
(whether the wife is obligated to repay with him)
our country's current
relevant laws stipulate that
the personal debts of a couple
should be turned into joint ownership.
As long as the debt
is incurred during the marriage,
after the divorce, the other party
still needs to bear the responsibility
of the debtor.
Although it protects
the rights of creditors,
it is
extremely unfair
to uninformed parties.
The perfection of the law
requires the supervision
of the moral level.
I believe that someday
this kind of
anti-humanitarian law
will be
perfected.
(Later,)
(the judicial interpretation of Marriage Law)
(and Civil Code)
(indeed made corresponding amendments)
(to this law.)
(Uninformed parties)
(no longer need to take on debt)
(more than the family needs)
(in daily life.)
(Lu Xun realized this)
(in 2011.)
(This young boy)
(is incredible.)
(Negative)
(Guanghua University 2011 Debate Team Recruitment
Competition List)
(Qian Wei, Lu Xun)
(Yang Yifan, Xu Dongdong)
(Positive: debates without arguing)
(Negative: harmony in diversity)
(Eye candy)
(Negative)
Both of them are good.
Who do you prefer?
(Eye candy)
If you call me sister now,
I will definitely not
make it hard for you in the future.
(Negative)
I'm not as kind as you.
If I am the chief,
I will make it hard for you every single say.
(Drink the ginger tea while it's hot
to prevent colds)
=Episode 4=
=The Red Line Has Its Own Thought=
=Legally Romance=
(Which is more important,
love or bread)
Everyone knows that
(Love: negative)
bread is rather common.
But love is like a ghost.
Why?
(Positive: bread)
Because many people have heard of it,
but few have seen it.
A thing is valued if it is rare.
Love is
something rare.
So I think between the two,
love is more important
than bread.
A very famous person
once said that
love without material things
is in a state of disunity
and cannot stand the test.
Moreover,
Nothing goes well to a destitute couple.
If you don't have
material support,
love can't be retained.
The pursuit of material desires
runs counter to that of happiness.
But no desire,
no thought.
Descartes once said that
no desire, no thought.
If people have no thoughts,
how can they still need love?
What's the point of life?
(Guanghua University)
What's more,
(2011 Debate Team Recruitment Trials)
bread won't forsake you.
But love will.
Love is
spiritual enjoyment.
Blindly pursuing materialism
only makes people
more and more vulgar.
You haven't even
held a girl's hand,
what qualifications do you have
to say that true love prevails?
You are not
a billionaire,
why do you say
money is supreme?
You will have no girlfriend
for the next eleven years,
and you have to work overtime every day.
Are you cursing me?
She couldn't win me in the debate,
so she started cursing me.
What if I curse you?
I am just cursing you.
So what?
We are debating.
Why are you cursing me?
Look at you.
Stop.
Time's up.
No personal attacks.
The two of you have an even score.
Her behavior was worse than a personal attack.
Enough.
Your grades are actually
neck and neck.
We decided to add
a two-person debate tomorrow
to elect the captain
of the debate team.
What are you muttering about?
What?
Am I not allowed to speak?
I have the right to speak.
Then can you stop talking about me?
I am not talking about me.
All right.
You did a good job today.
I am a law student after all.
I'm definitely better at debating
than any other job.
Your logic and thinking skills
are strong
and your reactions are fast.
I can't wait to see
your performance tomorrow.
Does talent discovery
require exams?
This topic
should be easy for you.
Hush.
Never let anyone else know.
Otherwise, we'll
have to say goodbye
to the debate team.
I just want to
see you more often
in training later on.
The debate is over.
You are still talking.
It looks like I'll have to find a place
where we won't be interrupted
when talking to you in the future.
Sorry to have
interrupted your date.
It's not a date.
It's…
(If I speak it out now)
(My plan to change my fate)
(Will be over)
I am leaving.
Do you think
she is special?
Just troublesome.
I hope you can take it.
I think we should
add this.
What are you two doing?
Come to take a look.
We are betting on the post bar of school
on who will win tomorrow
between you and Lu Xun.
(The support ratio of Lu Xun and Qian Wei is 2:1)
The odds are now two to one.
Lu Xun is slightly more popular than you.
So he leads.
But with
your performance today,
I bet you will win.
Yes.
And I found out that
Captain Li Chongwen,
who is popular
among thousands of girls of our school,
has been
locked on you today.
With his affirmation,
you will definitely win.
He's just a senior
of sophomore year.
The person who has the final say
is Professor Zhang.
Not at all.
I found out that
Li Chongwen
is a prominent
big shot
of the debate team.
No, the whole school.
When he was a freshman,
Group Wanyu,
the largest developer of our city,
illegally constructed near our school.
Even media exposure was ineffective.
Li Chongwen
sued them directly in court,
and won the first instance.
Since then, he become famous
and the pride of Law Department
of Guanghua University.
And
not only did the school
publicize his successful case
of rights protection,
but even our city promoted it.
Last year he led the team
to the national first place
in the debate competition.
Professor Zhang is about to retire.
In fact,
the affairs of the debate team
are basically managed by Li Chongwen.
With his support,
it must be you who will take over
as the captain of the debate team next year.
I can't necessarily win.
No, you have to.
Zixin and I
bet all our savings
on you.
(Lu Xun and Qian Wei's support ratio is 2:1)
You can't lose.
If you lose, we will lose a lot of money.
Yes.
Today we are here
to do assault training with you.
Come on here.
Eat something.
Perform well tomorrow.
It rose again.
After yesterday's game,
I think everyone should have
a clear understanding of the rules.
(Negative)
If there is no doubt,
(Does talent discovery requires exams)
we will go straight
to the final debate.
I have a doubt.
Professor.
I think this game
should be cancelled.
Why?
Because it's unfair.
(Guanghua University 2011 Debate Team
Recruitment Trials)
Unfair?
Before the competition,
the seniors
leaked the debate
to us.
(Report Letter
Dear debate team leaders:)
(Qian Wei)
What's up?
The prophet is going to beg for mercy?
Although I would love to win you,
it must be
in a fair and just manner.
Today, the senior didn't come to
invite me on a date,
but told me about tomorrow's debate.
You also knew it?
So for the sake of fairness and justice,
I hope this game
can be cancelled.
No need.
You have passed
the final test.
This is our final exam.
When two competitors
are faced with the same
unfair shortcuts,
the one who can uphold justice
and report it boldly
is the talent we need.
Congratulations to both of you
for passing the test.
(Guanghua University 2011 Debate Team
Recruitment Trials)
This is the first time
since the establishment of Guanghua debate team
that two candidates
have passed the final test together.
I announce
the exceptional appointment
of both of you as captains.
The team members
will also be divided into two groups,
led by each of you.
Next, let's badge
for the new captains.
(Guanghua University 2011 Debate Team
Recruitment Trials)
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And…
Sorry.
I had no choice
but to deceive you yesterday.
Never mind.
You are
an expert liar anyway.
Chongwen, come here.
Don't interfere with them taking photos.
Come on.
First-time leaders.
Take some photos together.
Be closer.
Qian Wei, closer.
It's okay, sir.
Closer.
(Captain Lu)
Everyone should know that
(Captain Qian)
for a good debate,
not only individual performance,
(You perform I guess)
but also teamwork is very important.
Today's practice session
will be divided into groups.
We'll decide by the game
you perform I guess.
Let's ask Yu Tian
to introduce the rules
of the game to you.
Come on.
Okay.
Next will be the battle between the two captains.
The captains will perform.
And everyone should guess.
Three minutes time limit.
The winning captain
could choose
team members first.
Lu Xun, you first.
Me?
(Mouse and Cat)
What's this?
That's all.
Lucky Cat?
I did two actions.
Anyone
else?
I will say it then.
Mouse and Cat.
(Wide-eyed at the sight of money-greedy)
What are you doing?
Glance at you.
What does this have to do with glancing?
A dog trying to catch rat.
Everyone knows he's a dog.
But how can I be a rat?
You look like a rat.
Stop it.
Hurry up.
Wide-eyed at the sight of money-greedy.
Just a waste of time.
Right.
Cool.
Tell me.
You know me so well,
is it because you have a crush on me?
Piss off.
I told you
I am a prophet.
you are doomed to lose.
Why are you struggling here?
What?
Step aside.
Waste of time.
Insight into the boss
is the law of survival as an assistant.
I have been your assistant
for so many years.
I know you better than your mother.
Let me announce
the result just now.
(You perform I guess)
Lu Xun.
Zero.
Qian Wei.
Five.
Qian Wei won.
Well.
Liu Shiyun, join my team.
Zixin, join his.
Just go.
Why did you switch teams?
Would you like to join me?
Switch the side.
Don't you want to be
on the same team with me?
There are people behind you.
Why do you talk so much?
I'm talking to my team members.
Did I talk to you?
They are no longer
your team members.
Okay.
All right.
Next,
Captain Li would perform.
The team that guesses the answer
within a minute
will be coached by him.
And the other will be led by me.
Let's begin.
(Scallop with mashed garlic)
(You perform I guess)
Four words.
He is even seasoning.
Mouse trap.
Eat.
Dig.
Dynamic light.
What's this?
Cumin.
At the BBQ.
Scallop.
Miss something.
Scallop with mashed garlic.
Bravo.
Don't you want me to lead you?
No.
I think it's better
for a boy to lead a boy.
You should lead Lu Xun.
Qian Wei.
Although this is a game,
it is also a key link
in selecting the leader of the team.
You are breaking the rules
by making such a mess.
You are breaking the rules.
Shut up.
It's okay.
Debate team
is always boring.
It is suitable
for a lively girl like Qian Wei
to come to our team
and warm up.
Let's do this.
You should lead Lu Xun.
And I will lead Qian Wei.
Why are you implying to me?
It's your own business.
Scallop.
Senior.
Well.
I am stubborn
and always disobey discipline.
So
I'd better not bother you.
I can go to another team.
Not at all.
Where there is trouble, there is a challenge.
I would appreciate your guidance.
Qian Wei.
When would the rain stop?
Let's go.
I will send you.
No need.
To be honest,
I could feel
you hate me
the first time I saw you.
If I offended you
somewhere,
just tell me.
I would apologize to you.
No.
Maybe I like being in the rain,
but you don't.
We are not the same.
We don't have to walk together.
Qian Wei.
Why are you following me?
You can leave
after the rain stops.
This is mine.
You took the wrong one.
It's okay, I am fine.
Well, you deserve to be single.
It's raining so hard.
It shouldn't be of any use.
Forget it, bye.
What a younger brother.
Qian Wei.
Your takeaway.
(Li Chongwen)
(Don't catch cold)
(Take care)
(I still remember)
(how embarrassed I was)
(when I first received your post-it note.)
Is the interview for debate over?
I just came back.
I know.
The debate is over.
And Professor Zhang has left.
Thank you.
Take the umbrella.
Qian Wei?
It's your takeaway.
(Li Chongwen)
(It doesn't matter that you missed the selection)
(If you like debate)
(I can teach you later)
(I'll reserve seat for you in the future games)
(Li Chongwen)
(Drink the ginger tea while it's hot)
(to prevent colds)
(Ambition all over the world,
Love in the campus)
(You are the best girlfriend
Li Chongwen)
(Later)
(Your post-it notes)
(accompanied me through countless moments)
(I thought at that time)
(that you were)
(the most thoughtful boy)
(You always captured)
(Chong&Wei Law Firm)
(my happiness and sadness sooner than me)
(Those post-it notes)
(smoothed out all the folds)
(in my heart)
(Li Chongwen)
(I was obsessed with)
(Ginger Green Tea Honey Ginger Tea)
(the world you created)
(with post-it notes)
(Eat breakfast while it's hot)
(I didn't find out)
(Take a rest when sleepy.)
(it was a cage)
(I can help you organize the information.)
(Li Chongwen)
(until you left)
(Disputes over damage)
(Keep warm in the morning and at night)
(Antitrust)
(A must for new shoes)
(Although you are strong, I hope...)
(Black tea, ginger tea)
(Chong&Wei Law Firm, Qian Wei)
(Guanghua University)
Qian Wei.
The debate team just informed that
the debate competition is about to start.
Take a look at the topics inside.
Okay.
Thanks.
(Don't catch a cold, take care. Li Chongwen)
Well.
I am back.
Okay.
Forget it.
It's okay, just go.
Our debate team is about to
enter the competition.
The subject this time
is labor dispute in the factory.
It stands to reason that
we have to use real cases as examples.
You're asking the right person.
There was a dispute in my factory
a few days ago.
I settled it myself.
Really?
Tell me about details.
Hold on.
Aren't you retired?
Well…
It's just…
I just stopped by.
Your dad isn't retired.
Some time ago, the factory manager
arbitrarily replaced the ink
with inferior products.
After he heard that,
he insisted on staying
to solve the problem.
How dare he?
Mom, stop him
right now.
I'll take care of the factory manager.
Understand?
I'll take care of the factory manager'
Would you like to…?
No.
I am not even finished.
If there is an abnormality,
there must be something wrong.
There is nothing wrong.
I have a very good
case source ready.
Would you like
to experience
being a lawyer?
(Haizhou Guangming Parts Processing Factory)
This is where your dad works.
Act of Lawyer stipulates that
if you pretend to be a lawyer
to provide legal services,
the judicial administrative department
will confiscate the illegal income
and impose a fine of more than one time
and less than five times the illegal income.
Tell me the school motto.
Great virtue. Master law.
Stop.
See?
Why does great virtue come first?
First of all, we have to establish
a good sense of responsibility
and morality.
Then we serve it
with law.
Right?
I know you think
I'm doing this for my own good.
But actually no.
That's not where
my dad works alone, right?
There are also many
ordinary employees working there.
Isn't the original purpose
of our study of law
to seek justice
and to speak out for justice?
All right.
I knew
you weren't so kind.
It's just a waste of time
preparing for you...
What?
You look so good in it.
You have a good taste.
This is new for the season.
It's only 2,500 yuan with discount.
Well.
Listen.
Actually he is my younger brother.
He had a girlfriend
who he was about to marry.
But she broke up with him.
Tomorrow is her wedding.
He just wants to wear a formal suit
to try again.
As his sister,
I really should support him.
But our family
is very poor.
I have only
less than a thousand Yuan.
Why did you get ill again?
My younger sister
was hurt by her boyfriend.
He cheated out of all her savings.
She's crazy
and has delusional disorder now.
You…
If you speak again,
I'll send you in.
Would you like to be sent away?
Would you like to?
No?
You know what?
She's very emotionally unstable right now.
Please understand.
She always imposes
her own story on me,
you know?
It's not my story.
It's his.
Would you like to be sent away?
I will make a phone call.
How did you promise me before?
You said you would behave yourself.
Are you going to keep making trouble?
It is such a blessing
to have such a brother.
Well.
Help yourselves.
I will offer you super VIP price.
70% off.
Thank you so much.
I am so grateful
that you could
understand
my strange younger sister.
Thank you so much.
All right, enough.
Or I will send you there.
Okay.
That means the suit
is only 937 Yuan.
We saved
1,563 Yuan.
So that we can
go to the restaurant eight times,
eat in the cafeteria one hundred times
or drink two hundred cups of milk tea, right?
Qian Wei.
You are so worthy of your name.
Brother.
I'm sick, brother.
I know you are sick.
But stop making trouble out.
Could we…
Calm down?
What are you looking at?
What?
Mature beauty.
Good.
Thank you.
You're welcome, fool.
Wear the tie.
Wait.
Let me try.
Just to wear a tie.
You think
I can't even do this?
Well, I can't.
You do.
Why didn't listen to me?
I am giving you a chance.
Thank you.
What are you doing, Qian Wei?
I didn't mean to do it.
You are really a fool.
It seems that
I have you send you away later.
Stop looking at me.
Am I in good spirits?
But why are you
so skilled at
wearing a tie?
Because I wear it for you
every day in the future.
I like to practice.
I always practice it at home.
Why practice this?
What's wrong with you?
(Processing Factory)
(Bless)
(Check carefully for safety)
What are you doing?
Don't be afraid of them.
The more frightened you are,
the more arrogant he will be.
My endurance has been exercised by someone
to be very strong.
What are you two doing?
Who asked you to take pictures?
Hello, we are
(Qian Wei, Lawyer)
lawyers of Zhanying Law Firm.
My name is Qian Wei.
This is my assistant Lu.
We got a request
from a client
saying that the oil and paint
used here are not up to specification.
So we're came to obtain evidence.
Stop it. Just leave.
Leave.
What are you doing?
(Security)
If you hurt us,
it will be another story.
Listen.
If we leave now,
Quality Supervision Bureau will be here soon.
Quality Supervision Bureau?
Get them out.
Leave.
- You…
- Leave.
Wait.
What happened?
Manager.
She said the two of them are lawyers
and took a lot of photos.
Sorry.
(Realize ambition)
My men are rude.
I beg your understand.
Come on.
Take some tea.
Miss.
Who commissioned you?
It's not right to
condemn someone out of thin air.
We cannot disclose the information
of other parties
before putting on record.
But we can check the information
of the factory together.
(Civil Construction Engineering Indoor
Environmental Pollution Control)
Our country stipulates that
the content of benzene per cubic meter indoors
cannot exceed 0.09 mg.
The air quality in your factory
is seriously exceeded,
and the staff
are not equipped with
relevant protective measures.
You even force them to work overtime.
Sir.
Your violation
goes way too far.
(Civil Construction Engineering Indoor
Environmental Pollution Control)
(Student card)
Meanwhile,
we just asked
the nearby residents.
There is often the sound
of working overtime all night.
Your electricity bill this month
is also twice as high as that of last month.
This makes no sense.
The situation of our factory is special.
The working hours are all determined
by the production period of the product.
It's normal to work all night.
Really?
I suggest you
take a look at this.
According to the labor law,
employees cannot work
more than 36 hours of overtime
per month,
even if under special situation.
Your employees seem to
have worked overtime
for more than 40 hours.
Okay, let's put time aside.
According to law,
if employees work overtime,
you must pay them
no less than 150%
of their wages.
so did you pay them?
Both of you are
young and promising.
But why haven't I heard of
Zhanying Law Firm?
Gosh.
I forgot that Zhanying was only
established next year.
There are so many law firms in China.
Do you know every one of them?
Please come in.
Manager.
Someone from the court
came to send the materials.
Invite him in.
Okay.
If you two
are true lawyers,
you should have regular contact
with the court.
Let's talk together.
And I would
listen to the opinion of the court.
Of course.
No problem.
Okay.
Watch your words.
Zhang Bohan.
Yes.
Yang Lirong.
Jiang Qing.
Yes.
Qian Wei.
Zhang Dongchen.
Yes.
Lu Xun.
Why looking at me?
Turn around.
It must be a girl.
Why doing this
on my class?
Who's that?
Turn around.
Stand up.
What?
You want to test my memory?
Okay.
Take turns reporting
from the first row.
If I find you,
your usual score
will be gone.
Start.
Ma Junqi.
Wu Fang.
Zhang Yanzhi.
Lu Die.
Yang Jiani.
Zhang Huilin.
Yang Lirong.
Wang Qianqian.
Jiang Qing.
Zhang Dongchen.
Wu Zu.
Wang Yinuo.
Personal loyalty
is top priority.
Let's get it.
Professor, I…
What's wrong with you?
Take her to the clinic.
Hurry up.
Do me a favor.
Let's go.
Come here.
Open the door.
(Realize ambition)
Mr. Liu.
Hello.
Perfect timing.
Today,
two young people
who claim to be lawyers
from Zhanying Law Firm came to me.
I don't think
I've ever heard of it.
You know
many lawyers.
Do you know them?
Uncle Liu.
Lu Xun.
Long time no see.
Chief Judge Lu
always talks about you.
I didn't expect to
meet you here today.
What are you doing here?
Good question.
What am I doing here?
They came to popularize law education
for the staff of our factory.
Legal education.
That's right.
You should be
well educated.
Regard law with awe.
Yes.
Of course.
Good for you, Lu.
Like father like son.
I believe
you would become a judge in the future.
Good boy.
Chief Judge Lu
could retire with peace of mind
in a few years.
Right.
Fulfill obligations well in the future.
This time the court lifted
the high consumption restraining order
against you.
This is the notice.
Pay attention to the repayment period
in the future
and avoid repeat offenses.
Of course I will.
Of course.
I am leaving.
Lu.
Bye.
Let me see you off.
Take a seat.
It's good to have a judge dad.
I will be a judge
in the future.
It's not too late for you
to recognize me
as your chief.
Why don't you
let me call you boss?
I predict that
you will not be a judge in the future.
Cool.
I believe that.
After Lu Xun's father
retired,
he became a lawyer
without hesitation.
Lu Xun
still doesn't know much
about himself.
Chief Judge Lu's son
is really handsome.
Let's have dinner together today.
Just to know each other.
There is no need to eat together.
But we have to
figure out something.
Was your repayment
embezzled from
oil and paint fees?
You allow workers
to continue to work
with excessive benzene,
which seriously affects
their health.
They are doing
high-risk jobs.
Therefore, according to labor law,
you must match them with
corresponding insurance
and protective measures.
Since you didn't do it,
you definitely have to
compensate them.
But
none of the surrounding factories did this.
You are forcing me to lose money.
The surrounding factories
didn't owe money,
didn't use
inferior paint,
neither did they violate labor law
and squeeze employees.
Think about it.
If you are
accused in court,
and other companies
see all the evidence
and your company's scandal,
will they still
cooperate with you?
Well.
You can refuse to
pay compensation now,
but you won't be able
to make money in the future.
Sir.
We don't mean to make it hard for you.
We also brought
a settlement agreement this time.
In fact, our request is quite simple.
(Collectively Negotiated Settlement Agreement)
As long as you replace the oil and paint
within the specified time,
equip all the staff
with corresponding protective measures,
buy them insurance
and pay compensation,
we will not sue.
Would you like to think about it?
Boss.
I don't think
he intends to reconcile.
I suggest we sue directly.
Sue?
It will have…
Let me think it over.
Okay?
Let me take a look.
Take a look.
Ten minutes?
Five minutes?
Go ahead.
Signs are all normal.
She should be fine.
But she has to be careful.
Okay, thank you, doctor.
Go back to class first.
Okay.
Besides pretending to faint,
I still have to jump out of the window.
I sacrificed too much.
You woke up.
What are you doing?
I felt chest distress,
so I'd like to open the window
for some fresh air.
You just woke up.
You'd better not do this.
Come on.
Let me help you.
Be careful.
Take a seat.
The coat of you
is quite different from your personality.
It's full of rivets.
Luckily it didn't hurt you
when you fainted just now.
I got up late this morning.
This is
my roommate's coat.
I'm not usually like this.
Relax.
Thank you, doc.
I am Liu Shiyun of
Law Department 2011.
- What about…?
- Hush.
(It must be God)
(who gave me a gentle handsome guy)
(because of my love and righteousness)
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪