Relax.
Thank you, doctor.
I'm Liu Shiyun,
from Law department of 2011.
- May I ask you…
- Hush.
(It must be the gift from God)
(to meet a pretty gentleman)
(as a reward of my righteousness.)
I'm Tang Lyu.
You can call me senior.
I'm from the College of Medicine.
I come to assist the clinic
in my leisure time.
Hello, senior.
Hello.
Your heartbeat is a bit fast.
It might be hypoglycemia,
Here you are.
(He gives me chocolate.)
(He must have a crush on me.)
(Shall we marry?)
(Where should we hold the wedding?)
(How many people should we invite?)
(What's the name of our child?)
What's wrong?
Don't you like chocolate?
Yes.
I'm just afraid of getting fat.
This is dark chocolate.
Each piece only contains
24 grams of fat.
60 percent of it is
saturated fatty acid
stearic acid
and flavonoid.
These won't get you fat.
It can reduce the cholesterol degree
in your blood.
Rest assured.
Doctor, doctor.
I pulled my muscle.
Liu Shiyun.
Why are you there?
Take a seat.
She just fainted.
It's hypoglycemia.
It's common for girls.
Let me check.
Doctor.
Don't be joking.
Is she a girl?
She's a Kong Kim.
One more word,
Zixin will hear
lots of ill comments on you tonight.
Is it so painful?
Wait for a minute.
I'll take the medicine for you.
So handsome.
To accost the guy,
you even feigned illness.
What a good guy,
ruined by you.
What a pity.
How dare you eat it.
Spit it out.
Let me go.
Spit it out. Spit it out.
Spit it out.
Are you mad?
(Mo Zixin)
=Episode 5=
=Life is Cruel to Me=
(Thanks for the invitation.)
(I'll be there on time tomorrow.)
=Legally Romance=
Let's cheer for
Mr. Qian Yanping's honorable retirement.
Thank you.
But
I have to thank Lu Xun today.
Don't.
You helped me a lot.
I have to thank you
for my colleagues.
The feast
represent my appreciation.
Just eat.
You're welcome.
It was my idea.
What do you thank him for?
Right.
My little girl has grown up
and been able to defend me.
This dinner
is really touching.
It was the kids
waiting for me to come home
from work.
From now on,
we have to
wait for them to come back home.
I'll take the soup.
Don't.
Let me take it.
Don't move.
Let me take it. Listen,
just leave the trifles to me.
It's OK.
Hurry up.
Calm down.
Is it boiling?
Boiling?
How come?
Not at all.
It's OK.
Just sit.
I'm so strong,
comparable to your little brother,
right?
I feel the smell of barbecue.
You're exaggerating, uncle.
I'm joking. I'm joking.
I was busy with work,
and had no time for myself.
From now on,
I will spend all my time
on the things
I wanted to do.
You wanted to travel
around the world, right?
I'll go with you.
You one-month pension
is not enough for a bag for me.
Let alone travelling around the world.
We can't afford it.
What bag is that expensive?
Listen,
the boy
won't have a girlfriend for the moment.
Let's just
use the money for his house.
Well, dad.
Who said I won't have a girlfriend?
Give me one month,
and I'll bring the girl home.
Good.
Well, dad and mom,
I do think,
I have a feeling that
travelling is not important
as buying a house.
Let's buy the house as a priority.
Uncle, aunt.
I assumed that Qian Wei
only fools people outside.
I haven't expected that
she even fools you at home.
Shut up.
If I was informed of this
by someone before,
I would be so grateful.
Hello, dad.
What's up?
Lu Xun.
I heard from my colleague today that
he met you and your girlfriend.
Well,
she's not my girlfriend.
You haven't succeeded?
Come on.
Your mom was so boring
and wanted to have a grandchild.
You know,
the undergraduate students
can get married now.
Hello?
Dad?
What?
The signal is bad here.
Well.
Hello? Hello?
What?
Somebody might diet a wrong number.
Are you going
to chase after my daughter?
He? No way.
It's impossible, uncle.
I like the girls
with high IQ,
good and gentle
personality,
and that
won't make trouble.
What do you mean?
Who makes trouble?
No, no, no.
Let me explain, Qian Wei.
I didn't mean that you have a low IQ,
abnormal
and makes trouble.
Dad, look at him.
You humiliate me in my home.
You're doomed.
Wait.
How can you say that
in front of my parents?
Qian Wei.
Stand up.
Dad.
Beat him.
Stand up.
You're doomed.
I don't have to beat you by myself.
For years,
I have never met someone like you
who knows my daughter so well.
Good.
Right, uncle?
You know her weakness.
And you have to help her
one-to-one.
What? What's do you mean?
How come
you speak for the outsider?
Well.
Not only helping her.
I have to pull her out.
Look at her brain.
Look at her temper
when speaking.
See. See.
She even hit me.
Eat your food.
See, how can it be?
Well, I'm…
It's painful.
She just learnt from her mother.
Really?
Well,
aunt is so gentle.
They're no way alike.
She's really
tougher than her.
(See, something's wrong.)
(ZX, Lu Xun)
(He renamed his ID.)
(He used his real name)
(for every social media account.)
(Why did he change?)
If I am to have a girlfriend,
- (What is ZX?)
- I will definitely choose the aunt's type.
(Zixin)
(Renamed his ID for courtship)
(and show love publicly?)
(Good of Lu Xun)
(So active.)
What?
What's wrong with you?
Why do you stare at me?
Is there food on my face?
Can you just eat your food?
Look.
Cool.
(He's really guilty.)
(My goal to exceed Lu Xun)
(is getting closer.)
(10 Top Elites of the Year, Qian Wei)
(Next is the news of law.)
(Qian Wei, the great lawyer)
(was awarded)
(10 Top Elites of the Year)
(When she accepted the prize, she said,)
(Thank Lu Xun,)
(my previous classmate.)
(who inspired me to fight.)
(Here,)
(I want to encourage those)
(staff and assistants
who are being oppressed.)
(Believe in yourself)
(and make your dream come true.)
(You can make it.)
(1. Run for the monitor; 2. Join the debate team;
3. Leave a good impression on Mr. Zhang)
(The plan to optimize dad)
(Prevent dad from getting leukemia)
(The task of preventing dad)
(from getting leukemia)
(is completed.)
What do you want?
The notes of
Chinese Legal History
for the exam.
The exams for this course by Mr. Jia
are very difficult.
If we fail for the first time,
the make-up exam will be harder.
So, we must
pass 60.
It's good to be ambitious.
OK.
Cleaning the dorm five times.
No problem.
OK?
OK.
Thank you, Lu Xun.
(Group of four)
(Notes of Chinese Legal History)
ZX
Lu Xun.
Why did you change your ID?
(Group of four)
I thought
it was from someone else.
I joined a group of
Students Union election.
The group owner asked me
to change the prefix into
my intentional position
and department
for counting, maybe.
But I changed my QQ ID
by mistake.
ZX.
President.
Bro, you're really amazing.
You're elected to be
the president of Students Union
in your first election.
President.
No.
I'm not that crazy.
I'm just a freshman.
It's just my intention.
I'm running for associate trainee.
Bro.
You're elected to be associate trainee
of Student Union as a freshman.
You're really amazing.
OK, OK.
Hurry up.
Mind your exam.
OK. OK
(Debate Championship of Haizhou Cup)
People are the products of society.
The change of world
will influence people.
Life was slow,
(When are you)
- (available this week?)
- and vehicles and mails were slow.
- (What do you usually do?)
- You can only love a person in your life.
- Could you please
- But now,
- don't disturb my mind
- the internet is advanced
- if you don't know
- the transportation is convenient.
what to say?
It only takes one second
to send an e-mail.
You're being pretentious again.
- Just take a glimpse of it.
- And it takes a day to take a train.
Rest assured.
- We will win.
- These are love,
and attitude.
I've read it.
- Well,
- These prove that
(The Third Debater, The Second Debater)
you're making a fuss.
- Mind yourselves.
- People can be changed by the world.
- It's a competition.
- I'm finished.
Hurry up.
(Negative)
Please answer
the questions above.
Our opponent.
Your speech
was with a logical fallacy.
If no one ever
study the internet,
build bridges and roads,
where can we get the advanced internet
and convenient transportation?
Isn't this the ironclad proof
that human changes the world?
Society has changed,
But some people still
write letters
while some send emails,
some are consistent,
some are half-hearted.
Which is true,
the world changed you,
or you changed yourself
and pass the buck to the world?
Good.
You did a good job this turn.
We will win this turn.
You cooperated quite well
for the first time.
Yes.
It's hard to tell who will win
if you become
the opponents.
It must be me.
It's me.
Don't be proud.
Qian Wei.
Don't change the arguments
we discussed before the competition.
The opponents are not strong this time
and didn't catch your fallacy.
The next time we may not be so lucky.
Chongwen,
we've won three times consecutively.
How about getting out to celebrate it?
I can't.
I have something else to do.
You just go.
He's gone.
What do we eat?
How about this one?
No, no.
You know what?
This restaurant will be the worst
of Guanghua University
in the next four years.
How about
the restaurant in the crossing?
No.
The oil they use
is insanitary.
Don't eat it even if it's delicious.
How about hot pot?
No way.
The heavy oil, spicy
and salt
are bad for your stomach.
You'll know it in the future.
It's important to care for your stomach.
You denied all of my suggestions.
You decide then.
You choose what you what.
I, I, I,
I wasn't finding fault.
It's just these restaurants
you mentioned are really bad.
Since you're so picky,
how about eating fish?
Eating fish? OK.
Coming.
Your seafood.
Senior.
What a coincidence.
Are you working here?
It's really a coincidence.
I didn't know
you would be here.
I should have arranged.
a private room for you.
Senior is really handsome.
You're so outstanding
wearing the uniform.
No wonder so many girls like you.
Well,
don't tell them.
If they
rush in,
senior would be so busy.
Well, just serve yourself.
Senior,
give us some side dishes.
OK, no problem.
Here are the side dishes.
Thank you, senior.
Senior.
Add water.
Fill yourself with water.
I haven't expected that
the most handsome guy
in our university is working here.
Yes, it's unexpected.
Mind the temperature.
Thank you.
Senior.
Could you add a pair of dishes?
OK.
Senior, give us a menu.
Here you are.
What do you want?
Flavor eggplants.
And fried string beans.
OK.
Here you are.
Check it.
It is right?
So cheap.
It's so cheap.
How about
your treat?
OK.
Well,
I've just received a scholarship.
My treat.
Never mind. Never mind.
It's my treat.
You come here for the first time.
It's rare.
Thank you, senior.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
- Take care. Take care.
- Bye-bye.
Sorry.
I didn't hold it well.
It's OK.
Are you alright?
Yes.
OK.
Sorry.
I messed your shoes and clothes.
This is the laundry fee.
Please accept it.
As far as I know,
they cook with dead fishes.
Well,
just look behind.
Let's walk backward.
There're lots of restaurants.
Let's go.
Do you know the punishment of libel?
You're deliberately
breaking the law.
Silence.
Qian Wei said she's guilty.
She decided to treat us
with the most expensive steak
in the front.
When did I say that?
I can't.
Really?
Let's go.
I didn't say that.
No.
We have to
pay by ourselves.
The girls
indeed have to spend money
for themselves.
I must handle
my boyfriend anyway.
You're born
beauty.
And your skin is good
Rest assured.
You will win
all kinds of boys.
I'm so good at catching.
Beauty.
How about trying
our set beautify projects
the next time?
Trust me.
It will be more effective.
Swimming pool?
(The message is right)
(He's here)
(I'll win him over)
(by the play of)
(Hero rescuing a Beauty)
It's you.
Where's Tang Lyu?
Sister.
Could you please play in another place.
If you drowned here,
the swimming pool
will be closed for days,
how could we train?
It's all your fault.
- What? What?
- It's all your fault.
You've feigned illness
and drown.
They're so tiring and ineffective.
How about
let me help you?
Are you so kind to help me?
For exchange,
you have to pry into
Zixin's moves for me.
You should be strategic
when chasing after a boy.
It's much easier to acquire information
between person of the same sex.
Let's cooperate.
Take the advantage
of a favored position.
It will be more effective.
What do you think?
Think about it.
Your bang is too long.
It will block your sight.
You'd better comb it up.
This is the see-through bang.
It will be popular.
What are you here for?
I didn't say thank you to you yesterday.
How about this?
Let me treat you a meal.
No.
I have no appetite recently
and don't want to eat.
No appetite?
I heard that
you ate up a whole chicken
yesterday.
It's a rumor.
Well, I'm actually
preparing for the election
of Students Union.
So, I'm quite busy.
How about next time?
I was also preparing for the election
at this time last year.
I've cleared up
some schemes for it.
I think
you must be running for
the associate trainee of the presidium
considering your ability.
I'm also the member of presidium.
We can eat together
and I'll share
my experience to you
and help you to win it.
(Scheme for win)
(At that time)
(I heard that)
(Li Chongwen's scheme was the best)
(To defeat Lu Xun)
(I'll take the chance)
(and be a matchmaker)
Well, senior,
is it OK if I invite someone else?
No problem.
(Election scheme)
I heard that many students
will write down the one they like
and attach them on the wall.
There's a piece missing.
Did they pick it off after breaking up
or someone else rub it off
by accident?
Let's make it up.
I've been wanting
to write down a name anyway.
People come and go.
What if our piece
is missing?
No way.
As long as I'm here,
I'll protect it well.
(Qian Wei, Li Chongwen)
Here you're.
See.
There a piece missing.
How about
making it up?
I've been wanting
to write down a name anyway.
Only teenagers
will do that.
I don't believe it.
You're a teenager, right?
My psychological age is 28.
I read a personality test
the other day.
It went like this:
If a rich girl
with billions of property
courting you,
and you have to abandon
your dream and the person you love,
what would be your choice?
Of course the person I love.
What is the significance
of a rich girl?
So, what's the result?
What's my personality.
Good.
It means you're a teenager.
As long as keeping
your original aspiration
and working hard,
you'll realize your dream.
Life is not that easy
as you think.
Where are your roommates?
If they are late,
the fish will taste bad.
And they might give
the negative comment
picking about it.
Don't let him go.
- Let's go.
- Little boy.
I finally get you.
Don't think you can get away
from the debt
as your father is dead.
Everyone is an independent
civil subject.
If he doesn't
inherit his father's property,
there's no way
he has to pay his father's debts.
If you ask for the payment
with violence,
I'll call the police.
Who are you?
Don't stickybeak.
I've paid
all my debts.
You're now asking for
the illegal usury.
According to the law,
The rate of loan
shouldn't be higher than
four times of that in the bank.
The exceeding part
is illegal.
So I won't pay
for the exceeding part.
Are you trying to repudiate?
Guys, smashing the restaurant.
If I can't get money today,
no one of you can go.
I'll call the police.
Buddy, buddy, buddy.
What?
Mind your words.
Don't smash the restaurant.
It's none of your business.
Go away.
Boy.
Good of you.
You can afford a meal,
but have no money to pay me, right?
Take care of yourself,
and then mind other people's business.
OK?
Well,
what are you doing?
Why are you rescuing me now?
Qian Wei.
What?
According to the penal law,
you'll receive at least
no more than three-year imprisonment for
intentional injury.
I'll call the police.
And you'll see the result.
Don't stickybeak
or I'll also beat you.
It's the same for threatening.
You…
I'll…
It's the same
for destroying private possession.
Don't you understand?
You,
you…
OK.
It's unfortunate of me to meet
a law advertiser
when asking for the payment.
Guys,
let's go.
Be careful.
Just wait.
(I thought he)
(only show off)
(by classed suit and resume)
(I didn't expect
that 18-year-old Lu Xun)
(is still so shining)
(even with seafood soup all over him)
It's OK.
Let me clean it for you.
I shouldn't have taken you in
if I knew you're
with so many debts.
They smashed so many stuffs.
How can you compensate for them?
I'm sorry, boss.
I'll compensate for the loss
according to the original price, OK?
How to compensate?
Your half a year's salary is not enough.
How much will it take?
Let me pay for you.
No.
I'll be responsible
for my business.
You don't have to do anything for me.
Senior,
since these are
your father's debts,
why don't you just give up
the right of inheritance
and you don't have to pay the debts.
My father not only
left me with the debts,
but also the family
and his good quality
as well as everything he cherished.
These are the most important things
in my life.
I can't give them up.
Exactly.
My family is poor.
But I'm not ashamed of it.
I earned all my fees
and allowance
piece by piece
by working,
part-time jobs
and scholarship
I didn't relay on anyone
till today.
So I believe that
only by working hard
can I change my fate
and poverty.
I also want to
bring hope to
more people
like me
with my professional knowledge.
So, don't pity me.
We're the same.
Well,
let me help you clean it.
Don't.
It's his job.
I believe he can handle it.
Whether the present works
or the works in the future,
I believe
you will do well.
As long as you keep
your original intention
and work hard,
You'll gain
what you want.
Don't worry.
Only three of us
know the thing happened today.
We won't tell anyone
after coming back.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
(Sorry.)
(This time,)
(I can't leave)
(a note for you)
(Election Scheme for Students Union
associate trainee of Guanghua University, 2010)
Teachers and classmates.
(Hello)
(I'm a student from)
Law Department of the year 2011.
(Election of Students Union, Guanghua University)
I'm Li Chongwen.
I'm here today
in wish of joining
the Students Union
of Guanghua University
and become a member of it.
I wish I could change
(Election of Students Union, Guanghua University)
the mood of
pursuing score and personal honor.
I want to call us people
to pay attention to the weak,
discrimination and injustice,
And achieve
Guanghua University's goal
of morality and justice.
Why are you so slow?
Do you want your saver
being soused by seafood soup?
The world will really change people.
The passion
and original intentions are true.
But they will be worn down by time.
No matter how passionate the person was,
he will struggle for interests
with others later.
So, this is not
the topic.
It's the reality.
You're so infirm.
I think you're not suitable
for the debate.
It'll be me
to shoulder the responsibility
to build the debate team.
Be silent.
You want to be a judge.
What if
you have to change racing track
in the future?
Even if you're right,
how about the future?
The reason why I fail to be a judge
is because
I want to change the world
instead of
being changed by the world.
Situation changes.
It's all up to you
to decide what to become
and how to get alone
with the world.
So, people are
making choices all the time.
(No way)
(I should have been a matchmaker.)
(Why did I discuss this with him?)
(Business matters)
Zixin.
Lu Xun's close got dirty.
Could you wash it for him?
It's because of you.
Why do you ask her to wash?
It should be you who wash it for me.
Zixin, were you checking
the stocks investment app last night?
I invest the stocks
in my leisure time
and earn some allowance.
Lu Xun needs money recently.
How about investing for him?
Well,
You owe me 500 yuan.
Pay me
500 yuan first
and I don't have to invest.
Keep silence.
I said,
I'll pay you once I have allowance.
What's the point of
talking about 500 yuan again and again?
500 yuan is important.
I will
pay you 500 yuan.
You just talk among yourselves.
I have some business
and come back dorm first.
Don't go.
Come back.
You said I'm insane.
You've gone mad
on the other hand.
You showed love publicly.
What's wrong with you?
You're returned and know nothing?
What's showing love publicly?
Fine.
I know you want to save your face.
I'll protect your dignity, OK?
But promise me,
take the initiative next time,
OK?
Like you to Li Chongwen?
Beating him first
and treat him a meal?
What's this?
Take the initiative?
You just stay single.
Don't teach me.
You know what?
I have no feeling
about him at all.
I just wanted to learn from him
the experience of electing
and ask for support.
Are you preparing for the election
of Students Union associate trainee?
Let me tell you a secret.
A top secret.
Civilian Lu Xun,
I'm the predictor.
So I'll win.
Bye-bye.
Qian Wei.
(I have to work harder)
(to be a matchmaker for Lu Xun)
(An 18-year-old boy)
(fall in love)
(and has no time to mind the business)
(I'll win the election)
(It's said that students here)
(will go to the roller-skating rink
on the weekends)
(Let's compete fairly)
(Tomorrow afternoon,)
(let's canvass here)
(Lu Xun)
Zixin,
Lu Xun asks you
to skate tomorrow.
Are you available?
OK.
I'm available tomorrow.
(Roller skating rink)
(is the perfect place to date)
(which has been verified by practice.)
(Lu Xun)
(I've done everything I can)
(Just give in)
(to your fate)
Do you bring the stuff?
Yes.
Let's begin.
OK.
Where's Old Liu?
I'm Old Liu.
Why do you look like this?
Let it go.
I found the custom-made model from
the browsing history
In target person's computer.
It can help you
prevent the date.
Where're mine?
The target person
is practicing acupuncture recently.
He practices on everyone he meets.
People all hide from him.
It's the perfect time to take actions.
I've prepared mustard for you.
(Mustard)
One bite
will make you a tender cat.
He will be attracted
by you immediately.
But it's a bit painful.
Are you afraid?
It's just acupuncture.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Succeed,
no failure.
Qian Chuan.
The mustard is unnecessary.
My true feeling will be enough.
Sorry.
This is the junction of
nerve trunk and ending.
Does it hurt?
You're working for
human's medical career.
It's so great.
I'm so happy to
be able to help you.
I just have to eat come strawberry cakes
to ease the pain.
You quite know it.
The sugar in strawberry cakes
can promote
the release of dopamine.
It can also
ease the pain to some degree.
When it's done,
I'll take you to eat.
Zixin,
you're here.
See.
This is for you.
Thank you.
(Now,)
(Lu Xun and Mo Zixin)
(might have met.)
(After returning the cloth)
(I can go canvass by myself)
Uncle.
This is for
Lu Xun of Law Department.
There're so many people here.
Who is the one?
It's easy to recognize him.
He is of this high,
and is dark.
But his heart is darker than his face.
His eyes
are like this.
And his hairs
are stretched out.
You know,
just like the rooster
with feather stretching out.
Is it him?
Well,
why are you here?
Why am I here?
There're not only problems
with your eyes,
but problems
with your mind.
Open your eyes
and watch.
This is dormitory for boys.
I know it's dormitory for boys.
Haven't you received
my message?
My phone is
cut off.
What did you send?
You didn't seize the chance.
It's not important.
I just wanted to invite
you to canvass
in the roller-skating rink.
It's OK you haven't been there.
There's still time.
Let's go now.
No, I can't skate.
Never mind.
I can.
Let me teach you. Let's go.
No.
Let's go now.
Well ,can you?
Let me teach you.
Uncle,
we just leave the clothes here.
Hurry up.
Well, Qian Chuan,
why are you there?
Where are you going?
Well,
you said
we can win over 200 votes
in roller skating rink.
There're only two students from
Guanghua University.
Don't waste time here.
Let's come back to school.
Please.
What are you thinking about?
Zixin
just entitled the first beauty of
Guanghua University.
If you ask her to canvass for you,
you can win over 500 votes
let alone 200.
Let's
just
compete fairly.
Qian Chuan
and Physical Department
will vote for me anyway.
The backup team of Mo Zixin
will vote for you.
And we can compete
formally and fairly.
Therefore,
you should show some sincerity.
(Skating: 25 yuan for 40 minutes)
(Skating: 50 yuan for one hour)
I owe you money anyway.
Don't try to
profit from me.
OK. OK.
Sir,
Two pairs of shoes of
37 and 42 respectively.
How do you know my size of shoes?
Who am I?
Let alone the size of shoes,
I know everything about you.
Are you…
OK, this is yours.
This is mine.
Here you are.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Don't be nervous.
Like this.
Lower down your weight.
Bend your legs.
OK. OK.
Go, just like this.
No, don't…
It's OK. Come on.
Come on.
Get up.
OK.
Stand up.
Time is limited and the task is heavy.
Well,
let me push you.
- I can't. What to do?
- It's OK.
Stand up.
Stand straight.
OK, move forward.
One, two, three.
Go.
Why do you push in this way?
I can't.
Why do you always push me, Qian Wei?
It's OK.
We can catch up with him.
How about this.
Go, go, go.
Quickly. Quickly. Quickly.
Hurry up.
Come here.
Move forward.
What are you doing?
Well.
Don't be with her.
Come here. Come here.
Come to me.
Slow down.
She can't.
What are you doing?
Never mind. You two enjoy it.
Let it go.
You,
come back.
No.
Oh my God.
Can you stand straight?
I can't. What to do?
Just wait.
Stand up.
What are you doing?
Stand by yourself.
Stand up.
Ready.
Well.
One, two, three, go.
Qian Wei, I haven't learnt it.
Zixin, wait a minute.
OK.
Lu Xun.
How about skating together.
I can't.
I was like that.
It's OK.
I believe
you'll be touched by this.
It's OK.
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪