Enjoy your meal.
No matter how much you eat today,
it's my treat.
It sounds like
you are often disappointed in love.
Not like that.
I always
couldn't win a person before.
Every time I lost,
I just came here for dessert.
Although my case
is different from yours,
the curative effect should be similar.
Is it good?
Well.
It's sweet.
Screw you!
If you were really disappointed
in love,
how could you taste the sweetness?
Tell me the truth.
Did you screw it up
or did you not care about it at all?
Didn't I?
Did I get the movie tickets
and book the dinner table?
Haven't I taken care of it yet?
You are striving to get to a point
when you would finally have enough.
You were not ready
for the first night.
Why did you think about
the second night?
That's why
you would be caught unprepared.
Do you understand?
Did you say that
it's safe to
do according to your plan?
What happened then?
What are you doing now?
You are blaming me?
I don't think I should trust you.
What are you doing?
It's okay you failed once.
You have already spent the money.
No need to do that.
Just find a good friend
and go with him.
That's it.
I really can't stand you.
It's enough for you
to know this kind of thing yourself.
Do you have to make it
known to everyone?
I don't need them. Throw them away.
Give it to me. Give it to me!
I'll go with you, okay?
Is it helpful for you to accompany me?
Since I am the matchmaker,
I will be a responsible one.
You take this thing
as a barrier
on your way to love.
Even if it's hard,
I'll accompany you to overcome it today,
okay?
Can you do it?
Stop talking nonsense and eat quickly.
When you're finished, let's go.
Which step did I make wrong?
Yes.
Which step is wrong?
You tell me.
=Episode 7=
=Don't Love Me Ex=
=Legally Romance=
But, why does Zixin…
Don't ask.
Once you ask,
it hurt me.
OK, I won't ask.
Eat quickly.
You ordered such a good steak.
Don't waste it.
Eat it. Eat it.
This…
I don't want to eat it.
I lost my appetite.
I am too disappointed to cut it.
OK. OK. OK.
I owe you, okay?
I'll cut it for you.
You paid a lot
to be worthy
of Zixin's taste, didn't you?
Don't be too sad.
Actually,
This feeling of cutting money
is no worse than falling in love.
Here you are.
Eat it.
I lost my appetite.
You lost appetite.
What can I do?
I don't want to eat it.
It's expensive. Have a try.
Take a bite.
Are you feeling better?
I haven't swallowed it yet.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
And then
the effect of that meat
will just come up.
Come on.
Have a mouthful of meat
and a mouthful of wine,
and you will
get your energy back
right away.
Have a try.
I'm telling you.
If every time
after being disappointed in love,
I could eat like this.
Then I am willing
to be disappointed in love every day.
We are running out of time.
If you are finished,
let's hurry.
Check out, please.
According to your teaching,
I have a surprise for you
after dinner.
Would you like to have it?
What's the surprise?
Escaping the charge.
♪The debris in my hand turns into you♪
♪Fill the emptiness in my heart♪
♪I'm willing to jump into your trap♪
♪The debris in my hand turns into you♪
♪The stars in the sky are
like your eyes♪
♪I'll always be here♪
I really, really…
I really can't run.
I'm telling you.
Your reputation's going to be
in the toilet.
You know the law but break the law.
Didn't you say that?
When dating,
make our heart beats
faster.
That will create unforgettable memories.
What is more unforgettable
than our Law students'
evasion?
Your education is complete.
You hurry back with me
and buy the order.
No way.
We'll miss the movie later.
It doesn't matter.
I can't watch a man of great charm
from law school
turn into
a juvenile delinquent
in Law in Action.
Come with me.
What about this?
(Western Restaurant on 52nd Street)
Are you kidding me?
Your poor trick.
I almost believed it!
What's wrong with you.
Keep them.
Just say it.
In order to chase Zixin,
how many of these strange sweet dramas
have you watched?
What is a sweet drama?
Sweet drama.
Sweet drama is…
Like this!
Feel it?
You're rude!
Are you feeling sweet?
(Floating City)
(Love triangle of three people)
All right.
Stop hitting me.
I'm wrong, okay?
- No!
- Stop chasing me.
The assistant
confessed her love to the hero
but she was rejected.
She just walked away
What a shame!
I'm telling you.
It would be more embarrassing
if you like someone but do not confess.
You're not like them.
You're a real man.
But if it were me,
if I were not quite sure,
I wouldn't confess, either.
That's true.
Let's go eat something.
OK. Let's go.
You said you would accompany me.
But you also escaped.
What do you check it for?
We haven't finished watching the movie.
Does it make sense for you
to check the spoiler?
Let's have rice noodles.
Go.
You watch out.
I found it!
They said that
Aaron Kwok finally
returned to family
and stayed
with his childhood sweetheart.
He didn't choose the assistant.
I'm telling you.
That's a good sign.
You will be with Zixin
smoothly.
It's all movies.
In reality,
how can there be
so many childhood sweethearts?
If I were me,
I must choose that assistant.
She could do anything.
Anything could be ordered.
And we could follow
the legal procedure
and let her
share some work for me.
Did you piss Zixin off
because of these
naive, frivolous and ignorant words?
Listen to me.
For you,
it's absolutely impossible
to be with your assistant.
Man's life is destined.
You are destined to be with your
childhood sweetheart.
Do you understand?
You'll never be with your assistant.
Then do you know
who will be my future assistant?
Who will it be?
It won't be Liu Xinyou anyway.
Don't be discouraged.
It'll be
the sodality soon.
The person in charge of this time
is very close to being me.
I'll help you
remedy the situation.
Who knows what will happen
in the future?
You give my two tickets
back first.
We can't even see the movie.
What should we do?
I will pay for it.
I'll treat you to this.
It's too cold. I don't want to eat it.
I want to eat that.
So picky.
Hi, I would like two ice creams.
OK.
Really.
Good performance can make money.
Have a drink.
Little beauty.
You look good.
Later,
how about we buy you a drink?
We're all single.
I don't need it. I don't have time.
No need.
Hands off.
Who are you?
My hand. My hand.
You stay here.
Come here, let me tell you something.
Come.
Forget it.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Go.
What did you tell them
to make them leave?
Nothing.
Just tell them that
you don't look good
when you remove your makeup.
It's not necessary
to be in the police station
because of this.
So they left.
You idiot!
Is it good?
Eat more if it's good!
Have some more!
The director
of Moral Education Department called.
I'm telling you.
I must be in charge this time.
Wait and see.
Hello, teacher.
Qian Wei.
People in charge of the sodality
are decided. You're one of them.
OK, thank you, teacher.
By the way,
and Li Chongwen, a sophomore.
This way. Get on the bus this way.
This way. This way.
Right. Right. Right.
Get on the bus here.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
This way. This way. This way.
Sodality,
the annual event of high popularity
of law school.
It's like a giant
youth hormone mixer,
it is brewing wonderful and fierce
chemical reactions,
but also creating
countless dangerous incidents.
At that time, this group of students
with excess hormones,
some drifted out of the water,
some turned out their home stay
and disappeared,
some tossed themselves allergic,
and some went to the hospital.
They said enough sincere words.
But I bore all dangerous events.
I lost my seat
on the presidium of the Students' Union
because of my poor work.
I'm in charge again this time.
I, Niohuru Prophet,
will never let it happen again!
I can make it!
Come on!
Pink leather clothes.
Where did this typhoon come from
to stir your young girl's heart?
Hello, classmate Qian Wei.
You applied to the school office
to transfer the school doctor's
entourage in case of accidents,
didn't you?
I'm Tang Lyu,
a school medical assistant.
I would appreciate your kind notice.
So you are the typhoon.
Sure.
I feel much more relieved with you.
Go on. Get on the bus.
You use public resources
for personal purpose.
I love you.
Come on. Go away.
You are so annoying.
Let me help you.
Her suitcase
shouldn't be so heavy, right?
Sure enough,
people in love are a little different
from before.
You are like a piece of white paper.
Are you qualified to judge others?
I'm telling you.
The opportunities are rare
in this sodality.
You should seize the opportunity.
Hurry and chase Zixin back.
You hear me?
Don't waste opportunities.
Don't talk nonsense.
Qian Wei
Isn't it all arranged?
The bus is too crowded.
Why is it so crowded?
Mainly because of the K Line.
The momentum of your stock
- is not good.
- Qian Wei, look.
The ones you chose
all hit the bottom and bounced back.
You still talk about the K Line?
You know what,
Zixin's Dad
is the real god of stocks.
It's not easy for me
to find this book.
The above case studies
can be called
the miracle of domestic stock history.
Sure enough, she is the daughter
of the invisible god of stocks.
Uncle Morris
must be particularly pleased.
How stupid you are!
Are they
really learning the stock market?
That's picking up girls.
I'm telling you.
Since Zixin made her first pot of gold
on the stock market.
Half of the boys in our school
now like to speculate
on the stock market.
What's it called?
It's called giving what one likes.
Can you learn something from them?
Are you talking about MPT?
You hurry!
Go and save the beauty!
Get rid of them all.
Forget it.
Nothing forcibly done
is going to be agreeable.
Don't you understand this truth?
You hurry…You!
You!
All right, I will help you to do it.
It's hard to have this opportunity.
I can't let these stupid guys seize it.
You guys.
All right. All right.
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
Hurry up.
You all have seats.
Go back to your seats.
How can we keep safe?
I'm telling you.
You guys are the biggest
hidden danger!
Go.
There are ten minutes left.
What's your hurry?
Yes.
- Yes.
- We're talking about stocks with Zixin.
Do you understand?
About what stocks?
You have to sit according
to…
Classmate.
This K Line is the one above,
not below.
And this classmate.
What Markowitz said was
the best investment choice
is to develop investment diversification
to reduce risk
under the background
of weighing risk and return.
This is the Modern Portfolio Theory,
MPT for short.
Also,
you see, there are so many people
on this bus.
There's no room for you gods of stocks.
There's a bus next to it.
Go to that bus and quarrel yourselves.
OK.
Go, go, go.
You go back to your seats.
Hurry up!
Forget it. Forget it.
Wait until we arrive at the destination.
Come on. Take it. Take it.
Thank you, senior.
Qian Wei, did you get hit?
No. Don't worry.
If they come back
and bother you again,
you'll let them call me.
Why are you going?
I have my own seat.
They're all gone.
It's all empty.
Just sit here.
My bag is still over there.
I'll take a seat over there first.
The effect of guarding
are the same.
I'll go first.
(Fantawild Dreamland)
(Dream Theater)
(Boonie Bears)
Zixin, sit with me.
The seats are all arranged.
Let's listen to the person in charge.
We are not at school.
We can change seats. It's okay.
Yes.
What are you guys doing?
Don't you see this seating chart?
It is written clearly that
the one with Zixin
is Lu Xun, okay?
Why do you have the final say?
Don't we have a choice?
- Yeah.
You have.
You can sit in a boat with me.
Shall we play together?
- Come on.
Zixin.
Later, if you think
it's a little dangerous,
you can catch Lu Xun.
He will protect you.
Thank you.
You go ahead. Go.
I'm a little afraid of water.
I won't drive the boat either.
Or I'll give it up?
What are you afraid of?
I'm more scared than you.
I'm telling you.
I specially prepared
life jackets and lifebuoys
to each ship.
I'm afraid someone will drown.
Even if Zixin
wants to bungee jump today,
you have to accompany her, okay?
Hurry up.
This.
You'll put it on for Zixin later.
Fasten it tight, okay?
Fasten it tight.
Go. Go.
Come on. Come on!
Bye-bye.
Qian Wei.
Let's go.
Let's get on the boat together.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you stay with Liu
and others?
Come on. Why is he here?
Zixin.
How boring it is to drive
with two people.
We can sit together.
I drive very well.
I can teach you.
It seems that
he signed up voluntarily.
I said
to the counselor in the Department.
He was the brother
of the person in charge.
He has the privilege.
But it's good.
You happened to be here.
We can come together, right?
There's only one boat left.
There's no way.
Let's get on the boat.
Come on.
Oh, no.
At that time, Qian Chuan also followed.
Will that happen…
I want this bubble machine, too.
Give it to me, please.
Be careful. You sit down.
It's okay. Give it to me, please.
You see.
Look, look.
They kissed!
What are you doing?
So romantic.
I knew the god likes to tease me.
Fortunately, I prepared.
I don't believe that I couldn't get rid of
this strange relationship.
Why are you wearing a mask on the boat?
Waterproof?
I caught cold.
I am afraid of infecting you.
Just in case.
Lu Xun.
I've sacrificed a lot this time.
You must remember my
great kindness.
Qian Chuan, come ashore quickly.
Tang Lyu feels uncomfortable.
That thing last time
was over.
We will still be friends, right?
Yes, of course.
Front! Front!
Mo Zixin's there.
Watch out.
Be careful!
Help!
Someone fell into the water.
Somebody!
Come on, someone's overboard!
- Help! Somebody!
- Someone fell into the water.
Help!
Somebody!
I told you that
don't drive around.
Now
someone fainted.
Who would have thought
that thing could break?
Yes.
Zixin has already called someone
for help.
Don't panic yet.
School doctor!
He swam across the river.
Who can apply artificial respiration?
This… I…
God, I admit defeat…
You defeat me.
I'll do it.
Well, I can do that.
I've learned a little before.
Artificial respiration.
I can do it.
I…
I'm sorry.
Well.
Don't tell the teacher
of the Students' Union
about it, okay?
They didn't expect this to happen.
Don't worry.
It's not your fault.
I didn't stand firm myself.
If you don't mind,
just listen to you.
Three of you. Watch out next time.
I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
I'll help you.
Thanks.
It's disgusting.
Don't talk to me.
Recently…
No.
Recent month.
Don't let me see you.
Especially your mouth.
It's disgusting.
Go and change your clothes.
Don't catch cold.
What's up?
Feeling shy?
He is talking to you.
Why don't you listen to him?
Really.
It's not that terrible.
I saw that picture just now.
Very beautiful.
It looks like you're
particularly heroic
and act bravely.
It's disgusting.
Don't mention it in the future.
(Ghost Ship)
What kind of scream does Tang Lyu like?
I am so scared.
Or you're great, Tang Lyu!
Forget it.
Just wait and see.
Anyway, Qian Chuan will help me then.
Hero saves beauty in ghost house.
With Liu Shiyun's help,
Zixin will definitely
falls in love with me.
These people
each harbors evil intentions.
Don't think that I don't know.
No one can succeed with me here.
(Zhu Gong)
Aren't you satisfied?
If it weren't for the only suit
in the store,
I'm telling you,
I don't want you
to take advantage of it.
I'm saving your life.
It would be nice for me
not ask you to make a commitment.
What are you talking about?
Male chauvinist.
Li Chongwen will take a rest first.
He won't come for the time being.
Then I can only plead with him again
later.
What?
Nothing.
Well.
Then let him rest first.
Let's have fun first.
Well, now that we've decided
to go into the ghost house.
Then rush in!
Go!
OK.
Let's go!
What do you want?
Are you scared?
It doesn't matter if you're afraid.
I can barely protect you.
Ask me.
Ask you for what.
Talk less.
I'm telling you.
I've explored the way
for you inside.
This ghost house
is not that scary at all.
At first,
there will be
a white-robed ghost out.
In that case,
just protect Zixin.
She must have fallen into your arms.
Then you go to the far left.
Go that way.
The whole process
may not be so terrifying,
but it's enough for Zixin.
Absolutely enough.
Just protect her.
You know?
I'll be in charge of Qian Chuan.
He knows
I have night blindness anyway.
I'll hold him then.
Today, you can
hold the beauty back, friend!
You have night blindness
but you still go into the ghost house?
I'm night blind. I'm not blind.
I can see it, too.
You don't have to worry about this.
Just protect Zixin.
Do you understand?
I'm telling you.
When she feels most terrified,
it's your best time
to put your arms around her.
See?
What are you doing again?
I'm telling you.
I'm ready for wedding candies.
Hurry in and cheer up.
Go.
Come on, hurry.
Just hold tight, okay?
The kind of suffocation.
Line up here.
I have no problem. You believe…
What's up?
Where are you?
I can't see, Qian Chuan.
What are you screaming at?
There are dummies around here.
Everything's…Everything's fine.
Help! Help!
Hurry! Hurry!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
Brother, is that you?
It's me.
How's it going?
I found the Tang Lyu.
He's on my side.
What about you?
I'll give Zixin to you right away.
A pleasant cooperation.
Zixin. Let's move on.
You follow me.
There is Qian Chuan ahead.
Don't worry.
Don't be afraid, Zixin.
It's all fake.
Follow me.
Don't be afraid, Zixin.
I'm here.
Come.
Senior.
You see.
From a medical perspective,
this man
should have died of blunt force
hitting his skull.
Look, there's a hole here.
Did you see that?
In terms of stress area
of this hole…
So terrible!
- Senior, I'm scared.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Don't worry.
Senior.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
Just go straight down this road.
You hear me?
Don't turn.
That's what my brother should do.
I'm telling you.
It's absolutely right
that I just grabbed you.
Are you walking the right way?
You're very strong.
You are good.
What are you doing?
You want to win Zixin
from Lu Xun.
I'm telling you.
Don't look at him like that.
He looks weak.
But I've seen his skill.
He's great.
You may not be able to defeat him.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry!
Don't fall behind.
Can you remind me of the steps?
Why it's you?
Why me?
Do you mean to ask me that?
I've always been the one you're holding.
The person you touch
is me, too!
Well.
Except for good looking
and this weak body,
anything else to add?
Sorry…
But what about the others?
A sorry
to send me away?
Others should
take other exits.
If something goes wrong again,
I'll really lose this time.
What lose?
What are you talking about?
I'm in charge of this activity.
That is,
if there is an accident,
the responsibility lies with me.
Let's meet others.
Wait.
Who just held me tight?
Now you want to run away?
What do you want then?
Win a present for me,
as a sealing fee.
Sure enough, this is a familiar scene.
Very familiar.
(Legal Methods and Modern Civil Law)
If I remember correctly,
Lu Xun will ask for the book
next.
See.
That book is out of print.
(Legal Methods and Modern Civil Law)
I want that one.
No.
You're almost tried
more than 200 times.
You couldn't get that book.
Just go.
The shopkeeper will close the stall.
It is easy for you to say.
You get one for me.
Come on. Go ahead.
I can't defeat you on learning.
I could defeat you on playing.
A little slanting.
You can't cover it like that.
You breathe.
I've asked that
it will take two hours
for an ambulance coming
from the nearest hospital nearby.
Why didn't you say it earlier
that you're allergic to dog hair?
Go. Go. Go.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Where to?
Go.
Come on, let me help you.
Because of that allergy,
Lu Xun missed the best opportunity
for confession in the sodality.
Qian Chuan took the lead.
In order to make amends,
I spent a lot of money
to buy that out-of-print book
and gave it to Lu Xun.
The last one. You do it.
I can't.
I'm so unlucky.
You play it.
Can you?
This is the last one.
The probability of two people doing
may be a little higher.
I've just tried so many times.
The probability is on you.
What if you got one
directly?
Come on. Come on.
Your turn.
It's like you can get it.
What's your luck?
You can even get that one!
Hit the jackpot.
Handsome man, congratulations!
Don't bring it.
Just put it here. Just put it here.
Just put it here.
It makes no difference for you couple.
No hurry.
He's allergic to dog hair.
Therefore…
How do you know
I'm allergic to dog hair?
I dreamed of it.
I am a prophet.
Dream of it?
What else did you dream about?
It doesn't matter what I dream about.
Just stay away from it.
Can we deposit it here?
Fine.
Come with me.
Why don't you
row the Ferris wheel first?
I'll come as soon as I've solved it.
Bye.
She knows me.
If you really want it,
I'll give you this number.
Come on.
You think you're lying to
an 18-year-old girl?
I know what's the price of this book
in my heart.
Two hundred and fifty yuan.
Give it to me if you want.
If you don't want to. Then forget it.
It cost me 250 yuan at that time.
I know
your reserve price quite a lot.
Sure.
Since you like it so much,
you have a connection with this book.
Then I'll give up my love.
You've had a long day.
Please help me to send the little dog
to the home stay on the mountain.
I got it. Don't worry.
Still not high enough.
I can't see it.
It's a pity for that book.
I guess it's hard to buy it
anywhere else.
Stop nagging about it.
You stole it?
Can you talk nicely?
I'm telling you.
I've been bargaining with him
for a long time.
It cost price
worthy of you.
Cherish it.
My price?
What price is worthy of me?
250?
You said it yourself.
I am not saying that.
But this price…
This price…
I bargained it myself.
He asked me for 500 yuan.
Price bargaining is my skill.
So this book
and the money for the cherry.
Let's wipe them out.
You're good at counting.
Why don't you major in accounting?
Why don't you change your career?
You must be particularly excellent
in the future.
Get out of the way. Get out of the way.