(Twenty years old, Early summer)
- Gosh.
- Look at that.
Gosh, look at that!
Surprisingly enough,
my first love...
is among these three people.
(Light on Me)
(2 years ago)
- Hello.
Hi, Tae-Gyeong.
You're Woo Tae-Gyeong
from Grade 11 Class 1, right?
I'm your homeroom teacher, Seo Haet-Bit.
Let's get along.
Oh, okay.
That's how kids are like these days.
They hate adults, and they avoid them.
I see.
But he's quite strange.
Kids these days
would say he's a voluntary outsider.
He's notorious among the students.
I was worried about him,
so I talked to him once,
but he said he doesn't need friends...
or my help.
He then said goodbye and left.
So don't get hurt.
It hurts me if you do.
Okay?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hey.
"I don't need friends." What a joke.
Hey. He can hear you. Stop.
Do you have something to say to me?
Right... Well... So the thing is...
If you do, can you say it louder?
I can't hear you.
No.
I don't have anything to say.
If you don't, speak softly.
Hey. I'm sorry.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
My friend likes to joke around.
Why...
are you apologizing on his behalf?
Because he's my friend, you punk.
That's why you don't have friends.
Stop it. Let's go. Come on.
"Friends"?
Hey.
Here. You dropped your wallet.
Thank you.
We're in the same class again.
I'm sorry,
but I've never seen you before.
What?
- Hey. What are you doing?
- Hey.
Did you write a review of a concert?
No. I was going to copy yours.
Gosh, want to die?
A review of a concert?
Yes. The one we had to do over break.
Isn't that too much?
How could they give us homework during
break? Are we in elementary school?
I...
I didn't hear about that assignment.
What? I announced it in our group chat.
Oh, I see. You're not in the group chat.
You weren't invited to it.
I see.
I'll invite you.
Let's go.
Can you show me your review?
There comes a day...
when the street you walk on every day...
seems different from usual.
Am I okay like this?
Excuse me.
Is this seat taken?
No, it's not.
Okay.
Enjoy your lunch.
- Don't worry about it.
- I can do it. I can eat it all.
- No, wait. Hey.
- Let me show you how much I can eat.
Hey. I'm telling you.
- Give me some.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
A day when
familiar things seem unfamiliar.
Am I okay like this?
Tae-Gyeong, you don't like beans either?
It's not that I don't like them,
I don't eat them.
I didn't eat them since I was young too.
My parents didn't say anything
about being a picky eater.
But one day,
I really wanted to try them.
So I got a spoonful and tried it.
What do you think it was like?
It has to be good...
so that you learn the lesson that
you shouldn't be a picky eater.
No.
It wasn't good.
But it was better than
I thought it would be.
I thought it would be disgusting.
So the lesson of this story...
isn't don't be a picky eater.
It's just try it.
It's better than you'd expect.
Think about something you'd never do,
and just try it.
Regardless of what it is.
You never know.
Something fun might happen.
Something I would never do...
(Woo Jae-Gyeong, Mom, Dad,
Mr. Seo Haet-Bit)
(Chats)
(You've been invited to the chat.)
(Saebit Boys High School
Grade 11, Class 1)
(Add friend)
Hey. You dropped this.
You dropped this!
My gosh.
I'm really sorry. Are you okay?
I think poked you a bit hard.
What are you talking about?
It didn't even touch me.
No. I'm pretty sure I did.
It must've hurt a lot. Let me see.
Don't touch me.
What? I'm sorry.
Your ears are really red.
It must've hurt a lot.
Just leave. Please.
Hey. I'll carry this for you
since you're in pain.
I'm not in any pain.
Also,
watch where you're going.
Right.
It's better to be alone than
become friends with someone like him.
Pass!
Watch out!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Luckily, I'm not bleeding.
Did you get hurt?
You must've been surprised.
Excuse me.
You're lucky he didn't get hurt.
What if he did?
It's dangerous to play in the hall.
I'll take the ball.
- Da-On.
- Can't you let it slide?
Just avoid playing in the hall.
Here.
Be sure to apologize to your friend.
I'll see you around, Woo Tae-Gyeong.
Thank you.
Hey. I'm sorry.
We should've been more careful.
It's okay.
Gosh, our school president is so cool.
I want to get close to him.
I heard he does people favors
all the time. He's very generous.
Nobody has ever seen him get mad.
I should've applied
to join the student council too.
Hey, let's go.
I'm sorry.
A friend like that could be nice.
Please help me.
I've never had friends.
So I was thinking about
doing something...
I've never done before.
But I don't know how to start.
That's why I came to see you.
What is it?
What?
No, it's nothing.
So you want to make friends?
Yes.
Let's see.
Then Tae-Gyeong,
do you want to join the student council?
"Student council"?
Ever since Mr. Kim went on leave
last year, I've been in charge of it.
I think you'd be a perfect fit.
Then will I become a member
of the student council right away?
Well... If the kids agree.
I'm sure they'll like the idea.
They're all great kids.
There are a total of 20 members,
but there are only three people
that you need to remember.
You know the president,
12th grader, Sin Da-On, right?
He's always smiling, caring,
and take good care of people.
That's why he's really popular.
- What should we do?
- Da-On, can I borrow your gym suit?
Oh, it's in my locker.
Okay, thank you.
If you spend time with him,
you'll end up liking him too.
Oh, right. I'll give you the notes
you asked for last time.
As expected.
- You're the best, Da-On.
- Hey. Want to go to the store?
Next is the head of volunteer work,
11th grader, Namgung Si-Un.
Move over. Move.
How dare you get in the way of
the school president?
Mr. President. Let's go.
He's really sociable and funny,
so it'll be easy to become friends.
- Want some ramyeon?
- Hey. Come on.
He knows everything that goes on
at school,
so he can answer all your questions.
Lastly,
there's an incredible person
who controls those two.
He's the vice president,
11th grader, Noh Shin-Woo.
"Noh Shin-Woo"?
We still have some time.
I don't think anyone is in,
so let's just look around
the student council room.
What? You...
Do you know each other?
- Hello, sir.
-  Mr. Seo.
Who are you with?
You're Woo Tae-Gyeong, right?
I'm against it.
I knew it.
Why did you stall to say that?
I was thinking it over carefully.
Are you sure you did?
Forget it. You know it's over
when he acts like this.
He's quite stubborn, you know.
Forget it.
We're done, right?
I'm leaving.
- Hold on, kids.
- What's your reason?
Everyone else is okay with it,
so why are you the only one
who is against it?
There are so many reasons that
I don't feel like saying.
- Do you want me to tell you everything?
- Yes.
Don't leave anything out.
- Why must I do that?
- Gosh, Shin-Woo.
Tae-Gyeong, are you in Grade 11?
Yes, I am.
I see. You're the same age as Shin-Woo.
After school, we should all...
Da-On, don't try to
let it go like that again.
There's no reason for us
to spend time with him.
You should leave now.
Tae-Gyeong.
In the student council,
everyone needs to agree to decide on
something, so please be understanding.
I'll talk with Shin-Woo.
Tae-Gyeong.
Do you want to wait in your classroom?
Namgung. Go with him.
Da-On. How can you tell him
to go to his classroom right now?
When you get rejected like this,
you should have ramyeon at the store.
Let's go, Tae-Gyeong.
I'll relieve you of your stress.
I'm not going to leave...
until you tell me
why you're against me joining.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
First, the period to join
the student council is over.
The official period set by the school
was a week and half ago,
and if you wanted to join,
you should've joined then.
You should've applied and joined
fair and square.
What? I never applied.
Da-On just asked me to become
the head of volunteer work.
What is it? Was this a secret?
Namgung was famous since before
he came to school.
He knows a lot of people
and a lot of things.
It's important that the student council
is well-informed.
In other words,
I scouted him as the president.
So if you think about it,
our newest member...
was scouted by Mr. Seo,
so he can join.
Second,
we're at full capacity.
The maximum number of members
for student council is 20.
If that's the issue,
I think it will be okay.
I saw how much difficulty
you had last year,
I thought of increasing the number of
members for the next semester.
That's right, Shin-Woo.
Why are you nitpicking at everything?
Are you a nitpicker?
Student council is not a market.
You want to skip process
and add new people.
If anyone can join,
how is it the student council?
"Anyone"?
In any case, I'm against it.
- I don't want him to join.
- Shin-Woo, why are you being like this?
Tae-Gyeong must feel uncomfortable.
Right. Why do you keep opposing?
"I'm against it."
"I'm a Post-it." "I'm a Fitbit."
- What are you doing?
- "What are you doing?"
- My gosh.
- Gosh. Mr. Seo.
Hold on, guys.
I understand what you mean.
Let's pretend this never happened.
Hey, hold on.
I don't want to join either.
I don't like people...
who don't like me.
(Light on Me)
Even though Shin-Woo talks like that,
he's not a bad kid.
- I don't care to be friends with him.
- Why don't you like him?
You could tell he'll be tiresome
and sensitive.
Shin-Woo is a good kid.
He's considerate too.
Life is like that. Nothing comes easy.
I really hate you.
(Light on Me)