♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 13
Zhu Zan's sworn brother Li Sanbing
Jiuling Drugstore
Opened by Jiuling
The plaque is previous as Jiuling will take it all the time
Minister of the Supreme Court  Tan Song
Assistant Minister of the Ministry of War Han Feng
Ning Mansion
Tomb of Beloved Wife Princess Jiuling
By Husband Lu Yunqi
Prison
Jiuling Drugstore
Mansion of Prince Huai
Jiurong's Teacher Gu Qing
Lord Cheng's Mansion
Zhou Mansion
Li Mansion
Ning Mansion
Lu Mansion
Your Ladyship,
you're back.
I woke you up?
Where did you go last night?
I was worried about you.
Didn't I tell you?
I went to meet an old friend.
I forgot it.
It's great as you're back.
Are you hungry?
I'll prepare some food for you.
Let's dine out later.
OK.
A restaurant next to us
makes delicious Runan dishes.
How about having a try there?
Besides, I want dried tofu in chicken sauce,
OK?
Sure, if you like it.
After the meal,
I want to see the shop.
OK.
I'll help you wash up.
Why did you resist?
You were right out of the capital city.
Why did you go back?
Your Majesty,
I heard that
a group of bandits from the North
robbed the people of their possession.
That day I heard by accident
from the conversation
of several passers-by that
the bandits showed up in suburbs of the capital city.
I didn't want
to miss the chance.
To find it out,
I left the man I guarded
and tailed after the bandits.
Later I eliminated them.
You were in the North,
but you got the news about suburbs of the capital city.
Both you and your father are great.
Though you were in the North,
you cared about the capital city so much.
Sanbing,
what shall we do now?
I know why Zan asked me in the letter
to eliminate
all bandits on the run
on Mount Yang.
He expected that
he'd be inquired today.
It's a double gain plan.
It helps him get out
and eliminate the  bandits.
However, it may be
seen through by the suspicious emperor.
It isn't a time to celebrate.
Wait and see
if Zan can make it.
I think he can make it.
Your Majesty,
my father knows nothing.
I planned to capture their leader secretly,
so I noticed news
about them in suburbs of the capital city.
However,
fearing that it would bother you,
I decided to
eliminate them on my own.
Back then,
why didn't you chase them
with those from Arm Moral Department,
so as to capture all of them?
Your Majesty,
if I had gone with  those from Arm Moral Department,
the bandits would have
escaped seeing the suits.
Fine.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
Ask
Tan Song of the Supreme Court,
Han Feng
of the Ministry of War
and Lu Yunqi
for the joint trial of three departments.
Explain to them
whatever it is.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Ladyship,
this is an old shop.
Yes.
However,
it's in a good location.
But it's near the palace.
Those living around are high officials and noble lords.
If they are ill,
they'll turn to the Imperial Academy of Medicine
instead of Jiuling Drugstore.
I think
it's better to open in the downtown area
with many people like that in Runan.
It's difficult to live in the capital city.
It requires more than
curing several patients
to keep a foothold here.
We should get to know high-ranking officials.
Let's go
to have a look in the firm.
Go.
Leave it to Deshengchang.
Don't worry.
OK.
See you. Bye.
Shopkeeper Liu,
Miss Jun is here.
Miss Jun,
finally you're here.
I'm Shopkeeper Liu
of Deshengchang in the capital city.
Young Master said in the letter that
you would be here a few days ago.
However,
you didn't show up.
I didn't know
where to find you
and worried
if anything went wrong on the way.
It's thoughtless of me
to worry you.
We spent a few days visiting
the capital city before coming here.
Young Master sent something to you.
Please check it.
We can buy anything here.
Why bother?
Jiuling Drugstore.
It,
it...
Young Master is prophetic.
Your Ladyship,
while you just select the shop,
he has sent the plaque here in advance.
And the characters
are painted with gold again.
Did you
tell him in advance
you would open Jiuling Drugstore?
I made the decision on the way.
I didn't tell the Fang family.
Young Master is so clever.
Besides,
he is considerate.
Your Ladyship,
a letter from Young Master.
you've selected a shop?
Yes.
It'll be opened on the 18th day of this month.
You're awesome.
The 18th day?
So there are only
5 days left?
I'm afraid there isn't enough time
to make a good preparation.
Never mind.
We only need to
clean the house,
hang the plaque
and set a desk.
You shouldn't open quietly
the drugstore.
Though you're
a famous doctor
in Runan and Zezhou,
if you don't
make it grand
to let more people
know you in the capital city
with famous doctors everywhere,
I fear that
you even can't
get a chance to amaze others.
Your Ladyship,
it's difficult to live
in the capital city.
Yeah,
that's true.
But it's difficult to do everything.
Don't worry, Shopkeeper Liu.
I know what to do.
Just do as I said.
Your Lordship,
it's
the joint trial of three departments.
Be serious.
Ministers,
let's begin.
Let's start from Map of Capital City.
It's the reason
why His Majesty
summoned you back.
Your Highness,
tell us
whether you did it or not.
I'd like to remind you.
We've got human testimony and material evidence.
You can't deny it.
I'm not denying.
I did it.
Do you know what crime you committed?
No.
Let me tell you.
By abusing your power
and using military strength,
you ordered post soldiers to sell the map of capital city.
Don't shift the blame on me.
The people need the map to get to the capital city.
Post soldiers along the way
can sell it to make money
and improve the posts.
You don't believe that?
Ask the Ministry of War
if they've saved
a lot of money.
Yes.
It did ease our funding.
Most obviously,
the post horses are much better.
If Lord Lu doesn't believe it,
check the account book.
Does it make sense
whether your account book is true or not?
What do you mean?
You mean we make false account?
Aren't you
questioning me today?
Lord Tan,
say something.
Ministers,
we're colleagues.
Calm down.
Be friendly.
Go ahead.
All people
can buy the map
as long as they have money.
The map has spread to Beiqi.
It's too dangerous.
Your Lordship,
as a general protecting the country,
don't you know
what it means?
Your Excellency,
just because I'm a general,
I know
what to do
and what not to do.
Everything in this map
is about dining and entertaining.
It doesn't involve the city defense,
the government offices and the imperial city at all.
Without precise measurement,
Beiqi people can't
use it to do anything.
But it's the map of the capital city.
As the enemies get it...
Yes.
On the map is
the prosperity and richness of the capital city.
Beiqi people
will covet it
so much
that they may
be driven crazy.
So
you provide them
with the map.
See?
In every state dogs bite.
When seeing great things,
you always want to
rob it.
Your Lordship,
now that you know
it's so attractive to Beiqi people,
why did you...
So what?
I want Beiqi people
and the rest of the world
to know how prosperous Tianyou is.
Many people
in the North
get no chance to visit the capital city this life.
It's impossible for them to come here.
Only through this map
can they see how prosperous
the capital city
of Tianyou, the state they protect, is.
The prosperity is
shared by the people
and makes their
fighting on the front line
meaningful.
How can we bear
to let it be invaded?
We'll never
let that happen.
Your Excellencies,
if you think
this map makes
Beiqi army go south,
what do you think of
the generals and  soldiers stationed on the front line,
the Ministry of War of Tianyou
and the authority of His Majesty?
If Beiqi people want to come,
let them come.
If they dare to come,
they'll be eliminated.
Eliminated.
Later,
Lord Tan said the case shall
be submitted to Your Majesty for judgment.
Both Lord Lu and Lord Han agreed.
As to Map of Capital City,
have they found it out?
Lord Zhu did it wrong
in this regard.
Those of the Department of City Defense checked it.
But this matter
can be serious or trivial.
Your Majesty,
even if you don't convict him,
you can't let him go.
As Lord Cheng has achieved gradually in the North,
keeping his son in the capital city
can check
the duke.
I didn't expect
the joint trial of three departments
would end like this.
This is the end of the matter?
It doesn't end completely.
This is fine.
One is merciless
and the other is  arrogant.
Just let His Lordship and Governor Lu of Arm Moral Department
check each other in the capital city.
If Zhu Zan
stays in the capital city,
it'll be troublesome.
Yunzhao,
whatever happens  in the capital city
has nothing to do with you.
Your top priority
is to study
and to prepare for the exam.
I got it,
uncle.
Master.
Aunt.
Master,
this is the gift list
I drew up
for Commander Lu's wedding.
Check it
to see if it is proper.
Uncle,
aunt,
I'll go back to my room.
Why is he
so strange
these days?
Perhaps study makes him tired.
Don't worry.
Remove some more.
We don't have much
connection with Lu Yunqi.
OK.
Miss Jun,
a guest wants to meet you.
are you there?
Coming.
Childe Ning.
Miss Jun.
How did you find me?
You told me in the daytime
you stay in an inn not far from the city gate,
so I asked inns around
one by one.
Is there any urgent matter?
Yes.
Well.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
Sit down.
OK.
Miss Jun,
I heard that
your clinic in Runan was called Jiuling Drugstore.
Will the new clinic opened in the capital city
use the same name?
You know all things.
Yes.
Miss Jun,
there is something wrong with the name.
It's the name of the late Princess Jiuling.
The name Jiuling Drugstore is from my father.
It has nothing to do with the princess.
So I think
the government won't punish me for that.
Miss Jun,
Princess Jiuling
was the late wife of Commander Lu of Arm Moral Department.
Commander Lu is odd
and unpredictable.
It's fine for you to open Jiuling Drugstore in Runan,
but you're in the capital city now.
What's more,
the opening day
is the wedding day of Commander Lu.
It may cause trouble.
Miss Jun,
change the name.
You mean
Lu Yunqi may purposely make difficulties for me.
Yes.
If so,
Jiuling Drugstore
will be known to more people.
Miss Jun,
but...
Childe Ning,
I know you meant well to remind me,
But I've made up my mind.
In this case,
I will not persuade you any more
Perhaps I think too much.
It's difficult to live in the capital city,
so it'll better to be prudent.
It's difficult to live in the capital city.
I've heard it for  times
since I have been here.
It may not be easy at first,
but you'll find a way
to make it easy.
It's late.
I'm leaving.
Thank you for your reminder.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Jiuling Drugstore is opened today.
Yes. She is coming out.
She is beautiful.
♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything♫
♫and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
♫Despite the rumors, I firmly believe you.♫
♫When I meet you again, I fall in love for you.♫
♫This kiss is our promise to be together forever, in life or death.♫
♫When you call me again, my loneliness is cured.♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything♫
♫and wait for the morning♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything♫
♫and wait for the morning♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything♫
♫and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Sister,
it's me.
I'm Jiuling, sister.
Sister.
Your Highness.
Sister, come back.
Sister, don't go.
Jiurong.
Your Highness. Sister.
Your Highness.
Sister.
Sister Jiuli, come back.
Your Highness.
Jiuli
and Jiuling left.
They abandoned me.
Sister, come back.
Your Highness.
Sister.
My Jiurong.
I'll go to my sister.
I'll avenge faster
and faster.
Wait for me.
Come back.
Jiurong.
Your Highness. Sister.
Her Highness will come back to see you.
The wind is strong outside.
You may catch cold.
Let's
go back.
-Sister. -Your Highness.
Go back, Your Highness.
Why are you in the capital city?
Because of...
...you.
Nonsense.
You left Zezhou without telling me
to get here
before Jiuli gets married,
right?
And in the crowd,
only you looked at Jiuling with different feelings.
You even cried
when seeing Jiurong.
How do you
explain all this?
Just for this?
I remember I told you,
Princess Jiuling and I were sisters,
so her family members are my close relatives.
Seeing Jiuli get married today,
I can't help being excited.
Moreover,
seeing Jiurong
so lonely at the gate,
I felt emotional.
Is it hard to understand?
How do you explain meeting with Yuan Bao?
He is an imperial eunuch.
Ordinary people can't see him.
And he disguised himself.
How did you recognize him?
I forgot to tell you that.
I met him when I went for
a banquet in the palace with my father.
Any more questions?
I feel that
you hide many things from me.
People often say our eyes betray us.
I want to see
if that's true.
Naive.
Jiuling Drugstore will be opened today.
I am busy.
Childish.
Zan,
though Jiuling Drugstore has been opened,
the door is closed.
It's strange.
She may do
anything expected.
Those around her drugstore
are royal relatives and nobles.
None will turn to her for a treatment.
She didn't come here
for business.
And her
drugstore shares the same name
with the princess.
If she is targeted,
it'll be troublesome.
I think she is asking for troubles.
She wants others to know the drugstore.
I'll keep an eye on Jiuling Drugstore.
I said nothing.
I think she came here
to avenge her father.
Hurry up.
Jiuling Drugstore.
Your Ladyship,
we've walked
on this street for 3 times.
Can we go to another street?
Are you tired?
Let's take
a break ahead.
OK.
Mrs. Zhou and relatives
of Marquis of Dingyuan are friends.
If I can cure his relatives,
I'll get a chance
to get chose to him
to find out about Jiurong and Jiuli.
Sister,
do you sell candies?
No,
but
if you want candies,
I have candies.
Great.
I want candies.
Liu'er.
I want. It's yummy.
Well.
One for each.
OK.
These are for you.
Well, be careful.  Be careful.
Be careful. Be careful.
One for each.
Be careful. All are for you.
Be careful. Be careful.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Be careful.
Does it taste good?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Mother.
Bao'er, come here. Look, candy.
Kids, come here.
What's this in your hand?
Throw it away.
What are you doing?
These are preserves
specially made by Jiuling Drugstore.
They are precious.
I've never heard of
such a drugstore.
You frauds.
Throw it away.
Don't eat it.
Excuse me.
We're hand-bell doctors.
Look.
I can't read.
Look at you two.
You're pretty.
Take a decent job.
Don't cheat others.
Let's go.
Well.
Listen.
Neither talk to strangers like them
nor take their things,
or
you may be hurt.
OK.
Throw it away.
Go. Go.
Go home. Go.
She goes too far.
Don't be fooled
by others easily.
Yes.
Your Ladyship,
instead of treating patients in the drugstore,
you work as a hand-bell doctor.
It's tiring and annoying.
It doesn't matter.
It takes a process.
Go.
Ding.
Young Master.
Have you sent my gift?
It was sent early in the morning.
Young Master,
you've told me many times.
I won't forget it.
Go.
Let's have a look
and congratulate her in person.
Young Master,
you've been caring
much about Miss Jun.
Your engagement
was broken off.
It's improper
to go there, right?
Can't we be friends as the engagement was broken off?
We were engaged out of our parents'  will
instead of that of our own.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go.
Young Master,
it's here.
Hot steamed buns.
Yes,
it's here.
It was open when I sent
gift here this morning.
Why is it closed now?
Steamed buns.
Sir,
excuse me.
Isn't Jiuling Drugstore
just opened today?
Why is it closed?
I feel puzzled, too.
After all these years in business,
it's the first time I've seen that
a store is closed
on its first day of opening.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Young Master,
what shall we do?
Shall
we wait?
Forget it.
She must have her own reasons
for closing it.
Let's come another day.
Hot steamed buns.
Highly skilled doctor
of Jiuling Drugstore
can work miracles
and cure
all kinds of complicated diseases.
Highly skilled doctor
of Jiuling Drugstore
can work miracles…
Your Ladyship,
though I try hard,
no one turns to us for help.
I'm starving.
I've seen that
you're hungry.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Tell me
what you want to eat.
Meat.
Meat?
I know a restaurant offering tasty meat.
Where is it?
Is it far away?
It's just ahead.
Let's yell and go.
Highly skilled doctor
of Jiuling Drugstore
can work miracles…
Jiuling.
Lord Lu,
I'm Jiuli.
Your Highness.
She never drank.
Your Ladyship,
I didn't expect that you can drink a lot.
You may not believe it,
actually
this is the first time
I drink.
Then don't drink so fast,
or,
or you'll be drunk.
Well.
Cheers.
You,
you drink so much.
Is there anything upsetting you?
I'm upset.
What upset you?
I can't protect those
who are the most important to me.
I'm useless.
Your Ladyship.
Your,
Your Ladyship, what did you say?
I didn't hear clearly.
Nothing.
We have drunk it all.
Liu'er, buy
more liquor for me.
I can't leave you along here.
Waiter, a jug of liquor.
Coming. Don't worry.
I'll
roast this meat
for you
and
wait for you
to eat.
It's hot. Don't get hurt.
I promise,
when you come back,
all meat will be ready.
The meat is not important.
Be careful not to get hurt.
Can you stay here alone?
Relax. Just go.
I'll be back soon. Don't worry.
Wait for me.
OK.
Go.
Wait for me here.
Sir, see you.
Your Highness,
rest early.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫