It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Granny! Get a grip!
Don't you dare die, you old hag!
You're going to make Marie sad if you die!
I wouldn't like it very much, either!
T-Take care of the children for me...
In any battlefield... the victims
were... always the weak.
It was always the innocent children.
It's because I wanted to protect the children
that I left the battlefield
and became a sister.
Granny!
What are you talking about?
All of you were born sinners.
What?!
You poor thing... Sally, look at
how much they've hurt you.
Master Licht...
Rest, my child.
Valtos.
Yes, sir.
See you later, Asta.
You belong to me.
I never want to see her again!
Forgive me, my lord. All this
because I let her go alone...
I never imagined all of this would happen.
There's no need for you to feel responsible.
I'm sure they used some underhanded methods.
Who are you calling underhanded?!
Look at what you did to all
those innocent children!
She mentioned earlier that the victims
on the battlefield are always the weak.
That is incorrect.
The victims are the strong.
Envied, feared, discriminated
against, persecuted, and...
stolen from.
What is he talking about?
That is why we will not
forgive the Clover Kingdom.
This time, we will destroy you
and create our own kingdom.
What the hell are you even talking about?!
You're the ones who attacked first, you jerk!
Shut your filthy mouth.
You're an eyesore.
Why does someone like you have that grimoire?
Grimoire?
Damn it... I can't see his attacks at all!
They hit me straight-on
at an incredible speed!
What do I...
This is the only way.
If I use my sword as a shield and charge
at him, I can avoid a fatal injury!
I'm not done yet!
That won't work.
I'll be taking that grimoire back.
I'm gonna...
di—
Seriously?
Captain Yami! What are you doing here?
Why am I here? Well, obviously...
I'm a little lost. Give me
some directions, damn it.
Light Magic vs. Dark Magic
Captain, you were lost?!
Of course not, you moron.
I was joking, dumbass.
What?!
We're Magic Knights. Of course
we're going to show up.
Everyone back at the base was useless,
so I decided to come myself.
I'll kill them all later.
What the heck are they doing when
we're in this much trouble?!
He dragged me out of bed,
and now we're in this mess!
By the way, didn't I tell
you to take the day off?
Want me to give you a permanent vacation?
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
So, what's his deal?
Apparently he's the leader of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Th-The Eye of the Midnight Sun?!
Oh?
I thought he'd be some big, burly guy
who could eat a cow in a single gulp,
but he's just a scrawny-ass beanpole.
Um, I'm pretty sure muscles
don't really matter.
What's with that guy's creepy,
infinite amount of magic?!
Not to mention, he uses light magic?
That's a super rare magic
that only a few people
throughout the history of the
Clover Kingdom have ever used!
Without a doubt, he's super
dangerous! I wanna go home!
That's the Black Bulls' captain.
Shall I summon the Third Eye?
There's no need.
I've always wanted to fight him,
since he uses dark magic.
Finral, please get the kids and
everyone else back to town.
Sure, leave it to me!
What are you going to do?
I can still fight!
I finally get a chance to see Captain Yami
in action! There's no way I'm leaving!
Gauche and, uh... you there! Can you walk?
More importantly, get to
the old hag! Hurry up!
Got it!
I've been around longer than you, y'know...
All right, Yami. I'm leaving the rest to you.
Hey. You better come back.
Gulp...
I was planning to just
stay out of harm's way.
You know, I think I'm running low on magic...
Like, for real!
What do you mean? I'm for real, too.
Of course you are...
Huh?
The hell do you think
you're doing to my ride?
Ride?!
Yeesh! I don't have enough
lives to stick around here!
Well, see you, Yami!
You better come back, damn it!
So cool! How'd you stop that?
What's up with that sword?!
Shut up, brat.
This is a weapon called a "katana"
from my homeland, the Land of the Sun.
And that was—
Like I have time to explain all this
right now. Besides, it's a pain.
Just watch!
Light Magic: Light Swords of Conviction.
Awesome!
He's boosting his physical abilities
with reinforcing magic
and cutting my light magic with
a sword cloaked in dark magic.
But that's not all.
How about this, then?
So this is the power of the
great Magic Knight heretic.
Huh?
Hey, have I met you somewhere before?
I'm pretty sure I don't know
anyone who uses light magic.
Who the hell are you?
And what's so fun about all of this?
Let me tell you a fable.
Long ago, in a certain village, there lived
a people with very strong magic.
They were loved by mana.
They changed the weather
and manipulated ley lines.
They had power to rival the gods.
The humans from outside the
village worshipped them as such.
However, gradually, the humans
grew to fear their power.
They envied it and wanted it.
They tricked them, massacred them,
and stole their powers.
What kind of story was that?
What's that got to do with you?
Planning to become a bard or something?
All right, I've got a little story, too.
In a certain place,
there was a pure young man.
His folks were fishermen, and they started
sending him out to fish from a young age.
And then he got shipwrecked...
Augh!
Seriously?
...and washed ashore in a strange country.
Who the hell is this?
He's wearing grass sandals.
You can't be serious!
Since his race and culture were different,
he went through some nasty stuff there.
But...
He kicked all their asses and
became the boss of a group.
The end!
Well? What'd you think of my response fable?
Well, it's half of my life, actually.
You bastard! You dare mock Master Licht?!
Shut up! Your face is scary!
Why are there lines on your face?!
You're bringing that up now?!
He got faster.
As a foreigner, I suppose my
story had nothing to do with you.
Would you mind stepping off the stage, then?
Captain Yami!
I wonder how long you can
avoid a fatal blow?
Are you the guy who took out Fuegoleon?
I am.
Although I laid my plans carefully
and had him walk into a trap.
Yeah, I figured.
You'd never take down that King
of Hardnoses with stuff like this.
Dark Magic:
Dark Cloaked
Lightless Slash!
Master Licht!
A-Amazing... He's so frickin' cool!
Trap, eh? I'm sure you wouldn't
have been able to win
without doing something underhanded.
How dare you?!
This time, come right at me.
I'll show you the true power
of a Magic Knight Captain!
Hey, brat. Were you watching that?
Y-Yes, sir!
Good. Now try the same thing.
Yes, sir!
Wait... Like I could actually do that!
Of course I can't!
Oh? Who do you think you're talking to?
Huh?
I told you to do it, so do it.
Ow, ow, ow, that really hurts! Ow, ow, ow!
That'll make you a bigger man.
Not only did he manage to stop
all of Master Licht's attacks,
he even managed to counter.
The Black Bulls' captain...
Does his strength actually
rival the Wizard King's?!
I see... So this is dark magic.
Light Recovery Magic:
Healing Light Particles.
He can use recovery magic, too?
I haven't seen it in person much,
but apparently, guys loved by
mana can use all sorts of magic.
It's especially rare for an
attack-type to also be able to heal.
Anyway, get ready.
He was actually serious!
No, really! I can't!
Not in the middle of fighting!
Not to mention, I don't have any magic!
I don't mean the last attack I did.
I'm saying do the thing before that, idiot.
And I can't block attacks that I can't see!
You're hopeless.
I'll explain it just this once.
You'll have to pay me 500 yuls later.
He's charging?!
The reason I've been able
to react to the attacks
is because of something called "ki"
from back in my homeland.
Ki? Not mana?
Yeah.
Ki
People looking at you,
the sound of their breathing,
their smell, the motions of their muscles,
the vague sense that they're there...
Ki is the blanket term for all of the
different types of life energy
the human body emits.
I read that ki and predicted
his next move, then made mine.
You've done that before, haven't you?
Come to think of it...
When I do it, I combine it with
magic and muscle, and fight that way.
I guess it's like being a magic
swordsman or something.
Muscles! So that's why your neck's
so thick, Captain Yami!
Like you can talk, kid.
He has the nerve to converse during a battle.
The insolence...
He's just full of surprises.
To think he could keep up
with this speed, as well.
I cannot allow him to trouble
you any further, Master Licht.
I know this is impertinent of me,
but would you allow me to assist you?
Thank you, Valtos. You're always so helpful.
In that case, that boy...
Would you capture him?
You may injure him slightly if need be.
An easy task.
Huh?
That was close!
Perfect timing. Practice on that
scrawny dude with the slanty eyes.
Huh?! On the scrawny dude
with the slanty eyes?
That's too sudden! Of course I can't!
Where I come from, we've got this saying...
"A warrior never goes back on his word."
You said you were going to
become the Wizard King, didn't you?
Surpass your limits. Right here, right now.
There's no other way.
Yes, sir!
I don't get it at all, but...
For starters, concentrate... Concentrate!
Someone with no magic like you
could never stop my attacks.
You're there!
I didn't stop all of it.
Wrong.
You can't fool me, kid.
You just reacted to your ears that time.
That ain't ki.
Use all five senses, and sense it
with your whole body, you moron!
With my whole body?
Yeah. You can't just rely
on your ears or your eyes.
Visualize something halfway between
instinct and a prediction.
If you don't do it right, I'll kill you!
That's insane.
But I think I kinda get it.
Not just my ears, not just my eyes...
Then... I'm just going to reset everything.
Concentrate...
You're there!
Wha—
I did it!
I did it, Captain Yami!
Wow, you actually managed to do it?
Talk about creepy, you weirdo.
What?!
Valtos...
How dare you... harm Valtos?!
I cannot allow people like
you to harm my comrades
ever again!
What's your deal? You're the
ones who started this!
The path this spell traces
resembles the motions of a whip.
Can you predict its movements?
It's said that whips were used to
punish criminals, once upon a time.
That makes it a perfect fit for you two!
Light Creation Magic: Light Whip of Judgment!
It's useless to struggle!
The cave!
That nutcase has gone ballistic!
Oh, dear... I held back most of my magic,
but it's all really too fragile...
Both this world and you fools.
You're amazing, Master Licht!
Your strength is practically divine!
If you felt like it, Master Licht, the Magic
Knights would be no more than infants!
What?!
The leader of the Eye of the
Midnight Sun... Licht, was it?
Talk about a huge forehead.
I guess you'd expect that
from a light magic user.
Black Clover, Page 35:
"The Light of Judgment."
Page 35
The Light of Judgment
Going beyond my limits is my magic!