It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
He's so strong...
What the hell was that magic?
So, how would you like to die?
P-Please spare us! We'll never
attack the village again!
I won't kill you this time.
Huh?
Because today is...
Marie's birthday.
Huh?
Come on. Celebrate Marie's birthday with me.
Who the heck is that?!
Rejoice greatly, rejoice
with all your might,
and then die.
I'm going to die anyway?!
The Mirror Mage
Village in the Boonies: Hage
Father!
They sent money again this month.
Great!
Are they doing well?
We'll be able to eat lots of tatoes again.
Yay!
Wizard King
Grand Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Senior Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
1st Class Junior Magic Knight
2nd Class Junior Magic Knight
3rd Class Junior Magic Knight
4th Class Junior Magic Knight
5th Class Junior Magic Knight
Apparently Yuno became a
first-class junior Magic Knight.
That's awesome! It's only been
two months since he joined!
Yuno is the hope of Hage!
What about Asta?
I'm sure he's trying too hard
and being a burden to everyone.
Asta, you can come home at any time!
Let's see... "Hello, Sister Lily,
brats at the church, and Mayor."
What about me?!
Wizard King
Grand Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Senior Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
1st Class Junior Magic Knight
2nd Class Junior Magic Knight
3rd Class Junior Magic Knight
4th Class Junior Magic Knight
5th Class Junior Magic Knight
Asta's also become a
third-class junior Magic Knight?!
What?!
I see... I guess Asta's working hard, too.
To think our Asta is finally...
Both of you stay healthy, and do your best!
The Golden Dawn's Headquarters
Yuno.
I heard you moved up to
first-class junior Magic Knight.
Congratulations.
It's no big deal.
Exactly.
We wouldn't want you to get too cocky.
I still far surpass you in
both rank and experience.
Klaus?
Take this.
A little gift from your senior
in honor of your promotion.
You sent all of your pay
back home, didn't you?
Klaus is so shy.
He was so happy when he heard
you had been promoted
that his glasses were sparkling with joy.
It's a bit smothering.
Black Bulls' Base
All right, all eyes up here.
We just got paid, so no work today.
Yeah!
All right! I'm gonna train real hard!
Thanks, Mr. Yami!
Awesome decision, sir!
Let's drink! The night's still young.
Time for second breakfast!
Munchy, munchy, munchy...
I'm gonna hit on all the girls!
Ocean girls? Mountain girls?
All the girls meet... me!
By the way, Gauche, good job
handling that many guys yesterday.
Today's my sister's birthday, so could I have
the next year off, until her next birthday?
No.
I'm so bored! I wonder if anyone
will attack the royal capital again.
Hey! Maybe I'll attack it!
That's a bigger no.
Your luck with money goes
up if you polish gold.
None of these guys intend to work at all...
Cotton Creation Magic: Sheep Cooks!
Time to eat!
Munchy, munchy, munchy...
You've got tatoes!
I procured the local specialty from my
meal-saving prince's hometown, Hage Village!
Dig in, everyone!
Thanks! So good!
It's so dry. Must be full of fiber.
It's so flaky.
It completely dried out my mouth.
So dry...
Munchy, munchy...
My love for my meal-saving prince
provides the best seasoning!
I wonder what I should get my
goddess Marie for her birthday.
All right! I'm gonna get all the cuties—
Hold it.
Oh, right...
You want to do some gambling, so you
want me to take you into town again?
No, before that...
Not sure if it's the fiber working,
but I'm about to hit my limit right now.
That is the one limit you may not hit!
Evil, begone!
Honestly...
How am I supposed to find anything to do
when we get a day off on such short notice?
Magna!
If you have some time,
I was wondering if you could drop me off
somewhere on your super-awesome broom!
I can't say no to my cute little underling.
Where do you wanna go?
To Nean!
I-Isn't that...
The place where those guys had the mixer?
And what are you gonna do there?
Well...
Well?
I'll tell you on the way!
What the heck?!
I-It's not like I care what he does.
A-And I have absolutely no interest
in who he's going to see!
Get on. Let's get going.
Huh? Right now?
Otherwise, we're not going.
Let's go!
Hold on tight!
O-Okay, so I do want to know!
City in the Common Realm: Nean
To my dear, beloved little sister Marie...
I just arrived in the city you live in.
My job as a Magic Knight is rough, but if
it's for you, it's not really rough at all.
I can even buy you presents with my pay.
A former convict like myself is
only able to live a proper life
for the sake of your angelic cuteness,
Marie. It's all thanks to you.
Ah, already, my nose won't stop bleeding.
Lord Gauche!
We've been waiting for you!
Come in! We've got plenty of birthday
presents for you to choose from!
Hurry up and show me around.
Right away!
First up, we have these!
All little girls love plushies,
and plushies love little girls!
I'm sure her delight will
show in her angelic smile.
Thank you, Brother!
I-I'll take them all...
Thank you, sir!
Next, we have this.
I'm sure the little darling will enjoy
her days playing house as she fantasizes
about living in a mansion like
this with her beloved brother.
Brother!
Welcome home!
I'll take that, too.
Thank you, sir!
Lastly, we have this! With this outfit,
your little sister can be a real angel!
Brother...
I love you!
Give me everything in the shop.
Thank you, sir!
What?! You're going to see a
chick you met at the mixer?!
Yup! I promised Rebecca that I would
play with her little siblings.
M-Man, you're already meeting
her family? Way to go!
Don't mess this up.
Got it!
There it is!
All right! I'm going to play
with all the strength I've got!
Don't get too crazy!
To my dear, beloved little sister Marie...
Please forgive your brother for
being late due to his anemia.
I bought you lots of birthday
presents. Please be happy!
I used up all of my pay, but no
price is too high for Marie.
I will be able to see my
little angel Marie soon...
I'll be able to see her smile...
Oh, my beloved Marie.
Marie... Marie... Ma—
How do you like that, Marie?
This is fun! You're so strong, Asta!
Me, too!
And me!
All right! Are you read—
Huh? What?
Get away from her this instant, you trash!
Hey, you're my senior with the sister complex
who's always getting nosebleeds!
Don't call me a guy with a sister complex
and nosebleeds, meathead runt!
I'll stomp you to death!
I train hard, so you'll have
to try harder than that!
He's so annoying.
I'm only able to see my sister,
who lives at the church, once a month!
Today is the one day that I get
to release my pent-up feelings,
worship the heck out of my sister,
and do all kinds of things with her,
so why are you worshiping her first, huh?!
See? You do have a sister
complex and a nosebleed!
So wait, she's your sister?
Don't you dare point at my angel.
I showed you her picture before!
Did you?
I was just visiting Rebecca,
and she just happened to be here.
Hi...
That guy is scary.
What does he mean by "all kinds of things"?
Shh!
Man, Marie sure is cute.
Of course she is! More importantly, why
do you have your eye on my little sister?
Stop!
Please don't be so mean, Brother!
I'm going to marry him!
I'm going to marry him... I'm going to
marry him... I'm going to marry him....
Marry him?!
I ended up following him because I was
curious, but what the heck's going on?!
Um... May I ask for the fare now?
Will this do?
That's too much!
I'll kill you... I'll kill you... I'll kill you...
Huh? What was that?
I'll kill you!
Mirror Magic:
Reflect Ray!
Wh-What the heck's up with that spell?!
I'll kill you!
Brother, stop!
It sure is noisy out here.
Marie, it's time. We must
go back to the church.
Sister!
Tch.
Oh, so you came, Gauche.
You old hag!
It's not "old hag," it's "Sister."
Marie's about to go on a date with me.
Go back to the church by
yourself, Sister Old Hag.
Not happening. It's time.
You go home, you sister complex punk.
In any case, it's not good for Marie
to spend time with a guy like you.
Your attitude's always terrible. You have
mean eyes and a filthy mouth.
What did you say, you shitty old hag?
See? Filthy.
Shut up. Die.
You've got some nerve,
saying that to an old lady
who's not long for this world, you fool.
Yeah, right, dumbass.
Says the old she-demon who'll
probably live another hundred years.
Don't talk to people like
they're monsters, you thug!
Shut up, gangster hag!
Gauche!
How can you talk to your elders like that?!
You shouldn't!
You stay out of this!
Anyway, go on home.
Let's go, Marie.
Brother, Asta! See you later!
M-Marie!
See ya!
See you later!
You okay, sister complex guy?
M-Ma... Ma... Ma...
What a weirdo.
Why don't you come in and have dinner at
our place while you wait for him to wake up?
You're welcome to spend
the night... if you want.
Really?!
Yeah!
Yeah, come over!
S-S-Spend the night?!
He's going to spend the night at the home
of a girl he just met?! Is he stupid?!
How stupid can he be?!
And Asta is so funny!
That really loud boy?
Yeah!
S...
So good!
Isn't it?
This is so good!
Would you like some moguro fruit?
So fast!
All these dishes are so good
that I can't put my spoon down!
Really? I'm glad to hear it!
You'll be a great wife one day, Rebecca!
It's no big deal...
What are you talking about?! There's more to
being a good wife than just being a good cook!
Sissy, are you going to marry Asta?
N-No, Marco!
Of course she's not!
You should totally jump him tonight, Sis!
You idiot! What are you saying, Luca?!
Goo goo.
Y-You too, Pem?! Do you even
know what you're saying?!
J-Jump him? No, you dummy, dummy, dummy!
What's going on? What is this?
It's not even winter! Why is it so cold?
Huh?
You should totally jump him tonight!
Goo goo.
Y-You too, Pem?!
You dummy! Dummy, dummy, dummy!
I-I would never do anything like that!
I-I'm just going to check and see if
Luca and Marco are actually asleep...
Asta...
Die, Asta.
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray.
Hot!
G-Gauche?!
Die, Asta.
Why? Wait, what? What's going on?
Huh? What?!
I won't allow you to marry Marie. I'll make
sure it doesn't happen by killing you.
What?!
Kids say stuff like that all the time!
Only cowards attack people in their sleep!
I don't care if it's cowardly or not,
as long as I can kill you.
Mirror Magic:
Real Double.
Now there are two Gauches?!
First he shoots beams out of a mirror,
and now this? What's up with his magic?
Your crime...
is the fact that you met my little sister.
Wouldn't that make most people criminals?!
Shut up. Die.
That's not even your house!
S-Snow? When did it pile up so much?
It's not even the season for that yet.
I don't care about that. Just die.
Hey! What do you two think you're doing?!
Rebecca! I'm so sorry!
Now's not the time for that!
The kids are gone!
Huh?
Urian, where are you?
Chris!
Hey!
Von is gone!
Starting today,
you're all my friends.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Double Gauche
Double Gauche.
Brother!
Spin me around like Asta did!
I'll... kill him!!
Spin... Marie around?!
Brother?!
I can't disappoint Marie...
I'll have to rely on my clone...
Mirror Magic: Real Double!
Spin her around...
I can't put Marie in danger.
That's true!
Then I'll just have to do it for her.
See? We're spinning!
You're not doing it right.
What? The ABCs of cooking?
All will Bow down before my Cooking!
Black Clover, Page 31:
"Pursuit Over the Snow."
Page 31
Pursuit Over the Snow
But now's not the time for that!
The kids are in trouble!