It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Well, this isn't good at all.
You're going to make an old man get serious.
Smoke Creation Magic:
Prison of the Fallen King.
You won't be able to get away anymore, kids.
No matter who we're facing,
we, the Black Bulls, will win!
I'm going to get serious now.
What are you...
Wind Creation Magic: Swift White Hawk
and Wind Blade Shower.
Simultaneous spell activation?!
It will be the Golden Dawn that
reaches the treasure chamber first!
Take that!
I'm getting dizzy...
The smoke just keeps getting thicker.
At this rate, we're going to suffocate.
This isn't good. We have to
hurry up and defeat that mage.
I can pretty much tell
where he is with my magic,
but he'll probably dodge, even if I attack.
Thinking back on our battle so far,
he's able to travel at high
speed within the smoke.
And his ability to sense magic is high.
If we're to land a hit on him,
we'll have to surprise him.
But how do we do that without
him noticing our magic?
Because I can sense your magic just fine.
Whoa, there!
Wow, a barrage. Are you getting desperate?
That's not going to hit me
or get rid of the smoke.
I think the difference in our
experience levels is starting to show.
After all, I've fought far
more mages than you have.
It went well.
I guess teamwork really is important.
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
Destroyer
Ow...
How could you do that to a
defenseless old man like me?
Man... It's definitely broken.
Pretty sure he got some of my ribs, too.
I won't be able to fight anymore.
There sure are some oddballs
in the Clover Kingdom.
A boy with no magic
who wields a giant sword...
I can safely say that even I've never met
someone with no magic on the battlefield.
If I'm going to end up a prisoner...
I'll di—
Or just run away.
Hey!
Wait!
You're not getting away!
Smoke Creation Magic: Hustling Lazy Car.
Caught up with you!
Aw...
Damn it! We lost him!
You two...
are way too fast.
I wanted to finish him off,
but I know we have more
important things to do.
We need to hurry to the treasure chamber.
You really have the nerve to say that?
Oh, yeah! Let's get going!
What is this magic?
It looks like there's someone
even stronger here.
Are you all okay?
I guess the treasure chamber is
the least of our worries right now.
Ow...
Well, I'm pretty sure Mars
will take care of the rest.
I mean...
Diamond Kingdom Mage Warrior
Mars
He's the Diamond Kingdom's
secret weapon, after all.
Such ominous magic...
Yuno's at full strength,
and even he stands no chance...
Those stones embedded in his forehead...
I've heard of them before.
There's a rumor that the Diamond
Kingdom is raising mage warriors
with artificially amplified magic.
They choose young children
with powerful magical abilities,
put them in fierce competition
with each other,
embed magical items that amplify
their powers into their bodies...
And finally, they have them
fight one another to the death.
The last survivor of that death match...
is him?
No matter who the opponent is...
Is this really acceptable?
What is happening here?
I'm a noble!
A member of the Golden Dawn!
I let my comrade get hurt so easily.
I'm being protected by my
subordinate, who's a peasant.
This...
This cannot be right!
Steel Creation Magic: Fierce Spiral Lance!
Klaus!
Wha—
A mineral clone?
Klaus!
Your magic has no effect on me.
It's no use.
I told you, it's no use.
Let's stop this training,
Asta.
Not yet!
I'm not quitting until I hit you!
Oh, no!
Asta.
Not...
Not yet!
Let's stop.
No!
I'm never...
...going to give up!
Stop your useless attempts—
I won't!
Move.
I won't move!
Give up.
I won't give up!
Yuno!
Hey, pale guy.
Hands off!
Yuno's my...
rival!
Yuno!
Hey, pale guy.
Hands off!
Yuno's my...
rival!
Unbelievable... and I thought
I finally repaid my debt to you.
I finally catch up with you, and look at you!
What the hell are you doing, Yuno?! Damn it!
Who said you could get your ass kicked?
Why'd you get in my way?
I almost had him.
Liar! You're all beat up!
You were about to die!
I was just about to unleash
a ferocious counterattack.
You're such a liar!
I was about to do it.
You're always like this!
Did you come to get in my way?
What?!
You can go home now.
Fine, then.
Let's see who can take this guy down first!
Wh-What's going on?
We, the Golden Dawn, didn't stand a
chance against his magic, and yet...
That peasant from the Black Bulls...
Oh, no!
Weak.
He's...
The one who made trouble at
the Entrance Exam by beating
his opponent far worse than necessary!
Luck the Cheery Berserker!
This was the other member of
the Black Bulls that was here?
How could I end up being
saved by the Black Bulls?!
Mimosa!
Well, this is embarrassing...
Just as you said, I'm a bit slow.
Yes.
You've always been like that.
That's why...
I'm going to protect you.
Noelle...
Are you the one who beat up the Golden Dawn?
What if I am?
The weak will perish,
and only the strong will remain.
That's all that matters.
He summoned so many at once!
There is no reason for the weak
to stand on the battlefield.
I was born to break people like you.
Oh, really?
Then go ahead...
and try to break me!
I intend to.
He's so strong!
Aw, man...
I wanted to be the one to fight him!
Impossible...
How could a peasant that I can't feel
a shred of mana from do all this?
All you've been doing is whining.
Negating magic...
That's Asta's power.
Negating magic?
How can he have a power
so unfit for a peasant?!
So he just got lucky and
ended up with this power.
Just watch him, and you'll
find out if it's just luck or not.
Hey, come on! Are you
finished already, you jerk?
Asta!
What...
are you?
I'm someone who was born without any magic!
He doesn't have any magic?!
So it really was just luck—
But even so, I'm going to
become the Wizard King!
And I'm alive...
to prove that!
What is going on with his body?
How much has he trained?!
The Wizard King? Does he truly...
Mars!
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I'm...
I'm just going to destroy everything!
Destroy everything?
The Wizard King protects everyone!
We were born to protect
everyone in this country.
Like hell I'm going to lose
to someone like you!
You're in my way...
Begone, pebble!
I may be just a pebble,
but I'm...
a pebble that shatters diamonds!
See?
If you don't give up,
you'll get there eventually!
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Treasure Chamber
Treasure Chamber.
Ooh! So this is the treasure chamber!
I wonder if there's any
treasure worthy of me.
Let's just randomly open
stuff up and see what's inside!
Hey, no fair doing it all yourself!
Open sesame—
It's no treasure chamber.
It's an organ chamber.
This isn't my fault.
This old man's exhausted.
I don't know how much more abuse
I can take from home and work.
Black Clover, Page 18: "Memories of You."
Page 18
Memories of You
Leaving the rest to the young'uns
is this old man's magic.