It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Hey, isn't this just messed up?
Why did I have to get kicked out?
I have more magical power than the royals do.
Magic is everything in
this world... isn't it?
This is a load of bull!
Who are you talking to?
I'm just talking to myself.
We're ready.
Yeah... I'll show the Clover Kingdom's
Magic Knights the true extent of my powers!
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
Capital Riot
There's no reason to run from these jerks.
Asta?
Calling us peasants, rats,
embarrassments, failures...
Who cares if you think we're worthy or not?!
Just you watch! I'm going to—
That's enough, you scoundrel.
You shouldn't even be allowed to talk!
Silence!
I won't shut up!
He just...
Listen up, you bastards!
I'm going to pile up merit,
become the Wizard King,
and shut you all up!
Leopold
Fuegoleon
Sol
Charlotte
Hamon
Alecdora
Shiren
Solid
Nozel
Nebra
You fool
A-Asta...
Not a chance.
Become...
...the Wizard King?
Don't make us laugh!
Water Binding Magic: Sea Serpent's Coils!
What?
Mist Binding Magic: Mist Spider's Threads.
I knew it...
He's erasing the magic.
He's no ordinary peasant.
But...
If that's his attack range,
there's no reason for concern.
Sand Creation Magic: Sand-Armored Guard!
A-Asta!
I-I think that's enough.
Keep your mouth shut.
Y-Yes, sir.
To act in such a way at a festive occasion
like the decoration ceremony...
You will surely be punished.
Come on, now...
Why so soft, Golden Dawn?
Anyone that self-confident
needs to be taught a lesson.
That's...
So that they can never talk back again.
Solid, please don't!
Holy Water Bullet!
Asta!
You're such an embarrassment.
Apologize...
to Noelle!
Did you just make me kneel?
You lowly peasant!
I'm not holding back anymore!
Solid, p-please, no more...
Nozel?
Solid, don't be so quick to use
your magic on a mere peasant.
B-But...
Silence.
Do you plan to shame the Silva family?
What is this chill in the air?
It's a cold pressure that's
different from Captain Yami's...
This is the Captain of the Silver Eagles?
A peasant that foolishly tried to
defy royalty... How shall I punish you?
Wh-What should I do?
At this rate, Asta will...
That's enough.
You're getting so worked
up over a little boy.
You should be ashamed of yourself, Silvas.
It's just as Mimosa said.
You're quite amusing!
Huh?
All right, rejoice! I, Leopold Vermillion,
declare you my rival!
Huh?
What was your name? Casta?
Leopold, it's Asta. He's Asta.
Asta, eh? That's a great name, my rival!
R-Rival?!
Come, now! Rejoice!
Rejoice.
Y-Yay...
Vermillion...
Leopold and Fuegoleon are my cousins.
Leopold
Mimosa
Noelle
Mimosa's
Father
Vermillion Family
Fuegoleon
1st Son      1st D.
2nd D.      2nd Son      1st D.      1st Son
Noelle's
Mother
Fuegoleon's
Father
Noelle's
1st D.      1st Son
Mimosa's
Mother
Silva Family
Fuegoleon's
Mother
2nd Son
My father's older brother is
Fuegoleon and Leopold's father.
Also, my mother's older
sister is Noelle's mother.
Too many royals.
Huh?
Um... Thanks, but my rival's actually
Yuno, who's standing over there.
No worries! One can never
have too many rivals!
What the heck?
Hey, Asta! You have a very nice body!
You are indeed qualified to be my rival!
All right! Let us arm wrestle.
Why?!
Guys really are dumb, aren't they, Sis?
Mind your manners, Sol.
My bad, Sis!
Call me "Captain," Sol.
Sol...
I know, Sis!
Sis!
Come at me!
Is now really the time for this?
Why are you holding back? Come!
What?!
Becoming Leopold's rival...
Asta truly is amazing!
My, aren't we all so very noisy today?
Looks like things have calmed down.
A royal acknowledging a peasant as his rival?
Lord Julius allowed the boy to be here.
He may be a peasant, but doesn't
he deserve a little credit?
I never thought I'd hear such
nonsense from a royal's mouth.
It appears that the Vermillion
family has gone soft.
You're a disgrace to us all.
What?
How am I, an eagle that soars the sky,
supposed to give any credit to an
insect that crawls on the ground?
Wh-What a tremendous clash of mana!
H-Holy crap...
You can feel it?
Even if I can't feel their mana,
I can tell... that this is amazing!
Shouldn't we stop them, Sis?
This is foolish. Ignore the men
and their boorish fighting.
Also, call me "Captain."
Sure thing, Sis!
Call me—
Th-There's an emergency!
What's wrong?
Th-The capital!
The capital is under attack!
Destroy!
Destroy, destroy, destroy, destroy!
Wh-What's going on?
Destroy all the fools who
can't understand my worth!
Such disgusting creatures.
Where did they come from?
You must not value your lives, if you're
invading the royal capital like this!
Wh-What are these things?
They keep coming toward us even
when we shoot their limbs off!
Do not falter!
Protect the Clover Ki—
You won't be able to, you scum!
Get lost, scum! Scum! Scum!
What is this magic?
You're stronger than me, right? Right?!
Get out here, Magic Knights!
The Royal Capital is under attack?!
Stone Creation Magic:
Stone Model of the World.
It's... a three-dimensional
model of the Noble Realm?
W-Wow!
Even the voices of the people at
the scene and their magic levels...
Is he lacing the whole area with mana
and simultaneously making it visible?
This is much more advanced than
my Magic Flower Guidepost!
A force with this much magic appears
in five places simultaneously,
without us noticing...
A formidable spatial magic user must have
made them materialize in an instant.
Even then, the guard mages of
the Noble Realm work in shifts,
constantly keeping a magic barrier in place.
It should be impossible to
enter with spatial magic.
Did they analyze the barrier's
mechanism and break through it?
Or did one of the guard mages betray us?
Either way, they must
be phenomenally skilled.
How should we assign the
members we currently have?
First, we need to guard the
area around the castle.
Wait, what the heck are we waiting for?!
I get it! There are people
out there who need our help!
I'm gonna go!
Asta!
Where do you plan to go?
We don't even know the full situation yet,
and you can't sense magic at all!
I'm going to where it's noisiest!
Wha— D-Do you think you're
an animal or something?!
Interesting!
Let's see what you've got!
Wait for me, Asta, my rival!
Guys really are dumb, aren't they, Sis?
Yes, they are.
And call me "Captain."
Leo's still very much a child.
I'll have to thoroughly retrain him later.
I'm sure you'd rather not take orders
from me, but listen well, Magic Knights!
I'll go after Leo and that Black Bulls boy,
and after I've joined them,
we'll head to the north district.
You, Black Bulls girl, come with me.
Silver Eagles, I ask that you
head to the central district,
where the magic is strongest.
Very well.
Blue Roses, head to the east district!
I'd rather not take orders from a man,
but I suppose I don't have a choice.
Here we go, Sis!
Call me "Captain."
Golden Dawn, split into two teams and head
to the west and northwest districts!
We will protect the people of the Nobel Realm.
Let us go.
I guess we'll just have
to save dessert for later.
If we fail to protect the royal capital,
we'll bring shame upon the Magic Knights!
Do not let the enemy escape, no matter what!
Right!
Munchy, munchy...
I managed to get in by following
Asta and the others,
but it looks like something
awful is happening.
This looks like a job for Charmy!
If I do good, I might get the chance
to eat even better food!
I smell something delicious!
I have to fuel up before the battle!
Central District
Don't think you're going to get away with...
What? What do you want?
I'll give it to you, just—
East District
Mind your manners, Sol.
My bad, Sis!
Call me "Captain."
Northwest District
Those who dare to bring chaos upon the
kingdom shall perish before my magic!
These things keep getting
up with half-assed attacks.
In that case...
West District
I guess we should work off
some calories before dessert.
Fools who disturb the peace of the capital...
You shall be eliminated!
North District
Wh-What is this?
I've never seen them before.
What country is that army from?
Where's Asta?
Little girl... Do you like the Clover Kingdom?
I-I love it!
So please... stop this.
Well, I hate it!
So the town... the people...
And you, too, little girl...
I'll destroy you all!
Then I'll protect them!
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Mr. Animal
Mr. Animal.
I'm going to where it's noisiest!
Wha— D-Do you think you're
an animal or something?!
An animal?
Woof, woof.
A dog... My, how adorable.
But a cat might be nice, too.
Meow, meow.
How delightful!
Oh, but maybe something
even wilder, like a wolf...
All men are wolves.
Oh, I just can't choose!
Not a chance...
What a creepy enemy! But there's
no time to be creeped out.
I will protect the citizens
of the Clover Kingdom!
Black Clover, Page 22:
"Wild Magic Dance."
Page 22
Wild Magic Dance
If you're hurt, please come to me!