grid
Wanhua Valley protector Ji Yunhe
would also like to participate in the training
I also hope that Xian Ji will be fulfilled
presumptuous
Don't drag her away
How does the angel know
Xianji does not want to
get me involved
you are very confident
Let's talk about why
Just because I'm just like Xianji
all women
naturally know
What does Xianji want
Xian Ji wants one
The puppet that bends to surrender
still want one
loyal servant
continue
Be the heart and the heart
Fear or forbearance
These surrenders originate from the outside
Not really reliable
only the will of the heart
the most precious
Throughout the Quartet Yu Lingshi
On controlling the heart
Xiaoxian recognizes the second
No one dares to say first
Besides, Fairy likes to be neat and tidy
Then why not let Xiaoxian join in?
New ways to try
It's all for Xianji
I think the Shaogu master should
won't mind
Right
I haven't seen you in a long time
Such a madman
What did you just say your name was
Xiaoxian Ji Yunhe
,
You are the one who gave the 'fairy'
person who posted a ban
Yes
So
rather than to please
Minions beside Xianji
That's what you said
Yes
This is your initiative
if there is any error
you can afford the consequences
Xiaoxian is willing to bear all the consequences
but
Xiaoxian wants to ask one more question
Xian Ji just said
Rewards for Shaogu Master
Not sure if the same applies to me
Xiaoxian thinks
Everything has to be fair
you're funny
The palace allows
You two train together
a training heart
Who will complete the mission of this palace first?
who can get
The Palace's Reward
Anyway, the master hasn't come out yet.
this palace as
watch a good show
Since Xian Ji likes
Then it's settled
every day
Yunhe
you two
Take this opportunity to compete
I believe
you all understand
How to do it
to not disappoint me
Yes
The merman is the master of the deep sea
powerful and mysterious
There has never been a sorcerer
trained
Look at the unboxing today
He got hurt
so many masters
you have to discipline him
you don't want to die
Ji Yunhe
Should you be rewarded by Shunde?
Confused
But Lolo
Think about it
sharp edge
What's the use of a sharpening stone?
If Lin Haoqing
Can take this shark
Got the favor of Xian Ji
then
It was he who took over as the valley owner.
best chance
If he becomes the valley owner
what will happen to me
you can't understand me
it's too risky
So that big tail fish
is our last chance
did not live on the fairy island
I'm not willing to die
You Ji Yunhe has countless royal spirits
I, Luo Jinsang, read thousands of books
i don't believe
the two of us together
Still can't catch him a fish
reading
look
Father
Shark training is a big deal
You just let Ji Yunhe go
public provocation
You and Ji Yunhe
is my right arm
no matter which of you two wins
All the glory of the Valley of Flowers
it's you
Are you afraid?
this battle
Haoqing will do his best
shame before snow
very good
then win for me
Yes
Day^4=1 day
What do you want to say to Xian Ji today?
what reward
something
Is it that Wanhuagu can't give it to you?
no
Hao Qing is just thinking about the changing world
Better to seek grace first
Maybe the Valley of Flowers in the future
can be used
Okay
Then go get ready
The main land of the day: Retreat at the eyes of the sky
Shaoguzhu
Want something
the child is older
have a plan
is a good thing
That Ji Yunhe's side
My mind moved to Xian Ji's head
It's a little smart
Pity
The ancient spirit beast of the East China Sea
It is also a leader among the gods
But you don't have to expect
who will save you
Fairy is already on you
under the ban
your clan
I can't detect your breath
Can't find your location
what you can do
Just surrender
So you can suffer less
thinking language
This merman is still wild
already on thunder
It's better to frustrate him first
don't let him die
Yes
Ji Yunhe Ji Yunhe
Shark training today
you can still sleep
Come
Get up and read a book
get some inspiration
I read the book overnight
Just a few words that are useful
shark dwelling in the East China Sea
Loyal, affectionate and good water control
The rest are some
How to take fish scale fish paste
for medicine
if these are useful
What do you want me to do as a master
But
don't be
I guess Lin Haoqing
Already thinking about it
until he's done
I have my own way to deal with sharks
What if
Lin Haoqing really took the shark
what to do
If you can really get that shark
make a call
Xian Ji can still put him
to Wanhua Valley
Immortal's Mansion's Punishment
Not heavier than Wanhua Valley
protector
Ji Yunhe
aunt
You still have time to chat here
Shaogu master has already used the punishment
Ji Yunhe, you are a god
this shark
There is still no half, the meaning of Xiao
Whether you are not convinced or stubborn
can't change the result
Just have to suffer more
Subordinates are a little worried
That Ji Yunhe has never appeared
I don't know what I'm planning
Use or not
How do you want to deal with her?
like when opening the box
you destroy
Like the golden amulet on the lock box
Subordinates know their mistakes
But the subordinates are all
For the sake of Master Shaogu
This thing is holy
you are restless
can't control
Shaoguzhu
This is what you gave me
first weapon
thinking language
starting today
Ji Yunhe's story
You are not allowed to act on your own
this to you to me
all good
Yes
go
The shark hasn't spoken yet.
I didn't expect
He speaks so easily
Just don't go
I'm afraid someone has to wait
3,
Disciplinary Law
The two immortal friends worked hard
I let Lolo give it to you
Prepared some flower and fruit fairy brew
rest assured
Still the same...
Delicious and not drunk...
Thank you protector
You two rest for a while
I will meet the merman when I enter
protector
you still don't go in
why
Shaogu's command
Naturally not
just the shark
too stubborn
Crazy again today
almost broke the barrier
such a monster
It's never seen before
If the protector wants to cure him
Why don't you bring some more people
Makes sense
That being the case
Not as good as two fairy friends
Come in with me;
I didn't ask for it before
do you want to learn from me
no no no no no
Please
1 I
protector please
Yunhe
This fish is so awesome
Otherwise we'll call
Qu Xiaoxing, they come again
to make friends
How can you call a gang of thugs?
rest assured
I fought him
I know
I still don't go
do not move
Naji
i won't hurt you
you're badly hurt
If not treated in time
you won't last
do you want to leave
you have your hometown
there's something you haven't done
someone you want to see
Then live well first;
only alive
you can leave
Although I was ordered to teach you
But I also have troubles
i won't be too bad for you
Trust me
Only the two of us have a turnaround
but if you don't trust me
you will live rather than die
I won't have any good fruit to eat
this is our place
i can get in
you can't get out
relax
I have no defense
okay
Is that right?
inch dagger
big tail fish
well well
Why don't I call you like that?
obediently don't move
I just told you
i won't hurt you
hold on
can't figure
it out
, why do you want to help you?
I can't figure it out
you just have to remember
i won't hurt you
What's up
You mermaids are hard-boned
The skin is soft and thin
Shouldn't this give you medicine?
hold on
look
as long as you cooperate
Medication is fast
I didn't expect fish to be so shy
I brought you a suit
After you land
The meeting ceremony where we became friends
what do you think
as a friend
I'll help you pull out that golden arrow.
1-front
Can not
Yunhe
Shaogu master Shaogu master
Lin Haoqing
what the hell are you doing
I told you you can't pull it out
you still don't listen to me
on this golden arrow
Hidden spell cast by Lin Haoqing
That's it
When someone else touches
will work
If it weren't for my immortal bodyguard
your beautiful big tail
It's already torn
time is limited
Lin Haoqing will be here soon
I can only help you here
If you don't want to continue
nailed to the wall
I can help you next
only yourself
remember
Resistance is never reckless and blind
You can also use strength
It seems that my sister is going to be here tonight
wasted effort
Yunhe, are you alright?
Congrats brother for taking precautions
Also know that dig a hole and let me jump
This is compared to before
Really improved a lot
Sister, I'm afraid you may have misunderstood
It's not you that the golden arrows protect against
It is the people who come to rob the prison
I didn't expect you to move
you want to treat him
But there are savages left and right
what he needs to remember
only who is his master
remember
You can also use strength
you taught him
Get rid of the golden arrow by the power of lightning
The merman is like the soul of the sea
I couldn't stand it
The golden arrow spell is powerful
Brother, please heal as soon as possible
to prevent the injury from getting worse
Here it can only be done by Yunhe
Worry for my brother
the injury matters
This arrow has mana on it
Okay
Come to Japan for a long time
Junior sister also be more careful
brother walk slowly
lolo
Beware of Lin Haoqing in the future
Do you understand
understood
Yunhe
What's wrong with you
so pale
fine
I just used the immortal seal
Help the shark block the golden arrow
Just got hurt
you
sorry
do you know
This immortal seal is difficult to repair
It is used to save lives at critical times
It's life saving now
critical time
this game
Never let Lin Haoqing win
This shark is so proud
I just want him to feel
He owes me a favor
I'll talk later
But the price of this bitterness
It must be too big.
eloquence
This mermaid looks like
silly look
Does he know what human love is?
he doesn't understand
I'll teach him until he understands
how to teach
fish
I
turn around
are you not shy
you turn around
don't do that to us
why are you shy
Isn't he a mermaid?
Why is the tail missing?
Two legs came out
I asked you to read, but you don't
they were
from land to sea
had legs
you look like that
that way
see it
why don't you let me see
I just want to see him
Why do you have long legs?
I see
He must be badly injured
I can't control it
I look at people
do not
Don't get on the drug
All right
The blood stopped you
Thunder, I also help you stop
as long as it is within my jurisdiction
you will be well protected
how about me
thank me
big tail fish
As long as you are obedient
I promise you eat well
sleep soundly
Shaoguzhu
This is the best elixir
It only takes a day or two to heal
Ji Yunhe dares to instigate the merman
hands on you
so mean
I didn't expect that shark
I really listened to her
It's just the art of tenderness
her usual tricks
Shaoguzhu
You still let Siyu
go watch her
Just go with her
The shark is delicate and expensive
She can't keep this fish
so many rare fish
is to spend
Bought a lot of spirit stones
and
Neither of us are willing to eat
you gave it all to him
Ji Yunhe
This fairyland does not have to feed on five grains
he's starving
he is so great
don't buy him
starving to death
But you will still be hungry
Let's talk about food supplements
Can assist in meditation
Don't we all eat every day?
The shark was injured
make up fast
But
He is the lord of the deep sea
The taste will definitely be
picky
If the spirit stone is gone, you can still earn it again
If the chance is gone
But never meet again
Ji Yunhe, you really are
I tell you
He is delicious and spicy
All the fees are our fairy island
he eats one more day
We are a small one in Xiandao
Spend on like this
Don't talk about buying Xiandao
Both of us will become
pauper
you see
and
Isn't he obedient?
why don't you be direct
Talk to him about the termination
mouth not open
How to bring up the tail
Moreover
Everything has a process
Expose yourself early
Just keep him on guard
so
Everything has to be planned slowly
Xu Xutuzhi
three days
The way the fish looked at me
already very different
three days
I'll make him speak
this
and this
These should always be you
love it
ok ok i don't look at you
eat by yourself
big tail fish
don't you know
what is a friend
It does not matter
I can teach you
Actually, before I picked up Lolo
no friends
wrong
i used to have a friend
but then
something happened
we are no longer friends
so
Friendship doesn't come easy
you should cherish more
my friend
big tail fish
they all say
You have committed the following crimes against Shunde Xianji
even injured
Disciple of the Immortal Master's Mansion
But I think you're pure in nature
Not quite like a tyrant
can you tell me
what happened?
nothing more
If you don't want to say
then don't talk about it
I'm not forcing you anymore
hear the guards
Afraid that you will become stronger in water
So I dare not take water
come for you to drink
Are you thirsty
I'll go get some water for you
Water Repelling
you are seriously injured
Spirituality will inevitably be weak
It does not matter
wait until you heal
You are still the most powerful fish
I know you want to go
But this is the Valley of Flowers
heavily guarded
Now there is also the blessing of the fairy master's golden talisman
you are so weak
How can you escape
So just listen to me
heal the injury
Don't waste your spiritual power in vain
Don't run away blindly
Otherwise, if you are caught again
The guards will be stricter
Punishment will be harsher
I can't help you
But for the sake of friends
I can give it to you
bring something else
Ming Ji Yunhe
I see you are not a shark
Are you being trained by sharks?
This is Ningxue Wan
I've saved this bottle over the years
You were frozen before
wounded by a golden arrow
you are reluctant to use
Now you're going to take it
Yaoyiyiyuan"隹I
lolo
Reluctant to let the child catch the wolf
Moreover
Lin Haoqing's injury
it will be ready soon
I don't have much time left
Is there no other reason?
Mr. Qing Shu
Valley owner please
Rumors are true
The coexistence of shark legs and tails
I make you suffer
I'm the bad guy
Ji Yunhe will give you some food
is a good man
You are really in the deep sea
live too long
shortsighted
show you something
This is the Valley of Flowers
Token of the highest order
Ji Yunhe also has one
How did she get such an identity
Why is the fairy princess in Shunde
give you to her
This is the Valley of Flowers
The sorcerer will not
to you criminals
gratuitous goodwill
I grew up with her
I've seen it this way a lot
Think about what I said
Valley Lord
Disciplinary Law
I heard that you trained the shark well.
Even Haoqing was taken away by you
rested for two days
This kid looks good
Don't let anyone mention it to me
I'm the boss
It's an afterthought.
Valley Lord
It was Yun He's impulse
Injured Shaogu Lord
I also hope that the lord of the valley can be forgiven
If the owner is still not satisfied
Na Yunhe
you did a good job
hone
I have to suffer
But let me warn you
Disciplinary Law
Since it's something you take care of yourself
Just think about the gains and losses
Forgot your identity
it doesn't matter
but nothing else
should not have thoughts
Antidote to Frost
Missing it is gone
scorpion
big tail fish
This is the Valley of Flowers
The sorcerer will not
to you criminals
gratuitous goodwill
look
What good things did I bring you
This is the healing medicine
after using it
your injury
will get better soon
But then again
We pay attention to etiquette
Do you know its meaning
I will give you medicine to heal your wounds
you want to tell me your name
look
My name is
, --one person
And you
so handsome
The name should be nice too.
Such a beautiful fish
Won't be dumb
1 1 day
Token of the highest order
Ji Yunhe also has one
How did she get such an identity
Why is the fairy princess in Shunde
give you to her
what to do
you think i'm used to you
won't hit you
You thought I was holding this token
Do you want to be rich and prosperous?
Do you think
Do I want to be a sorcerer?
But look at my wounds
If you don't obey first
Bundles of the Valley of Flowers
how can i leave
this ghost place
I use the immortal seal to block the golden arrow for you
give you medicine
bring you food
Send me and Lolo's fairy island
almost gone
And that Ningxue Wan
You know how hard I am
Can you save those?
I don't want to use it myself
I'm Baba
bring it to you
think for yourself
have i done one
things that hurt you
I just want to be your friend
But what about you
you never trusted me
don't believe me
if you are annoying
Then if I don't come
Seek more happiness
Ji Yunhe is Ji Yunhe
such a short time
make up such a touching speech
On Playing Every Scene
I'm afraid no one can compare to you
if you don't know
How cool are you
just now
sincere speech
I'm afraid even I will believe it
I should have thought
you won't let it go
Yu Xin is not only tender
There is also separation
Sister is careless
How do you know what I do and say
Just Huairou
rather than sincere
Maybe my words are heartfelt
the words of your heart
I've heard it in the snake cave.
Every word kills the heart
never forget
why do you
destined to have
The Master of the Valley of Thousand Flowers
I can only be your follower
Lin Haoqing
you stay here
between my brother and me
Does it have to be so tit for tat?
tit for tat
I thought it was to die
that's right
since already
come this far
Can't get out
The test is not over yet
Brother is coming to Japan for a long time
Ji Yunhe
I hate you laughing like that
hypocritical
arrogance
The owner of Shaogu is still worried about Ji Yunhe
she has lost
The sharks trust her
It must be difficult to turn around again.
She won't give up easily
As long as she is there, there are variables
have to figure out a way
let her out
Yunhe
Yunhe, you are back
Wait a minute
I sent a whole bottle of Ningxue Pills
Why are you looking like that?
That mermaid is still oily and salty.
3 Qi Gong
Wudingwu
wasted, wasted, wasted
wasted
Ji Yunhe
did you hear me talking
I'm listening
you are wrong
what are you thinking about
lolo
you say regret and regret
which is more sad
what do you regret
What are you sorry for?
Did someone bully you
Did the shark bully her?
impossible
The merman is not as smart as I am
Is it Lin Haoqing?
This Lin Haoqing
But look at my wounds
If you don't obey first
Bundles of the Valley of Flowers
how can i leave
this ghost place
I use the immortal seal to block the golden arrow for you
give you medicine
bring you food
Send me and Lolo's fairy island
almost gone
And that Ningxue Wan
You know how hard I work
Can you save those?
I can't even use it myself
But Baba sent it to you
think for yourself
I have done one all the time
does something make you sad?
I have done one
does it hurt you
I just want to be your friend
but you never
never trusted me