in the middle of the night
come to enjoy the flowers
interesting
Yunhe
what did you find
I don't see anything
I'll teach you another trick
watch people
can't look at his face
what is revealed
but to see him
what do you want to hide
separation
wisteria tree
what are you doing
still remember
what day is today
fifth day
It is illegal to travel late at night
go back
Then ask the lord to punish
Actually
I should be the punisher
three years ago today
It's the day you and I met
you forgot
It's by day
the gift
where we first met
There is also a wisteria tree
when i was in the valley
When I found this wisteria tree
I just want to give you a surprise
it's not legal
If anyone finds out
you will have an accident
The most unruly in the valley
In love with me in violation of the ban
isn't it you
Do not worry
It's just you and me tonight
you just tell me
this gift
Are you happy?
Then should you return a gift?
what are they doing
I
I am not wrong, right
Li Shu is biting Xue March's mouth
I didn't expect this snow in March
Usually a piece of iron
encounter this love affair
It can only be described in four words
girl huaichun
How dare they
The fierce beast Zhu Yan
Bewitching all the celestial beings
after being suppressed
The control of the gods to the gods has been strengthened
Especially like in the Valley of Thousand Flowers
This specialized training ground
I'm afraid you will be favoritism
So it is strictly forbidden
The Spiritualist and the Earth Immortal are in love
How
inform them
In the Valley of Thousand Flowers
Isolated
It's definitely not going to last
we want to be friends with them
master
Snow Chief
I have ordered this to be blocked
No one is allowed to enter
Disciplinary law please come back
i came today
Not for the merman
Instead, he came to find Commander Xue.
me and the law of discipline
as if nothing
special friendship
Yesterday under the wisteria tree in the sea of ​​flowers
I seem to have seen something
Commander Snow, don't be nervous
If you want to hurt you
I won't come to you
but directly
Go to Mr. Qingshu
what do you want 4
cooperate
I see you are heroic
a man of righteousness
Coincidentally ^^ yes
Since we are aspiring
Why not help each other
walk in the same direction
Discipline protection law is good at knowing people and observing hearts
Too bad I didn't see it
my life
I hate being blackmailed
Since you have seen
Then I can't keep you
5 Nissan,
go
Watch out for that shark
He was captured by Ji Yunhe
won't shoot
separation
you dodge
This issue
I will do
don't touch her
The merman really spoke for you
what happened
Shaoguzhu
someone saw
Ji Yunhe and Xue March
have entered the cave of thinking
I'm afraid there is something strange about this
come, come, come
i tell you
big trouble
Lin Haoqing doesn't know
what wind do you hear
Came here with someone
today's trouble
it's not over
separation
the three of them
I can't stay today
you
Why are you so ignorant?
Can't we make peace first?
easy to say
you think i don't want to
Snow Chief
you can't be calm
talk to me
nothing to talk about with you
Xue Ming Xun
you also
Me and Changyi are lovers
You and I are in violation of the ban
so i will never tell
can you trust me
I
Lin Haoqing will be here soon
you hide inside
come, come, come
Today's pondering cave
It's so lively
Commander Xue didn't say
Don't let anyone in here?
Snow Chief
how to explain
Me and Changyi are lovers
You and I are in violation of the ban
So I'm definitely not going to tell
can you trust me
It must be the law of discipline and the law of private intrusion into the cave of thinking
It's arrogant
wait
I heard about the guardian
Once let the shark speak
a little curious
Just call her to verify
Lord Shaogu's Immortal Servant
It's quite an idea.
Master Shaogu has not spoken yet
convicted law enforcement
Snow leader wants to verify
Does the merman speak?
Can
You are known to everyone
will not be selfish
Three-day ban
You said it yourself
Hope to be careful
avoid falling into reality
All right
Now that the misunderstanding has been resolved
Then let's go
separation
Step aside
what is your purpose
Why do you have to work with me
Snow Chief
if it's about your life
are you trying to get confused
Still willing to risk death to wake up once
the back of your neck
do you have one too?
Frostmark
so what
This is the logo of the Yu Nakaya
Every spiritual master who enters the valley
must be planted by the owner of the grain
To show loyalty to Wanhua Valley
loyalty
Okay
Then I'll take you to see
Loyalty of the Valley of Flowers
what exactly is it
what is this place
why is it so cold
such a wicked place
why
Never heard of it before
This is the Valley of Flowers
a place that was purposely hidden
And all those who are in frost
final home
Muzi
It's the mark on the back of your neck
it's not just a logo
this is its name
it is from
Frost Flower of the Frigid Land
As long as this frost flower is planted
will form a
An unbreakable ban
every time a frost strikes
freeze the meridians
Congealing spiritual power
excruciating pain
Frost is Lin Canglan
Used to control the Valley of Flowers
All Spirit Master's Means
these years
He seems to be reusing me
give me gong
is actually motivating
Frost in my body
I get heartbroken every time
to get the antidote
If so
my frost
How come it's never been the same
Just be obedient
let him send
he will be with you
without knowing
let you take the antidote
But the snow leader
you are willing to live
Are they all manipulated?
The lord of the valley has nurturing grace for me
why should i believe you
Lin Canglan manages the Valley of Thousand Flowers
Hundreds of years
I wonder if Commander Snow still remembers
there's always some sorcerer
will leave suddenly
nature
The lord said
If you don't want to
those who remain
You can remove the frost logo by yourself
Leave
Wanhua Valley will never stop
Commander Ruoxue does not believe
Then try to see if you can remove it
she said frost
It turned out to be true
Commander Snow understands now
no one can crack
This frost prohibits
from where it was punched into your body
from that moment
you have become
A chess piece of Lin Canglan
all who disobey
will eventually be brought here
Trapped in endless ice and eternal sleep
So it's so cold here
called the cold grave
Lord, please forgive me
Forgive me, Lord of the Valley
I beg you to spare me
I don't dare anymore
Valley Lord
please forgive me
remember
This is
The fate of betraying the Valley of Thousand Flowers
Once upon a time, the Valley of Thousand Flowers
is a paradise
But now it has become Lin Canglan
imprison us
Speaking of
we might as well
A fairy from the lower world
come free
The teenager kept the matter a secret for many years
'【He suddenly decided to tell me
because i want a friend
one who will never betray me
Friends who escaped Wanhua Valley together
Haven't you thought
do you want to leave
get out of here and be free
live the life you want
You can also be with your loved ones
stay together
rather than as it is now
and your loved ones
We can only meet secretly in the middle of the night
it's too dangerous
I can't take my life
go on an adventure
I'm not afraid to take risks
I'm just afraid of your life
Always hold in your hands
It's scarier to me than death
Ji Yunhe
I believe in your story
but i don't believe you
You are in love with a shark
I doubt
That scene just now
Haven't you seen it all
I've been with him
just a kiss
I will not part
with my life
in the hands of the unreliable
I want you to prove it to me
your love
That
The spirit of the beast made trouble that day
Changyi has been cared for
are arguing with me
I want to see proof now
then i'm afraid
I'm afraid it couldn't be more appropriate
I can prove to you
I'm in love with him
We are absolutely reliable
Okay
Banned for three days
You can go quietly to see him
But if three days later
I found out you were lying
I won't leave trouble
hit, rush
Okay
Is it over?
who made you hot
Kiss the shark
You are lifting a stone
smash yourself in the foot
if not
We're afraid we can't even save our lives
You really want to talk to the snow in March
allied
Snow March is the strongest
allied with her
Our odds of escaping the Valley of Thousand Flowers
just one more point
But you coaxed well
that fish master?
You lied to him before
just kissed him again
Now you ask again
He plays with you
i'm really worried
big tail fish
You are helpless today
If you and I get through this
In the future, I will give birth to support you
tell you to eat meat every day
Ji Yunhe
make you owe
live with
but
It should be alright
Er Mi
1,
屣 0,
big tail fish
It's been a night
still angry
it matters a lot
really angry
it's so wrong
only
yesterday's events
too urgent
I didn't have time to think about it
really wrong
don't keep your mouth shut
don't be angry
forgive me, okay?
you are
Bitten by a dog
dog
you are so angry
Is it because
that was your first kiss
Then me too
big tail fish
Great fishy smell
you've been locked up for so many days
stinky big tail fish
do you want to take a bath
I will take good care of you
if i can make you happy
will you forgive me
That's it
I promise to make you feel good
absolutely no loss
water is less
, but there is always water
Come, come, let me help you
bring it on
How
with water
I'm in a bad mood
as long as you can forgive me
let me do anything
what do you want
you tell me
The etiquette of apology
really special
Like it
Come
Are you impressed?
fell in
I'll help you
Come
That day Ji Yunhe and Xue Sanyue
doesn't seem right
Is it secretly plotting something?
How
failed again
these three days
How many times have you coaxed him
Good B's good drink female Yuan's
1 have tried
I'm wasting so many spirit stones
the fish
How big is he going to play?
he is finished
okay
The three-day deadline is coming soon
Snow March right now
go to the cave
Check result
lolo
you say me this time
Volunteered to train sharks
is it wrong
I used to be very confident
It's easy to see people's hearts
But this time
encounter big tail fish
I became overwhelmed
should i not this time
Really going to fail
stop
Ji Yunhe I know
never will,
Giving up so easily
you didn't say it before
Do people compare their hearts to their hearts?
You look like that stupid fish
you know for sure
How can he be happy
I am like him
He's the toughest shark
Coincidentally
You are the most hard-backed spiritual master
all involuntarily
unwilling to yield
you two
Just a kind of person
I'll serve you a bowl of sweet soup
After you drink
reinvigorated
Fighting again and thinking about the cave
And this bowl
you take him there
After all, a solitary fish
Unrelated on the shore
miserable
give lolo
you are in this world
the smartest person
I know
this gives you
I figured out a way
no sweet soup
don't drink
Then I drank it myself
big tail fish
Actually, you don't forgive me
also closed eight
I did something wrong
Recently
I was thinking
find something delicious
to coax you
But it's never been legal
finally
just this
Worthless little thing
I don't know any other sharks
I don't know what you like
but
exile
lonely person
most missed
It must be home
the conch
Although not like other magic weapons
so precious
but heard
dagger
hope you are
it can make you happy
you
why
for me
so good
because
because I like you
like you
I love you
I want to be your lover
I want to be with you all the time
But
US
Haven't known each other for a long time
But you help me protect me
have no reservations about me
big tail fish
like this thing
irrespective of the length of time
It's only about you, piece
only about your heart
And you
do you like me
do you think of me now and then
do you want to be with me
or
kiss you
let you think clearly
Father"
and loved ones
want
hug first
talent
kiss
Guarantee
rule
you've always been alone
Feeling like an ally for the first time
how
It's just a cooperation of interests
only for alliance
no friends
US
Now
is not it
called
Do you mean to say that we are in love with each other?
long right
you are not used to it yet
language on shore
This is the book from the shore
There are words and pictures on it
You can quickly get acquainted
language on shore
They say sharks are smart
I believe you will see
When Lolo and I are free
will come to teach
How
did he believe
Yunhe
why are you unhappy
nothing
a bit tired
Then he believed you
Are we
It's time to persuade him to cut off his tail.
So fast
, central
We're not trying to win two games
Is there any chance of winning?
Yunhe, what happened to you?
nothing
continue
I've already thought of a way
What about your collection?
Not entirely useless
It contains
So many delicious and fun
What about you, you go to seduce him
Said there was everything on this shore
I want to have fun with him
He can definitely give up the fishtail
Willing to go ashore with you
I see you as yourself
wanna go out
I am Luo Jin Sang
How could such a person
Anyway you go tell him
The shore is better than the sea
the person I like
should it not
take her back to the sea
The training period has expired,
The next three days are yours
But three days later
It's Lin Haoqing's turn
Thank you Mrs. Xue
Don't get close to me
I have no interest
not one
why
just go ashore
there will be many
Mountain and Seafood
Why not
Shan Zhen is not delicious
There is seafood in the sea
no need to go ashore
wrong
It's only one night
how do you speak
so neat
Yunhe
you two last night
what are you doing
are you
secretly taught him to speak
Did she bite your mouth?
don't talk nonsense
big tail fish
In fact, there is nothing but food on the shore
There are so many fun things
correct
It must be dark in the sea
Can't see anything
It's as bright as the shore
I live in a clam
there is a big pearl
will shine
can illuminate everything
just a pearl
how big can
almost
Just as big as you are
so big
But living in a clam shell
Must be very frustrating
clam shell i live
ten times bigger than here
father's residence
Also bigger than Wanhua Valley
if you like
I can take you back to the sea
But big tail fish
Is it
There's nothing on the shore
Is it something you don't have in the sea?
father said
There are cunning villains on the shore
covet fish tail
no sea
You mermaids are real
so important to this
flashy tail
is that important
fish tail
is the source of my power
Except three we voluntarily
otherwise
even with a knife
both, will break
but
Once the tail is broken
Spiritual power will be lost
and
never go back to the sea
lose tail
The consequences are so serious
Can't even go home
worker docking
' : Yo
Ran.
burning water
betrayal
So my father said
even dead
, , 2 " , 3
years 7 \
Nor can the tail be cut off,
Yunhe
Or we both have long tails
Let's go to sea together
I have something to do
we go back first
what else can you do
lolo
she is angry
It's me
said the wrong thing
but
Once the tail is broken
Spiritual power will be big
and
never go back to the sea
shark man docked tail
Burning into the water
The clan regards as back' against
from the very beginning
my goal
Isn't it just training clothes to hang people?
why do you hear
he will lose his tail
back, hog
I'm so sad
I'm not as good as you
Is this a fish?
You're not as good as my cat
But I heard this mortal world
Men's tillage and women's weaving
Fang is the rule
We don't have this rule
as long as your loved one likes it
We do laundry and cook
All are sweet
say more
I'm so weak
If you don't have a little cooking skills
How to be worthy of you
Snow Chief
Yunhe said
we are allies
should help each other
just for each other
I'm not going to help her
i'm not looking for you
I am looking for separation
You asked me to teach Ji Yunhe
how to make long
like her more
more I can't say
anyhow
Only Changyi prefers Yunhe
would be willing to go ashore for her
and
Among us
the most emotional
don't hang [is that you?
why do you say that
You can even win the snow in March
There must be a way, right?
If it really doesn't work
Then I will give you the spirit stone
You're so weak anyway
should also need
OK little butterfly
Save your spirit stone
Just because you trust me
I'll help with this
but
This teaching Ji Yunhe is useless
Really need to learn
It's that stupid fish
cat to teach fish
can he agree
you don't understand
疋疋疋
you know you know
Kindness as donkey liver
I knew so
I won't teach you
You and I have old grudges
how can you look at me
You and Ji Yunhe as soon as possible
Reconciled
I can bring March as soon as possible
Escape from the Valley of Flowers
Moreover
Ji Yunhe is in trouble with Er
don't you suffer
you don't want to see her
early recovery
that bright smile?
you are so weak
how to teach me
about love
Is it useful to fight?
When I met March
Not nearly killed by her
then
I am king of mountains
admired
then
March and a Beast
return from fighting
seriously injured
Passing by Qiongling Peak
I met by accident
lecher
Don't miss
let go
A beauty that is hard to come across
How can you let it go?
I just happen to be missing a Mrs.
I don't know beauty
would you like to
won't be dead
This is Hantan Lingyu soup
after
I cook for you every day, okay?
beauty
beauty, don't hit me
It doesn't look good if you fall down.
take care of you
I promise
after
I will cook you fish soup every day
OK
When the injury is getting better in March
my men
discovered her existence
Everyone is afraid to take in the Spirit Master
will bring trouble
So force me to take March
Ferocious beast trapped by the female
Kiss the Master of the Spirit
hand it over hand it over
To her is a psychic
hand her over
let her out
hand it over, hand it over
She is the sorcerer
hand over
you protect her
I don't care if she's a spiritual master
She is my dear baby
If you want to fight, come at me
We also put up with you, you rubbish leader
For a long time
let's go
this broken place
neither do we
walk around
beauty
Today's fish soup is very fresh
I thought
After March
never come back
Also decided to leave Qiongling Peak
to ask for another life
beauty
I'm not dreaming
how are you back
Without Qiongling Peak
where else can you go
stop-and-go
always find a place
Too bad it's gone
I can't catch you as Mrs. Yazhai
beauty
I'll be with you
I'm here to save you
just got kicked out
you are responsible
How to be responsible
Naturally
Serve with good wine and good meat
coaxing sweetly
From the ends of the earth
accompany
In fact, there is no good wine or meat.
I'm well fed
as long as you keep me
i take care of you
I make fish for you every day
OK
are you talking
How