(two
deep sea
merman
Heart broken like a mirror
Yunhe
Yunhe has an accident
Lin Haoqing knows that sharks are afraid of heat
to force him to speak
Don't hesitate to turn the cave of thinking into a melting pot
He's so stupid
The mermaid would definitely rather die than give in.
What now
look
The allusions say
the merman the fisherman will stranded
send back to the sea
The story of the shark carrying a pearl to report
Saying that the sharks are grateful
affectionate
Since Lin Haoqing
to gamble with mermaids
he's going to hurt
then i want to save
Shaoguzhu
Come in
Disciplinary Protection Law has been with Qu Xiaoxing
I'm off to think about it.
The guards of the Thinking Cave have all withdrawn.
leave a few pretense
Yes
Why did Master Shaogu send the news
Intentionally let it go to Ji Yunhe
It's not right for her
Do you have a chance to show the sharks?
If you are Ji Yunhe
how would you show up
Of course, to save the sharks
Regain the trust of the sharks
If you want a six
must have the
main mouth
help him escape the cave
Today's move by the Shaogu lord
It's not a mermaid
It's Ji Yunhe
It is a felony to release prisoners
if today
can hold her
No one after that
Can compete with Shaogu master
Yunhe
You must not be fooled
big tail fish
Yunhe
let me tell you
This is Lin Haoqing's conspiracy
let's go
I know
you know you're breaking in
do you know
Private release of prisoners is a felony
If caught by Lin Haoqing
he killed you on the spot
no one in the whole valley
can pick his fault
lolo
You know me and Lin Haoqing
the biggest difference?
My bottom line is my life
I can't die
say more
Let the merman see that I gave my life to save him
He will let go
have the opportunity to be educated by us
It's good for the merman, good for us
be your fairy
I've been down for eight lifetimes
You are carrying Hyosung
Help me lure Lin Haoqing away
and his guards
I
I walked with the big tail fish
I carry him
So am I at a loss?
go
Ji Yunhe
you better come back safe
Come with me
You do not trust me
Who told you to overturn my Ningxue Wan
I won't let you go easily
come with me
stop
Qu Xiaoxing, stop
Dharma protector
protector
where is she
why you
why can't it be me
My Hyosung and I are good friends
Good Relationship
I'm tired and he carries me
What's up
Then why are you wearing Dharma-protecting clothes?
cover your face
Are you kidding me?
that is
I made a bet with Luo Jinsang
I said she was normal
no feature
Just cover your face
no one will recognize her
this is not
She is not a guardian
I borrowed a coat to block it and try it
You really didn't recognize
how
jokes between friends
you have to take care
It's hard to think about the cave
go
sure
well dressed
why did you just
Said that I'm normal and uncharacteristic
I'm in such a good shape
you can't see it
when is this
you still care about this
never mind
don't compare with you
Yunhe should have taken the merman
brought out
I go to them
hold
do you feel any better
Do not be afraid
Wanhua Valley alarm bell masterpiece
The defense will be several times more than usual
with your current physical strength
Not suitable for fighting with them
Lin Haoqing will be here soon
hide yourself
you just hide here
no matter what happens outside
don't go out
still can't figure it out
why should i help you
probably because
Are we in a similar situation?
big tail fish
you should live in water
That is your freest
the most beautiful
・・・”.
That Lin Haoqing
what did I tell you
But there is one thing we do
we all want
live in this hell
so i don't want you to die
start worrying about me
Also ask the discipline protection law to come out
Can't escape
you leave me
I have dealt with Lin Haoqing for so many years
i have my way
millet
you will call my name
You are not a little dumb
you believe me
i will protect you
no Xuanhe
solve,
, love
And we have rules on the shore
debt must be repaid
Before paying off my Ningxue Pills
You are not allowed to sneak away
Merman, inch [right
The sharks keep their promises faithfully
I believe you
What does the master of Shaogu do?
Disciplinary Law
Don't blame me for not reminding you
Prisoner of Xian Ji's private release
a felony
To force me out
Master Shaogu this time
took a lot of thought
By now
Still obsessed with winning
You give up training now
I'm begging for you, father
Shaogu master is good at calculation
But you read it wrong
The mermaid is not here
comer search
bold
my place
You can enter if you want
what if my order
If Shaogu mainly pushes hard
Then don't blame me for being ruthless
Yunhe
Ruined
So many people can't beat it
you stinky snake
so brave
Dare to take action against our discipline protection law
Ji Yunhe's private collection of sharks
break valley rules
should be killed
what happened
Mr. Qing Shu
What's up
I was about to go in and search
Disciplinary law can do this
Don't hide it, Mr. Qing Shu
I'm relieved when you come
The merman is indeed in my room
pen,
Xuan He is not a mermaid
The young master of the valley is pressing too hard
I'm afraid the merman will be in danger
So this is the way to go
Please also ask Lord Qingshu to inform the owner of the valley
Yunhe has successfully made the merman speak
really
Now the merman is not very stable
Why don't you take him first
stay in my room
Otherwise I'm afraid of sharks
Once resisted
another one
time-consuming fighting
It is about the order of the fairy godmother
It needs to be decided by the owner of the valley and the elders
Also please Shaogu master and discipline protection law
Follow me to Lifengtang
9 consecutive
Yunhe Luoluo
you like mermaid
don't let anyone in
don't let him out
be careful
Disciplinary Law
the shark
Since you have been trained to speak
why are you
Why don't you bring him to see us?
This mermaid is extremely afraid of the Shaogu Lord
If you rush to bring him
The shark was so frightened that he could no longer speak
Wouldn't that be a waste of time?
I have let Luo Jinsang
look at this shark
never let him go
so
This time it's the master of Shaogu
act wrong
Haoqing acts recklessly
willing to be punished
Yunhe
you act like this
But it's for rewarding me
Appreciation of nature is to beg
After all, for training sharks
I will give up
already spent a lot
But that's not the most important
Then tell me
what is most important
Yunhe Yuling
has its own method
Now that I've made the merman speak
Prove my way
is productive
I also hope that the owner of the valley agrees
don't let anyone else
Punish the sharks
Valley Lord
The shark speaks
Only the Disciplinary Law witnesses
Besides, there is no evidence
rashly reward
I'm afraid it's unfair
What Elder Donglian said is very true
Wanhuagu behaves strictly
i can't
break the rules
Yunhe will have a way to prove it
See you tomorrow
Okay
then tomorrow
I'll personally take someone with you
Verify that the merman can speak
if what you say is true
then your condition
Natural Satisfaction in the Valley
But if you dare to lie
I will never show you any mercy
Yunhe obeys
Shaogu owners don't have to worry
Ji Yunhe is just
temporarily prevail
if I
Who told you to take action against Ji Yunhe?
Ji Yunhe does everything in your way
Why don't we take the opportunity to get rid of her?
Lord Shaogu, don't worry
subordinates will ensure
She can't do it tomorrow
By the time
The position of Valley Master is naturally yours
what else did you do
you are hook snake
blood is poisonous
You refine poison with blood
where is it used
Tempered on the hidden weapon
Just scratch the skin
I won't survive tonight
Ji Yunhe's life
you don't have the right to touch
For the Lord of Shaogu
Si Yu would rather die than regret
antidote
Yunhe
how's it going
Did you win the first game?
Lin Canglan doesn't believe it
Description day
Come and see the merman opening for yourself
Gotta keep him overnight
lolo
you let me sleep first
talk later
Yunhe, what's wrong with you
the wound is poisonous
Siyu that bastard
go
I'll help you in to rest
Yunhe
Yunhe, wake up
Yunhe, you promised me
Yunhe will be fine
Yunhe, you can't die, Yunhe
you promised me
Yunhe who wants to escape together
I don't want you to die, Yunhe
Yunhe
Wake up, Yunhe
Yunhe, don't die, Yunhe
Yunhe
big tail fish
what are you doing
Yunhe
Mermaid scales can detoxify
But how do I remember
The book seems to say
This scale can't be pulled out
Otherwise it will
big tail fish
Thank you
but also sorry
soon you will know
I'm not worth it
Yunhe
i found it
Although this mermaid scale has a miraculous effect
But when you pull it up, it's heart-wrenching
That's why this guy
bite the heart
I feel this fish now
not bad
mouth
Yunhe
go and have a look
do not talk
he's awake
big tail fish
Does it still hurt?
Actually I save you
just a little effort
you don't have to be for me
spend so much
you save me
i give you medicine
It turns out that you never spoke up before
not used to
The language of the shore
this is easy to do
I saw in the book 'inch
I want him to speak fluently
have to bite his mouth
I help you
What crooked books are you reading?
don't scare him
Thank you
you are welcome
He's quite polite
big tail fish
You were brought to the Valley of Thousand Flowers
I've always wanted to go home
Actually, I want to leave too
this ghost place
better
let's run away
I am familiar with the road of Wanhua Valley
all defense
all enchantments
There are also bans
It's just that my injury isn't healed
You're putting so much effort into it
they are many
We have little chance
you have a good sleep
I'll be ready tomorrow
we're gonna run away
where do you rest early
big tail fish
let's go
what
Yunhe
That should be his name
The merman only treats close relatives
tell a friend
friend
Then let's get to know each other again
My name is Ji Yunhe
Ji Yunhe
Yunhe
Danger
you act so well
Coax that shark
Pull out the scales for you
Do you have a conscience?
I'm really hurt
All right
no
What's wrong with you
The sharks spoke up
why are you not happy
you said if tomorrow
He found out that he had been deceived
will it be sad
Maybe
but
If he can obey Xian Ji
Be a good fairy
Maybe it can be delicious and spicy
Can fish tanks be made of gold?
Maybe even better than the sea
Right
at this time
Don't make mistakes
Go in and watch the merman
Okay
victory is imminent
Brother is still in the mood
hang out
My brother is here to give me medicine
You are in the limelight today
Any accident before tomorrow
Yanaka will think it was me who started
I'm just taking precautions
Throw it away if you don't need it
Brother, I'm afraid you misunderstood me
Yunhe just wants to win the game
Never thought to frame anyone
must win
Pay attention to size
Avoid playing with fire
Yunhe, are you alright?
He didn't bully you
fine
It's me who's got some grass and trees.
why are you out again
Yunhe I'm afraid
what are you afraid of
I'm afraid I'll look at him again
will let him go
tomorrow
compensation
Yunhe
big tail fish
I am sorry
Known to be wrong
subordinates do not understand
I don't know how to admit my mistake
How long have you been with me
Master of the Valley
Accept the subordinates to serve as immortals
It's been a hundred years
Then you should know my temperament
I hate people making their own decisions
without my permission
You dare to touch Ji Yunhe again
a hair
i won't let you go
Understand
Master Shaogu vs Ji Yunhe
what are you thinking
you to her
abnormal
How dare you talk nonsense
i want your life
Thinking is just
For the sake of Master Shaogu
not tomorrow
Let Ji Yunhe succeed
she won't make it
Master Shaogu has a plan
rest assured
all explained
After you lure the merman to speak
we'll start right away
won't let him escape
won this time
Don't forget to invite the brothers to drink
Hyosung
give me a hand
Waiting to catch the shark
you got me too
don't let him find out
we are a gang
he has lost his freedom
if he knows
betrayed
will be more sad
What's up
you used to be a spirit
But never so much thought
this shark
what's so special
can be anything special
What makes him special is that
He is the fairy servant who wants to serve Xian Ji
if you offend him
There will be good fruits to eat in the future.
didn't you say
become
Snow leads to the West Mountain
Catch the beast
Now the war department, I have the final say
this requirement
Wrap it around me, Qu Xiaoxing
Yunhe
Twenty-one. Eleven
The merman is in my room right now
Please also have a look outside
I will prove it to you
big tail fish
wait for me here
Yunhe, are you alright?
War Department Snow March
see Valley Lord
Okay
March is indeed my Valley of Flowers
first soldier
only one person
the spirit of the beast
all annihilated
The West Mountain Lion has been captured
The elixir is here
Father
Snow Chief
Disciplinary Law
not please everyone
To witness the merman speak?
This is
It's time for my brother
Valley Lord
Wanhua Valley has enchantment
How can there be evil spirits raging
There must be something strange about this
I trained a beast in the valley before
He has done many evils without repenting
I have obeyed the order of the fairy
destroy its elixir
Maybe he's too hostile
Turned into an evil spirit and wandered in the valley
just unlucky
Ruined the shark training plan of the junior sister
Just a few wandering spirits
in the overall situation
The most important thing today is
The old man wants to listen to this merman
Yunhe
Would he like to speak?
宀 ~
Hiroichi
big tail fish
today's event
I'll explain to you later
can you do me a favor
±7 ±7 - 7 u1 u1 u1
Yunhe
Looks like you're still in a hurry
It is Yunhe who is greedy
Disappointed the boss
left the cave
you had a chance to escape
but rather
The way of Ji Yunhe
so stupid
Now Ji Yunhe can't protect himself
I'm afraid I can't take care of you
do it yourself
big tail fish
you should live in water
That is your freest
The most complete and most beautiful
Although I don't know Lin Haoqing
what did I say to you
But there is one thing we do
want to be in this damn place
live
so i don't want you to die
Before the discipline protection law, he uttered wild words
now
But the bamboo basket is empty.
Disciplinary protection law in order to train the merman
Disregarding the rules of the valley
Hidden sharks greedily advance
I want my father to order
Get her out of the training shark
Even if I don't do law enforcement
continue to train sharks
Ji Yunhe you
Let Yunhe and Shaoguzhu
Let's train sharks together
From Fairy's Order
Can Yunhe quit
Only Xian Ji herself
Are you elders?
Are you planning to take over?
Yunhe
do not talk
Ji Yunhe
Are you threatening the Valley Master?
Yunhe is just thinking
If the master of Shaogu wins without force
How to convince the public in the future
Father
The game of training sharks
Haoqing will win by virtue of his ability
Don't break the rules
Yunhe
Since you want to be thorough and transparent
I'm not that unfair
Then you will be with Hao Qing
Continue to participate in the training
remember
I care about results
I'll be off for a few days
About the training shark
Always have a rule
Tell me in March
subordinates feel
It's better to let Ji Hufa and Shaoguzhu
Three days of training per person
when the time comes
can no longer interfere
Fairness
If there is a favoritism
Severely punished
Okay
that thing
It's up to you to supervise in March.
After I leave
hope to get
good news for you
scorpion
why
what why
The shark has lost trust in you
you have no chance
why don't you just stop
he didn't believe me
I didn't surrender to you
we tie
why should i quit
Do your best to protect the law, okay?
Don't compete with me
Can't you just give up that merman?
I didn't fight with you
i just think
if i were to quit
Such a stupid fish
will fall into your hands and be beaten
I'm so upset
Then I can only be with you
keep fighting
Valley Lord
Why obey today
The words of Na Ji Yunhe
Agree to let her continue training
Haoqing can only rely on
own strength
win Ji Yunhe
to be justifiable
people's heart
But
Now is the critical moment for training sharks
your retreat
In case that Ji Yunhe
got lucky
This
no problem
As long as Hao Qing is ruthless
In the end, no matter who is responsible
It's all thanks to the Valley of Flowers
Yunhe
how long
Spiritualists
punish him again
The things we lied about
Being disturbed by that Lin Haoqing
all exposed
Can he still trust you?
in case you go in
what if he hit you
If he doesn't believe me at all
won't listen to me
catch up
Just go in now
his trust in me
how deep
go out first
here is me
Bad law enforcement
what's so bad about this
I let you out
I have a problem
Sharks are related to the future of Wanhua Valley
this responsibility
Law enforcement can't afford it
these three days
It's my training time
This is my way of doing things
Others don't need to interfere
It is a misunderstanding to let the shark privately
But you did break the rules of the valley
Three-day ban is required as punishment
go out
what if i don't go
Valley Master has orders
Severely punished
We can't beat Yunhe
to beat
Snow Chief
But the owner of the Valley of Ten Thousand Flowers is below
Mana cultivation is the first person
always enforce the law impartially
Sisters have been punished
I'll leave the training of the shark to my brother.
Snow rules this time
exercise supervisory duties
quite hard
This is Shaogu Master
A little thank you gift for you
Ji Yunhe Xun Shark was frustrated
The spirits of those beasts who spoil the situation
Should be out.
Shaogu Lord's Hair
Privately defending evil spirits is also prohibited
Master Shaogu is the same as Ji Yunhe
to prevent fraud
Thinking Cave Banned
No one is allowed to enter
two
please
so so
'The hard-earned snow has ruled
Snow Chief
Yun He also said goodbye first.
Lord of March
didn't say
don't have to come here
come with you
lolo
you are so different from this
What's your impression
Do you mean Xue Sanyue's Immortal Servant?
Lynx
The side branch of the mythical beast Lu Wu
My character is not as good as me
Doesn't look as good as me
weak spiritual power
It's far from me anyway
What's up
nothing to go
Yunhe
why did you bring me here
messed up now
Except for Lin Haoqing
One more snow in March
I have to figure out a way
how to get her
Otherwise, how to coax Changyi back?
think about it
But you come outside the house in Snow March
what are you staring at her for
want to fight
you can't beat her
to win someone
Why don't you have to beat him?
Everyone has weaknesses
Snow March is no exception
Not always
Xue March has been gifted since childhood
By Lin Canglan
Personally selected into the Valley of Flowers
she was never
Can move but not speak
And she follows the rules
never banned
It doesn't seem to have any weaknesses
Yunhe
I advise you not to fight with her.
you want to win this contest
Just to escape
Since bitter meat
if it doesn't work for that fish
why don't you try
other way
What if it wasn't all bittersweet?
What's the meaning
if someone owes you a debt
will you forgive him
roasted him
so now
I still owe an explanation
Even if I have to train him
I don't like Ji Yunhe either.
owe someone a favor
But
Why is this alienation sneaky
I have a secret in my heart
nature sneaky
what do you mean
if this thing
Exactly as I guessed
That snow in March
But it's interesting
What do you mean
this place
How can there be a boundary?
Go in and see if you don't know
separation