Your Highness did not report it as soon as possible
It is indeed the handmaiden's fault
But now that you know
Why don't you stop it at once
Be stubborn and refuse to listen to advice
Even if her hand is broken
It is also self-inflicted
If you really don't care,
Why bother to send medicine
Who delivered the medicine
I've never been here before
I haven't sent any medicine
If you talk nonsense again,
You are the only one who asks
Yes, it's from me
It's all from me
Continue
Yes
Let's get started
Meng Shang Shi
Please allow me to deliver the meal
Zi Jin
Although there was Guo Guifei before,
Turn around on your behalf
But it will eventually make the dragon unhappy
You go now
I'm afraid it won't help
Go ahead
Yes
Meng Shang went to deliver food
Can Your Majesty not be angry
I hope so
Your Majesty
I am facing Emperor Taizu
There was a drought in Haozhou in a small time
Blessed by a kind-hearted person
Cabbage and tofu soup to survive the famine
Today's Shangyuan Festival
Handmaiden dares to offer this meal
Your Majesty, please taste it
Your Majesty
When Emperor Taizu was here,
You must drink this every day
Pearl Jade White Jade Soup
It's been a long time
I'll never see it again in the palace
In my opinion
Why don't you order it
Make this dish a royal meal
So that the descendants of the royal family can
Remember the hardships of ancestors' entrepreneurship
Do not forget the sufferings of people's lives
OK, let's take this example
Spread to officials
Yes
Your Majesty
This sweet-scented osmanthus skin silk
It's a good leather silk
Stir-fry with egg yolk
Orange in color
Just like cinnamon
It can also nourish and benefit qi
Eliminate upset and stuffy
This white jade collects treasures
Hidden Gankun is fresh and elegant
Tender and delicious
This orange crab
It is a combination of orange fragrance and crab freshness
It is not the season of eating crabs and enjoying chrysanthemums
Yisheng new wine chrysanthemum
Orange crab
In fact, it is so beautiful
Mandarin duck fish fan made by Hu Shangshi
Of course it's wonderful
But this golden dragon spins silk
Root silver wire
They are all made of fresh and tender fish
This meal is more beneficial to the five internal organs
Effect of tonifying deficiency and invigorating qi
Your Majesty, if you use a bite,
I'm afraid before putting chopsticks
I still don't realize that the golden plate is empty
Handmaiden talks a lot
Come on, go down after that
Yes
Fortunately, it is the father
If this is Grandpa Huang
You can't drive out at random
Look at this boasting
I'd like to try it
How delicious it is
Your Majesty left
Golden Dragon Spinning Silk and Orange Crab
What a pity
Hu Shangshi is still slightly better
Zi Jin
Why do you want to
Deliver food in person
The kitchen was injured and struggled to cook
Your Majesty witnessed it with his own eyes
Maybe it will be merciful
Allow me to finish
What are you doing
Go to the royal demonstration for the next dish
Yes
Your hand
Nothing
I went
Rest assured of food
I can't think of Meng Shangshi's knife skill
So exquisite
It can be called the best in the world
This kind of pot
It is based on eight kinds of fresh ingredients
Main material
But what it tests
It is not an exquisite knife skill
It's fresh ingredients
With the natural taste of food
Original flavor
Yesterday Guanglu Temple
Emerald soup bag sent
Seemingly exquisite in appearance
But it makes people thirsty after eating
Just because it puts too much seasoning
It can be seen that blindly pursuing
Precious ingredients and skills
Will only put the cart before the horse
Fresh boiling soup micro-rinse
The real purpose
Is to discover
The taste of the food itself
After all, what diners eat
It's the food itself
Instead of cooking skills and seasonings
Your Highness is right
Guanglu Temple Office
It's getting more and more perfunctory
They should be punished well
Am I
What are you talking silly about again
This fragrance
I can't help but boast
When is Henan flavor the same as Sichuan flavor
It's getting mixed up
Your Majesty
This meal originated from the Eight Treasures of Zhou Dynasty
Called a cannon dolphin
Fill the pork belly with dates
Wrap it with reeds and grass mud
With fierce artillery
Then peel and wipe
Into the tripod to prevent water
Steam for three days and nights to eat
Handmaiden thought
Although this method has been maintained,
The original taste of food
But the loss is complicated
Try to use a new method today
Shake and bake with charcoal over slow fire
The taste is better than before
Your Majesty
I heard that this suckling pig
After roasting,
The color is amber
The entrance skin is crisp and the meat is tender
Delicious anomaly
My brother is also looking forward to it
What's that
Kirin pattern
Your Majesty, this is a unicorn pattern
Your Majesty
Shangyuan Festival is auspicious in this world
Congratulations, Your Majesty. Congratulations, Your Majesty
Hu Shang Shi
In order to prepare this suckling pig,
You put a lot of thought into it, didn't you
They are trying to please me
This pig
Maybe what pattern
It can burn out
Your Majesty is wise
After this meal has been improved,
It's called Tuwen suckling pig
Come
Exemption from gifts
Thank Your Majesty
Crown Princess
In case the kitchen is not careful
The pig burned a golden dragon pattern
What should I do
Father
Your Majesty
Send my father back
Zhan Ji
Don't let the assassin go
Chen Wu
Zhan Ji
Save the driver quickly
This way
Bold
Why don't you get out of here
Quick and quick
Help me, help me
Come quickly
Your Majesty
This way
Father
You go away
Waiting for you to rescue me
My life is over
Quick Xuan Tai Yi Quick Xuan Tai Yi
Your Excellency
Your Majesty
Love Princess
It scared me to death
Scared me to death
Innocent
Are you all right
See your majesty is safe
My brother is relieved
Back to the palace
Help me back to the palace
Hold on a little longer
Your Highness, are you hurt
Zhan Ji
Nothing
Go back after sending your mother
Yes
Let's go
Chen Wu
Aftermath
Yes
Hu Shang Shi
Fuck off
Your Highness
You're hurt
I'll report it now
Stop
Your Highness
Mother tonight
Has been frightened
Don't worry her any more
Go and find Sheng Yin
Just show me
OK, I'll go now
Your Highness, although it is a skin injury
But the wound is narrow and deep
I will be your highness later
Prescribe a prescription for stopping bleeding and invigorating qi
And
It is estimated that there will be a high fever in the middle of the night
Serve carefully
Never be careless
Father-in-law Yuan has arrived for supper
Your Highness
Empress Empress
Asked someone to bring supper
How much would you like to eat
Wait
Your Highness
Your Highness is badly hurt
Dietary aspects
Don't neglect carelessness
The head here is
What's the matter
Your Highness
There is a bowl of rice congee in it
There is also a peach cake for enriching blood
In addition
There are also two light side dishes
Peach Crisp Blood-enriching Cake
Warming spleen and stomach and enriching blood
Okay, this is good
Kunning Palace
Do you know your highness is hurt
I forgot to prepare
Ingredients for breakfast tomorrow
You go back first
What's the matter
For whom to prepare
You know it in your own heart
You went back
Go back
Come out
Yao canon meal
Hu Shangshi, let me give you a message
I knew you'd come
My support for you
Sincerely everywhere
Coming
You should have come to see me
The skin of this gun dolphin is crisp
The meat is fresh and tender
It is indeed a
A rare delicacy
I thought I had been suffering for many years
I can finally be proud
Unexpectedly
Life
You've already lost
I choose
Pearl Jade White Jade Soup
In fact, it is for
Dispel Your Majesty's prejudice
A real competition
After all, it is necessary to return to
The food itself
You choose this dish
It's nothing more than a peculiar pattern
To please Your Majesty
That and the officials who offer good fortune
What difference does it make
Pigeon soup
And
Coconut juice and red dates
Coconut juice instead of dripping water
The soup base is really nourishing and sweet
Sweet but not greasy
Not bad
The sour taste of this fish soup is
Clear rice soup soaked with glutinous rice in advance
Pour it into a bamboo tube
Heat it over and over again
After natural fermentation
To get sour soup for appetizing and invigorating spleen
So it seems
Nine different soup bases
It must be painstaking
Each has its own merits
Sure
Shine on you is better than blue
It's not wrong for me to lose
Sit down
He Shu told me
Before you left the palace,
Have something to tell me
Do you hate me
You helped me
But it also ruined my right hand
I'm interested in you
Have nothing to say
All this I've done
It's all about atonement
When I first entered Hu's house,
It coincides with the birth of the third sister
She was born
It's only over three pounds
Everyone says she won't live long
Even my father and grandmother
I also think she is a burden
I'm always afraid of my sister
She can't grow up safely
I just made a mess of it
Told a lie
What lies did you tell
I say to everyone
The day the third sister was born
I see red and white gas coming out of the house
It didn't take long
This is in the local area
Passed to Chery
Third sister was lucky enough to survive
Who would have thought
A child's joke
In the end, it became the Hu clan
A carefully planned beginning
Third sister has been weak since childhood
Have been rejected a lot
Said the father
I went into the palace
You can avoid a corvee
I was
I already said kiss
But for her sake
I said yes anyway
Sell it, sell it
The daughter of the Hu family
How is it different from goods
Every night I do
It's all carved here
I can't stop for a moment
Do you know why
Because I'm afraid
I'm lonely
I can't even look in the mirror
Because I don't want to see
The face in the mirror
How cold and disgusting it has become
You told me everything
Aren't you afraid I'll tell on it
The first emperor said it was auspicious
Is auspicious
Everything you've lost
I can't come back.
All sins are because of me
If you want to blame me, blame me
Hate you, hate me
It has nothing to do with the Crown Princess
If you hate it
You kill me
Don't bring her into trouble
The source of this evil
It's all because of me
You promised
Once you lose
Leave the Forbidden City
Never enter the kitchen for life
Take care all the way
Zi Jin
Crown Princess
My sister sincerely prayed to heaven
May you have peace and joy all your life
This wish is enough
It's late at night
I'll leave first
Why do you want to do this
You tampered with the seasoning
Why did the design let Hu lose
Once upon a time
I blame you
Hate you
But I can't deny it all the time
My heart
I have been looking forward to the reunion of mother and daughter
But the hearts of the palace are sinister
My existence
It will only become your weakness
You disown me
I don't blame you
But I can't stand it
Others hurt you
So
This is what I can think of
The only thing I can do for you
Father married his stepmother
Have younger siblings
No one cares about me anymore
So
Regardless of all the hardships,
I must come to you, too
Looking for that
The man who gave me life
Go home
Mother
When I first entered the palace
I am reckless and ignorant
It will only become your burden
But it's different now
I can do anything
I can help you
Can be your arm
I must be better than anyone else
Well done
Mother
Are you sure you can't recognize me
It's you
Let me ask you something
How did Master die
The book left for me is not finished yet
Master is not
People who give up halfway
She sacrificed herself
It's all about protecting you
And you're trying to cover up the truth
And kill people
Are you still a human being
She knows too much about me
Living is a hidden danger after all
Who can guarantee that
She will never reveal secrets
So you killed her
Right
You know the truth now
How is it
Do you want to kill me
Avenge her
Do it
Kill me
Thank you very much
Give me a ride
Crown Princess
Hu Shangshi only ordered the handmaiden
Go and invite Yao Dian to dinner
The rest of the handmaiden really didn't know
Please pardon the Crown Princess
Go down
Yes
Stop crying
You see
How nice this is
Sister sister
Sister Miss
You wait for me, miss
Miss and sister
Wait for my lady to go back
Don't leave me
Go home, miss. Don't leave me
Sister
Have you all heard about it
Hu Shang Shi
Hu Shangshi committed suicide
Really
Keep your voice down
Guanglu Temple
Miyagi's men are here
This kind of thing is the most taboo in the palace
Don't let it be mentioned
What's the matter
Nothing
Kill down bridges
I made a deal with Meng Shangshi
Before my right hand recovers
I'll stay in the still food bureau
Do chores
You can also help the little palace maidservants
The concubines of the prince
It's no better than being here
It's strong to get supercilious look at people
Give it to me
Don't do it
You don't want splendor and wealth
Nest here and bask in Chinese cabbage
What for
Do you see it
My face is green with anger
It's greener than this Chinese cabbage
Su Yuehua wants to cross me
It's not that easy
Zi Jin