Your Highness
You're hurt
I'll report it now
Stop
Your Highness
Mother tonight
Has been frightened
Don't worry her any more
Go and find Sheng Yin
Just show me
OK, I'll go now
Your Highness, although it is a skin injury
But the wound is narrow and deep
I will be your highness later
Prescribe a prescription for stopping bleeding and invigorating qi
And
It is estimated that there will be a high fever in the middle of the night
Serve carefully
Never be careless
Father-in-law Yuan has arrived for supper
Your Highness
Empress Empress
Asked someone to bring supper
How much would you like to eat
Wait
Your Highness
Your Highness is badly hurt
Dietary aspects
Don't neglect carelessness
The head here is
What's the matter
Your Highness
There is a bowl of rice congee in it
There is also a peach cake for enriching blood
In addition
There are also two light side dishes
Peach Crisp Blood-enriching Cake
Warming spleen and stomach and enriching blood
Okay, this is good
Kunning Palace
Do you know your highness is hurt
I forgot to prepare
Ingredients for breakfast tomorrow
You go back first
What's the matter
For whom to prepare
You know it in your own heart
You went back
Go back
Come out
Yao canon meal
Hu Shangshi, let me give you a message
I knew you'd come
My support for you
Sincerely everywhere
Coming
You should have come to see me
The skin of this gun dolphin is crisp
The meat is fresh and tender
It is indeed a
A rare delicacy
I thought I had been suffering for many years
I can finally be proud
Unexpectedly
Life
You've already lost
I choose
Pearl Jade White Jade Soup
In fact, it is for
Dispel Your Majesty's prejudice
A real competition
After all, it is necessary to return to
The food itself
You choose this dish
It's nothing more than a peculiar pattern
To please Your Majesty
That and the officials who offer good fortune
What difference does it make
Pigeon soup
And
Coconut juice and red dates
Coconut juice instead of dripping water
The soup base is really nourishing and sweet
Sweet but not greasy
Not bad
The sour taste of this fish soup is
Clear rice soup soaked with glutinous rice in advance
Pour it into a bamboo tube
Heat it over and over again
After natural fermentation
To get sour soup for appetizing and invigorating spleen
So it seems
Nine different soup bases
It must be painstaking
Each has its own merits
Sure
Shine on you is better than blue
It's not wrong for me to lose
Sit down
He Shu told me
Before you left the palace,
Have something to tell me
Do you hate me
You helped me
But it also ruined my right hand
I'm interested in you
Have nothing to say
All this I've done
It's all about atonement
When I first entered Hu's house,
It coincides with the birth of the third sister
She was born
It's only over three pounds
Everyone says she won't live long
Even my father and grandmother
I also think she is a burden
I'm always afraid of my sister
She can't grow up safely
I just made a mess of it
Told a lie
What lies did you tell
I say to everyone
The day the third sister was born
I see red and white gas coming out of the house
It didn't take long
This is in the local area
Passed to Chery
Third sister was lucky enough to survive
Who would have thought
A child's joke
In the end, it became the Hu clan
A carefully planned beginning
Third sister has been weak since childhood
Have been rejected a lot
Said the father
I went into the palace
You can avoid a corvee
I was
I already said kiss
But for her sake
I said yes anyway
Sell it, sell it
The daughter of the Hu family
How is it different from goods
Every night I do
It's all carved here
I can't stop for a moment
Do you know why
Because I'm afraid
I'm lonely
I can't even look in the mirror
Because I don't want to see
The face in the mirror
How cold and disgusting it has become
You told me everything
Aren't you afraid I'll tell on it
The first emperor said it was auspicious
Is auspicious
Everything you've lost
I can't come back.
All sins are because of me
If you want to blame me, blame me
Hate you, hate me
It has nothing to do with the Crown Princess
If you hate it
You kill me
Don't bring her into trouble
The source of this evil
It's all because of me
You promised
Once you lose
Leave the Forbidden City
Never enter the kitchen for life
Take care all the way
Zi Jin
Crown Princess
My sister sincerely prayed to heaven
May you have peace and joy all your life
This wish is enough
It's late at night
I'll leave first
Why do you want to do this
You tampered with the seasoning
Why did the design let Hu lose
Once upon a time
I blame you
Hate you
But I can't deny it all the time
My heart
I have been looking forward to the reunion of mother and daughter
But the hearts of the palace are sinister
My existence
It will only become your weakness
You disown me
I don't blame you
But I can't stand it
Others hurt you
So
This is what I can think of
The only thing I can do for you
Father married his stepmother
Have younger siblings
No one cares about me anymore
So
Regardless of all the hardships,
I must come to you, too
Looking for that
The man who gave me life
Go home
Mother
When I first entered the palace
I am reckless and ignorant
It will only become your burden
But it's different now
I can do anything
I can help you
Can be your arm
I must be better than anyone else
Well done
Mother
Are you sure you can't recognize me
It's you
Let me ask you something
How did Master die
The book left for me is not finished yet
Master is not
People who give up halfway
She sacrificed herself
It's all about protecting you
And you're trying to cover up the truth
And kill people
Are you still a human being
She knows too much about me
Living is a hidden danger after all
Who can guarantee that
She will never reveal secrets
So you killed her
Right
You know the truth now
How is it
Do you want to kill me
Avenge her
Do it
Kill me
Thank you very much
Give me a ride
Crown Princess
Hu Shangshi only ordered the handmaiden
Go and invite Yao Dian to dinner
The rest of the handmaiden really didn't know
Please pardon the Crown Princess
Go down
Yes
Stop crying
You see
How nice this is
Sister sister
Sister Miss
You wait for me, miss
Miss and sister
Wait for my lady to go back
Don't leave me
Go home, miss. Don't leave me
Sister
Have you all heard about it
Hu Shang Shi
Hu Shangshi committed suicide
Really
Keep your voice down
Guanglu Temple
Miyagi's men are here
This kind of thing is the most taboo in the palace
Don't let it be mentioned
What's the matter
Nothing
Kill down bridges
I made a deal with Meng Shangshi
Before my right hand recovers
I'll stay in the still food bureau
Do chores
You can also help the little palace maidservants
The concubines of the prince
It's no better than being here
It's strong to get supercilious look at people
Give it to me
Don't do it
You don't want splendor and wealth
Nest here and bask in Chinese cabbage
What for
Do you see it
My face is green with anger
It's greener than this Chinese cabbage
Su Yuehua wants to cross me
It's not that easy
Zi Jin