Your Highness did not report it as soon as possible
It is indeed the handmaiden's fault
But now that you know
Why don't you stop it at once
Be stubborn and refuse to listen to advice
Even if her hand is broken
It is also self-inflicted
If you really don't care,
Why bother to send medicine
Who delivered the medicine
I've never been here before
I haven't sent any medicine
If you talk nonsense again,
You are the only one who asks
Yes, it's from me
It's all from me
Continue
Yes
Let's get started
Meng Shang Shi
Please allow me to deliver the meal
Zi Jin
Although there was Guo Guifei before,
Turn around on your behalf
But it will eventually make the dragon unhappy
You go now
I'm afraid it won't help
Go ahead
Yes
Meng Shang went to deliver food
Can Your Majesty not be angry
I hope so
Your Majesty
I am facing Emperor Taizu
There was a drought in Haozhou in a small time
Blessed by a kind-hearted person
Cabbage and tofu soup to survive the famine
Today's Shangyuan Festival
Handmaiden dares to offer this meal
Your Majesty, please taste it
Your Majesty
When Emperor Taizu was here,
You must drink this every day
Pearl Jade White Jade Soup
It's been a long time
I'll never see it again in the palace
In my opinion
Why don't you order it
Make this dish a royal meal
So that the descendants of the royal family can
Remember the hardships of ancestors' entrepreneurship
Do not forget the sufferings of people's lives
OK, let's take this example
Spread to officials
Yes
Your Majesty
This sweet-scented osmanthus skin silk
It's a good leather silk
Stir-fry with egg yolk
Orange in color
Just like cinnamon
It can also nourish and benefit qi
Eliminate upset and stuffy
This white jade collects treasures
Hidden Gankun is fresh and elegant
Tender and delicious
This orange crab
It is a combination of orange fragrance and crab freshness
It is not the season of eating crabs and enjoying chrysanthemums
Yisheng new wine chrysanthemum
Orange crab
In fact, it is so beautiful
Mandarin duck fish fan made by Hu Shangshi
Of course it's wonderful
But this golden dragon spins silk
Root silver wire
They are all made of fresh and tender fish
This meal is more beneficial to the five internal organs
Effect of tonifying deficiency and invigorating qi
Your Majesty, if you use a bite,
I'm afraid before putting chopsticks
I still don't realize that the golden plate is empty
Handmaiden talks a lot
Come on, go down after that
Yes
Fortunately, it is the father
If this is Grandpa Huang
You can't drive out at random
Look at this boasting
I'd like to try it
How delicious it is
Your Majesty left
Golden Dragon Spinning Silk and Orange Crab
What a pity
Hu Shangshi is still slightly better
Zi Jin
Why do you want to
Deliver food in person
The kitchen was injured and struggled to cook
Your Majesty witnessed it with his own eyes
Maybe it will be merciful
Allow me to finish
What are you doing
Go to the royal demonstration for the next dish
Yes
Your hand
Nothing
I went
Rest assured of food
I can't think of Meng Shangshi's knife skill
So exquisite
It can be called the best in the world
This kind of pot
It is based on eight kinds of fresh ingredients
Main material
But what it tests
It is not an exquisite knife skill
It's fresh ingredients
With the natural taste of food
Original flavor
Yesterday Guanglu Temple
Emerald soup bag sent
Seemingly exquisite in appearance
But it makes people thirsty after eating
Just because it puts too much seasoning
It can be seen that blindly pursuing
Precious ingredients and skills
Will only put the cart before the horse
Fresh boiling soup micro-rinse
The real purpose
Is to discover
The taste of the food itself
After all, what diners eat
It's the food itself
Instead of cooking skills and seasonings
Your Highness is right
Guanglu Temple Office
It's getting more and more perfunctory
They should be punished well
Am I
What are you talking silly about again
This fragrance
I can't help but boast
When is Henan flavor the same as Sichuan flavor
It's getting mixed up
Your Majesty
This meal originated from the Eight Treasures of Zhou Dynasty
Called a cannon dolphin
Fill the pork belly with dates
Wrap it with reeds and grass mud
With fierce artillery
Then peel and wipe
Into the tripod to prevent water
Steam for three days and nights to eat
Handmaiden thought
Although this method has been maintained,
The original taste of food
But the loss is complicated
Try to use a new method today
Shake and bake with charcoal over slow fire
The taste is better than before
Your Majesty
I heard that this suckling pig
After roasting,
The color is amber
The entrance skin is crisp and the meat is tender
Delicious anomaly
My brother is also looking forward to it
What's that
Kirin pattern
Your Majesty, this is a unicorn pattern
Your Majesty
Shangyuan Festival is auspicious in this world
Congratulations, Your Majesty. Congratulations, Your Majesty
Hu Shang Shi
In order to prepare this suckling pig,
You put a lot of thought into it, didn't you
They are trying to please me
This pig
Maybe what pattern
It can burn out
Your Majesty is wise
After this meal has been improved,
It's called Tuwen suckling pig
Come
Exemption from gifts
Thank Your Majesty
Crown Princess
In case the kitchen is not careful
The pig burned a golden dragon pattern
What should I do
Father
Your Majesty
Send my father back
Zhan Ji
Don't let the assassin go
Chen Wu
Zhan Ji
Save the driver quickly
This way
Bold
Why don't you get out of here
Quick and quick
Help me, help me
Come quickly
Your Majesty
This way
Father
You go away
Waiting for you to rescue me
My life is over
Quick Xuan Tai Yi Quick Xuan Tai Yi
Your Excellency
Your Majesty
Love Princess
It scared me to death
Scared me to death
Innocent
Are you all right
See your majesty is safe
My brother is relieved
Back to the palace
Help me back to the palace
Hold on a little longer
Your Highness, are you hurt
Zhan Ji
Nothing
Go back after sending your mother
Yes
Let's go
Chen Wu
Aftermath
Yes
Hu Shang Shi
Fuck off