Bro.
I never thought
I would be so close
to you like now.
I've fired all the bullets
and thrown all the grenades.
There's no turning back now.
But
I will never be a captive.
Bro!
Jiang Nanzheng.
Take care.
Jiang.
Are you okay?
Slow down on the way.
Don let him get hurt.
Daguo.
You okay? Can you hang in there?
Yes, I can.
Bro, hang in there.
Beihai.
How are your legs?
They hurt.
I never felt a sharp pain like this.
Gu.
Can I shout?
Not now.
We're still unclear about this place.
After we cross the river,
we'll arrive at our defense area.
Then
you can shout as loud as you like.
Do you think my legs
can be kept?
Yes.
I promise.
If you they cut your legs,
I'll ask them to give you new ones.
I don't want to hear a joke.
Why did you let him sit up?
Prevent him from drinking more water.
I couldn't stop him.
He insisted on getting up.
As a platoon leader,
I can't lie on a stretcher
and let my soldiers carry me
while retreating.
Now I'm the acting platoon leader.
You have to listen to me.
I'm still alive.
You already can't wait?
If I knew that,
I wouldn't ask you to buy dresses for Xiu.
I'll buy dresses.
Well, I'll buy 20 dresses for her
after I go back.
I have to buy more dresses than Gao Liang.
Please keep
your promise.
I never
break my promise.
Where's his stretcher?
He gave his stretcher to someone.
Three soldiers got injured on the way.
One of them stepped on a toxic pole.
The other two stepped on land mines.
Stop drinking!
No.
You have to lie on a stretcher.
Lie down!
Alert! Hurry up!
Be careful, everyone! There are enemies!
Somebody help!
Come on! Help!
Follow me!
Come on!
I need two more people.
- Have a check there.
- Alert!
Come on!
Somebody help!
I regret that
I married Xiu.
Go!
Tell her to
forget me.
How's our platoon leader?
Platoon leader!
Say something!
Medic!
Sergeant Han.
Is there a radio that can never be blown up?
Is there a radio that can never be destroyed?
Is there a radio?
Platoon Leader Xia.
Sergeant Han.
Is there a radio that can never be destroyed?
Gu Yiye is back.
He's in the field hospital.
Press here.
Hurry up.
Move into the center.
Yiye.
You're injured.
Let me have a check.
I'm fine.
There were only two shrapnel.
They've already been taken out.
How could you be fine?
Are you really fine?
Yes, I'm fine.
As you can see,
if I was not okay,
they wouldn't let me go.
No kidding.
Where's Gao Liang?
Why didn't I see him?
He's at the back.
At the back?
He covered us.
He was alone...
Doctor.
How's our platoon leader?
Our platoon leader.
Which platoon leader?
There are a lot of platoon leaders
in this room.
Who are you looking for?
Zhang Fei who's with the Ninth Company
of the Third Battalion of Regiment 720.
Your platoon leader is already dead.
That's not true, doctor.
He was fine. How could he die?
When he arrived here,
there's already no breath or heartbeat.
What are you going to do?
We've already been through
three disturbances today.
We're also sad.
- That's not true, doctor. He couldn't die!
- I'm busy.
Jiang.
Doctor!
Enough.
- Sergeant.
- Enough.
- Stop, Gu Yiye. Stop.
- Liar!
Liar!
Yiye, calm down.
You're already back.
How can I calm down?
Yes, I'm back.
But where's our platoon leader?
Where's our platoon leader?
Liar! Liar!
Return our platoon leader to me!
Platoon leader! Platoon leader!
Platoon leader!
No way!
Return our platoon leader to me!
You bastards!
After knowing or seeing
that other comrades left and died
one by one,
especially after knowing that
Platoon Leader Zhang Fei died,
Gu Yiye suffered from
mild post-traumatic stress disorder.
He became very emotional.
[6 months later...]
I know
he needs time to heal the wound.
I believe one day he'll move on
and escape from the shadow of the war.
Gao Liang.
Jiang Nanzheng.
I thought you wouldn't come back.
I almost died there,
but I'm back now.
They all said you didn't come back.
It scared me to death.
It's okay. Now I'm back.
Do you feel relieved?
Not yet.
So many people
are watching us.
Think about the influence.
Stop.
Let me show you something.
You gave me two pieces of White Rabbit candy.
When I almost gave up,
I ate one piece.
About this piece,
I didn't eat it.
It's put in my pocket all the time.
It's thanks to it
that I could go back.
Stop... Stop crying.
Take a seat.
Wipe your tears.
Why would you use this?
Did you forget that it was given by you?
You gave it to me
when we were going to August Town.
Let me show you another thing.
What's wrong with your waist?
Nothing.
The wounds have already been healed.
It's just that there are two scars left.
They all put the order
in front of their chests,
but I put it on my waist.
Look.
I used cartridge cases
to make this fruit knife.
It's yours now.
When did you come back?
After you retreated,
I stayed behind the enemies
for about 11 days.
Why did you come back so late?
Actually, I'm glad that I could come back.
I also wanted to come back early.
I...
I jumped off a cliff.
Then
I met Niu Mancang.
Later,
we fought against enemies all the way.
We met a lot of enemy agents.
It's very hard to get rid of them.
We had fought for three to four days.
We didn't have any guns or bullets,
so we robbed them
and picked up their bullets.
In the end, we were starving.
We ate everything in the mountain.
We ate mice and snakes.
However,
we defeated many enemies
and captured three soldiers.
You know what? Niu Mancang
didn't even get hurt. It's amazing, isn't it?
Let me tell you something more amazing.
I heard
Niu Mancang and me
have already been listed as martyrs
by the company.
The memorial service was about to be held.
Really?
I was angry.
Well, we
stayed behind
and fought for so many days.
We're still alive.
However,
they believed that we're already dead.
You've been back for a long time.
Did you ever visit Gu Yiye?
What's wrong?
Gu Yiye.
Hands up! Don't move!
Hands up!
- Mancang! Mancang!
- Hands up!
I said hands up! Did you hear me?
I said hands up!
Mancang!
Mancang.
We're your allies, Mancang.
Mancang, calm down.
I'm Lu Pingfan.
Mancang, it's okay.
Mancang, put the gun down.
- It's okay, Mancang.
- Calm down.
It's okay.
Mancang, it's okay.
Ever since then,
I haven't seen him again.
I just heard
he's always in the dormitory.
He doesn't want to go out or see anyone.
I was worried about him.
I came to visit him
but he refused to see me.
After I was dispatched
to the Division Command
to help them make the martyr list,
I had no time to visit him again.
I don't know
what happened later, either.
Well,
others told me that
in order to protect him,
Platoon Leader Zhang Fei was blown up.
But at that time,
we were surrounded
by enemies in the ravine.
We couldn't move.
If he didn't
lead people of two squads back,
none of us would be able to return.
It's not his fault.
He reported the accident to the military
by himself.
Himself?
Was he insane?
He dwelt on it.
He said if he didn't insist
when Platoon Leader Zhang Fei
assigned tasks,
Platoon Leader Zhang Fei wouldn't go look for
missing people with others.
If he didn't move the plank,
Platoon Leader Zhang wouldn't be blown up
by the land mine for covering him.
He claimed that
Platoon Leader Zhang Fei died
because of him.
If this is the case,
I'm also guilty
because at that time,
I also insisted we should rescue people
instead of going back.
Why are you all like this?
I also feel terribly sad
about Platoon Leader Zhang's death.
I even dreamed of him for two days.
But if you all think that,
Platoon Leader Zhang's death will be a waste.
You don't have to comfort me.
I almost died once.
I know what death is.
You should comfort Yiye.
He needs you more than I need you.
Go talk to him.
But you're his best friend in the army.
But he likes you.
It's easier for you to persuade him.
OK.
After I return to the station,
I'll go visit him.
Go back early.
It's dark.
Take care.
I have to go.
OK.
I gotta go.
Jiang Nanzheng,
do you know that
I told myself
I would never tell anyone about this?
However,
when I held the Honor Grenade
and stood by the cliff...
When Niu and me ran in panic
in the unknown jungle...
When those bullets and shells
showered down around me...
I thought
if I could survive
and see you,
there would be no hesitations
in telling you,
"Jiang Nanzheng,
I also like you."
I fell in love with you
at first sight.
I know you have feelings for Gu Yiye
[People's Liberation Army]
and you won't like me.
I'm kind of
carrying a torch for you.
Anyway, it's okay.
As long as I'm not a bother...
As long as I can stay with you,
seeing you fall in love
and live a happy life,
it's okay.
♫ Yearning for you, watching over you ♫
♫ Yearning turns into winds.
Read my mind, read your mind. ♫
♫ Yearning for me, looking at me. ♫
♫ Time turns into flowers,
like you, like me. ♫
♫ Yearning for you, watching over you ♫
♫ Yearning turns into winds.
Read my mind, read your mind. ♫
♫ Yearning for me, looking at me. ♫
♫ Time turns into flowers,
like you, like me. ♫
I didn't expect that
the Ninth Company would suffer heavy losses.
If I knew that,
I wouldn't give the main station
to Qin.
Gu,
don't be too sad.
You...
This time you performed
well.
A couple of cadres
have privately talked about it
in the camp.
None of the enemies
could
rescue so many people.
You're good at leading people.
After we go back,
you'll be
praised and promoted.
Can I request
to join the First Company?
Why?
This time the Ninth Company
impressed us.
The Trash Company
no longer exists.
However, the First Company
was not as good as the Ninth Company.
Why do you want to join the First Company?
I can't even spend one more day
in the Ninth Company.
If I stay there for one more day,
I think I'll go crazy.
[Live and die together]
[August Town]
[Triumphal Arch.
Welcome back, front-line heroes]
What are you doing?
We're welcoming the army back.
Welcome?
You asked these students to
wait here for one night.
[Learn from our soldiers]
How could you do that?
That's not my plan.
The city's leader wanted us to do that.
The army performed meritorious service
by winning a victory.
We couldn't remain silent.
Didn't you hear about
the order of the division?
Don't bother people.
Go back to the station quietly.
Ask them to disperse now.
- Disperse? How to disperse so many people?
- What are you doing?
Ask them to go away. We'll go first.
What are you doing?
Go away!
[Triumphal Arch.
Welcome back, front-line heroes]
What are you doing?
Chief.
The Third Company is marching.
They insisted on jumping the queue.
They should go away
and let us go first!
Why can you go first?
We're with the Reconnaissance Company
of the division!
Why can't we go first?
Listen,
our Regiment 720
wasn't basking in the sunshine!
We lost over 300 soldiers!
Why are you so arrogant?
Yes! Why are you so arrogant?
Why can you go first?
Stay here!
Chief of staff.
He serves under the division commander.
You...
So what?
What are you doing?
Stand up straight!
[Triumphal Arch.
Welcome back, front-line heroes]
Can you learn to control your temper?
My temper is just like this!
If you go to the battlefield,
your performance will be worse than mine!
Soldiers of the Ninth Company are coming!
[Live and die together]
[Triumphal Arch.
Welcome back, front-line heroes]
[Live and die together]
[Triumphal Arch.
Welcome back, front-line heroes]
[Comrades, welcome home]
When will they arrive?
I think they'll arrive here soon.
They're coming!
They're finally back.
Salute!
Welcome back.
[Learn from our soldiers]
[Comrades, welcome home]
Hi, comrade.
May I ask
are soldiers of the Ninth Company back?
Sorry, we have no idea.
Thanks.
Company commander!
Pull over.
Comrade.
Company commander!
I know him.
Thank you.
Hi, comrade.
May I ask are you
Zhang Fei's company commander?
Yes.
I'm Qin Hanyong,
the commander of the Ninth Company.
You're Xiu, right?
Yes.
Great! All of you are back.
Where's Zhang Fei?
Xiu.
Well,
the army just came back.
We don't have much time.
We have to take a rest.
You don't have accommodation, right?
Could you please stay
in the guest house first?
I'll visit you
after I arrange everything for the army.
Let's have a long talk.
I won't stop you from working.
I just want to know
if Zhang Fei is back.
How's him?
I just want to know this.
Well,
the army need to
arrange,
coordinate and deal with
some things in batches.
I have no right to make decisions.
Was Zhang Fei
timid on the battlefield?
Did he make any mistakes?
No, no, no.
Zhang Fei was very brave
and tough.
He's the bravest platoon leader
in the Ninth Company
of the Third Battalion of Regiment 720.
I promise
everything I say is true.
Please trust me.
What a relief!
Company commander,
I don't have any other questions.
I don't want to bother the army.
I won't stay with the army.
I stay at Hongxing Hotel in the town.
If you're not busy, I'll go visit you.
Commander Qin, there's a traffic jam.
Let's go back first. Talk later.
Xiu.
As you can see, there's a traffic jam.
Could you please go back to the hotel first?
Tonight, the commissar and me...
I'll visit you tonight.
Please don't leave.
Wait for me.
OK.
Salute!
[Comrades, welcome home]
Company commander!
102 soldiers of the Ninth Company
of Regiment 720 should be here.
All of us are here now.
Please advise!
[Archives Center]
Disperse, everyone.
You can do anything.
Anyway, don't leave the camp.
[Archives Center]
Gu Yiye, follow me.
You want me to talk to Xiu?
No.
I can't.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
Zhang Fei was your platoon leader.
You were there when he died.
You have to go.
No.
Anyone can go
except me.
Gu Yiye.
I can understand how you feel.
Everyone will feel terribly sad about it.
But we can't pretend
that nothing has happened.
We have to move on even if people died.
Three soldiers of the Ninth Squad died.
28 soldiers of the Third Platoon died.
Our company lost 75 soldiers in total.
If I act like you,
how to keep living in the world
as a company commander?
I've talked to the battalion.
The battalion replied that
notices of martyrs' deaths
should be sent in batches.
Don't tell people about it now.
Just say that combatants
will be dispatched by the army together.
But we have to visit their family.
His family is already at the door.
You can't pretend not to notice.
If this is the case,
you shouldn't have returned
from the battlefield.
Say something.
Where's the courage
you showed when you passed the blockade line
with others?
You have to go with me tonight.
Think it over here.
I'll go to the hospital to
visit the wounded of our company.
Call the hospital and come to see me
after you make a decision.
The quartermaster and me
are the only cadres left in our company.
You're the acting platoon leader
of the Third Platoon.
Continue being the acting platoon leader
until the formal organization is complete.
Soon some soldiers will receive merits.
You're smart. Think about it for me.
In our company,
whose names should be on the list?
I'm kind of resorting
to the carrot and stick approach.
It's just that...
It's just that
there are no other suitable candidates.
[Strengthen combat readiness.
Get ready to fight]
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
[Strict discipline, invincible army,
tough soldiers, great physical fitness]
Gao, were you discharged from the hospital?
Yes.
I'll go visit the company commander first.
Company commander.
I'm back.