Unforgettable Love
EP24
Xiaobao
You played tricks.
Look.
We haven't seen each other for years.
Why are you still
not good at playing basketball?
He Qiaonian
I miss you.
Qiaoyan
I'm sorry.
Your sister-in-law and I were gone,
leaving Xiaobao for you to take care of.
I know
you have done a lot
for Xiaobao over the years.
Thank you.
You're his father.
I will play basketball with you
in my next life.
He Qiaonian
Qiaoyan, what's the matter?
I'm fine.
You had me scared.
I saw my elder brother just now.
What did he say?
He said that
he hoped us all to be fine.
Come on.
Dad, Mom and Xiaobao
will be together forever.
We will be together forever.
So
that's how I have been evicted.
You can live here first.
No hurry.
Life is a long journey.
Take it easy.
You can sort your things out.
You must be hungry.
I'll cook for you.
Thank you.
There are no ingredients at home.
Would you mind a bowl of noodles
with tomatoes and eggs?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
What are you drawing?
Is it a trench coat?
A trench coat?
Sorry.
I know nothing about design.
Nailed it.
Is it done?
Is it pretty?
Yes.
In fact, I always wanted to design
an unique dress.
But I'm not satisfied with what I have drawn.
What you said just now
gave me a lot of inspiration.
Look, there are
three wearing methods.
Three contrast colors are combined.
And I plan to
choose waterproof fabric.
I hope
the person who wears the dress
can become unique.
It can be adapted to any occasion
without any constraints.
I hope I can
see it earlier.
It is just a preliminary idea.
It is still a long way to go
whether it can be turned into reality.
But before going further
you should have eaten something
right?
I'll cook another bowl of noodles.
OK, thank you.
Yummy.
It is so late.
I'm sorry.
As soon as I work
I tend to forget the time.
Do you know what?
When a person does
what she likes to do most
she will shine.
I believe that
designing
will be the best way
to relieve your mental worries.
But I think you cured me.
But for you
maybe I unable to be reinvigorated
after a fall.
You don't know,
but I feel alive
when I get back
to work
just now.
It feels good.
So
thank you so much.
You really helped me a lot.
Don't thank me.
It's your heart
that doesn't give up what you are.
Now
it's my turn to help you.
Help me?
You should say goodbye to the past
and start a new life.
Dr. Ning
A doctor could not find out his own medical solution.
You were a good talker
when you persuaded me just now.
But it doesn't work
when it happens to you.
You're right.
It's time for me to look forward.
OK.
OK, OK.
OK, no problem.
Yes.
I can arrive in France next week.
Bye.
Anything good happened?
I talked with my French friend
about my design we discussed before.
He is interested in it.
And he told his boss.
His boss wants to invite me
to be the cooperative designer of his company.
You're great.
Congratulations.
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook for you tonight.
How about western-style food?
OK.
Then you will go back to France soon?
I'm leaving tomorrow.
You're in a hurry.
They want me to participate in
the design of new products next quarter.
So I have to
go earlier and prepare for it.
That's great.
Qin Yiyue, He Qiaoyan.
He Qiaoyan
Please call me according to the law.
Call me hubby.
H...
Comrade He.
Comrade He?
What do you call me?
He
He?
Are you sure?
He
Hubby.
One more time.
I have realized
my biggest wish.
Do you have
any wishes unrealized
before going to Germany?
Go to Germany?
I heard that
you called Dr. Huang that day.
I made a decision for you.
I told him that you would go to Germany.
I have told Dr. Huang that I won't go.
I'm not going.
I don't want to go.
I want to stay with you.
We want to stay with you, too.
But Xiaobao and I
prefer to see that
you are free
to pursue your dream.
You're willing to part with me?
Of course not.
So
it's a part of your plan.
Right?
I was wondering
why you took me to get the marriage certificate
in such a hurry.
It turns out that you want to hold my heart
by the little red book.
But
I'm not willing to part with you and Xiaobao.
I promise you.
Xiaobao and I
will fly to you every month.
Really?
Really.
Then I have another condition.
I want weddings.
OK.
I also want
a long, long
and long floor length bridal gown.
Then I will have a long and long
floor length bridal gown tailored for you.
You know what?
When I was a child,
I'd like nothing better than to play the part of the princess
by putting on a sheet and mosquito net.
The sheet is like a cape.
The sheet was dragged back and forth.
Mom came in and saw
the clean sheet sweeping the ground.
She almost killed me.
Hang on a sec.
You hang up first.
You first according to old rules.
Tomorrow
is the first day you go back to Heshi Group.
Are you excited?
In fact, it's three days later
than I have expected
to return to Heshi Group.
Although the bracelet is almost perfect
after upgrading.
But it delayed
for three days
to win back the contract of Cooper Five Group.
The company and staff
are not satisfied with the agents
they recommend during this period.
I think now the board of directors
have known that
you are the only leader
to take charge of the overall situation.
It's me who have led them to
make the achievements of Heshi Group
over the years.
Your husband is confident.
Nobody can be convincing except me.
Mr. He is not the average.
Is it the time for Mr. He
who is not the average
to go to sleep?
Your face will be puffy
if you don't sleep now.
Well, stop here.
Dr. Huang needs to see me.
I'm going.
Bye.
Mr. He
Welcome back.
Is it over? Is it over?
Almost, almost.
Hurry up.
It's really an awful movie.
It staggers me that
it's the best horror movie of the year.
I feel so calm.
Boring. I'm going home.
Don't go.
I'm scared.
Let me go.
What are you afraid of?
Look.
Do you see the corner?
As long as you won't see the corner
when you wake up at midnight
you will be fine.
I, I do not want you to go.
I'm scared.
I.
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
You are a man.
Wen Gu
Dad.
You, you live together?
No, no.
No no no, Mr. Wen.
Well, I'm going.
She is my girlfriend.
Don't be mischievous.
You are the manager of the company.
She is your secretary.
Aren't you afraid of
being gossiped?
Look.
What's the rank of this one?
What?
She is my secretary
during work.
She is my girlfriend after work.
Which piece of laws of the universe says
a boss can't fall in love with his secretary.
And
it's prejudice and discrimination.
You see the career women
through colored glasses.
We are both unmarried.
Why can't we be together?
Why should we be gossiped?
Get into the room.
I will talk to her alone.
No.
You can talk to her
in my presence.
Don't irritate your father.
I will have a good talk with Mr. Wen.
No.
Hurry up.
Get into the room.
Please sit down.
What did my Dad say?
Don't give me a hard time.
I really cherish this job.
I've just seen a glimmer of hope
in my career.
I don't want to destroy it by myself.
Just stop here.
Your father is right.
I'm just a two-bit secretary.
Please let me disappear
in your world
like Wang Beijin and Wang Miao.
No way.
Calm down.
I can smooth things out.
And
never mind
what he said.
I'm a man and I can bear the burden.
I'm tired, OK?
What's wrong with you?
OK, you won't tell me the truth.
Dad just needs to see me.
I'm going to ask him.
I tell you to come here early.
Are there some misunderstandings
about the word "early"?
Dad, what did you say to Yang Ruowei?
I told her to break up with you.
Then
I allow her to
skip to the management of the group.
If you want to make a deal with her
you'd better make a deal with me.
50 million yuan.
Only 50 million yuan.
I will leave her immediately.
I will be in a big hurry
and at high speed.
Do you think I'm stupid?
50 million yuan.
25 million yuan
for each.
You will go to somewhere I don't know
to enjoy your unrestrained life.
Do you think your father
is rich but stupid?
No matter.
It doesn't matter if you don't agree
as long as she agrees.
What if I give up
Wenshi Group for her?
Just look up.
Wenshi Group is the group of our Wen family.
You can't get rid of it.
To give up the company
is to give up yourself.
I don't care.
I am who I am.
I belong to nobody.
I have the right to choose
what I want.
OK, I'll count for you.
Look.
Your basic necessities
your car and house
are all a part of
the profit of Wenshi Group.
I have the right to take them back.
And your bar.
Wenshi Group owns all the shares.
I also have the right to take it back.
And your bank account.
I can freeze it
right now.
What do you have left?
Love is more than anything else.
You mean
if I choose her
I will give up everything I have now.
Yang Ruowei
is not right for you.
She is not right for Wen family, either.
I will find another assistant
for you.
The second daughter of the boss
of Linmei Group
has loved you at a young age.
Her academic career is also great.
She's a sophomore now.
And she wants to come for an internship.
Then I ask her to follow you.
Isn't it good?
As long as you break up with Yang Ruowei,
you can do whatever you want in the future.
No work.
E-sports or racing.
You can do
whatever you want.
I see.
Good morning, Mr. Wen.
Yang Ruowei
Are you ready?
If I were nobody
would you like to accept me?
What do you mean?
Would you like to accept me?
You ask me to feed you?
It's impossible.
But I can lend you half a bed.
Come with me and go to see my Dad.
Here are
my house, car, deposit and the bar.
Now I return them to you.
And I don't care
the position of CEO.
I quit.
But
you still have to
pay me this month.
After all
I'm shielded by labour laws.
I will not touch
your resources in the future.
Wen Gu, I'm not worth it.
Stop talking.
Don't worry.
I can hold on a little longer.
Then I'll find a way to deal with it.
You are
thinking of
disowning me?
No, that's quite another matter.
You are my Dad forever.
Even if I wanted to
Ruowei can't agree.
You had many
girlfriends before.
As long as I get angry
you'll break up with them.
Why don't you
do so
this time?
It's true that I used to be faithless.
But I'm in deadly earnest this time.
I can give up everything
if she could be mine.
Yang Ruowei, you are really something.
In that case
I feel relieved for the girl.
You know that.
Mr. Wen.
He's stayed with you for so long.
He is getting on a lot.
If there is any disadvantage
he has now,
it's the responsibility
for love and choice.
You've been together for a long time.
Do you think
you have no sense of security?
How about this?
It will make you feel wronged.
I'll test him for you.
It's a loss.
Yang Ruowei
You should tell me early.
In this way,
I can ask my Dad
for 50 million yuan.
Then I pretend to break up with you.
And I catch you two months later.
Now we have lost 100 million yuan.
What are you thinking about?
Dad.
Can I have my
house and car back?
The word once spoken
can never be recalled.
I'm your son after all.
Then you can't make me
sleep on the street.
I can sleep on the street.
What about Ruowei?
Don't use Ruowei as a bargaining chip.
If our Wen family
is lucky
and you can finally marry Ruowei,
I'll buy you a big house.
No.
I'll earn money on my own
to buy a house for my love.
Then you won't be unconvinced
and take it back.
OK.
OK, OK.
Nice.
Be careful.
Don't spoil the flowers for Mom.
OK.
Well.
You can see your Mom later.
Are you happy?
Duh! Of course.
He Weifei
It's getting more and more presumptuous.
Let your Mom give you a lecture
when we meet later.
Mom won't give me a lecture.
Boy! You've also learned to talk back.
Did you prepare
the test paper
and the certificate of awards in programming contest?
They are in my bag.
That's good.
Remember to give them to your Mommy
when you see her later.
And the most important one
is to tell your Mommy
that you can get them because I usually urge you
to study every day.
Ice cream.
OK, no problem.
As long as you say it
I will buy you ice cream.
Yiyue
Do you arrive earlier?
Qiaoyan, I'm sorry.
There's something wrong.
And I will go back to Germany.
What's up with that?
Is it serious?
No, it's about the project.
When will you be back next time?
Maybe over one month.
Maybe...
It doesn't matter.
Xiaobao and I are waiting for you.
By the way, Xiaobao is here.
Would you like to have a chat with him?
No, no.
I'm in a hurry.
You, you kiss Xiaobao for me.
Bye.
Are you hungry?
I'm going to cook for you.
I'm not hungry.
It seems that
nobody wants to eat pork ribs.
Mommy.
Xiaobao
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
I miss you, too.
He Weifei
Wash your hands first.
Go ahead.
Keep control of yourself.
Do you miss me?
It's good that you are back.
I miss you so much.
Me too.
He Qiaoyan
Now, I'm leaving my daughter to you.
From now on
you must treat her well.
Don't worry.
I will treat her well.
Can Xiaobao remember so many words?
He can remember all he has seen and he is calm.
He learns that from me.
It's so long.
He stayed in my study
writing and drawing for a long time last night.
I didn't expect him to prepare so much.
Dear guests and friends
ladies and gentlemen
good afternoon.
In the moment of golden autumn,
we are pleased
to send best wishes.
Babe, get to the point.
OK, Mom.
What's the point?
It seems that
the ability of reading comprehension of our son
is not good.
Xiaobao
Start with "Do you want".
Groom, do you want...
Yes, I do.
Bride, do you want...
Then please exchange the wedding rings.
Do you really want it?
Now the groom may kiss your bride.
What's wrong?
Scratch my back.
Hurry up.
Is it the right time now?
You can't make a bride
scratch her back with everybody present.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Here?
Left, left, left.
Left.
Higher, higher.
Thank you, bro.
Bro?
Please throw the bouquet.
Hurry up.
Come on, throw it to me.
Give me that.
Hurry up.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Throw it to me.
Bro.
It's useless for you since you're single.
It's the blessing of marriage.
There's not the slightest sign of anything happening yet.
Here is a sister
who is old enough to get married.
Please give me the bouquet.
Who do you say is older?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hi.
Come on, Ning Fang.
And Mom.