[English subtitles are available]
[Imitation]
[Episode 9]
I must've kept you waiting.
No.
How long has it been since we last met?
Has it been a week?
Yes, something like that.
I knew it. I missed you so much.
Ma-ha.
What is it?
Why can't you just say it?
I can't bring myself
to say it to your face.
Let's
break up.
Of course.
Were you going to stay with me all night?
It's not like we are an item.
My love for you has stayed the same.
The love of a fan.
-As a fan?
-Since before you debuted.
It was even before Fins was established,
so I'm a true fan. Right?
-Ma-ha--
-Hold on.
You're more dangerous than I thought.
A sad soppy breakup isn't in your cards.
I'll get going then.
Let me take you home.
No. It's okay.
From now on, your junior, Lee Ma-ha,
will show lots of support
for my senior, Kwon Ryoc.
Go, Kwon Ryoc!
[Where are you?]
[Get back here already.]
Hello?
-[Ma-ha?]
-Sorry about that.
Where are you?
Hold on.
Where am I exactly?
Stop it. You're scaring me.
I'm almost home. It won't be long.
[Bus Stop]
How could she be that unfazed?
How could she be okay with this?
Why was she pretending to be okay?
It worries me even more.
I'll wash up.
That.
You should take that off first.
I'm totally out of it
due to the back-to-back incidents.
Why do I feel an itch
that needs to be scratched?
Where were you all night?
Do-jin, Hyuk, I-hyeon,
get your late-night snack!
You? At this hour? A late-night snack?
I should on a day like this.
And what day would that be?
This isn't like you at all.
You've been watching your figure.
I'll get back to it tomorrow.
Eat. You want to.
It's been a while
since we ate together like this.
Right? It's been so long.
I'm kind of scared.
Me too, but just eat.
Come on.
Fine, let's eat.
Thanks.
-Who wants to start with the chicken?
-Me.
Hyun-ji, why is your face
half its original size?
-What?
-It's half its original size
while mine is bloated.
Don't tell me
you couldn't eat
because of what I put you through.
Hyun-ji, don't stay mad at me.
Pretty Hyun-ji, please.
Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
It's over between us.
I broke up with Ryoc.
Although, it wasn't much of a relationship
since there weren't many dates.
I should've focused more on you guys,
and I'm sorry.
I have no more secrets now.
Are you kidding me?
You broke up with him?
Why inconvenience those around you
if you were going
to break it off so easily?
Hey.
You lost sleep while worrying about him,
but this is what you do?
Stop it, Hyun-ji.
This is already hard on her.
Right. Of course she's in pain.
But don't forget
that you've caused pain for others too.
-What?
-You only care about how you feel.
Hyun-ji, you're being too harsh.
-Hyun-ji, I--
-Tea Party.
The whole team has been booked for a gig.
Will it be okay?
Of course. We need to show
our faces more open
to be invited to perform at MML.
Your ride's out front.
Won't you be joining us?
Hi, guys!
What are you doing here?
As of today, I will be working for
JH Entertainment as Tea Party's manager.
Hi, I'm Go Ba-wi
Who knew that Mr. Ji was a saint?
Always so benevolent.
I, Go Ba-wi, will ensure
the smoothest path for Tea Party--
The smoothest path? How?
I'll work hard until my body gives in.
The passion is real!
Always the smooth talker.
-I hope we get along.
-Sure thing, Ma-ha.
I'm going to have my eyes on you.
You know that, right?
So what's today's gig?
Mr. Ji wouldn't tell us.
A photo campaign for outdoor gear.
You'll be working with Sparkling.
Sparkling?
[NOG Entertainment]
I need a break.
Get up. We're trying that again.
I knew he'd be this way.
He fooled us good, darn it.
Ryoc is back.
He's back to his old self again.
You heartless jerk.
Why get us to eat the fried chicken then?
Do a clean job then.
Let's take it from the top. Get up.
You're back to your old self.
Okay. We'll go through it again
and then rest.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
[NOG Entertainment]
And go.
Good. Here we go.
Nicely done. I love it.
Smile. All of you.
She must be auditioning for "Survivor".
What do you mean?
She survived getting cut from Music Holic
and once again
after being dragged off stage.
It took us three years
to do a photo shoot.
If you're jealous,
ask to be a member of Tea Party.
-Be a co-ed group.
-Just you wait and see.
All that's waiting for them
is disbandment and a scandal.
Don't. They'll hear you.
I see they're real celebrities now.
-Sorry?
-When they got here,
things were ice-cold between them
as if they had an argument.
But in front of the camera,
they're in perfect sync.
-Nice!
-The poses look natural too.
-Be more natural.
-Yu-jin,
get ready for your couple photo.
-Got it.
-Nice. Can you change it up?
Okay, that's good.
But make it seem more dynamic.
Be more friendly. I know you're friends.
Yu-jin, Hyun-ji,
why don't you hold hands?
Okay, here we go again.
Nice. This is great, guys.
Seem more natural though.
You have filming lined up,
so why did you wear yourself out?
-Dae-gwon.
-Yes?
What other projects do I have lined up?
A few movies came in,
and we're still choosing.
Why?
Just get me on board one of them.
Take a break first
and look over them yourself.
One must work when one can.
Besides, it's not like you
to suggest a break.
Ryoc, you're not being yourself.
This is exactly who I am.
Maybe it's because
I haven't warmed up in a while,
but I'm more energized than ever.
Who warms up for half a day?
Something's up with you, isn't it?
Whatever.
Just get me my next movie, okay?
When did he become the Energizer Bunny?
Something's definitely up.
Where's Hyun-ji?
Maybe she went to the restroom.
She won't give me a moment to apologize.
I haven't seen her that mad before.
Jeez, you're so dense.
Hyun-ji.
I see you still have cold hands.
Here.
And use this if it cools down.
I'm sorry, Hyun-ji.
That day.
I made a mistake.
I should've been more attentive,
and I'm really sorry.
Will you accept my apology?
What a relief.
Maybe it's because we teamed up once,
but I was told we looked
the best together.
I overheard the staff talking.
Are you busy this week?
-Me?
-If you're not,
let's meet up briefly.
So are you in or out?
You agreed to a new album ages ago.
How can I get you on TV
when you don't do anything new?
You've been rejecting every offer.
That's because none of the projects
speak out to me.
La Ri-ma,
I went up Mount Halla last week
which took me ten hours.
I wore out my legs to get to the top,
but do you know how long I stayed there?
I descended 15 minutes later
after taking a few photos,
The place up top you're occupying
won't be yours forever.
I know that.
If that's the case,
why not release some albums,
show your face on variety shows--
Okay.
But I'll choose the songs
to release in my album.
And I won't just be on any variety show.
Only those that are
as popular as "Y.M.S.A.".
Okay?
[CEO Hwang Yong-tae]
"Y.M.S.A."?
Be the CEO yourself, why don't you?
I'm the CEO,
so who's she to call the shots?
So how are things going?
Music Holic and SJ Entertainment
will soon sign the contract.
And Queen Entertainment?
[CEO Park Jin-man]
Well...
I told you to focus on the deal with them
since we lack female artists.
La Ri-ma alone costs quite a lot.
Unbelievable.
Why take the difficult route?
Since when did we spend money
to get what we want?
Create a situation that goes in our favor,
and the money will come rushing in.
All we need is a headline that would work.
Gosh.
Book a meeting with
Queen Entertainment's CEO.
Hyun-ji.
I'm sorry for being so dense.
I was so wrapped up in my problems
that I made it hard on you and Ri-a.
I didn't even notice how you felt.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
You've always been a good friend
who worried about me.
It was my mistake.
I took you for granted
because you're my close friend.
I'm sorry for hurting you like this.
But
I have something to tell you.
I used to like you.
Since our training years.
Yu-jin.
-Did that surprise you?
-Why would you say that out of the blue?
Just because.
I just wanted to tell you how I felt.
I'm finally unburdened.
You're so full of surprises.
I couldn't see it before
because I only had my eyes on one person,
but now I can.
I can feel the heart
that someone has for me.
He dumped me as soon as
he confessed his feelings.
That jerk.
Things were hectic,
so I forgot to share this with you.
Sorry.
Yu-jin
likes you, not me.
You know that he's a really nice person.
He's warm and always sincere.
Right.
Hyun-ji.
You've been keeping me company
from the first day I went to OMEGA.
I've always been grateful,
and I'll do better from now.
I won't be preoccupied,
and I'll focus on Tea Party only.
Okay.
I'm sorry
for being so small-minded.
Also,
I'm grateful.
Hey, B!
Don't look at her and keep the distance.
Hey.
A is here.
Hey!
Hello, Ryoc.
That's right. Act like this
when there are people around.
It's our lunchtime. Did you eat, Ryoc?
Join us if you haven't.
No, he can't! He has a meeting.
He has the meeting
for a variety show today?
I'll get going.
Good luck with your shoot.
Gosh, you guys.
Well done. Don't even exchange looks.
-Wasn't that weird?
-Both A and B were.
-There's something going on.
-That we don't know of.
Thank you.
I'm even more grateful.
I don't know how the words got out,
but so many brands want to do a PPL
on our show.
Of course. Ryoc has star power.
Now that you joined us,
let's raise the stakes.
-Thank you in advance.
-Here.
-Sure.
-It's nice to be busy.
-What do you mean?
It's been so long, Ryoc.
I thought you two would be
smiling like fools in love,
but things seem cold.
Did you fight with her?
Please lower your voice.
You two are old enough.
Thank goodness you're no longer
in the pool.
Hello, Ri-ma.
Hi, you're here.
I called her.
-Maybe I shouldn't have?
-I'll get going.
Darn it, maybe I went overboard.
Tell me, Lee Ma-ha.
Ab... About what?
What's with you two?
The thing is,
it's not like what you think.
Of course it is.
We decided to remain good colleagues
who cheer for each other, and...
And...
That's enough.
[Enjoy! Hot pepper chicken]
What's all this?
You can't leave unless you finish them.
Hurry up and eat them. They'll get cold.
Okay.
-It's good.
-It is, right?
Gosh, the coffee smells nice.
You won't kick me out
just because it's closed, right?
Of course not.
Oh, right. They dropped the charges.
It's thanks to you.
I didn't do much.
You wrote the follow-up article.
Thank you so much.
I only wrote the facts as a reporter.
Also, I got something in return.
I've told you before,
but if it's about Eun-jo...
It's not about him
who has no right to be forgotten.
It's about someone
who doesn't have any right at all.
[Let's go, SHAX!]
[2017 MML Festival]
[The wires are ready.]
[I'm sorry, Eun-jo.]
[Annie.]
[I'm sorry I couldn't be with you.]
I'm sorry,
Annie.
Eun-jo and Annie
were a couple
even before their trainee days.
They had the same dream.
Eun-jo became a trainee in NOG,
and Annie joined OMEGA.
Eun-jo debuted as a member of SHAX
and became a top star.
But Annie couldn't even debut.
And one day,
I received a photo...
Annie was involved in
a scandalous case, wasn't she?
Someone anonymously
reported about Eun-jo's girlfriend
with this picture not so long ago
regarding his disappearance.
Why did you do that
when your debut is just around the corner?
There could've been other options.
Did you have to go that far?
I'm so sorry.
I'm not saying this
because you're seeing Eun-jo.
Didn't you think it'd harm the two of you?
I was worried that she'd get in the way
of Eun-jo
after their relationship gets revealed.
Did you tell Eun-jo about it?
No.
Eun-jo doesn't know about it.
Don't you know how crucial this period is?
It's better for you to break up.
It's for both of you.
So just wait until we handle this first.
Okay?
[NOG]
Then what will you do?
Answer me!
I can't break up with her. I'm sorry.
If you leave now, SHAX will disband!
Are you just going to end it?
You'll end SHAX?
[It's all my fault.]
I pushed him to maintain SHAX
instead of understanding him.
That's because you were their manager.
It's my fault
that Annie chose to end her life
and Eun-jo decided to disappear.
It's all my fault.
Then you formed Tea Party
in order to atone for what you did.
Atone?
I don't know.
["Fact Check" sees the world
with facts alone.]
[Byun Jeong-hui]
My gosh.
The night is wearing on,
and I don't have any stories.
[SHAX]
Why did they report it
three years after the incident?
[Byun Jeong-hui]
[Eun-jo didn't leave NOG
because he was sick.]
[I was grateful that you came to see me
in the States.]
And the things
you told me.
You told me to do
what my heart tells me to do.
It was really encouraging
to me when I was devastated.
Also, I know that you looked for Annie
until the end.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
This isn't
what you wanted to do.
You should also do
what your heart tells you to do
just like you told me.
[I'm still at the dorm.]
[You should eat
even if you don't have work, all right?]
[Okay. Have a great day.]
[Yu-jin]
-I'm starving.
-Me too.
Hyun-ji is here.
The lunch is on me.
I'm melting by your beautiful smile.
That's right. This is how we are.
You're right.
It does seem weird
to see you all smiling after a long time.
Tea Party.
-Hello.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
Do you want to
hear the good news first or...
-What's the bad news?
I don't have one.
They dropped the charges.
The breach of contract is dealt with.
Thank goodness.
One more thing.
They must've wired you.
Wire what? Today's not our payday.
It's your first payment.
You did really well, Tea Party.
It's not much, but check your mail
for the details.
[Korea Music Copyright Association,
JH Entertainment Ji-hak]
Since you got your first payment,
I hope we'll work harder from now.
Why aren't you answering me?
-Okay!
Wait, what's this?
"Copyright royalties,
mechanical royalties, performance fees?"
[Yoo Ri-a, "Show Me"]
-Copyright royalties?
-Mechanical royalties?
You're the artists and lyricists
of "Show Me".
So you should be paid for everything,
including copyright royalties,
mechanical royalties, performance fees.
That's such great news!
I never even thought of that.
I'll work harder on the songs.
Go ahead.
Yes!
This is great!
Guys! We got our first payment!
We got paid!
Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
-I'm so dizzy.
-I'm tired too.
All right. Up next
is our toast to celebrate
our first payment.
All right.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
All right.
-Cheers!
This time, we'll take a photo
to commemorate this.
That'd be nice.
All right.
Gather up, guys.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3.
We got it.
And you two.
Don't ever fight again in front of me.
When did we ever fight?
I know, right?
Wow, these two...
This won't do. I should take a photo
to leave it as evidence.
You two, shake hands.
All right, here we go.
1, 2, 3.
Ma-ha, if anything's bothering you,
you should tell me.
I'll share it with you too.
Sure.
You guys are so adorable.
I love you!
This is nice.
Now that we got
paid for royalties and all,
how are you going to spend it?
-I don't know.
-I haven't really thought about it.
-What about you?
-Then how about
spending it together meaningfully?
Why do you all look so determined?
What is it? You're making me anxious.
We want to invest in JH Entertainment
although it's not much.
Invest?
We've been thinking about it,
and we want the agency to be our base
that we grow with you.
Since you put your trust in us...
We also want to go the full distance
with JH Entertainment.
We've been talked about,
but our names are yet to be known.
We want to do it with our own style.
Your own style?
We don't want to
obsess over who comes first.
We want our stage to make everyone happy.
Hello. Always happy, Tea Party.
Just like our greeting.
We want to communicate with our fans too.
We were nervous because of the accident
during the music show,
but we'll never forget the thrill
we had on stage.
[It was exhilarating.]
I was very happy to be there with you.
-We can do it!
-Gosh, that's such an ancient saying.
-I'm in too.
-Me too.
Mr. Ji, then you know what to do.
Always happy,
-Tea Party!
[Upload a video]
[Uploading]
[Always happy, Tea Party]
♫ Step after step ♫
♫ On my way back home ♫
♫ I pretend like I'm fine ♫
♫ As I take every step ♫
[Upload a video]
[Uploading, Video uploaded]
Good. Let's see.
Gosh, you look wonderful.
Thank you.
Pretty girls are always pretty
no matter what you wear.
Tea Party, sir. Please take a listen.
The three unique girls, Tea Party.
It's a cold beverage.
Let's see.
[OMEGA]
Okay, there you are.
All right, now.
This is Tea Party's practice room!
[You're all so pretty!]
-All right!
-Yes!
-This is it.
[-I love you!
-Will you marry me?]
-Isn't it pretty?
-Isn't it?
[-Ri-a, have you eaten?
-Come stream often!]
The comments are way too fast.
Look, "Ma-ha."
[I'll run over right now, Ma-ha!]
[I love you, Tea Party.]
Hey. We love you too, everyone.
-We do!
-We love you!
[-I love you more!
-Hyun-ji's heart!]
[-Ri-a, you're so pretty!
-Blow a kiss!]
That's Tea Party pre-debut?
Yes, a song titled "Call Me"
from their OMEGA-3 era.
I'm starting to like them.
Something still seems missing.
You have too much already.
I told you.
I don't want to associate with SHAX.
But I'm interested.
Not romantically.
I'm very interested in your voice.
You're way too ambitious.
You should try singing over this.
Are you two hitting it off?
Or are you two already in a relationship?
Why are you suddenly here?
Hello.
How many times do you think I knocked?
Have you been flirting
with a member of Tea Party too?
No, there's no romance here.
Romance or no romance,
that's for you two to decide.
Where's the proprietor?
-Ha-seok?
-AMMONITES.
Anyway, what's this song?
[Most-searched Terms:
Ma-ha, dance practice, Tea Party, OMEGA-3]
[OMEGA-3]
["Tea Party's Failed Debut"]
["OMEGA-3 Came Before Tea Party"]
["Tea Party's Hyun-ji
Captures Eyes with Her Beauty"]
["Tea Party Climbs Up the Charts
with 'Call Me'"]
"The song, good. The dance, good.
The looks, good. Very good."
[Comments]
"I'm a true fan of Tea Party as of today."
[968 Comments]
"I've been binging
on videos of Tea Party."
-This is awesome.
-What's going on?
How did our dance practice
from OMEGA-3 era get here?
♫ Party, party now ♫
I, Go Ba-wi, uploaded a legendary video
and helped Tea Party
climb back up the chart.
-What?
-I said I'll do my best as a manager.
I guess you just paid for your sin
of leaving Ma-ha and running off.
Ri-a, let's put a beautiful ending
to this story, okay?
I'm not the type
who easily gets rid of my grudges.
"I'm not the type
who easily gets rid of my grudges."
Thanks to you,
we were the most-searched term.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.
Hey, Tea Party. Not bad.
You won't need me anymore.
Mr. Ji, we need you.
-We need you to push our back.
-Then you need to pull us forward.
-Ma-ha, let's get to work.
-Okay.
-We'll be back.
-Good luck.
-I'll be back.
Bye.
[Tea Party's dance practice
from OMEGA trainee days]
This is frustrating.
Why am I here?
Why did you come here again?
Have you gone insane?
Did you think I'd get scared
if you came to the studio for no reason?
No, it's not like that, Hyeon-o.
You wouldn't pick up your phone,
and you wouldn't see me either,
but I missed you so much.
If it's because of the agency,
then I'll be careful not to get caught.
If we're done, we're done.
Don't be so clingy.
Once a scandal breaks out,
will you take responsibility for my life?
I mean, I can't live without you.
Don't get clingy.
Hyeon-o.
[From now on, your junior, Lee Ma-ha,]
[will show lots of support
for my senior, Kwon Ryoc.]
We can do this!
I'm going to kill myself!
Do as you wish.
Hyeon-o.
Is that all you can say?
What are you doing?
There's a fight.
You!
-Stop them.
-Hey, break them up.
-What are you doing?
-Stop that.
[Only in the agony of parting, do we look
into the depths of love. By George Eliot]
That agony stings to death.
Hey, you know SHAX's Kwon Ryoc, right?
I heard he got into a fight
in the props storage.
They fought over a girl or something.
What are you talking about?
Kwon Ryoc of SHAX is in a love triangle?
Yes, they threw a fit crying,
saying neither of them won't let her go.
My gosh. No way.
-Are you sure it was Kwon Ryoc of SHAX?
-What?
That guy in a love triangle
who threw a huge fit.
Are you sure it was Kwon Ryoc?
It's nothing.
-Ryoc is in what?
-A woman? In a love triangle...
Be quiet.
It's just a rumor, and there's no proof.
Keep your mouths shut, okay?
We'll begin our emergency system
around the clock from now on.
Protect Kwon Ryoc!
-Protect!
["Love Virus"]
Kwon Ryoc of SHAX
punched him to steal his girlfriend.
Then the rumors must be true
about how he only dates rookies.
I'm telling you. He's a player.
That's unbelievable.
I thought it was just a rumor.
["Love Virus"]
He only goes after rookies.
What are you talking about?
-It's just something we heard.
-Yes, we just heard it.
-We have to get ready.
-Yes, let's get ready.
Call Dae-gwon.
Hello? Dae-gwon.
What's going on?
[Star Is Born]
Don't you know
how things are at TV stations?
Is this your first day here?
Once you fall down,
rumors say you were found dead.
If you hit someone,
people soon say they were hospitalized.
What has gotten into you?
I'm sorry, Dae-gwon.
I'll be careful. Please don't be mad.
Goodness, I should've known
when you wanted a lot of work.
How could he do this
to a guy who needs to look good?
How many times did you punch him?
Isn't Hyeon-o your junior?
Why isn't Tae-geun
keeping his kids under control?
I started the fight first.
So what? Lift up your head!
You're Kwon Ryoc of SHAX!
Straighten your back.
Get in.
Get in already.
Yes, sir.
What happened?
I heard Kwon Ryoc punched someone
and got arrested,
but that wasn't true.
But you did get into a fight.
You're not a kid.
You're too old to get into a brawl.
Things just happened.
Ma-ha told me you two broke up.
Is that true?
None of your business.
You're right.
I know this isn't my business,
but why are you two
beating around the bush?
Was this just a fling?
Or was she that easy?
It's not like that.
Really?
You've been in the industry long enough.
Yet you got into this relationship
in a rash?
You weren't ready to face this?
I don't know what someone has on you
to make you be so pathetic,
but weren't you seriously into her
when you went for Ma-ha?
This conversation ends here.
I have nothing else to say.
Ryoc.
You step on your own brake,
instead of letting anyone else do it.
I thought you'd be different.
But you're such a bore, Ryoc.
Yes, sir.
Then let's settle it like that.
Yes, thank you.
All right. Goodbye.
Hey, do I have to sit here
and let someone from the TV station
say something like this to me?
I'm sorry.
In return for covering this up quietly,
Ryoc and two more members of SHAX
will appear on "Y.M.S.A."
Two more?
You idiot.
[CEO Park Jin-man]
Hey, they wanted everyone there,
but I got it down to two
and changed the show to "Y.M.S.A."
So stop complaining
and put it on their schedule.
Yes, Mr. Park.
Ryoc.
Why can't you get a grip?
You're starting to be more like him.
Who wants to be on "Y.M.S.A."?
Y.M.S.A.? All of a sudden?
Ryoc is in for sure.
-Why?
-What do you think?
Good work.
We decided to cover it up
by letting two more come.
So who wants to go?
If it's for Ryoc, I'll go.
I'll go even if I can't win.
-Then it's Hyuk and Do-jin.
-Thanks.
-Who else will be there?
-We don't know yet.
Okay, we got SHAX and La Ri-ma!
Then we can throw in some rookies.
Since we're going to have SHAX,
how about this guy from Sparkling?
[Lee Yu-jin]
I heard he once got into a fight
with Kwon Ryoc during a music show.
Wouldn't it get interesting?
-Really? Give them a call.
-Yes.
What about the girls?
Blue Velvet? Honey Pink?
They're in another show at the same time.
How about them?
Tea Party? Oh, the idols on monthly pay?
They didn't seem special
outside of music shows.
No, their YouTube video went viral,
then they climbed up the charts.
They're the hottest.
Their fancams and cover videos
keep getting uploaded.
-They're that big?
-Yes.
They're on a roll.
Who'll be on the show?
Yu-jin is fixed.
They wanted one of you too.
What about me?
-You won't be working for a while.
-What?
The agency decided to put you off,
so just keep quiet.
Kwon Ryoc hit me first! Look!
Do you think
it's just because of this incident?
Do you think we didn't know
you've been partying with girls?
Tae-geun.
Hyeon-o, you better
look back on what you did.
SHAX will be on the show too,
so pick out a good song.
-Okay.
-You should be on the show with Yu-jin.
-No, you should.
-Forget it.
Tae-geun, I think it'd be better
if Min-su went with Yu-jin.
What do you think, Min-su?
-Thanks.
-Don't mention it.
Ryoc! What are you doing?
The lineup for "Y.M.S.A." is out.
Let's see. Who'll be on the show?
Yu-jin, Min-su.
I don't like this Yu-jin kid.
La Ri-ma.
Ryoc, it's Tea Party.
[Open: Coffee, juice, and tea]
Gosh, I'm starving.
Yes.
Yes, okay.
Tea Party.
Hyun-ji, you got an ad gig on your own.
Ri-a and Ma-ha,
you'll get to go on "Y.M.S.A."!
Y.M.S.A.? "You, Me, Singing Again"?
Yes.
Ma-ha, Ri-a.
This is amazing!
I'm so glad! I knew you two would do well!
You too, Hyun-ji.
What's going on?
My gosh.
This is your power, Tea Party!
Come here!
-This is so great.
-This is great.
[KBC]
And now, Kwon Ryoc and Ma-ha
will get to choose.
["You, Me, Singing Again"]
Who do you want on your team?
[Epilogue]
[Chairman Seok Jin-wook, Investor]
Yes, Chairman.
Hey, I can't reach CEO Park.
He's probably in a meeting for...
-"Probably?"
-Sorry?
He's busy out there
trying to grow this business,
but you don't know what he's doing
as his right-hand man?
-No, that's not what I meant.
-Forget it. Hang up.
I'm sorry.
This is exactly why you need
competent people working for you.
Who does he think did all the work?
I did all the work!
That darned Mr. Park.
I can't believe
I'm working with these people.
[NOG]
La Ri-ma alone costs quite a lot.
Unbelievable.
Why take the difficult route?
Everyone around me
thinks I'm a joke.
Man, I don't want to live
like a servant anymore.
[NOG Entertainment]