[English subtitles are available]
[Crush]
[Episode 17]
Here.
Thank you.
It's only been a few months.
Why do I feel that you've grown taller?
It's been more than just a few months.
The last time we met each other
was more than six months ago.
Mr Su, you almost forgot about me,
haven't you?
I was a little occupied at work.
What about Ms Sang?
You told me she's busy with work.
She's never visited me since then.
Is she never free?
Ms Sang is also very busy.
Please don't blame her.
I miss Ms Sang so much.
I really miss her too.
Mr Su, when you told me the story,
you said that
Ms Sang recorded the story for you.
Will you let me listen to it?
No.
It's only for me.
How petty.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just received a phone call
from Director Xia from Finance.
It's about the acquisition of Toro.
The result of their internal assessment
is out.
They would like to have a meeting
with you and the legal department.
What do you think?
Send Xiao Wei home.
Notify them that the meeting
will be held in an hour.
I'll see you again...
It's okay.
[World Trade Business Centre]
Okay.
I'll report it to our boss.
By the way, Xu Qian,
regarding Toro's case,
did our boss tell you anything?
Does he plan to name you
as the leader of the project?
Me?
Forget it. It's nothing.
I have to go.
Don't lower yourself to his standard.
We've been working for such a long time.
You should know him well by now.
What's wrong with him?
Why did he say something strange?
What's wrong, Ms Fei Fei?
Even you...
Haven't you heard about it?
About what?
Why are you so slow?
The affair between you and our boss
has been getting around.
Some people claimed that they saw him
sending you home after office hours.
Let me remind you.
Our company
is against office romance.
In general,
it's usually the female staff
who resigned in the end.
You should be ready.
Ms Fei Fei, believe it or not,
I've never been together with our boss.
[Dried Peaches]
Can't you bring me to your office?
I'll just sit at the side.
I promise I won't say a word.
There are many
confidential documents in the office.
If something happens,
you can never clear your name.
All right.
Take it.
I bought you a makeup remover,
as you requested.
I don't know if I have got it right.
Peaches were not available
in the supermarket.
Hence, I got you dried peaches.
Don't eat too much. It's heaty.
All right, got it.
Give it to me.
I just have to work overtime.
Go back now.
I'll go home now.
Send me a text message when you're
almost done. I'll pick you up.
Why did you come back out of the blue?
Did something happen?
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
It's quite scary.
Just tell me if anything.
What happened?
I resigned.
I've decided to move back.
I was wrong.
I didn't figure out what I wanted.
I blamed everything on you.
Hold on.
I'm confused.
Let me ask you a simple question.
Do you still want me?
Won't you blame me?
Are you silly?
No matter what happens, I won't blame you.
Hold on.
If you come back,
you won't be able
to make big money anymore.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to go out
and make big money?
No, I don't mean that.
Let me sustain your life from now on.
Besides paying my grandma,
I've saved up a lot.
If I come home,
I would become jobless.
If you don't want me anymore,
I'll lose both you and money at once.
Of course I want you.
What are you doing?
Why are you loitering around
late at night?
What is going on?
Isn't this Xu Qian?
Come, let's go home.
I haven't even gotten to hold her hand!
Sang Wu Yan, you...
You mean you're going to propose to her?
You two have only just made up
and you're already proposing to her?
Isn't it a tad reckless?
It's called strike while the iron is hot.
While she's confused, I have to act fast.
Otherwise, she might run away again.
That's right.
Grandma, I'm here to see you.
Look, I got a lot of goodies for you.
Have an orange first.
Grandma.
Let me tell you a secret.
Do you know that Wei Hao
plans to propose to Xu Qian?
It's not confirmed at the moment
but it'll eventually become true.
Why are you standing here?
Are you going to propose to me?
I haven't come out with the plan.
You're a typical science student.
Don't bother.
Since my grandma is here,
just admit that you want to marry me.
Yes.
Okay, I'll marry you.
See?
I told you I could make it happen.
Dear, take a rest.
Let me do it.
How disgusting.
No couple on earth is innocent.
Here.
Eat more.
Mum, you've gone too far.
Mind your own business.
Xu Qian, eat more.
Look at you, your chin is so sharp.
She never puts on weight in the face.
Her chin has always been that sharp.
Xu Qian, how do you like the dishes?
All the dishes that you ordered
are delicious.
You'll have to address us
as mum and dad soon, right?
Mr and Mrs Wei,
I think there is something
I need to explain to you.
Although it's a little soon
for Wei Hao and I to get married,
and it appears to be a hasty decision,
I've thought it through.
I know full well that
marriage binds two families.
Therefore,
I think I need to be honest
about my family background.
Wei Hao has told us about it.
We understand the whole situation.
You must've endured a lot
since your childhood,
haven't you?
After listening to Wei Hao,
I admire you more.
If I were you,
I wouldn't achieve
what you have achieved for sure.
It's okay.
Thank you, Mrs Wei.
There's no need for thanks.
Family takes care of family.
I think your husband is almost ready.
I'll go get him.
Sure.
What did I say?
I knew that
you could handle Mr and Mrs Wei well.
It's because they're really nice to me.
Were you looking for this?
You left it behind
when you're getting changed.
Hence, I kept it for you.
I can't believe that
I'm looking at Sang Wu Yan
who used to leave things behind.
Why do you look so beautiful
in a wedding gown?
You're so beautiful.
Wu Yan, I always think that
you're so much luckier than me.
You know about my family.
Since I was young,
I always had to work so hard.
I always had to curry favour
with people around me.
To be honest,
I envy you.
Why did you say that?
Wei Hao makes me understand that
I must not think that way.
Everyone
has their own life and happy moments.
I shouldn't compare my weaknesses
with others all the time..
I just have to grasp my own.
Now, I got it.
I'm very happy now.
All the best to you too.
I bet the groom is getting impatient now.
[No one is a lone island.]
[There is always a song
that will get into your heart.]
[Welcome to "The Lone Island Playlist".]
[An audience said that]
[he's been requesting this song
to be played]
[Tongcheng Music Broadcast]
but it's never been selected.
All right, his request is granted.
[Crush]
Let's listen to the last song written by
the mysterious songwriter, Yi Jin.
♫ Every time I thought I would cry ♫
♫ When the light fades away ♫
♫ I look for the familiar voice
around me ♫
♫ Slowly penetrating the tides
and raindrops ♫
Excuse me, I was trapped in the traffic.
It's okay.
This is the first song.
Thanks.
♫ Even though I try to carry on ♫
♫ And I leave my past behind ♫
♫ I feel like I can hear your breathing ♫
♫ And the night turns translucent ♫
♫ Be it the city or forest ♫
[Crush]
♫ A gloomy tranquillity ♫
♫ Lost in the midst ♫
♫ I close my eyes ♫
♫ But I see your silhouette ♫
♫ Forever shine for me ♫
♫ Unafraid even when faced
with the unknown future ♫
♫ Because you're
the only thing I think about ♫
♫ I only think about you ♫
♫ Forever shine for me ♫
♫ Never doubting even when I continue on ♫
Boss.
The latest romantic
and thriller movies are here.
They're here.
Thanks.
Is there anything else?
Boss.
Yi Jin's "Crush" was played.
I heard it.
Boss, may I know why?
Why do you always want me
to request the song?
Isn't the song nice?
Of course it's nice.
I actually think that
girls will be fond of the song.
I knew that you would be here
visiting your grandma.
I went home and no one was in.
I guess you're here.
Keep quiet.
Let's talk outside.
What do you want?
Why do you speak that way?
I mean it.
What do you want this time?
Why did you come back
if nothing had happened?
I came back because of your wedding.
My daughter is getting married.
Of course I have to be there.
Who informed you about it?
Did I invite you?
To be honest,
I really admire you.
How did you do this?
You can pretend
nothing has happened.
If I don't do that,
how do I face you?
Yes.
I know I've hurt you
but I also know that
I can never make up to it.
It's been so many years.
If you really hate me to the core,
you'd better do what you said.
Never live my life.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
Don't you worry.
Qian Qian,
I only hope that
I could witness my daughter's wedding.
After the wedding,
I'll leave immediately.
Again?
Whatever.
Mum.
The wedding lasted for the whole day.
Are you exhausted?
Xu Qian purposely
passed the flower to you.
You get the meaning, right?
Remember Xiao Xiao
who came to our place last time?
What do you think of him?
I think he's quite okay.
He's nice and polite.
His height is okay too.
Who is that?
Your dad's former student.
How could you forget him?
He always called you
"little girl".
Forget it.
At your university,
is there any guy who gets along with you?
Yes.
He's helping me
in conducting research for my thesis.
How is he?
Don't you even think about it.
He's already married.
Look at you.
We're talking about something serious.
Got it.
[Interview with RD Group CEO,
Su Nian Qin]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going on a blind date tomorrow.
Your mum sure acts fast.
Of course.
Look at you.
It's just to meet a person.
Have you confirmed the details?
Yes.
That person is really funny.
I thought
I could contact him by phone.
However,
he insisted on wearing
a brown jacket
so that I could recognise him.
The moment I heard that,
I decided to do the same.
Why don't you hold a copy of
"Best Friends" in your right hand
and a rose in your left hand?
And have a secret pass code too,
such as "I won't tell you anything"?
What nonsense is that?
Go away.
I'll have to meet him tomorrow.
What a drag.
So Ms Sang, you're Professor Li's
graduate student.
[How was the blind date?]
It was okay.
What does "okay" mean?
It means it's not okay.
Why?
I'm still studying, my dear mum.
If I date him,
it'd become a teacher-student affair.
There's no way I'd do that.
Ms Sang, when will you graduate?
Next year.
I'm interested in applying as a
postgraduate at your university.
I would like to know,
how did you study for
the postgraduate entrance examination?
Just study and do worksheets.
I also got a senior
who had passed the examination
to help me with the revision.
Do you mind helping me with the revision?
Last year, I failed English
and a core course.
I would like to try it again.
Was he even there for a blind date?
He's there with an intention.
He's there to look for a tuition teacher.
I see.
Yan Yan, be patient.
I have a new guy to introduce to you.
Take a break, my dear mum.
Do you know
I'm becoming famous
in the academic world
in our hometown?
Do you plan to introduce me
to all the single male teachers?
Have faith in me one last time.
The guy I'm about to introduce to you
is such a rare gem.
Not only is he nice, but handsome too.
And tall.
And he has an impressive career.
Mum.
What subject does he teach?
Is he teaching in high school
or elementary school?
He's a lawyer!
[Crush]
♫ Every time I thought I would cry ♫
♫ When the light fades away ♫
[Su Nian Qin, Sang Wu Yan]
♫ I look for the familiar voice
around me ♫
♫ Slowly penetrating the tides
and raindrops ♫
[Crush]
♫ Even though I try to carry on ♫
♫ And I leave my past behind ♫
♫ I feel like I can hear your breathing ♫
Are you practising your writing?
Nian Qin, I think
you should know about something.
[Wu Yu]
Mr Su.
Hello, thanks for coming.
Hello.
It must have been a long journey.
♫ If ears and promises ♫
♫ Hadn't met each other ♫
♫ If wishes and future ♫
♫ Hadn't come into contact ♫
♫ Perhaps ♫
♫ We could pretend ♫
♫ That nothing has happened ♫
♫ Move on easily ♫
♫ When forever is still ♫
♫ Not too far away ♫
♫ When a hug is still ♫
♫ Connected to love ♫
♫ Throw everything aside ♫
♫ And bet on the uncertain tomorrow ♫
♫ What's left are lies ♫
♫ That can't come full circle ♫
Ms Sang.
What's wrong?
♫ Who is willing to take the fall? ♫
Are you okay?
Nothing, my head
is pounding out of a sudden.
♫ And give up on taking the initiative ♫
♫ Spending all the years ♫
What's wrong?
♫ In exchange for an apology ♫
♫ Is it stubbornness or determination? ♫
♫ Refuse to listen to people's advice ♫
Ms Sang.
♫ Watching the memories ♫
It's a rare surname.
♫ Burn in flames ♫
You are...
♫ ♫ I'm willing to take the fall ♫ ♫
My surname is Su.
♫ But I can't escape from rising ♫
I'm Ms Su's old friend in Xiamen.
♫ The hurt along the way ♫
♫ Can only be written, not erased ♫
Perhaps
she's forgotten about me.
♫ The blue past ♫
♫ Is now covered in snow ♫
I see.
Nice to meet you.
♫ How can love melt away? ♫
And you are...
Ms Sang and I...
He's my boyfriend.
♫ If we had brushed past each other
without looking up ♫
Are you not going to introduce him?
He...
♫ If we hadn't moved beyond friendship ♫
♫ What we hope for
is an unpredictable gamble ♫
His surname is...
My surname is Wu.
My name is Wu Yu.
♫ A precious chance ♫
♫ Who is willing to take the fall? ♫
♫ And give up on taking the initiative ♫
Boss, it's time for the meeting.
♫ Spending all the years
in exchange for an apology ♫
♫ Is it stubbornness or determination? ♫
♫ Refuse to listen to people's advice ♫
♫ Watching the memories burn in flames ♫
Let's take a seat.
This way.
I guess you've heard about it.
I'm a lawyer.
I'm usually quite busy at work.
I don't have any hobbies.
Also, I...
I'm sorry.
Sorry to interrupt.
Mr Wu,
my boss would like a few words
with your girlfriend.
Would you mind?
Of course not.
Well...
I'm sorry, Mr Wu.
Sorry to have troubled you.
I have to go now.
There's nothing much to talk
about between me and your boss.
Sang Wu Yan!
I'm sorry.
You can see now?
You just noticed that?
You're not
[paying attention to me at all.]
Congratulations.
Long time no see
and you look more energetic now.
It looks like you're living quite well.
What do you do for a living?
[Su Nian Qin]
This is my name card.
Are you here
on a business trip
or a vacation?
Sang Wu Yan, don't worry.
I didn't come here for you.
Without you,
I can live well too.
That's great.
I'll get going then.
[Wu Yan, how's the meeting
with the lawyer?]
Mum,
I'll tell you about it when I go home.
I'm tired.
I have to go for now.
What happened during the blind date?
Don't mention it.
Did you run into
that guy who intends to apply
as a postgraduate at our university?
No.
I ran into him.
Who?
Su Nian Qin.
I was wondering.
Mr Su is unbeatable.
Is he here for you?
He told me
he's not here for me.
Why do you simply believe in him?
You were fooled by him before.
Will you stop bringing up the past?
Haven't I told you?
I'm no longer the old me.
["The Lone Island Playlist"
has come to an end.]
[Su Nian Qin, stop dreaming.]
[Can you even consider yourself a man?]
[She has made it clear.]
[She doesn't want to see you again.]
Boss, do you want to switch on the lights?
Just switch the lights on
if you need them.
I think we should switch on the lights.
It's warmer that way.
[It's the warmth.]
[Sunlight]
[is not all about brightness.]
[Warmth is very important too.]
The collaboration with Toro
moves on smoothly.
The agreement is drafted.
You'll need to make a trip
to Toro's office tomorrow morning
for a meeting
with their senior administrators.
Also,
the branch office manager
hopes that you can
pay the employees a visit.
Ms Yu called.
She hopes that you could return her call
when you're free.
Boss.
Are you done?
That's all.
What else do you need?
Bring me
the agreement that we're
going to discuss with Toro tomorrow.
As for the trip to the branch office,
make arrangements for it.
All right, got it.
What is the phone number?
It's 101.
Do you need anything?
I need a bottle of liquor.
Ms Yu said that
your eyes...
[If reading
is taking a toll on your eyes,]
[just let someone read it for you.]
[If you need to note it down,]
[then just jot it down.]
Please send me a bottle of whiskey.
[Chinese privet and Ilex
are not the same thing.]
[What is this?]
[It's aloe vera.]
[Here.]
[These are eyebrows. They're messy.]
[That's because
I don't take care of them.]
[These are eyes.]
[These are eyelashes.]
[Eyelashes are thick.]
[My eyes always get teary]
[but I have good eyesight.]
[Su Nian Qin,]
[I don't want to see you again
for the rest of my life.]
Wu Yan.
Wu Yan?
[Tongcheng University
Autism Research Centre]
Madam, based on our analysis,
Xiao Jie has autism,
but there are no problems
with his intellect.
He might even have some hidden talents.
The autism that you mentioned...
Is it a serious illness?
We're from the countryside.
I don't think we can afford the treatment.
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
Please take a look at the agreement.
What does it mean?
It means with the consent
of the guardian,
we'll give him basic support
and treatment.
So if I sign the agreement,
you will give him treatment?
Is that right?
To put it simply, yes.
However, if you have any concerns...
Patients with severe autism
require lots of support,
whether in terms
of language or socialising skills.
I think you have conducted
preliminary examination.
You may take a look at the details.
Wu Yan, I need to remind you.
Treating him will be a tough battle.
You need to be mentally prepared.
We mustn't take in a patient
on impulse
and give up later on.
Some people do it just
for their thesis writing purposes.
In the end, they will be left unattended.
We can't do that.
I got it.
Don't worry.
[Toro]
Dismiss.
Nian Qin.
This is Ms Peng, the former owner of Toro.
Ms Peng, how may I help you?
Just call me Dan Qi.
You don't have to be so polite.
We were busy attending
the meeting just now.
I forgot to exchange name cards with you.
I'm sorry.
I gave the last name card
to someone else yesterday.
It's okay.
Nian Qin, I heard that this is
the first time you're in Tongcheng.
Do you want me to show you around?
Thank you for the offer, Ms Peng.
However, I have a tight schedule today.
I'm sorry.
Let me be the host tonight.
I'll buy you a welcome dinner.
You should have time for dinner, right?
Thank you for the invitation, Ms Peng.
I want to get changed.
Her perfume has tainted my suit.
Okay.
Thank you.
What are you looking for?
Where is the MP3 player
that I always have with me?
Did you leave it in the hotel?
Go back to the hotel now.
What about the dinner with Ms Peng?
I'll skip it.