[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[The show is an adapted fiction based on
stories of National Park Rangers.]
[All characters, events, regions,]
[organizations depicted in the show
are fictitious.]
[The Black Bridge Valley area.
Don't ever go north.]
[Black Bridge Village.]
Have you forgotten
all that's happened there?
This place is perfect for cable cars.
We have no intention of moving out.
Get out of here.
You'll regret this.
It's him! The cable car man.
He messed with the well
to kick us out from here!
[Most villagers have left.]
I'm not leaving!
[It's all because of him.]
[If he hadn't ruined the well...]
The deceased was holding this.
Did you really do this?
Did you do that to everyone else?
Tell Yi-gang at Haedong Ranger Station
that I didn't leave the mark this time.
He said he didn't leave the mark
this time?
[If it wasn't Hyun-jo,]
[Who and why would they leave a mark?]
[Episode 11]
[Yi-gang!]
[Can you hear me?]
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
What have you been doing here?
[No Entry]
Why did you try to go up there
in such a state?
I heard the commander got arrested.
I also heard that a cell phone
and gloves were found.
How were they found?
-Thanks.
-No worries.
You know...
[Haedong Ranger Station, Entrance]
Anyone can take the gloves
if they want to.
Don't people wash the gloves
at the ranger station with other uniforms?
If one is a national park ranger,
taking some gloves would be easy.
I'm just saying.
See you, then.
[Damsung Police Station]
The investigation is still ongoing,
but he's denying all charges.
[Meeting Room]
Detectives are looking into
relevant facts.
But I think he'll be released soon.
[Meeting Room]
I came to ask you something.
On the day that Da-won died...
Why did you go to Jeonmukgol?
Do you still
suspect me for this?
I only...
want to know what happened on that day.
I don't know
what happened to her either.
If I'd brought her down with me
on that day,
she would probably still be alive.
That's all I can think of.
I saw blood-stained yellow ribbons.
Why were they in your desk drawer?
The ribbons that mislead hikers...
The poisoned yogurts...
You knew about them.
Is that why you're back?
How did you know that?
Time's almost up.
Go see Il-hae.
I told him everything I know.
Hello?
[Sekyung Central Hospital]
[Intensive Care Unit]
He's been able to breathe by himself
even though he was unconscious,
but since the seizure,
he's unable to do that.
If this state continues,
he might be declared brain dead.
His family knows about the situation.
I think they'll make a decision soon.
Before that...
If the time comes to let Hyun-jo go...
Please let me know in advance. Please.
We will.
[You must be unable to leave the mountain]
[because of your desire
to catch the murderer.]
[So what if...]
[What if I catch the murderer...]
[Will you be able to wake up?]
[This mountain listens
to people's prayers,]
[Perhaps it'll hear my prayer]
[of wanting to save you.]
[Another death on Mount Jirisan
has been reported.]
[The police have found signs of homicide
on this case,]
[and they're investigating
the main suspect.]
We need to talk.
Whatever it's about, let's talk later.
We must talk now.
It's important.
Didn't you run off to the headquarters
complaining about your leg?
Did you come with Yi-gang?
You suspect the commander, too?
No.
Not the commander.
You asked why I came back.
Someone's been killing people
on the mountains, disguised as accidents.
I came to find out who that is.
What are you talking about?
The commander was thinking
the same thing as Yi-gang.
That someone's been killing people
on the mountain.
[Mount Jirisan National Park
Missing Person Search Report]
[Name of victim: Yang Geun-tak]
He got lost in Yiseokjae,
but his body was found somewhere else,
near Gaeam Falls.
That's right.
The commander found it fishy
and looked around the area
where the victim was found.
[Then he found strange ribbons
near the valley above Gaeam Falls.]
[Ribbons?]
What ribbons?
Like the ones illegal hikers use?
Yes.
Not just there.
[Name of victim: Choi Gi-yeong]
This missing case was from this February,
in Oerae Valley.
This person was also found
near Bongjaeam Rock,
far away from where he got lost.
The commander patrolled the area
just in case,
[and found another set of ribbons.]
[Above Gaeam Falls and Bongjaeam Rock
are so dangerous]
that illegal hikers rarely go there.
But why were the ribbons there?
Someone led them there to get lost.
[The path in the opposite direction
from the peak.]
[The criminal led them
to the rough mountain path]
[where hikers can easily get lost.]
But...
it's not just the ribbons.
Please give this to Seo Yi-gang.
You don't have to do this.
We're only doing our job.
But thank you.
Goodness. She saved my life.
Hwang told me that someone left
a yogurt drink in Jeonmukgol, too.
Excuse me?
I mean, he didn't go to collect herbs
or anything...
A yogurt?
Remember? I also drank one
and almost died before.
The commander went to Jeonmukgol
that day to look for this.
He came to see me with it,
asking for an ingredient check
at the headquarters.
So what happened? Did you get the result?
It's too old and spoiled
to identify the ingredients.
Hang on.
Then it's only the commander's guess.
Right?
It could've been a coincidence.
The ribbons could have blown away.
The yogurt could have gone bad.
Hyun-jo knew about this.
What do you mean?
Hyun-jo knew who the murderer was.
And who would that be?
You asked
why we went up the snowy mountain.
[Year 2019]
[Kang Hyun-jo]
Hyun-jo, where are you right now?
Kang Hyun-jo!
[CCTV In Operation]
[Even on that day,]
[Hyun-jo was chasing the criminal alone.]
Are you all right?
Yi-gang...
Maybe it's the heavy snow,
but there's no radio signal.
I'll go check
if my phone signal works anywhere.
Please wait here for a moment.
On top of the cornice...
Someone left a pole on purpose.
Hyun-jo, you know...
Hang in there.
I’ll be right back.
[He went out to report,]
and never came back.
Right, I heard that he called
the station that morning.
Haedong Ranger Station.
[Black Bridge...]
[Yi-gang's hurt.]
Hello? Hyun-jo?
I can't hear you. Where are you?
[Black Bridge Valley!]
[Quick!]
Seo Yi-gang!
Hyun-jo.
Kang Hyun-jo!
Seo Yi-gang.
-Kang Hyun-jo!
-Yi-gang!
-Is that Hyun-jo?
-Hyun-jo!
Hyun-jo!
Hyun-jo.
He has no pulse!
No pulse, sir.
That wasn't just an accident.
We weren't the only ones
up on the mountain that day.
Seo Yi-gang!
You mean someone tried to kill you two?
Who's that? Did you tell the police?
You're saying,
there was someone else
at the site besides you and Hyun-jo?
Yes. Someone left a pole
on a snow cornice.
-That person led us to get into this.
-I'm not asking about that.
Did that person threaten you in any way?
No...
But he had blood on his clothes.
I'm sure Hyun-jo got hurt
because of him, too.
Did you witness Mr. Kang Hyun-jo get hurt?
No one believed me.
But, someone was surely there.
Though I couldn't see the face...
We must find the person.
That way,
we can clear the commander's name.
How can we? We don't know who it was.
There is a way.
What's that?
Black Bridge Valley.
Hyun-jo went there before the accident.
There must be evidence there.
What evidence?
I'm not sure yet.
But we'll find out when we get there.
Please take me there.
I can't do this alone.
Please. Help me.
[No Entry]
-One, two, three!
-Let's go.
I said we can go by ourselves.
How will you get there without assistance?
[4 hours ago]
[Honam Express]
[No Smoking Building]
Jeong Gu-yeong?
No way. Why would he?
It has to be one of the park rangers.
The murderer was wearing our uniform.
Gu-yeong was on the mountain
when Da-won got lost.
He could've easily got
the commander's gloves.
So? What are we going to do?
Take Gu-yeong in?
No. The police won't believe us.
We must take him ourselves.
Once he finds out I have crucial evidence.
he'll try to kill me.
-Let's get the proof then.
-No.
No way.
You could get into danger.
Be careful.
There.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
By the way...
Why did you go to the mountain that day?
The day Da-won went missing.
Why did you go there?
Da-won?
Is that you?
[No Entry]
I had things to do.
Let's get going.
[One thing
I couldn't tell you guys about...]
[Hyun-jo.]
[If I end up dying,]
[maybe I can meet Hyun-jo.]
[If I see him,]
[maybe I could tell him
what I couldn't hear,]
[what I couldn't say.]
Let's take a break here.
[Warning: Bear Frequenting Area]
Here.
Thank you.
How long have you and Hyun-jo
known about this?
Have you two been investigating
the whole time?
That's why you two were always together.
Did Hyun-jo tell you anything
before the accident on the snowy mountain?
No.
After that incident last summer,
I haven't been able to see him.
Last summer...
A lot of bad things happened.
[Year 2019]
Gosh.
Why do we lose every single game?
You shouldn't throw
the "yut" sticks so hard.
You only throw "do" every time.
Hey! We could've easily won
if you avoided "geol" there.
Exactly.
You should use your brain more often.
You said you saw black hiking gloves.
Yes.
As you're aware, there are plenty of
black hiking gloves on Mount Jirisan.
And I don't mean just rangers.
If you include hikers and residents,
you can't even count them.
[No drinking allowed in the national park]
We can't catch the murderer
just with the gloves.
It has to do with the mountain.
All the victims had something to do
with the mountain.
Poachers, herb collectors...
Hyeon-su, who died during the march,
also said that this is his hometown.
Again.
There are plenty of people who have lived
near Mount Jirisan for generations.
It could just be a coincidence.
But why?
Why is the murderer
killing people on this mountain?
One thing I'm sure of.
It's a totally crazy person.
You know what though?
What?
Today's our one-year anniversary.
Are we dating?
Why would you keep track of that?
I didn't say that.
I just meant it's been a year
since the day we saved Seung-hun.
So what?
Do you want to celebrate
with a cake or something?
Seriously.
My goodness.
Hey, go run the errands by yourself.
Huh? But we lost together.
I'm busy!
Gosh, seriously...
[Bidam Shelter]
Look who it is!
Loser Hyun-jo!
-Hurry over here.
-Hurry up!
[Sand]
This is lukewarm.
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
It's four hours to get here.
That's 240 minutes.
Back in my day, we carried an icebox
with drinks on our heads.
-Filled with ice.
-I'm leaving.
Hey!
That's my drumstick!
Hey! That's not yours.
This one's spicy.
How dare he take the crispy one?
Really?
[Weather Conditions]
Ready to go?
So...
Loser Seo Yi-gang.
We'll head out first.
See you tomorrow.
[2019 Summer Disaster Prevention Workshop]
Hello? Hello?
What happened?
I saw a collapsed man
on my way down the mountain.
I shook him, but he didn't wake up
and didn't seem to be breathing either.
I was too scared, and my battery ran out.
-So I just ran...
-Where did you see him?
Well, so... Where was it?
[Haedong One. An injured man reported
at 2.5km on the trail, near Sonbawi Rock.]
Kang Hyun-jo speaking.
I'm 2km away from Sonbawi Rock.
I'll mobilize.
[I'll leave now, too.]
[It seemed like he was unable to breathe.
Hurry up.]
Are you all right?
Have you called the police?
I'll keep watch until the police arrive.
You go down first.
It's fine. I'm a ranger, too.
Remember...
I told you about my colleague
who died on the mountain?
Back then,
his military dog tags...
were never found.
That kept bothering me,
so I came here to look for it.
[This mountain frightened me]
[since Hyeon-su had died.]
[But I wanted to find his belongings]
[and return it to his family.]
[I walked with my head down,]
[because I didn't want to see
anything else.]
[I only thought about
finding the dog tags.]
[That was the only thing on my mind.]
[But on that day,]
[the mountain looked beautiful.]
[The mountain I saw that day
wasn't an object of fear.]
I don't know why he came here today.
But...
I hope he got comforted by
the mountain like I did.
[These flowers represent happiness.]
[2019 Summer Disaster Workshop]
Mr. Needle.
Are you looking for Ms. Thread?
I think you're the needle and the thread.
-Should we sit here?
-Yes.
You haven't had breakfast, right?
Here, try this. It's good.
-Thank you.
-The coffee's hot.
I also haven't had breakfast yet.
It's almost lunchtime. You should wait.
Is it good?
Let me know if you want more.
Yi-gang took a day off today.
I'm sure she doesn't want to be here.
Is everyone here?
-Hello, sir.
-Sit, sit.
[2019 Summer Disasters
Prevention Workshop]
I'll go ahead since everyone's here.
The most representative summer disaster
is a torrential downpour.
There's a saying,
"clouds hang on the mountain ridge."
When rain clouds can't pass over huge
mountains over a thousand meters high,
local torrential rainfall can occur,
which is unpredictable by weather forecast
and is therefore dangerous.
[Such local torrential rainfall
is dangerous]
[because it's pouring on the top
of the mountain but clear below,]
so it's hard to estimate the danger.
The rougher the geographical features,
the more water it'll collect,
increasing ever so fast.
[At its fastest,
it'll be 3 meters per second in speed]
[and engulf downstream.]
[That is strong enough to uproot
trees and wipe buildings away.]
Like the expression,
"water comes standing,"
it might be too late
by the time you detect danger.
A good example would be
the Dowon Valley flood in 1995.
[Over 200mm of torrential downpour
occurred then,]
[sweeping everything in the valley]
in less than an hour.
We were helpless in the past,
but not anymore.
Thanks to the response systems
such as AWS and automatic rain gauge,
casualties are decreasing.
But we still need to be vigilant.
Take special caution
on preventing flood-related accidents
by fortifying patrols during
the disaster prevention period
for illegal camping and cooking
in the national park and on campsites
near valleys vulnerable to flooding.
-Yes, sir.
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
Put that in the cabinet.
You know it's the village ancestral rites
today, right?
Come to the town hall and help.
So...
Yi-gang's parents...
How did they pass away?
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
The shelter they were in
got swept away by a flood.
I understand why Yi-gang doesn't want
to come to the ritual.
What?
There are records from before
the building got swept away.
Records?
Yes.
There's a notebook
with people's conversations from that day.
They put it in a safe just in case,
and it got found later.
Everyone there
left a will to their family,
but only Yi-gang's parents
didn't leave a single word.
That must have been hard on her.
[Closing early today.
Sorry for any inconvenience.]
Hey! Where are you going again?
I told you, not today.
We're in charge of the food this year.
You want me to cook everything alone?
You're not alone.
You have plenty of helpers around.
What are you saying? Hey!
If it's that hard, don't do it.
Stop right there! You brat.
When will you stop being like this?
Won't you prepare a ritual table for me
when I die?
Stop saying that.
What are you saying?
Hey!
Oh, that brat. What will I do with her?
Gosh, what a pain in the neck!
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
-You must be from the national park.
-Yes, we are.
Thank you for coming out.
[Yang Geun-tak, President of Mount Jirisan
Cable Car Promotion Committee]
-There's 11 of you in total, right?
-Yes.
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
We'll be climbing 7km to Deokseoryeong
as you requested.
Today, we'll spend the night
at Bidam Shelter,
and climb the rest tomorrow.
Very good.
What about the environmental organization
who are coming with us?
Here.
Hello, sir.
-There's five of you, right?
-Yes.
Do you have all your stuff?
Then, let's roll.
How have you been, sir?
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
Yes?
Where else? I'm on the mountain.
Because of the lottery ticket, of course.
Okay. I'll call you back.
[Yi-gang]
[Your call cannot be completed...]
[Village Hall]
Why are you so late?
Is Yi-gang here?
Do you even listen to me?
I told you she's not coming.
Hey!
Why are slacking off?
What? I've been working so hard till now.
Enough of that. Go put these on the table.
-You should help, too.
-Yes.
You...
I did all this.
[Dump trucks not allowed in village]
[Haedong Village Volunteer Rangers]
[Choi Il-man]
[Choi Il-man.]
[Choi Il-man, October 15, 2018]
[Potato bomb exploded
at the tombs in Saemagol]
[Kim Jin-deok]
[Kim Jin-deok.]
[Kim Jin-deok, March 23, 2018
Fell and died in Narigol, Daeyeong-ri]
[Lee Jong-gu.]
[Lee Jong-gu, Jan. 20, 2018]
[Fell and died
from Buam Cliff, Deokseoryeong]
[Haedong Village Volunteer Rangers]
Why are they together?
Hey, get to work.
[Dump trucks not allowed in village]
Gu-yeong.
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
You said there were records
of the 1995 flooding.
-Yes.
-Where are they now?
In the document room
at the main station. Why?
Hey! What...
Let's get some work done.
[Document Room: Authorized Personnel Only]
You can look for it on this shelf.
Thank you.
[Photos at the scene]
[List of people evacuated
from Dowon Valley]
[Park Jae-il, Han Cheon-yung, Lee Joo-hee]
[Choi Il-man, Lee Jong-gu,
Kim Jin-deok, Jo Dae-jin]
[Dowon Valley Flood Victims
at Mujin Station]
[Seo Yung-jin, Yoon Su-mi
Lee Hyun-sik, Jeong Mi-ja, Kim Nam-sik]
[Record Number 1]
[August Status Log]
[Flood Status Log]
[8:45 a.m. Showers continued
and water in the valley started to rise.]
[1:15 p.m. Damage on deck detected.]
[Stones and sand
from the trail got inside.]
[Removed dangerous objects.]
[2:20 p.m. Water in the valley kept
rising due to heavy rainfalls.]
[3:50 p.m. Rainfall got severe.]
[Valley starts to flood.
Reached out to the main station.]
[4:50 p.m. Contacted the main station
to report damage,]
[but due to the worsening weather,
call got cut off.]
[No radio signal either.]
[Log Details]
[5:15 p.m. 5 hikers, volunteer rangers,]
[and 2 residents who were isolated at
a nearby campsite escaped to the office.]
[Hikers, an old man
with a fractured leg and his wife.]
[3 college students.]
[3 college students]
[Volunteer ranger squad Choi Il-man]
[Volunteer ranger squad Choi Il-man,
Lee Jong-gu, Kim Jin-deok.]
[Residents Seo Yeong-jin, Yoon Su-mi.]
[Residents Seo Yeong-jin, Yoon Su-mi]
[Rangers Jo Dae-jin, Kim Nam-sik.]
[Decided to wait on the first floor
in the shelter.]
[7:34 p.m. The bridge collapsed.]
What happened?
-Have you contacted the rescue team?
-Yes.
They said they were leaving,
so they'll be here soon.
Let's just get out on our own.
-We'll all die if we stay.
-Yes.
Let's just go.
Please wait.
For how long?
[8 p.m. No rescue squad yet.]
[People started discussing the possibility
of escaping the office building.]
-Oh gosh.
-Ouch.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, we're good.
See? We must move now.
Wait!
I'm so scared.
I'll cross first and connect the rope.
It's too dangerous.
The current is too fast.
I'll try. I'll go bring the rescue squad.
-Let me come with you.
-Me, too!
Let's go.
-I'll go, too.
-Let's go.
Let's get out!
I'll stay here.
We'll stay, too.
If anything happens,
you could use some help.
We'll return soon to rescue you all.
Are you all right?
I'm so scared...
[9:32 p.m. 2 hikers and 2 residents left
in the office building.]
[August Status Log]
[Kim Nam-sik]
[9:40 p.m. Water level has exceeded 1m,]
[and the building has tilted
more to the left.]
Why are you writing that?
No one will be able to see it.
I'll put it in the safe.
We should let people know
what happened here.
Can I write in it, too?
I want to leave a message to my children.
Won-sik, Won-jae.
Thank you for everything.
I wish you good health and happiness.
Would you like to write something?
No, thank you.
And you?
Don't you want to leave a message?
I did leave a message.
[Won-sik, Won-jae.
Thank you for everything.]
[I wish you good health and happiness.]
[My dear son Hyeon-su.]
[Take care of your mother.]
[I hope you continue to be healthy
like now.]
[Kim Nam-sik,
Mount Jirisan National Park Ranger]
[Kim Nam-sik]
[My dear son Hyeon-su.]
Hyeon-su...
Kim Hyeon-su.
Kim Hyeon-su, are you all right?
This is your hometown, right?
-That's right, sir!
-It's a nice place.
I hope your hometown energizes you.
[Yes, Captain Kang.]
I need to check something.
Could you give me the full name
of Private Kim Hyeon-su's father?
[Sir?]
It's urgent. Please check for me.
[Hold on, please.]
[I'm in the administration office now,
so let me pull that up.]
[Hyeon-su]
[Captain, I found it.]
[Private Kim's father's name]
[is Kim Nam-sik.]
[Kim Nam-sik]
[List of people evacuated
from Dowon Valley]
[Choi Il-man, Lee Jong-gu,
Kim Jin-deok, Jo Dae-jin]
[Dowon Valley Flood Victims
at Mujin Station]
[Seo Yung-jin, Yoon Su-mi
Lee Hyun-sik, Jeong Mi-ja, Kim Nam-sik]
[Kim Nam-sik]
[My dear son Hyeon-su.]
[Kim Nam-sik,
Mount Jirisan National Park Ranger]
All the victims
are related
to the 1995 flood.
What brings you here?
Didn't you go to the ritual?
You know...
I'm kind of tired of them now.
Seriously?
Then why are you here? Because of that?
To get some energy?
Gwigam Rock.
It's surely a powerful rock.
Are you here because of that?
Or...
Is there another reason?
That's strange.
Doesn't the air feel heavy?
Please cross carefully.
-Okay.
[Haedong Town Hall]
[Jirisan]
Get out of the valley!
Quick! Get out of there!
[More localized rain can occur.
We must rescue everyone before then.]
[I'll go.]
[You must keep watch here.]
[Black Bridge Village is gone
because of you.]
[You might not get the benefit
if it was suicide.]
[I think the murderer has
something to do with the incident.]
Did something happen back then?
They just made an unfortunate choice.
-Yi-gang!
[-Don't lie.]
[I wanted to forget.]