[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 4]
Your Highness.
Slow down, please.
[Princess Xinghua]
Your Highness.
Please slow down!
[Mingguang Hall]
Zixing.
Xinghua?
Here are some dim sum
from Nanxiao paid yesterday as their tribute.
They're made of wild honey, wild oranges
and wolf's milk.
Very good for your health.
I got some specially
from my brother so that you can have a taste.
You can put it here.
I'll eat it when I'm done.
Just forget about your work for a minute, okay?
They won't taste as good in no time.
Come on, try this.
Is it good?
Have some more.
Master!
You're three hours ahead of schedule.
The ambush was nowhere near good.
Xiaoyu and I kinda thought we could be faster.
Let's cut to the chase.
Okay, cut to the chase.
Master.
We came across a bunch of monks
when we were on our way here from the west.
They came from Zhongli.
Monks?
The army of the Southern Dynasty
even attacked the temple?
It's not because the temple was under attack.
The monks saw the refugees coming to the south
and took in hundreds of them in their temple.
As more and more refugees gathered,
the monks could not afford to feed them in the temple.
So the abbot of the temple
decided to escort these refugees
to somewhere safe.
Since everyone knows that
the Western State's got you.
And the city is almost unbreachable.
They have every reason to come here.
Those monks and refugees,
where are they now?
The refugees have been resettled.
The monks are at the Qielan Temple outside the city.
Eleven?
You've grown taller, right?
You're more like a beautiful young lady now.
I told you not to come to the military camp, did I?
What can you do in such a place?
After all, you've never learned any martial art.
What?
You want me to explain for you?
All right, enough.
Since master is here.
Will you give Shiyi a break?
And you, Master,
shows lack of respect for yourself.
And always make fun of Eleven.
Act like you care.
Do you want to join us to go to the Qielan temple?
When did you get hurt?
Why did nobody
tell us about this?
It doesn't matter. Just a minor injury.
[Qielan temple]
Master.
The monks are all inside.
And there are also dozens of
refugees who have yet to be resettled.
Leave your weapons outside.
Yes.
You guys wait outside
and watch the horses.
Yes.
Amitabha.
Your Highness.
This is the abbot from the south.
Why are they all sitting here?
Actually, we had arranged a monk room for them.
But there are still some refugees
waiting to be housed.
So they gave that room to the refugees.
Thanks for your kindness, Abbot.
The kindness is yours, Your Highness.
Thank you for taking in these poor refugees and us.
The civilians are innocent.
And you masters
are all people from beyond our secular world.
We're far away from keeping you.
Xie Yun.
Escort the refugees to the Western State.
Resettle them properly.
Yes.
Master, I'll help.
Please lead our way to the monk room.
General, please come with me.
Master.
It's time for the tonsure.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll be right there.
Got it.
I wonder what kind of person
would require a tonsure conducted by you at this place?
He is one of the refugees.
Touched by the Buddha during his flight
he decided to become a monk at our temple.
Unfortunately,
our temple has been deserted.
We can only tonsure him today,
and save the rest for later.
If you don't mind,
I'll build a new temple
for you.
Is that true, Your Highness?
Amitabha.
You are really kind, Your Highness.
I really appreciate it.
Now go tonsure your disciple.
Don't keep him waiting for too long.
Please feel free to look around, Your Highness.
I have to go now.
Eleven.
As for the name of the new temple,
help me with it.
Me?
Take your time to think about it.
Do you want to see
how they take the tonsure?
Let's go.
[Great Buddha's Hall]
I'll take you to the sutra depository and have a look.
Master.
Abbot.
I want to
have a few words with him.
You can't do that.
Okay.
Leave the razor.
Hold me as your hostage.
Who are you?
Get up!
You can go back.
I have made up my mind.
We will never leave Your Highness till we die.
You are from Nanxiao?
Go out with me.
Back off. It's none of your business.
General.
Did you catch the wrong person?
This man came all along with us.
He was a big help
in guarding the civilians.
Back off if you still want to be alive.
Master!
Master! Here's your sword!
Well-articulated.
I should...
It's okay.
No rush.
Long time no see.
Second Prince.
Your Highness.
I should miss such a big show?
Act seriously
and decently.
Master.
Why don't you just swap me
for Feng Qiao,
and let her be my senior sister?
She's been pulling her face and lecturing me all day.
I don't see why not.
Master.
Is the man at the temple
an old acquaintance of yours?
Yes.
He's the second prince of Nanxiao.
A few years ago,
we had met a few times.
At that time, he came to have a peace negotiation with me
representing the emperor of Nanxiao.
He was a very favored prince
and was only second to the Crown Prince.
After that, I don't know
what happened,
he began to live a secluded life
and refused to see any visitors.
Even if the officials from his jurisdiction
wanted to visit him,
they had to see him through a veil.
That's why only a handful of people
have seen him in the past few years.
I thought he was an assassin.
Report this back to the capital secretly
and leave it to His Majesty.
Feng Qiao.
Take him to the Buddhist Tower later.
Yes.
When I became your disciple,
I wasn't able to call you “Master”.
Please let me do it today.
Master.
Master can't get happier
to see that you are able to speak.
You don't have to do this.
[Nanchen Royal Mansion]
If you need anything,
please let me know.
A mouthful of alms food,
and a wooden fish.
Even though you helped me today,
don't expect me to make your life any easier.
I wasn't helping you.
I was just helping myself
escape from Nanxiao.
[General's House]
Go in and report to General Cui.
Yes, Madame.
[General's House]
General Hong.
General Cui.
[General's House]
I've been waiting for you for a while.
Not just a while.
It's four hours.
He's been waiting on the rampart,
the moment he woke up this morning.
He even missed lunch.
After every possible persuasion,
he finally decided to come back for dinner.
Yet the moment the news of your arrival came,
he put down the utensils at once.
Watch your mouth.
Come in and have a chat.
[General's House]
Okay.
Here, General Hong.
Thank you, General Cui.
General Hong.
Help yourself.
I...
General Cui.
This... this thing...
How do we eat it?
Oh right!
Come on.
I'll shell the crab for you.
Have some vegetable first.
Allow me, please.
It's okay.
You've been in the Northwest many years,
and don't eat this a lot.
I just want you to...
try something new.
Come on, try the crab roe first.
It's nutritious.
Is it good?
Yes.
You can have some, too.
Okay.
Here.
Okay, okay.
You first.
Here.
Thank you.
[Taiji Hall]
Drag him out to some bustling area.
Club him to death!
Zhao Teng, you eunuch!
Even if I died,
I'll make you pay!
Drag him out!
Eunuch!
Who else?
Who else wants to submit his statement?
Well...
Prime Minister?
No statement.
Good.
Leave the court if you have nothing to submit.
I, have something to submit.
I beg Your Majesty
to allow me to return to Qinghe County.
What for?
Your Majesty...
Do you still remember this cane?
Of course, I do.
Grand Preceptor, this is the royal scepter I ordered the craftsmen to build
and give to you as a birthday gift
for your 70th birthday.
According to the rites of Han,
when aged 70, the senior will be given a scepter,
and will be allowed to have porridge and live a good retired life.
I have reached the age of seventy.
Your Majesty, please allow me to leave the court
and spend the rest of my life compiling the history of Han.
Your Majesty.
Why don't you allow him to do that?
I...
Permission granted.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Grand Preceptor!
Zhao Teng collaborated with General Liu Yuan,
and imprisoned the empress.
Control the emperor and command the nobles.
Now that you're gone,
there is no one in the court
to stop Zhao Teng.
I am more than willing to help yet I don't have what it takes.
Before I leave,
I have a word for you, Your Highness.
Please go ahead.
Keep a fief to yourself if you want to survive
and leave the Central State as soon as possible.
Do you still remember
I have an engagement with the Cui's daughter?
Forget it.
Kid, did you ever wake up in the middle of night?
I...
You ordered people to imprison me for so many years.
Do you feel guilty?
Your Majesty.
It is time to leave.
All the ministers are waiting for you.
Are you going to keep me here
for the rest of my life?
Mother.
You should just enjoy your life here in the imperial harem.
Don't interfere with state affairs
and throw yourself in danger anymore.
Zhao Teng, you eunuch!
You held the emperor hostage and imprisoned me.
I made a mistake of trusting you.
Calm down, Empress.
I almost thought there is no one left in the hall.
The ruler has left,
leaving behind the imprisoned Empress,
and the Crown Prince who will never be crowned.
If you want to break free from the prison,
allow me to express what I thought.
If we keep complaining to each other,
none of us will survive.
The only way to get out is by helping each other.
Those who I trusted were trying to save me.
Yet they were all killed by Zhao Teng one by one.
What else can I do now?
I will save you,
and then,
you give me what I want.
What do you want?
The Crown Princeship. The Ceremony of the Enthronement.
And...
The throne?
Only the injustice of Heaven and the indifference of human beings
can cultivate a good boy.
I never knew
the last one who is standing next to me
would be you.
So, do we have a deal?
You save me first.
And I'll fulfill your dream later.
Your Highness.
Is Shiyi inside?
Yes. She comes here every night.
She has almost finished reading all the books
in the library.
I thought there are people cleaning this place every day.
I'm afraid they're not careful enough.
So I wanna clean it by myself.
Throughout the entire mansion,
this is the only place that can't have fire.
Are you cold?
No.
I won't if I am occupied.
You'd better come up here
next time when it gets warmer.
The books are always here.
They're not going anywhere.
I got a letter from Qinghe County asking you to go back.
Why do I have to go back so suddenly?
The Grand Preceptor resigned from his post and returned to the hometown.
He summoned all the descendants of the Cui's clan back to Qinghe County
to compile the country's history with him.
Including me and my brother?
Yes.
When is it?
Next month.
So, can we come back after that?
I can't decide whether you can go or stay.
After all, the Qinghe County
is your hometown.
Jr. Prince of Nanchen's beloved disciple
has to climb up to the roof in secret
to take a look at the Western State under her master's jurisdiction.
I doubt if there's anyone who will buy that?
Uncle has returned to Qinghe County.
The Clan Chief is already over seventy.
He should have returned earlier.
He's now summoning the descendants of the Cui's clan to return,
including me.
When?
Ma said the sooner the better.
I'm already engaged.
I could be called to enter the Imperial Palace at any time.
The sooner I return to Qinghe County,
I'll be able to serve mom a few more years,
and stay with her for some longer time.
I should be happy
that I can go home earlier.
Right?
It's understandable that
you don't want to leave here.
You don't have to blame yourself.
Your Majesty.
Zixing, there couldn't be a better time for you to be here.
We got a secret letter from the Western State.
Zhao Teng.
A prince of Nanxiao has escaped to the Western State.
And he is currently being held in custody in the royal mansion.
My uncle wants me to decide what to do with him.
But I can't make up my mind.
Should I kill him
or persuade him to surrender?
Or maybe
I should ask a minister I trust
and hold a secret trial in the Western State.
Your Majesty.
Don't bother to concern about such a trivial matter.
Just leave it to me.
I'm willing to go to the Western State for Your Majesty
to hold a secret interrogation of this man.
That's exactly what I had in mind.
Your Majesty.
My fiancée is there.
Even if this does not exist,
I would have asked for your permission to see her.
I knew you wanted to see her.
You've been waiting to see her for ages.
I'll give the order right away.
You can leave tomorrow.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Xianyang Hall]
Say hello to my sister-in-law for me.
One more thing, tell my uncle that
I've been looking at the Western State from the Central State,
and I am looking forward to our reunion.
Your Majesty.
Given your high status,
you should think twice before
going to the Western State.
High status?
I'm just a member of the Liu's Royal family.
I will write a letter later
to tell my mother to come to the Central State and live for a short time.
I am sorry to trouble you
to take care of her, Mr. Zhao.
I'll take care of the Princess.
Don't worry.
How about I send my own men
to help you pick up the Princess?
Sounds good to me.
If you still don't believe
my loyalty to our alliance,
you can have your trusted men follow me
to make sure I am in one piece.
My men will definitely follow you,
but that doesn't mean I don't trust you.
I was just thinking that it's really a long way for you
to go to the Western State.
And I will feel more comfortable
to know that they are with you.
Then I'll wait for your arrangement.
All of them have
been following me for many years.
You must stay close to him at all times
and take good care of Prince of Guangling.
Yes!
Go take the gilt jade sculpture
sent by His Majesty last year.
Yes.
Wait.
Maybe it would be better to take
the inkstone, paper and brush sent by my father
She'll like it.
Yes.
Who do you think will like it?
Your Highness.
Leave us alone.
You're going to see her?
My brother said
you asked for permission to go to the Western State
just to see Cui Shiyi,
right?
Xinghua.
I understand.
To be the crown prince, you must marry her
for the support of the Cui's clan.
The most important thing is,
you really like her.
I'm just jealous.
You've already started to care about her so much
before you actually see her.
If you really marry her,
I'm afraid there won't be
any space for me in your heart.
You and I have been close since we were kids.
No one can break the bond between us.
[Nanchen Royal Mansion]
Master.
What is it?
The emperor has granted permission
for Prince of Guangling to leave the Imperial Palace,
for the Western State to see his fiancée.
Two things for you to know.
Yes.
Although Prince of Guangling has yet to be crowned,
he's still a prince-to-be.
You should accompany him throughout his visit and make sure he is well taken care of.
Yes.
He's coming from the Central State.
I'm afraid this trip
has something to do with the prince of Nanxiao.
If he needs anything,
you are his responsibility.
Yes.
Master, you are not gonna see him?
I am not a big fan to
deal with the nobility.
I'd rather go back to the barracks
with my counsellor.
You're leaving again?
I thought you were spending new year at the mansion?
Miss Cui.
We have no clue about that either.
You should ask His Highness directly.
As for Prince of Guangling's arrival.
First, he's to interrogate the prince of Nanxiao.
Second, to meet his fiancée.
And the third purpose...
What do you think it is?
There must be a reason for a guest to travel from afar.
Master. Counsellor.
Master, why don't you
stay in the mansion to celebrate the new year?
The military situation has been very tense in the past few years.
The rebellion is still going on.
I'd be more at ease to stay in the camp.
But there's no war during the new year.
And it is rare to spend a new year without a war?
Actually, the reason he leaves the royal mansion
is that he wants to leave some space
for you and Prince of Guangling.
If so,
I have nothing else to ask.
I'll leave now.
♫No expectation for people's eulogy.♫
♫Only hope to leave no regrets.♫
Shiyi's birthday is coming in a few days.
♫With me a bottle of unstrained liquor, ask for directions among the universe.♫
Even if Your Highness wants to leave,
you should wish her a happy birthday before you go, right?
♫The horse galloping, the sound reverberating throughout the battlefield.♫
♫The lofty aspiration held firmly in my hand.♫
♫Fearless in the face of hardships, my heart and blood remain red-hot.♫
♫Military ranks on my shoulder, forget about being black and blue.♫
♫Willing to hold fast to the light of my life.♫
Every time we leave,
Shiyi always sees us off at the library.
If she returns to her hometown,
there will be no one left
to see us off.
Master is so cruel
as he never once looked back.
When leaving the capital,
His Highness didn't look back either.
He had his own reasons.
What reasons?
Can you tell me secretly?
If you don't look back, you don't expect to return
and you have no emotional attachment.
This way,
you don't fear death,
and you can sacrifice yourself on a battlefield.
Master has already prepared
a birthday gift for you.
[Huo Shan Huang Ya (Yellow Tea)]
[Fangshan Luya]
[Birun Mingyue]
It tastes weird.
Is it because melting the ice in well water
changed its flavor?
Why did you pour away the tea?
Come inside with me.
Master.
Why don't you let Eleven listen to the music?
It's a rare opportunity to have a musician from Nanxiao.
She poured away a pot of tea.
I was asking her to write the name of tea as a punishment.