[English subtitles are available]
[Love Under The Full Moon]
[Episode 12]
Wei Xuan He,
Chu Xia has turned you down.
What tricks are you trying to pull here?
Chu Xia!
Chu Xia, stop...
Chu Xia, stop running.
Chu Xia.
Chu Xia, my child.
Come home with me.
I'm not!
Chu Xia.
Why won't you
acknowledge us?
Chu Xia, how could we possibly be mistaken?
You're my daughter.
You've got the wrong person.
Yes, that's right.
You're not Chu Xia.
We mistook you for our daughter.
We're old.
We couldn't see clearly.
Sorry.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Would I mistake my own daughter
for someone else?
Chu Xia.
Honey,
our child still wouldn't acknowledge us
even at this point.
She must have her reasons.
Let's not push her, alright?
Let's go back first.
We'll wait for her at home.
When she wants to come home,
she'll come home.
Right?
Xiao Dong.
Uncle.
You have to take care
of this good friend of yours.
She must also be
the most beloved child of her parents.
Uncle, auntie, don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect her.
Leave her to me.
Come on, let's go home.
What's wrong?
What's on your mind?
Why is this happening to me?
I just want to be an ordinary person,
who can live with their parents,
and doesn't remember those unknown fears.
Is that too much to ask?
Is this how I'm going to be
for the rest of my life?
This is not what I want at all.
What do you want to do then?
I want to see my parents.
I want to tell them the truth.
Including the fact that you fell off the cliff
and your strange encounter
over the past ten years.
I don't want to put them in danger,
but I really want to tell them I'm still alive.
I don't want the people I love the most
to drown in pain.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Now this is the Lei Chu Xia I know,
the one who will never surrender.
Alright, now.
Xiao Dong,
you're saying that
although Chu Xia has returned,
she has lost all her memories.
And because of some
special reasons,
she can't acknowledge us?
But she's our daughter.
Auntie, uncle,
I'm still helping her
to find her memories.
I want to help her solve all the mysteries
and remove the danger.
So that she can return
to her normal life,
return to your side as soon as possible.
Is there anything we can do
to help her?
Honestly,
Chu Xia and I
have been coming back secretly these days.
But apart from some intuitions
from her past,
it didn't stimulate
more memories of her past.
I had wanted to ask Chu Xia
to move back home.
If there is anything she wants to know,
we can tell her slowly.
But since she can't
acknowledge us now,
looks like this idea
is not going to work.
What should we do?
I have an idea.
Maybe we can give it a try.
Chu Xia loves desserts.
She has always wanted to be
a dessert chef since childhood.
Her father and I used to
take her on trips.
We tried the desserts from different places.
Here's my idea,
we'll visit those places again.
We'll collect all these dessert recipes
and give it to Chu Xia.
Maybe her palate can stimulate her memory.
Honey,
that's a brilliant idea.
Maybe when Chu Xia
tastes those desserts she used to love,
she would remember everything.
We've been looking for Chu Xia for ten years.
Ten years.
But we never thought of giving up.
Now that we know
she's healthy and safe,
and she have
reliable friends like you
by her side,
we're relieved.
She will definitely regain her memory.
We'll get through this.
She wants to find her memory.
As her parents, it's our duty
to help her get through this.
As for reuniting,
we can wait for a few more months.
When she is fully recovered,
our family will be reunited.
Why did you come in?
Xiao Dong,
please tell Chu Xia.
Our daughter has always been full of energy.
When she encounters any difficulty,
she always overcomes it with optimism,
just like when she was learning
to make desserts.
I believe that now, while recovering her memory,
she will do the same.
She'll always have our support.
We'll wait for her to come home.
Tell your
cute teddy bear friend here,
next time she comes,
she can role play
a character without head piece.
[Mr Wei,]
[Miss Qin is drinking with some clients.]
[They are being rather difficult.]
[Should I help her out?]
She can take care of her own business.
♫ Gazing at you ♫
♫ Time is reflected in the heart ♫
♫ Tears fall down ♫
♫ The monologue that has been kept
in heart for years ♫
Well done.
Miss Qin Yue,
you're not only pretty,
you can sing too.
You're the best influencer
for the sales of our product.
Mr Zhou, you flatter me.
We'll need to count on you for
the sales of our products in the future.
No, no.
Come on, cheers.
Let's set a deal on
our cooperation plan first.
Mr Zhou,
your company's products
are already selling very well.
My promoting your product
is just like icing on the cake.
You're too kind.
I think
you should finish this glass.
You're the boss.
Mr Zhou can drink this,
but don't you think you should
drink a cross-armed wine with Mr Zhou?
Right, guys?
That's right.
You won't turn him down, right?
We haven't signed
the contract yet.
Miss Qin...
This is quite the party.
Xuan He.
You came, Mr Wei.
Sorry that I'm late, Mr Zhou.
Are you coming to her rescue?
This is such a great party,
how can I miss it, right?
Besides, I came here to surprise you.
Let's have a drink.
You came just in time.
Xuan He, don't drink too much.
Mr Zhou likes to drink.
I'll have a few more drinks with him.
Come.
Xuan He.
Drink.
Here.
Here, bottoms up.
♫ When we connect, your eyes shine ♫
I'm warning you.
Stay away from Chu Xia,
or I won't let you off.
♫ Is there something to be said? ♫
♫ Say nothing to spare your feelings ♫
Xuan He,
♫ No one likes the naked truth
to be suddenly exposed ♫
are you okay?
I'm fine.
You can't drive.
You drank.
Who says I'm going to drive?
Cyber Tech's best streamer
actually had to drink with clients.
Were you worried about me?
No.
As part of
Cyber Tech's image,
you'll affect
the company's commercial value by doing this.
♫ When we connect, your eyes shine ♫
You need to
♫ Is there something to be said? ♫
learn to protect yourself.
♫ Say nothing to spare your feelings ♫
Why did you have to make
your words of concern so awkward?
♫ No one likes the naked truth
to be suddenly exposed ♫
I'm not concerned about you.
♫ All these years ♫
♫ It's true that there are many happy moments ♫
♫ But one has to learn to live on one's own ♫
Have you started to have feelings
for me?
♫ Some people are meant to be ♫
♫ Kept only in the heart ♫
No.
You're afraid to admit it.
♫ But at least we once loved ♫
Yes, you're afraid to admit it.
♫ We need not be together ♫
♫ When we're in love ♫
♫ Why should we hurt each other ♫
♫ If there is no future between us? ♫
♫ No matter how hard we try ♫
♫ Our love would be defeated by a thorn ♫
♫ I wish you happiness until the end of time ♫
♫ No matter how hard we try ♫
♫ Our love would be defeated by a thorn ♫
♫ I wish you happiness until the end of time ♫
Chu Xia,
Professor Chen has asked someone
to deliver the wrist band.
Great.
Now you don't have to go to the company
with me anymore
and I don't have to go with you
to Summer Time anymore.
It's fixed?
Why did someone make it seem like
this is such a pity?
Is it that obvious?
This is good.
With this wrist band,
I can speed up on the investigation
of the truth back then.
This is the plan I made last night.
[Sui]
[The mainframe room is to be
relocated for maintenance.]
[Here's your chance to observe and learn.]
[Come now.]
What's the matter? Duty calls?
Personnel adjustment.
They want me to come down there now.
About our plan...
It's fine, you should go.
You mustn't delay your work
because of me.
I have the wrist band now, don't I?
I can go anywhere freely now.
And like my parents said,
no matter what difficulties I face,
I won't give up easily.
So, for their sake,
I have to work hard.
Your family
is quite optimistic.
It's probably hereditary.
Just like your dad is a genius,
and you...
Although you're just an ordinary guy
and an IT personnel
who is often unemployed,
I think
you are hidden gem.
If you want to praise me,
just praise me directly.
Don't mince your words.
Alright now.
Now that you have the bracelet, I'm...
Relieved?
Even more worried.
Who knows what sort of new trouble
you would make?
Life is full of challenges.
That's enough, go out now.
Don't delay your work.
That's enough.
Go, go, go.
I'm going now.
Bye-bye.
Stop looking. What are you looking at?
Listen,
I've found some information.
The mainframe room is going to be
relocated earlier for maintenance.
This is your only chance
to go in,
you hear me?
Stop looking.
What?
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
Thank you, Sui.
It's no big deal.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
The mainframe room.
You're just going to waltz in there?
Didn't I tell you
with your qualifications,
you can't enter
the core area of the company?
We'll do the same as before.
I'll use your ID.
That'll work.
My...
My ID tag...
is in the office.
I'll tell you the truth.
I am
not qualified too.
You're not qualified too?
Then why did you call me here?
Hold on,
since I called you here,
of course I've already figured something out.
We might not be able to go in,
but someone can go in.
What is that?
Don't touch it first.
Xu Xiao Dong,
I'll ask you again.
Are you going into the mainframe room
just to learn and improve?
Sui,
what are you implying?
I want to enter the mainframe room
to learn from the IT experts in there.
I want to use my own hands
to help you move up the corporate ladder.
Knock it off.
I was once like you.
Stop pretending.
I know what's on your mind.
You want to go in there
to copy the source code
and see the core essence of
Yao Yang Tech, don't you?
Fine, kid.
I can't give you for free.
You've just joined the company
and you want to learn
the core of the company.
Anyway, I've completed
the new project you assigned me.
And I believe that
after Mr Zhao sees the completed work,
he will be particularly pleased.
"Particularly"?
Director Zhou.
Let's go.
You finished it in a day?
I...
So this is the idea you came up with?
Cut the nonsense.
It's good enough that I have a plan.
You have no idea how difficult it was
to get these uniforms.
Breathe evenly, stay close.
Don't... don't panic.
What's wrong?
Didn't you say to breathe steadily?
Xiao Dong,
this is as far as I can walk you.
You're on your own after this.
Hang on.
You need to take me in.
Don't push me.
Didn't you see the guys there?
Xu Xiao Dong!
I don't know where the room is.
Use your mouth.
Ask them yourself.
What are you doing here?
I dropped something.
Stop there.
Which department are you from?
I...
Didn't you guys say
you need help here?
And you called me here?
We need help?
You don't need it now?
I'll leave then.
Stop.
Go now.
Okay, thanks.
[Work Schedule]
Turing,
help me analyse my latest situation.
Okay, Chu Xia.
What do you want to know?
Let's see.
First, I know
I have a dessert shop.
Summer Time
was established ten years ago.
It was jointly established by
by two friends, Lei Chu Xia and Yuan Yuan.
[Summer Time]
And,
I had a boyfriend in college.
Wei Xuan He,
founder of Cyber Tech.
Cyber Tech's rapid growth
is due to the talent and ability of its founder,
Wei Xuan He.
[Wei Xuan He's personal info,
founder of Cyber Tech]
And he told me last time
there was a restaurant we really wanted
to go to ten years ago.
It's called Peninsula...
Peninsula Restaurant.
When I was in college,
you really wanted to
come here with me for a date.
But he told me that ten years ago,
because he was starting his own business,
so we were not be able to go.
Information error.
Chu Xia,
there is information error.
Why?
Comparing the information
[Peninsula Restaurant opened August 8, 2012]
[Lei Chu Xia disappeared November 18, 2011]
found online and the information
you just provided,
[Not a match]
there is some inconsistencies.
[Our city's first premium theme restaurant,]
The information indicates that
[Peninsula Restaurant is located in Trade
Building, Wenjin Road, Tongcheng City.]
the Peninsula Restaurant you visited
opened on
[A branch has opened in Tongcheng]
August 8, 2012,
which means it was opened
after you graduated.
[Congratulations on the Grand Opening]
That means
Wei Xuan He was lying.
But why did he lie to me?
Thank you for helping me out.
It's nothing.
By the way,
every time I come over,
I don't have a change of clothes
and I have to bring a lot of things.
How about
I leave some of my stuff here?
Okay.
You can take a look around.
Where there is free space,
you can put your stuff there.
You didn't say no.
What's going on with you?
You've been looking troubled lately.
You seem worn out.
Is there something bothering you?
You can talk to me.
I'm hungry.
Make me some supper.
You're hungry.
Okay.
It's been a long time since I cooked for you.
[Zhao Yao Yang]
I need to check my phone.
I'm going now.
Okay.
[Zhao Yao Yang]
[Our company's server was hacked,]
[the source code was deciphered.]
[Looks like someone is trying to find out]
[what happened back then.]
[Wei Xuan He]
[It's been ten years.]
[It won't be easy to find out what happened.]
Xuan He,
do you want noodles or wontons?
[Find out the suspicious individual]
[as soon as possible.]
What are you looking at?
Qin Yue,
we have an intimate relationship.
But some boundaries
can't be crossed.
Thanks. Excuse me.
Liang.
Xiao Dong,
seeing you here, I can stop rushing.
I didn't expect that I'm not the last person.
What's going on with that?
You don't know?
The company was hacked.
Everyone will be investigated.
They suspect it was an inside job.
When did it happen?
Yesterday.
Sui sent everyone an email.
You didn't receive it?
[You have an unread email]
[Please click to view]
Xiao Dong.
[You have an unread email]
We're just following orders too.
Our company secrets are leaked.
The computers of everyone in the company
have to be checked,
including President Zhao's computer.
He's leading by example.
Also,
you have to hand over
all the hard drives too.
The one who is capable of
stealing company secrets
must be an expert.
Other than the staff from the core office,
there is your department.
Sui,
your department is highly valued and
have been performing well lately,
but we have to follow the protocol
and focus the inspection on you guys.
Please cooperate.
Don't worry.
We will certainly cooperate, right?
Yes.
It's true that our department
has been highly valued lately,
because we are really competent.
But take a look around,
these people are tech nerds.
I mean, they won't have the guts to...
steal the company's secrets.
Also,
please hand over your phones too.
Our phones?
This is out of line, isn't it?
That's right.
What rights do you have to take our phones away?
This is a violation of privacy.
-That's right. -Exactly.
Is he going to take responsibility of this?
They can't do this.
Alright, silence.
I'll say something.
Director Gao,
we've known each other for quite a long time.
I think this really is a violation of privacy.
And there are girls too.
What if their phones have...
Come on.
Everyone, put your phones into this basket.
Hurry up.
One by one, put it inside.
After this, disassemble your computer.
Disassemble it.
They need to check the hard drive.
Make it easy for them.
Cooperate with Director Gao.
Do you hear me?
-We got it. -We got it.
Seriously.
[Cleaning in progress]
I know someone's in there.
Come out.
Come out, stop pretending.
I'll count to three.
One.
Two.
Sui.
You need to pull.
They found out about it so soon.
Tell me. Did you take
something particularly important?
I didn't.
And to prevent leaks,
the source code in the mainframe room
is intelligently encrypted.
Once cracked,
it will trigger an automatic alert command.
In that case,
the smart encryption
of the source code in our mainframe room
is quite interesting.
The automatic alert function
is quite impressive.
Put that aside for now.
If they find out about you,
they will know about me too.
And I just got promoted.
You must ensure that
nothing happens, okay?
Sui, don't worry.
I've cracked
the file tracking algorithm.
Even if they try to trace me
from the source code,
it'll only get them to a virtual IP address.
They can't trace it back to me.
Also,
about the mainframe room,
I took care of everything.
Don't worry.
Good.
Just a false alarm, right?
Something is wrong.
What is it this time?
Nothing.
What nothing? Spit it out!
Nothing, really.
Forget the tissue paper. Tell me now!
The surveillance.
A clever IT elite
like you
would forget about the surveillance?
I didn't forget it.
I took care of the surveillance
in the mainframe room.
There's no problem with it.
I just forgot the surveillance in the lobby.
Xu Xiao Dong,
do you think we are in a soap opera?
Why didn't you finish your sentence
in one breath?
Believe me, I can die right now.
Sui, calm down.
Don't panic.
Calm down.
Breathe.
And,
why am I saying this?
If they did find us out,
they would've arrested us immediately.
They wouldn't have
gone through so much trouble to check everyone.
A small part
must have gone wrong in the process.
We got lucky
and got away.
Small part gone wrong.
We can't afford to have that.
The small part is usually the fatal part.
We could get exposed at any time.
What about the future?
What if we get exposed in the future?
Small part.
We have to find out this small part.
You hear me?
I think we'll be fine.
Listen to me.
The surveillance out there got us, right?
It's not like we were doing anything.
I just pulled you to the corner
and had a conversation with you.
There's nothing wrong with that.
You're right, Sui.
Nothing wrong.
Besides, I know that that surveillance
broke down a week ago.
That's right.
Xu Xiao Dong!
Are you messing with me?
Do you think it's funny?
How could you mess with me?
You made my feelings go up and down.
I almost lost it.
What's wrong with you?
Do you know how I felt just now?
I almost lost it!
And you still messed with me.
Okay.
Anyway, I've done you a big favour this time.
You will have to help me in the future.
Keep this in mind.
Okay, don't worry.
I can't believe you messed with me.
I need to take a breath.
I need to use the toilet.
Don't worry.
[They're making such a big move.]
[Looks like the truth behind the source code]
[isn't simple indeed.]
[Zhao Yao Yang,]
[you are not getting away this time.]
Mr Wei,
we have a meeting
at the company at 2 p.m. today.
You'll need to attend it.
Wei Xuan He!
Who are you?
Stop pulling me!
I want to see Wei Xuan He!
Wait!
I want to see...
Sir...
Stop him!
Let go of me!
Let me in!
Wei Xuan He! Let me go in!
Get out of my way!
Get out of my way! Let me in!
Wei Xuan He,
I want to talk to you about Lei Chu Xia!
Who is that man?
Why is he looking for Xuan He?
I don't know.
Do we know each other?
No.
But I know Lei Chu Xia.
What is your relationship with Lei Chu Xia?
We have no relationship.
But I know her biggest secret.
I think I heard him say
Lei Chu Xia.
I think he said
he knows Lei Chu Xia's secret.
Find out about it.
Investigate this man.
Okay.
I suppose you're not just here
for a free breakfast.
What I'm about to tell you
is worth a million free breakfasts from you.
It'd better be.
You might not know me, Mr Wei.
Let me introduce myself.
[Tongcheng University, Wang Yi Xin]
I'm Wang Yi Xin.
I study astrophysics.
I don't care about who you are.
What about Lei Chu Xia?
See the band on Lei Chu Xia's wrist?
That's her stabilizer.
If you don't believe me,
you can take it off and see.
You're saying that
the current Lei Chu Xia
is the Lei Chu Xia from ten years ago?
She's still 22 years old?
Yes.
The current level of science
can't corroborate it,
but all the facts indicate that
I'm right.
On the day of the super full moon,
a powerful gravitational wave
was formed between the earth and the moon.
Ten years ago,
some coincidental circumstances
might have allowed Lei Chu Xia
to attach herself to this gravitational wave.
Gravitational waves
can change the timeline.
Our ten years may be long,
but Lei Chu Xia's ten years
is fleeting.
Why did she lose her memory?
It's possible that
the gravitational wave has interfered
with her memory nerves.
Or some other reasons.
I don't know about this.
Tell me then,
how can she regain her memory?
Recreate all the events
of the moment when she attached to
the gravitational wave ten years ago.
Maybe she'll get her memory back.
Or maybe
she can travel back to ten years ago
or another time period.
What a great scientific moment
it would be.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I want to study Lei Chu Xia.
Mr Wei,
you've waited for her for ten years.
Don't you want her to regain her memory
so that you can start over?
I'm the only one
who can help you now.
So you just want to experiment on Lei Chu Xia.
No.
I'm just pursuing science.
Studying Lei Chu Xia
is good for all of mankind.
It's just that in
my pursuit of scientific truth,
I happened to meet your needs.
We can work together, right?
So what do you want
to get from me?
The funding for my research.
That's not too much to ask, is it?
Chu Xia.
What are these?
Why did you come by yourself?
What are you guys doing?
Next Saturday is
our shop's anniversary.
You don't remember?
Sorry, sorry, my bad.
Come here, check this out.
These are all the gifts
I bought for the shop anniversary.
Count it from the beginning.
Summer Time
only recorded great sales
during its first year
and its tenth year.
As for the period in between,
I managed to
muddle through.
But you're back.
Our Summer Time
is now considered a viral shop, right?
Hold out your hand.
What is this?
We all have this.
So I'm planning to hold
a tenth anniversary store celebration.
What do you think?
It needs to have a sense of ritual.
I'll hang it here. My side here...
Check the length.
Okay.
Let me measure it.
Get the scissors.
Cut the extra part.
Okay.
Be careful up there.
Scissors.
I just left it here.
You can check...
You can check
that box.
What are you looking for?
How could it be Wei Xuan He?
[Chu Xia, just tell me.]
Where did you put it?
This is a critical period of my first venture.
You can't do this to me.
[November 18, 2011]
I found it.
Chu Xia,
what's the matter?
I'm okay.
Are you alright?
When I disappeared ten years ago,
was it November 18?
[November 18, 2011]
Yes.
November 18.
I went to the police station
with uncle and auntie
to lodge a report the next day.
Did you remember something?
When you were rummaging through stuff just now,
the scene overlapped
with some part of my memory.
I think I remember something.
I have some place to go.
Get them to help you.
Okay, okay.
I'm going now.
Be careful.
Okay.
[Summer Time]
Dr Tian Yu,
I just remembered something important.
I need to talk to you.
About 30 minutes.
I'll be there 30 minutes later.
Okay.
Sir.
[Yao Yang Tech, Cyber Security Department]
Accelerate the inspection of the phones.
Hurry up, the higher-ups are anxious.
Hurry up, work faster.
[Incoming Call]
[Sorry, the number you have dialled]
[is temporarily unavailable.]
[Xiao Dong,]
[I just remembered something.]
[I'm on my way to see Dr Tian Yu.]
[Give me a call]
[when you see my message.]
[The Peninsula Restaurant you visited]
opened on
[Congratulations on the Grand Opening]
August 8, 2012,
[A branch has opened in Tongcheng]
which means it was opened
after you graduated.
[Wei Xuan He was lying.]
Ten years ago that night,
I was thinking of
celebrating with you after work.
But when I came back,
I found that you were missing.
[November 18, 2011]
[Wei Xuan He said]
[the day I disappeared,]
[we separated early.]
[If the image I just remembered is real,]
[that means he's lying.]
[Why did Wei Xuan He]
[lie to me?]
[Does he have anything to do]
[with my disappearance?]
[Gravitational wave]
Gravitational wave.
Ten years ago.
Amnesia.
Chu Xia,
I didn't expect
you would have such a big secret.
What is she after?
Why is it the same as ten years ago?
At the most critical moment of my career,
you showed up again.
What are you trying to do?
Could it be that
you remember something about
what happened ten years ago?