Sorry
We will close the door
Is he didn't reply your message
Sorry
I will leave soon
Hello Qiu ying
I am so sorry
Are you OK now
I was in a hurry just now
I didn't expect it will waste a long time
I didn't reply your message at once
I am sorry about that
It is ok
Are you still at milk tea store I am sorry to you to wait me for a long time
I am going to pick you up
Don't worry
The team has a specified return time
If you come to the milk tea store you will late to return the Team
I
I backed home already
I'll invite you to eat something when you a spare time that express my apology
OK
I will eat a lot of things then you pay the bill for me
Then you go to bed earlier
ok
You too
Good night
You come back to China in order to Ji xiangkong
Are you serious
I am so serious
No wonder you will use the out of sky as your theme song for the development of returning home
Mi Ya
You are break up for a long time
He will leave because he don't want to become my obstacle
My feelings for him have never changed for so many years I believe that he is same with me
Whatever you agree or not I will be together with Ji xingkong
Are you crazy
Because of Ji xingkong
You want to give up everything that you have possessed now
Do you know how much did I pay in order to you could have a good acievement
Do you forget it
I don't forget
Is me
I practice every day until two o'clock in the morning and I have never rested 365 days in a year I am so hard
Did anyone want to know
Because you choose the career
You should learn how to accept
You need responsible for your fans
Your words and deeds have to suitable for their expectations
But I am a human
You are not an ordinary person
You are enjoying the superstar's aura
This is your obligation that you need to hard working
If Ji xiangkong love you
He shouldn't bring the bad influence to you
Mi Ya
Don't destroed yourself
Since you came back already you should hard-working in the next time
You need to improve your status in China
Today I receive an activity
As a special guest
Don't worry
I will finish my work with a high quality
But about Xiang kong
I will never let him to leave
I am so tired now
Who left the ground and who wanted to fly farther and  they said they are willing to go to the seaside
Who didn¡¯t open her wings but she was chasing very helplessly then she only choose stay at there
When the migratory birds come back in four seasons the sky has been empty for a long time
We are waiting for the wind
The wind is blowing into the sea
You thought the migratory birds flew forward without feeling tired
Finally the day will come
We could understang we should still fall in love
Come back to the tree and give up you pride The wind is blowing into the sea
They can get to the out of sky
Freedom and love which one will be harder to release
Without your future I'm lost in the sea like a dolphin
Such as unpredictable and untouchable love that they go to the out of sky
Class 3 played a good basketball game yesterday
Yes what are you doing at there Did you help me make a like point for my sister We did it everyday
Why the data is so low
Qiao xin get a lot of likes
What are you looking for
Gu jiayi is so pretty
She is so wonderful
Xia ling
Gu jiayi are looking for you
Don't look at her please sen th post first quickly
Let's congratulations Team VNG They beat the Team Tiger VNG VNG
I will buy milk tea for you Which flavour do you want to drink
They are so excited
Pei xi
Why are you here you should go back to training with your teammates
OMG Are you serious
What did you say
You
You are laughing to Ji xingkong
No I don't
Although you don't admit it But i saw it at the moment
Why are you so happy that Team VNG won the game this time
If Ji xiang kong could become my opponent at the playoffs
I feel that is interesting
Why did I hear a taste of appreciation from your words
Congratulations you have won five games
Congratulations you jumped to the second in the Star of Tomorrow network vote
Good comment
The second
Why I got the higher popularity suddenly
Summer
Can I take two hours off
Where do you want to go
You are good
You really succeeded in apprenticeship
I think he is so busy in the daily life
In addition he need to check my revise video
I should say thanks to him actually
He
He is not interested in anything except work
He is a workaholic but he is also a imbecility person in the life
Are you sure
At the time when we were in a team, he used the water glasses is belong to us
I got it
What did you think about why are you so excited
Thank you Summer
I will go first
Bye Bye
I haven't given you a holiday yet
Thank you Summer
Director Guo
GDV is different from You xing Company you are so professional
Our company just lacks female commentators who are good and powerful such as you
I also need your help and support
Of course
Coach Luo
Are you know each other
Of course
I listened the revise video from Coach Luo I want to learn more professional knowledge
It was great
Luo tian
Qiao xin is so popular in the list of "Star of Tommorrow"
If you have free time please concentrate on her
Star of Tomorrow is the professional competition your profession is an important thing in my opinion
Hope I can see your wonderful performance on the field
OK I will hard-working then
I came to this position step by step by my own efforts
I am not like someone else she wants to rly on the relationships to earn the successful
Post the support notes everywhere
Stepping on the black material of other players somehow got countless praise
I am so sorry Coach
I am so excited now
I said more words but I hope I could get a unfair environment to prepare my competition
Don't worry Qiao xin I will check the series in a certain time
Thanks director Guo
I have something need to do Director Guo I will leave first
Bye Bye Coach Luo
Qiao xin
I will take you away
OK
Do these useless things
Hello
Hello Director Luo Qiu ying have a meeting with you
Coach Luo
Let her go to the commentary room to wait for me
OK
You should think carefully about whether you are really qualified to stand in this position
Coach Luo I am so sorry I just want to wait here for you
So can I help you
In order to express my gratitudethat you give a guide of my revise video I bought a gift to you I hope you could except it
So what do you want to know
This is my Commentary video
I saw a lot of commentary video of you
Today
I want to see your live commetary
Let's start
But coach Luo I did not do a preparation
I think that live commentary do not need time to prepare
If you don't want to show I will leave now Coach Luo Coach Luo
Today I will inroduce the first competition of Iconquer Team VNG vs Team Xiao long
Don't rush you couls speak slowly
At the 21 minutes and 36 seconds The two team started a wave of team battles
This team fight should be the most critical team fight in this game you should pay attention to your tone of voice
At the 21 minutes and 36 seconds The two team started a wave of team battles This team fight should be the most critical team fight in this game
Five people in Xiaolong Team vs Four people in Team VNG
If Team VNG without Pei xi in the competition they will lose the game this round
From your commentary I can't heard that you are interested in Iconquer Competition
I
Sorry Coach Luo
I couldn't control my voice tone Don't call me Coach Luo
If you are not passionate about this sport you are not qualified to stand in front of me
If I don't like the Iconquer Competition I will not appear in front of you
Oh really
A good commentary will not come to the fore by brushing support posts
support posts
Actually I never do that
I think we have a little misunderstanding
Please could you give me a free time I want to know what happened
I need to work now
Bye Coach Luo
Coach Luo The weather is cold your stomach is not very well please drink more hot water
He did a good basketball game they are class five
I thinks they are class three originally
Did James playing basketballs very well
You should introduce you sister to us No No No you should to look the cheerleading competition of Gu jiayi
We are waiting for you please quickly
Sister
Why you come to my school
I come here to find you
This is the first time you came to my school
Do you feel hungry We could eat something together
I don't need
I just want to tell you
Don't do something without significant
You know that
I am just want to help you Do you think it is useful to me
Xia ling
Whatever you did I will not forgive you
Are you understand I just want to keep quiet by myself
Sister
What am i doing wrong you don't call me sister
I could solve everything by myself
Xia ling
Put away your pity and sympathy
I don't need them
Let's see the data analyse
In the recently won game of Dragon Team They usually use the hero chariot and spike warrior
There was a certain outbreak in the early games and they have tacit cooperations in the later games
So we have a goal on the selection of hero
Qi yue
You should practice more the hero of Zhi heng
What happened
Qi yue
We are discussing the tactics please put down your phone
I am listening
Captain request you to practice Zhi heng
I know
Anything else
No I will leave first
Bye
Captain If you have any requestments please tell me
I will tell Qi yue at the first time
The next game we also use the double moon
You guys should take more practice ok no problem
We finish the meeting today
Wen Wen
Wen
I saw that
Recent three games of Qi yue
His data is not stable
He has been too bloated recently
We win the 7 games recently Each round he is the MVP
So this is why
I will find Li gan that they could have a relax chat
And you
Don't be nervous go back to home and take a rest now
Helll everyone I am Qiu ying Today I will introduce the 2017 the world competition of Iconquer the third round of BO3
Team Legends vs Team Super Sense
Team battle are beginning Queen of Thorns flashes into the crowded to unleash the three skills and they want to reap Chariot
But the Mogra at the same time
He use the skill to circled the queen of thorns they two outputed together reasonably This translation software said it was better than me At this time Juggernaut chose to rush into the crowd but when he rushed in half
Suddenly Why are you come to here
I finished my training so I just walking around
OK what's wrong with you
You looks like worried something
Tomorrow is the final competition of Star of tomorrow
It is terrible when I listen to my revise video
When I heard Coach Luo tian to comment somethig that he could express the full emotion
But about me It is such like I just finish my homework with no emotion
I tried a lot of times but I cannot do it
I want to give up
Do you know what is the important thing before your exam
You shold take relaxed not temporarily hold Buddha's feet
Please don't listen to these at the moment
Please give me your earphone
I invite you to listen to my private music list
Before the competition I will listen to them to relieve my stress
It is useful
Oh you could close your eyes
If you have to waste time it shuld be waste with a suitable reason such as fall in love you
If you can’t be alone you are the one who started to be a figurine
Why doesn't it rain on a sunny day
Didn't you close your eyes
Because of you
I am so lucky to meet you
How are you feeling now
I like the song
As long as you let go of your worries be confident and focus on the competition you must do it
Don't forget the agreement between us go to the top of the world together
Oh
Ji xiangkong
I have a question
I want to ask you for a long time
Actually
Actually you see that Mi Ya has been filmed to meet the male god alone at night
I heared that she want to recover her first love boyfriend and she use the out of sky to become the AP song
What's wrong with you
I forget it
You are fans of Mi Ya
What happened
Are you sad
I don't need to feel sad because I am only a fans
As long as it is her choice, I will bless her if she could happiness in the future
Oh
What do you want to ask me
Tomorrow is the final competition of Star Tomorrow
You will come to the scene to cheer for me right
Of course
Tony
Did you do the online scandal about me and Ren xv?
He is very popular now you just returned to the country which is helpful to enhance your popularity Didn't you say I'm not qualified to fall in love
You met Ji xingkong in private and you was photographed by journalist
D you know this is the biggest rescue I can do Since they were photographed let them expose I don't care
Exposed who
Ji xiangkong
Do you know about him
His criticism is very poor you will pull lower about your image when you want to fall in love him It is because no one understands Xiang Kong
Ji xiangkong  He is a person with a good ability and enthusiasm
I never feel ashamed to be with him
Mi ya
Are you confused by feelings
So many years have passed
Although you alwanys love him But Ji xingkong will change his feeling actually It is impossible
OK
Now a girl has a good relationship with him
Her name is Qiu ying If you don't beliebve me you can check by yourself
The person in this picture is you
After so many years you finally waited for her to come back
Everyone else is blind method
You don't need care about that
I know
She and Ren xv they don't have anything to happen
But she and I
Also nothing happened between us
So what is the relationship between you and her now
she told me
She will back to our country totally because of me
And then
She will stay at China
Also she is willing t give up her job
However
You are afraid of delaying her
So what do you worried about
Xiangkong
You have been single for so many years
In addition to trying to concentrate on the game the other reason is because of the influence that she gave you
But she backed now
And she wants to redeem this relationship
Why you don't try to give her a new start
Hello
Xiang kong
Don't get wrong I don't have relationship with Ren xv
This is an arrage of my company I don't know about that
I know
They want to protect your image
Thanks you could understand me
Don't worry this will never happen again in the future
I will talok to Tony I will let him clarify as soon as possible and tell everyone that the person I always like is don't impulse
You are a super star
You should be careful to do each decision
Xiang kong
You gave up our relationship in order to the development of my career
But I understand now
Compare with the idol aura you are the important thing in my heart
Can I meet you now
Today is too late
And photos already upload to the Internet
It is so dangerous if you go out now
How about tomorrow
I will go to Star of Tomorrow to be a guest
Before the beginning of games I want to see you first
Don't refuse me please
Please you come here please
I will wait you
Hurry up Which room
They write it on the door
Dressing room dressing room
Qiu ying
I am so sorry
Why are you come to here I told you It's lively outside All of your friend come to here help you to cheers
Emmm
Are Ji xiangkong come here
Why you remember him only
He said he will come to live to cheer me up
You should believe him
He will come soon
Are you fans of Ji xingkong
Alright I heard that they want to recommend Qiao Xin to become a championship
I can't believe Don't speak fake news
But You xing is the important sponor this time
I will go back to rest room now see you soon
Coach Luo
Hello Director Liu
Thanks for everyone Today I will go back to the dress room
Qiao xin
We are looking forward to your wonderful performance
I won't let you down
Let's go
Prepare well please
Qiu ying come come come
come here
Director Liu Director Guo and Luo tian send Qiao xin to dress room together
In my opinion
It is not a fake news
I don't believe that
Yes
Don't worry about that
Fighting later
Qiu ying you are great
Fighting
What did you see Sorry Qiu ying I will arrive late
It is ok you can do your things first
What happened
Ji xiangkong said he will come later because he has something to do
Did you say Ji xingkong will come on time
But now he is late
He must come here I promised you
You come back to prepare
you could prepare first
We will support you at the audience seat
Cheer up Qiu ying
Hello everyone welcome come to GDV the commentary final competition of Star of tomorrow I am the host A can
Welcome everyone
According to today's game rules there are votes from our live audience and votes from the judges The one with the most votes is our champion today Today we are divided into two parts The first round is a question and answer session
Two players will enter the second round of live commentary
They will compete for the championship
Don't skimp on your applause cheer for your favorite players Qiao xin Qiao xin Qiu ying Qiu ying
In addition to the four heavyweight guests who have arrived today there is also a mysterious guest who will come to our competition today and she is the very popular singer Mia
Mia Come here Why Ji xingkong still not arrive
Ji xiangkong is fans of Mia he should not to late
Welcome to Mia
Welcome to Mia come to the live of competition
Qiu ying
Miss Mia
I heard that she would imitate you dancing very well her CTR  ranked first is your wild grass dance
Next let's enter the first question and answer session
Hello can you help me to scan it I am sorry I don't have free time
Hello Can you waste your 1 minute time could you help me to scan the QR code she is my sister she will join the competition today
She looks so pretty we can help him to scan
Thanks you very much you can scan here or postcode
Let's go now thanks bye bye
Hey bro Can you waste your 1 minute time could you help me to scan the QR code she is my sister she will join the competition today
What is the maximum distance of Jincan's five-legged injury A-800 B-1000 C-1200 D-1400
Please answer
Qiao xin is so quick
Qiao Xin is worthy of being the first female host of GDV she was so great
Please give me your answer
Although Jincan only has 1000 after he has full skills he can play a maximum of 1200 with some props
I choose C-1200
Congratulations Qiao Xin answered another question correctly
I can't see Qiao Xin is so powerful
Every time she thinks about it she doesn't need to think about it she could answer it as a fast speed even a professional player like me can't do that
Emmm
So she knew the answer beforehand
I choose D You are right
I choose C correct again I choose A
You are right B  C   D you are right
I choose A
D
Congratulations Qiao xin Correct again
Sister have to answer next question
OK The next question please you make a prepare
I don't care I will push my point first A26-31 B28-31 C30-32 D33-38
Please Answer
This round is belong to Qiu ying Please give me you answer
We have a limited time to give your answer
Why she didn't give her answer
Cheers up Qiu ying The question is so simple You could answer it
Maybe she is thinking the question
It was originally Pan Shen who had the lowest initial hero damage
But after the Xuan tian enter to the organization
Asin took this position
When the hero's damage is less than 28 they can't make up the minion's armor
So it must be more than 28
I choose B
OK Congratulations Qiu ying she gave me a correct answer
Qiu ying Qiu ying You are so great Qiu ying
Hello Can you waste your 1 minute time could you help me to scan the QR code she is my sister she will join the competition today
Ok Alright you can scan here
Thanks Thank you very much
Hello Hello
The competition is quite fierce now
There is still one last question The second place is Qiu Ying the first place is Qiao Xin There is still suspense about who the champion is.
Please listen to the last question
If there is a black screen on the scene how did the commentary do that they could solve the problem
The range of answers to this question is very wide Are you sure you want to answer the question if you do not hear the options behind
Or you just feel nervous and push the button not on purpose
Don't laugh her
She just grabbed the question first the answer is still thinking
This kind of question can't be answered correctly with a few numbers can there be a standard answer
If she is not careful she could easily answer partial questions
Qiu ying please give me your answer
Because we have the time limited for this question
You should answer the question in the limited time otherwise your answer will be wrong answer
If I suddenly get a black screen while I do the comment
I will stay at the stage of commentary
Try my best to keep the audience's focus on the expectations of the game
Instead of expanding the impact of the emergency on the audience
I think it is Qiuying's answer
I remember you were doing a show in Vancouver before and then you encounter a sudden situation you will use singing and dancing to resolve
If you encounter unexpected situations in the future should you still use sing and dance to resolve it
He made it clear that he was digging a hole for Qiu Ying  she is a lucky girl
The easiest way is to verify and inform Guanzhong of the reason for the black screen
But this will interrupt the audience's expectations of the game
If it were me I would be as active as possible to comfort the audience
The professionalism of commentary is not only reflected in quick commentary and accurate analysis  But it is reflected in the explanation of whether the bridge between the audience and the game can be made if there is a sudden situation on the spot
Treat the audience with the awe so that the audience is always full of enthusiasm for the game
So is this your answer
Yes I finish my answer
The correct answer is arouse audience emotions and continue to comment as usual
Congratulations Qiu ying your answer is correct
Great
What is your opinion I think she have an ability to become a professional Commentator
Qiu Ying answered this question correctly she successfully tied the score let us congratulate Qiu Ying and Qiao Xin for entering the next commentary pk round
Qiu ying Qiu ying Qiu ying
Hello everyone I am commentator Qiu ying This is my first time to stand the big stage
Making a commentary for you
I am so nervous
One more time
Hello everyone I am Fu Mia Today is my first public performance I hope hope
I hope that
What did you write down
I don't want show you
Go sit there
Quichly go to there
Do you know
When do you look best
When
It ’s best to look when you are serious
Annoying
I am so nervous now
Hello everyone my name is Fu Mia
Today is my first time  Please don't read it don't look it
The first time what you return to me please
Do you think I will succeed or not
You are so hard I believe that you will successful in the future
Don't nervous tomorrow
This is my first time to stand the big stage to make a commentary for you
I am sorry for late
Congratulations you won the first place in the first round
You tell me the process of game is particularly thrilling right
But thanks to your advice
So that I have the confidence to answer again and again
You are confident and hard working then I look forward to your second round performance
The second round I am doing live commentary
If you have spare time Could you go to the live and cheer up for me
I'm here in order to watch your game do you think I have free time or not
OK I am not bother you to prepare I will go to find Lin yixuan First
See you later Fighting
Don't grasp me
Mia you are a guest now you are recording a program can you be professional?
Tony
Qiu Ying's smile and her efforts are exactly the same as I did five years ago
If Xiang Kong really likes her it is to find my shadow on her
I know Xiang kong still remember me
I will go to find him
Mia
Please recognize the reality earlier
Ji xiangkong just talk with me before
He let me to tell you
Forget him
Become yourself early
Is it ok