Episode 7
The pictures are all deleted.
Can't finish the task now, what to do now?
I'm also caught.
It's not auspicious to go out today.
chest out, take deep breaths.
It's okay. Heads up,
Let's go.
We have to work hard tomorrow too.
Boss, four computers.
Identification card?
Surprise!
Are you suprised? Are you shocked?
Why did you all come here?
If we don't come here, can we find you?
Busy man.
let's have a gathering.
Since we're already here,
Sure, let's go.
It seems like I can't leave.
Ah Xuan,
look after the shop well.
Eat, eat some.
Luo Tian, this rascal.
Let me tell you, he's too unloyal.
We agreed to come together.
and went to work overtime.
Midway, he received a call,
He's always been like that.
He's a workaholic.
Let's understand him.
Unreliable, come, let's drink.
Lao Gu,
I couldn't go for your departure today,
I'm really sorry.
What are you saying?
between brothers.
There's no need to be sorry
It's okay.
We know you're not used to these occasions,
we won't force you.
You guys specially came from so far,
just to see me,
I do feel a little-
A little what?
Today,
I do feel a little embarrassed
I said I will treat you guys to a feast.
We made it too simple and crude.
Time really flies.
Lao Gu has quit now.
Boss.
Is your computer working?
Why not you go home, is that okay?
It's not suitable to game today.
Our training
really rack our brains.
No one dares to even relax.
We pushed ourselves and practiced daily.
weren't fast enough.
We were just worried our hands
We made it seem like we weren't tired.
That's why you're the ace.
I'm not-
This is not what I mean.
Okay.
Did you know? That time, he-
Do you remember?
plain steamed buns daily.
He'd drink water and eat
I thought he came from a temple.
He doesn't do anything else,
doesn't even have a girlfriend.
I'm not as handsome,
I can't talk as well as you guys,
how to find a girlfriend?
You should forget it,
It's okay to exaggerate about others,
but in our clique,
uncountable pretty ladies,
Shu Wen,
are all attracted to him in a matter of minutes.
don't blindly say things.
You drank too much,
It's okay.
It's all in the past now.
Come, let's drink.
Don't talk about it, it's over.
It's in the past.
It's over yet you are still
in contact with her.
Who's in close
contact with each other?
The current situation now is pretty good.
Is that right?
Let's drink, okay?
the old days today.
We're here to talk about
Come, talk about the old days.
You're here?
What time's your flight tomorrow?
I'll go send you off.
No need.
I can go alone.
Oh right,
I heard Manager Zhao
but you rejected it.
pushed you to go for a reality show,
I don't like those things that
are a waste of time.
You should know
why Lao Sun
left this industry right?
I know.
He has his difficulties.
Actually, in those years,
Amongst the five of us,
he was the most fanatical.
He was also the most gifted.
During the digital competition back then,
people thought he wasn't promising.
So once his parents fell ill,
he could only accept reality.
Leader, I don't understand.
Do you want me to go against reality?
Or do you want me to accept reality?
There are down sides to a business,
but there are also plus points.
We must learn to adapt,
in order to go further.
I understand.
In future, as long as it doesn't affect
the team's practice
I'll try my best to cooperate.
Okay.
I'll take this away.
It's photographed pretty well.
The five new heroes of Conquer,
Zhi Heng, Jin Can,
Yu Bang, Gong Xi Chang Qing,
and Ah Xin's details are all here.
Our most urgent mission currently
is to get this five heroes.
During the internal trial game,
catch the opponents off guard.
for this competition?
You want to rely on the new heroes
Have you thought this through?
these new heroes.
We just started practicing with
If we want to win
I'm afraid it'll be tough.
Not bad.
But, our opponent and our situations
are the same.
We're both getting to know the new heroes.
If we can
grasp the characters earlier,
we can win.
On the other hand,
if our opponents familiarise and use them,
we will also be easily defeated.
Kong ge is right.
Ji Shuai,
you are our leader now.
I'll comply with everything you say.
Me too.
Thank you for your trust brothers.
Let's work hard together.
But, now we have a new problem.
The time is too short.
Manager Zhao let one of us
attend a reality show.
It's such a waste of time.
It's okay, I know this.
Okay.
Let's start training.
Let's practice, brothers.
All the best!
Yu Bang is mine,
no one can snatch from me.
Finally done with it!
Thinking about it,
it's good enough that people are watching.
Let's seize time and practice
with the new heroes on Conquer!
Chairman Jin,
Yesterday, the director of Aurora videos
called and said that
it'll be impossible to
work with us in future.
Why?
Don't you know?
Aurora videos selected
Ji Xiang Kong to attend the reality show.
It was all rejected by Ji Xiang Kong.
He said he has no time.
But
But what?
Speak.
But he has the time
to be with that UXStar host
played as a duo.
The two live streamed and
There's such a thing?
Chairman Jin,
we can't afford to offend
Aurora videos.
Chairman Jin.
XiangKong.
Just nice, I was going to look for you
I heard from Manager Zhao
you and Aurora videos
Chairman Jin,
I came to talk to Manager Zhao
about this matter.
I already confirmed the
reality show's schedule with Aurora videos.
Impossible, this-
I- How come I didn't know?
You didn't know?
Then, you'd have to ask your phone.
Staff from Aurora videos
kept calling you but you didn't pick up.
Really?
There's no call!
Look!
There really isn't.
Right, Manager Zhao.
In future, any business collaboration
that doesn't affect the team's practice,
as long as you tell me
I will cooperate actively.
Chairman Jin.
If there's nothing else, I'll go first.
Practice well.
No, I really didn't receive it.
Really didn't.
Have some tea.
I'm not drinking, leave quickly.
Close the door for me.
Am I really not suitable
to be Conquer's host?
Although you just adjusted from
the real life version,
maybe you're still not used to it.
But, I can only give you
one month's time.
If until then,
the problem's still not solved,
I can only be apologetic.
[Dear Miss Qiu Ying! Your China Business Bank's loan totals to RMB 2,200,000. Currently you've paid RMB 10,600, please arrange for repayment before the 25th of this month. Thanks!]
[Unknown number]
Hello?
Hello,
Is this UXStar's Qiu Ying?
Yes, and you are?
I am Director An from Aurora videos.
This week, Saturday,
we are holding a reality show.
We're inviting Conquer's professional players
and female hosts to participate.
Do you have the time?
Director An, about that,
Time isn't a problem for me.
But...
Don't worry.
We will pay you for appearing.
I will send the
full details to your email.
Thank you Director An.
There's always a way out!
Thank you God.
Pei Xi!
I just applied some hand cream,
my hands are a little slippery.
Can you help me out?
No need, thank you.
I have mine.
Qiu Ying.
Director An.
Ji handsome.
This is Qiu Ying who's grouping with you.
No, Director An,
I-
I'm pairing with Ji Xiang Kong?
Yeah.
Pei Xi and Qiao Xin are a group.
You two are a group.
You guys can rest here first.
I'll inform everyone
before the filming begins.
Qiu Ying.
What's the matter with you?
Aren't you always in good relation
with Ji Xiang Kong?
Why does it matter to you?
Your idol is leaving.
Pei Xi, wait for me!
What are you looking at?
In order to appear on this show,
you did quite a lot right?
What do you mean?
Don't tell me the grouping
is purely a coincidence.
Ji Xiang Kong, I'm telling you
I, Qiu Ying, came to this show.
I am honestly
invite here.
Besides, before I came here,
I didn't even know
my partner is you, asshole.
Really?
Okay.
Then, later, I'll
definitely let you enjoy the limelight.
Wrong answer.
Still pretty awesome.
Am I wrong?
Is it D?
Qiu Ying, are you okay?
It's okay.
There's still another chance later on.
Okay, come.
Third question.
We're coming back to Pei Xi's team.
How can the rock beast be able
to take on various positions in the team?
A, decided by skill.
B, decided by attributes.
C, decided by looks.
D, decided by outfit.
The correct answer is?
D.
Congratulations, correct answer.
Pei Xi, love you.
Qiao Xin is really lucky.
Pei Xi answered correctly again.
Then, we've come to
Ji Xiang Kong again.
Will they be able to get it right this time?
Listen to the question.
How many times can
the ignited stick cause harm?
A, once.
B, twice.
C, thrice.
D, unlimited times.
Please answer carefully.
D.
D, is that right?
Wrong answer.
Ji Xiang Kong!
Our punishment set up
still has a little bit of
visual illusion.
Qiu Ying, are you okay?
Quickly find someone to help Qiu Ying up.
Ji Xiang Kong,
you're just messing with me.
You're just messing with me.
Now, we see that Qiu Ying
is a little angry.
A little frustrated.
Why do you always answer wrongly?
I'm participating on a reality show
for the first time.
I'm a little nervous.
Qiu Ying still
looks a little moody.
Did it hurt when you fell?
Okay, so currently,
we are at our last question.
It's also on Ji Xiang Kong.
Currently, this side has yet to succeed.
So you'll need to work hard.
Listen to the question please.
Hero Lightning God's skill
is shot from the left hand
or the right?
Simply choose between the two options.
Please answer.
Ji Xiang Kong, if you have the ability,
continue answering wrongly!
Let me tell you.
I
I, Qiu Ying, was never
afraid.
Left hand.
Wrong answer.
Qiu Ying.
Qiu Ying are you ok?
Ji Xiang Kong, you did it purposely.
You did it purposely.
Today, this team
didn't get any questions correct.
Qiu Ying who is inside, you must hold on.
Okay.
After this round's tussle,
Pei Xi and Qiao Xin's team
are currently first.
Then, let's invite Qiao Xin
and Qiu Ying on stage.
Please.
Congratulations to Pei Xi's team.
So, do you guys have anything
you want to say now?
I'm very grateful
Is it meaningful?
And my partner, Pei Xi.
I'll decide if it's meaningful or not.
Okay.
Then, let me once again congratulate
Pei Xin's team
for entering the next round first.
Dear Audience, you are now watching
Aurora video's
heavily weighted reality show's
ace heroes competiton site
brought to you by
Good shop high end snacks.
Coming up next,
we are entering the second round,
2V2 battle.
I hope that you can treat
this competition seriously.
Let me see your true abilities.
We can see that
the two professional gods
are peacefully developing on the line.
not bothering about their team mates.
But Qiao Xin and Qiu Ying
are fighting fiercely.
Qiao Xin.
Who called you to be against me?
Qiu Ying, stop chasing.
If you're unable to fight, then retreat, Qiu Ying.
Dodge.
Qiu Ying was chased into the vacinity of
the imperial tower by Qiao Xin.
She's 'bleeding' and injured.
Pei Xi, quickly come and help me.
Pei Xi appeared at this moment
and controlled Qiu Ying with one move.
Ji Xiang Kong, I'm dying.
Quickly come and save me.
I can't anymore.
I don't want to die
with you.
Qiao Xin turned around to cooperate
with Pei Xi's creator,
killing the injured Qiu Ying.
Nice.
First blood.
Died again.
We see the injured Ji Xiang Kong,
is still remaining in the middle,
Don't you want to play 1V2?
What do you mean 1V2?
I think it's more like 1V3.
This Ji Xiang Kong
is in with you guys right?
If you want to win,
then follow me.
I said, if you want to win,
then follow me, don't go anywhere else.
I'm not helping you,
I don't want you to drag me down.
Am I seeking help from Ji Xiang Kong?
Wait, what are we doing?
Why did Qiu Ying
ran till midway and stopped moving?
Ji Xiang Kong is midway.
Pei Xi, come here quickly.
He's injured.
Quick, chase him.
You stay here,
don't go anywhere.
Pei Xi,
directly charged towards Ji Xiang Kong.
You're making me wait for death alone.
Is this your tactic?
If you want to win,
then follow what I instruct you, do you hear me?
Wait in the bushes.
If I don't call you over, don't come over.
What's she doing?
Pei Xi is following Ji Xiang Kong.
After reaching the tower,
hide well.
Don't be in their line of sight.
You- you're sure
that you don't me to help you?
If this continues, it's dangerous
for Ji Xiang Kong.
Stay there, don't move.
I've attract Pei Xi over.
Okay, go, we can fight now.
Fight.
What do I do?
Fight, do something drastic.
Okay.
Control him, control.
This is a trap.
Ji Xiang Kong's used his skills
to control Qiao Xin and Pei Xi.
Qiu Ying cooperated with Ji Xiang Kong
and killed Qiao Xin.
Nice.
A wave.
Continue chasing, don't.
Don't let your hands leave the keyboard.
Got it.
What a wave of waiting for the target.
Follow me and push.
Coming.
The speed that they're pushing
the tower is really fast.
They pushed it off.
Now, push the last crystal.
Come on!
Nice.
Congratulations to Ji Xiang Kong and Qiu Ying.
Ji Xiang Kong, we won!
Congratulations.
This was also a very exciting
competition.
Come, let's also welcome
Pei Xi and Qiao Xin.
Come onto stage, please.
Okay, Pei Xi and Qiao Xin.
Then, I announce.
The second round of the competition
Ji Xiang Kong and Qiu Ying
won the 2V2 battle.
Congratulations to both.
Hi?
I'll tell you a piece of good news.
I won!
You- You won!
The prize is
Limited edition Conquer's doll,
Good shop's member rewards card
and a laptop.
Really?
No.
But,
based on your standard,
It's Ji Xiang Kong.
At first, he was truly messing with me.
But, in the end, when it got urgent,
you don't know how powerful he is.
He defeated Pei Xi and Qiao Xin
like falling water.
Too addictive!
This isn't reasonable.
But the reality is exactly so.
Maybe he conciously discovered.
Director An.
Qiu Ying, sorry.
Ji handsome left this doll behind.
Can I trouble you to hand it to him?
I'm really too busy.
Thank you.
Can I take a picture with you?
- Thanks.
Sure.
One, two, three.
Okay.
Thank you!
Others call you the battleground's swindler
There definitely are people who call me that.
You definitely tricked me just now.
It's merely a small trap.
I didn't expect you to really fall for it.
Not bad.
At first, I thought that rookie
will become your burden.
I didn't expect
you'll still be able to make use of her.
People do their best.
This is my principle for using people.
If the battle today,
was 1V1,
you definitely won't win.
Perhaps.
You are the quickest in all the alliances.
If I battled you alone,
there's a higher chance of me losing.
But, don't forget.
Conquer is never a
solo competition.
It'd be best if you brought out your capabilities today
during the internal trial game.
I'll only do better.
Because we are
a five member group.
See you at the internal trial game.
Ji Xiang Kong!
Wait a minute!
You forgot your doll.
Director An asked me to send it to you.
Thanks.
No problem.
Actually,
I should be the one thanking you.
Thank you.
For allowing me to be a champion today.
And you did well
for today's battle.
Without you, I could have played better.
I know.
But I still want to thank you.
Is there still anything else?
Hand.
I want to
treat you to a meal.
Treat me to a meal?
I messed with you the whole day.
Yet, you still want to treat me to a meal?
You didn't injure yourself during the fall did you?
It's ok.
Actually,
the elevation stage,
was pretty exciting.
Actually,
I have a dream.
I've always wanted to be a
gaming host.
I've been learning these days.
But I figured
Conquer doesn't seem
as simple as I thought.
And before I understood,
I got to know you.
A professional gamer.
So,
So you want me to teach you.
Sure.
How to teach you?
It's like this.
I made a brambles queen
hero skills explanation video.
But it's horribly made.
And I got scolded badly by netizens.
If it's convenient for you,
can you have a look at it for me?
Okay, let's watch it here.
Or do we watch it at your home?
My home?
You put in so much effort
isn't it all to have
an affair with me,
and spark some gossip out?
I-
I didn't mean it this way.
Let go.
Act, continue acting.
Loosening the reins in order to grasp better isn't it?
You're already so direct.
Let's be more straight forward, okay?
Let's go, to your home.
Ji Xiang Kong.
You are too much!
Am I too much
or are you being dramatic?
It's you who were pretending
to be Gu Fang's fan in Vancouver.
On the conquer programme,
in order to increase views,
you were the one who danced.
The one who didn't ask for the truth
and secretly filmed and uploaded the conflict video
was still you.
Including today's reality show.
Ask yourself.
Besides being a little smart,
how are you good enough
to join the gaming industry
as a qualified host?
Let me tell you.
Many people worked hard and
seriously in order to get
the industry to this stage.
and seek a shortcut,
If you want to have a quick success
Sorry, there's no way.
Ji Xiang Kong.
No matter what I, Qiu Ying, do
there's no way an asshole like you
can educate me!
Step aside.
Why did you come to my room again
when there's nothing to do?
It's because I miss you.
Besides, it's comfortable here.
What's this?
Why does it matter to you?
What are you watching?
Qiu Ying's video.
She got scolded really badly.
When the brambles queen is laning,
it can't be too long.
Can't use up too much of
the opponent's hero's blood levels.
But it will cause oneself-
But she will use up her own skills
so you can't use it normally.
I made a brambles queen
hero explaination video.
I got scolded badly by netizens.
If you have nothing to do, don't watch
this type of nonsense.
How is this
a nonsensical thing?
Didn't she also go for
that reality show of yours?
You two even became champion.
Speaking of which,
the both of you are pretty fated.
I think you are pretty bored.
Why not we add
two hours of practice for you?
I-
I'm not bored at all.
I'm busy, let me tell you.
I'm busy.
When faced with an opponent's hero
of the same level,
it can cause really bad damage.
When the brambles queen is laning,
it can't be too long.
Can't use up too much of
the opponent's hero's blood levels.
It's an auxiliary hero.
If it dies once,
it affects their own blood levels as well.
What she says is true.
So, you need to develop it carefully.
Was it a little too much?
How was it?
You thanked that liar
Was he shocked
by your generousity?
And reflect on how mean he was?
I just
told him thank you.
Let me tell you.
Ji Xiang Kong was
always talked about negatively.
It's best to stay further away from him.
I got it.
Thanks for your reminder.
Mom.
Am I really that bad?
I will definitely work really hard.
I won't let others look down on me anymore.
The hero here with me
also has the speeding effect.
You can use it after you've used the first two skills.
Produced roughly, excessively made.
There are many mistakes.]
[Produced roughly, excessively made,
Although your comment was very negative,
but I'm still very grateful that you
clicked into my video.
I'm still working hard and learning.
As for the wrong parts in the video,
you're welcome to criticise and correct it.
Still pretty humble...
Then I'll come and
guide you.
And pick out your problems.
You're here.
Hello.
What would you like to drink?
Have a seat.
That-
The traffic's pretty bad right?
If I knew, I would have booked
besides VNG.
Right?
That way I won't hold up
your practice time.
Being able to get you to meet me
is really too difficult.
Truthfully speaking,
I've been in this industry
for many years.
I've never met
such a genius player like you.
The five kills that day,
was really awesome.
Double kill.
Quadraple kill.
Runaway.
Did you know?
Earlier, before you were in VNG,
I've started noticing you.
But your cousins, Xia Tian and Shu Wen,
are old friends for many years.
I'm too inferior to compare.
I don't have a choice.
But, I'll say something truthful.
VNG isn't really suitable for you.
Do you know?
Being strong alone, can't be qualified as strong.
Besides, this is a
team game, am I right?
Your team mate is messing with you.
They can't bring good results.
Then what do we do?
That's why in these years
VNG is always
one step away from championship.
Am I right?
You want me to transfer to Legends
As long as you're willing,
I'm willing to accept anything, really.
Who's the leader?
Is it Ji Xiang Kong?