GANK YOUR HEART
Episode Nineteen
Manager Zhao  Where are you going
Yeah Where are you running
You were quite powerful
Don’t touch me
Don’t move Where are you going
I tell you not to touch me
Why are you running
Where are you going
Where are you running
Don’t touch me   Where do you want to go
Don’t touch me
None of you can touch me today
What are you yelling
Stop
What are you doing
want to rebel
Stand still
You see
This is what you teach
Is it necessary
Do you really have to be so ruthless
Get out
Coach
Manager Zhao
Be careful
Manager  Goodbye
Do you guys get stronger
No sir no no
We are just kidding
Shut up
You guys
Including you
Go to the playground
Everyone runs fifty laps
Now
Right away
Fifty laps
Now
Let’s go
So energetic
Maybe fifty laps are not enough
Let’s take a rest
Can’t run anymore
Yao  Today’s issue
We’re still good brothers
The anger in my heart
is finally released today
That old fox Zhaoyang was beaten
so hard today
But today
The manner that Xipei fights against Zhaoyang
looks like he has a grudge against him
I tell you
It’s not because they have a grudge
It’s that Peixi
kicks Zhaoyang when he’s down
Peixi  Pei
Mr. Luo punishes us to run laps
It's none of your business
it's me
that made him fall
It’s him
Let’s go
Our captain is great
Captain  Look
Zhaoyang deserves to get caught
He deserves it
Excellent
Yeah
I haven't expected that
Zhaoyang from Legend Team
could be so bad
This article written by LuYiyi
is very great   Of course
Look our LuYiyi is so cool
Finally
The revenge of brother Kong and Qiuying is taken
Zhaoyang deserves it
Good job
Good
It's a good work
Really
That’s so great
I will bring it
to teacher Luotian tomorrow
Right
Tell me
How did you capture
the overwhelming teacher Luotian
There’s no capture
You have no idea
how badly he scolded me
Let me imitate him
He’s like this
Qiuying’s commentary
is not commentary at all
You
just retell
what others
have seen
In the future
Don’t make me see
things that are so meaningless
Great
You imitate him quite well
He scolded you like that
You still show him the video
As long as he is willing to watch
He can scold me whatever he likes
What about this
I have a close relationship
with Mr. Luo
What about helping you pull a few strings
Who told me that
In our industry
There is no need to gain advantage by trickery
Who  Which one is so blind
that say such superficial
and naive words
If I knew this person
I would never let him go
Excuse me
Sorry to interrupt
There’s only one piece of cake left
You are a couple anyway
You can eat together
No no no
You misunderstood
We are not a couple
It’s okay
Though you are not a couple
you can still have this cake together
Enjoy yourself
Thank you
What about
You  you eat it
This is
a strawberry cake
which is your favorite
so you eat it
I’m a man
How can I
make girls hungry
What about this
Just like what he said
Two of us
can share together
The cake is cut
Why are you laughing
Let’s eat
Well
A whole heart
is divided into two halves
Otherwise how to cut it
Cut it horizontally
Mr. Ji
Are you available tomorrow
Take you to a nice place
Where
Don’t you want to find a place
to cheer e up
No
It’s so crowded today
You see that's a castle
and there are so many
Cartoon shops
And there are balloons over there
So beautiful
You like it too
Then take a photo together
Come  Stand here
Everyone shows off
moment
Three Two One Okay
Every breath around you
Come let's take a selfie together
Forever
Okay
Let’s go play something else
The second hand moves slowly
A little more every day
Xiangkong
I see there are Dumbos
Peter Pan and Winnie the Pooth over there
And looks like we don't need to wait in line
Shall we
Wait  wait
You bring me here today
to cheer me up
You have to ask me anyway
what I like to play
I know
but
We have plenty of time today
Don't worry
As long as you like
I will play with you
You promise
I want to play this
TRON Lightcycle Power Run
Heard that it’s very exciting
and very fast
I know this
Just like roller coaster
But I think
we just entered the park
Will it be too exciting
It’s your suggestion to come
Are you
getting afraid now
I have nothing to fear
Don’t worry
I come out with you to relax today
As long as you like
I will play with you
Loyal enough
Let’s go
What's wrong
Well
Let’s play some
light projects
Then I will play TRON Lightcycle Power Run
with you
Is it okay
Fine
As long as you’re willing to accompany me
I don’t care what I play
Moment
It’s funny  It’s funny
Let’s play
Every breath around you
becomes sweet
Forever
is not so far
The second hand moves slowly
A little more every day
Love
Your dishes are ready  Enjoy yourself please
Thanks thanks
These dishes are so cute
Fortunately
there are not many people at this time today
We have played so many games
this morning
After we finish the meal
Let’s go play TRON Lightcycle Power Run
What’s wrong
You can make it
But I didn't expect that
I can have such a good time
with you today
That really exceeds my expectations
Really
As long as you are happy
I will do anything
Go eat
Right
Today
I saw some tourists took part in
the first-time activity
They share all interesting moments
on the internet
Really
Sounds interesting
Well we
have also shot so many photos
Let’s take part in as well
Sure
I think this one is great
Let’s call it
Light up the fairy tale world for the first time
Good good  use this one
Okay see more
I think this one is also good
You even closed your eyes
choose this one
call it
Too light to open the eyes for the first time
You want to show my ugly photo
You also have ugly photos okay
You  show me
So many
I ask you
Are you really not afraid
to play all these games
I’m not afraid
I have told you I’m not afraid
Said not to be afraid
You see this photo
I can feel that you’re so nervous
You said I closed my eyes
You also closed your eyes
It's just an accident
Eyes also closed in this one
An accident
Fine  Fine
Actually
You are not as bold as
you said
It’s because you want to accompany me
Not all because of you
JiXiangkong
Thank you
It is because you are here
making me have courage
to play so many
games that I was yearning but fear to play for the first time
Besides
You are here with me
The moment I cry
I feel the whole body
has been released
All of my worries
are swept away
I hope you can feel it too
Gather all energetic
to face the games in the future
You were so scared
but still here with me
because you want to cheer me up
Qiuying
It is me that should say thank you
Wait for me
Where are you going
Mickey
God
May I
take a photo with you
Great great
Well  You teach me how to pose
Come on
Thanks Daisy  Thanks Daisy
Thank you  Thank you
It’s a perfect day
I can take photos
with so many friends in Disneyland
Byebye
Is it perfect
Your princess dream
is so small
God
These
Are these all for me
The moment you entered Disneyland
You stared at these balloons
I saw it
Thanks
and this
Today
My princess dream
completely comes true
Princess Qiuying
Your princess dream
just starts
If I say
Follow me
Time
It’s worth wasting
As long as I am with you
If I say
I can’t be alone
Carrousel
That is you
Princess Qiuying
Your ride
is ready
Follow me
Let’s go
Why it doesn’t rain on a sunny day
Why the desert is full of flowers
Because of you
How lucky I am
to meet you
Time freezes
for this moment
Indelible moment
How unforgettable
to become so close to you
Then discover it is too much
to hug
Staring at each other
is enough
If I say
I can’t be alone
It is you
that do it to me
I accept you interrupt me
Qiuying
Your look
tells me that
you are thinking at random again
I  I am not
I’m thinking
We have been
playing so many exciting games
It’s really great
how about
Let’s go play
TRON Lightcycle Power Run
I don’t want you to regret
But you are afraid
Don’t force yourself
As long as you are here
I have nothing to fear
Knight JiXiangkong
This is order from Princess Qiuying
Yes Princess
I  I'm not afraid
So close to you
Then discover it is too much
to hug
Staring at each other
is enough
Princess Qiuying
Has your dream
come true today
Not yet
I wish you
join the competition with no worries
Come on
Don’t worry
I will definitely get
the championship back
JiXiangkong
You’re always the best
Freeze
Indelible moment
How unforgettable
to become so close to you
Then discover it is too much to hug
What are you doing
Well I
I’m thinking about life
Well wait wait
Well
Let’s chat
Make it quick
Don’t delay me to sleep
Well
Thank you
No  no
I didn’t mean it
I’m not thanking you
to allow me go back to the team
I was not willing to come back
If It is not Mr. Luo
What do you want to say on earth
I heard that
You help a lot secretly
about Zhaoyang’s issue
So thank you to fight for justice
and sacrifice your interest
Sacrifice my interest
No
I just want to apologize
I misunderstood you before
I thought
You are the same with Zhaoyang
So
You admit that you're blind
You are blind
But
It doesn’t mean I reconcile with you
Do you understand
That's another thing
After all brother Kong left
because of you
I will never forgive you
because of this
You know
In the future
we still mind our own business
You
It’s for you
Thank you
LuYiyi
You see
On account of your article
Now the whole magazine
is busy again
What should I say to you
Sor  sorr
Sorry for what
Master Ren
Well LuYiyi
works in your place  right
Yes yes
The script this time
is written by her  right
Yes yes yes
It’s LuYiyi again
Well I think
the script is great
We have decided to
ppropriate more funds for you
It’s more convenient for you
to make inverstigation
Really
Okay okay okay
We must pay attention
we must
Okay okay
Goodbye Master Ren  Okay
Chief Shi
It’s all my fault
I’m willing to take responsibility
You want to take
How to do it
I
Well
You brought the trouble
and now you want to just go away
Then who copes with this disaster
Well then you want
Just now
Master Ren
especially praised your article
and said in this industry
it has aroused consistent praise
asked us to hurry up
In the next issue
we will make a cover story
Besides
The bloc will appropriate
some funds to us
for interview in specialty
go to the scene
Really
Thanks  Chief Shi
Well  Take this
If there was not you
Our magazine
might be like this
and has nothing to do
When we can’t run it a few years later
It will be closed
The future of the magazine
depends on you
Don't worry Chief
The future is up to us
We will work hard
Come on
What are you dong
That team fight in
Eight minutes and forty-five seconds
There were three seriously injured in the opposite team
Your condition
and position were great
Why didn’t you chase
They entered the tower
I would have died if I crossed the tower.
Are you a wimp
For me
It is just a job
Why are you so serious
Yes
Why so serious
You have played basketball with me for half a month
you never scored a goal
You are the captain
I can only stay with you if you want to play
I overestimated you
Do you really think
I can’t win
I know that
In a competition
you didn’t follow the command
crossed the tower to kill enemies
and lost the game in the end
You were kicked out by the team
Later you changed four teams
There’s no team
allowing you to hit the mid
I can’t do it
can’t do it anymore
The chance is right in front of you
It depends on whether you choose to seize
Hello everyone
I‘m the host today
Luotian
Hello everyone
I'm the host today
Acan
After a short rest period
The 2018
Peak Fall Regular Season
comes as scheduled
In this competition
Our strong teams
will gather again
They are destined
to experience
very fierce fighting
The Regular Season
will continue to use the point system
The top four
will enter the playoff
to compete
The team that win the championship
will directly get
the tickets to
Vancouver Global Finals
Is everyone
already looking forward to it
Let’s have two teams
with opener
The glorious
Polaris Team
and
Never Give-up
Legend Team
Welcome
Let’s cut the crap
We announce that
the game officially starts
Next
Our first round-robin match
will fight against the Polaris Team
Tell me
your ideas about it
Old rules
Four guarantees one
I hit the mid
It’s both safe and secure
The Legend is four guarantees one just now
and they win
Tongwu What’s your opinion
I  I have no opinion
What about Lusheng
I wang to hear from the captain first
His strategy
We haven’t practiced for a month
No need to hear
I will not lose face on the stage
I think we should focus on
the choice of heroes when against the Polaris
What's your point
In the early period of Fall Season
Most teams must use
the previous hero system
If we adopt a new
hero combination
They will not be clear about
our tactical intentions
so they will have a conservative strategy
In the early stage we unite and play the sidewalk
when they have support
then push the mid
Qiyue
How is your practice in Axin
Sister Wen
I firmly oppose the use of new heroes
This is Fall Season
not the Test Match
Besides  we're not familiar with the new heroes
Don't
joke about my career
Even if I really
joke about your career
I won’t bet on Weiteng
We must use new heroes
to make new combinations
If we still adopt the old routine
we may not win
You lose because of your poor skills
Captain is right
I think
The advantages of using new heroes as soon as possible
far outweigh the disadvantages
Even in this round
the Polaris doesn’t choose new heroes
It’s very hard to assure
that other teams won’t choose next round
If this is the case
we lose from the start
Why you have
so much bullshit recently
Mind your own business
If you’re afraid to use Axin
to hit the mid
Say it and let me play
What do you mean
Alright
Sit down
Qiyue
The advantages of choosing new heroes as soon as possible
indeed outweigh the disadvantages
This time
We perform training
according to Xiangkong's plan
Well now
You unite against me
Right
Sister Wen
You are a professional coach
The strategy is a shit
Can’t you judge it
Are you really willing to
see Weiteng lose face on the stage
Mind your manners
Qiyue
It is not your game
and please practice your
new hero first
Then come talk to me
about the issue of shame
Remember
You are a professional player
Dismiss
Captain
We’re about to go trianing
Thanks
You’re welcome bro
Shuwen
Take it easy
I will urge Qiyue to practice
Now I get it
In Weiteng
He only listens to you
Qiyue was a bit too much just now
But don’t you think
You believe
JiXiangkong too much
I’ve been working with you for ages
Don’t you understand my style
I'm the person
that have no doubt about my choice
But it’s too risky this time
It’s not our style
Well  sorry
Now it is
Shuwen
From now on
Weiteng
gives up conservative to win
This is also what I hope
Shuwen
I’m about to work
Sleep early
We have first round tomorrow morning
Few more minutes
It’s the first round after all
Don’t push yourself too hard
No one will blame you if you lose
Sleep
Condition is the most important
Okay
Thank you
What for
The game is not
your own issue
Sleep well
Goodnight
Hello  everyone
I’m your old friend
Luotian
Hello everyone
I’m your old friend
Acan
The upcoming game is
Weiteng versus Polaris
The team Weiteng
has experienced
major personnel changes
Their main player changes from Mid Peixi
to
JiXiangkong
We will see whether
Weiteng collapses
due to Peixi's departure
or
gains a new life
because of the joining of battlefield fraud
Let us
wait and see
Welcome the two teams
Welcome
Our audiences are very passionate
I will cut the crap
Next our game
starts
Great
Please have a seat
Fat cat
Which side do you think can win
Hard to say
It depends on which hero they choose
I think
JiXiangkong will win
Because his strategy is mysterious and flexible
It’s very rare in this coterie
That might not be
Wait and see
Peixi
Now the two teams have reached
the selection stage
Let us see
everyone's choice
Okay  let us have a look
In Weiteng
Qiyue
chooses Axin
It’s different
from his previous habit
Yes
He is less likely to choose
Lose
How come
It’s just the beginning
What he says will not be wrong
Wait and see
Make everyone's eyes brightened
Don’t you have a game later on
Why don’t you go to get prepared
I am preparing
Lusheng  don’t be so brave
Hold back  don’t fight against them
Okay  okay
Shenyue  go to the mid to support Qiyue
There are two people opposite
I obstruct them
Hurry up  Shenyue
Okay
Qiyue watch out your view field
Shenyue
Why don’t you come quickly
Sorry brother Qi
Now the Polaris
begins to push the crystal
Finally the Polaris
pushes Weiteng's crystal away
Excellent
Let’s congratulate the Polaris
win the first game
of Regular Season
Congratulate again
So fast  so fast  this round
I think  this game is
beyond out expectations
It’s too short
Yes  it seems that everyone
hasn’t enjoyed it enough
and it’s over
Now you are satisfied
Hope next round
Weiteng can adjust the state
and be able to
bring a better game
to audiences
Just the first round
But Peixi
won the first round
Go away  none of your business
Yeah
JiXiangkong doesn’t
care about losing this round
What do you mean
I’m leaving
Wait and see
my two winning streak
Peixi
Fighting
Brother Qi
Take it esay
Are you alright  Brother Kong
I’m good
Just lost a game
It’s your turn later
Fighting
Xiangkong
Play hard
We’re waiting for you to win
You have my word
Peixi
Well done in the season
Thanks Sister Wen
Fighting
Let’s go
Come on
A game can’t explain everything
I believe in you
Don’t worry
What happened
Lose again
What’s going on in Weiteng today
After the new season begins
Lose four games in series
They were runners-up last year
Yeah
If they lose again like this
There’s basically no hope
to enter the playoff
Brother Sun
What’s going to in Weiteng
Lose four games continuously
What the hell
Mind your own business
No  Brother Sun
Well
JiXiangkong
You are hand-damaged and brain-damaged
Lose four games in series
Because of your rubbish arrangement
Do you really think
I dare not beat you
What are you doing
Can fight solve the problem
JiXiangkong
We have
lost four games
We’re last one in the standings
If we lose again
We have no possibility
of promotion
Should you give
a reasonable explanation to everyone
It might not be a bad thing
to lose a few games
I made a survey
Our new arrangement
Everyone’s statistics
has increased substantially
Tongwu's
data  data  data
They are useless
We still lose the game
Just because of you
Everyone is not
in the most suitable position
It requires early development in the middle road
Then cause great damage in the late stage
But you
always wander and catch people in the early stage
You’re not suitable for mid position at all
So next round
I will transfer Lusheng to mid position
In the meantime
restart bimonthly group
What
Bimonthly group
Are you kidding
I tell you again
Don’t come up with bad ideas
without skills
Who doesn’t know
that out bimonthly group has been cracked
What I mean is new bimonthly group
You use the new hero to jungle
Shenyue supports you to invade
the enemy field
Lusheng is in the mid
push enemy to join
Meanwhile
The bimonthly winds back to mid
to harvest
This four minutes
We will take a huge advantage
I think you
take it for granted
But I think this strategy
is smart
It is indeed a risky strategy
but this skill
is more suitable for our player
Before Peixi entered Weiteng
This group has always been
our magic weapon
Qiyue
I have faith in
your skills
And this time
we add new hero strategy
I agree to restart this group
Sister Wen
Even so
Do you really think Lushen can play mid
I can
The game is coming
change the positions suddenly
adopt new strategy
I’m afraid it’s too risky
Boss
No one
knows Legend better than me
and no one
knows Peixi better than you
Do you really think
we have no chance to win
Don’t say too much
If we lose
You can afford it
I give up this position
Is it okay to let Lusheng play mid
Besides
The bimonthly group  we
Ligan
I know what you are worried about
but now it’s the key moment
As two leaders
We have to give our players
more confidence
But Shuwen
We can’t lose anymore
If we lose again
the whole effort of half the year
will all be wasted
We have nothing to lose
We have overcome
all the difficulties
Just a Regualr Season
You have no faith
I just don’t understand
Where do you get the faith
towards JiXiangkong
Just because
SunZeyi focuses on him
What do you mean
Nothing
I’m just worried
If you have decided
Then follow
your plan
I’m coming home
You should come home early