[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 35]
Boss.
I'm at the venue.
Film your surroundings.
I want to see the venue.
Boss, look.
There are so many people.
Wow, looks crowded.
Lu Yi Yi, listen up.
Do a good interview.
Don't just focus on
cheering for your boyfriend.
Don't worry, Boss.
We will definitely have the best news!
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Welcome to the final match
of the ICONQUER Championships!
Quick! The match has began!
Coming..
I'm glad to be here
with you again.
I asked a friend I'm going to invite on stage.
She is from China.
Please everybody give a big hand.
Qiuying!
This competition..
Qiuying is the narrator
and host for this competition.
Hi to all fans, nice to meet you!
I'm the host tonight.
Qiuying!
Our daughter is the first female narrator
in history on the ICONQUER Championships.
Really?
Are you guys ready?
All ready!
Let's go.
Let's go!
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Welcome onto stage, Team..
Tatan!
Welcome Team Tatan!
Being the champion team last year,
Team Tatan is totally invincible.
They have never been defeated before.
They have won numerous championships.
They are.. Tatan!
Next up on stage,
they are a team from China..
Team Phenix!
Phenix is a newly formed team.
Despite suspicions and mockings,
they have fearlessly battled their way
to the final match.
They are..
Team Phenix!
It's time to ask Tatan
how they are feeling in this moment.
Hey losers!
You guys are definitely going to lose this!
I'd like to ask the Captain, Ji Xiang Kong,
what do you have to say?
I have nothing more to say.
The champion goes to us.
China Number 1!
Never say die! Rebirth with burning passion!
Thank you, Ji Xiang Kong.
But..
The harsh reality of
there will only be one champion!
Absolutely.
I think it's time now
to start the final match.
Ladies and Gentlemen, let the final game begins.
The competition officially starts.
Ready?
Don't be nervous.
Hi Ladies and Gentlemen.
I'm the Chinese narrator of 2019 ICONQUER Championship.
Your old pal, Luo Tian.
Hi everyone!
I'm the new narrator, Qiu Ying.
This time, we have invited
a special guest.
He is the ex-Captain of Legends.
King of E-gaming, Gu Fang.
Hi everyone!
This year, you're back to the stage you're familiar of.
Do you feel different from last year?
This is the first time I'm attending this competition as a narrator.
Compared to sitting in the see-through room there,
sitting outside,
I'm able to feel a stronger ambience.
Phenix is the continuation of my dream.
I hope
they are able to win the championship
to bring glory to China
and enhance the charm of e-gaming.
Xiang Kong, which players should we select?
Make your selections.
I'll be the last.
To surprise them.
Such an important competition..
Using Global Strike,
isn't this strategy too common?
Because this tactic is too common,
Tatans will not be able to predict Phenix's intentions.
Spiritual Princess.
Spiritual Princess?
Gu Fang.
Isn't this your hero icon?
Seems like Phenix is trying to salute to their former Captain here.
Our former Captain..
should be tearing by now.
Spiritual Princess.
She used to bring honour to me.
I hope Spiritual Princess
will bring better luck to Phenix today.
The return of Spritual Princess!
Jeffery must be surprised to see us
using Spiritual Princess.
Spiritual Princess?
Ji Xiang Kong is a solo dub player.
Why is he picking a solo mid?
Is he trying to use shadow tactics in his lineup?
Shit! What are they thinking?
So what are we going to do?
We can beat him with our secret weapon.
Let's see what Ji Xiang Kong has first.
Come on guys!
Come on! We can do it!
C'mon!
Let's do this!
C'mon guys, know what to do right?
I'm coming..
Retreat. It's time to retreat.
Nice shot!
Guys, go go go!
How is it, Ze Yi?
Can I come with you?
Come..
I've surrounded one.
Wait for me.
Ji Xiang Kong and Pei Xi are attacking solely.
This is effective during the early game.
Attacking solely?
I can't understand Phenix's strategy.
We can see that..
They don't seem nervous at all.
Pei Xi appeared out of the blue!
Steadily.
Ji Xiang Kong was nowhere to seen.
Tatan seem confused about their strategy.
Cyborg and Mogora attacked at the same time,
Trying to attack Ji Xiang Kong.
Not an issue.
Don't forget.
Sun Ze Yi is nearby.
He is here!
Sun Ze Yi used his 2nd-degree attack,
Divine power.
He managed to protect Ji Xiang Kong
from Cyborg and Mogora's attack.
His swift reaction..
doesn't seem like a newbie.
Sun Ze Yi's reacted fast.
They are fighting back!
Xiang Kong, praise me.
Ze Yi, you're still as good.
Sun Ze Yi blocked Cyborg and Mogora.
Ji Xiang Kong and Sun Ze Yi attack Cyborg together with their strongest skill.
Bravo!
Nice!
Nice shot!
Just keep going! Guys!
Come on!
Jeffery intercepts the tower
but was attacked by Ji Xiang Kong.
Awesome!
Jeffery wanted to escape
but it was too late
Xia Ling double-attacks!
You're dead, Jeffery.
Nice shot!
There is a price to pay for intercepting the tower.
Jeffrey has no idea what Phenix's tactic is.
But Phenix is simply using
the most common tactic, Global storm.
As the saying goes,
the onlooker sees a clearer picture.
Boys, I don't think we can win this one.
What do..
Alright.. This is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna pretend to lose to them.
What?
Just do it as I say!
Trust me.
Okay..
Retreat..
Pei Xi and Xia Ling defeated Jeffery effortlessly.
Phenix's vision has been set.
Is Ji Xiang Kong trying to lure the opponent?
But it is an obvious trap.
Will Jeffery fall into it?
I think Jeffrey is having a mental breakdown.
Jeffrey tried to kill Ji Xiang Kong in one attack,
But Ji Xiang Kong escaped.
Am I seeing things?
Did Ji Xiang Kong expect that move from Jeffrey?
What is Ji Xiang Kong doing?
If it was me, I'd have won.
Stop being a showoff.
Just as the Tatans gathered,
with Ji Xiang Kong's strongest attack
all of them were suppressed.
With another attack,
it controlled Musk, Jeffery
and killed Mogora!
The rest of Phenix appeared out of the blue.
Xia Ling attacked first
using his first and secondary attacks.
Jeffery was dragged away!
No Tatans remaining.
Phenix elevated up.
Nice shot!
Phenix took down the jewel!
Nice! Good shot!
Nice shot!
Xiang Kong won!
Pretend yeah.
Congratulations, Phenix!
For winning the first round!
It is 1 versus 0 now.
Come on.
Why are they acting this way?
What's going on?
No matter what are they up to,
we won the first round.
We're a step closer now.
Let's talk inside.
Well done guys!
Awesome!
What's going on?
Phenix is a formidable team.
What's wrong, President Jin?
Now..
I'm regretting for what that has happened.
If Xiang Kong didn't leave us,
the team on stage today will be Legends.
It's alright, President Jin.
We will do well the next round.
Sister Wen.
What's the matter?
Despite winning the first round,
what are those gloomy faces for?
Sit down.
Though we have won the first round,
Tatan's tactics earlier
are what I've not seen before.
Despite our victory,
it was partly based on luck.
Xiang Kong,
next round..
Shall we use the shadow tactics?
Yeah.
Since you guys made your way to the finals with shadow tactics,
it will definitely work.
At this crucial moment,
don't let your guards down.
We're fighting against
the champion team last year.
No mistakes allowed.
Believe in us.
We will not make any mistakes.
Take it easy.
I...
I will avenge this for Legends.
Looking good, guys.
Hey, Ji Xiang Kong!
Your team is left with the shadow tactics right?
We're really looking forward to it.
Alright, guys. Go!
Look at Jeffery's attitude.
What is up in his sleeves?
Could they have the solution to break the shadow tactics?
Shadow tactics
is not easy to deal with.
We're left with this match to go.
Come on, we can do this!
Welcome back to the competition.
Now,
the second round will begin.
In the first round,
Phenix defeated Tatan with 'Global Storm' tactic.
Phenix is leading.
Judging from the lineup,
seems like Phenix is planning
to use the shadow tactics.
Oh man! Losers!
I knew they got nothing else but stupid shadow.
Alright boys!
Stick to the original plan.
It's bulletproof.
They are using back the previous lineup.
Maybe they're too lazy to change.
I doubt so.
I don't know what are they up to either.
Play with caution.
Let's try not to attack during the early game.
Okay.
Alright.
Tatan chose the exact lineup
as the previous round.
They don't seem to have any breakthrough.
Or maybe..
is he overconfident with this lineup?
I think Tatan will change their gaming tactic.
In terms of vision,
this lineup is pretty strong
to control the shadow tactic.
Top laner, vanish.
Bottom laner, vanish.
Careful, mid laner.
I'm blocked here.
Can you retreat?
Xia Ling, I'm coming to support you.
Let's switch positions.
Retreat.
Don't attack first.
Tatan multipled their substitutes.
Whenever Phenix tried to attack,
Tatan managed to avoid it.
Tatan's defense is getting tight.
Tatan prevented Phenix's mid-laner
from moving.
They are changing their positions too quickly.
Be careful.
They kept changing positions.
My shots were all missed.
That's too much.
Quad switch?
Since when did Tatan switch positions?
They have broke the shadow tactic.
Jeffrey has became the mid laner.
Besides that,
Tatan's support player has switched his position too.
Tatan isn't using the same shadow tactic.
Accurately speaking,
Tatan is using duo-shadow tactic.
Quad switching positions.
They are being fully surrounded.
Phenix has no way to attack.
I didn't expect them to use the duo-shadow tactic.
3 of them are attacking me.
I can't escape.
Oh! Nice.
Alright, let's go to the other one, guys!
This is gonna be easy.
He is waiting for us.
Second killed! Three killed!
Nice! One tower down!
Oh yeah!
Five killed!
Phenix go!
Nice!
Tatan has defeated Phenix!
Jeffrey's economy shot up!
There is no way for Phenix to attack.
What's wrong, Ji Xiang Kong?
Unexpected, right?
Shadow tactic..
We have resolved it long ago.
Judging from the current situation,
shadow tactic is not going to work anymore.
The first round.
We lost it deliberately.
Xiang Kong,
what should we do?
Abandon the top lane.
Fight the dragon.
Kill the dragon! Quick.
Fighting the dragon is our last chance.
Come..
Everyone fight the dragon with me.
I'm coming..
Since the second round has begun,
Phenix has been on the losing end.
They're trying to look for a way to breakthrough.
Phenix is heading towards the dragon!
Tatan has planted vision at that area.
To get rid of the dragon,
be careful, Phenix!
Tatan is attacking our tower.
Ignore them.
Let them be.
Xiang Kong, what about our highland?
Ze Yi,
guard the top-lane.
- Pei Xi, you too. - Okay.
Go! Go!
The dragon is left with..
One-third life span.
Lin Yi Xi saw two Tatans nearing the dungeon.
He tried to divert their attention
while his teammates fight the dragon.
But the Tatans avoided him
and dashed straight into the dungeon.
Ignore them.
Keep attacking the dragon!
Its life span is critically low.
I will attack the Tatans.
Xia Ling, what are you doing?
Come back. Fight the dragon!
It is almost dying.
The dragon is dying, Xia Ling!
Kill the dragon!
Lin Yi Xuan, what are you doing?
Kill the dragon! Come back!
No.. I can't go.
Retreat!
Go!
Blue, help me.
The Tatans dashed into the dungeon.
Ji Xiang Kong is critically injured!
Wow! Ji Xiang Kong was killed!
Xia Ling was killed!
Why didn't you listen to my orders?
Congratulations, Tatan.
For winning this round.
The current score is..
1 versus 1. Fair match.
After the 10 minutes break,
let's welcome the final crucial round.
Stay tuned!
Stay.
Give them some time to cool down.
There is still chance.
I'm going to see Xiang Kong.
What tactic are we using for the final round?
From Tatan's playing tactic,
it's clear that they have studied us thoroughly.
If they're able to break the shadow tactic,
they're able to break all our tactics.
So..
What should we do?
I'm sorry.
I've no idea too.
Captain..
Xiang Kong.
Don't stress yourself too much.
I need a breather outside.
Sun, I..
Xiang Kong.
Miya.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see your game.
When I was watching you earlier,
while listening to Qiuying's narration,
I realised..
she knows you better.
She understands you better than I do.
We..
We have really lost too much time.
And my eyes..
You knew that my eyes have recovered, right?
The recovery of your eyes..
To me..
It's the best thing to hear.
Though it is a draw now,
this must have been quite a huge blow to Phenix.
If Phenix is keeping up with this dampened spirit,
it is a bad sign.
Perhaps,
it might do good
if someone could enlighten them.
Me?
With Sister Shu Wen around, I think..
Qiu Ying..
It's not just about Ji Xiang Kong and the rest.
It applies to you.
10 minutes break.
Be back before the final match starts.
Go.
Then..
Thanks, Teacher Luo.
Xiang Kong, I'm sorry.
I was too selfish.
To stop you from leaving me,
I've made used of you.
I must have hurt Qiu Ying too.
Please apologise to her on my behalf.
I hope it's not too late.
I have never given up on Qiu Ying.
When the match ends,
I will make things clear with her.
I sincerely wish all the best to the both you.
Qiu Ying!
Xiang Kong!
Leave this after the competition.
The game is starting.
Xiang Kong.
Are you ready?
Sorry, guys.
For the final round,
I can't think of any tactic.
This competition..
It isn't just about us.
But all e-gamers in China.
We must fulfil everyone's dream
on behalf of all of them.
This.
Guys.
It's time for us to show the best of us!
Welcome back!
Let's give a big hand
to welcome Phenix back on stage.
I'm 30 this year.
I've passed the prime period of an e-gamer.
I thought
I wouldn't be able to do crazy things anymore.
To be able to return to the stage I yearned,
to prove that I'm not a failure,
it's more than satisfaction.
I've said before..
My biggest dream in my life
is to compete the competition with you.
I have fulfilled my dream.
Captain.
It's only been 6 months as an e-gamer.
Yet I'm entering the International Championship.
I'm even competing with my idol!
There is nothing more left to regret.
My biggest dream is
having a united team to fight the game with.
My dream has been fulfilled today.
Let's enjoy it till the end.
I was doubted.
I wasn't a gifted e-gamer.
Thanks to you guys for believing me in this.
The match we have lost a year ago..
Captain left the team.
You guys have never left me when I was down.
This time, our opponent team is invincibly strong.
At this point of time,
countless attention are focused on this stage.
I don't want to lose this.
Our Champion dream.
Let's make our dreams come true!
Right now,
Phenix is standing on stage.
Why are they on stage? Phenix!
Hang on.
What are they doing?
Blazers.
Legends.
VNG's badges.
They are pinning the teams' badges on their jackets.
I think..
They are not competing
for themselves.
Actually Phenix is formed by
a combination of VNG, Legends and Blazers.
They carried the dreams of 2 generations.
The best moment of China gaming history.
Stand up.
No matter what,
we still got to defeat them all.
Stay focus.
Let's choose our best individual players.
Alright guys. Are we ready for this?
Yes!
Do it!
Phenix, all the best!
We can hear the audience cheering for Phenix.
According to the statistics,
Stone beast.
Dictator.
Ah Xin.
Chariot.
Jin Can.
The heros Tatan won the most battles with.
But the heros Phenix chose
are comparatively weaker in stats.
If Tatan play like how they did earlier,
it is going to be a tough war for Phenix.
I believe..
This final round is going to be exciting.
Lin Yi Xuan, loiter outside.
Okay..
Be the spy.
I'll be the spy..
Gather.
Things don't seem good for Phenix.
Tatan are surrounding behind them.
Phenix attacked first
by controlling Jeffrey.
If they managed to get rid of Jeffrey,
it will be easier for them.
Oh dear!
Jeffrey and Knight's trio attack.
Phenix life span is running low.
Xiang Kong, should we retreat?
I will do the lead.
Head to the wild.
Oh okay..
I'll take over the top.
Pei Xi, mid.
Xia Ling, bottom.
Without vision,
it is dangerous for Phenix to fight against Tatan.
Judging from the current situation,
defence is the only way for Phenix.
If Phenix can't think of a way to attack,
it is risky.
Tatan and Phenix's economy stats
differs by 5000 points.
Man count..
It is currently 5 versus 1.
One of Phenix's towers has already been crashed.
At this rate,
Tatan's economy is getting stronger.
Tatan is surrounding us!
I can't move!
Attack the dragon, Xiang Kong!
Tatan is attacking the dragon.
As long as they kill it,
there will probably win this.
Things are getting tougher for Phenix.
Why is Phenix not taking any action?
Is Phenix running out of tactics?
Pei Xi, Xiang Kong, Lin Yi Xuan
all 3 of them were killed.
They are acting too rashly.
Tatan is moving together.
Phenix is lacking too far off.
It's best for Phenix to retreat and not attack.
Or things may go out of hand.
Something is wrong with Phenix.
Is anything wrong over there?
Don't give up!
Are you letting down those who trusted you?
Xiang Kong, can you think of a solution?
I want to win! I don't want to lose!
Keep quiet! Let me think!
Is Phenix giving up?
If Tatan were to kill the dragon,
Phenix is gonna lose this.
The dragon has been killed by Tatan.
Xiang Kong, what should we do?
Defend our territory.
Forget about the tower.
Phenix's tower has been demolished.
Tatan is getting ready for their last attack.
Give me five!
Oh! I wanna see their faces.
Phenix is not a team that gives up easily.
Believe that Ji Xiang Kong will come up with a new tactic.
Ji Xiang Kong, you can do it!
Phenix, you can do it!
Why are you using this weapon?
The flaming rod. It looks stunning!
It is only effective during multiple attacks.
At least 3 consecutive times.
Ji Xiang Kong!
You will definitely get the
International Championship!
I've got an idea!
Xia Ling, Pei Xi. Sell all the weapons.
Use the flame rod.
What's the use of using that rod?
It has self-damaging effect.
Ze Yi,
are we really using the flaming rod?
Let's believe in Xiang Kong.
The flaming rod has effects of multiple damages.
We have no other way now.
Go ahead!
These guys never give up easily.
There should be a way.
Believe in them.
Hang on.. Pei Xi?
What is Pei Xi doing?
He..
Why is selling all his weapons?
Xia Ling too!
They are selling all their weapons.
Are they giving up?
Flaming rod?
Pei Xi and Xia Ling
are both using the flaming rod!
This is the lowest cost-performance weapon.
You like fireworks?
All girls love it.
Whenever I watch fireworks,
it feels like..
my world is lit up.
I will win the International Championship!
I'm ready.
Change the highland to mid lane.
We can see that Tatan is surrounded by Phenix.
Sun Ze Yi hides at a secluded corner.
Jeffrey stood on highland.
Phenix's vision has been blocked.
Finding a chance..
Blind ditch.
Sun Ze Yi grabbed Jeffrey up to the highland.
Attack!
I caught hold of it! Attack!
Nice shot!
Nice shot! Sun Ze Yi!
The rest of them are here!
Hang on..
Don't attack first.
Hold it.
What should I do?
Their attacks are too strong.
Retreat for awhile.
I'm attacking first!
Peixi!
Jeffrey's stats is critically low.
Peixi lit up the first flaming rod.
PeiXi! Pei Xi appeared!
He blocked a crucial attack in front of Sun Ze Yi.
Pei Xi's life span is running low too.
1 protecting 4.
Pei Xi is sacrificing himself
to buy time for his team.
Jeffrey has collapsed.
Before collapsing, Pei Xi lit up the first flaming rod attack.
Pei Xi! Well done!
What?
Tatan's support has joined in as well.
Jeffrey wasn't knocked off yet.
Are they planning to avenge?
Xia Ling and Lin Yi Xuan
joined forces too.
Lin Yi Xuan is helping Xia Ling.
Xia Ling! The second flaming rod!
I'm about to!
God! Damn it! What just happened?
Flaming rod?
Xia Ling attacked with the second flaming rod!
It has brought down Jeffrey!
God of Axe dashed towards Ji Xiang Kong.
As he was going to attack him..
Sun Ze Yi dragged God of Axe towards him.
Sun Ze Yi held down God of Axe!
Ji Xiang Kong attacked along the way
towards the fountain..
He.. He is selling off his weapons!
Flaming rod!
Ji Xiang Kong has purchased a flaming rod too!
I can't handle this anymore.
Xiang Kong! Quick! Attack!
Time's up! Attack!
Lighting up the third flaming rod..
Ji Xiang Kong attacked!
It was indeed a fatal blow!
No one can handle that blow!
Awesome! Xiang Kong! Good job!
Three killed! Nice!
C'mon guys!
Ji Xiang Kong
killed three Tatans in one attack!
Three killed!
Before Tatan's support blacked out,
in a leap,
he killed Ji Xiang Kong!
Lin Yi Xuan has been killed too!
Sun Ze Yi has killed God of Axe!
Phenix is left with one player.
Smash the jewel! Quick!
Phenix's army isn't looking good.
Sun Ze Yi decided to attack Tatan's army.
Attack at one blow!
I can do it!
Sun Ze Yi crushed Tatan's highland.
Tatan couldn't purchase any weapons now.
Attack! One shot!
Attack them!
Phenix is an unbelievable team!
If they lack in chemistry,
how can they be able to accomplish this?
Sun Ze Yi is getting nearer to Tatan's jewel.
But Tatan's army is in the midst of cracking Phenix's jewel.
Quick! Crack the jewel!
Push! Push it!
I'm pushing it!
Sun Ze Yi!
No...
Nice shot! Crush the tower!
Crush it!
Crush it through!
Will Tatan's army or Sun Ze Yi crush the jewel faster?
Crush it!
Tatan's jewel stats balance is 75.
Phenix's jewel stats balance is 35.
No!
Crush it!
Phenix, go for it!
No!!
Champion!
Phenix!
See you next year.
Never say die! Rebirth with burning passion!
Victory!
What a bunch of amazing guys!
Congratulations!
Everybody! They are 2019 Champion team.
Phenix!
I've grew along with Phenix.
From being unknown,
to criticsms,
through ups and downs,
they revived.
How tough has it been of them.
They are the only ones who know.
Phenix is a perfect team.
They proved themselves with their capabilities.
In honour to China!
They made us proud!
They brought honour to the world!
They are ICONQUER's pride!
China's pride!
Never say die! Rebirth with burning passion!
Congratulations!
Ji Xiang Kong,
as a Captain of Phenix,
what you would like to say?
I want to say..
This trophy doesn't solely belong to the 5 of us.
I want to thank
all those who stayed with us
during our toughest times.
Without their support,
we wouldn't have come this far.
They are here today.
I'd like to invite them on stage
to receive the trophy with us!
They are Team Blazers!
Welcome them!
Congratulations to champions!
Allow them to enjoy this moment!
Besides that,
there is one person I'd like to thank.
Without her,
I wouldn't have make it here.
I've promised her.
I'd bring her to ICONQUER finals.
Oh my god!
What a moment on stage here!
What a special moment!
Absolutely amazing!
Everybody!
The champions!
Feels awkward when everyone is on holiday.
Yeah.
It feels like a dream.
I still remember when I gave you the key,
it felt like yesterday.
Captain, thank you.
This ring..
shall return back to its owner.
is to thank you for your support to Phenix.
Captain.
I promised you.
To win the 2nd Championship ring.
I've finally did it.
I'm not the one you should be thanking.
But your old self.
Be thankful to your old self
for not giving up.
These two rings
neither belong to you
nor me,
they signify China's glory in ICONQUER
this isn't the end,
but a continuation.
We should leave the rings here
for the future teams to continue this glory.
Be careful.
It's so high up here!
Is this where you want to bring me?
But..
Besides its unique height here,
what else is unique?
Close your eyes. You will find out.
Why?
Just close your eyes!
3, 2, 1!
Open your eyes!