[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 32]
This Xia Ling
hasn't talk to us
since yesterday.
Not sure how did his
rehabilitation go.
We should think of
a solution to cheer him up.
I hate these bunch of people
scolding Brother Kong
and Xia Ling online.
Take a look at Pei Xi's Weibo.
Xia Ling is a rookie
and also a brave person.
We're at where we're now,
we won't back away.
The five of us
are inseparable.
but we'll never yield
during competition.
This Pei Xi
usually pulls a long face
but at crucial moment, he's pretty nice.
Indeed.
Yes.
He don't even use on Weibo.
He specially opened
an account for Xia Ling.
Have to make a response.
Repost,
Changing of position is agreed by
all members after discussion,
everyone please respect
Phoenix's tactic choice.
Everyone, please
give us some more time.
Xia Ling,
stop right there.
Are you
defeat just because of a match?
No need for you to care.
All of us believe in you,
why can't you
believe in yourself?
I don't want to be a burden.
From the day you entered the team,
you're already a burden to us.
How did you play when I gave the
middle position to you?
Is this how you treat me?
Is this how you treat the whole team?
Pei Xi...
Trash!
Pei Xi, are you insane?
What are you doing?
Don't you help him.
-He's just a trash.          -Get up.
A trash that
doesn't dare to even stand.
Shut up.
What are you blabbering about?
And you Qiu Ying,
you understand Iconquer?
You don't even know what Iconquer is.
I really don't know
how you become a commentator.
You're nothing to your name today
if it's not for Ji Xiang Kong.
You're trash. He's a trash.
Trash.
Pei Xi, you're too much.
Pei Xi, shut up!
Xia Ling, you're
standing now.
We're back.
Leg... you don't need the clutches anymore.
No, Pei Xi...
He's leg is okay.
What happened to your face?
Kid doesn't know well.
I saw all the Weibo
post you guys posted.
I can't be defeated
so easily.
Nice one, lad.
You get back pretty quickly.
Ah Xuan, let's play for a round.
Call Brother Xuan.
With you being like that,
you're not even any mature.
Still ask him to call you Brother.
You guys are bullies.
Okay, shalln't play with you.
-Who's this?         -Brother Xia Tian.
Pei Xi.
Captain, what brings you here?
Thanks, Brother.
Don't say thank you anymore,
I'll be scared if you say it again.
Xiang Kong, I'm sorry.
Why did you say sorry suddenly?
We shouldn't have asked you to give up
on Shadow just because of that match
and even question your own teammates.
I know,
you did it with us
in consideration.
Okay, enough said.
Let's start quickly.
Let me feel
your tactic, Shadow.
Anyhow, we took the
championship before.
Although you guys are young,
but we
will not show mercy.
Haven't been practicing in a while,
I don't know if I'm rusty now.
You definitely are.
Fellow Masters,
are you going to practice with us?
Let me tell you, it's all Pei Xi's fault.
You lad,
said you will treat me to a meal.
He asked me to come for training
on the first meal he treat.
Nice.
Able to gather the 5 Masters here,
steady.
It's just a matter of a meal.
Okay,
let's see if these bunch of old people
are still as good as before.
Saying if you aren't old.
You... Aren't you
lack of one person?
It can be settled with adding the computer.
Add the computer?
We play despite 4 vs 5.
Let Qiu Ying to go over.
Come.
Who's that?
Who is that?
Oh god, Li Shao Feng.
Xiang Kong, he's
the first man of China for E-sports.
That Li Shao Feng?
He's the first man
from China to stand at the
top of the world with the China flag
for consecutive 2 years.
The first man from China to win
the championship for E-sports,
-Li Shao Feng.          -Oh god.
Afraid now?
Am I dreaming?
Pinch me.
An introduction.
Li Shao Feng, my good friend of many years.
Recently, setting up a business
specialising in E-sports equipments.
It's not easy to ask him out.
I specially asked him out to
give you special trainings.
No, captain.
Why did you not
tell me before?
I can't possibly
tell you everything.
Why?
Seems like I'm not invited,
I'll get going first.
No.
Xiang Kong quick, introduce yourself.
Hello, Brother Shao Feng.
I'm Ji Xiang Kong,
captain of Phoenix.
We're just too shock,
didn't expect you to be here.
Ji Xiang Kong,
Gu Fang mentioned you to me before.
The legendary Master of Deception.
I came today
to see how good
you really is.
Don't,
you're too flattering.
You're then our senior,
we should be learning from you.
Then...
Brother Shao Feng...
Another handshake.
I'm blessed now.
We... We all watched you
since we're young...
grew up watching you compete, then...
You're the idol of
every E-sports player.
It's really my pleasure to be able to train with you,
I'm really agitated now.
Lin Yi Xuan.
You know me?
Yes, I know you're the
support with this look of yours.
Look, my idol knows me.
Of course, not just you.
There's
Pei Xi, Xia Ling and Lao Sun.
You guys are the dark horse
that came out of nowhere this year.
It's difficult to not know you guys.
It was then when I saw you getting
the championship
when I decided
to do this as my career.
I... I'm also a fan of you.
Xia Ling, you're my fan.
Is your phone with you?
Enough, go.
Okay.
Talk about signatures
and photos later.
Now, use your time for the competition.
Come, training.
Let's start.
Welcome!
Can you even do it since you
only do commentary now?
What if you're rusty...
Better than you okay?
Be careful, go.
Xia Tian, you don't have to come over.
Ji Xiang Kong and I
don't have a problem here.
Be careful of Luo Tian.
Teacher Luo still blocked me.
Teacher Luo,
your guess is pretty accurate.
How did you know I'm here?
How can I be a commentator if I don't understand you?
Okay, no problem.
I see Xia Tian.
Can you chase him?
I've waited long enough.
Xia Tian, don't go after him.
Look, look at the who.
Xia Tian is here again.
Save me.
You're an embarassment.
Young kid, not bad.
Are they...
Are they starting a group fight? Quick.
Come, we're here to take revenge.
Still as childish.
Enough of talking, let's start.
Congratulations to Phoenix for winning twice in a row,
successfully leaving the losing group!
They will be up against Wei Teng
next for the championship.
-I let you.            -Not bad.
We're leaving
but really,
thank you all.
If it'snot for your special training,
we wouldn't have
such improvement
in such a shortspan.
We aren't that important.
The greatest statesman
is still yourselves.
Yes, looking at you guys now
reminds me of us then.
Our training evironment then was
worse compared to you,
without sponsers
and encouragement.
It's all based on our passion and faith
for games that
pull us through the matches.
Brother Shao Feng,
do you have any tips
to get the champion?
Better still, get two of it.
Tips?
Actually, training is still the most important.
Target your weakness
and practice continuously.
Practice till you exceed others,
turning your weakness
to your strength.
Other than that,
your understanding and
attitude towards E-sports balance out
every one of your strength
and the teamwork among all of you,
this is a very
important point for your
competition this time,
Indeed.
When we practice back then,
it was really not interesting,
thought of giving up.
Xia Tian and I even
tried escaping once.
So many kids around.
Was it only once?
It was numerous times okay?
Every time I have
catch the both of you back, still have to
give you psychological treatment.
-That's because...           -All his fault.
-No, it's because...          -He's burdensome.
What, I'm burdensome?
You look honesty but you're so evil.
Do you know?
I really envy you guys
to have such
like-minded brothers
to go forward together.
Iconquer is a game for brothers.
As longas the five of you
work hard together,
you guys will be invincible.
Don't worry,
we'll definitely not
let your hopes down.
Allowing China E-sports
to get to the top of the world.
I believe you guys can do it.
The finals is tomorrow,
we'll be waiting to celebrate for you all.
All the best!
What are you all doing?
Brother Qi, don't go over yet.
Top your head.
Push in the middle.
Don't abandon me okay?
Top.
What top? Middle.
Tong Wu come and help me.
Brother Qi, do't go over.
Brother Qi.
Just follow me
wherever I go okay?
And you, don't play anymore.
What are you all doing?
The bunch of you are useless.
Especially you, Tong Wu.
Why didn't you come and help me?
Aren't I asking for death if I were
to just go over?
I'm the captain,
you come when I ask you to.
I'm sorry.
Qi Yue, can you not get physical
even if you're the captain.
What's wrong with scolding him?
Leave if you don't agree.
You're not worthy to be the captain.
What did you say?
I asked you to be careful.
Wei Teng is doom
to have a captain like you.
-Lu Sheng.          -You can't fight, Lu Sheng.
Stop fighting.
I'll expose you if you comtinue fighting.
What are you exposing?
Let me tell you, don't think that nobody
knows what happened in the meeting room.
I saw it,
I saw everything.
Tong Wu!
Tong Wu, don't you run.
Borther Sheng, thank you for just now.
Are you okay?
I knew you'll be hiding here again.
Qi Yue is looking everywhere for you.
What do you mean just now?
Why is Qi Yue so anxious?
What did you see?
Nothing.
Is it regarding leakage of tactic?
I long suspect that he was the one behind it.
He just wants to chase Ji Xiang Kong out.
I saw him record
with my own eyes
at the meeting room
that day.
After the meeting,
he went to meet Qiao Xin.
Why didn't you speak up then?
I don't dare to.
Also, Ji Xiang Kong and Sister Wen has already
left when I wanted to say it out.
Although Ji Xiang Kong has left
but if this incident
is not explained properly,
it will forever be a stain
for his career.
Also Qiu Ying,
she got fired from
Ji Guang because of this.
Tong Wu,
if you still treat Ji Xiang Kong
as a brother,
I think you should step up.
Why are you still hestitating?
You're afraid that Qi Yue will chase you out?
How far do you think the
Wei Teng now is able to go?
I'm not afraid that Qi Yue will chase me out
and I'm also not scared of Qi Yue
but do you know?
I don't have evidence.
Do you think the committee
will believe me even if I step up?
How about
we look for Luo Tian?
He's investigating on this matter.
Why are you hestitating?
I'll go with you.
At most, we'll leave Wei Teng together.
Teacher Luo.
Are the both of you speaking the truth?
Qi Yue really did record
and passed it to Qiao Xin?
I saw it with my own eyes,
at the entrance of the hotel gym.
Let's go to the hotel
and ask for their CCTV,
see if we can get evidence.
Let's go, take my car.
Teacher Luo, you're so busy
yet help us with our special training.
We haven't play
a match in a long time.
This reminds me of
hose days where
we strive here together.
Oh,
there's progression for the
issue of tactic leakage,
the committee
should release the results soon.
Thank you
for always helping me.
I promised you before
that I'll bring you justice,
After the tactic leakage incident
is over,
are you still willing to return to be commentator?
Of course
but now,
Phoenix needs me.
[2019 Spring Tournament Finals]
Return me Pei Xi!
Return me Middle!
Change Xia Ling away.
Return me Pei Xi!
Fellow summoners,
welcome to the venue of 2019
final Iconquer
Spring tournament.
I'm the host for today, Luo Tian.
I'm Ah Can.
Welcome everyone here.
The new dark horse,
Phoenix will be up against
Wei Teng in the Iconquer
final match today.
The winner between
them
is able to get the only ticket
to
the global final competition.
Yes,
Iconquer is finally organizing
a global competition here in China
so I hope
that our China team
is able to gain glory on our own land.
Next, we'll
use our loudest applause
to welcome both teams,
Phoenix and Wei Teng!
Welcome everyone.
Everyone,
I announce the competiiton
officially begins!
Both teams, please have a seat.
Okay,
attack.
Take a look.
The jungle can't go out yet.
Don't be afraid of him,
Ji Xiang Kong only has these two tricks.
This Lu Sheng
can't get a single economy.
-We'll continue to presurize him.          -Okay.
Middle is pretty steady.
Xia Ling, is Xia Ling.
He's operation in the middle
has triple kill instantly.
Xia Ling isn't the rookie
Xia Ling we knew then.
Shen Yue, go.
Take down the overconfident Xia Ling.
-Okay, got it.         -Quick.
I don't know
Where Pei Xi is now.
You guys be careful.
Attack.
Give it to you.
Chase him quickly.
Let us see,
Xia Ling's assist came on time,
Based on his economy now...
Xia Ling, do your kill.
Xia Ling, start your show.
Push, another wave.
Another wave.
I'll tank the turret, don't wait for the minions.
Group fight, Shen Yue attack, quick.
Let us congratulate Phoenix
in winning on the first match!
Congratulations Phoenix!
Young lad,
my Son is competing in there.
Can I enter?
Do you have a ticket?
Bought the tickets?
No, it was sold out long ago.
I gave Ying ZI a call,
she's coming out to fetch us.
Ying Zi!
Here's my working pass.
Dad,
why did you come
come suddenly?
We don't understand while watching it at home
and she's worried about Xia Ling.
Let's go in.
Auntie and Dad,
come in quickly.
Let's go.
-Sorry for troubling you.         -No problem.
That's Xia Ling.
Look,
Xia Ling.
I see him.
Auntie, come over quickly.
Thank you.
Dad, sit.
Both sides of the team are
1 to 1 now.
1 to 1?
Yes, it's the match point now.
Which is Xia Ling?
That, middle, Zhi Heng.
Which?
The one in purple hair,
do you see it?
The one wearing red?
Yes.
That, the one in the middle.
I'm looking.
Don't talk too much,
the competition is about to start.
Be the eyes.
Okay, I'll go now.
You be careful.
Okay.
Top, I'm at the top now.
He has his skill now.
This wave is okay.
There's only 4 of them, go.
Group fight.
Auntie, don't worry.
Xia Ling is only
lacking of 300 coins,
as long as he buy
all his  equipments,
he can fight others.
How much is needed?
It's fake, auntie.
Attack, can push.
I can attack.
Attack.
I'll go first.
Attack, I see Xia Ling.
Qi Yue and Shen Yue
are in our jungle.
Do we catch them?
No,
let's put on an act.
Okay.
Xia Ling, bait them.
Let us have a look,
Xia Ling position is a little dangerous.
Xia Ling is trying
to be a bait?
But Double Moon
will not let
such an opportunity slide.
-They're baited.        -Nince.
Xia Ling, I'm here to help you.
Pei Xi came, entering from the back.
Attacking the opponents unprepared.
Nice one.
This tactic
of baiting the opponent is not bad.
Pei Xi, just you wait.
We can't attack.
It's just the both of them,
mana isn't enough.
Double Moon escaped death.
Ji Xiang Kong...
Ji Xiang Kong and Lin Yi Xuan are coming.
Seems like
Wei Teng is losing a turret.
Phoenix is at an
advantage for this operation.
What does that mean?
He took a detour,
they'll win as long as
they destroy the crystal.
Pull back a little.
I'll retreat first.
Develop first,
don't fight.
Develop first.
Enough.
This wave is too painful.
Xia Ling, you and Pei Xi
change positions. We push from the middle.
Understood.
Okay.
Push middle, I'm coming.
Let me see,
it's getting to Wei Teng's head
and they don't intend to give up.
Shen Yue and Tong Wu are
chasing after the escaped Pei Xi.
Phoenix assist after seeing the situation.
I think good teams
assist very quickly.
Yes, Lin Yi Xuan and Sun Ze Yi
cooperate with Ji Xiang Kong,
reaching almost instantly
besde Pei Xi,
Wei Teng better run.
If not, they'll be in trouble.
They'll be doomed.
It's a win.
Not yet,
they're destroying the turret.
They win as long as they
down they crystal.
Can attack.
Still can attack.
Attack.
I'll charge.
You Phoenix know how to support,
we Wei Teng are not easily dealt with.
It's coming,
Wei Teng's remaining 3 members are delivering.
5 of them gather,
are they starting a group fight soon?
They can't start a group fight,
mana isn't enough.
but they didn't realised that
the one in the middle
now is Pei Xi.
Isn't Pei Xi
jungling just now?
This is the Shadow tactic,
changing positions flexibly,
catching the opponents off guard.
Also, take a closer look,
Xia Ling is at a
disadvantage if opponents were
to start a group fight.
They only have 4 poeple now,
let's start a group fight. go!
Hurry.
They're all coming up.
Stay back if you can't follow up with the damage.
Wait for me.
They're starting a group fight.
Fight with them.
Shen Yue...
Shen Yue started a group fight here.
I controlled one.
She Yue, you're too front.
Pei Xi is very direct,
casted a skill
and slain Shen Yue.
At the same time, retreated
to behind Lin Yi Xuan.
Be ready for another wave before entering.
Slowly.
Shen Yue, steady.
Xia Ling, come and do your kill.
Slain the four of them.
Start your show, Brother.
Starting up the lawn mower.
No,
you... Xia Ling...
Where did Xia Ling come from?
How did he
appear behind Wei Teng?
Wei Teng is in danger.
Cool, double Kill. Nice one.
Triple kill, quadra kill.
Not yet,
Almost winning.
Wei Teng wiped out.
Xia Ling did well for this wave,
very ghostly.
Also, I think
that it's really unexpected.
Phoenix push forward aggressively
destryoing second turret and after the base.
The wave is simply...
simply as if half a hand is already
touching the ticket to the global finals.
Don't...
Wait for a while.
Take a look at Wei Teng,
the fastest to resurrect has 8 more seconds.
Let's see if there's any chance
for another group fight.
Queen of Thorns
has 3 seconds more to resurrect.
Let us look at Xia Ling,
what is he doing?
He pulled an arrow,
firing out the arrow of fire
wanting to stun
the Qi Yue who just resurrect from the fountain?
This Xia Ling is trying to kill me beyond the fountain!
What is he doing?
He jumped out
of the fountain after
he slain Qi Yue.
This operation is brilliant!
Xia Ling single-handedly
blocked Wei Teng
of their resurrection.
Who still dare to say Xia Ling
is a crippled middle?
Xia Ling, all the best!
On this side, Pheonix
destroyed the their last base,
not giving Wei Teng
a chance to breathe.
Nice one!
Are you guys a bunch of trash?
What are you all even playing? Stupid.
Champion! Pheonix!
Congratulations Phoenix
for being the champion for
this Spring tournament.
Congratulations Phoenix!
for being the champion for this Spring
tournament.
Also, they gotten
themselves the ticket to the global
competition!
I believe Phoenix has
suffered many doubts
along the way,
especially on their tactics
so I'd like to ask their captain,
Ji Xiang Kong,
what made you insist on using
Shadow tactic?
Because I always believe in
my teammates.
Believe in his teammates
is the biggest Lethality towards their opponents.
That's awesome!
Yes, so Brother Yi
I believe you suffered
a lot of stress and
doubts after your
re-emergence.
Actually, it's not easy for me
to return to the competition.
Brother Yi, I support you. All the best!
Thank you everyone.
I only enjoy
the process of the competition.
Thank you everyone!
I believe Phoenix
has a long way ahead of them,
enjoy the match that
belongs to you it to the fullest.
The MVP for this round goes to
Xia Ling!
He got himself the MVP
in just one round.
So Xia Ling,
do you have anything
you'd like to tell everyone?
I, actually...
Xia Ling, you're the best!
I...
I wish to tell my Mum and Dad
and also my Sister that
I got the champion.
I've proved myself!
Xia Ling used his own actions
to tell us
fans who likes Iconquer that
life can let your body down
but
it can't let your will down.
Congratulations, Xia Ling!
Previous members of Kai Tuo Zhe,
Xia Tian and Shu Wen,
ar there on stage too.
Below,
there's also Phoenix's leader, Qiu Ying.
Let us accompany Phoenix
to a bigger and larger stage,
hope that they will help China
take down the champion.
We go to the top together!
What's their slogan?
Our passion doesn't die, Nirvana reborn.
Cheers!
This is ice cold.
That...
I have something to say.
Since everyone is here
is so happy today,
as a reporter myself,
I have some questions
to interview you guys.
Cooperate please.
So I'll start now.
We start from...
Ji Xiang Kong.
Okay.
As the captain,
do you have anything to say
seeing where Pheonix
is at today?
Let me ask,
is this official
or non-official?
Be serious, you're being interviewed.
I want to say,
Phoenix went from nothing to something.
Till now,
I've been wanting
to thank my Brothers.
How official.
Brother Xia Ling,
as the youngest
player among them,
what do you have to say?
I dream earlier
was to be
the hero on the basketball court.
But now, there's everyone.
There's Phoenix.
I'm still able to be a hero.
Nice.
You see
your Sister, Qiu Ying, is about to cry.
Don't cry.
Let's continue.
Pei Xi,
many said you've changed.
Unlike the past,
you only cared for yourself.
So comparing to the past,
which of yourself do you prefer?
Of course, it's the me now.
Then can you tell us
why?
Enough,
where did all the whys come form?
I'm all ready.
Come, ask me.
Don't be anxious, I'm still not done.
Oh, Pei Xi.
I've always been wanting to ask you,
why do you like
working as a waiter at Meng Lu Ren
and even cook coffee for us?
Right.
It's because
I like to be with everyone.
I like the feeling
of being needed.
The me now
has something more important
than winning in competitions.
I have a group
of true
brothers
that I can compete with.
Thank you all.
Brother,
seeing you change so much,
and befriended
so many true friends,
I'm really happy for you.
Notify me when you need to
open up your shield.
You're a hero in my heart.
Don't worry,
with bad friends like us,
you'll never be lonely again.
I'll say something
since it's emotional.
Thank you, Brother Kong
for cultivating me into
a professional player
from a delivery boy
to be able to enter the global final.
Thank you to all of you here
for putting up with me, Lin Yi Xuan,
a body of faults.
Thank you Phoenix.
I only have confidence
to get to the top
because of Phoenix.
Phoenix isn't just a team,
it's also a home.
I'm thankful to everyone for allowing
the oldest player to participate
in the competition again.
I hope we're able to walk down this path,
step by step, towards the top.
Phoenix has fulfilled everything
you want to in the past.
Xiang Kong, congratulations
for finding
the perfect team for yourself.
Okay, don't be emotional anymore.
I'm so hungry.
Hurry, it's all in the drink.
Xiang Kong, say something.
Okay, I'll keep it short and simple,
see you guys in the global finals!
Bottoms up!
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
how you'll look when you stand
on the global final stage,
must be really handsome.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry for?
I didn't help you
fulfil your dream.
Tong Wu and Lu Sheng
came to look for me yesterday
saying that Qi Yue and Qiao Xin
came up with the
idea of tactic leak.
I implicated you
causing you to not able to be a commentator.
How can I blame you?
If there's no Qiao Xin,
Qi Yue can't
accomplish the matter alone.
But if
this didn't happen,
you might've really
be able to stand on the global final stage
commenting on every match of Phoenix.
It's it good that I'm going as
the leader of Phoenix?
But your stage is being a commentator.
-It's your dream.          -It's okay.
I'll be able to be a commentator again
once the committee
are done with their investigation.
[Fu Mi Ya]
It's okay, answer it.
I'm not so petty.
Ji Xiang Kong,
it's me.
Something happened to Mi Ya.
What?
She fell from the
hanging wire during rehearsal.
She's being sent to the hospital now.
Nurse, hello.
How do I get to room 1709?
Thank you.
How is Mi Ya now?
Talk outside, go.
How is she now?
She just fell asleep
but
there's blood clot in her brain
pressing against her nerve.
we need the results
from the doctor for more specific details.
What actually happened?
She value the concert a lot
and did a lot preparations.
Actually, there's no need for hanging wire
for this rehearsal
but
she doesn't want any details to go wrong.
In the end, never thought that
the staff made amistake while operating.
This happened too quickly.
Mi Ya doesn't have any relatives
so
I could only contact you.
I hope you'd understand.
We'll go over to the doctor in a while
to ask about her situation.
The situation isn't ideal.
Look,
the patient's blood clot in her brain
is pressing against her visual nerve.
She might go blind.
What? Blind?
How did it happen?
Is it temporary?
If she's really to go blind,
it's hard to say if she's able to recover.
There's an old injury on her head.
What I worry most now is
the degree of damage for her nerve
caused by both injury on the head.
You have to be
prepared that she might go blind forever.
Xiang Kong,
Mi Ya's injury is an accident.
Don't be like this, okay?
We can think of a solution together.
She'll definitely get better.
Really, it's not your fault.
No, I'm to blame.
If it's not for me back then,
she wouldn't have gotten her old injury.
So you be a substitute actress
just so that you could gift me a computer?
Sit.
You want to be a professional player.
Of course
you need a professinal computer.
With the computer,
you can practice well.
Next time, you'll definitely
be a professional player.
Go to the global finals
and get the champion.
Thank you.
Promise me then
that you'll not do such
dangerous act again.
Okay?
Yes.
It's not early now,
you and Xiang Kong
should head back and rest.
I'll go get him.
Xiang Kong,
you guys should head back and rest.
I'll contact you
when she's awake.
It's fine,
I wish to be with her.
Master, you look for me?
Qi Yue,
this is the staffs from the committee.
They are here to talk to you regarding
the leakage of tactic.
What's there to talk about?
Isn't it done by Qiu Ying?
I still want to ask
you people
how did this
kind of people get in the semi-finals?
We're not investigating on
Qiu Ying this time
but you.
If this matter
is really related to him,
I'll support you
in however way you handle him.
You worked hard.
Teacher Ah Can,
this is the analyze I did for
the global competiton, take a look.
Leave it.
Okay.
I'll help you organize.
Tacher Ah Can,
I heard
Teacher Luo has yet to confirm the
namelist for
the global finals.
You know how Luo Tian
does his work,
if there isn't any one suitable,
he'd rather leave it empty than choosing randomly.
We worked together for so long,
can you help me ask him?
I have something on, shalln't talk anymore.
Teacher Ah Can.
Teacher Ah Can, wait up.
Did I do something wrong?
Why are you giving
me such an attitude?
Teacher Luo.
Qiao Xin, this is Lucy from
Iconquer committee.
They're here for you.
Miss Qiao,
regsrding the leakage of tactic,
we'rehere to understand
the matter better from you.
Didn't you verify previously?
We got our hands on some evidence
proving that you're involved with the tactic leakage.
I...
What does it have to do with me?
Teacher Luo,
they must've misunderstood me.
Miss Qiao,
please cooperate with us.
Who's that?
Mi Ya, it's me.
Xiang Kong.
I bought you a bouquet of lilies,
does it smell good?
Yes.
What time is it now?
4:30pm.
4:30pm...
Only 4:30pm?
Why is the time passing so slowly.
Don't worry, I'm here with you.
Okay.
Xiang Kong,
my eyes
should be unable
to see for real this time.
I won't be able to
beon stage again.
Mi Ya,
your eyes will recover.
But i'm really scared.
My surroundings are dark,
it's a endless darkness.
I'm really tired.
I don't know what I should do.
Take a nap,
you need ample of rest now.
I can't sleep.
Be good, take a nap.
I'm here with you.
You can't leave okay?
Don;t worry,
I won't leave.
Okay.