Why are you looking at me
I don't
Is it ok?
Good
You need to find the top100
initiating a invitation
Then I will lose
It's ok
I can help you
Actually we didn't order any drinks
I give you guys for free
Is it free
When Dream trevaller is generous
We are still generous
Thanks
agree with the invitation
Are you teaching her to finish scaling ladder
Why are you stay here
It is waste your time
But I have a lot of spare time now
Choose the champion
Give me
Do we have more strawberry
Yes we have
It is for this customer
I will send it to council chamber first
About yours Later I will cook a better one for you
OK alright
I am so sorry about this
Mr.Summer
Is there anyone in the membership room
Ji xinagkong in the room
Ji xiangkong
Also have Qiu Ying that she stay here everyday to play the district service
It is not useful that you just memorize the order number. You have to play it flexible
You should not play the creator like this you should fight it now
Are you serious But I have lost blood
Listen to me fight it now
Go
You need to control it first use skill E
W point Injury in the game
Move the suitation
Equal to A
He flashed away
Flashed again Fight it with you strong skills
You should continue do it Please dont leave your keyboard
Continue
Fight the crystal
Xiangkong I am No.65 in this area
You are great
You should give more confidence to yourself you can do it
Do you know Peixi
I am No.65 now in the area
Our new products
Please try it it is free
Thank you
Is still free
Then I will try it
Thanks
It is a lot of strawberry inside
It is different compare with your menu
Help me say thanks to your cousin
Did you find the new Team
Why you don't go now
In addition
I think there is no connection with you which Team I need to go
Don't tell me any team that they don't want to invite you to join
You give me too much suggestions
I am only worried about next term
I don't have a good competitors
Thanks you
You can encourage me
But you should join a team training with your teammates
Not walk around at here
Also you should try to find another team
You should not have an appointment at here
Alright Can you stop wrangle
Please stop angry
Pei xi
I give you a suggestion
Please don't be serious when you talk with girls
Maybe you will scared them
I don't have a lot of spare time like you
Sorry for your waiting
I did better than him
Thanks
Don'ask me
I didn't ask
What's the matter
I am lucky today because of you
I can experience the VIP room
Also I have the free food to eat
Free food is not my reason
I think Peixi enter our room a lot of times
Maybe he don't hope I stay at there
Really
What do you mean
Do you feel he is apperaciate you didn't you
Maybe I need to keeo a distance to you
I don't want to get in the way of your happiness
Coach Ji
Since I had a goosip with you last time. I don't have any new idea until now
So I need to take a resonsibility to you forever
Don't say it
In fact
I really want to know
Which team you will go
Do you want to listen to the truth
Actually until now
There has no team contact with me
It is so strange
Why I don't want to talk with others
But in our conversation I am willing to tell you the truth
So we are best friend
Hi Leon
Hi Ji xiangkong
This is En-ception's manager I heard you are leave from Legend team
I ask you would you like to join us for the next year's Championship
Thank you for invite me
I know En-ception is one of the best teams
But my dream is went to be a chinese player
Thank you
Bye
En-ception
Who called you what's the matter
En-ception invite me to join their team
But I refused
Why
It is
En-ception is No.3 team in the world
It is a little difficult to say
You can talk with me
I am your most loyal audience
When I was a student in the University
I took part in a peak domestic exchange competition
I heard the foreign team mocked the Chinese team
I am so angry so I want to have a solo with them
Do you want to fight the Queen of Thorns
Hell emissary bought the congealed soul tears It is clearly to see through the queen of the thorn set
He didn't hurt by Queen of Thorns
And he earn the blood use the strength of Queen thorns
This is an awareness that many professionals don't have
mind your back
no please  in the front of the line
No no no we win
Ji xiangkong
You are so great
You have won honor for China
Hello do you have intersting to join the professional team
Then you went to the professional team
Formally I went to the prfessional team after I graduate
My favorite chinese team Exploiter they are already dissolved
After them
China has never won a world championship again
The foreign media moched there is no tacticalwith us
Then I graduate
And I join a club
Start my professional job
Thus
You still to refused invitation from foreign teams
If I can get the trophy of championship
It is definately belongs to China
It is my purpose to become the professional players
Also this is my pledge for Gufang
Me Qiuying
I am so admire
Someone who had a dream
Ji xiangkong
I believe you you can win go to the top of the world
I hope that day
is you
Stand on the Commentary stage  And speak to the world
Chinese team earn the championship of the world
It's a deal
It's a promise
Let's congratulations to the Team Legend they are the championship of the world
Thanks for your support
Congratulations Ji xingkong
The moment you wake up
Decide go to the top of the world
It's the most exciting adventure
The most exciting adventure  do you dare or not
Achieve your dream
At the moment
We are together
You scared me
What are doing
Are you serious
You need to explain to me
What did you dream about
Laughing like a maniac
I think you are doing a good dream now
Why you make a face mask in the morning
The face mask is a special for me because it is you give me I want to try to more times
I
I also want to become a pretty girl from now
Look at me My skin will be better after I did the face mask Do you admire me
OK You are a pretty girl
I am so admire you
Don't talk this
You need to say
When did you back last night
11:00pm
Are you sure
12:00am
You backed too late
Tell me
What did you do yesterday
I need to do a face mask
No You come back
Why you do it now
You need give me a explanation
Don't tell me you stay at Dream traveller because I can't find you at there
Alright
I will tell you the truth
I am stay with Ji xiangkong
With him again
I gussed it
But he only help me to improve my skills in the game
Do you know my ranking is increse to No.65 in the area
It is great Isn't it
And the important thing is
Jixianging refused the En-ception Team which is the No.3 in the world
Hei Hei Hei
Qiu Ying
Can you control yourself at the moment
At least you are the Ying goddess who once had hundreds of thousands of fans
But now you looks like a Non-brain fans for Ji xaingkong
I can't understand you anymore
Maybe it is useless for about our conversation
I am going to work now
You are free to have a face mask time now
Captain
Thanks for you help at the period
Whatever you are stay here or not in the fulture
I will continue to hard-working
Hello, captain
Oh sorry
You are the captain of Legend Team now
It is cakes
Who bought it
It is for the a farewell party isn't it
Because our captain will leave
I paid the bill
Today
Woo Our former captain provide a free cake to eat
I am so surprised
Oh Hands shake
We will be rivals when the next time we meet
You don't need to do like that
It is not necessary
Qi yue
What are you doing
We need to describe the truth
Pei xi
When you at VNG
Shuwen and me tried our best to cultivate you
All the tactics and methods are around you at all
I trained you to be No.1
New term will begin now but you said you want to leave
Do you consider other teammates
This kind of selfish devil will not consider our idea
The night before we got together to figure out how to protect you and make sure you got the MVP
Maybe VNG could earn the championship
How the result
You tell us you already went to the Legend Team
You are great
Both of us want to become a championship
But according to the urrent tactics
We can't achieve our goals
If we continue to play as the same method
Maybe we will bring some bad influences for our careers
Do you understand what's he saying
Only you to talk about our tactical
But you can't do it
You selled everyone's effort
Then,you went to become a captain for the opponent team
Is like this
Without our sacrifice
Can you be as famous as you are today
What happened
Nothing
In addition Coach shuwen is so kind to treat you
Why are you do this
You are ungrateful
Stop talking
Pei xi
I respect your choice
We also appreciate everything you've done for VNG
I hope you have a good future
Thanks you coach
I will rememeber you forever
You are my teacher
Xuan  what are you going to do
Bro
I can understand your mood now
I'm more upset than you. I want to beat zhao Yang as well
But the problem can't be solved
Commander Ji already left
Pei xi is my captain now We cannot change it now
If you go on like this, zhao Yang will spread the rumour
Do you remember what he said when commander Ji left
They hope we can concentrate on our training
He hope we can get a good result
I can't stand it if you keep doing this
Captain left and Kong left I don't want to do anything now
We still have two years left on Legend's contract
You are ruining the career of your dude
OK OK I know I know
Xuan please speak
Zhao yang come here with Pei xi
Director Jin
Pei xi
Welcome Peixi
It doesn't matter
Everyone will be a family in the future
We don't need to be squeamish
Yes
If someone don't have a coporation with you you can tell me
Director Jin
You know Pei xi
Having a contract with us that information will be disseminate by mass media
Two major sponsors from VNG called me at the moment
They want to have a good business corporation with us in the next term
You can see that
Sponor will come to our company follow with Pei xi
I think the championship
We can except it will be come as soon as possible
Is it because of me that Ji xiangkong left
You have got nothing to deal with his leave
You don't need to worried about this
You didn't visit our place did you I can help you to know the new environment
This
Coach Luo What does he do
What are you doing What happened
You want to make a trouble for me Did you
Lin yixuan
Are you crazy
Why are you come to here with fitness equipment
Our new captain come
I need to say hi with our new captain
We are homie now
We need to prepare the next term togrther Is it alright
Coach Luo Peixi already join us we can work together to create brilliant
Go to the top of the world
You wait
young people
He is so young
You're not familiar
Once you get familiar with it It would be fine
Is it right Coach luo
Pei Xi
What's the matter
He is a talent
That's how a genius does
cross the line
Coach Luo
Shame on you
Is this your student
You need to strict to treat them
I am going to find Pei xi
This is my tactical analysis for the Team Xin Tu
Last season 26 wins
20 wins are counted on conventional tactics
If we could make some changes on our strategy
I believe in the new term
Maybe Team Xintu has the chace to enter the Vencouver series
Xiang kong
We don't need to discuss the tactics today
You can see the contract first
If you don't have any questions we can signed directly
Gu fang already called me
Team Xintu usually concentrate on your match
But different team have different systems of tactics
If you require our team to use your tactics at the same time
I think it is not suitable
But we can wait for one or two terms If you have a good performance
Board of directors will consider choose you to do a leader
Director chen
Which position are you gonna to play
I don't mind that
I hope I can show my edge
If my tactic is nugatory for your team
Then my joining is meaningless
Xiang kong
As your friend
As the older generation
I will give you an advice
Don't be too idealistic
But I want to bet my dream
Thanks for your coffee I will go first
Dishes are already to eat
It is looks so delicious
Did you guess I was going to break up with the Team Xin Tu
It is not suitable for you
Stop complimenting me bro
I will be shy Are you serious
Don't you feel embarrasssing for living at my place
From tomorrow I can work there
At least you are a world champion How can I afford your life
But I have thought be careful
Although Xintu Team is not suitable for you
I can recommand another team for you
Which team
VNG
It is Wen's team
Sun
I know you for a long time But it is the first time you mentioned Shuwen by yourself
Are you joking me
You continue to say
What do you think about Shuwen
Wen is definitely the female role model
In the gaming industry only you  captain and wen can get my respect
So far the gaming industry
Only her can be that adventurous as Gufang
Yes
In these team
VNG team is the only team I haven't contacted
Their sponsors are basically going for pei xi
After Pei xi left
They are also experience a hard time
I'm afraid I'll get her into trouble
I think you don't need to consider about this
Pei xi
Maybe he is better than you as a player
But you know how to socialise with others
In summary Iconquer this game
Is to interpret people's mind
If you go to VNG Team they can get to a higher stage
But Wen will contact me if she wants me to join them
Gave up
If you are afraid you can come back
To become a network manager
If you want to challenge yourself
You can call Shuwen
You tell her you can give her a new VNG Team
Enjoy your deal meal Thanks
Director yuan called me yesterday
I know
He is going to Legend team with Peixi
Nowadays the sponsorship are so materialistic They only care about the profit that you can make
Your stomach hurt
Did you have a drink with Director Yuan Yeaterday
I am alright
If our team can be improved to a new level
They will be back that the sponsors who left
But you can trust me
I am still hard
We are so hard in this period
Good job today
Alright
In the junior training camp there is a kid with a very high potential to be a professional player
I think we can cultivate him
Maybe he can become the next Peixi
But I don't want someone similar with Pei Xi
Since Peixi come to VNG We never changed our tactics
So I think that
Maybe Peixi leave is a good thing for us
But we have a good result when we use the tactics
Yes so Pei xi left It feels like VNG has been teared apart
This is not my ideal team
However there is a gap between ideal and reality
I have a simple idea
Pick a kid from a junior camp to replace Peixi's position
Then we choose Qiyue to become our Captain
Li gan
Qiyue has a good ability
But he doesn't have the right personality to be captain
We also don't have better choice now
Give me more time to consider that
Wen do you have free time tomorrow I want to chat with with you
Why are we practicing this thing
It all the same
Don't exercise anymore
Yixuan
Stop talking I said wrong did I
Lin Yinxuan
Training it's gonna to be started
Why don't you take a break first
Peixi
Director Jin
You are my lucky team member
At the before time
Dorector Yuan Who is the sponor from VNG
Because of you
Now come to provide sponsorship to us
I don't know he will come
It doesn't matter
Anyway we got the sponsorship
After three days
We will improve our equipment
The benefit is from your new captain you guys should thanks to him
Thanks Director Thanks Captain
OK I will not bother you
Training is gonna to be start
You should have a good connection with your new captain
Work together
We know fighting
OK I go Bye Bye
Our kong
He don't care about the sponsor
In order to change equipment to ask someone else
But our new captain
You don't figure out a strategy
Only focus on finding sponsor
Amazing
I said
I don't let he come to here
Don't think that your little favors can help you
Who wants to buy over you
Up to you
About support palyers
There a lot of
Look down on the  support players Aren't you
Lin Yixuan
We only have five minutes to prepare the game
You are great Arrn't you
I don't play it
How can you do it
Lin yixuan
Lin yixuan Lin yixuan
Don't stop him
Captain
We don't have support players how can we finish the game
Four vs five
We can do it
Please come here
come here come here
come come
What's wrong Ditrector
Are you all here
Today morning
Director Li called me
Invite us to interview Qi yue from their team
I can't refused
Who want to do this interview
Me Me Me Me Me
Anyone else
Yiyi are willing to do the interview
OK Yiyi
You can do it
I go
Thank you
Go go go I am not finish my tea
Linan Go
I admire you
We win althrough we only have four people
how strong psychological quality with him that he was be able to withstand so much abuse
What can I do for him
In fact There are people who support him
Take a screenshot of them
I come back
I am so tired
What are you doing
Nothing
You are so strange what are you doing
I am doing other things
Why are you so tired
About your periodical office
Is it leisure isn't it
They are leisurely and carefree
But I am not a lucky girl
I help you to release the pressure come come
This side This side
Don't push too hard
Is there anything unpleasant thing you tell me that it would cheer me up
Are you my best friend
Tomorrow
I am going to VNG to Interview Qiyue
It is great isn't it
But I only know a liitle information about him
I am slap together
Whole day I am doing about him
I am so hungry about this
Actually they asked us to interview them
As a result, the interview time was adjusted three times
I am looking forward
Qiyue
Why does he so rude
Oh I feel hurt
My mistakes
Speak carefully
Qiyue is the captain of VNG now and he is also a oldest team membership in VNG
He is the boss's apprentice
It is normal about that
He is the apprentice of shuwen Does he
No he is the apprentice of Li gan
You know a lot of information
Because of you know a lot of him
Could you come with me to do the interview
You could become my assistant of camera
Tomorrow you can boarden your horizon
I will let you know what is the professional team
It is good for you to join the competition named Tommorrow star
How about this idea
I think I I provide you a good method to learn
I don't think you dare go by yourself
Why I will be afraid Actually you are afraid
You don't tell me what are you doing a moment ago
Alright I can go with you and I can do your assistant
Are you hppy now
I am stop talking with you because I am so busy
You
You are so strange You must be keeping something from me