[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 27]
Ji Xiang Kong.
Qiu Ying.
How... how are you?
Why did you faint suddenly?
Are you feeling better now?
Fainted? I didn't faint.
You see, I'm fine here.
Who did you hear from?
Qiao Xin.
Stupid.
You believed what she said?
It's good that you're fine.
I'll leave first.
Sorry.
Its all because of
that you're aggrieved
but don't leave me
and ignore me okay?
Don't say sorry to me already.
We...
We shall not bother each other.
I don't believe.
I don't believe you can do it.
Why is it that
you're so anxious just now?
Ji Xiang Kong, let go of me.
Let go.
Qiu Ying.
Qiu Ying, listen to me.
I like you.
I didn't take you
as anyone's replacement.
I don't know
since when it started,
probably when
you're on the star's tomorrow's stage,
probably its that night
when you're drunk at the convenience store.
Didn't we agreed on
to rise to the top of the world together?
Don't leave me.
You know that I like you.
Long before,
I already like you
but
I don't know what am I now.
You and Mi Ya...
Mi Ya and I is already over.
Believe me.
Give me some time,
I will settle it properly.
But now,
the whole world knows
that you guys are together.
How do you end it just like that?
What do you want me to do?
Ji Xiang Kong,
I cannot be compared to Mi Ya.
We have never started before,
just end it like this.
I have never seen
you so serious
to someone,
what's more its a
newcomer commentary.
Teacher Luo,
this is all my commentary,
please advise me.
Hurry and go back.
Thank you Teacher Luo.
Qiu Ying,
you have already absolutely gave up.
You already rejected him.
He is then a match with Mi Ya.
Don't be stupid already.
If you want to cry, just cry it out.
You'll be fine after crying.
Teacher Luo,
don't worry.
I will adjust my emotions properly,
I wouldn't affect my job.
Hope this is the last time
I'll see you cry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's start.
We'll wait awhile for Sister Wen.
No need.
Okay, let's start.
Tomorrow,
what's different about the Team Xiao Long
that we are competing is...
Sister Wen.
Sorry, I came late.
Xiang Kong, start.
Okay.
Tomorrow,
the difference between the team Xiao Long
that we are competing is,
their top play is very strong.
Relying on the top
to have more damage in the earlier part of the game
so at the top
we have to choose some tank hero,
this way we can guard a little
to void getting killed,
causing it to snowball.
Lu Sheng, under the condition
that you can fully develop in the early part,
try to catch the top.
Okay.
Until the back part,
we will try not have group attack,
go solo.
Mainly we will go top as priority.
Come.
Brother Yao.
Hurry up.
Wait for Pei Xi.
Don't care about him.
Come. Three, two, one.
Hey, Ji Xiang Kong.
I indeed admire you.
On one hand, you're dating the star.
On the other, you're having ambiguous relationship
with our commentary.
Not bad.
What do you guys want?
Better have some respect,
don't find trouble.
If you have the energy to argue,
why not research on the tactics?
Be careful getting bashed by our substitute.
Your tone isn't small.
We were wondering previously
why is that when Qiu Ying is commenting,
she always speak good of you.
So it is because the both of you
are related.
You guys know
what's the situation with Qiu Ying?
Even this kind of girl, he wants.
You better keep your mouth clean.
Leader!
- Ji Xiang Kong. - Leader.
Pei Xi, are you fine?
Ji Xiang Kong beat someone up.
Pei Xi,
you can go to the main committee.
You're crazy.
Leader, he's agitating you.
You still don't want to leave?
What happen? Finding trouble?
Lin Yi Xuan will accompany.
What you doing?
Let's go.
Didn't you like to show off your tactics?
Prepare tissues,
don't cry too badly later.
Let's go.
What happened?
They find trouble,
Pei Xi helped Ji Xiang Kong to talk.
You still helped my Brother Kong to talk.
Finals,
I only want to compete with Wei Teng.
Thanks Pei Xi.
You fine?
I'm fine.
Okay,
don't affect your state.
All the best.
We'll meet during finals.
Morning.
Teacher Luo.
Thanks.
Last night,
how was your rest?
I slept right after I reached home last night.
Then didn't I bought the coffee for nothing?
Why would that be?
Coffee in hand, double the fighting spirit.
Okay, match the script.
You're here.
What happen?
Sister Wen,
just now when we were outside,
people from Xiao Long actually provoked us.
Provoke us?
Provoke? That's not just provoke.
That attitude don't be too furious.
Still said something like
asking us to prepare tissue,
don't lose the competition
and cry too badly.
This whole competition season,
they have never won before.
I really don't know
where is their confidence from.
What's the situation, Xiang Kong?
Something happened.
What happened?
The difference with the other teams is
their top is very strong.
Relying on the top
to have more damage in the earlier part of the game
so at the top
we have to choose some tank hero,
this way we can guard a little.
This recording was posted 3 hours ago,
its already spreaded all over internet.
No wonder Xiao Long's leader
is so arrogant.
Like this,
I'll go report to the main committee first.
I've already reported.
What's important now is
how are we going to handle it.
The competition later,
don't panic.
We still have the second scheme.
Xiang Kong...
No need.
Ji Xiang Kong,
you have violated the team's discipline,
disclose the team's strategy.
From now on,
you'll be on substitute.
Qi Yue, you're up on the next competition.
Okay, Master.
Li Gan, what do you mean?
Do you know what are you saying?
What do I mean?
Shouldn't you ask him
how did the recording
got disclosed?
Qi Yue saw Qiu Ying
entering our Wei Teng's
meeting room
before our strategy meeting.
Sister Wen,
this is 100 percent
purposely done by Qiu Ying
to revenge on Ji Xiang Kong.
Qi Yue, what nonsense are you saying?
Xiang Kong.
Yes.
Okay.
Teacher Luo, sorry to disturb.
Lu Xi,
why are you here?
You're Qiu Ying?
Yes.
Hello, I am Iconquer's competition's
main committee, Lu Xi.
Today competition,
you don't have to be the commentary.
There's something that needs you
to corporate with us in our investigation,
you have to make a trip with us.
Lu Xi,
the competition is starting,
can we speak about it
after the competition?
A few hours ago,
Wei Teng's strategic recording
was uploaded online.
This...
Wei Teng's strategic recording?
That's right.
We've investigated
the hotel's CCTV.
Other than Wei Teng's members,
only you
went into their meeting room.
No, I...
Yesterday, I... I just...
You don't have to explain to me now,
there will be a chance for you to explain later,
please corporate with our job.
Teacher Luo.
Don't worry.
Hand this over to me,
explain the situation
first and it'll be fine.
Okay.
Teacher Luo.
Get going.
Hello, Director Guo.
I received the notice
from Iconquer's main committee.
Qiao Xin have already rushed over.
You will partner with her
for today's competition commentary.
She have arrived already.
Hello Teacher Luo,
I'm very happy to work with you.
I will cherish this chance a lot.
If you said the speech wrong later,
just don't talk
and just sit there will do.
Teacher Luo, don't worry.
This competition
I've prepared sufficiently.
Didn't you always say,
the chance is left for those who have prepared.
You and Qiu Ying
have stayed in our meeting room
for 15 minutes.
Ji Xiang Kong,
as a leader,
you don't know
the team's discipline?
Other than those from the team,
no one is allowed in the meeting room.
I know.
This is my responsibility,
I will bare it.
Xiang Kong.
Wait a moment.
Qiu Ying did come to the meeting room,
but its impossible for her to record
and disclose Wei Teng's strategy.
Where's the evidence?
I can testify for her,
its not easy for her
to go up the commentary stage.
She wouldn't ruin her own career.
You don't have to prove anything for me.
Something that I've never done,
it will naturally be investigated.
You focus on your competition.
Li Gan,
how its not the time to pursue,
the strategy have to disclosed.
We have to hurry
and re-customised our tactics.
Qi Yue and I have already thought of the new tactics
on our way here.
As the coach,
I have the right to keep
Ji Xiang Kong's chance to compete.
As the Manager,
I also have the rights
to remove you as the coach.
Okay, come here everyone.
Sit down.
Listen to me
talk about the tactics later.
Qi Yue will play mid.
Lu Sheng will return to playing the top.
Tong Wu, Lu Sheng,
did the both of you heard what I said?
Play well,
you have to take the competition down.
No wonder they are so arrogant.
Cheating like that,
still dare to show off.
This is all internal meeting,
why would there be someone that record and disclose it?
If they lost this competition,
Wei Teng will be disqualified.
Cannot be.
Brother Kong always have a plan B,
he can't lose.
Welcome everyone to the
2018 Iconquer playoff,
the live of losing team competition.
I am today's commentary, Luo Tian.
I am the commentary, Qiao Xin.
Where's Qiu Ying?
Today, the team competing
are Wei Teng vs. Xiao Long.
To the both teams,
this is a battle life and death.
The winning team
would be able to enter semi-finals.
The losing team
will be disqualified.
Today, Wei Teng team members
have some changes.
Leader, Ji Xiang Kong,
have been change off
and Qi Yue wil return
and play back his original
mid position.
They changed my Brother Kong away.
Coach Shu Wen is not around too.
Li Gan became the coach.
Wei Teng is doom.
This is you right?
That day,
I heard that Ji Xiang Kong fainted
after that I gave him a call,
but no one answered.
I was anxious,
I ran to
the team's meeting room to look for him.
In the end, he didn't faint.
Its all their nonsense.
Them?
Qiao Xin and my two other colleague.
Okay, what you have said
we will look for Qiao Xin to confirm.
Before the investigation is clear,
you have to stop
all your job on commentary.
I understand.
Then
I'll wait for the main committee's notice.
President Zhu.
Yes,
yes,
she was not feeling well
after days ago.
We will go according to the contract.
Okay, let'e work together next time.
Why isn't Xiang Kong on the competition?
Probably is
the problem of the disclosure of the tactics.
What's going on with the disclosure of the tactics?
Hurry up.
Why is Xiang Kong not answering?
Kai Lun,
prepare the car.
What are you doing?
I want to go and look for Xiang Kong.
You still have a recording later.
I have to accompany him by his side.
You really
don't know the propriety.
There's a chance.
There's a chance, okay.
Go and assist Liu Liao.
Sheng Yue go.
Wei Teng have been forced to open teams.
They strategy of playing is very messy.
The double moon team tacit
did not show at all.
If this continues,
this round Wei Teng is very dangerous.
Ji Xiang Kong.
I heard...
I heard its because of Mi Ya
and Qiu Ying affair
that he got changed down.
Right.
Qiu Ying isn't on the commentary stage too.
Definitely its because of this.
Hurry attack.
Brother Qi, he's following you behind,
protect the base.
Hurry attack.
All out, I don't care anymore.
Let us congratulate Xiao Long
for successfully entering the semi-finals.
and hope that Wei Teng
can make more persistent efforts
in the next competition season.
Can you drive faster?
Almost there already.
I think now
is not a right time
for you to rush over,
you can't help Ji Xiang Kong too.
Moreover,
your current popularity
just recovered a little.
This time if anyone made an article,
your popularity will go down again.
I've never been by his side
through the hardship he been through these years.
This time,
I want him to know
no matter what happen,
I'll be by his side.
There's so many reporters,
we can't go already.
Xiao Zhang, u-turn.
No u-turning.
I must meet him today.
Detour over.
How is it?
Don't worry,
I've known Lu Xi
for many years.
She have always been fair
in handling such matters.
During this time,
just wait patiently,
it will definitely be investigated clearly.
Thank you Teacher Luo.
By the way,
how did the competition go?
Wei Teng lost.
How... how can that be possible?
Ji Xiang Kong
usually prepare 2 sets of tactics,
just in case.
How did
Wei Teng lose to Xiao Long?
Ji Xiang Kong
got changed off last minute.
Its because of me,
its because of the disclosure of the tactics.
Don't think too much.
This have nothing to do with you.
Hello,
the number you have dial have been switched off.
Why is it off?
Qiu Ying, don't be anxious.
Ji Xiang Kong is out.
Ji Xiang Kong.
You got changed down last minutes
is it because of the disclosure of the tactics?
Why did Qiu Ying appeared
at Wei Teng's meeting room?
Did she really do the recording?
The internet have raise a babel of criticism
that Qiu Ying have turn her love to hate against you
so you did a revenge.
Ji Xiang Kong, currently on the internet,
all the rumours
are pointing towards Qiu Ying,
what do you have to say
about this?
Ji Xiang Kong,
I think you
should not avoid it anymore.
Reporters,
please separate the team's issue
with my personal relationship.
About the disclosure of the tactics,
the main committee is currently investigating,
I will also corperate.
I take my career
as guarantee,
this have nothing
to do with Qiu Ying.
There's no existence
to the netizen's guess of revenge.
Thank you.
Wait a moment,
The only reason
why the internet
have such a guess...
Qiu Ying where are you going?
Chasing the roots,
its because between you and Mi Ya
as well as Qiu Ying
have a complicated relationship status.
About this,
what do you have to say?
Mi Ya is indeed my first love
but now between the both of us,
we're just friends.
We did not patch back.
So having that said,
Qiu Ying did not
break the both of your relationship,
is that right?
Between Qiu Ying and I,
we're also just friends
but I want to become
her boyfriend.
I also earnestly request
Mi Ya's fans
to stop attcking Qiu Ying.
Everything is my fault.
Thank you.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Mi Ya.
Ms Mi Ya, why are you here?
What do you have to say
to Ji Xiang Kong?
Can everyone move aside?
I have something to tell Xiang Kong first.
Xiang Kong.
Can you give me
a definite answer?
Sorry.
Is he at the hotel?
Not yet.
Qiu Ying, now you
should care about
yourself,
not Ji Xiang Kong.
Qiu Ying.
Where are you going?
You can't leave.
I advise you
to better not
seduce other people's boyfriend.
Ji Xiang Kong
is a heartless rat，
just wait to get abandoned.
Exactly.
You're the third party,
you know?
Go and die.
Good splashing.
What are you guys doing?
Come, do it again.
Do it again. Security.
You guys are Mi Ya's fans
right?
If you guys still have intellect,
if you guys really love her,
you guys should think about
why
she dont uprightly
date with others.
Why
she got forced to separate with her love one.
Spoiling people's relationship,
still so courageous with sufficient reasons?
Exactly.
Of course I'm courageous,
because
I respect Ji Xiang Kong and her
once relationship.
I also believe
Mi Ya respect
the relationship between us.
Ji Xiang Kong and I
are truly in love.
We did not
go against our humanity.
You guys don't have the rights
and competency to care about me.
Pleaase move away.
Not moving away.
Don't make an unreasonable scene here.
Don't make an unreasonable scene.
You are
the third party that destroy others.
Move away, what are you doing?
Are you guys crazy?
Who dare to scold another sentence, try.
Don't leave.
All of you keep quiet.
Thank you.
I'm at fault.
I'm the one that let Wei Teng
become what is it now.
Knowing how to find the problem on yourself
is your virtue
but you're too strict with yourself.
But I promised Ji Xiang Kong,
I didn't do it either.
Now
you've already done good enough.
Don't give yourself too much stress.
Disclosure of the tactics,
adding on to
him getting changed down like this.
This will be Ji Xiang Kong's
biggest blemish
in his whole career.
From Legends
to Wei Teng,
he've been through too much.
I believe he
can face any rain and storms.
Don't worry.
What is it?
Brother Sun, Coach Shu,
did Ji Xiang Kong come before?
He's not here.
He's mobile phone is off.
Where can he go?
Its fine.
I chased the both of you half the day,
did you guys hear mr calling?
Who can care about you?
That...
Brother Sun, Sister Shu Wen,
is Brother Kong here?
He didn't come.
i thought
he will be together with the few of you?
No.
Where can he be
if he's not here?
Everyone, don't panic. Don't be anxious.
Maybe he just want to
be alone.
I think I know where he is already.
I will go look for him.
Qiu Ying.
No,
why are you going?
She's alone,
how can I not be worry?
Wait for me.
I'll get going too.
Bye bye Brother Sun, Sister Shu Wen.
Wait for me.
Like this,
I'll go take a look at the hostel.
Shu Wen,
everything will be fine.
Thank you.
About relationship,
it can't be forced.
I'll support you.
Thank you.
Previously, there was one night,
she was here waiting for you until midnight.
She really like you.
Give her a call.
Why don't you call?
Qiu Ying.
What happened?
Why are you like this?
Its Mi Ya's fans?
Just some juice only.
Sorry, because of me,
you became the enemy of the world.
So what?
Xiang Kong.
During this time,
your hard work at Wei Teng,
everyone witness it
but this matter
have a big negative impact.
The sponsors...
President Li, I know.
As a leader,
the disclosure of the tactics,
I should bare the responsibility.
Okay.
Xiang Kong,
if you need any help in future,
you can voice out.
I'll try my best to help you.
Thank you President Li.
If there's nothing else,
I'll leave first.
Okay.
Sister Wen.
Let's go, I'll send you off.
Xiang Kong,
this is for you.
Sister Wen,
looks like I still earned.
This is what I kept
the first time
I went to Vancouver for competition.
No wonder when I hold it,
its heavy.
Sorry,
I failed to protect you
and leave you behind.
Sister Wen,
I should be the one saying sorry.
I said I'll give you
a perfect team.
I didn't do it.
But a perfect team,
I believe I'll find it
one day.
I believe you.
Leader.
I heard you're leaving,
I came to send you off.
How is it?
Want to play a round with me?
The only person that
admire you in the whole Wei Teng
is him.
Get going.
Let's go.
What you doing?
Brother Shen.
How is it?
Can't bear the thought of him leaving?
Why not you leave with him?
No Brother Qi.
I'm just casually taking a look.
Right, go get drinks.
How is it?
Can't play the electric gram,
went to play basketball is it?
Oh yes,
you still can dance.
I'm not sending already.
Bye bye, see you.
Don't care about them.
Actually in Wei Teng,
the person that can't bare you leaving is Tong Wu.
Before you came,
nobody realised his
advantages.
So he can
make a brother like you.
Xiang Kong,
in my entire life,
I don't admire much people.
You're considered one.
Do you think I'm very fake?
Just because
you have this energy in you,
I then admire you.
Its this real energy of yours,
nobody can beat you,
its pretty good.
Maybe
leaving Wei Teng is better for you.
I just don't know
when
can I play basketball with you again.
If you're willing,
any time is possible.
You said it,
its a deal.
Its a deal.
Why are you here?
I'm here to do my duty as a girlfriend.
I'll help you hold.
No need.
Why not you hold this for me?
Brother Sun
asked us to go eat at The King.
I told Brother Sun already,
we'll go other day.
Today, I want to bring you somewhere.
Where?
You'll know when you reach.
So secretive.
Shu Wen,
I have made an appointment with a sponsor,
let's go meet them.
You settle it yourself.
Shu Wen,
sorry,
I was too anxious that day.
Now its Wei Teng's
crucial moment,
I need you.
I want to resign.
What do you mean?
I'm tired.
Shu Wen,
you can't because of some small matters
and be emotional, you know?
Until now,
you still think
what happen between us is a small matter?
The biggest problem with us
is the different in views.
If you can solve it,
it wouldn't be
how it is like today.
You want to
leave Wei Teng
or leave me?
Li Gan,
I have operate Wei Teng
together with you for so long.
All your contribution,
I remember them in my heart.
Just that now,
I... I don't know
what I want.
Shu Wen, its been so many years
I've stick by your side.
Everything,
you say east,
I will never go west.
Everything
goes according to your plan,
according to your steps.
But in the end I realised,
you have never love me before.
Li Gan.
Can you please calm down?
How do you want me to calm down?
How?
Is it because of Sun Zhe Yi?
Enough.
Wei Teng
I return it to you.