Your current district server ranking is 735
You don't have to remind me
According to my current level
let alone the champion of Tomorrow's Star
I am not qualified to be a waiter
in MengLvRen
I just want to say
the ideal is full
the reality is very harsh
Do you want to think twice about
taking part in the competition?
No, I don't
I can do it
No, are you serious about this?
When have I ever made a joke?
If I want to improve
my professional knowledge quickly
I must acquire it in practice
Start
What are you going to start?
Practicing the hero
Sister, it's half past twelve
Crazy, really crazy
All right, you do it
I'll put on a mask
and go to bed
Sleep!
Here you are
Your natural delight
Ok, thank you
You suck at video games
Are you talking about me?
Try the mage
The mage?
Why?
Actually, I don't think
I'm good with shooters either
But if I use a wizard
which one?
I know you're the first mage
Or you can recommend some to me
The main thing is that
if I practice the mage,I have to start from scratch
So how do I fit the early inscriptions?
And you know what?
To the early and late stages
you say this outfit...
Is this for me?
Thank you
Puppie is so cute
Why did you give me a lollipop?
You talk too much.Eat!
Sort out the questions
and send them to me
The mage?
I think Xi Pei
used Zaowuzhe
Anyway, try it first
Sister, what time is it?
You haven't gone to sleep yet
You want to be friends with the panda?
I don't have much time left
before the game
I must hurry up
All right, all right
Then I'll go to bed first
Don't stay up too late
Go to sleep. Good night
You're amazing
XiPei teacher
These are all the questions
abot the Zaowuzhe that I'd like to ask you
Look at me
Look at the computer,not at me
That's the difference
between a pro and a rookie
Do you understand?
No, teacher XiPei
You were moving your hands too fast,
like playing the piano
and I was dazzled
Could you repeat it for me?
Watch the replay for yourself
XiPei, XiPei, XiPei
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
In order to thank you for your guidance
I would like to stay in MengLvRen
to help you make coffee,do chores
and do other chores
And I don't want a salary
I'm capable
You are not the first in the district
You are not qualified to be
a waiter of MengLvRen
XiPei, XiPei, I really...
I can do anything
Move the table
clean the table, sweep the floor and so on
I really...
Thank you
Here we come
Brother Kong
The Coach
Xiangkong
Are you prepared the materials?
So let's get started
Where is the Yao Huo?
I just had dinner with him
and he said he needed to
go out on something
Where is he going?
He didn't tell me
Leave him alone. Let's start
Everybody knows that
What Weiteng is best at
is four guarantees one tactic
As long as we can
arrest the development of XiPei in the early stage
we may win the game
I've prepared all of XiPei's videos here
so let's take a look
Brother Yao, You have come
Sorry, guys
I'm late
See the video
You've been in great form lately
Your contract with the Ledends team
is due to expire in two months
This is a contract for next year
Thank you,manager Z hao
Who thinks for the team?
who is capable?
who is really good?
The board and I
know that
YaoHuo
What do you think of
the choice of captain?
If the test match won
won't Xiangkong become the captain?
You, Xiangkong Ji
Yixuan Lin, Feng Lu
Of the four of you
you are the one I admire most
If gu fang hadn't insisted on
recommending Xiangkong Ji as the team leader
I would definitely
recommend you to the board of directors
Manager Zhao
My ability is also average
It's not about ability
YaoHuo
I'll tell you the truth
Time and tide wait for no man
You know
the golden age of the professional
is just a few years
Chairman Jin has been very thoughtful
about your furture development orientation
If you
continue to follow Xiangkong Ji
like this
I can't help you
A straightforward person does not resort to insinuations
You are a wise man, too
If you can understand
what I mean
Do you want to be the captain
or are you waiting so awkwardly
for the elimination?
When it comes to the test match
it's up to you
Don't let me down
I have something else to do. I'm leaving
XiPei
likes to fight alone
with a low participation rate
and little cooperation with his teammates
so this is our breakthrough
We need to harass XiPei
in the early stage
Very good
YaoHuo, say it
YaoHuo
Tell me about it
Sorry, coach
I'm a little off my head today
Brother Yao, do you have a fever?
No,I don't
If you don't feel well
go back to have a rest
Okay, I'll go home and rest
You guys settle down
I'll do it tonight
I'm sorry
Go for it
It's too difficult
What,did you see the handsome guy?
What are you doing here?
Yixuan Lin told me
that you stay here a lot
I was just passing by
and came up to have a look
I didn't realize you were actually here
So little food and sleep
Only forget to sleep, did not forget to eat
What are you looking at?
Xipei can do this wave operation
How do you know it's XiPei?
His operation can be seen
at a glance
Why are you looking at this?
He's teaching me how to use it
That is too harsh
He was obviously showing off his operations
How can someone like you learn?
I, I have to start early because I am poor
And you said
If you say I can, I will
So you come to
MengLvRen to study
I want to be a commentator
And I want to participate in
the competition of Tomorrow Star
so many masters here
I just can improve myself quickly
Don't rub your eyes like that
Have you been looking too long?
Don't look at it. He's hectoring upon you
and you can't understand it
Come on, I'll show you around
Go
Is someone calling me names?
Thank you
It's nice to have flowers
Do you think today is perfect?
Why?
Because I can go shopping
with a handsome guy like me at night
Why are you so narcissistic?
I have a million fans
Ok?
Seriously
the finals are coming up
Are you nervous?
Nervous?
How can you be nervous?
I could have gotten 90
If I add my thousands of fans
I can get 99 points
Where is the other one?
You, if you come
I'll get a full mark
Perfect
Am I only worth one point?
One point is pretty high, okay?
You're already my number one of fan
Can teacher Ji
tutor your number one fan?
No problem
I'll give you top secret tutoring
to ensure that you become a master
Come with me
What are you bringing me here for?
You'll find out later
Welcome to
the high-end snacks LiangPin shop
we have hundreds of high-end snacks
for you to choose from
thank you
Didn't you say you were going to teach me?
What kind of expert are you?
I think you're just lying to me
Just now
XiPei's operation, as you can see
What is the core?
It's fast, accurateand tough
That's right
Professional players in addition to the tactics
beyond the ordinary players
more important is the operation
that is the basic skills
But I play this game very late
Can I succeed?
Why not?
You're not playing IConquer
for a competition
You're playing IConquer to be professional
So you need to understand
the process
not just say it
Teacher Ji
you train me the way you train the pros
Ok
Today we have the first class
training hand speed and reaction ability
Five dried mangoes
Four boxes of pistachios
Pistachios, strawberry jelly
Hold it
Xiayi scallops
Five boxes of dried mangoes, quickly
I'm coming,I'm coming
Come on.    -1,2,3,4
Every hero
has his strengths and weaknesses
in the face of own abilities
beyond the scope
of the need for the cooperation of teammates
How do I feel like
you're not teaching me
but playing me
Doesn't what I just said make sense?
Ok, you're Xiangkong ji
You are a battlefield swindler
You're right about everything
Two bottles of orange juice
Hand speed
and reflexes were good today
Practice more
Next time I'll take you whack-a-mole
Is it useful?
It works for you
Well, here I am
Just walk me here
Here you are. Here you are
Is this for me?
Don't you girls like to eat these snacks?
Just don't eat too much
and get fat easily
Thank you
What do you like to eat?
I'll treat you some other time
I...
I like strawberry tea with milk
Isn't it?
As a big man
you like strawberry milk tea
Your style pf eating is too jumpy?
Believe it or not
Anyway, thank you today
You are welcome
Please feel free to ask me
any questions in the future
I'm an encyclopedia
It's no use
asking XiPei
who can only fight alone
Are you sure?
I remember a thing
You answered wrong all six questions
in the section where the name you ask me  to answer
XiPei...
That was a misunderstanding,okay?
Well, to make it up to you
I have prepared
two invitations for the test match
and I hope you can come here
I will cheer you on
I told you that
the millions of fans
cheering me on was only 99 points
The last point is yours
Well, it's getting late
Quickly go upstairs
Be safe on the road, too
Bye    -Bye
Oh my god
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Face still hot
Don't think too much
Don't think about it
Ying Qiu, you need to calm down
Need to calm down
Yiyi, Yiyi
Where did she go?
Oh my god
You scared the shit out of me
What are you doing here?
I saw it all
What do you see?
What do you think I saw?
Sending flowers to each other also
He is only on his way
Only you can believe that
He meant well
A girl like me
and still grow so beautiful
What if I meet a sex maniac?
Isn't it?
He looks like
the biggest sex maniac to me
Xiangkong Ji gave me
two tickets for the test match
Would you like to come with me?
This little sugar-coated trick
is just trying to impress me
I'm telling you
As long as I'm a firewall
he can't take you down
Firewall student
This is an industry event
Are you sure you're not going?
I don't go to there
To deal with
a philanderer like him
we must adhere to the three cardinal principles
Don't take a reason
Don't take the bait
Don't accept
That's right
This ticket won't help
And you're in that nursing home
like this big news
you just copy and paste
Where's the trash can?
Throw away,throw away,throw away
Wait a minute
I just figure it out
If I don't go
Xiangkong ji
will have more chance to close to you
No
I have to go there for you
Now, don't be angry
I tell you
I don't forgive you
Little angel
I'm not your little angel
I bought you
your favorite dried mango
Count you have conscience
You said you didn't want to come
You couldn't wait to get in here
Now that I'm here
just take some pictures
to pass the time
I'll go over there and have a look.
Yiyi Lu
Yixuan Lin
What are you wearing?
You come to see me play
and you should dress up
and put on a tuxedo or something
What I wear
is none of your business
Besides, I'm here to watch the game
I'm not here to see you
Why are you so narcissistic?
You talk to me well. Be respectful
I want to hit you again
Don't do it. Stop
I tell you
These are my fans
I have many fans. Do you hear me?
I don't watch it
No, you have to watch it
I have a seat reserved for you
Yiyi Lu
Yiyi Lu    -Go away
So busy
They are quarrelsome lovers
They'll be back in a minute
By the way, don't forget
what you're here for today
LiMao chairman
jiGuang video company executive
and Tian Luo teacher
the big names
in the industry are here
Won't you come up and get acquainted with them?
I don't know anything about this
How can I talk to them?
First time strangers,second time friends
Meet them more often and you'll get to know them
In this way
someone will label me as a vase again
I don't want to do this
In that case,are you worthy of
my invitation?
Thank you for the invitation
But
All right, I get it
Do it at your pace
I'm going to get ready for the game
Remember to cheer me on
Of sourse. Come on
Come on
Where did Yiyi go?
What's your relationship with Xiangkong Ji?
What?
I ask you
What's your relationship with Xiangkong Ji?
I...
We're just friends
Why do you ask?
Bacause I'm curious
I'm a little nervous.
A test match
What are you nervous about?
Can I not be nervous?
This game will decide
whether you stay as captain or not
How terrible
You're in no hurry. I'm in no hurry
It' ok
Take it easy. Play hard. Take it easy
That's easy for you to easy
Brother yao, what's on your mind?
You're not
as nervous as Yixuan Lin,are you?
No
I'm just not feeling well
You have a drink of water
What are you staring?
I'll unscrew it for you
I , I'll do it myself
You are very thirsty
Maybe I didn't sleep well last night
In this way, I...
I'm going to the bathroom to wash my face
I'll be fine
Row 1,seat 11
Such a good location
Did he arrange it specially for me?
The race will begin soon
Have a good performance
I'll never do you any wrong
Good evening
Welcome to
the IConquer new version of
the beta finals
I'm the host tonight
Tian Luo
Hello, everyone
I'm YingQiu, the host for tonight
YingQiu
One day
I will stand on this stage
Come on
First
I'd like to introduce you
to the IConquer series of heroes
Xuantian Warrior
Look at the big screen
Here are five new heroes
designed by IConquer
specifically for Chinese summoners
Well, they're Yubang
Axin, Zhihen, Jincan
GongxiChangqing
Their attributes
are made up of the five elements of China
They are formed by the interaction of
metal, wood, water, fire and earth
Yes
This design
is very Chinese
Their story
is also adapted from
the myth of Xuantian Warrior
which is
a unique benefit to Chinese fans
Yes, the Xuantian warrior heroes
will be a great historical innovation
at the IConquer of history
Today
Legends and Weiteng
will bring the first show of Xuantian warriors
So
are you looking forward to it today?
Yes
Well, no more talking
Let's bring out the two teams
Please welcome Legends
Weiteng
Ok, let's announce that
this new version of the beta finals
is now open
Please take your seats
Come on, come on
I just looked at it
About 70 percent of the people now say
Xipei will win
Of course
Why?
Wasn't Legends the runner-up
in the vancouver finals?
Legends without Fang Gu
gets much worse
The cooperation of group battle
is really too tacit       -Great
It's really a one-second judgment
Without mutual understanding
and absolute trust
So strong mid like Xi Pei
is difficult to be killed
You just said that
Legends would be much worse
without Fang Gu
Did I say that?
Ok
Because Xi Pei was killed just now
Now Weiteng
chose to open the fog to secretly shoot down tai lung
But Legends' false eye
has seen them fogging
They're in ambush here
Let's see
if they can sneak down the dragon?
The enemy has come
They're coming. They're fighting
This...No
What's the matter, Yao Huo?
His big move was way off base
That's too bad
What's wrong with Yao Huo?
Brother Kong
You retreat and defend the enemy
Let's retreat first
Don't fight yet,don't fight yet
Move it back
Brother Yao, move it back,move it back
What's wrong with you, brother Yao?
Okay, I'll go back. I'll go back
How did Legends feel so bad today?
We'll win, we'll win
Yes, yes, yes
Can we kill one?
We can't fight this group war
Weiteng has stormed
the final defensive tower of Legends
It looks unstoppable
They're going to break the crystal
No,brother Yao
What's the matter with you today?
Wake up. This is a private test match
This is the final game
Yao Huo has a problem
Yixuan
The second game is about to begin
Cheer up
Brother Yao, what happened to you just now?
Why don't you come on?
Brother Yao
We have so much
economic advantage
The win in the last game is in the bag
I'm sorry, guys
I didn't sleep well last night
In the last game
Yao Huo have problem
Maybe I was too nervous
I'm not in the zone
Then please stay competitive
for the next round
If we lose again
This is only a test match, brother yao
Our opponent is Weiteng
How many times have we beaten him?
I've been fighting with you for so long
When have I seen you nervous?
If we lose one more game,brother Kong will leave
Can you
improve your concentration?   -Stop
Now is not the time for argue about it
BrotherYao
You just need to adjust
Masters
What are you doing? One by one
Can you play well?
You don't want to win, do you?
Do you have any questions?
Manager Zhao, don't worry
What can happen to us?
YaoHuo
What are you nervous about?
Do you have any questions?
No problem
Be relaxed
You have to play well
It was up to you last time
Come on, everyone
Ok
The next match is about to begin
Let's go
Brother Yao
All right. We just lost one game
We still have a chance in the next game
Don't take on too much weight
It doesn't matter to me if I'm not the captain
the important thing is
to fight with the brothers
Don't worry, captain
In the next game
I will make no mistake
We have been brothers more than two years
I believe him
Ok, the two teams
are now in the second game
Now this is BP
I wonder what kind of hero
each side will choose
in this game
Yixuan, I help you pick
Gongxichangqing
Ok
Let's take a look
Legends first chose
Gongxichangqing
They chose Gongxichangqing. Oh, no
They must want to choose
The sup was robbed
this powerful sup hero for Xuanyi Lin
We chose Jincan