You want me to transfer to Chuan Qi.
Your contract with Wei Teng is about to be up.
If you could come to Chuan Qi,
I will give all the best resources to you,
and turn you into a Dian Feng king who’s stronger than Gu Fang.
Today, I come with 100% sincerity to discuss with you.
As long as you’re willing, I will accept anything. Really.
Who will be Team Lead?
Will it be Ji Xiang Kong?
According to you,we can go ahead and sign Pei Xi.
Of course. I closed it myself.
Plus your reputation and power in the field, it won’t be a problem.
Indeed.
Candidates who can replace a star
player like Gu Fang are few and far between.
Yeah.
Quickly get on it.
There’s one problem. He wants to be Team Lead.
This was his only condition for signing with us.
President Jin.
I think that this Pei Xi,
regardless of ability or reputation or future potential,
is a hundred times stronger than Ji Xiang Kong.
You said it yourself.
Pei Xi may very well be the next Gu Fang.
You don’t know this,
but once the news
of Ji Xiang Kong taking up the deputy Team Lead
role spreads,
the others will talk and think badly of us.
But the matter of Team Lead has been discussed
and agreed with Gu Fang.
If Ji Xiang Kong
wins the new inner competition, he will join us.
We can’t go back on our word.
President Jin.Gu Fang has left.
We can’t keep on protecting his feelings
if it affects our team’s growth and future.
Am I right?
Instead of keeping Pei Xi as a mighty opponent,
we should turn him into one of us.
What do you think?
Okay.
Alright, President Zhao.
Leave this matter to me. Bye.
Sister Xin! Your coffee.
Thank you.
Today’s temperature is perfect.
It tastes pretty good too.
If you like it,
I’ll buy coffee for you every day.
Earlier on, a
friend from an advertising company gave me a call
to ask for a model for a lingerie shoot.
You’ve shot commercials before, right?
You could be suitable.
A lingerie shoot?
This is your remuneration.
Three thousand?
I wouldn’t introduce you to a job
that pays a measly three thousand.
Now, all of the hosts in the company
are gearing up to the Dian Feng version.
You should know
about the Qiu Ying situation.
The show’s ratings have fallen through.
It’s a tough road ahead.
Your situation would only be worse than hers.
I heard that your prize money
has been deducted till next year.
I do urgently need money.
We always say that even the best of friends
are useless when you need help the most.
Those aren’t your real friends.
Yan Yan.
I am someone who tends to speak her mind.
People who don’t know me
think I have a bad temper.
Actually, I have a huge sense of justice.
I mean, you even call me Sister Xin. Right?
If you face any trouble in the future,
let me know. I’ll definitely help you out.
Thank you, Sister Xin.
You’re welcome.
Don’t be so polite with me.
Let’s go.
The Creator, without lightning speed,
will not be able to complete this combo attack.
Looks like Xia Tian’s cousin
is even stronger than Xia Tian.
I’m Pei Xi.
So?
Are you interested to join Wei Teng?
Why do I have to go?
You need a truly strong team
to help you win the world championships.
If this is because of Xia Tian, I don’t need it.
I’ve always spoken with my abilities.
I won’t risk the entirety of
Wei Teng because of Xia Tian.
Being strong alone isn’t strength.
After all, this is a team game.
All these years,Wei Teng has brushed the
shoulders of the winners.
So late? Who’s there?
It’s me. Yan Yan.
Coming.
Yan Yan!
Come in.
Come.
Why are you here
so late? What’s wrong?
Don’t change your shoes.
Come.
I -
I fought with my boyfriend.
I had nowhere to go, so I came to find you.
Did he bully you? Why didn’t you ring me?
I could have picked you up.
You could stay here tonight.
Sit. Sit.
Aren’t you cold dressed so thinly?
Are you hungry?
You haven’t eaten, right?
Shall I make you something to eat?
Alright, just sit there.
I’ll make you some noodles.
Qiu Ying.
I’m sorry.
I really had no choice.
Yan Yan. Do you eat chilli?
Sure.
I remembered that you did.
I’ll put in more for you!
Sure.
Yi Yi.
You’ve been with us for some time.
You still can’t quiet your heart.
Director.
I really, really want to do news.
Haven’t I told you?
Reorganise the other
news and find a unique angle.
This is a skill, too.
But -
Plus, the headliners won’t fall to small
magazine firms like ours.
My goodness.
Director.
There’s a headliner!
Pei Xi’s Live Hero -
Creator can achieve at least
three 5-kills in one game.
I’ve tested this hero’s abilities.
Its sudden explosions are powerful.
It can release heaven fire on the whole map
and harvest blood heroes.
This hero is really so powerful.
Why don’t I train on this hero?
Enough. You’re not Pei Xi.
I think Pei Xi and I are 50-50.
None of our individual capabilities are a match for him.
Yeah. That’s why,
no matter
which of us will meet him,
we shouldn’t think of anything.
Just run.
The strongest single?
I don’t believe we have nothing against him.
We do have something.
As the strongest single, teams against him
have a hard time winning.
But there’s a weakness too.
Do you know what it is?
Brother Kong.
You know?
I don’t, but come see this.
Come.
The later half of this video is fake.
Who made this?
What’s that?
Isn’t that me?
That’s me next to you!
You weren’t there.
It wasn’t like this at the time.
At that time, we were -
Stop laughing.
The inner competition is about to begin.
A video like this being released now
isn’t as simple as you think.
That makes sense.
Hello, Yi Yi?
Have you only just woken up?
I stayed up all night last night.
So you definitely don’t know
what’s happening right now.
What’s happening?
Quick, search for the keyword
Ji Xiang Kong. Hurry.
Who sent this complete version?
So many netizens are
saying that you uploaded the video.
How is this possible?
I was at the hotel parking lot.
This is different from what I saw.
Different?What do you mean?
I didn’t see Ji Xiang Kong hitting anyone at all.
Why would this video -
Are you sure? Think carefully.
I’m very sure.
Ji Xiang Kong only grabbed the collar of Jeffrey.
Looks like someone intentionally
framed Ji Xiang Kong.
That’s fine. This liar bullied you before.
He’s asking for it.
There’s karma for bad people.
What’s happening?
These netizens are so mean.
Look at this.
Qiu Ying, get out of the e-sports industry.
Don’t harm anyone anymore.
That’s harsh.
What about this?
He’s completely over the line.
Indeed,
once Manager Zhao attacks, the results are amazing.
Looks like we’ve achieved each other’s small goal.
Most importantly, it was seamless working with you, beautiful Qiao.
Then again, these netizens
think that the culprit is Qiu Ying.
Manager Zhao.
Don’t you think that her punishment is too light?
Great minds think alike.
I’ve already prepared her lawyer’s letter for her.
You’re brilliant, Manager Zhao.
Ah, yes. If you’re free,
shall we go for a meal later?
Of course. This is a cause for celebration.
Yeah.
But, Manager Zhao,
shouldn’t you head back to control the situation today?
Should I?
Yeah, you’re right.
I’ll send you back.
Don’t be so polite. Let’s go.
Manager Zhao.
What is it? Spit it out.
President Jin.
What happened?
Well -
It’s like this.
I’ve found the source of that internet video.
It’s the female host of You Xing,
the one who live streamed
Ji Xiang Kong and Jeffrey’s fight. Qiu Ying.
Manager Zhao.
Is this your guess, or is it backed by evidence?
Take a look, President Jin.
The video’s IP address
and Qiu Ying’s live stream IP address are the same.
I’ve confirmed it. They’re the same.
What does she want? What’s wrong with her?
Does she have something against us?
My phone has been exploding with calls today.
Everyone’s asking me
what relationship Mr Ji and Qiu Ying have.
Plus, it’s heavily rumored outside that our Mr Ji
has played with her feelings.
Stop.
I didn’t believe it.
I remember you and Qiu -
Qiu what?
Qiu Ying.
Yeah.
Haven’t you played doubles with her?
Yeah. I brought her down.
No wonder.
You brought her down.
She would take revenge, right?
Perhaps
Look. We’ll arrange for a press conference.
Apologise for the scuffle.
Also, clarify your relationship with Qiu Ying.
Xiang Kong, you have to protect your image against rumors.
Understood?
Everyone was present.
I didn’t hit anyone. Why apologise?
Plus, the video was clearly falsified.
If you have proof, Manager Zhao,
then sue Qiu Ying.
Let her prove my innocence.
I think Xiang Kong is right.
These issues should be solved by the law.
Otherwise, it’ll get more complicated.
President Jin.
I still need to go practice.
If there’s nothing else, I’ll take my leave.
Brother Xuan.
How was it?
Was it Qiu Ying?
Yeah.
I heard that Legal has sent her a lawyer’s letter.
Yi Xuan.
Don’t you think that Ji and Qiu Ying
are a little -
I don’t know.
I’m going outside. I know who to ask.
Brother Xuan. It’s full of fans outside.
I have a plan.
My goodness.
What’s happening?So many people.
No matter what, let me take a shot first.
I should somehow get Lin Yi Xuan
outside for some insider news.
Clever.
Lin Yi Xuan.
I -
-Let’s go. -What?
Let go!
Are you crazy?
No.
Are you crazy? What expression is that?
Let me tell you. I can’t take this anymore.
Yes.
Before, during the doubles,
it was Brother Kong’s fault for disconnecting.
But why would Qiu Ying take revenge like this?
Wait. -Why are you yelling? -Don’t push.
-Why are you yelling? -Don’t touch me.
What revenge? Our Qiu Ying did nothing of the sort.
Ji Xiang Kong bullied her,
and now he wants to frame her too?
Tell me. What revenge? What revenge?
Let me tell you what revenge is.
Tell me.
I’ll tell you. Qiu Ying wanted to use Brother Kong.
When she failed, she took revenge. That’s revenge.
Try saying it one more time.
Stop hitting me!
Today, you’re asking for it.
Don’t hit me.
-Stop hiding! -Stop hitting me!
-Stomp! -Ouch!
Ouch!
Stop hiding!
I’ll stomp on you!
Listen up. Our Qiu Ying doesn’t want to rely
on your liar Brother Kong!
She definitely won’t use these
stupid methods to take revenge.
She’s the kindest girl I’ve ever seen in this whole world.
If you dare to slander her again, watch out.
I might kill you!
Stand there!
What are you doing?
You -
No -
I didn’t mean that.
Don’t hit me.
No. I have proof, okay?
The IP address of the video uploader
is Qiu Ying’s live stream IP address.
What?
Chuan Qi’s lawyer has just left.
Look at it yourself.
The video uploading IP address
is the live stream IP address at your place.
They’ve got iron-clad proof.
That’s impossible, President Liu.
This is a setup.
Plus, even if I wanted to,
I wouldn’t be stupid enough to use my own computer.
You saying this doesn’t help solve the issue.
No, President Liu. Give me some time.
I’ll get to the bottom of this.
What’s there to check? All evidence points to you.
This is creating a very bad image of our company.
Do you understand? I am at my wit’s end.
President Liu.
You’re -
firing me?
If we don’t resolve this issue,
Chuan Qi will never work with us again.
We’re restructuring,
and we offend the strongest team in the mainland?
If you were me, what would you do?
I’m sorry, Qiu Ying.
I’ll ask Finance to send you this month’s salary.
We’ll throw in a month of severance.
I’m sorry, President Liu.
I’ve caused trouble for the company.
Sister Xin.
Taking revenge when dumped.
She doesn’t know what she looks like,
or if she has the capital.
I heard that Ji Xiang Kong isn’t a good person.
Birds of a feather. A perfect match.
Let’s go.
Captain.
You’re here, Brother Kui.
You’re practising.
I’m getting old.
I couldn’t take it after only two hours.
You’re the hardest worker amongst all of us.
We should all learn from you.
Oh, yes.
How did your problem go?
Don’t let it affect
your inner competition participation.
Sorry.
I’m causing trouble before the competition.
Ever since Gu Fang left,
I’m the oldest in the team.
You know, people like us
are in the golden age of professional e-sports players.
It only lasts a few years.
For me, it’s one fewer
competition every time I join one.
Ji.
I’m putting my life’s final hope to win
entirely upon you.
You and Qiu Ying -
Brother Kui.
There’s nothing between us.
I promise you
that I won’t let anything affect the competition.
Let me train with you.
Let's do it.
Ji Xiang Kong’s news are everywhere.
These netizens are so vicious.
But they’re right.
Ji Xiang Kong is so unlucky.
Unlucky?
If he didn’t ask for it, this wouldn’t have happened.
He asked for it.
If you don’t want people to know, don’t do it.
Look at what this netizen said.
China Dian Feng’s face is completely lost by you.
The Chuan Qi team is a complete mess.
It’s getting complicated.
Looks like resolution is tough.
I didn’t think that Ji Xiang Kong
would be fallen by a woman.
Isn’t that good?
The competition is in two days.
The fiercer the fight, the better.
We’ll win silently.
Look at this person
Handicapped in the competition, punching someone after.
And this -
I was speechless after reading it.
These netizens are heartless.
We’re interrupting Captain Pei’s training.
The training room isn’t a place for you to gossip.
It’s 6PM. Time’s up.
Let’s go.
Steamboat is on me.
Brothers.
There’s a training match at 9PM.
Four protect one.
We’re familiar, Captain.
You can win all by yourself, can’t you?
Thanks, Brother Qi.
We really haven’t had steamboat in a long time.
Let’s go, Lu Sheng.
Captain, we’ll be back before the training match.
Let’s go, Tong Wu.
Don’t disturb Captain Pei’s training.
Drink up.
No.
The video has been online for days.
He’s still hiding.
We’re Chuan Qi’s biggest sponsor.
We’ve put in so much money.
What do you take me for?
Yes.
President Bai,
Xiang Kong is in a training match.
At this hour, what training match is there?
No, President Bai.
They’re preparing for the inner competition.
Ji Xiang Kong is deputy captain.
Who let him be deputy captain?
I wanted a captain with a healthy image!
Isn’t this Ji Xiang Kong?
You’re really something.
What’s your relationship with Qiu Ying?
The net says you toyed with her feelings
and caused this revenge.
President Bai.
There’s nothing untoward between Qiu Ying and me.
Sorry.
Due to my carelessness, I’ve brought trouble to
the team and the company.
I’m deeply sorry.
I’m here today
in the hopes of resolving the problem.
How do we resolve the problem?
I want this issue to die down quickly!
The assault video on the net is clearly fake.
We can clarify it with the involved party.
I’m afraid Qiu Ying won’t -
I don’t mean Qiu Ying, but Jeffrey.
Jeffrey. That’s right.
If we tried to explain this ourselves,
the rest won’t believe it.
If Jeffrey can step up to explain it himself,
the video has nothing to stand on.
Yes, the assault was fake.
The conflict, however, was real.
We’ve already offended them.
Why would they step up to clarify matters with us?
Right?
Jeffrey is a very proud person
If he knew that everyone thought I could bully him,
he would step up to deny it.
Plus, he’s coming to China in a few days.
Really?
That’s great! Isn’t it?
Don’t worry, President Bai.
I’ll bring along my company’s most sincere apologies
to invite Jeffrey out to clarify it for us.
Calm down. Relax. Don’t worry.
We’ll have to trouble you then.
Of course, Manager Zhao.
Don’t mention it.
Shut the door.
When is Jeffrey coming? Check it out.
I’ve checked. Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Another obstacle suddenly surfaces.
This -
Manager Zhao, do you think Jeffrey will really step up?
I can’t say.
What should we do? Manager Zhao.
Let’s do this.
Go arrange more training matches for them.
If Ji Xiang Kong looks for Jeffrey,
no matter what you do, you have to stop it.
Got it?
Got it.
I’ll blow up the news on the internet.
A month later,
even if Jeffrey steps up to clarify things, it’ll be too late.
Clever.
Try this new tea, Manager Zhao.
No.
It’ll be okay.
I’m here.
We’ll wait for Lawyer Chen.
We’ll find a way to solve this.
Who is it? Why didn’t you read it?
Xia Ling.
Your brother?
He’s not my brother.
Even without blood relations, he’s still legally your brother.
Look at it. Maybe it’s urgent.
Sister. I saw the threads on the internet.
How are you doing?
I’m worried, and Dad is worried too.
See. Your brother cares about you.
Yeah. He does. If not for them,
I wouldn’t have become like this.