Episode 29
Xiang Kong.
Actually, I still don't really understand
why you wanted to reject Pei Xi.
You really don't understand?
Is it because you don't like the way
he plays solo?
It's not that I don't like it.
It's that it doesn't match.
But now, he
is the best player in all districts.
So many teams would want to sign him.
Yet, he's so stubborn about competing with you.
How hard to come by that is.
Pei Xi's personal awareness is too strong.
When he was in Legends,
Coach Luo talked to him before.
But he's still not willing to change.
Then you can help him.
You've also helped Tong Wu and Lu Sheng.
You mentioned before.
Everyone has their own flaws.
So,
I want him to be able
to see his own flaws.
Be sincere about
wanting to change.
Without a perfect tactic,
you can only succeed with a team
where everyone trusts each other.
But,
what if you rejected him in this way
and he really give up.
What do we do?
He won't.
With that personality of his,
once he made a decision,
no one can stop him.
Okay, don't think about it anymore.
Let's go settle Sun ge's situation first.
Sun ge.
Ask yourself
do you really not want to return to competing?
Don't you want to work hard once more?
Afternoon, 1:40pm,
flight GF2839,
travelling towards Singapore.
Hello?
Why are you going to Singapore?
It's not me, it's Shu Wen.
Looks like she really doesn't intend
to tell you.
Did she tell you about the
situation between her and Li Gan?
No.
Then, right now, I'll
clearly tell you.
She already told Li Gan clearly.
After leaving VNG,
she'll be going to Singapore
for a study exchange
She's going overseas to study?
That's pretty good.
Pretty good?
Bro, after she leaves,
we don't know when
she'll come back.
Boss, I'll take three computers.
I have things to do here.
I'll hang up first.
Hello?
Gu Fang.
Is everyone here?
Right now, what
rights do I have to keep her?
Xiang Kong.
Wen jie.
You can't bear to part with me this bad?
That you must have breakfast
with me before I leave.
There's still three more hours
until your departure time.
After we finish this breakfast,
if you still insist on
going to Singapore,
I gurantee that I'll send you
to the airport on time.
So, there was another motive.
but that's a pity,
over here, I
have nothing that'll make me reluctant to leave.
Take care,
have a safe trip.
What kind of boss are you?
Running out just like that.
You're not going to look after the store?
I helped you greet
the customers.
Saying you had some family matters.
So I closed the store earlier.
You...
Aren't you in the plane?
You only messaged me
after the plane has departed.
Looks like you really
don't intend to keep me.
Sun Ze Yi.
That year when I first saw
you playing on the competition,
I started liking you.
Do you know that?
My family chased me out the house.
I was thick skinned and followed you.
And you?
How could you
leave me and the team
just because of
Li Gan's RMB 300,000?!
This thing...
Let me explain.
Tell me.
I don't want to hear it now.
Follow me to a place now.
Hurry.
That year, after we won
the championship,
we bought this place
Although the team disbanded later,
but no one was willing to sell this place.
This place,
became like our home.
No matter how long you leave,
you'll always be the Founders's big bro.
Do you still remember?
You had the most fans.
After every competition,
your fans
placed boxes of
drinks for us.
The drinks the fans sent back then,
were all secretly finished by Summer.
Let's go in and have a look.
Dear audience,
you can see that Sun Ze Yi
is making a prediction without a field of vision.
Making a prediction without a field of vision.
What a powerful move.
And he collected the opponent's kills.
Too amazing.
Sun Ze Yi defeated three people alone.
This is a move similar to those in
professional educational books.
Sun Ze Yi killed many opponents.
He's currently escaping.
He's escaping from death.
Okay.
Sun Ze Yi turned and killed the opponents chasing him.
Sun Ze Yi killed many opponents.
Wait a minute.
Look at his position.
He's currently turning around.
Sun Ze Yi has entered.
The Founders's chance is here.
Sun Ze Yi!
Sun Ze Yi has started catching.
Start catching the kills.
Quintuple kill!
Sun Ze Yi got the quintuple kill!
Big bro!
Big bro, we're still here.
Big bro, where have you gone all these years?
Big bro, we're here to send drinks.
from Conquer's competitions.
Big bro, you've never been forgotten
Big bro.
All of us are here now.
You owe us a championship.
That's right.
Why did you all come?
Thank you, thank you guys.
Big bro.
The one who should be thankful
should be us.
Big bro.
Without you,
there won't be the Founders.
Big bro.
stage five years ago.
You were missing from the champion
It's the biggest regret in all our hearts.
Sun Ze Yi.
Do you still remember our team's slogan?
Not scared of the rain and wind,
swords pointing to the king.
What are you hesitating for?
Fire of desire doesn't extinguish.
Rebirth after death.
This is what you used to encourage me.
I'm using these eight words,
as the slogan for Phoenix.
Join us.
Sun ge.
I, Sun Ze Yi,
I'll work hard once more
for you guys.
Amazing.
Fire of desire doesn't extinguish.
Rebirth after death.
Thank you for today.
What's there to thank me for?
I heard Summer ge said,
you arranged everything today.
You were the one who looked for the fans.
He's such a blabbermouth.
Anyway,
I must thank you brothers.
Thank you guys.
For allowing me to find the first member of Phoenix.
I know you rejected me.
But I still want to join Phoenix.
This competition season
other than Phoenix,
I'm not going anywhere.
What if Phoenix
is really unable to accept you?
No matter what position you give me,
I will do my best.
No matter what position?
Yes.
If it's training partner,
are you still willing?
Okay, it's decided.
I'll be Phoenix's training partner.
The five of us
have finally gathered today.
That's right.
Usually we're missing either you or you.
Shouldn't you guys thank me today?
Yes, thank you.
Should I introduce a girlfriend to you?
With your taste,
I don't trust you.
Summer, you really
have nothing nice to say don't you?
Let me tell you.
Summer ge.
Let me toast to you.
Today's incident
is done too reliably.
No, from what you said,
am I not reliable previously?
No, you've always been reliable.
You know how to sweet talk.
Ge,
ge.
No.
What did you call me?
I'm calling you ge.
Don't.
Everytime you're this affectionate,
I feel that it's not something good.
I want to use Dream Journey
as Phoenix's training ground.
You haven't even joined the team.
Why are you helping them?
I am part of Phoenix now.
I am officially announcing now.
I am Phoenix team's
training partner.
Ji Xiang Kong.
You're letting my brother be a training partner?
No, Summer ge.
Let me explain.
About this, he-
I'm willing to be a training partner.
As long as I can enter Phoenix.
You rascal.
Have you become dumb?
Did he hypnotise you with drugs?
Since when I have that ability?
Enough.
That's really enough.
Pei Xi already said he's willing.
Then just let him join.
That's right.
Phoenix
is lacking a training place now.
Why not we gift them
our training place?
Why not... Dream Journey...?
My god.
My brother is becoming a training partner.
Adding on Dream Journey...
Everyone tricks their fathers.
This guy is tricking his brother.
Forget about Dream Journey.
Xiang Kong.
I want to represent the founders
and gift you guys
with our training ground.
How's that? Does anyone have opinions?
No, as long as it's not Dream Journey.
Of course, I have no opinions too.
I don't, I'm too happy.
Here.
This.
Is gifted to me.
For our Phoenix team
to win championship someday,
let's cheers using tea.
Come. Okay.
- Fighting leader!
Fighting.
- Fighting!
Thank you leader.
- Fighting.
- Xiang Kong.
Ah Xuan.
Yi Xuan, you're here.
Yi Xuan, come.
Have a seat.
Hello leader.
Hello Sun ge.
Hello teacher Luo.
Hello Summer ge, hello Shu Wen jie.
I- I bought some fruits.
I don't know if it's enough for everyone.
You're pretty obedient.
Leave it here.
Kong ge.
You formed a new team?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why is Pei Xi here?
I am now a member of Phoenix.
You called him but not me?
Do you think that he's better than me?
Ah Xuan, you're mistaken.
We didn't tell you
because I know
you will definitely support us. Right?
Besides,
right now we still can't afford
your transfer fees.
The termination fee.
I paid for it myself.
Ah Xuan.
Stay at Legends.
You'll be able to enter the worldwide finals.
If you join my team,
is like starting over again.
Such a huge risk.
I don't want to bear that simply.
Then, Kong ge.
My
biggest dream in this lifetime
is to compete together with you.
And become champions together.
Termination fee.
I will think of a way too.
You guys don't have to worry.
Ah Xuan.
Forget it.
You know about his temper too.
Let him calm down first.
We'll look for him again.
And discuss slowly.
Rascal, you really don't know how to speak nicely.
I'm speaking the truth.
I wouldn't know if it's the truth?
You've all come down to send me off.
Don't need to be so grand.
Shu Wen, don't leave.
Head up first.
And help big bro
clear the place.
You guys haven't met for so long.
The rest of you.
Be more obedient.
Leave quickly.
Leave.
I'm leaving.
Return home quickly, bye bye.
Be careful of your safety.
If there's nothing else, I'll go too.
I'll go send master off.
Okay.
Master.
Travel slowly.
I've already watched this week's commentary.
Overall,
you've improved a lot compared to before.
Really?
I'm still worried that I
was too busy the past two days.
The commentary was a little rushed.
It's hard being captain right?
You have to learn a lot.
And still have to lead the whole team.
If you have anything you want to say,
you can ask me anytime.
Don't worry.
If the disciple has issues,
you, the master, can't run away.
Right.
The leakage incident.
I'm still investigating.
Once I have news,
I'll let you know firsthand.
Actually, whether or not it's investigated,
It doesn't matter anymore.
At least,
I got to meet such good friends.
The things I learnt at GDV,
will also be helpful for Xiang Kong and the team.
Okay.
Having a girlfriend like you,
Ji Xiang Kong is really blessed.
I'll leave first.
Sun ge.
It's getting late.
I'll leave first too.
Why are you laughing?
Wen jie, I'm leaving.
Sun ge, bye bye.
- Bye bye.
Wen jie, bye bye.
Be careful of your safety.
Okay.
When you're home, let me know.
We're leaving.
Your group of bros.
All left one by one after eating.
I'll head upstairs and clear up for you.
Shu Wen.
Don't clean up anymore.
You're also tired now.
It's late.
I'll send you home.
What do you mean?
You're chasing me away?
No, I don't mean that.
In the afternoon,
didn't you say
you wanted to explain?
Then, tell me.
I want to listen now, speak.
I thought too simply back then.
I thought
after we were champions-
You still have the cheek to mention that?
Do you know
the night we became champions,
I cried for the whole night?
At that time, I was really upset deep down.
I was alone.
Alone outside.
Without you by my side,
what's the purpose of the championship?
Everyday that you were in Vancouver,
I know it all.
I asked someone to take care of you.
But until the end,
you're gone.
The moment I lost you,
I realised
I don't have a chance to find you again.
Shu Wen, sorry.
Do you still love me?
Throughout all these years,
other than you,
no one else has entered my heart again.
Sun Ze Yi.
You are a jerk.
Come.
Let's start.
Wait a minute.
What are all these?
It's very dirty here.
Thank you.
I don't need it.
Pei Xi.
Why not let's do this?
If you really think it's dirty here,
you can go to the yard outside.
And wait for us a little.
And once we're done cleaning,
then we'll call you in.
Okay?
No.
Okay.
Xiang Kong.
Pei Xi is willing to be a training partner?
If not?
Where would I get the ability?
But Pei Xi's ability
is highly anticipated.
In order to enter Phoenix,
he's even willing to be a training partner.
Yet, you don't want to accept him?
It's a pity that currently, he
isn't my best choice yet.
We're finally done.
I'm almost done here too.
Done cleaning up.
Food is ready.
Come down and eat.
I was wondering what smelt so nice.
I'm so hungry.
I feel like it's tasty.
I'm excited.
Let's eat.
It smells good.
Delicious.
Thank you Xiang Kong.
For allowing me to return to this place.
Sun ge, why are you thanking me?
You belonged here originally.
Right, Sun ge.
Are you willing to room there for now?
Yes. I used to room there.
Okay.
Then you'll still room there.
And then I'll stay
in the room beside the practice room.
Pei Xi, pick a room.
Where are you rooming?
Me?
I'm fine with anything.
I'll room beside Sun ge's room.
Okay.
Help me to shift a bed.
I'll room with him.
No.
Why are you rooming with me?
This way, Qiu Ying will be jealous.
That's right.
Okay.
Then I'll move it myself.
I must stay with you.
Pei Xi.
I will be jealous that way.
This...
- Pei Xi.
Why's he rooming with me?
You're practicing?
Don't look at me.
I'll be nervous if you're watching.
Why are you doing that?
Ignited walking stick, how pretty.
It is pretty.
But it's useless.
It's more effective when multiplied.
You need at least three or more.
I don't care, what matter is that it's pretty.
Look, how pretty.
Like a firework.
You like fireworks?
Which girl wouldn't like that?
Everytime there's fireworks,
there's that feeling
as if the whole world is lighted for me.
Then right now,
don't you feel lighted?
Xia Ling,
when are we going to play Conquer together?
That's right.
You're a professional.
When will you carry us?
Son.
Are you hungry?
Come, eat something.
I'm not hungry.
How can you not be hungry?
You didn't eat much this afternoon.
Quick, be obedient.
I want to be alone, is that okay?
What's wrong?
He still doesn't want to eat?
The transfer window
is left with less than a month
before it's closed.
Let's find people quickly.
Actually, I feel that these few
are pretty good.
Why not
you guys reconsider them?
And they're all
the top few players in the country.
This.
Have already agreed to join us.
We'll reconsider.
Actually these people
aren't unique.
It's a suggestion, you don't have to listen.
But our current situation is
one,
we can't give them a satisfactory salary.
Two,
we're a new team.
Being able to attract the country's top players
is already pretty good.
If not,
call them and we'll try to match.
But I think what Pei Xi said is right.
These people aren't unique.
They're not the ones we're looking for.
That's right.
There's someone.
You might be interested in him.
Who?
Let's check.
ID 409.
In half a month, he rose quickly.
He's always winning.
Now he's 4th in China.
But,
this person is pretty mysterious.
Everytime I message him,
he doesn't answer me.
And no one knows his identity.
He's online.
Do a 1V1 with him.
Let me try.
Let's try with your account.
Anyway, everytime
I send him an invite,
he rejects me.
Let's wait and see.
He's willing to battle.
You're still more attractive.
Let's try playing a round with him.
He thought his outfit through.
exchange for experience.
At the start he used, draining items to
He's good.
Seems like he's something.
He's pretty good at 1V1.
And he's flexible in his dressing and weapons.
Has his own traps.
And he can steadily collect economy.
The results are good.
So easily defeated, you don't match Qiu Ying.
Looks like he's your fan.
Come,I'll talk to him.
Come.
Hello, 409.
I am Qiu Ying.
Let's wait and see.
409, I'm Qiu Ying.
Are you interested to meet up?
No.
He's not my fan too.
If I had the chance to meet him,
I definitely won't go easy.
I think he's pretty good.
Is there any way we can contact him?
I can try to find out at Dream Journey.
That's right, you can ask your brother.
He's not replying anymore.
Hello?
Ying Zi,
do you have time now?
I want to talk to you about Xia Ling.
What happened to Xia Ling?
Did something happen to his leg again?
Have a seat, let's talk.
What happened to him?
Yesterday, when we videocalled,
he said he was fine.
He was lying to you.
In future,
he can't play basketball anymore.
The main nerve on his calf is damaged.
He can not do any vigorous exercise anymore.
He's scared that you'll feel guilty.
So he didn't let me tell you.
Then,
how about walking on daily basis?
Walking on daily basis.
That shouldn't be a problem.
It's just that now,
he still has to use a crutch.
Does he have to use it for his entire life?
No.
The doctor already said
thankfully he's still young.
The recovery will be quick.
Now, what's most important is
there's issues with his attitude.
Issues with his attitude?
It's exactly like
he's completely changed.
He's hiding in his room everyday,
refusing to come out.
He talks less than three sentences with us daily.
His classmates came to look for him,
he refuses to meet them.
Me and your Auntie Xia are really worried.
We have no idea what to do now.
He's still so young.
He's suffering from the set back now
but what about in future?
I thought about it.
I'm afraid he'll only listen to
the things you say.
Why not you convince him?
I'll go now.
Don't go now.
Auntie Xia is at home.
Why not tomorrow?
Let me tell you, Ying Zi.
If you leave this house,
don't ever come back.
You're here.
Quickly come in.
Is Xia Ling awake?
He's at home.
How about this? You
can talk to him first.
I'll go out first.
How many times have I said
can you let me be alone-
Jie.
Why are you here?
Can I go in and have a talk with you?
Sure.
My leg is healing.
Can you stop acting strong?
Have you decided
to stay in this house forever?
Is it dad
who told you something again?
Xia Ling,
did you decide to keep it from me forever?
Jie, don't read too much into it.
I'm pretty good.
I know.
No matter how much I blame myself or feel guilty,
I can't change reality.
But I really hope
you can pull yourself together.
And change back to
the cheerful boy from before.
I will.
Don't worry.
How can I not worry when you're like this?
Right.
The tactic leakage incident,
has it been investigated?
The organising committee
is still investigating.
But I've already
resigned from GDV.
I formed a new team with Ji Xiang Kong.
You're playing Conquer too?
Why not
I bring you to see the new team.
Ji Xiang Kong and Pei Xi are all there.
If there's anything you don't know
you can ask them, okay?
No.
Someone with an injured leg like me,
can only cause more trouble.
Xia Ling.
Come, hurry.
I was still worried
it'll be cold if you came later.
I'll pour some vinegar for you.
I ordered your favourite Siew Mai.
Come let's eat.
How's it?
Have you talked to him?
He still shut himself in.
I wanted to bring him out.
But he's unwilling.
It's good enough that he even talks to you.
But don't be too worried.
Once I have time,
I will come and see him.
Did you resign from GDV?
How do you know?
The incident
was pretty popular online.
After you resign,
is it true you can't be a commentator anymore?
I'm forming a new team with Ji Xiang Kong now.
About the leakage incident.
I will definitely investigate it well.
Someday,
I will go back to commentating.
Then,
is Ji Xiang Kong your boyfriend?
Pretty good.
He feels pretty stable.
Different from what others say.
You're also at
an age where you should have a boyfriend.
In future, remember
observe more, personality is most important.
Got it.
I have to go get some vegetables.
Hurry, eat more.
I'm leaving.