[Gank Your Heat]
[Episode 3]
You guys finally
gotten the champion after participating
in Iconquer for so many years.
It's not easy, congratulations.
Losers.
If we are losers just because
we lost a match,
then haven't you guys
been one for many years?
The champion is still ours next year.
Where's Gu Fang?
Is he hiding under his blanket crying?
-Talk nicely.             -Don't be rash.
Isn't he very strong last time
when he used the Spirited Princess?
How did he become
so so so so useless?
Who are you saying?
Ji Xiang Kong attacking someone,
and it's Jeffery.
Hey Jeffery,
stop.
Stop.
Get on the van, all of you.
What are you guys doing?
Still not behaving yourselves even at overseas. Hop on.
Sister Xin.
Sister Xin,
your review
for Iconquer just now
was done really well.
It's no doubt the first
host in You Xing.
Everyone, don't you agree?
Yes.
Without you guys,
supporting me behind my back,
I wouldn't be
able to be where I am today.
How about this,
I'll treat you guys coffee next time.
How about it?
Okay. Thank you, Sister Xin.
Based on how she talks, she's indeed number 1.
Not bad,
trending number 1.
President Liu.
Come on in.
Hurry, Qiao Xin, have a seat.
President Liu, what time is it now?
Aren't you going home yet?
Don't bother with those.
Here, do take care of your health.
Have a seat first.
Here.
How can I trouble you
with this stuff?
You see, our Iconquer page
is able to get it's first opportunity
is all due to your hard work.
Iconquer in the future
will be our company's
highly valued programme.
You'll have to work harder.
Don't worry, my programme usually is the first
amongst all programmes with highest views
but sadly, I'm down on luck.
Who gets to go to Vancouver
to interview was decided
through lucky draw.
Such a good opportunity
is missed just like that.
The life programme transfer some people over.
Boss have to be fair
so he had it drawn.
It's not nice of me to object right?
You say this Qiu Ying, she's
definitely incomparable to
you interms of professionalism and experience
but if there's a chance,
do help her more.
But you don't say,
she just sent me a video
on Legends and Tatan
getting into a fight
after the competition.
If this goes online, it's going to trend.
It's now trending number 1.
Our You Xing, gamer programme
is after all young
comparing to big
companies like Ji Guang.
This is not comparable
so we can only have suprises
on our content.
Qiao Xin,
I watched you grow up.
I have high expectations of you.
Ji Guang
has such top notch commentator like Luo Tian.
I hope you'll become
the Luo Tian of our company.
I won't let
your hopes down.
Qiao Xin is indeed Qian Xin,
I definitely see you well.
Let me appreciate this
number 1 trending topic a little longer.
Ji Xiang Kong, congratulations.
You're on the trending topic again.
Isn't it a usual thing
for us to trend?
Usual?
You fighting with Jeffery
just now, was filmed
and uploaded online.
See for yourself.
Who filmed it?
Even posted it online, there's no morality.
Someone named Qiu Ying
under You Xing.
Do you guys know her?
You guys just hope that your Manager Zhao
is able to settle
this issue properly.
Otherwise,
punishment will be waiting for you all.
This Ji Xiang Kong,
I can't get through his phone.
-His phone is always off.          -Qiu Ying.
Yan Yan.
Welcome our great hero home.
Do you know?
The moment you posted the video
yesterday, the views rose up to
number 1 online.
Number 1?
I surpassed Qiao Xin?
Yes, it's a sensation
in our company.
President Liu is very happy.
Go look for him quickly.
He's waiting for you.
Okay, I'll head up first.
Where are you going?
I'm... I'm buying something to drink.
Do you want anything? I'll get it for you.
Did Qiao Xin get you to buy her coffee again?
We are colleagues anyway.
I'm just helping her on the way.
Yan Yan, you can't be so weak.
I'll teach you a way.
I guarantee she wouldn't
order you to buy her coffee anymore.
Let's go.
No,
why isn't there anyone?
Is there no work today?
Shouldn't there be fresh fowers and salutes
to welcome us?
We are at least still the first runner up.
Second in the world okay?
Nobody cares about the second.
So practical?
This society is this practical.
Everyone must be tired,
unpack your stuff
and rest well.
But coach, where do we place the trophy?
-Put it at the achievement shelves.         -Okay.
Bye, coach.
I'll head out for a while.
Help me put my luggage back.
Don't enter my room.
If you were to make
my room a mess,
you'll sleep in the training room.
No, Brother Kong,
it was pretty harmonious
when we were dorm mates.
Talk to me about harmonious
when you have
pack up your pig sty.
Aren't you also staying...
Let's go.
Qiu Ying, you're back.
That's great, congratulations.
Thank you.
Qiu Ying.
Yi Yi,
you're awesome. Number 1 on the net.
It's also your credit too.
How?
Isn't Qiu Ying awesome?
Our Qiu Ying is back,
isn't it?
President Liu.
You did well this time round.
Nice work.
Here, give her a round of applause
as encouragement.
Thank you President Liu and everyone.
You've worked hard this time.
Here, clet's have a chat on the results
this time round.
Okay.
I'll go get busy first.
-I'll wait for you at home.          -Wait for me.
All the best.
Hello.
Hello, manager Zhao.
Xiao Xin Xin.
It's regarding the video that filmed
the conflict at the carpark.
I have something to say.
This trip to canada
must be tiring.
It's okay, that's what I should be doing.
And I have many shortcomings this time
with my job,
I'm here to apologise.
It's nothing,
your performance is great.
This is your first interview.
Everyone do see
your hard work,
it's already perfect.
Thank you, President Liiu.
I'llcontinue to work hard.
All the best.
Oh, President Liu.
Will i bring trouble to
the company after I uploaded
the conflect video
between Legends and Tatan?
Totally not.
You're only reporting the truth,
you're not adding oil to fire.
The team will not
hold it against us.
-That's good.           -Don't worry.
Hello?
Hello, I'm Zhao Yang from Legends.
manager Zhao,
hello.
I'll ask you something.
Is there such person, Qiu Ying under your company?
Yes.
We do have such a person.
You should know then
about the video she uploaded.
Qiu Ying
is not back yet.
What to do?
Why not let's wait for her to return
so I can understand the situation better.
Don't give me bullshit.
You better settle
this matter well, otherwise
wait for my lawyer's letter.
Do you hear me?
No, Manager Zhao,
don't get angry just yet.
President Liu, did I caused
trouble for the company?
He said it's a bad influence
so he will nnot accept
our interview in the future.
How about
I go and explain to them
and apologise?
See if it's able to be resolve.
You don't have to go, don't worry about it.
The company will settle this issue.
I remember
Qiao Han and Manager Zhao
has a good relation.
She can settle this issue.
Also, about trending number 1...
Technically, our company
will give a sum of money as reward
but now,
we are revamping out programmes
so I'm in a lot of stress.
Let us talk about
the cash reward next time?
if only Ji Xiang Kong arrives earlier
in that operation just now,
it wouldn't be like this.
He's known for being a crippled,
what do we do?
Is there any free instant noodles here
today, Boss?
Yoou're already the world's first runner up,
you're still here to eat my instant noodles.
Bos,, the computer hanged.
Coming.
Xiang Kong, wait for me upstairs.
Qiu Ying, I'm done with my stuff.
How about you?
What reward did President Liu gave you?
No reward.
If the issue is not settled,
I might even need to compensate.
Why?
Don't film on the streets
if you have nothing better to do.
Don't you think that you can
do a random broadcast just because you thought it was something big.
Just in case,
you cause trouble to the company.
Okay, we know.
Yan Yan,
I told you to get me coffee.
Why did you take so long?
Here's your coffee.
I wanted ice removed,
why did you get something so hot for me?
I... I... I forgot.
What's this?
It's so disgusting.
This is the cafe's new release,
it's called Sea Salt Butter Beer Coffee.
I bought you a cup
thinking that you'll like it.
Is this even for human?
You can't even do a simple
task Sister Xin asked
you to do.
Look how angry you made her.
She still has to host later.
Right, Sister Xin?
I'm... I'm... Sorry, Sister Xin.
I'll definitely buy the
flavour you like next time.
I'll definitely not
hold you back for your hosting.
I'm sorry, Sister Xin.
Sorry.
I don't need you to
buy me coffee anymore, do you hear me?
So stupid.
Why is she so stupid?
She said I don't need to buy her coffee anymore.
That's right.
Is Gu fang still okay?
Why don't you ask about me?
Aren't you
used to getting scolded?
Why didn't you change tactics?
Gu Fang's condition is clearly not okay.
I mentioned to let Brother yao
to switch with captain.
but Zhao Yang and Coach Luo
doesn't agree.
It's not bad.
Huo Yao goes to mid
to contain Jeffery,
you guys have a 80% chance to win.
Gu Fang is unwilling to?
I didn't tell him.
He's almost 30,
he doesn't have much time
in this battlefield.
If Gu fang were to retire,
what do you have in mind?
I really hasn't thought of this question.
Truth to be told,
it's all thanks to him
that I'm able to stay in Legends.
Don't you forget,
what did you say
when you were taken
away from me.
How could I forget?
Getting the champion is my dream.
You'll go on forward
with Gu Fang's and
mine dreams.
Brother Sun, I'll be really stress
if you say that.
Afraid now?
Are you backing out?
I heard
Manager Zhao from your team
don't see you in the eye.
It doesn't matter if he don't see me in the eye.
He have thoughts
on earning money only.
Scheduled us to participate
in commercial events
one after another.
He doesn't dare do anything
when captain is around,
I don't know
what it'll be like
after captain retires.
Here, big host Qiu.
Congratulations. You gained fame in a single battle.
Don't laugh at me anymore.
Producer Lu,
you're spot on.
The days of eating grass awaits me
when I'm back
from this impromptu trip.
It's okay.
I didn't ask you to return me the money right?
I'm... I'm not rushing
you either.
No hurry.
Our Yi Yi is
still the best to me.
Of course.
Because you're my favourite.
Hurry, eat up.
Eat more, you're too skinny.
I'm famished.
It's not bad.
Right? It's nice right?
Oh,
the day you went Vancouver,
the car booked by the company
went to the train station instead.
You guess, what happened?
Is there still a need to guess?
Must be Qiao Xin's doings.
You say Qiao Xin,
doesn't put her energy
into work
but thinking of pranking others,
how despicable.
Forget it.
I have no energy to even
think about her now.
Right, don't mention her.
Do you know, Yi Yi?
This trip to Vancouver
brought me many touching moments.
That moment when the competiton was lost,
I saw many fans of Legends
crying.
I almost cried myself.
Although I don't understand what's going on.
Then why did you cry?
I was touched.
Then,
I followed Legends to the bar.
I saw Gu Fang
sitting in a corner drinking.
Then he told Ji Xiang Kong
something.
That moment, I suddenly understand
that to many people,
it's not just a competition,
it's their dream.
I know,
you're a person with dreams.
So when you see people who are similar to you
out there,
you definitely
can't help but to relate to them.
Actually, I'm quite envious of them.
They'd do anything for their dreams.
They can just cry out loud if they fail,
unlike me.
Ever since my Dad married that woman,
my biggest dream is
to have a house of my own.
So I work my life off to earn money,
work hard for my job.
I used up all my savings
to pay for the
down payment of this house.
This house
is a promise I gave my Mother.
So no matter what, I have
to secure this job
at You Xing.
Right, Yi Yi.
I suddenly
have a new thought.
Since I chose this job,
and I got transferred to gamer programme.
I must be a professional host
that understands my job well.
It's good to have dreams
but I have to remind you that
on the road to success,
there's many obstacles
waiting for you.
Even if there's no obstacles,
there's many things
that's different from what you think.
Forget it.
Enough said.
I'll go get some fruits.
Who are you calling?
That damn Ji Xiang Kong
from Legends.
I've been calling and texting
him from
Vancouver till now,
but he's not picking up
or replying my text.
Wait, you mean Ji Xiang Kong?
No,
what's the situation between the both of you?
Why did you have his number?
He took my Mother's necklace.
From now on,
I'll call him every
half an hour.
If he doesn't pick up
by tomorrow morning,
I'll go straight down to Legends.
I must get my
necklace back.
How did he get hold of
you necklace?
it's a long story.
Get off.
You kicked me?
Who asked you to sleep in my room
and even placed you feet on my pillow.
This... This is your room?
No, that...
Your phone kept ringing yesterday night,
I came in to check on you.
Then, I fell asleep.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
You continue to sleep.
Go back to your room.
NO, don't move.
Don't you move.
I can claim rewards if I can continue my dreams.
Claim rewards?
If you don't go back,
you'll be sleeping in the training room.
No, don't be fierce.
Are you going back or not?
I'll leave, okay?
Come back.
What do you want now?
Wash up my pillow.
Stubborn enough.
How many calls did she make?
That's right, it's here.
Hello, who are you looking for?
Hello.
I'm looking for Ji Xiang Kong.
Did you book an appointment?
No.
You must be a fan.
You can't enter without appointment.
Is he in today?
I'm not too sure.
Why don't you wait for him outside?
Okay, thank you.
Qiu Ying.
You are?
I'm Lin Yi Xuan.
I'm a member of
the team, Legends.
I know.
I've seen you during the competition,
it was wonderful.
Really?
I watch your broadcast too.
Really? Such a coincidence.
The one where you ate worms was really nice.
The one where you guys didn;t get champion
was splendid too.
You're here to apologise right?
You know how much trouble you've
caused Brother Kong
after you upload the video
of them in conflict.
Yes.
Didn't I came specially
to apologise?
Because I thought it's more
sincere that way
so I came specially.
Can you bring me to Ji Xiang Kong?
Sure.
But do you dare to go?
Of course.
Thank you, Brother Xuan.
Welcome, follow me.
You place is pretty big here.
Of course.
I'll tour you around.
This is one of my
favourite hero.
-Brother Xuan, all the best.             -Bao Di.
Brother Xuan.
Both of you stop playing.
So noisy.
Yi Bo, pass me a bootle of water.
No need.
Give me the bag,
it's not for you.
Here, give it to me.
Let's go.
Zi Xuan and Xiao Yu, work well.
Stop gossiping.
Stop playing games there.
Go back to work.
Okay, Brother Xuan.
Brother Xuan, you're impressive.
I'm already very conservative.
Here's the history of our team.
Everytime I walk pass here,
I get emotional.
Whhy don't I see you?
Look carefully before saying.
This are the trophies
won by our team.
This few are won by me.
Of course, it's only a portion.
Rest are in the storage area.
I know that one,
it's the one where
you got first runner up.
I sa wit with my own eyes
when the trophy got handed over.
I was so touched.
Here,
is the best place
of our team Legends.
It's our training room.
Seems awesome.
Of course.
All our equipments are
world's top notch.
These are the brothers from
the training team.
They are practicing their basic foundations.
You professionals
have to practice basic foundation?
Of course.
Basketballer
have to practice how to dribble a ball too.
Ding Guan Sen,
you worked too hard.
Remember to rest okay?
Be mindful of your body.
Guys, buck up.
Let usshout our slogan.
Come.
It's the Legends calling...
We never give up,
it's the Legends calling.
Everyone is so passionate.
It's about done.
That's the gym.
We could've reach by just
coming up from there,
yet you made me walk such a big round.
Are you playing tricks on me?
No.
Go on in,
Brother Kong has ben in there for a long time.
Let me tell you,
Brother Kong is a very nice person.
You just have to
beg him a little,
he'll definitely forgive you.
He must be thirsty after gyming for half a day,
give this to him
and melt his heart.
He's clearly the one
that tricked me multiple times,
why do I have to beg him?
Thank you.
Don't you know it's rude to not
knock the door before you enter?
What are you here for?
I...
Why did I look for you for?
What are you doing?
You came looking for me,
how do we talk
if we don;t get closer?
wear your clothes properly
before talking to me.
My clothes are on?
You...
You call me 50 over times last night
and came looking for me today,
what do you want?
Sorry.
I uploaded the video
where you had a conflict with jeffery
online,
I've caused you trouble.
Also, I filmed you and Gu Fang
without permission
so please me maganious
and forgive me.
Then,
return me my necklace.
So you apologise to me
just to get back your necklace.
don't go.
What?
I'm in a body of sweat,
At least let me shower first
before talking to you.
Sure, go ahead.
but don't you run away.
Okay,I won't.
Wait for me at the cafe beside.
What are you wearing?
Here,
put this]s pink romeo on.
I guarantee you to have her.
Still have her?
What taste.
Act, continue acting.
She's already here at Legends.
Don't think that I don't know
what's going on.
You're sweet enough to
prepare a gift for her.
I did not.
Act.
Yes, look for it.
Can't find it right?
Don't bother, It's with me.
Give it to me.
Wait.
Tell me clearly,
which state are you guys at?
There's not state to talk about.
What state?
I have to return it to her.
Give it to me, quick.
I saw this necklace
when we were in Canada.
You're still telling...
Enough, give it to me.
You don't...
Lightly.
It's pretty fragile.
Brother Kong.
Brother Kong, I...
Did I screw up again?
What do you think? Leave.
Okay.
Is there a need to be shy?
Here, your coffee.
Useless.
Anxious?
First you left you necklace in the car,
then you gave me your number.
Based on dramas,
it should be a
prefect beginning.
Not bad.
Ji Xiang Kong,
do you really think
I left my necklace
in your car on purpose?
Okay, I admit
I lied to you that day.
I got close to you on purpose
but I'm not so munipulative
to leave the necklace in your car.
I came today
to get back my necklace.
Return it to me.
Thank you.
Why is it broken?