[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 22]
Okay,
once again, congratulations to two contestants
for entering the finals
live commenting segment.
Coming up next,
the screen will randomly play
Dian Feng Competition's
exciting moments
for two contestants
to comment.
Okay.
First, let's welcome Qiao Xin
to
comment.
Let's welcome Qiao Xin.
Thank you everybody.
I'm going to start
my commenting.
Not long after the game starts,
Bei Xi is
defeating
Lu Sheng.
It causes Lu Sheng's
creator
to be unable to develop.
Now the competition has started for
eight minutes sixteen seconds.
The situation in the competition
has
a drastic change.
Pei Xi,
due to the advantage in economy,
want to kill Lu Sheng.
However end up fainted
by Lu Sheng's
"extreme cold" skill.
For luckily, Pei Xi reacted fast
and chose to fall back
and retreat to the tower.
Surprisingly,
the conservative Lu Sheng
have suddenly
become a changed person.
Went up to the tower and kills.
Two members from Chuang Qi Team
came in time
to protect and support.
Lu Sheng's attack is very powerful now.
CEO Guo, how is it?
Your You Xing have a talent.
I think
she's very likely to become
the female Luo Tian.
Defeated.
The help from the two Chuang Qi team members.
Luo Tian,
how is it?
Lu Sheng is fighting against three.
Not too bad.
Using on clever movements
he avoided Chuang Qi Team.
Miss Mi Ya,
what's your comments?
I'm came here
having the attitude to learn.
I don't really understand game commenting.
But based on what we see now,
I feel that Qiao Xin is not too bad.
Help Qi Yue to achieve triple kill.
Thank you everybody.
That's the end of my commenting.
Very excellent comments!
Thank you Qiao Xin.
Dear audiences,
how do you feel
about
Qiao Xin's performance just now?
Is it good?
No!
What about the popularity...
Based on the audiences here,
the live voting shows that
Qiao Xin is still
the number one.
While Qiu Ying is number two.
The difference between both is also getting bigger.
So
who will be crown as the
winner?
Okay,
Let's welcome Qiu Ying
to give us
the live commenting.
Let's welcome her!
Qiu Ying fighting!
Don't be nervous!
Hi all the gamers,
welcome to the
the live of the autumn match of Dian Feng.
Since the start of the autumn match,
VNG is in
long dark moments.
Under the pressure,
VNG have made a
very bold decision
by changing the front Lu Sheng
to the middle position.
In the first match,
VNG lose.
The second match is starting soon,
could they change the situation,
let's look forward to it.
VNG's double moon team
choose to avoid the fog and go to the river,
at the beginning of the game.
What does that mean?
Let us look
Lin Yi Xuan is here.
Looks like VNG knew about
Lin Yi Xuan's move beforehand.
They started.
Shen Yue's second level skill
have trapped Lin Yi Xuan,
Qi Yue back that up
one blood is done.
This move is really beautiful
and have helped VNG
to develop their advantage in the early stage.
After the short peace,
VNG's double moon team
started to attack
the lower route.
Both used the same tactics.
First, Shen Yue controls Lu Feng,
Qi Yue
uses skills to kill Lu Feng.
At this moment, Qi Yue
activate the speed skill
go over the tower and kill
in one breath.
This is a beautiful double kill
and have create the chance for
VNG's victory.
Bravo Qiu Ying!
Is everyone
very familiar with
this set of tactics?
That's right.
This used to be the double moon team
who dare to use an abandoned tactic
in such an important competition.
In the whole legend,
maybe only him
and he is VNG's
new team leader
who is known as the best tactic master,
Ji Xiang Kong.
Ji Xiang Kong,
went to VNG
with a yearly pay of $1.
With the pressure from the negative feedbacks,
he restarted the double moon team,
Just like VNG's motive,
Born with no fear,
strive for the future.
In this competition,
he made it!
He created a
brand new VNG.
With the hope,
strive for the future
to accompany you to the top of the world.
I believe you
you will reach the top of the world.
Then I hope that day,
its you standing at the commenting stage
announcing to the world that
our China team
is the world champion.
Does Qiu Ying really that understand you?
Xiang Kong,
how much did I missed
in your life?
I'm about to cry.
If there isn't so many people,
I will cry.
This girl is not too bad.
But I feel that
Qiao Xin
is more suitable for
our GDV's style.
Qiu Ying you are the best!
Qiu Ying fighting!
Fighting!
Qiu Ying!
Thank you everybody.
That's the end of my commenting.
That's very exciting!
Thank you QIu Ying.
Come, this way please.
Also, Qiao Xin
please come to the center of the stage.
Both commenting
are as exciting
and hard to say who's better.
Now,
I have the
final results for the
audience votings.
Qiao Xin,
have a slight advantage
and are slightly higher votes.
But who is the winner
for today
is still unknown.
So
according to our rules,
all the judges will have one vote.
If you are voting for Qiao Xin,
please raise the blue card.
For Qiu Ying,
please raise the red card.
Every judges votes
is equivalent to
hundred votes of the audiences votes.
Therefore,
all judges,
it's now
all over to you all.
This two-
Congrats Qiao Xin
for getting two votes now.
Okay, what about Summer's side?
Who are you voting for?
Qiu Ying, you are great!
Brother Xia Tian I love you!
Nice Brother Xia Tian!
Congratulation Qiu Ying for getting one vote.
What about Teacher Luo?
Who are you voting for?
Before voting,
I want to say something.
I couldn't find
any flaws
Qiao Xin's performance just now.
No matter from the tactics analysis,
or the judgement of the match-
What does he mean?
Is he voting for Qiao Xin?
Whereas Qiu Ying
from how she handles the details,
it can tell that she's more inexperienced.
This Luo Tian...
Qiu Ying has already
performed so well.
Where is the inexperience part?
Teacher Luo is too strict.
Do you feel that
Qiao Xin
is better too?
Profession is not just the skills,
and also attitude,
we, the commentators
is the bridge between the audience
and the industry.
If the commentator
couldn't present her passion,
how will the public
fall in love with
this new sports?
All those
youngsters who want
to be in this industry,
please remember,
if you does not have
the passion and the faith,
please do not step into this industry.
This is because its a hard path
and yet its a honor.
This is also
our motive
for organizing this competition.
To choose
the talent truly love
this industry.
So this vote
goes to Qiu Ying.
It's a tie now.
Qiu Ying's commenting just now
really make me feel
the passion she have for this industry.
Thank you Teacher Luo,
I will continue to work hard.
Okay.
So now,
both contestant
each gotten two votes.
Even though Qiao Xin's
votes are slightly higher
but the winner
is still an unknown puzzle.
The crucial vote
is in
Miss Mi Ya's hands.
So who would you
vote for?
Xiang Kong,
did you found my shadow
on her?
I have a friend
who really love
this sports.
She has friends from the game industry.
got to understand this sport very long ago
but given that,
I have never try to understand
how hard it is for the professional players.
Till today
after listening to the commenting,
then I realise
there's so many hardship and difficulties
behind these professional players.
So they really worth the
honor.
Thank you this stage
for giving the chance to understand it
within such a short time.
In this industry,
China also have a group
brave players.
So my votes goes to
Qiu Ying.
Excellent!
The winner of
Next Star
Competition is
Qiu Ying!
At the same time, congratulations Qiao Xin
for being the second runner up.
Welcome to
GDV's commenting team,
becoming Luo Tian's
partner in the new show.
Congrats.
Thank CEO Guo.
Thank you everybody.
QIu Ying!
Is it 120? Someone got knock down by the car.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Come, thank you, thank you.
Hi Mi Ya.
Hi Qiu Ying.
Mi Ya,
thank you for the vote.
Is your performance just now
worth my vote.
I always love your songs
especially
your top song in your new album,
Tian Kong Zhi Wai.
It feels like I am
experiencing the first love
whenever I listen to this song.
He is indeed my first love.
Here.
My new album as a gift for you.
Thank you Mi Ya.
You are welcome.
Do you want to come to
my new song release next week?
Of course I do.
But
I didn't manage to get the tickets.
It's okay.
I will save the best seats for you.
You can look for me at the backstage
before the start of the release.
Really? Thank you Mi Ya.
Can I take a photo
of you two?
Okay.
Okay Director An.
She's here.
Qiu Ying!
Yi Yi!
Qiu Ying you are so cool today.
You are so good Qiu Ying.
Is Qiu Ying someone
you can anyhow hug? No-
Qiu Ying's commenting just now
is so great and touching!
If who were to say that
I will immediately marry her.
Stop matchmaking.
You go one side.
No,
I'm just help my Brother Kong
to say out his inner voice.
You go one side.
Come,
let me get some
happiness from the winner.
Today,
you really amazed the crowd.
Let's go
celebrate at our usual place.
Let's go.
Let's go celebrate!
Come come come.
Let's celebrate.
Congrats Qiu Ying
for being the winner of Next Star
becoming GDV's
intern commentator.
Congrats!
Qiu Ying is the best.
I still feel like it's a dream.
I know right.
When Luo Tian is giving his comments,
my heart
is almost popping out.
Thank goodness,
at the crucial moment,
there's a twist.
Actually what really shocks me is
not just Teacher Luo
but also Mi Ya.
A big star like her
not just listen to my commenting
but also gave me her vote.
Also,
she gave me
an autographed album.
Mi Ya's album.
Ji Feng Xiang Yang.
Tian Kong Zhi Wai.
She signed?
Qiu Ying you are so privilege.
I heard that
the song, Tian Kong Zhi Wai
is written by
Mi Ya for her first love.
Yes.
I heard of this too.
What
What's the name of her first love?
He's called...
Ren Xu!
Yes.
Mi Ya ditched him after she got famous.
Why did I feel that this song
doesn't sound like it's written for Ren Xu.
This song
sounds like it's for lover
but also sounds like for family.
It's like they have been through a lot together,
supporting each other,
giving warm to each other.
No matter what we say,
this first love is quite sad.
He got to become the topic
when she release her new album.
So poor thing.
Right Brother Kong?
Enough,
stop gossiping.
Aren't we here to
celebrate for Qiu Ying?
Faster dig in.
Yes, let's eat.
Come, Qiu Ying eat more.
Eat more. Thank you Yi Yi.
Eat more meat.
Send this two tickets to Qiu Ying.
Ask her to find me at the backstage
when she come for the fan meeting.
Tony,
now you can tell me right?
Sister Mi Ya,
I shall go send out the tickets.
What did Xiang Kong
told you?
I don't believe anything
that you mention just now.
He agree
to meet me today.
Did you stop him?
Just the opposite.
He came to look for me.
Please wait a moment.
Mi Ya is busy.
You can tell me if you have anything to say.
Actually I came
to look for you
not Mi Ya.
What do you want to say to me?
Are you telling me
how you and Mi Ya
can't forget each other
and ask me not to
stop you two for being together?
No way.
How much effort we put in
for what Mi Ya
got to today.
I don't allow you to destory Mi Ya.
Great minds think alike.
Before you became her
manager,
I have witnessed
how many times she fails and her hard work.
She won't rest even if
she injures herself when dancing,
sing until her throat is sore.
This has all become a commonplace.
As long as there's chance to perform,
no matter if it's winter,
wearing thin clothes,
in the strong wind
she can dance the whole day
in the outdoor stage.
This is the dream that she have
been chasing for over ten years.
I have no rights to ask her give up.
Didn't you
think of that before?
On the day we break up,
I knew that
we will be
people from different world.
Please help me tell her
the beautiful past
is the best gift
for both of us.
Forget the past,
live the fullest now
I will give her my blessings.
Ji Xiang Kong is right.
Both of you are no longer
from the same world.
He have never thought of
reconcile with you.
Xiang Kong is just thinking of me
and doing his best to fulfill my dreams.
The more he say
the more I could not
give up.
Tony, I'm going to look for him now.
What are you doing?
Don't you know
the number reporters out there?
Do you really want to drag
Ji Xiang Kong into this situation?
Sit down.
Tony,
we used to be very poor
that we cannot even afford cup noodles.
It's Xiang Kong who
support me by
working part time in hunger.
It's him who beg the management company
to give me a chance.
Without him,
there won't be today's Fu Mi Ya.
So I rather give up everything
just for him.
I hope you can give me your support.
Mi Ya,
can you stop being one sided?
He has already
got someone he likes.
Let me tell you the truth.
He did not go backstage for you
but he was there to support Qiu Ying.
Do you know that?
Ji Xiang Kong has already
made his choice.
This is
just taken today by the netizens.
He and Qiu Ying
are celebrating at the BBQ restaurant.
Take a look yourself.
Congrats. Thank you everybody. Cheers.
What should we do later on?
What can we do?
Go home
and look for your own mother.
Just like this?
I still want to treat you
treat you all to sing karaoke.
Why are you so generous today?
Since when am I not generous?
Why did you...
Do you want to treat us
or just Yi Yi?
Qiu Ying.
Of course is you all.
Why should I treat her?
Ya right.
What's there to sing for the both of us.
If it's not you
who sang very happy that day-
Will you die not saying anything?
Xiang Kong,
thank you.
Without you,
I might not
be able to be the winner.
So-
Sorry,
I got to answer the call.
Why is he so secretive for the call?
Who is it?
I don't know.
I won't tell you even if I know.
Hello.
Xiang Kong, it's me.
I'm flying back
tonight
so I want to meet you privately.
I'm opposite of you.
Tony should have told you
whatever I want to say.
I don't believe.
Even if you doesn't
want to reconcile with me,
I want to hear you say it in person.
I got it.
Sorry.
I got something urgent suddenly,
I got to go first.
Ah Xuan,
send both of them back.
Okay.
It's okay.
If you have something on,
go ahead first.
Oh ya,
just now you say-
I have a gift.
Sorry.
Answer it.
He has been helping with your votes.
It's not easy for him.
Hello.
Why must you make your brother injure
because of your competition?
Do you know he met a car accident?
What?!
The doctors are still saving him.
Xia Ling
Xia Ling is now undergoing rescue?
Which hospital is he in?
Okay.
I need to go to the hospital first.
Don't panic, I will send you there.
Bills. I...I-
I will go too.
Yi Yi, both of them is enough.
This way, this way, this way.
Wear the helmet.
Don't panic.
Slowly.
Faster.
How is Xia Ling?
You still have the face to ask. You-
What are you doing? You-
How can you hit people?
It's my son in there.
It's not over
if there's anything that happen to my son.
Auntie,
we can understand how you feel
because of what had happen
but please calm down.
No matter what's wrong,
you can't hit people.
Who is the patient's family?
I am.
He needs an emergency blood transfusion.
However the hospital's A blood type stock
is not enough. What?
Such a big hospital
and you have no A blood type blood.
Are you joking with me?
Stop auguring.
What to do now, doctor?
Quick think of some solutions.
I'm A blood type.
Take mine.
Qiu Ying has my Brother Kong with her,
so don't worry.
Now Xia Ling is in danger
Qiu Ling will sure be very guilty.
Let me tell you.
Their two famailies
used to be neighbors
and their relationship was very good.
Xia Ling
will alway go Qiu Ling's house for meals.
The two of them
are really like real siblings.
But
why are they in so bad relationship now?
Not long after Qiu Ying's mom have passed away,
Qiu Ying's dad
married Xia Ling's mom.
You mean
her dad
were with his mom
when Qiu Ling's mom is still around?
How would we know
what exactly happened?
Yes, yes yes.
Qiu Ying
is always very stubborn,
she couldn't get along with Xia Ling's mom.
Her dad is between held up in between them.
Most of the time,
he sides Xia Ling's side.
Therefore,
once Qiu Ying move out of the house
and cut ties with her dad
at the year when
she got into university.
But Xia Ling
is a very sensible kid
who always feel that
is he and his mom
who destroyed
the relationship of Qiu Ying and her dad.
So he think of all kinds of way to be good to Qiu Ying.
It's not that Qiu Ying doesn't know
how thoughtful is Xia Ling
but she just couldn't bring herself
to forgive her dad
and
forgive Xia Ling's mom.
Therefore
she's quite cold
towards Xia Ling.
However
based on Qiu Ying's reaction today
it seems like she still
cares for this brother.
You just donated blood
your body needs more nutritions.
Come.
Be good, drink it.
It's been one night,
why isn't he out yet?
Don't worry.
He will be okay.
But today you
need to report at GDV.
You shouldn't be late on your first day.
Get going.
I will help you keep a look out here.
Xia Ling is not out yet.
I can't go.
He had the car accident
in front of the competition venue.
It's all to help to get votes.
He treat me with his whole heart
and how could I treat him like this.
I even went to his school to scold him.
Okay.
You didn't do it on purpose.
You can tell him
when he wake up.
Don't worry.
He will be fine.
Doctor, doctor.
How is my son?
You are patient's family member right?
The patient suffers from slight concussion,
fractured his right tibia,
too much bleeding that leads to shock,
but it's already fine now.
But
he needs to stay in the hospital for observations.
Thank you doctor.
All because of you.
You go!
Auntie, calm down.
Go away you all!
Qiu Ying is as hurt as you.
My son
still needs to join the basketball competition.
Go away you all!
Can you lower down your volume?
Son,son. Xia Ling.
Xia Ling.
Xia Ling wke up.
The car is here.
You better get going.
I ask you
tibia fracture
will it affect him
when he plays basketball in the future?
Don't worry.
He's still young.
He will recover very fast.
It's not early now,
quick go report at GDVs.
Thank you.
You have competition today right?
You been awake the whole night.
It's all my fault.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I will take a nap
at the holding area later on.
Whereas you
also got to find time
and take a rest.
Maybe tonight's competition,
I will see Teacher Luo
and you doing the commenting.
Fighting.
Get going.
Bye bye.
Teacher Luo
just now in the show
luckily you react fast
if not,
I might say something wrong.
Your performance
is not too bad
but
got to work on
your professional knowledge.
Teacher Luo,
Qiu Ying,
why did you just came?
Teacher Luo have waited half day for you.
Do you know the show
almost couldn't go on?
Teacher Luo,
sorry.
I have something on.
Don't say sorry to me.
Is your sorry
so cheap?
Being late is my bad.
I must apologize.
Professional players
will participate in the competition even if they are sick
this is what we call
sportmanship.
Same goes for our commentators.
Being punctual is the basic principle.
Don't think that
you can be indulgent after winning.
You does not have the rights yet.
Teacher Luo,
I will never
be late again.
Qiu Ying.
From You Xing to GDVs,
your lazy attitude to work
has never change.
Luckily
I am here today
to replace you for the show
if not,
there will really be problem
with this show.
You replaced me?
Yes.
You Xing and GDV
have a collaboration
so
from today onwards,
I will also be GDV's
intern commentator.
Xiao Zheng.
Teacher Luo.
You will be in charge of Qiu Ying
start from familiarizing the place
and setting up the set.
You can slowly pass on
whatever logistic stuff you have.
I will go back to the office first.
Teacher Xiao Zheng,
in the future,
if I have anything that's not sure
please help me along.
From Luo Tian's new partner
to becoming a member in the logistic team with me
what is all these about?
Let's go.
The competition is starting soon.
After so many competitions,
VNG's main member
Qi Yue,
can say is quite popular
and most likely
will become the MVP
of this seaon match.
Based on my understanding,
Qi Yue's
attack value for every match is 4.8,
every minute's economy
is 518.
While every minutes experience points
is 521.
It's a very good figure.
So let's
look forward to
his performance.
Let's continue to see
the two team's...
Okay,
your performance today is very good.
Fighting.
I got to go, see you tomorrow.
Teacher Xiao Zheng bye bye.
Why
didn't you explain to Teacher Luo
why you are late?
No matter you explain or not
it's stil the same.
It's my fault that I'm late.
Also,
my professional basics are not strong,
if I'm on the stage,
I might make a bigger fool out of myself.
Since I'm in GDV,
I'm not worry that there's no chance.
Don't worry.
I will adjust myself.
I know.
You are the cockroach that never dies
but you are also not
iron woman.
Don't shoulder everything by yourself.
But I really
doesn't want to create burden for others.
Because of me,
Xia Ling is still lying in the hospital.
Actually today outside the emergency room,
my whole head is all about
the images of us when we were young.
In my heart,
he is already
my brother.
But these few years,
I will scold him whenever he came to look for me.
The better he is to me,
the angrier I am.
The more I don't want to care about him.
You say
why am I so cold hearted,
so vicious.
Fool,
do not under estimate yourself.
You are the
strongest,
kindest,
cutest person I ever met.
Stop crying.
Dad, look how well my sister said.
A lot of people recoginize my sister
and all support her.
Dad,
this incident
is really not my sister's fault.
And my sister is so great,
I'm really proud of her.
Sister,
when did you came?
I just came.
Oh ya,
brought a lot of food for you.
It's all your favourite snacks.
Give it to me.
You two talk.
I go
and get some water.
Come,
let's see what's there to eat.
I remember
this is all your favourite.
Come, quick
eat it.
Is the injuries better?
Is it still pain?
I'm fine.
I'm a sport student.
These injuries are nothing much to me.
It won't affect the tournament.
Also,
there's so many good food,
who cares about the pain.
You must listen to the doctor,
don't panic,
rest well.
When you are having a match next time,
remember to tell me earlier,
I will ask all my friends to go
and be your family and friends supporters.
Family and friends supporter?
You are silly?
Sister,
don't worry too much for me.
You just enter GDV,
you must be very busy.
My classmates ask me
when my sister
will be partnering with Luo Tian.
I told them
it's anytime.
My sister is the best.
Sister,
I'm really proud of you.
For your words,
I must really fight for it.
I couldn't let my
brother
throw face in front of his friends.
Are you going?
You accompanied the whole night yesterday
and donated blood,
it's indeed time to go back and rest.
Get going.
Ying Zi,
Xia Ling's accident is not your fault.
What did the doctor say
about brother's injuries?
Say is to observe,
shouldn't be a big problem.
Why didn't you accept
the money that's transferred to you via wechat?
That's your allowance.
Accept it.
Go.
The doors are closing any time later.
Your competition video,
send it to me.
The one where you won.
Please enjoy it.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
Why are you free
to come here?
Why?
You don't welcome me?
I didn't have a proper farewell with everyone
after the Next Star competition.
You came at the wrong timing,
Brother Summer is not around.
It's okay.
You are around.
I'm not good at
conveying message.
Afterall,
we used to be colleagues,
must you be so cold hearted?
Brother Summer will be very happy
if he knows you are here.
Actually I came today
to have a
good farewell with everyone
and also thank everyone
for the care.
But I'm sure I will come here often.
I really like this place.
Do you want a cup of coffee?
Okay.
Seriously after so long,
I have not tasted
your coffee.
Just nice,
I invented a new item.
You will be my guinea pig then.
Teacher Luo.
Training materials.
Thank you Teacher Luo.
Oh My.
Teacher Luo's notebook as my
training material.
Teacher Luo,
did you regret?
There's a competition today,
you go and help out at the set.
Remember,
listen and learn.
Yes.
What's going on?
It's just one night
and Teacher Luo's attitude
to me has a 180 degree change.
Since you have already accept Qiu Ying as disciple,
why didn't you listen
to her reason for being late?
Since when did I say
she is my disciple?
If it's not disciple,
would you teach her?
If it's not for the love of talent,
would you scold her
because of a few supporting post?
Will you give her your vote
under the pressure of CEO Guo?
Can this be her reason
for being late?
Commenting stage is a
place which does not allow any disrespects.
On this matter,
if you really want
to help her,
then this is the end
of our friendship.
The supportive post are posted by her brother.
Because of this,
Qiu Ying blamed him.
In the end, he went all over
to help Qiu Ying get votes.
In the end,
he got into a car accident.
Qiu Ying is very guilty
and stayed in the hospital the whole night
and even donated blood to her brother.
She went back to the office
once her brother is out of danger
but she's still late.
Qiu Ying knows that
you don't like to listen to explanations.
So no matter if its supportive post,
or her lateness,
she didn't explain
anything for herself.
Teacher Luo,
she only has passion for commenting,
does not have disrespectful.
Darling,
you have entered GDV,
When can we announce that we are together?
We are in the company.
I just bcame
Luo Tian's new partner.
If anyone found out,
the impact is not very good.
We are
dating legally,
what's there for people to say?
You Xing and GDV
just collaborated
and they want
me to be the first female commentator.
For this,
I promise CEO Liu that
I will not be in relationship
to avoid any
disadvantages
and to portray my professional image
in front of the audiences.
You are a commentator,
not idol star,
why is there so many concern
just for dating?
Futhermore,
you are dating with
a professional player,
this will help your
situation right?
Commentators depends on profession.
Popularity
is not enough.
Furthermore,
if we expose
our relationship,
I couldn't join any competition
with you in it.
People will say its
favouritism.
You doesn't want this to happen too
right?
For your career,
I shall wait a while more.
Give me a hug.