GANK YOUR HEART
Episode Seventeen
Qiu Ying.
The online preliminary of Rising Star
requires to earn one thousand points in one hour.
The time is limited.
There's not enough time
even searching answers online.
Also,
if you miss one,
you have to start from the beginning.
Do you have confidence in this?
I have to be confident even I'm not.
Then, let's start!
Alright.
Are you ready?
Fighting. Fighting.
Don't be nervous.
Fighting. Fighting. Fighting.
All set.
Choose A.
It's correct!
Be quick! D.
Right again!
Choose C.
Quick. Quick. Quick.
B C. Choose B.
Choose D.
It's right!
You rock!
Right again!
Choose C. Choose A.
Yeah! CCC.
And this, choose A.
Good. Good. Good.
Ten seconds left for the last question.
What's the initiate Health Point for Jin Can?
Only five seconds. Be quick!
Three.
Two.
One.
Choose C.
You've got it!
You are so wonderful!
Let's see.
What's the rule for the preliminary contest.
Let me see.
All the people who get promoted,
in group of five,
answer questions on site.
Only the first can get promoted.
It's not a problem for you.
You even finished this one thousand points test.
At the site,
you just relax. Don't be nervous.
You definitely can pass.
But the questions at the site
must be harder than the ones online.
Can't you be more confident?
Sure.
Start to do more exerscise.
Alright.
I'll stay with you.
Get promoted.
Don't even tell your teacher Ji?
Just the preliminary.
You are so busy.
I am afraid to bother you.
I originally plan to celebrate with you.
If you say so,
forget it then.
Qiu Ying.
What are you expecting for?
Or,
why do you feel hollow at heart？
No matter how busy I am,
there is always time for a milk tea.
Ji Xiangkong?
Why are you here?
I miss
the strawberry milk tea at here.
Who knows that
I can accidentally meet
the ungrateful little apprentice.
It's not like that.
I am going to
the preliminary contest soon.
I'm a little nervous.
So I stop by to review my notes.
No matter how busy you are,
you need to take care of yourself.
You looked so worn out.
This is for you.
Your girls' favourite.
UNIFON facial mask.
Thanks!
You just
swotting up at the last moment.
Can you remember all these?
Let me share you a secret tip.
Ok.
What's the tip?
This secret…
What?
Secret tip
can't share with others.
Forget about it.
Who doesn't know
your little secrete tips?
The great captain of Legends,
Gu Fang, once said,
"This Ji Xiangkong,
no matter choose which heros,
only has four fixed modes.
They are
pretending not to see,
pretending can't hit,
pretending can't run away,
and pretending there is someone behind.
After all, this is
a textbook example of jerk." Keep saying.
You keep saying.
looking for a fight.
looking for a fight. My bad. My bad.
My bad.
You.
Why are you staring at me?
Can't I look at you?
When you become the best commentator later on,
I can only watch you on the screen.
Don't make fun of me.
No matter I can be the
best commentator or not,
if you want to see me,
I will come for sure.
Also, you said before.
We are brothers.
Ji Xiangkong.
You and VNG's coach, Shu Wen.
Do you have good relationship with her?
As a matter of fact,
we've known for many years.
But…
You have somethings else to do?
Today is the preliminary contest.
Then, let me
take you there quickly.
OK.
Thanks for your ride.
Be more careful when you drive back.
I am going there now.
Bye.
Wait a second.
You hair is messed up.
Later on, when you in the competition,
Don't be nervous.
Fighting!
I have faith in you.
I will try my best.
Bye bye.
You get fired up today！
It's fine.
Losing to me. It's not a shame.
This year,
CUBA,
We must be the winner.
Xia Ling.
Good job!
Not a big deal. Just normal play.
How is it? How is it?
Is the result released？
Right on time. See.
My sister gets through to the final.
Great. Xia Ling.
Let your sister give us few
tickets to the final. That's right.
We cheer up for her.
No problem. Everyone gets two tickets.
That's a deal.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
Hello, sister Xin.
Qiu Ying.
Congratulation
for entering
the final of the Rising Star.
Actually, if you are here,
I won't fell bored.
I am also glad
to compete with sister Xin
on one stage fairly .
But I heard that,
this time,
you can only win
with true ability.
Can't play little tricks.
Speaking of this,
I am really worried about you.
But it's fine.
Try you best.
I think high of you.
I already sent you the exam questions.
You will definitely be the winner.
Ok. Ok. Teacher Can.
I get it.
Thanks so much!
Want to compete with me?
Lu Feng!
Bad luck.
I am telling you. This doesn't count.
What doesn't count?
Doesn't count you win.
I have ran for a while before.
Who compete with you?
You didn't compete with me.
Then when I speed up, you also speed up.
What do you mean?
This is my regular running speed.
Is you the one who speed up, alright?
Can't stand you.
Ask you a question.
On the internal game,
Why did Huo Yao miss the hit?
If wasn't Zhao Yang, who wanted you to win,
played dirty behind to force Huo Yao,
will my brother Kong lose internal game
and drove away by you?
So everything
is Zhao Yang's conspiracy?
Do you really don't know all these?
I am telling you.
If you are here for one day,
I won't let you stay well.
So this is why you hate me?
Or should I like you?
Weirdo.
Wait. Where have you been?
Wang Bin and Zhao Yang
is cleaning up the things of captain Ji.
I heard them say that
they will throw away captain Ji's trophy.
They are looking for a fight, aren't they?
Gosh!
Throw all these for me.
This one.
This.
And this.
OK.
Especially this photo.
This one.
What are you doing?
Leave him alone. Keep throwing.
What?
Who let you throw my brother Kong's things?
He already left.
Things are in the way here.
Lin Yixuan.
This is the company's decision.
Release me.
Dare you to move. Try it.
Lin Yixuan.
I just let Wang Bin
throw some garbage.
Is it really necessary to act like this?
Wang Bin. Keep throwing.
Why are you beating? I am going to call the police.
I am calling the police.
Did you hear me?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Something wrong with you!
What are you doing?
Dare you insult him again. Dare you.
Pei Xi.
You are the captain.
Is this your teammate?
If he act like this again,
I can call the police to catch him.
Lin Yixuan. Don't act impulsively first.
Don't think I don't know that
you are in the same team with them.
You teamed up to drive my brother kong away.
Right now, you even throw his stuff.
Zhao Yang. You are a great bully.
You've gone too far. Do you know?
Lin Yixuan.
Things you don't know,
don't come up with a conclusion too soon.
You
find a place on the bench for one year.
Stay in the reserve!
Director Zhao.
It's not that serious.
I don't need you to say good words for me.
Stay in the reserve, right?
Will do.
I am telling you.
The last thing I need is a Support.
Pei Xi.
What are you doing?
I don't hope
when I leave the Legends,
all these will
be threw away by you like a garbage.
Not like that.
Pei Xi.
Director Zhao.
They.
Are you alright?
Brother Nine.
I want another drink.
I haven't had enough.
This way. This way.
No. No.
My gosh!
OK. I am here. Here.
What's wrong with you?
Why call me here at the middle of the night?
I have been waited for you for an hour.
I am going to die if you don't come.
Keep on.
You seem in high spirits.
You won't die in a while.
Do you have any human feelings?
I am like this.
You are still being sarcastic.
You had a fight? It hurts!
Who beat you?
Let me revenge for you.
Being beaten?
Today, Zhao yang's assistant
threw my brother Kong's trophy away.
I beat him to kneel down on the ground and call，
"Brother Xuan. Brother Xuan. Don't beat me anymore.
It hurts. I am begging you.
Let me go."
And then what?
Say focal point.
And then.
And then, I've been
switched to the reserve.
This season,
I can't go on the stage anymore.
Are you being stupid? It hurts!
Don't you think
I shouldn't have this fight?
Of course.
Give me a drink.
You're hopeless. Too stupid.
He threw sway. Can't you just pick them back?
Just because of this,
you've been dropped to the reserve.
You are so stupid. Hurts!
By the way, why you and Qiu Ying
being so loyal to him?
What ecstasy did he give to you both?
Being like a fanboy all the time.
If wasn't brother Kong,
right now,
I am still being bullied at the street.
Sorry. Sorry.
It's on my treat.
Don't give negative feedback, OK?
I don't care.
That's your business.
You are late, then that's a late.
The meal is cold. How can I eat this?
Wait. Don't throw it if you don't eat.
Lost your job?
How's that your business?
Do you still remember, two days ago,
we had a game at The King.
You lost.
You have to call me brother.
I lost indeed.
But why should I call you brother Kong?
I can introduce
a more suitable job to you.
How's that?
I don't want to be a network manager.
Who let you be a network manager?
Do you want to play the professional game or not?
The Legends.
Do you know?
The Legends?
Just take a hike.
Leave me alone. I am at work.
Alright.
I am leaving then.
Wait a second.
Call me brother Kong or not?
Brother Kong. I am ready.
When is the training?
Brother Kong.
A toast to you.
Let me see.
Can't believe that
this liar
can be so chivalrous sometimes.
I, Lu Yiyi,
toast to you.
He is still alive.
How can you toast like this?
Then you toast to a photo.
What do you mean?
Where's my phone? My phone?
Your phone.
You. You steal my phone.
My little Yingying
is calling me.
Hello. You. Where are you?
Have you drink alcohol?
I haven't.
Why are you drinking?
Drink less.
Send me your location.
I am picking you up now.
Come here. Come here to drink.
Stay away. Wait for me.
I am coming.
Thank you, master!
Qiu Ying.
Why are you here?
Lin Yixuan that guy is drunk.
I am picking him up.
What about you?
I am here to pick up Yiyi.
They stay together.
That's how it is.
Then I am relieved.
Let's go then.
Right.
The Rising Star competition.
How's your preparation going?
If you have any problem,
just ask me.
I'm just one call away.
Qiu Ying.
Wake up.
He just treats you as his brother.
Right now,
he and his ex-girlfriend are back together.
You have to keep distance from him.
No.
It's not necessary.
Aren't you preparing for the new season?
I am not going to bother you.
And right now, I work at MangLvRen.
There are many professionals at there.
They all can help me.
Why do you treat me as a stranger suddenly?
Did I offend you?
Or
you don't need me as your teacher.
Not like that. You think too much.
I just don't want to bother you.
You are too heavy.
You can't drink more than me.
Lu Yiyi, You can't drink more than me.
How much have you drunk?
Laughing like this. Brother Kong.
Brother Kong?
A toast to you.
That's my brother Kong.
You call me brother Kong?
Why have you drunk like this?
Qiu Ying.
Why are you still holding a microphone?
Qiu Ying. You are here.
I am here. I am here.
Why have you drunk like this?
You can't drink more than me, Lu Yiyi.
I am telling you.
Who can't drink more than you?
The great reporter Lu.
If I haven't got it wrong,
you just called me brother Kong.
Shouldn't I be a love rat in your heart?
Love rat.
Right.
You are a love rat.
Former sister-in-law.
You already have a girlfriend
and still play around with other girls.
If you are not a love rat,
then what you are?
She is drunk.
she doesn't mean this.
She has drank too much.
I am not drunk.
Former sister-in-law?
Playing around?
Shu Wen.
Lin Yixuan already told me.
Shu Wen is his
former sister-in-law.
Drink too much.
Wait. What do you mean?
No meaning.
She has drank too much.
I am not drunk.
Shu Wen.
It hurts.
The gossip of me and sister Wen online.
You even add more to it.
You guy, see how I am gonna deal with you.
See how I will deal with you.
No.
It's like this.
Sister Wen
is not only his former sister-in-law,
but also mine.
Sister Wen is my big brother,
Sun Zeyi's former girlfriend.
So the messy gossip online,
you thought it's real?
I finally figure it out.
That's why
you are so distant from me.
I am not being distant.
Also, the things online look real.
It's hard for me to not believe.
What if it's real?
So I need to keep some distance.
Of all my gossip girlfriend,
the one looks most real
is you.
Make some sense.
Lu Yiyi can't drink more than me.
Why are you so heavy?
Keep drinking.
Why have drunk like this?
Come. Don't fall down.
I want another drink.
What's wrong with you face?
Don't touch me.
I am telling you.
If you dare to touch my brother Kong's things again,
I am not done with you.
Not done with who?
Xiangkong.
Who is he not done with?
No.
Coach Luo told me that
Zhao Yang and Wang Bin
want to throw my trophy away.
He was so angry,
so he beat Wang Bin.
And then,
he has been switched to the reserve.
This punk,
sooner or later, will has this day.
He gets angry too easily.
Yes.
He still has two years of contract with Legends.
He can't leave there.
Coach Luo let me persuade him.
Who knows he drank this much.
Well, I
still have meeting tomorrow, this punk.
Then you go back first.
When he wakes up, I will talk with him.
Lu Yiyi can't drink over me.
Brother Sun. Sorry to bother you.
Don't worry. Go back first.
Don't leave. Keep drinking.
Leaving.
Want some water or not? Are you thirsty?
Who is Lu Yiyi?
Lu Yiyi is so beautiful.
Put your hands inside.
Lin Yixuan. Keep drinking.
Alright. Alright.
Go to sleep. Behave well.
Can't drink more than me.
You are the best.
He can't drink over me.
Keep drinking.
Have you arrived home?
Yes.
Is Lin Yixuan doing well?
He is sleeping
like a pig.
Right.
Forget to congregate you
for entering the final of the Rising Star.
An accomplished disciple owes her accomplishments to her great teacher.
You are finally back to normal.
Go to bed early,
good night.
Good night.
Bunny.
Do you know
that Ji Xiangkong doesn't have a girlfriend.
Shu Wen and he
are not in relationship.
Restrain yourself.
Do you know restraint?
What is restraint?
I don't know.
Even though
Shu Wen is not his girlfriend,
he doesn't necessaryly like you.
I think he likes me.
Otherwise,
Why he explained this to me?
If this doesn't show his feeling,
then what will do?
Am I right?
Go to sleep.
Qiu Ying. Fighting.
You must become
the commentator of GDV.
We've promised
to walk towards World IConquer together.
Ji Xiangkong.
You have to wait for me.
The rising Star.
I can make it!
Fighting.
Something interesting.
What a pity. It's a waste.
Haven't slept yet？
Ready to sleep.
Good night. Good night.
OK. Good night.
This is rich!
Good morning, captain.
Morning.
The breakfast for Qi Yue and Shen Yue?
Do you want anything, captain?
No need.
Tong Wu.
You finally understand my point.
Today's meal is wonderful.
Meat bun?
I don't like meat bun.
Buy vegetable bun next time.
There is no next time.
Later on, Tong Wu has no time
to prepare breakfast for you.
This period of time,
he needs to do an hour of extra practice with me.
Ji Xiangkong.
You do this on purpose.
Qi Yue.
Do you know how people
talk about you?
How they talk about me?
They say you rely on your identity as president Li's apprentice
to bully the newcomers.
Who says that?
Let him see me.
Brother Qi.
Easy. Easy.
Alright.
Eat quickly.
Meet at half past ten.
Tong Wu.
The morning practice starts today.
Don't have any burden.
You are not worser than anyone.
Captain.
I have something to ask you.
Before I come to the team,
What happened to Ji Xiangkong?
Why after he losing the game,
he has to leave?
You really don't know?
What should I know?
This is what happened.
After Gu Fang's retirement,
captain Ji made promise
in front of the board of directors.
If we loose the internal game,
he will leave team.
But the one who made mistake during that game
is you.
From emotion to reason,
I should be the one to leave.
But Zhao Yang
made the decision to drive him away.
Plus,
the only condition for you
to join our team
is to be the captain.
Having no choice,
chairman Jing had to drive captain Ji away.
The only condition for me to join the team
is to be the leader.
Who says that?
Zhao Yang emphasizes this to us all the time.
This is the only condition for you to transfer here.
Brother Summer, good morning. Morning.
Brother Summer, morning.
Morning.
You did well in the preliminary contest.
How is it?
Did you successfully become an apprentice?
Luo Tian, this guy.
You see, you look pretty
and also work hard.
I don't know what he is thinking about.
Maybe it's me
who is not professional enough.
You are not professional.
That means
my fellows at MengLvren are not professional.
When he arrives here, I need to ask him this.
Don't do that. Brother Summer.
I know you wan to help me.
But my professional skill is not enough,
There is no use for you to help me.
Alright.
You little girl has ambition.
Come here.
Tell me
how he refused you.
He told me
not to think about the short cuts all the time.
If I want to be a commentator,
I need to work towards the more professional field.
Saying these words
is not necessaryly a bad thing.
Why is that?
This means,
you already successfully
attract his attention.
He thinks you are
a promising person.
So he treats you
more strictly.
Really?
Really. Trust your brother Summer.
Alright.
I will definitely work harder.
Fighting.
Right. Right. Right.
If you have any question,
just ask Pei Xi quickly.
He will definetly explain to you with great passion.
Fighting.
Pei Xi?
Why?
Brother Qi.
Don't be angry.
Ji Xiangkong, this guy,
relies on sister Shu Wen.
He teaches lessons to whoever he wants.
The thing just now
will not end like this.
I am telling you.
The meeting later on,
both of us don't attend.
Let's see what he can do.
Brother Qi.
If you lose your temper at this time,
we are trapped by Ji Xiangkong.
What trap?
He is aiming at us.
Can't you see that
he is isolating us?
He is cunning.
Firstly,
He left the single room alone
and stay at Lu Sheng's room.
Secondly,
he stood up for Tong Wu today.
What does this mean?
This means he want to break us down one by one.
Continue to develop like this,
VNG
has no place for you to stand.
OK.
He wants to play.
We play with him.
OK.
But
we cooperate with him on the surface,
Especially in front of sister Shu wen.
It's not early.
Let's go to the meeting.
Sorry. Sorry.
OK.
Everyone is here.
Let's discuss
how to prepare for the fall competition.
Xiangkong.
During this time, I organized
everyone's data from the last season.
And plan the training schedule
according to everyone's characteristics.
Shen Yue.
Your position is not changing.
You are still the support.
OK.
Tong Wu.
You play the top and bottom lane with me.
Qi Yue.
You gave all your resource
to Pei Xi before
and still have such beautiful data.
Without extremely strong ability,
you can't make this.
Play jungle.
You definitely rank in top three of the professionals.
So
your position is not changing.
My position is not changing?
Then who can be the Mid?
Lu Sheng.
You are the Mid.
Me?
Lu Sheng was the Top before.
He often defends three enemies at once.
But his death rate during the game
is extremely low.
This is not easy.
After Pei Xi's leaving,
VNG's Mid,
under the premise of guaranteeing carry,
also requires highly stress resistant.
I think
Lu Sheng is able to play Mid.
Then you should respect him
and ask for his opinion.
Mid can't be played by anyone.
All the eyes are on him.
Lu Sheng.
Can you handle this pressure?
I don't want to play Mid.
Why?
I can't make it.
You have such low confidence in yourself?
Let's brother Qi play Mid.
After Pei Xi's leaving,
brother Qi is the one who plays Mid all the time.
We already used to this.
There is no need to change.
What kind of material I am,
I know very well.
Xiangkong.
Your hope to change VNG's current situation.
we all can understand.
But,
the game is coming up.
Chaning posiiton temporarily
is a huge risk.
And what's more is that
Lu Sheng hasn't played this position before.
Even when the best Mid, Pei Xi, is here,
he is not able to guarantee
success in every game.
You can see how tactical cooperation is
more important than individual ability.
If all of you think this has risk,
then we use the new plan
for a month.
After a month,
let's decide
who will be the Mid.
How about this?
OK.
A period of one month.
That's a deal.
Shu Wen.
Lu Sheng.
Except from the normal training,
Starting from tomorrow,
you play one hour of basketball with me.
Playing basketball?
How could he come up with this?
How's this related to the competition.
Why don't let us
dance with you?
You are the captain.
You make the decision.
See you tomorrow.
Hey. Xiangkong.
Brother Sun.
How's Xuan?
He has been driven away by me.
I let him go back to the team to apologize.
He refused to do it.
He said that
he wants to stay at reserve for two years.
Xiangkong.
Your leaving
has great impact on him.
Right now, he looks like
there is nothing to lose.
That's his characteristic.
When he gets impulsive,
a bunch of cows can't stop him.
Professional player
doesn't play games for a long time.
The competitive condition can't come back anymore.
I know this point clearly.
I don't want him follow my old path.
I understand. Brother Sun.
I will fix this thing of Xuan first.
Hanging up.
Quickly. Quickly.
No need to change shoes.
I am telling you.
I have to leave in a while.
Be quick.
Wait.
You call me here so rashly to…
Why are you standing at there?
So many words. Be quick!
Wait. Yiyi.
We. We. Aren't we two
a little bit
too, too soon?
I am not ready yet.
It's also my first time.
First time?
Didn't you tell me
that you are a computer expert.
You can catch
any computer hacker behind?
Computer hacker?
You call me here to?
Investigate Zhao Yang!
We two made a deal that night, aren't we?
Right. Check on Zhao Yang. Come. Let's do it.
Or why do you think
I am calling you to my home?
I am just here to investigate Zhang Yang.
Lin Yixuan.
What are you thinking?
I think of nothing.
Say it one more time.
Don't beat me. Don't!
You are such a rogue！
Don't!
Don't beat me!
I will beat you to death.
Qiu Ying. She is not here.
I am here for you.
For me?
New product.
Try it for free.
Free again?
Don't you earn one yuan per year at VNG?
This one
is on my treat.
Please.
Even my annual salary is one yuan.
A cup of coffee is still affordable.
Taste good.
Let me get this straight.
I am here for you today
to talk about the thing of Lin Yixuan.
He beat people.
I can do nothing.
You are the captain of legends.
Then what?
He doesn't listen to me.
I can't do anything.
The things of your teammates,
no matter big or small,
is related to the whole team.
You are the captain.
It's sure related to you.
With the capability of Legends right now,
even Lin Yixuan leaves,
The next Support
will be found soon.
That's different.
Xuan's idea on Support
is very clear.
It is not an exaggeration to say that
of all the national professional players,
if he says he is the second,
No one dare to claim the first place.
You switch him to reserve right now.
On the fall season,
will you have
a better substitude?
Even
he is as good as you said.
A Support that doesn't listen to command
is no better than a reserve.
Xuan seems
to be a impulsive person.
But he is not a bad guy.
He has kind mind.
Legends has lots of things happened recently.
He needs some time
to adapt.
Do you hate me as he does?
Hate is too serious.
I would like to consider you as
the most respective competitor at the game.
Do you really think Legends
needs Lin Yixuan?
You are the captain.
It's your business to make decision.
I just tell you the truth.
If you want to win the game,
it's necessary to have him.
Then aren't you afraid that,
after I switching Lin Yixuan back,
On the fall season,
you will lose to me?
The stronger the competitor is,
I feel more proud after winning the game.
Wait. Why today's conversation becomes Q&A session?
Any more questions?
The last one.
How do you think of me?
A team with you is invincible.
But
only at the first six minutes.
Only the first six minutes?
I am not done yet.
After the first six minutes,
it depends on what kind of competitors you meet.
If you are in bad luck,
meeting me,
then you will
fall on the seventh minute.
Arrogant.
I will prove it to you.
In this world,
the one who can beat me
is only myself.
Drink water.
How's that?
Almost done.
Investigation on Zhao Yang
needs to start from the video of the airport.
This is Qiu Ying's computer.
If we can find out
Who hacked her computer,
We can find Zhao Yang.
But,
this computer
doesn't seemed to be hacked.
How's that possible!
Then,
that faked video of beating people
is uploaded from this computer.
Qiu Ying is not the one who sent it.
Other than the hacker, who else can be?
In this situation,
normally, there is only one possibility.
What possibility?
Acquaintances commit the crime.
It must be Qiu Ying's best friend,
like you.
What are you talking about?
No. No.
I just give yo an example.
I didn't say it must be you.
Wait.
I think I know who that is.
Who?
Well. Coach Luo.
Lin Yixuan.
Come back for training.
If you are late,
I will punish you to be the reserve next game.
I can attend compete again?
Don't talk rubbish.
Come back quickly.
No. Caoch Luo.
I am not OK.
What’s happening?
I. I have to go back first.
I am leaving.
You. Wait. Wait.
Lin Yixuan!
Acquaintances commit the crime.
That's not possible.