I'd better not do that,would I?
No
He broke my necklace
He didn't apologize to me
Why should I forgive him?
He talked all sorts of nonsense.
No
What are you looking at?
Let me guess
Are you here to ask me for something?
Yeah, how was it?
If you don't come to me
I might think that necklace
is really important to you
But now I'm more sure
you're a showman
Xiangkong Ji
I don't care what you think of me
But you said
you could do anything Iwanted
Do you want to back out now?
I never go back on what I said
Okay, then you can
play a double qualifying live with me
Is there nothing else to ask?
Is it as simple as double qualifying?
Ok, no problem
Xiangkong Ji
From when I was in vancouver until now
You've been teasing me
I wish you wouldn't tease me this time
After we had finished this double qualifying match
We don't owe each other
Be careful
Stop imitating Miya
There's something wrong with you
That's where the address should be.
Hello
Is this the Donggan esports magazine?
That's right
Are you here for an interview?
Yes,I am
Wait a moment
Handsome boy
You seem to have a lot of leisure here
Director Shi advocated an adle life
An idle life?
Come on, take you upstairs
Handsome boy, handsome boy
Don't you need a job here?
No ,we do
Didn't I tell you?
Director Liu advocate an idle life
Let's go
Come on
Thank you, thank you
You are a top journalism graduate
and we went to school together
Hello,seniors!Hello!
You worked at YouXing for two years
Yes
Do you know anything about professional esports?
To be honest
I switched to the Conquer section not long ago
I used to work in the lifestyle section
So
I don't know much about it
Just because I was in a hurry to get a job
I applied widely.
I didn't look too closely
at your job requirements
I'm so sorry
I see!
Our magazine
is a professional esports magazine
In nearly a decade
It has experienced many challenges in the industry
Now it's going really well
In the last few years
Our industry is getting more and more attention
Therefore, we are in urgent need of
recruiting some professionals
who are specialized in collecting and editing
I see what you mean
Thank you for your time
I'm so sorry
Then I'll go
You're not bothering me
You'll be paied
according to the job Posting
When do you think you can start job?
Director
Do I get paid for working overtime?
If I go out for an interview
how do I arrange it?
You don't have to work overtime
you don't have to go out and interview
All you have to do is
sort out the news from your peers
He really doesn't care
Hi!
Hi, yiyi
How was your interview today?
I got a job in a nursing home
I'm kidding
I changed my job to a magazine
that specializes in esports news
I'll cover all your news from now on
You have to buy me something delicious
I remeber something
How about you asking Xiangkong Ji for help?
He promised to double with me
He said yes?
Please enjoy your meal when the dishes are ready
OK
I heard about Xi Pei
Yang Zhao was clearly well prepared this time
And I see what chairman Jin means
If we can sign Xi Pei over
he's sure to make him captain
Xi Pei as China's first mid
in the generation
has strong strength
If he comes to our team
I think he's more than a captain
Yang Zhao
can not accommodate Xiangkong
As a coach
I can't do anything about it this time
I understand that
I've heard chairman Jin mention one thing before
If I retire
He wanted me to leave esports forever
If I do that
My image will be bound to legend forever
I heard about it
But the board is not in a position
to ask you to do that
Coach Luo
If I sign this agreement
Wait a minute
Do you want to use this agreement
to make a deal with chairman Jin?
Then you must  think it over carefully ,Fang Gu
I think if you do it
it's too much for you
And what if you want to come back in the future?
I wouldn't have done it for something else
But because of Xiangkong,
I think it's worth it.
How about you? Are you ready?
Yes,I am
Why do you buy so many masks?
This facial mask is very popular on the Internet these days
I use it as a fan welfare
to boost my popularity
So generous?
I've never seen you so generous
What do you mean?
I've always been generous, okay?
OK,OK
I'll cheer you up by looking at the Ipad
OK
Hello, everyone
I am Ying Qiu
from the IConquer section of YouXing video company's
I have a surprise for you today
That is tomorrow
I'll have a double qualifying with a super pro.
Let's guess who he is.
Perfect! She left the suspense and then she said
The one who guesses correctly will get a prize
The prize is YuniFang mask with YuniFang mask
It is also a magic weapon
to keep my skin in good condition every time
Let's guess
Ying Qiu, Ying Qiu
Xin Qiao said she had an appointment
with a top player for double qualifying
and she want to challenge you
It's hard to get rid of her
That's good.I accepted her challenge
I am not afraid of her
Come on
This is probably the best data
we've ever had on the IConquer board
That's great
Who came up with the idea of double qualifying
I wanted to do this activity myself
Unexceptedly
you are interestedin participating in it
I heard you're under pressure to perform
If your show doesn't rank within a month
you're leaving the company
I also loathe to part with you
So as a senior
I have to help you
Yes, thanks to sister xin's help
My popularity went up
That's right
We help each other
don't we?
Who are the masterswho cooperate with you?
Masters are mysterious
If I say the name,it won't be mysterious
Yes,it should remain a my stery
It was such a great event
Will you hold more such activities
in the future?
Mr. Liu, can we ask the publicity department
to put this activity on the homepage of the website
This will get more attention
This is a good idea
I should give you a good publicity
Thank you,manager Liu
Let's go get ready
OK
I'll wait and see
Manager Liu, see how we perform then!
Brother Yao
Have you found any problems
with the matches of Xiaolong?
Tell me about it
View is not good
Jungle has been caught
He did not arrest anybody earlier
Captain,fox Zhao comes
Each ace
There's something I need to tell you
JiGuang video company
There's a reality show over there
You arrange foor a person to attend
Manager zhao
Didn't we make an appointment?
The new beta is only a few days away
We all have to train
We're not doing any business these days
Xiangkong
If you don't participate in commercial activities
Where do you get the operating expenses of the team?
Isn't it?
Manager Zhao, operation is something you
and chairman Jin are thinking about
Coach luo and I are only responsible
for playing games and getting good results
Besides
the win and loss of the new version of the test match
determines whether I can become the captain
At this time
you arrange for us to participate in the reality show
Those who know will say that
manager Z hao has devoted himself to the company
Don't know the people also think that
manager zhao is not willing to let me be the captain
so deliberately give me difficult for me
You're not going, are you? All right
You go on with the meeting
This double qualifying is very important to me.
Please be sure to keep the appointment
The appointed time is almost up
Are you ready?
I'm coming
Quickly come in.
How's it going?
Did you find out who Xin Qiao's partner is?
No one in the whole company knows who he is
It seems that
Qiao xin is prepared this time
What's the matter?Are you scared?
I am not afraid of Xin Qiao
It's because Xiangkong Ji hasn't come online yet
He.. He won't tease you again,will he?
Who knows?
Why hasn't he come yet?
Hello
We're going to have a race in a few minues
you have to protect me
I'll reward you first
After win the game
I have a surprise for you
Feng Lu, please practice  with this hero
named Zhanche xia
But this hero...
There are no buts
When Xiangkong asks you to practice,practice
He must have plans
That's all for today's meeting
This is the end of the meeting
I'm leaving
He's logged into the game
Hello,everyone
I am Xin Qiao
Then the battle between me and Ying Qiu
is about to begin
I hope you will support me more
cheer me on
I'll try, too
Thank you,everybody
I invited her
You see, Xin Qiao's partner is Xi Pei
Who is Xi Pei?
Xi Pei?
WeiTeng's carry
The first in the new generation
The strongest mid
There are wonderful games to see
Why haven't you gone yet?
I want to watch the fun
Take the computer back for me
If you want to play with the girls yourself
just say it
Then he must be really good
He is the dark horse of the year
But that's okay
Tatan was defeated by Legends
Don't worry,don't worry
That's good,that's good
So today's live broadcast is the battle
between the champion and runner-up of
the Chinese IConquer game
also is the game the first host of the battle
Be relaxed,don't be nervous
Come on, come on, come on
You have to beat her
Come on
The game is on
There are so many people
Then you have to run
He's after you
I'm running,I'm running
He attacked me,not a good man
They're trying to kill me over the tower
Xiangkong Ji, come and save me
Where are you,Xiangkong Ji?
Xiangkong Ji, Are you in a daze?
What is Xiangkong Ji thinking?
He's so close to you
he didn't even save you
Xi Pei is mid in the game
Why did he become Jungle today?
Ying Qiu is not so strong
It's not hard to play
You scored too fast
Leave it to me
I want to get points
We don't play games by mouth
Let me remind you of one thing
Xiangkong Ji has a nickname
called Disabled Hand
This...
What's going on?
Looks like
I picked the wrong teammate again
That's normal
You...you stay calm
You're coming back to life
You go ahead and play
Let me check for you
Brother Kong,brother Kong,brother kong
Why are you back again?
No,I just heard Bing Wang say somehing
Because of you
the captain will sign an agreement to quit esports
with the company in the conference room
What should we do?
Go and have a look
They are hitting you again. You run
It's over, it's over, it's over
Take it easy
Take it easy, take it easy
I'm lost again
I was so worried.What does it say?
I ...I... I...
I'll read it to you quickly
You read it quickly
Xiangkong Ji
Professional esports embroidered pillow
Weakness of Legends
Shame on Chinese IConquer
This guy is famous for his broken hands
The second line didn't want him
Is he so weak? -yes
I don't know how he can join the Legends
Hang up?
Is he hang up?
Xiangkong is a scum
Even if he hangs up
I can't give up
QiuYing , quickly
Xin Qiao is alone now
This is a good opportunity
Hit her,hit her
I'll be there now
Go,go,go
I beat her. I beat her
Do you want to beat me?
I'm sure to win
Finished,finished,finished
Xi Pei caught up again
What kind of dark horse mid is he?
As a professional player
he bullies a girl
I bet he's an ugly, creepy guy
Yeah, it's a middle-aged man
who's afraid to see anyone
Fang Gu
You've been in Legends for so many years
I really hate for you to leave
Thanks for everybody taking care of me
for so many years
There's not much I can do
for the team
The future of the team
depends on chairman Jin
coach Luo and manager Zhao
OK
I hope you remember that
Legends will always be your home
You can't sign it
Xiangkong, what are you doing?
This unequal agreement is
to take you out of esports forever
Whatever your purpose
You're gu fang. Even if you retire
You should stay in esports
You stay out of this
Xiangkong Ji
Fang Gu puts so much thought and sacrifice
to make you captain
What kind of childish behavior
are you playing here
If my captain was paid for this,
I'd rather not be captain
Xiangkong,this is not
the time for your passions
Don't you believe me?
I certainly believe in your ability
Since you believe me
you should listen to me
In the new beta
If I can let the Legends win,
you'll let me be the captain
If I lose,
I quit
Xiangkong Ji
Never make an impulsive decision
You are responsible for what you say
OK, I believe you
You can prove yourself
That's what it takes to be a captain
That's all for today
Thanks for watching
See you next time
Goodbye
He makes me so angry
What kind of people are these people?
What the hell are that?
It was all because of Xiangkong Ji
If he hadn't hung up
we wouldn't have lost so badly
The problem is that
he didn't help me
while he was in the game
No
If ywe don't teach him a lesson
he really think we're a pushover
Yiyi, where are you going?
I'm go to hit him
I'll go with you, and so will I.
It doesn't matter
if I stay in the business
You are too impulsive
Captain
I can't stay behind you all my life
and let you solve my problems
By the way,I heard Yang zhao
was talking about a contract with Wei Teng's Xi Pei
What's going on here?
Wei Teng's coach Shu is not an ordinary person
It's difficult to snatch someone from his hand
The rest of the way is up to you
Don't worry, captain
Then I'll leave
Come on, come on
All right, I've got work todo
I'll go first
Brother Kong
If we lose
will you really leave the team?
What?
Don't you believe me?
Of course I believe you
Xiangkong Ji
What's going on?
I guess it's because I hung up
and they came after me
Well, you go first. I'll stop them
Can you hold up two people?
Yes,I can.No poblem
I'm leaving. Don't worry
Are you still running? Stop
He is over there
Don't move
Get out of the way
No,wait a minute
Don't move,don't go
Who are you?
My name is Yixuan Lin
You don't care who I am
I don't care who you are
Yiyi, let's go
No, you come back, yiyi
Ying Qiu, you look for Xiangkong Ji
I'll take care of this guy
Hold on. Don't go
You mustn't go
What's wrong with you?
Why do you swear?
I hit someone. How about that?
I tell you
I don't hit women
You don't hit women,do you?
It's just that I hit men
You don't hurt me
I'm going to fight back
What's your name?You tell me
Don't hit me.Don't hit me.
I'm going to fight back
What are you doing?
Can you explain to me
why you did that
What?
About the double qualifying
So many people watched the live broadcast at that time
you didn't help me at all
Do you know how humiliated I am?
You're talking about double qualifying
But you said you played double qualifying with me
and I didn't say I was protecting you
I thought you were good
and played with me just to make it harder
Well, even if you're not obligated to protect me,
at least you should ginish playing the game
Why did you hang up halfway?
Something has come up.Really
Something's come up,haven't you?
OK, Xiangkong Ji
You think it's funny to tease me,don't you?
What are you doing?
We don't owe each other any more
Are you crazy?
Because you've been teasing me
Yeah, I was just trying to trick you
I just want to see
how long you want to stay on the show
You're going to cry again
How cheap your tears are
Haven't you been talking about
making a transition?
What did you do?
You've been trying to
suck up to us all day long
That's your effort, isn't it?
You don't know anything, Xiangkong Ji
Yeah, I just don't know anything
I've seen a lot of people like you
who like to suck up to people to gain popularity
but you're first in there
Xiangkong Ji, you are bastard
Yeah, I'm a jerk
You're sucking up to the wrong person
I give you some advice
There's no shortage of vases like yours
Get out of the way!
Don't think so much
Today is his lucky day
Next time I'll help you catch him
and give him a good beating
Be happy
I made a mistake in this matter
I deserve to be scolded
for bringing shame on myself
I've always said
I'm going to succeed on my own merit
But from vancouver to today
I am still an esports idiot
What makes me think
I can get ahead by taking shortcuts
Why do you think so again?
I've been trying to persuade you
all night in vain
OK
We have to work tomorrow
Go to bed early
I walked back on my own
All right, all right
Think about it for yourself
I"ll go home first
Don't worry
Bye
She's a girl after all
It's inhumane of you
to do her such a disservice
Who are you calling inhuman?
I didn't say that,I didn't say that
Keyboardist, forget it
What happened to your arm?
Don't mention it
I was nearly killed by
the madwoman next to YingQiu today
No, no, wait a minute
I have to give you a piece of my mind
You can't harm her like that
She has ambition,
only to strive to transform to the IConquer version
Ying Qiu is at least a girl
It wasn't easy
OK
You can give her your help
I'd like to give her some help
but she looks down on me
I'm warning you
Don't go out with girls like that
She may sold you out
and you foolishly helped her
Come on
Mom, I just can't do it
Really?
Come on, shall we get a drink of water first?
Little Ying
The children who take part in
the New Year's performance must be the best
Isn't it?
So try to be the best kid you can be
Don't be afraid of hard work
Don't be lazy
Well, we have the last three
Hold it
Will you finish it?
Come on, I believe you
You can do it
Come on, little Ying,the last one
You're amazing
Little Ying, are you hungry?
Yes, I am
What would you like to eat?
I'm sorry,I let you down
Only 30 seconds left
Be careful,Carry
Someone is in the grass
They will come after you
There's someone in the middle of the grass.-OK
Take a look at the view of the river
Be careful,Mid.-OK,OK,OK
Upper way,upper way.-OK
Top goes to middle way
Be careful,Mid
The opponent Mid has a 30 second cooldown
Manager zhao
The organizers of the private test event
made adjustments to the event
Don't let them know that
tomorrow's opponents are replaced by XinTu
I'll see what they can do
You didn't even look at it
How do you know opponent is XinTu?
Did you do it?
How else could the organizers
have easily changed?
Cool, cool, manager Zhao
Coach  Coach  Coach
The first game is WeiTeng vs XiaoLong
The second game is Legends vs XinTu
Coach
Haven't we been fighting with XiaoLong?
Why did the opponent suddenly change to XinTu?
It's impossible for the organizers
not to inform us of such an important event
This must have been done on purpose by fox Zhao
It's really a big trap
Manager Zhao
You see this
The organizers changed the schedule
without informing us
What should we do?
Yeah, the tactics haven't changed
How can we do that?
This game is sure to be lost
My god
When did they adjust the time?
Bing Wang
Didn't you get the message?
Yes
Coach Luo
Didn't you get the message, too
What?
We were never informed
This...
We used to practice against XiaoLong
What should we do now?
Yeah, yeah
What are you doing?Go and ask about it
I'll find them now
No, we can't win at this point
The tactics are all practiced
Suddenly they changed our opponent
We can't fight.We can't win
It's a waste of time
What are we doing here?
Manager Zhao, do something about it
I know, I know
I know
Don't worry
You see
I ask Bing Wang to do something
and that's what happened.
Do not worry
Shall I ask about it now?
You wait to hear from me
Manager Zhao, you must get justice for us
OK,OK,OK
We're counting on you
We trust you.
You have worked hard, manager Zhao
Come on