Sister Yiyi Have some coffee.
Do not give me that.
Say.
Why do you call me here?
Big deal.
In your bag
is it
something unpresentable?
My Cup.
What am I thinking as a family heirloom.
You asked me here to show off your trophy?
No.
Yiyi.
You know a lot of people.
Could you help me ask some information?
Would anyone like to purchase trophies to collect?
Not so simple.
Your salary with bonus is not a few.
What is wrong with you to think of selling trophies?
Say.
Who you spent all your money on?
I can't spend it on anyone
My brother.
He married in the first half of this year.
I give all cash for him to buy a house.
within all property exclude the trophies
I am the most valuable
But nobody will buy me.
If you buy me
I can give you 20% discount.
Bug off.
Then why do you need to lots of money?
Have you owed some money?
I did not owe someone money.
I am collecting the liquidated damages.
I will leave this team
in order to join in Team Phenix.
If you depend on selling trophies
How long can you collect the whole liquidated damages?
I still own the money for marriage at least.
No.
I can not understand.
Xiangkong Ji
What is his charm anyway?
You prefer going to his team
rather than getting married.
I can not really understand.
No.
The wife still wants to marry.
But now
Yiyi
I am begging you. Please.
Could you help me? Please.
I treat you to coffee.
Xiangkong
Come back.
The things for Xialing
You do not have much pressure.
I just did not
expect it to be bad.
He is walking in a swamp
The more he struggles
the deeper he is caught in
Give him a period of time.
Take things easy.
Come. A laugh.
Big baby will leave soon.
Where will our big baby come?
It will go to a remote place
and meet its new master.
You want sell it?
Yeah.
This is indeed your favourite locomotive.
Are you willing to sell it?
You could sell something else.
Others are all sold.
Yiyi Lu told me that
Xuan is selling trophies to make money.
It can not be helped
For Xuan
I have to sacrifice them
If we own enough money
We are sure to redeem it again
Sweetie
Even if I have nothing
you represent the whole
Now I have enough money saved up
Tomorrow I will go to Team Legend.
Come
Finally give a shower to my baby.
Brother Sun
I accompany you to lane.
Do you lane against me?
Is that training partner supposed to be?
Come on
Ok
Then I will open again.
I would choose top-solo.
All right
I will work with you.
Fine
The game room is ready
Inferno lords fights top-solo.
It can not see that
you have a little of conventions
Isn't that so you can
practice compression resistance better
What is wrong?
What do you laugh?
Nothing
You will find out later.
Let's go
That was a pretty tough fight
Not bad Brother Sun
The mistake was caught by me
Come back to water spring
Coach Luo
Sit down
When Xi Pei left
He told me he was going to your team
I still didn't believe him
I did not think you guys
ten days to build up the team
I just took the opportunity
to make up my mind
Congratulations
But you guys took
two of my generals at one go
Coach
No matter where we go
we will never forget
being part of Team Legend
Xiangkong
Seeing your
love for professional e-sports
without being restricted by business events
you are free
to realise your dreams
from my point
I am really happy for you
Thanks you coach
You are welcome
As a coach
that is all I can do
You have to walk
the road by yourself
Brother Kong
Coach Luo
What are you doing here
What are you saying?
Signature
What are you doing?
Sign
Have not you always wanted to
go with your brother Kong
I have not collected enough money yet
When you have saved up enough money
the next of next season has ended
I am ready for the transfer fee
Sign your name
How did you get so much money
You did not cost as much
as the price of a few motorcycles
You sold all your cars?
Do you sign now?
If not I will get it back now
I sign
Brother Kong
I will give you
as cattle and horses
shun no difficulty and danger and
not to hesitate to lay down my life
All right all right
Go back and pack up
I will go with coach Luo
to finish the last procedure
Coach Luo
I do not know how to speak well
During the time with you here
I have given you some troubles
You have never blamed me
Although I will follow brother Kong
But
I will always remember your goodness
I will leave
Xiakong
Do not forget
You also have
my love for professional e-sports
Team Phoenix
Do not let me down
Don't worry
Brother Sun YingQiuI came to report
Xuan
The bad guy
Have you sold the trophies yet
You all know about
This Yiyi Lu.
I will punish her sooner or later
What are you doing here
Enemies often cross each other's path
I think so
We are different this time
I Yixuan Lin
The regular of Team Phoenix
You are no more than a training partner
Even if I am a training partner
I am better than you
The young guys
Work hard to
get into the regular team one day
Do not lose hope
Enough Xuan
There are two rooms
already packed up here
You can choose one
Which room does brother Kong live?
He lives on the second floor
It is okay.
I am just gonna stay in a room with my brother Kong
That room is my place
After all I come first
I am here
You should
have a little bit of a pussy
Get out of here
what relationship between me and brother kong
We go through fire and water
Do you know?
Then you let him sell the car
I…This…
Xiangkong Ji
You say
Whether I live in that room
or he lives in it
Brother Kong I want to live in the same room with you
Look, he has been here
for a couple of days
So you
do not bother it.
Fine
I Yixuan Lin
From today
I can not set foot on the second floor
I will sleep on the sofa
Please
Xuan
These two guys
will be enough for us
Is not?
By the way
I have been looking for 409 recently
Xi Pei
ask all people of the dream traveler
Nobody knows
his identity
So brother Sun
do you recommend anyone?
Temporarily no
Xuan sometimes
just talk without thinking
Do not care too much
I do not mind
His telling is the truth
In fact recently
I have been in lane against with brother Sun
I find
it is not bad that I play as top-solo
I can in different positions
and be able to help other players
This experience
in other teams
I have never experienced
You play without the role as top-solo
and do not make Four guarantees one
Can you accept it?
I want to enter the Team Phoenix
I just want to change myself
Before
I just thought
The tactics from Xiangkong Ji
are amazing
but recently
he was in VNG
I saw a miracle
Wu Tong
Sheng Lu
Each of them
seemed a different person
Xiangkong just
taps into their potential
Yes
so I believe he
will lead Phoenix
and lead all of us
to the world championship podium
Look how cute you were when you were a kid
when I am a kid
It is only cute
You still have this picture
this picture
Dad kept
This picture is that we are
at the amusement park
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember calling it what
air bike
At that time for the middle of riding
suddenly it stopped
so scary
I immediately cried out
when you were a kid
You were really timid
Why are you back so early today
I will take our son to rehab tomorrow
and I have a lot of work to prepare
Who is here
They are talking so happily
Ying came
What is she doing here
Shumin
Ying
your aunt Xia is back
Then I go back
and see you another day
Sister
you said
you would take me to your team to have a look
You can come any time you want
Let's go now
Go Go
Go out and play happily
don't have to stay at home
it is boring
yes?
I will take care of him
Stay safe, you two
What is wrong
You calm down, ok?
What do you mean?
You say that what do you mean?
What can I mean?
I just want Ying to come
and enlighten Ling Xia
You do not except to see your child
depressed all day
Have a look
After Ying came
how happy Ling Xia laughed
Let bygones be bygones.
Let it go
What could be
more important to you than a child getting better
you
Yes or no?
when she comes
You must let me know next time
i must
I think we can
look at these two
Let's look at Wenjie Zhou
He took part in the college league
to express good performances.
Here is a video of his operation
have a look
Take care.
Not bad
I am back
with a new friend.
My brother
Ling Xia
Hi Xia Ling
Hi brother
You are the Xiangkong Ji
Many people say you are
Battlefield Fraud Division
But it's more like
in the professional world
You have the stiff hand
Ling Xia
Yeah
I am
the legend of the stiff hand
Right
Ling Xia also play the game Peak
Just today there are all master-hand
or else
You can consult with the others
Come on brother
Brother Xuan will take you up in a minute
come sit
What can I fight with you
a supprot
It seems that
Ling Xia still
has a certain understanding of everyone
By the way
This is brother Sun
the former captain of Pioneer
One of the five ancient players
Can I play a game with him
Is it ok
You want to play with Xi Pei
Xia ling said
Xi Pei is his idol
Is Xi Pei ok
Why do you play with him?
He is our intern
Play with me
I just want to challenge the strongest one
Ok
I can take your challenge
As expected is the best top-solo
Getting a touch
actually
You are not bad at it
Losing to the best top-solo is not a shame
After that we practice hard
It is you who should work hard
I practice I practice
Do you think
Ling Xia plays like a person
It is really like
actually like
No
What do you really to express?
Give Mangoes during one to one
And always use consumables
to maintain skill set
in the early stages use high burst
and mana cost skills
to neutralise each other
This is
exactly the same as
409's unique item builds ideas
Yeah
when he started to do item builds
I knew
something happen
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You said he was
the guy you were looking for a while ago
Genius in Chinese server 409 brother
I do not know what you are talking about
I do not think Ling Xia is
as good as he is
Winning the ordinary people at best
This has been good operation
It just looks like 409
but I just played him
with twenty percent of force and skill
I still won easily
brag brag brag again
I think that
He is a bad imitators for 409 at best
Xiakong
Don't overdo to say
Am I cranky?
He just loses his temper to me
I am telling you the truth
He also needs to know his level
You think you know 409?
You also lost to him
How do you know
they have played against each other
until I give you a kick
I don't think you'll admit it
well done
He really is 409
Ling Xia
Sister I'm going back
Would like to join the Team Phoenix
No interest
I am seeing him off
slow slow
This is a bonus for us
Here he comes
Ling Xia
When you were a kid
when you were unhappy
you used to look for ice cream
Be happy
I can not believe
my brother is 409.
You plays very good
I understand your meaning
Let me join in team
just want to give me something to do
I brought you out
In order to get you out
Do not stay at home
I didn't realize you are 409
Just Xiakong Ji
would like to invite you to join
He is sincere
You don't know
we look for you so hard
You let Xiakong Ji give up
Sister
You and they are
running to win the championship
what's the use of pull me such an unprofessional cripple
Ling Xia
I forbid you to say that about yourself
Sister Your are also busy
You come back first
You let me do it myself
Ling Xia
I have told you not to be brave.
Let's take our time.
You see
What am I
Hey
how was the conversation
I meet him
But he is in bad condition though I come
I wouldn't be able to push him
Are you sure he is the one Phoenix needs now?
Right now
There’s no one better suited than him
I don't want to miss him
Now that he's in the abyss
let's show him some light
and I want him to know his meaning and value
What do you mean
I will give him a big dose
hello
Ling Xia
you are too good
Brother Respect
You are the legend of the sweeping monk
Your hidden is too deep
Yeah
I said master next time bring me play
Dude This time you are
famous all over the school
Someone just asked you to WeChat
Go to the school forum and check it out.
It's all about you
Yes Ling Xia go and have a look
Ling Xia in Basketball class
is the top player in Chinese web server
Amazing
Unspoken
Ling Xia is really 409
It's a shame not to go professional teams
I heard that he was injured
and could not play basketball
He used to play basketball very well
How can this happen now
By the way
Hei, the sixth of Chinese web server me
and said he would like to join us
Let's take a meeting sometime
Is he?
Other?
We can wait for short time
I'm sure Ling Xia
will come to us
Have a dinner
Ling Xia
Why do you com
come come come
It is time for dinner
slow down
Xi Pei you are awesome Xi Pei
Did you guys post the video online?
What’s going on
It's none of their business
I posted the video
Why would you do that
for exposing that you are 409
I apologize
But I did it to let you know
You're not a cripple
I'm not a  cripple
Now the whole school knows
my leg is broken
Xia Ling No
now whole school know
You are the 409 who only spent half a month
playing for the fourth in Chinese web server
You are the 409 who courage
battle me and Xiangkong Ji one-on-one
Ling Xia
In fact except you
no one treats you as useless
Yeah
we
besides playing basketball
we have a lot of things to do
Right?
if you want to
You can do the best in any field
Just like in the Peak
you can play to the fourth of Chinese web server in a short time
and can also play professional games
for the glory of the country
Who do you think you are?
You do not have right to care me
Ling Xia
Yes, I'm an outsider.
if you're not the brother of Ying Qiu
I don't care
Xiangkong Ji
About what happened to you
If I say empathy
You must feel very hypocritical
But Ying Qiu has worries, guilt and remorse to you
Every day I see
since she knows
you can't play basketball
She can't eat or sleep every day
Try to
make yourself happier every day
Including your parents
dote on you every day
afraid you are sensitive
and take a matter to heart
Do not dare to say the word ‘run’
People are not doing this to look you as cripple
but to make you feel positive about life
Ling Xia
You have been 20 now
Are you going to spend your life as a loser at home
Xi Pei
Use your low attitude
to torture everyone around you
Or do you have to get back up
and use your hands
to get back what was yours
Think it over
That's enough
I don't need you to take care of
Ling Xia
The transfer window of Peak
is about to close
and we are willing to wait
until the last minute
I get into trouble I'll take care of it
Ling Xia
Would you stop following me
I apologize for the video
Who wants you to apologize
This is my personal act
if you feel that
it hurts you
and you can hate me
But it has nothing to do with them
Then I ask you
to leave me alone
No
I won't leave
Your sister is the same
Team Phoenix
all of us do not leave you alone
Even if you do
I will not join Phoenix
As much as I want you
to join Phoenix
But it's your choice
What I want more now is
for you to pull yourself together
Your sister told us
you used to be
a sunny boy
But now you are
but how I used to be
What to do with you
Stop!
I don't want you to be
what I used to be
I just don't want
anyone to pity me
so I'd rather be alone
I was afraid that others would see me
as a strange person
so once
I would rather stay alone
You
Who dare say you as that?
Anyone who worked with me almost
All people
I don't care what anyone else is doing
even if while playing a game
I'd rather say nothing
listen to music
There's no communication with my team
Even if others say
Xi Pei can win nine
Xi Pei is selfish
and no team spirit
I do not care
But you still won.
You were the best of top-solo
No
dI've never made it to the global finals.
What's number one?
Peak
It has never been a one-man sport
I've only recently learned this
So
I regret so much
Regret what?
I regret that
I have been so closed
and I really want to be part of the team
And the feeling the warm of team
But always afraid of
those strange eyes seeing me
I do not have the courage to take this step
That's why I don't want to
in my free time
Stay at team
I'd rather in dream traveler
make coffee for a stranger
These words
are also the first time I said
Because
I don't want
you like I used to be
to wrap yourself up
I really envy you that
when you are most confused
so many people are willing to help you
So Ling Xia
promise me
not to turn away people who care about you
You have talent
Peak and basketball
both are competitive sports
We
the player of competitive sports
are not willing to be ordinary people
Then why do you prefer to practice with Phoenix
What I got in phoenix
in other places
I could never get anywhere else
What do you want?
Want know?
Then you join phoenix to try
and find the answer yourself
Is there a reaction
The tingling
Care your strength.
I see
The acupoint we talked about last time
What is the acupoint?
Yongquan
You can't remember how many times I've said it
Why don't you lie down and let me do it
How many days have you been practicing?
How many acupoints have you memoized？
You don't practice without manners
to make sure our son
can handle it
Come back my son.
Have you eaten dinner yet?
Have eaten
Our son finally smiled
What is wrong?
You still worried about Ling Xia?
Yeah
I wanted to call him
but I didn't dare
I was afraid of affecting his mood
I hope methods of Xi Pei can cheer him up
In fact
Xi Pei has a hot heart
just he usually hides too deep
Yeah
but now he doesn't have to hide it
through the thing from Ling Xia
I realized a different Xi Pei
I believe he will shine in Phoenix
What do you mean?
Ling Xia
We miss you
Waiting for your feet good
We accompany you to play basketball
yes or no
yes
Ling Xia
I knew it was you
The ferocity
Just Ling Xia you have
so cool
Ling Xia
I knew you wouldn't fall down
Life everywhere is a race
Rush forward
Ling Xia
Our class students are all excepted to you
You do not have difficult passing
Ling Xia Ling Xia look
look! ddwho is this?
Ling Xia
I saw the solo of you
You are the same as the former
The place with you, you are the king
I don't want you
like I used to be
to wrap yourself up
In fact I really envy you that
when you are most confused
so many people are willing to help you
So Ling Xia
promised me
not to turn away people who care about you
I wonder if our son is awake
Son   has a dinner
Mom and dad
I prepare to come back to school
Go back to school.
Go back school to have lessons?
You don't have to study
any acupuncture points
I'll go to the hospital
for rehabilitation
Think clearly!
Eat your breakfast
after dinner
Your mother and I will take you to school
Son
I'll take you to your dorm
Just ask your classmates
to take good care of you
It is ok
You can all go back
I told my classmates
to wait for me downstairs
You
only know how to worry about kids
What do you worry about
at school if having something incommensurate
Tell us
Give you
If what is missing tell mom
I can bringing it to you
I'm leaving.
You quickly go home
I'll give it to you
It's too heavy
You let the kids do it themselves
Ling Xia can do it herself
Do we really want the Hei come?
Why not
we wait for Ling Xia for short time
We really don't have time
to wait any longer
You listen to
Ying
Your brother has gone to school
I and your aunt Xia
express thanks to you
these days
for you to enlighten your brother
It was very hard
Ling Xia really can't come this time
All right
let's call Hei
Ling Xia
No   Ling Xia
Didn't you go to school?
Everything has been arranged at the school
I just have a question
if we can win the championship here
Let's work on it
It's possible
It's very possible
Congratulations
on joining Phoenix
Come on  Brother
After Brother Xuan over you
You can't look down upon the support later
Listen?
Fine.
I declare that
Xi Pei
has officially become
the last member of Phoenix team today
Me?
No
I'm not ready
You're ready
What do you think?
I think it's almost interesting
This period of time
Everyone speaks highly of you
and you have learned to cooperate
and understand to pay out
Now you have proved that
you are no longer
a first top-solo only with four guarantees
And the period of time
The thing of LingXia
I admire you
Well
today
Xi Pei Ling Xia officially joined
the Team Phoenix
Our Team Phoenix
also formally established
Let's remember this day
Fight
come on
Rebirth of Nirvana
Top-solo dismisses
Watch your step
OK OK
attention
I was arrested
and three men beat me
Come
Xuan  you carry
I am coming
Hit him   Beautiful
Wonderful Xi Pei Good Brothers
amazing
Come One rise We can attack
it is ok
it have be a model
We finally have a team logo of our Team Phoenix.