GANK YOUR HEAR
Episode 23
Qiuying
Axuan
Pei Peixi
Qiuying
My brother wants me to tell you
Go back to see him when you have time
It suprises me that
Peixi has been cheated for so long
Qiaoxin is so excessive
Why
are you staring at me like this
No nothing nothing
I have to go first  byebye
Peixi has a game to play today
Don't look  go
Should I tell him
I tell you
That's my brother Kong's girl
Don't ever think about her
Forget it
It has nothing to do with me
But Peixi is my friend
Besides
He helped me a lot
No
I should be in charge of this matter
Peixi Peixi
What's up
I have something to tell you
Right
I also have something to tell you
So aggressive
Brother Kong  brother Kong
Your girl is going to be taken away
You speak first
Peixi
Actually I want to tell you
there's no wrong and right in love
Sometimes
When you find out you're in a wrong road
you have to turn around in time
When you fall in love with the wrong person
you have to take your love back
It's just
some things
no matter how much you like them
they won't belong to you
even if you miss
some people so much
you have to learn to give up
Are you sure
you want to be a professional commentator
not a host of the emotional show
Be straightforward
Well I say it then
It's that
your girlfriend
My girlfriend
It's your girlfriend
Well
You get it
I don't have girlfriend
You don't have girlfriend
So have you broken up with Qiaoxin
I say it again
I don't have girlfriend
Are you and JiXiangkong
having a relationship
No
We are not
That's good
If something happens to you later
stop looking for him
You can come to me straight
What do you mean
Are you still ignoring it
Xiang  Xiangkong
You heard
what I said just now
I heard
what I should and should not hear
But listen to me
You'd better put your heart into the contest
You Legend team
is almost caught up by Weiteng
That's interesting
Right
Remind you
Be careful with Qiyue
He is easy to be over-confident
Thanks for reminding
You're welcome
Are my brother Kong handsome when he gets jealous
LinYixuan  look at yourself
What's going on to you recently
Do you still want to play the game
Gently
Can't keep up with Tongwu
and can't support Qiyue
JiXiangkong  are you really jealous
Son  Mom
Are you feeling better today
Why on earth she brought
lots of things
Does she show them to her father
Mom
Stop talking my sister in this way
These are all sent by her
with good will
Good will
If she has good will
she won't make your leg broken
After so many years
Has she been kind to me
Let alone calling me mother
She even doesn't call me auntie
Mom
These things have past
Don't always mention it
Don't talking my sister in this way
Also
I accidentally broke my leg
It has nothing to do with my sister
Mom
The school basketball league starts next month
When can I
leave the hospital
Son
It's always about rest when you get injured
so have a good rest
I went to school to help you ask for leave
The coach said
you can go back when you recover
My classmates are about to get in the national team
while I'm here to rest
When is the end
Don't worry  have a rest
Xialing's relative
Doctor Zhang is calling you
Coming coming
Mom goes to check
Here
Okay thank you
Compare these two pictures
This place is raised obviously
Laoqiu
Hello
The reason why I invite you today
is to talk about
the condition of Xialing
After observation, his damage in the brain
has no sequelea left
However
His leg is not just about
tibia fracture
Look
His nervus peroneus communis
has been damaged
Well
Can this be cured
Sure, it can be cured
But afterwards
The activities of his ankles
might be controlled
Doctor
The activities of his ankles are controlled
What does it mean
It might influence
his walking
or working
Well
Doctor
Will I be able to play basketball in the future
I just want to know
Will I be ablt to
play basketball afterwards
I'm afraid not
The nervus is fragile
Even though it's repaired
it might cause drop foot
You're not allowed to have intense exercise
Thank you doctor
So funny  so funny
Qiuying
Come here
Show you something funny
Qiuying
What are you doing
You scared me
You ignored me first
Call you a few times
Are you dazing  don't answer me
I'm wearing the earphones
can't hear you
What are you looking at
Commentary
It's two o'clock  Why are you cooking
I go to close it
Stop stop stop
Don't touch  don't touch
Don't close  don't close  Yiyi
The pigeon soup can be nutritious
if it tastes delicious
Xialing is so blessed
If I have
such a good sister
that'd be good
Having a brother like Xialing
is also great
You're cooking
while watching the games' videos
So hard-working
That Luotian
even doesn't allow you to go to the analysis table
Why are you still so hard-working
Actually
That he doesn't allow me to the analysis table
is great
The storage of my knowledge right now
is not enough
So I have to learn more
It's not a bad thing
Am I right
Yes
Xialing
Sister
I bring pigeon soup to you
Why do you have time and come today
There's no game today
What about you
How's your recovery
Not bad
I will go to the rehabilitation room later
I can be with you
No
Sister
You stayed up late again
Your dark pouches are so deep
I'm fine
You should drink the soup before it gets cold
It won't taste good when it's cold
Sister
You're also busy
Afterwards
You don't have to visit me very often
Xialing
Are you worried about something
today
You're so weird
No
I'm just tired
You should leave
I want to have some sleep
I help you
Watch out  your legs
Have a good rest
I will come to see you some other day
Remember to have the soup
Captain
Are you not leaving
You're looking at
Jishuai's notebook
During the Autumn Season
the performance of the bimonthly group in Weiteng
is so strong
I'm looking at his notebook
to see if I can
get inspired
Do you remember
when we fought against Weiteng last time
Coach Luo used JiXiangkong's way
to cope with Weiteng
At last
We were beaten
by him
He knows too much about us
On the other hand
You know much about him as well
What do you mean
Do the same thing
that he does to us
The understandting towards him
is our best weapon
I won't come back today
You help me deal with it
Where's Qiyue
His mother came to see him from Taipei
He is with his mom
And let me ask you for leave
Why doesn't he tell me in person
He might be too busy
to tell you
Four of us
do exercise in pairs first
Qiyue and Qiaoxin
I don't know  a few days later
Tell me where you are at any time
Your turn
Hurry up  we'll be witnessed
Hurry
Be good
Byeybye
Let's have a
short meeting
The fight against Xintu
You guys
have to win
this game
If we win the game
we'll enter the playoff
in the first place
Therefore, we'll have
the priority of choose side
and take an advantage
in selection
More importantly
If we win the game
we'll break the record
that Legend team won ten games in series last year
Master
Sister Wen
Don't worry with me here
I will definitely break the record tonight
From now on
I will make the Legend
call us big brother
What's up Qiyue
Didn't you have enough sleep yeterday
No  my mom came to
see me from Taipei  and then
I picked her up and kept her company for a day
So I'm a bit tired
You haven't come home for a long time
If you have time
be with your family
Master
The game later
won't be affected
There's a break before the playoff
You can go back home then
to be with your family
Thank you sister Wen
Qiyue
You didn't show up to practice yesterday
We made some slight adjustments
on tactics
The key in Xintu  Chengchen
In there few games
he has a huge output
So
Chengchen  Chengchen
I have fought against him for many times
He doesn't have many skills
You don't have to tell me
I will beat him later
Okay
One more thing
You won't forget
what day it is today
Remember
It's sister Wen's birthday
Glad you remember that
It's too busy recently
After the game
we'll celebrate it
Master's gift is prepared
Alright
Winning the game
is the best gift for me
Do you have faith
Yes
What are you taking
I write down
the important points
that Weiteng fights against Xintu
What's the point
Tell us
Actually
Every team
has its own style
and fighting tactics
When to open the group
On what condition will they open the group
When to beat the dragon
If they can beat the dragon under bad circumstances
After I know
these points
It will help
my commentary afterwards
I remember
the habit of Xintu
is to grab the dragon from the beginning
gain early advantage
But Weiteng
They have severl tactics
which is easy for enemies
to expose shortcomings at first
God
Qiyue fought so fiercely
that they are completely messed up
Fortunately  JiXiangkong arrived in time
It depends on this group fight
Although it's too risky
it's worthwhile
Even though it's just to grab the dragon
for Xintu, a conservative team
it's a big hit
Let me have a look at your notebook
Sure
So full
You've taken every note of each game
Qiuying
I thought you were just
pretending to do it in front of us
I didn't realize
you are so hard-working
It looks like
you are more qualified than Qiaoxin
to go to the podium
Weiteng wins
Excellent
How to go  how to go
Open group in the mid  open group in the mid
Hold it  hold it
Skill skill
Now push
keep pushing him  pushing him
Okay  push now
Good job
Control line  line  line
Today
Weiteng sets a new record
in the regular season
with an eleventh win in series
which can be called a myth
Let's hava a look
Who is the MVP in this game
Qiyue
Win eleven games in series
the MVP in twenty rounds
He has surpassed Peixi
to become the
best MVP in this season
with no doubt
Congratulations
Well
Good job Qiyue
That's my good apprentice
No big deal
It's no problem to win thirty games in series
Xiangkong
Hard work for you
No sister Wen
This is the result
that everyone fights for
Okay okay
I've arranged
the place to eat
You take sister Wen to there first
Aren't you coming
Sure
We go to prepare first
Go go go
Okay let's go first
Hurry hurry hurry
Happy birthday
Brother Yi
Ligan
Why are you coming here
Congratulations
Right
It's Shuwen's birthday today
Do you still remember
Good day
So I hold a party
to celebrate
I want to
invite you to come
I'm too busy
to leave
Summer and Luotian also come
I know you might not
like to go to this crowded place
as usual
So
I invite you in person
I'm the only one here
I really can't leave
Brother Yi
Shuwen has always wanted to
find a chance
to reunite
our trail blazers
I want to fulfill
her dream
on her birthday
Right
She also said
that we can get
this result today
is because of you as well
Brother Yi  come with me
Have a good time
I really can't go
Brother Yi
After so many years
haven't you still got over it
Happy birthday
I'm texting you two
Here
Here  have a seat
It's special for the birthday girl
The birthday girl is so young
I don't see you like this usually
Good talk
We don't have to introduce ourselves
Hi teachers
Hello hello hello
You did a good job today
Very brilliant
It's because of captain's good tactics
It has nothing to do with the captain
I think the coach is better
You have to cherish
these two teachers
won't praise others easilt
It's really great
Almost catch up with us at that time
More wines  hurry
Okay
Xiangkong  help me
Where's Ligan
He called us to come here
Where is he
He might be preparing gifts for sister Wen
Don't give me too much
I know your capacity for liquor
Come I'll give you more wine next time
Come
Brother Sun
Happy birthday
Thank you
Okay don't stay still
Sit down  sit down
Come here  come here
Long time no see  brother Yi
It's so hard to invite you
Hurry
Have a seat  sit down
Great
Ligan
Have a seat too
I'm going to prepare
How's your store
Is the business good
Same as usual
Gufang is not here today
If he comes
five of us will
be reunited
Okay
Drink drink drink
Here Xiangkong
Cheer
Like you
Happy birthday to you
I wish
everyone here
can achieve your dream
Happy birthday
Say yes  say yes
say yes  say yes
say yes  say
Shuwen
Say yes to me
Ligan
You give such an expensive gift to me
I really can't accept it
Now we should
focus all our energy
on games next
Don't we have a deal
We have to win the world championship together
Today
I really like
what you've done for me
Thank you
Sister Wen
It won't have a conflict
Okay
After we win the world championship
I will put this ring
on your hand in person
Come  drink
Come come come
Hurry hurry hurry
Come drink
Here  brother Yi
You see you
Why are you being so unmerciful
Don't you know
what Shuwen looks like
I'm curious
I'm curious that
what I am
in her heart
If you want to prove
what you are in her heart
There are so many ways
Why did you invite
her ex-boyfriend
She can't forget brother Yi
Okay okay
The reason why Shuwen refused you
not all beacause of brother Yi
They have broken up for many years
If JiXiangkong didn't go to Weiteng
they wouldn't have a chance to meet
You think too much  bro
After so many years
You all know
what I've done to Shuwen
Clear
We are all clear
Shuwen knows it as well
Does she know
No no no
She doesn't understand
Enough enough
A few years ago
I turned down the invitation
from American team
for her
I stayed here
Without
any foundation
I established Weiteng with her
In Weiteng
She has the choice
To tell you the truth
I'm not afriad of being laughed at
I, Ligan
the boss of Weiteng
In our team
I have no position
No
Shuwen wanted JiXiangkong
to be the captain
Do you know
the sponser
gave me  no
gave us
how much pressure
Who takes it
I take it
How I treat Shuwen
How much have I paied
How much have I paied for Weiteng
All of these can't be compared with brother Yi
Here here here
I drink with you
Brother Sun
It suprised me that
sister Wen would refuse him
Brother Sun
Actually
I don't believe
you were the lamster at that time
Why you left the Pioneers
Why you left sister Wen
I think
you must have
something difficult to talk
It's all past
Don't mention it
But I think
sister Wen is still thinking about you
Impossible
Why impossible
Anyway I think
sister Wen doesn't like Ligan
Besides
Don't you want to be together with her again
Remember I told you
Time
can change everything
I and Shuwen
are not who we were
Don't talk about me
How's you and Mia
You just mentioned
Time changes everything
Mia has been left for many years
You always think about her
Now she's back in China
While you...
Do you really fall in love
with the girl called Qiuying
It looks like you admit it
Then go to chase after her
Don't escape
Don't let Summer's
cousion take her away
No
How do you know this
Is Summer
talking something to you
Is Peixi really serious
Yixuan talked to me a little
I have no idea
whether Peixi is serious
However
it's obvious that you're serious
LinYixuan
What's up
have been playing the regular game for three monthes
now we have ten days' off
But in the end
we have more exercise
I've promised my friend
but I came here in the morning
Where are they
It's just you and me today
Just us
Why
Are they on purpose
I'll leave
It's me and sister Wen
that have you exercise more
Not Lusheng and Tongwu
For brother Qi
he can also leave
He has the most mistakes
MVP every round
Where is the mistake
In the last round
when grabing the dragon at the eighth minutes
if Shenyue didn't protect you in time
you would have been killed
At twelfth minutes
why didn't you follow my instruction
and take action alone
When opening group at fifteenth minutes
if you got there in time
we could
finish the game at that time
Just a few mistakes
Besides
yesterday
brother Qi's mother
came to see him from Taipei
even if he had a few mistakes
we can forgive him
Did you be with your mom or dating
You know it
What  what date
JiXiangkong
I warn you
Don't ask for trouble
You will regret it
If you really want to charge me
Go
I don't care
The bimonthly group
is our key tactics
The status of you and Shenyue
is very important
Qiyue
You play games in the mainland
which is far away from  your home
I believe your persistence towards your dream
Now it's your highlight
in your career
Whether you can be more successful
depends on these two years
You think about it
Xialing
You leave the hospital
What are you doing  Mom
Mom get in the car
I have something to talk to my sister
You have nothing to talk to her
Dad  go go go
You just let them
What are you doing
There's nothing to talk
Okay  get in get in
Sister
Xialing
Why don't you tell me
that you leave the hospital
There is rehabilitation training afterwards
I come with you
No
Sister
You see
My mom has a bad attitutie to you
If we keep in touch
there will be so much contradictory
In the future
we should meet less
Xialing
Is it your idea
It's my idea
I don't want to live
in the middle of you and my mom
Besides
You're busy with your work
There's no need to think about me
That's it  I go now
Yingzi
Don't be sad
You can go back
We are with your brother
Go
Sister
Sorry
I don't want to escape from you
I'm just worried that
you will know what happened to my foot
and you will be sad
Thanks to
the thoughtful instructions from Mr. Acan
which make me today
Qiaoxin is the most hard-working
commentator I've ever seen
Just one
Well
They are so funny   flattering each other
Come
Let's sing today
Who will come
I don't have time
Excuse me
who are you looking for
Hello
I'm looking for
You are
LinYixuan
in Legend team
You know me
It's really you
Brother Xuan
Come come
Please please please
Okay okay okay
LuYiyi look who is coming
Brother Xuan in Legend team
LinYixuan
Hello hello
Hi director Shi
Hi hi hi
What are you doing
I'm picking you up
Aren't you getting off ther work
I'm so busy
I don't have time
to go to karaoke with you
You are going to sing brother Xuan
We are getting off the work
Can we go with you
Do you want to come
Yes
Well  come together
My treat
Then get prepared  let's go
Aren't you getting off the work
LinYixuan
What the hell
I think he's great
Yiyi
Your love is coming
Hurry hurry hurry
Go together
Love is coming
Well let's go together
No problem  no problem
Come  go together
You can go as you wish
I won't go
Off the work
Goodbye
Are you not coming
No
Well if you don't come
Brother Xuan
Why are you leaving
I've booked the room  yeah
So soon
Before we sing
shall we go to have dinner first
Go go
Well
Let's change to another day
No
It has to be today
Today
Go go go
The room is booked
I'm here for LuYiyi
Go
Go hurry
You
like milk tea so much
Don't you say you will come home
Why are you here
Do you want to come cross me
I
walked half the way
ang then
It suddenly occurred to me that after leaving Dream Traveler
for so long
I haven't been able to see them
Miss them a lot
So just drop by
and buy some drinks for them
Our Qiuying
is such an emotional girl
Right
at this time
Peixi should be in Dream Traveler
Don't you want to meet him
Right
What happened to you
What
Don't you really think
he committed love to me last time
It's obvious
No
Well
I just think
It might because
he experienced sadness from love
and had a bad mood
Hurt from love
Do you know Qiaoxin and
Leave it
Anyway he didn't commit love to me
Are you saying
after Peixi knew the relationship
between Qiaoxin and Qiyue
So
You also know their
underground love
I also know that during that pair game
the person who tried to kill you
is not Peixi
is Qiyue
Qiyue
Qiyue stole Peixi's account
and the realationship between Peixi and Qiaoxin
is exactly
designed by Qiaoxin
So Peixi
hasn't been hurt by love
He was really committing love to you
Rubbish
I told you
No committing  no committing
He
It's can't be viewed as committing love
Nothing happened
Why are you getting anxious
Are you guilty
What am i guilty for
Even if he said love to me
I wouldn't like
his cold face
A big fool
Right
Is the attitude Mr. Luo towards you
getting better
Same as usual
But it's okay
I'm new in this industry
There are so many things
I need to learn
I wish
I can go up step by step
Would you mind
showing me
your commentary video
Sure
I have a lot that don't understand
Otherwise
We go to Dream Traveler
Dream Travel again
Why you like it
so much
Or because
someone is there
You tell me
You take me there
Say it
Why calling us
I want to have
a meeting about tactics today
The theme is
JiXiangkong
Brother Kong
I'm enlighented
For the first time, the theme of a meeting about tactics
is a person
Yes
What do you mean
I don't understand
Well
Let's listen
to the captain
According to the status of Weiteng
it's likely that we will fight against them
in the playoff
Before
JiXiangkong relied on
his understanding towards us
and won
At this time
Why don't we
win him
according to our understanding towards him
It sounds
right
Make sense
Accept it
isn't it
I'll go first
My brother Kong
Name  JiXiangkong
Constellation  Lion
Loves strawberry best
The best brother
is me
It's a tactics meeting
or a tea party
Yes
You ate things that he bought
Can you be serious
Captain
Excuse me
Well
Seriously
According to my understanding of him
If he gain a huge advantage
at the first stage
then in the late period
he must expand his advantage
You turn brother Yao
The biggest merit of JiXiangkong
is his imagination
Don't think that
we have an advantage in the early stage
and take it lightly
It might be his trap
Have to keep focused
JiXiangkong
This person
he is especially
strong
Stop joking
An important point occurred to me
and you haven't thought about it
He likes motorcycles best
Do you find out
that Peixi is not as cold as before
Lufeng
Tell me more
Why asking me again