Why did the necklace break?
Is it broken?
Let me have a look at it.
This shouldn't be.
It was fine when I left the house just now.
Is that ok?
How much is it? I compensate for you
What is priceless you know?
Well, since you think it's priceless
Money won't pay you back.
So let it be
You make a request
No matter what I can satisfy you
Xiangkong Ji,
I thought you were a decent guy
Now it seems that I misunderstood you
Mom,I'm sorry
I'm sorry
I broke the necklace
Whatever you think of me
I still hope you can help me
Because Fang Gu is
The idol of domestic esports circle
What is priceless you know?
Why are you still playing with your phone?
What's the matter?
The captain is retiring
Where's the captain?
He's right downstairs.
Wait a minute
The captain
Don't call me captain
There will be someone more suitable to replace me
At least for now you're still the captain.
Are you really retiring?
I'm thirty years old
It's time to retire
Xiangkong
The team can do without me
But not without you
Over the years
If there's anything esle I can do
it's because I found you
From vancouver
Come back later
Many people have written a lot of bad things about you on the Internet
Among the pros
My hands are not fast enough.
I'm sorry
You've suffered a lot.
It's all right. They call me names.
I don't care
No matter what I did as a child,
I was questioned and ridiculed.
I'm used to it
I've been fighting for years
And I still haven't won a second ring
Before
my dream was to win a second championship
But now the dream is to see you win the cup
The captain's burden is on you
Captain, you think too highly of me
My hands aren't fast enough
How can I be captain?
In front of me
You still wear a mask
And pretend you don't care
How hot you are inside!
We all felt it
Don't let external factors affect your own mood
Come on
You are my hope and the team's hope
The captain
I don't know if I can do it
You have to trust me
You can do it.
A Xuan is very talented
Yao Huo is an experienced veteran
Lu feng has a good personality and strong combining ability
Give you such a good team
My regrets may be fulfilled
Don't refuse me
Come on
The captain
I'll do my best
We'll get the championship back
Captain, you're not leaving here
The captain
It was our fault that we lost the game this year
Next year
Next year,
We are sure to win the championship
The captain
We fought together for so many years
Let's not miss this year
Don't leave. We'll fight for another year
Don't cry
Haven't you cried enough in Vancouver?
You said you were going to take us to the podium
After you come second
Aren't you guys having a good time?
I want to win the championship
Even though I retired
I am still your brother
I will be your fan in the future
You must work hard next year.
Go! Go! Go!
Xiao Yu,
If you lose the game, you should treat us to hot pot
You must be willing to bet to lose.Go and buy it.
Let's play another game
I just killed you so many times in the game
You fell for his trick.
He took you on the road to be killed on purpose.
You are right. Almost no one understands my tactics
Boy, do you know who he is?
Brother Sun, I know.
Gris - Fang Gu.
He is the captain of the legends team
Hello, my name is Xiangkong Ji
Hello
I'd like to invite you to be the team leader
I hope you use your tactics to help our team to the top
Are you interested in it?
I've got the hot pot for you
Please have your dinner, Xiao Yingzi.
It smells good!
Am I being nice to you?
Thank you, Yiyi.
There 's something I want to tell you
I think Mr. Liu was especially right
After I moved to the IConquer game section to work
It's really different from working in the lifestyle section
Not only is the work much fresher
But the most important thing is that I need to have professional knowledge
Otherwise the audience will question your ability
They left a message at the bottom of my micro blog
And said they wanted to watch my live broadcast
I hope I can make a good start
How smart you are
Why are you so innocent now?
Qiao Xin!
She contacted the legendary team manager Zhao
And she got the exclusive right to interview
Mr. Liu was very happy
I think...
If you get along well with ji xiang kong and become friends
Then maybe...
Stop!
Xiangkong Ji is a jerk
I don't want to see him any more
If I in order to win over Xin Qiao
So as to become like her
Then I lose myself
Do you think it's worth it?
Look what it says
Life can not be without pepper
Youth is not youth without dreams
Do you remember what I told you
On the path to your dreams
There are traps everywhere
Now,Xin Qiao thinks you are imaginary enemy all the time
Last time she made you miss the plane
And then we don't know what she's gonna do
Do you think if I'm right?
You... You shook your head
What do you mean?
It is really good
Eat as much as you like
Good morning! Coach Luo
Good morning! Have you had breakfast yet?
I'm not in the mood to eat right now
I'm so worried
On our team
You are the most steady person
So much has happened now
You're still in the mood for breakfast and coffee.
Very fierce!
It's not a big deal
We just had a board meeting. Nothing happened.
Isn't it a big deal?
Fang Gu retired
Who do you think will be the captain?
Isn't it?
In this case
Let's go back and talk it over
Don't worry
Coach Cao
Do you have a team leader in mind?
I think...
What do you think of Yao Huo?
How nice Yao Huo is!
He's been the longest on our team
We have to choose the captain according to seniority
Isn't it? Coach Luo
Seniority is only one facctor.
The main reason is huo yao's golden period has passed
Although his performance these two years is relatively stable
But he didn't surprise me.
Coach Luo, What is your meaning?
You're amazing!
Positioning, awareness, coordination
Every aspects are very good
You have a gift
That's because everyone works together.
I was really nervous
Both of my palms were sweating all the time
Modesty is not in fashion here
It's not like you've only been playing for three years
He has been playing better than you for three years
You'll follow me later
Why is he following you again?
Didn't we say the new guy would follow me?
The newcomers follow me
Stop!Stop!
Brother Yao, what do you think?
Brother Yao?
Good.He's the best of the new boys
Come on
Okay, I'll announce it now
From today
Nan Li officially became a member of our Legendary team
Thank you
Thank you for your attention
Come on!come on!
It's your treat tonight
Your treat tonight
You just get used to it
Gu fang is retiring
I think everyone knows about it already
Today
I've called everyone together to discuss a matter
Who can take the captain's burden instead of gu fang?
In fact, the best candidate is here
Xiangkong Ji
He has been the leader of the team
And the lineup and tactics are he and coach Luo ordered
His ability should be seen by all
I think...
He is the best candidate
Let me say one word here
It just so happens that everyone is here today
Let's just go back to the last game
Let's find out what the problem is.
Why did we lose the game?
This is the first game
Xiangkong Ji was killed seven times
He was hit five times in the second game
There are 16 teams in all
Data from 80 players
Ji xiangkong was last
Should we think about it
Is there a problem with the player's ability?
Everybody
Actually, the biggest responsibility for losing this game lies with me
It's because I'm selfish
Gu Fang...
In the first inning
Because Xiangkong Ji wanted to protect me, he lost seven points
And at halftime
I heard everything he told you in the lounge
What did he say?
What are you doing here if you don't training ?
Their meeting today will be abnormal
It's been a long time
Do you think there will be any trouble?
No, when did you fuck the president?
No,you think about it.
Ever since we got back from vancouver
Zhao Yang is bothering us every day
And make it hard for us every day
You see him, you see him.
Look at him
Do you think he'll say anything in front of chairman Jin?
All right, don't worry about it
Come back with me for training
No,we...we...
Let's go!
I'm coming. I'm coming
He knew I wasn't in good form.
Even if he had been shot so many times,
he can't protect me
His sacrifice really gave the team a big advantage
Fang Gu
You brought Xiangkong Ji into the team
If youwant to protect him
There are many reasons
But the problem is
Even the fans know
Xiangkong Ji's ability is insufficient
We're a professional team
Why should we care about the unprofessional comments on the Internet?
Now it's fan economy
We can't help but look at it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm a little emotional
I'm sorry
For the dream
We just hold on to today
But dreams don't fill the stomach.
A commercial team
The most important position is the captain
We have to find another star player like Fang Gu
Let him take on the responsibility
With Xiangkong Ji's current public image
If we make him captain
The fan will yell at us
Winning the championship
It is the best explanation to the fans
Why our Legend can become the top team in the country?
Why does our team have so many loyal fans?
This is because our goal is consistent
To win the world championship
This is the basic
We can't put the cart before the horse
But the thing is we're going to...
All right, all right, all right
Originally
We were supposed to discuss the matter together.
Everyone gave his opinion
Everyone has their own reason
Let's do it this way
Let's give him a try
I just got a message
IConquer is launching five new heroes
A new version of the beta will be held
Let Xiangkong Ji as acting captain to participate in the game
Use it as a test to test him
Everybody
Captain,Coach
May I have your attetion,please.
Let me make an announcement
From today on
Xiangkong Ji
He is our acting captain
No. Why the acting captain?
He should just be the captain
That's right
You talk so much
The captain is a man of no ability
Even if you sit on it now
you will fall down sooner or later
That's right
What manager Zhao said is reasonable
I haven't been a group leader since I was a child
Now I'm suddenly the captain
I'm not used to it
You get used to it.
Xiangkong, this is just a transition
I believe in you
Everyone should follow Xiangkong have a good match in the future
I'm sure he can lead you
How's that?
Are there still unconvinced?
Dare a disobedient man play a game with me?
I agree.Do you agree?
Do you have a problem?
I don't have, I don't have.
Captain,in the future
I'll be with you from now on
Didn't you say you were following me?
I won't follow you
You're not the captain
Isn't that right, Brother Yao
It's right
Congratulations to you!
Thank you, Brother Yao
Thank you for your support
But the new version of the beta is about to begin
Since everyone is with the goal of winning
I'd like to make three demands on the company
A new broom sweeps clean
You have the nerve to ask the company
Come on, let me hear it
First
We need to train fast.
So there's no time for  commercial activities
Secondly
I have a customized training program with my coach
I expect everyone to cooperate unconditionally
Thirdly
Each team is upgrading equipment
Our equipment also needs upgrading
OK
I agree with Xiangkong Ji's three demands
Everyone who agrees with it clap
Manager zhao has always supported us unconditionally
I don't think he'll say no
Isn't it?
Then I'll thank manager zhao
In the future
Please give manager Zhao a lot of attention .
Manager zhao,please be careful where you walk
Leave youself
A group of uneducated  people
Manager zhao
Don't be angry
It's not certain yet!
Calm down and have a cup of tea
I don't drink
He was just an acting captain
I wonder what he's proud of?
He challenge me in front of so many people
He also said that
They do not engage in all commercial activities
That's not for him to decide
The activities are all arranged
if he doesn't go
How much will I have to lose?
yes,yes,yes
Anyway
Xiangkong Ji is just wanted to stop me from making money
Xiangkong Ji also relied on Fang Gu
When the retirement dinner is over
The Fang Gu is gone
How long do you think he can stay proud?
Why don't we find someone from the outside
The man had to be famous and focused on the game
Chairman Jin was absolutely pleased with the man
Is that the man you mean?
Mannager Liu, are you looking for me?
Wait a moment
Let's settle the matter like this, manager Liu
OK
Ying Qiu,come and sit down
Manager Liu
I've noticed that you don't look very well recently
From the personal column of the heat and attetion of live broadcast
They've all come down too much lately
Manager Liu,in fact I have been training hard
But I don't know why I can't practice well
I made a lot of mistakes when I played
Can you consider the diversity of the programs?
For example, you combine the game analysis with your individual talents.
Manager Liu, here is what I think
I think the IConquer version is a professional version of pro sports
I don't want people to think I'm unprofessional as a host
You set high standards for yourself
This is a good thing
But you know there is too much competition in our industry
I can only give you one month
If the problem hasn't been solved by then
I can only apologize for that
I get it
She's been in there a long time
What hasn't she come out yet?
How's it going, Ying Qiu?
A month
A month?
In a month
If my show doesn't catch on
I'll be fired
Yiyi Lu, come in
Now I'll go in and deliver his papers to him
Why did manager Liu suddenly do this to you?
I know why he did this to you.
Just now I watched Xin Qiao go in for a long time
Then he called you in there
This is not a good thing
She helped manager Liu to appease
manager Zhao of Legends
Of course he will help more valuable people
This is normal
I should blame my lack of professional ability
The company is good everywhere
The coffee made in this coffee machine is not as good as
the coffee made by hands outside
Yanyan
Actually, I miss the days when you bought me coffee
when you bought me coffee
You didn't fire me.
I fired you
Don't be angry.Let's eat the shrimp
Don't be unhappy
Thank you
Come on, cheers!cheers!
Be happy
You're a guy who
sends me positive messeges every day
Then your actions are more honest
than your mouth
Impulse is the devil
I really want to know
how manager Liu bullied you today
so that you suddenly broke out
Actually, he didn't abuse me today
He's just touching his feet
What?
I watched him touch his feet
and read my mancscript
The words you said to me
just come back to me
You have nothing to fear.
You ae Yiyi Lu
You have substance and talent
You're not afraid of not getting a job
Then I told him impulsively
Manager Liu, please don't take my manuscript
with your hands that have dug out your feet
You're still laughing at me
No, you're so cool. Really
Cool? The jobs are gone
How's your job going?
Ever since you come back from vancouver
Manager Liu hasn't let you go out
for a live interview.
You don't want to sing and dance
The popularity of personal column is not good
But if you want to go professional
It's not something you can do in a month or two, is it?
If you want to be popular now
you can only create hot spots
What is your meaning?
How do you make hot spots?
I have an idea
Did you say your necklace
was broken by Xiangkong Ji?
Don't mention this man to me
Did he still say he would grant you
anything you asked for?
Did I remember that correctly?
So?
We can count on him for attention
Let him to help you advertise
For example,at two in the moring
Esports handsome boy
accepts the invitation beauty host
You... Stop! Stop!
What a bad idea!
Can you give me a good idea?
Isn't that a good idea?
How about this idea?
You ask him to play a double qualifying with you
When the time comes
I asked a friend to write a promotional article for you
The title of the article is
Famous professional esports player
live double qualifying with beautiful female hosts
I promise to make you popular with fans
who like the IConquer
How about it?
Yiyi
I really don't want to have anything to do
with these people anymore
And this sound...
This sounds like a deal
I don't like doing that
Sister
It was he who did the wrong thing
Not you
Secondly
Is there any other way for us to go
besides this method?
Don't forget that you have a mortgage
on your house every month
Is ther really nothing else I can do?
Chairman Jin
This is the player I told you about earlier
Xi Pei of WeiTeng team
is the biggest black horse
in professional esports this year
He is currently the no. 1 player in the world
I also learned that
his contract with WeiTeng is about to expire
If we can sign him over
Over the next year
We are sure to win the vancouver finals
For such talents
our Legends team welcomes you with open arms
Do Manager Zhao means to replace Fang Gu
with XiPei as the mid?
No
I wanted him to be captain
The captain?
He  was raised by Shuwen
They couldn't let him just switch teams
And I also studied Xi Pei
His hand speed and handling
are truly top-notch
But have you ever wondered
why Weiteng only finish fourth this year?
Because the other members of the WeiTeng team
are not good except Xi Pei
It is not that WeiTeng is not strong
but Xi Pei's playing style is too arbitrary
A pack of wolves can live well
but a Wolf cannot live
His personality
is definitely not suited to be captain
Don't shout
The audience like to see Pei Xi
a dozen of this kind of play
How interesting to watch!
How wonderful!
No one likes to see you
with this esoteric tactic you don't understand.
You...
So thirsty!
The two of you quarreled
when you met
Whenever you meet, you fight
What do you think, coach Luo?
I admit that
Xi Pei is a talent
But he is definitely not the kind of person to be captain
And how high the signing fee is!
Can we afford it?
This not your job decription
Don't worry about it.
Xi Pei's signing feeis high
but you should see how many Xi Pei fans there are
He can attract a lot of investment
There is many sponsors lining up to sign him
Chairman Jin
Since Fang Gu left
On our team
We don't have any more star players
It's hard to talk about
next year's sponsorship.
I'm also under a lot of pressure
Yang Zhao
Well,You talk to Xi Pei about it
Sure. No problem.
I have interviewed so many companies and failed.
I don't believe I can't get a job
after I leave YouXing company
Hello, are you Miss Lu?
I tell you
I won't buy a house or a car
I won't take out a loan.Don't bother me.
Wait a minute
This is Donggan esports magazine
Your resume has passed our first round of screening
Wait a minute
Donggan esports magazine?
Please hold the line
I'll be right there. I'll be right there.
What should I say?
Hello, Xiang Ji
Didn't you say you could
grant me anything I asked for?
No,my tone is too hard.
Xiangkong Ji
could you do me a little favor?
No, it's too soft
Let me improvise!
I'd better not do that,would I?
No
He broke my necklace
He didn't apologize to me
Why should I forgive him?
He talked all sorts of nonsense.
No