[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 2]
3,
2,
1.
My leg,,,
My leg hurts so much.
I'm sorry, are you okay?
Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
I can get up on my own.
I'll assist you.
She's fine, don't worry, get back to the car.
I'm okay, it's alright.
You should board the car quickly.
I can walk.
Are you sure you're okay?
Do you need me to send you to the hospital?
No.
I still have to look for Gu Fang.
I came to Vancouver
just to see Gu Fang.
I won't go back
if I don't see him.
You're Ji Xiang Kong, aren't you?
I am.
I know you both are teammates,
that...
Can you
bring me to Gu Fang?
You're my last hope!
I beg of you!
Seems like it's another failure.
How can I reject since you're
already begging me.
Hop on.
Really?
Thank you.
Your leg...
I was too happy,
I forgot my leg was injuried.
Let's go, hop on.
He shouldn't have suspected a thing.
Are you cold?
No.
Are you hot?
No, the temperature is just right.
Are you thirsty? Do you want some water?
No, thank you.
Are you nervous?
No.
Act, continue acting.
Is your leg still painful?
Still a lttle,
but it's a lot better now.
It heal so fast?
Weren't you almost a crippled just now?
I was still wondering
if I had to be
responsible for you for the rest of your life.
It's not that serious.
You're already helping me
since you're bringing me to Gu Fang.
I'm more than grateful.
Are you really Gu Fang's fan?
Of course.
I really like him a lot.
I'm his ultimate fan.
Then tell me
which year did he
first won the champion?
Which game was it
for his best performance?
Who was his opponents when
he first gotten wiped out?
You don't know?
I forgot
but...
But you must really believe me,
I really like him a lot.
Really.
Why are you so nervous for?
What is tricks is he playing?
Is he suspecting me?
I think I've seen you somewhere before.
So he wants to strike a conversation with me.
Add me on wechat.
I... This...
On a closer look,
seems like I haven't seen you before.
My apologises,
I've mistaken.
Play me?
Now we considered met.
Actually,
I took a lot of your handsome
photos just now during the competition.
I was saying to leave your contact
so it's easier to send it to you.
Look.
So handsome.
This is good too.
There's even nicer ones at the back.
Hurry,
send them to me.
Not bad taken.
It's because you're handsome.
where's my phone?
I left it in the main car.
Lef tit in the main car?
It's alright.
Next time will do.
Forget it, it's fine.
Keep my photos
well,
do not delete it.
It's so well taken.
Sure.
Ridiculous
and weird.
Seems like I met the drama king himself.
Gu Fang is inside?
Yes, captain is in there.
Hurry in.
Aren't you going in with me?
You head in first,
I'll come after I parked the car.
Then...
I'll wait for you inside.
See you.
Hi, how can I help you?
I'm looking for Gu Fang,
is he here?
You know Gu Fang?
Are you looking for someone?
Okay, wait.
Have you seen this person?
I don't know.
Team Legends,
very famous.
Gu Fang,
very very very famous.
Michael?
Did she just say Team Legends?
Yes.
I love those guys.
Gu Fang, is he here?
Where?
Oh you think he's here,
no.
I definitely would have notice if he was here.
-Not here?          -No.
Sorry.
I hope you find him.
Thank you.
Hello, how was it?
Did you interview Gu Fang?
Yi Yi, I was played.
I don't even see
Gu Fang's shadow.
Oh,
I told you to monitor Legends' fans
on Weibo,
what's their update now?
you... wait for a moment.
I'll look it up for you.
They uploaded a team photo,
seems like it's at
Vancouver's top pub.
Got it,
I'll go over now.
Captain.
What's wrong?
We sat here for half a day
but nobody dares to go over.
In any case, we are still
the world's second
okay?
First runner up is embarassing.
We are above millions
but below one team.
Is that right, Brother Yao?
Get high, come on.
Get high, hurry.
Not embarassing?
What are we here for?
we arehere for the champion
and not the first runner up.
Reflection upon yourselves.
Okay, everyone?
Hello, Yi Yi.
I've reached the pub.
I'm looking for him.
I see Gu Fang.
I'll take some background and environment first.
Ensure that the connections are smooth
when I interview Gu Fang later.
Don't worry.
This is your first interview
for Iconquer.
You tried to hard
to get an exclusive,
how'd I dare to be careless?
Furthermore,
you're to get even with me
if a problem arises.
President Liu will fire me,
right?
I'll go now.
All the best!
Captain,
don't think too much.
Don't you always tell me
that most importantly, is to stand up again
even if we lose the competition.
Those are words to comfort you.
If you were to say that,
your words hold no power
here with me
next time.
Xiang Kong, I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry for?
Losing the competition
isn't solely your fault.
Actually, I did saw
that you told them
to change my position with Huo Yao.
Captain, so you knew it all along?
My condition is bad now.
If I had supported you
in changing tactics,
we might not have lost today.
You already said maybe.
There isn't a 100%
guarantee tactic to win.
But I lost so unwillingly.
It's been 4 years.
I've taken the first runner up for 4 years.
I'm sorry.
Stop saying you're sorry.
Losing the competition
isn't entirely your fault, we...
I've played in competitons for 10 years.
I know my condition
the best.
My prime will not come back.
Actually, sometimes I know clearly
when they are attacking,
from where,
which route
but I just can't avoid it.
So it's because of Gu Fang
that's why they lost.
This is definitely a hot topic.
This... Is there a problem with the signal?
President Liu...
Hurry, don't just sit there.
Give her a call, quick.
I... why is it cut off suddenly?
Then.. It must be that she...
Call.
Pick up your phone and call.
Okay, I'll call.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Hello, Yi Yi.
What are you up to, Qiu Ying?
Why don't you interview Gu Fang
when you clearly saw him?
And what did Gu Fang
tell Ji Xiang Kong?
What can't be avoided?
Continue up
the video now.
That... President Liu...
I...
Shouldn't I
build up a good relation with them first?
You say,
if I were to get rejected
when I ask for an interview
it won't be easy for collaboration next time.
What did I ask you to go there for?
You're the host,
I get you to go there to interview...
I'll foot the bill.
Wait for me in the car.
Thank you, Brother Kong.
Sorry.
Don't worry, President Liu.
I'll think of a solution.
Don't tell me all these bullshit.
Go now, immediately!
Yes.
Hey, beautiful.
What are you doing?
I like you.
No.
Don't touch me, no.
What are you doing?
This is my Girlfriend.
He said,
my girl?
Okay.
Thank you.
You really won't give up.
Aren't you angry
for getting played?
Why would I?
You just saved my life.
Otherwise, I'll treat you to a meal next time.
Trying to satisfy me with just a meal?
Then... what do you want?
Simple,
turn right when you exit, bye.
I really want to thank you.
No need to.
You are the one that
pretended to be a staff
and sneak into the restrooms?
Be careful of your skirt.
Sorry.
What? Be careful of your skirt.
You have been continuously
been pretending to be a fan,
your motive is
to have news on Gu Fang right?
Sorry,
he does not accept any interview now.
He need time alone.
I couldn't care less,
I must interview Gu Fang.
Ji Xiang Kong.
Wait up.
Wait a moment.
I admit, I lied to you
but it's also because
of my job.
A self introduction,
I'm a host at You Xing Entertainment.
I'm Qiu Ying.
I came to Vancouver
to interview the competition
and to interview Gu Fang.
No matter what you think of me,
I still hope you can help me
because Gu Fang
is China's idolized gamer.
This battle for him...
Is it that females with good looks
have bad memory?
I've said it
very clearly just now.
Please do not harass him.
Or is that
you can agree to any condition
as long as you can interview him?
It's late now,
I still have work to do.
I'll write you my number.
I really wish to interview him
but I know
he's not in the mood now.
Call me anytime
when his mood gets better.
I'll go now, bye.
Remember to give me a call, you must!
You sit here.
How is captain?
He kept sleeping.
Manager Zhao called.
He said the fanmeet tonight
will be cancelled if captain drank too much.
This sly fox.
You saw how he was just now.
I don't believe he'll do this to us
if we were to win today,
But it's better if it's cancelled,
I don't bear to see
the captain now
forcing a smile infront of everyone.
Playing tricks with me?
Who's is it?
None of your business.
It's none of my business.
Driver, let's go.
Let's go.
Hello, Yi Yi.
Hello, Qiu Ying.
What's the situation there?
Interview Gu Fang yet?
No.
He just lost in today's competition,
he's still upset about it.
If I were to interview him now,
isn't it
a little inhumane?
At times like this, you're still
thinking if your inhumane or not?
If that's the case, President Liu is inhumane to you.
I intend to
ask regardlessly,
but
it was see-through, and I got chased out.
Forget it.
The main priority now is to
quickly do broadcast
of Gu Fang's fanmeet.
You have to start on time,
you can't afford to be late.
Who know,
maybe by then
you may even get the chance to interview Gu Fang.
Okay, I know.
I'm on my way there.
Then you better hurry up.
Don't worry.
The event got cacncelled?
Why do they only say it now.
Connect her on,
the broadcast is about to begin.
Nothing should go wrong.
Qiu Ying, are you there yet?
Let him see their official post.
It was said 5 minutes ago that
the event was cancelled
due to Gu Fang being unwell.
President Liu, the event got cancelled.
I don;t care for what reason,
or who's at fault.
The company has invested
a lot of resources,
this can't go to waste.
Let me tell you, Qiu Ying.
I want you to go on live
in the next 30 seconds.
You have to be online!
No, President Liu. Hello?
President Liu, Qiu Ying is alone,
can she do it?
Hello everyone,
I'm the host from You Xing Entertainment,
Qiu Ying.
Today, I'll bring you the lastest news
of Iconquer.
What do we do, President Liu?
The views kept going down.
You say,
everyone is here to see Gu Fang
but now the event is cancelled
our broadcast is
not necessary
to continue anymore?
No, it mustn't stop.
Is there other stuff
about Iconquer,
that is possible to push it up?
No, ask her to think of a solution.
This broadcast
mustn't stop.
Isn't this putting her in a bad spot?
If this broadcast were to stop.
we can all consider
to get fired.
Seems like everyone's
participation is pretty high today
but sadly,
today's event
got cancelled last minute.
I felt that it's a pity.
Legends once again
missed out the champion.
How about this,
I represent You Xing Entertainment
and give everyone
a special programme
as a form of encouragement to Legemds.
Please don't go away.
The programme is about to begin.
Everyone, please don't leave.
Qiu Ying is really going to dance?
Not bad.
She managed to think of something
despite there's no event.
Isn't this where the fanmeet
venue is?
Yes.
This Zhao Yang...
If it's not for him,
I couldn't seen Qiu Ying today.
I remember it now.
I saw her at the
pub entrance today,
talking to Handsome Ji for some time.
I think I saw her too.
Then why didn't you both tell me.
Are you asking for death?
Captain's asleep.
Handsome Ji, you know this Qiu Ying?
Are you farmiliar with her?
Introduce her to me.
I've noticed her for a long time now.
This kind of flamboyance acting
with low EQ
and uses online fame person,
how can I be familiar with her?
Handsome Ji is Handsome Ji,
he has such peircing eyes.
What are you saying?
Good, the views are going up.
Now
upload the video of
Gu Fang and Ji Xiang Kong.
President Liu,
isn't it not appropriate to
upload that video up?
What is not appropriate about it?
Strike when the iron's hot. Quick, upload it.
Even if it's against the officials, hurry.
I think
she's comparable to the
idol, Miya.
You're comparing her to Miya?
Brother Kong will beat you up.
Why?
Handsome Ji is Miya's die-hard fan.
What are you thinking? Die-hard fan?
Let me tell you
that's called being faithful.
Collecting Miya's albums,
that's called devotion, right?
He buys 3 of each album.
One for listing, one for keeping
and one for bringing around.
-Right?          -Yes,
I even bow 3 times
to her poster everyday.
Nothing.
Her dancing
indeed looks at little like Miya.
Brother Kong, do you know her?
Brother Kong?
Miya is too far out of reach,
why not just make
do with her?
Go to bed.
Although your owner is a little mean,
but that's not your fault.
I'll let you unleash your
usage for the last time.
Hello, Qiu Ying.
It was a close call just now.
Luckily you're quick-witted,
make use of dancing to fill up the gaps.
The views for the broadcast went up again.
Really?
That's great.
Alright, you worked hard the whole day.
Head back and rest early.
I'm already at the hotel's entrance.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
[Don't you think that Qiu Ying looks a little like Miya?]
Are they really similar?
Why are you sorry for?
Losing the competition
isn't entirely your fault.
Actually, I did saw...
Film in secret when you can't get to interview?
She really go all out
just to gain fame.
Actually you long know
my condition isn't ideal.
Don't blame me for being
nasty since you're like this.
It's still a little cold.
Maybe it won't be cold if I were to stand up and jump.
[Your necklace is with me, come to Marco Polo hotel tomorrow at 7am to ge tit.]
3,
2,
bye.
Is it out of battery?
Hello,
excuse me.
Hello, how can I help you?
I want to know him
from team Legends,
Ji Xiang Kong.
His room number.
I'm sorry
but we can't tell
client's information.
I'm his best friend
but his phone is
off now,
I think maybe he's still sleeping.
Okay, let me check.
Thank you.
Actually,
he checked out 15 minutes ago.
-Checked out?        -Yes.
My name is Qiu Ying,
did he leave anything for me?
No, he didn't leave anything.
Okay.
It's only just past 7am.
Tricked me?
Excuse me, maybe you
can check out parking lot?
Maybe he's still there.
What?
You can check the parking lot.
P, parking lot.
P!
Yes, maybe he's still there.
That's great.
Okay,
thank you.
-Good luck, bye.            -Bye.
Why isn't our car here yet?
Why is their car
so much bigger than ours?
This necklace is very important to me,
I'll go and get it tomorrow.
I'm already at the hotel.
Which room are you at?
If playing tricks on me makes you happy,
do whatever you want.
But you have to
return me the necklace
otherwise, I'll not let you off.
Please.
Please take good care
of my necklace.
What are you smiling at?
Your fans.
Are those my fans?
They are all here to support us.
This is China's fanbase,
right?
Hello, friends!
Hello.
Hey, losers.
What's up?
You all finally
won the champion after
joining Iconquer for so many years.
It's not easy, congratulations.
Losers.
If I were a loser just because
I lost in a competition,
then you guys
must have been one for many years.
We'll still be the champion next year.
Where's Gu Fang?
Is he hiding under his blanket crying?
-Talk nicely.          -Don't be rash.
Isn't he very strong when he used
Spirited Princess last time?
Why did he suddenly become
so so so useless?
Who are you saying?