[Gank Your Heart]
[Episode 1]
Qiu Ying!
Why are you only here now?
The flight has already departed.
What do we do?
You're really the death of me.
The driver booked by the company
sent me to the train station.
What?
Hello.
Is there still tickets
for the earliest flight
to Vancouver?
There's still one last ticket for business class.
How much is it?
31,500RMB.
I'll get it.
Qiu Ying, you're insane.
[2018 Iconquer World Championship]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the 2018
International Iconquer Champion Show!
I'm the host, Alan.
This game is played by millions of people
around the world everyday.
You can play as many as over 100 different
heroes in this game.
Let invite onto the stage my host and friend
from China,
please welcome
Sky!
Hello everyone, I'm Sky.
I'm one of the host for today.
Similarly,
I'm also
the Chinese translator for the show tonight.
I'm Luo Tian.
I wonder what President Liu is thinking,
is Qiu Ying even up for the job?
Yi Yi,
how is Qiu Ying over there?
I don't know.
I'm waiting for her news too.
Hurry on and contact her!
Hello Yi Yi.
Qiu Ying,
are you at the venue yet?
The competition is about to begin.
I couldn't hail a cab at the airport
so I travelled 2 stations by train
and I don't even know where I am now.
I'm trying to hail a cab on the streets.
If I'm lucky enough,
I should be able to make it.
You're not even on the way?
I've already
prepared everything.
President Liu is really pissed.
He said if you were to screw up
this live broadcast,
he's definitely...
I can't talk now,
the cab is here.
Sorry Sir.
Sorry.
It's my Boyfriend's car.
This is your boyfriend?
Where would you like to go?
Rogers Arena.
Okay, Rogers Arena.
Let's go.
Don't be nervous,
you're making me nervous too.
Just treat is as
how you play during trainings.
Is that so, Brother Kong?
Don't think about it.
Captain, we are ready.
Please move faster.
I can't move any faster,
the traffic is so bad.
Are you insane?
President Liu said,
people like us who does
reality shows
either convert to an Iconquer program
or we are fired.
I did not get this
opportunity easily.
I'm definitely going.
I can't give up.
But you have zero knowledge
on career battles,
what can you do even if you're there?
Yi Yi!
Thought of snatching?
If you were to buy this flight ticket,
you won't be able to pay for your house instalments.
If President Liu knows that I did not make it for the flight,
he'll definitely fire me.
By then,
all the more I can't pay for my house instalments.
I...
Excuse me!
Please, stop.
We are not even there yet.
I know.
Please, just stop.
Okay.
Everyone, it's about time.
Don't forget
the reason why we're here.
All the best!
Look at them,
it's like they are walking in slow-motion.
Oh my god, this is hilarious.
They think they are so cool.
Can't wait to see the looks
on their faces when they lose.
This is going to be so much fun.
Are you guys even ready for this?
Tatans, let's go.
Tatan!
They are the black horse this year.
They appear out of nowhere during battles,
defeating the other teams
one by one.
They are, Tatan!
Let us welcome
Legends from China
who is the champion for
10 consecutive games!
[Legends, Gu Fang]
[Legends, Ji Xiang Kong]
Welcome to the stage, Legends!
They got into the semi-finals
with 10 consecutive wins.
Similarly, they are the
first runner-up for Iconquer
for 3 consecutive years.
They are
Legends.
Gu Fang, mid
has high popularity
through the world.
He is one of the ace players
who once represented China
and won the first Champion.
Huo Yao, jungler.
Lu Feng, carry.
Li Yi Xuan, support.
Ji Xiang Kong, top.
Alright Gu Fang,
as the captain
of Legends,
is there anything you'd like to say?
Tatan's potential this year
should not be
underestimated
but we're in a longterm battlefield.
There will be no suspense
for all the accidents.
Jeffery,
do you have anything to say
before the match?
You passed your prime.
From now on, the world of Iconquer
is ours.
This era
belongs to us!
Fighting words.
Le's cheer for our heroes!
Alright, we will now announced
the competition officially begins!
Both teams please have a seat.
Jeffery, triple kill.
Legends are all resurrecting.
Is anyone able to resurrect in time?
On this side of Tatan,
they are ready to attack the base.
They are attacking the crystal soon.
On this side of Legends...
Hello everyone.
I'm the host, Qiu Ying.
I'm doing a live broadcast
on Legends vs Tatan
for the champion.
Let us congratulate Tatan
for winning on the first round.
The score is now 1 to 0.
Now we're looking at
China's number 1 commentator, Luo Tian.
We're only
2 meters away from him.
Even his back view
gives off an aura.
Film the stage!
Film the glass room and the members!
Let us have a look.
The first to leave
is the captain, Gu Fang.
What I just say?
Qiu Ying, you're doomed.
You missed the broadcast for the first match.
President Liu said
he doesn't need you
for other programs.
You say what do we do?
I don't wish to either.
Who knows thatI'll be stuck
in a jam on the way here.
Do you know how
how far I ran?
But I still couldn't make it.
I think
you should
think a something good
to make it up.
President Liu always wanted me
to get You Xing exclusive
and interview Gu Fang.
Just nice,
it's break time now.
Why don't I give it a shot?
Gu Fang usually keeps a low profile,
he never accepts
interview from others.
I can pretend to be a fan
and get first-hand news.
How are you going to sneak in?
Even if you're a fan,
I doubt you're even allowed
to be near their restrooms.
Yi Yi,
I can't talk now.
I got a way.
Gu Fang, are you confident
in getting
the champion after battling
at Vancouver for 4 years?
Of course.
Rumours has it that
you will be withdrawing from the team because
your condition isn't as good as before,
is this true?
We're running late on time
for the competition.
Thank you, everyone.
Here, thank you.
Sorry.
Captain.
I'm fine.
Your Tenosynovitis is acting up again?
Captain, you're my idol.
You willingly gave me a chance
when I was at my lowest.
I still remember
that you always tell me,
"kid, don't put up a front.
I'm still here for you."
Don't give yourself too much pressure.
Don't be emotional,
I'm the captain
and also the big Brother of yours.
I'm still here for the team.
Alright, let's head back.
Our Brothers are still waiting.
Damn,
will I get exposed?
Hold it right there.
I'm doomed,
what do I do?
It's not to late to apologise now right?
My apologises.
What are you saying?
Becareful of your skirt.
How is Gu Fang?
His hand is shaking very badly.
we'll lose if this persist.
So what you're trying to say is
to change our strategy?
Switch captain's and Brother Huo's position.
Jeffery wouldn't let
captain go,
captain couldn't do his best.
We might have a chance to win
if Brother Huo is to go mid.
Ji Xiang Kong,
what stupid strategy is that?
Gu Fang is being idolized by the world
as the ace player of mid.
You want him to play jungle?
What are you even thinking?
Manager Zhao,
Gu Fang condition isn't the best,
I can guarantee that.
Do you know how many fans are anticipating
Gu Fang's first battle
with Jeffery
in the mid lane?
What will people say if we were to
change his position now?
Gu Fang is a coward.
Legends is a coward.
This will affect the team
and the company's image,
do you know?
Zhao Yang,
if you're really
thinking for the team,
you should be supporting me.
Ji Xiang Kong,
watch your attitude!
This is the global semi-finals
not just any game, you know?
What tantrum
are you showing me here?
Ji Xiang Kong, remember this.
Gu Fang
does not only represent himself
but the whole team
and the entire company,
do you know?
You're the team's commander,
your task
isn't to formulate tactics
put rather, executing the tactics
and win the champion
okay?
I suggest a change of tactics
in order for us to win the champion.
Xiang Kong, whatever you're saying
has it's own sense
but have you wondered
how the world will question you
if we were to lose?
For the team and captain,
it doesn't matter
how they question me.
Anyway, I do not agree.
Xiang Kong. just forget it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
get ready
to make some noise
because the second round
is about to begin!
Hello, everyone.
I'm the host, Qiu Ying.
In the first round,
Legends lost a point.
Let us anticipate for the second round.
Hopefully they are able to make a comeback.
Everyone saw how
Legends made numerous mistakes
in the previous round,
the five of them
couldn't even handle jeffery alone.
Indeed.
So the first thing Legends did for this round
was to topple
Jeffery's most impressive White Rabbit.
In contrast, on the Legends' side
seems like a sea of heroes.
Especially the one who
goes by the nickname, Deception Master,
Ji Xiang Kong.
Iconquer has a total of
101 heroes
and there's none that he can't play.
But in the previous round, Ji Xiang Kong
was slain 7 times.
Some even said,
if they don't replace the crippled,
Ji Xiang Kong...
Brother Yao,
I'm letting Baturu to you.
Sure, no problem.
Gu Fang represents
our pioneer team,
the first Chinese team,
to get the champion.
He's a man that crosses eras...
Captain, which hero are you using?
So what you're trying to say is
to change our strategy?
Switch captain's and Brother Huo's position.
Gu Fang is being idolized by the world
as the ace player of mid.
You want him to play jungle?
Captain?
I'll use the...
I chose Creator for you.
Okay.
Gu Fang actually chose Creator.
Creator is said to be
the most difficult mid lane hero
in Iconquer.
He picked Creator,
what are we going to do?
Okay let's do this, I'm going to pick the Worm Queen.
Miki,
you're going to get the Dictator, okay?
Okay, alright.
Then we can
counteract his attacks.
Alright everyone ready?
Ready.
Let's do it.
How will you comment on
Gu Fang's current condition?
Gu Fang
as a contestant with age,
he's is very clear
on what he's about to face.
Okay, both sides have already confirmed their line up.
The second round
is about to begin.
Steady, don't get caught.
Okay.
Not an issue.
I'll be the eyes,
Lu Feng be careful of the minions.
Don't be nervous.
Bottom is disappearing,
bottom is disappearing.
Everyone, look.
This is Ji Xiang Kong,
he's the brains of Legends
who is able to turn the table
and also the team's commander.
Rumours has it that he never plays conventionally,
tactics are strange and variable.
Nickname,
Deception Master.
Oh,
he's definitely the visual
of Legends.
He has a lot of fans.
You girls only look at visuals
that's why you'll like
goodlooking yet useless person.
Why does he look familiar?
Let's take a look at Ji Xiang Kong,
taking down a turret
and going towards the warrior at the peak
while beginning an attack.
Solo time?
Is he insane?
Blue, come with me.
Let's get him from the top.
What does this operation means?
Is first blood going to happen?
Nice one, Xiang Kong.
They're baited.
Brother Kong,
you've tricked
two of them over.
In your face, Ji Xiang Kong!
Look,
he's the first blood again.
He's really such a burden.
Ji Xiang Kong
is the first blood again.
Captain, send another surge in mid.
Okay, coming.
Brother Yao, Ah Xuan,
both of you ambush on the opposite.
Coming.
Follow up.
Walk a little.
We can see that
Gu Fang and Jeffery
met in mid.
Dictator goes to the back suddenly,
sending a warming strike,
freezing Gu Fang in place.
Jeffery silences him.
3, 2, 1, attack!
Attack him.
We did not expect Lin Yi Xuan and Huo Ya
saved a skill.
Coming,
Lin Yi Xuan's skill
is able to control Jeffery continuously.
Huo Ya as
and amazing, natural occult force.
Beautiful.
It's the last wave!
Gu Fang casted a meteor
combining with Lin Yi Xuan's
King's Command.
Double kill, beautiful!
Damn it!
Let us see
Mars on the other side,
he came running back.
Triple kill.
The operation is a
literally asking for death.
When was he there?
The ace, Gu Fang
has gotten triple kill.
The entire venue has been ignited.
Sorry.
Legends!
This view is too spectacular.
The game has just started
and Gu Fang has already gotten triple kill.
This teamwork is indeed beautifully done.
Legends in one of the world's
top teams indeed.
They've already planned the attack
waiting for Tatan to fall into the trap.
Captain, this wave of operation
can be in your collections of best moves.
Everyone assisted well.
This wave of 1 vs 3 steadied us.
Out Brother Kong is the king of first blood.
What are you saying?
This is called strategizing.
But the way Jeffery plays
is still pretty impressive.
Let us be careful.
Let's protect captain more.
Rest assured.
They're coming.
It doesn't matter.
We're respawning.
Come on!
Keep going!
We can see that
on Legends' side,
is making use of the opponent resurrecting time
to push forward.
Furthermore, at this time
Legends are leading by 1500 economically.
This is a huge advantage to them.
If Tatan still doesn't
work hard...
Excuse me,
I have a question.
Why is it an advantage
to be leading economically?
When you have more coins as compared to your opponents,
it means you can buy better equipments.
There's still a need to buy equipments?
No, why are you here
if you don't know anything?
When Gu Fang did a counter kill just now
during his wave of operation
is so refined.
If it's not for Ji Xiang Kong's first blood,
Legends will definitely
have a dream-like opening.
Ji Xiang Kong's job is to be the first blood.
They still have Gu Fang,
it's alright if he's a crippled.
I'm guessing that there's no way
for Legends to lose this round.
Lu Fang, fight continuously for economic development.
If you can't attack, harass them will do.
Lin Yi Xuan,
come with me to jungle.
Coming, it's your showtime.
We cans ee that Legends
are starting a fog in opponent's jungle.
In order to investigate their defenses,
they saw a
spirit jungling.
Captain, I have it under control.
Push!
I have my Ultimate skill.
Captain, release now!
Captain, ampilfy it.
This skill is a miss.
No.
Gu Fang actually missed his Ultimate.
This is the global championship,
how can a mistake
like this occur?
My god,
this is so unexpected.
If Gu Fang did not
miss his Ultimate,
he could've killed Spirit instantly.
Don't push anymore, guard the last turrent.
I'll divert their attention,
protect captain.
Everyone look, Tatn's Jeffery
seems to go wild with joy.
Huo Yao is pushing
but Jeffery is going up against him.
I got it!
I said I got it, god damn it.
They are approaching in a grand manner,
Legends are putting their lives in the line.
All the best!
Block him.
Beautiful!
Gu Fang followed up with a metoer,
it's a blessing from heavens.
Full output,
killing Jeffery instantly.
The skills of other members of Tatan
are still on cool down.
Things aren't looking great.
It's the perfect chance for Legends
to flip the tables now.
There's hope for Legends once again.
Legends has started...
This is our last chance.
Captain, you retreat.
I'll go against them.
I can do it.
Let me do it.
Trust me,
I got this, I said I got this.
Tatan's support
is attacking Gu Fang now.
But why did Gu Fang
missed again?
This is very unlikely of Gu Fang.
Protect captain!
He's being controlled.
What exactly is the problem?
Where did his
concentration go to?
Ji Xiang Kong, he's here.
He used his Ultimate
in order to protect Gu Fang.
Jeffery purchased
flying shoes and continued battling
alongside with his teamates.
Retreat.
I'll go against them.
Under his influence of his Ultimate,
huo Yao and Lin Yi Xuan both got killed.
Retreat.
Let them in.
Protect captain.
There isn't enough mana for now,
mana isn't enough.
Ji Xiang Kong jumped into the fight once again,
unleasing his second skill
to protect Gu Fang in retreating.
Gu Fang managed to flee for his life.
But Ji Xiang Kong
anf Lu Feng can't hold on any longer to
Tatan's crazy attacks
and was killed when retreating.
What was that?
I said I got it,
didn't I?
Jeffery is really
out to kill them.
He doesn't want to give
Creator any chance of survival at all?
Although Legends
is in a state of absolute disadvantage
but they are not giving up.
Gu Fang charged out of the spring
single-handedly
wanting to block them from entering.
I can't hold on any longer.
But Tatan's controlling moves are too powerful.
Gu Fang is killed
under the Nexus.
There's no chance of countering attack at all.
At such a point of time,
although very unwillingly
but we have to admit
that China's team has already
tried their best in this round.
Captain,
let's go.
Let's head out and shake hands.
Let's do this.
Nah not you,
just keep going.
Well done, good job.
Legends
has already tried their best.
On such an advance stage
like this one,
their performance
made us proud.
Let us cheer them on.
Legends, all the best!
I'm sorry, everyone.
I did not perform well enough.
Don't worry, captain.
We will definitely
win it back next year.
Let's go.
The world of Iconquer
is ours!
Hello, President Liu.
Hello, Qiu Ying.
I just received the news.
Gu Fang might retire,
think of a way to find him
and do a broadcast.
President Liu,
they just lost the competition,
if I were to ask for an interview
and it's about retirement,
this...
Isn't too nice, right?
Qiu Ying,
our page is at it's peak now.
It's our prime time to gain popularity.
They lost the competition anyways,
capturing the hot topic is the main point.
As a host yourself,
you should've this professional standard at least.
Also,
Legends Official is organizing
a fanmeeting for Gu Fang.
We've already release the notice
that we're doing a live broadcast,
you better not
screw it up.
Yes, President Liu.
I know.
I'm sorry everyone,
we've let you all down.
Gu Fang,
never say give up.
We'll never concede defeat, it's the legends calling.
Cry out loud
if you want to.
Look at the fans outside,
They followed us all the way
from China to Vancouver
just to see us win the champion.
Remember their tears.
We'll use 10 times of hard work
to repay them when we get back.
We do not rest till we get the champion.
Let's go.
There are too many fans,
I can't move.
How about
I comfort them for awhile?
How will you go back then?
Isn't there another back-up van?
I'll meet you guys later.
Becareful and be safe.
I'll go with you.
We'll never concede defeat, it's the legends calling.
Everyone, calm down
and listen to me.
Don'y stand under the rain,
tell me if you have anything to say.
Okay.
Ji Xiang Kong!
We support you, Ji Xiang Kong!
We'll always support you!
We'll always support Legends!
Thank you.
It's okay, stop crying now.
Captain will be upset if he sees this.
We will continue to work hard.
There's still hope next year.
Handsome Ji,
I like you a lot.
You're my fan?
Yes.
I came specially to see you.
How specially?
I only look at you ans no one else.
Can I take a photo with you?
Why is it him?
Where's Gu Fang?
Here.
One more.
He's so friendly,
looks like the kind that does what you say.
A guy who can't reject people.
If I were to follow him,
I might even be able to find Gu Fang.
Thank you Handsome Ji, awesome!
Handsome Ji, all the best!
Bye.
We will always support Legends.
Bye, all the best!
Bye.
3,
2,
1...