[Subtitle from WeTV by Hwang_24]
=My Forever Sunshine=
=Episode 14=
♪What's wrong?♪
♪What's going on with my heart?♪
♪Never expected I would experience this feeling♪
♪Why am I being soft-hearted?♪
♪Why do I feel sad after you've left?♪
♪Am I crazy? I don't miss you♪
♪You make me mad and you are annoying♪
♪Then why?♪
♪My heart is always moved by you♪
♪I find it strange without you around♪
♪I feel lonely without you around, right?♪
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪I want to follow my heart so that I no longer feel lonely♪
♪Please come back and irk me, my heart will be full of vitality♪
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪Continue being my troublemaker♪
♪Even if you cheat me again♪
♪Come back and ask for my forgiveness♪
♪Maybe I'm obsessed with your waywardness♪
♪Maybe I have never met a girl like you♪
♪Who softens my heart♪
♪You make me sad for your leaving♪
♪Am I crazy? I don't miss you♪
♪You make me mad and you are annoying♪
♪Then why?♪
♪My heart is always moved by you♪
♪I find it strange without you around♪
♪I feel lonely without you around, right?♪
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪I want to follow my heart so that I no longer feel lonely♪
♪Please come back and irk me, my heart will be full of vitality♪
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪Continue being my troublemaker♪
♪Even if you cheat me again♪
♪Come back and ask for my forgiveness♪
(Previous Episode)
You investigated me.
So you shouldn't be surprised when I investigated you.
When you're hugging me,
it has turned me on.
I really want to throw myself at you.
Haven't you seen each other before?
I have a mining ground here.
It's not far from here.
Aren't you so capable?
He came out of a sudden to save her.
We had no other way.
Arthit.
You're getting in my way.
Do you want me to leave you here?
No way.
We have to escape together.
-Hurry up. -Get them!
You have to do what I say
because if we go together,
both of us may die.
Hey!
He is over there!
He ran so fast.
Where has he gone?
Look for him there.
Yes.
Brother Arthit!
Mark?
Why are you here?
I followed you from the exhibition.
But I'll explain it later.
Are you okay?
Mark.
I heard a gunshot.
I'm afraid that Brother Arthit was shot.
Is Mr. Arthit here?
We were caught here by some bad guys.
Brother Arthit tricked them into another direction.
Then, I ran out.
I heard a gunshot.
I am worried about Brother Arthit.
Calm down.
I think you should leave here now.
It's not safe here.
No.
I have to meet Brother Arthit first.
Okay.
I promise you.
I will come back for Mr. Arthit.
But now, you have to follow me.
Paeng, wait for me in the car.
Never open the door if you see a stranger.
I'll save Mr. Arthit.
This is my phone.
Call the police.
Mark.
You must find Brother Arthit.
I absolutely will.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Well, still won't tell?
I will.
Brother Arthit.
Brother Arthit!
Paeng.
You told me
you'd be safe.
I...
I'm sorry.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Can you get up?
Brother Arthit.
Brother Arthit!
Stay awake!
I can't carry you, Brother Arthit!
Paeng.
Don't be afraid.
I'm fine.
I just feel dizzy.
I'll be fine soon.
Let me get some rest.
Really?
Are you really okay, Brother Arthit?
Who is over there?
We are the police!
Help!
Hey, let's go!
Brother Arthit!
The police are here, Brother Arthit!
Are you alright?
Hang in there!
Check the wounded's condition.
Help.
Calling for help.
Are you alright?
Someone got shot.
We request an ambulance.
Calm down.
(Operating Room)
(Operating Room) Uncle, Thanon.
Brother Arthit was shot.
We knew it.
Doctor.
What is my son's condition?
The bullet missed the vital parts.
It has been taken out.
The patient is out of danger now.
Can we go in and visit Brother Arthit?
The patient is still asleep.
We will monitor his condition for one night.
(Operating Room) You may visit him tomorrow.
Is my son really okay, doctor?
We need to monitor his condition.
But he's safe for the time being.
Thank you.
Arthit is okay, Paeng.
Uncle.
Has Auntie known it?
I didn't dare to tell her.
But now,
she is probably asleep.
I'll tell her tomorrow.
Uncle.
Can I look after Brother Arthit tonight?
I'll stay together with Paeng.
Okay.
In this case,
I'll leave him to your care.
Please.
Sure.
I'm going to the police.
I'm not afraid of anything that may happen to me.
But I am afraid
that you will be in danger because of me.
If it happens again,
I'll be too  ashamed to face Uncle and Auntie.
Paeng.
Your clothes are dirty.
I'll take you home to change it.
I want to look after Brother Arthit.
Arthit should be glad
that you're worried about him.
Put it on.
Thank you.
Be strong, Paeng.
Paeng, you haven't rested for a bit, have you?
I want to wait until Brother Arthit wakes up.
I'll go home first.
I'll be back later.
Brother Arthit.
You got shot.
But you are safe now.
Do you remember?
Paeng, are you okay?
I'm fine.
That's good.
What's wrong?
Thank you for worrying about me.
You are worried about me, too.
I was afraid
that something would happen to you.
Why are you smiling?
I'm glad
that you're worried about me.
I'm thirsty.
The doctor said you can only take a sip.
Brother Arthit.
Are you hungry?
Is there anything you want to eat?
Brother Arthit, you look a little tired.
Do you want to continue to take a rest?
Hold my hand.
What?
Brother Arthit.
Why do you ask me to do this?
So I can rest assured.
Madam.
Yes?
Boss made a call and said
he'd pick you up later.
Where to?
I have no idea.
Has he left?
Yes.
Uh, what is he up to?
He came home late
and got up early.
What on earth is he busy with?
He didn't tell
where he was going to bring me.
How do I prepare for it?
Hello, Uncle.
How are you, son?
I've talked to the doctor.
Don't worry.
Paeng, you can rest assured, too.
Yes, Uncle.
This is your clothes.
I asked Aueng to get them for you.
But I didn't tell her anything.
I just told her that you were with me.
Okay.
Paeng, go get changed
and go back for a rest.
I'll look after him.
No, Uncle.
I want to stay and look after Brother Arthit.
Paeng.
Can you ask the nurse
when Arthit can start eating?
Okay.
I haven't told your mother yet.
I don't know how to tell her.
But I guess I have to let her know slowly.
I'll bring her here to visit you later.
Be prepared for that.
Can you not tell Mom?
No way.
She's your mother.
If she learns it from others,
you and I both will be in deep trouble.
Well,
let's not tell her
it's related to Paeng, okay?
You want Paeng to look after you, right?
Arthit!
I'm sorry!
How do you feel?
I thought you were dead!
Who dared to hurt you like this?
Weren't they afraid of going to jail?
Arthit, are you okay?
I'm okay.
That's good.
Hey.
Why are you lying here alone?
Is no one taking care of you?
I'll look after you. What do you think?
No, thank you.
Why?
Someone is taking care of me.
Someone?
Where is that person?
She's gone to the restroom.
I see.
Is it your mother?
Hello, Auntie.
Hello.
Paeng?
Brother Arthit, do you need me to adjust the height?
Is it okay?
Alright.
I'll leave you be.
Paeng.
Help me move the pillow.
Okay.
Are they...
Is it okay?
I'll leave you be.
Paeng.
Uh, please bear with me.
I need to go to the toilet.
I can take you there.
That's okay.
Paeng, take me there.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Easy.
What?
What is going on?
No way.
Paeng.
What's wrong with Arthit?
I have no idea either.
Besides being shot,
did he get hit in the head
or hit against the ground?
I think so.
But
I don't know which part of his was hit.
Paeng, do you find it strange?
Of course.
Brother Arthit has changed a lot.
Look, I'm not the only one having such a thought.
Should we get a doctor here?
I agree.
Let the doctor check him carefully
and scan his cranial nerves.
That's not necessary.
Just get used to it.
Get used to it?
I mean we will get used to it.
Give him some time.
What has happened to Arthit actually?
Tubtim.
Okay.
Get right to it.
Where do you want to take me?
You said you would take me out at noon.
It's afternoon now.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
For what?
Arthit is sick.
He was alright when he was at the exhibition yesterday.
What are you going to tell me?
What happened to Arthit?
Calm down.
Our son is fine.
What happened to my son?
Arthit is safe.
But
an accident happened yesterday.
Say it, what happened?
Was he involved in a car accident?
No.
Are you sure my son is okay?
Of course.
Take me there right away.
-Let's go. -Dear.
Calm down.
Do you have any enemies?
I have no conflict with anyone.
I believe they targeted you.
Is it possible
that it's related to my farm?
Do you mean you're their target?
It's possible.
Are you in dispute with anyone?
Actually, it's not a big deal.
But this person
is the prime suspect.
Who is it?
I had a dispute with Dandim, the mine owner.
Mr. Dandim?
Yes.
Thank you.
We will continue the investigation.
Yes, please do.
Yes.
Brother Arthit!
Why do you leave the bed?
What do you need?
Nothing.
I didn't see you have any food today.
Have you had anything?
I...
I'm not hungry.
Then...
Did you look after me all night long yesterday?
Yes.
Did you get a rest?
Paeng.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But don't make me worry about you.
It's almost one PM.
Go get some food.
I'll place an order for you.
You can rest better after eating.
I'm not hungry.
Fine.
I won't have dinner then.
I...
I'll have my meal.
I'll go downstairs for food.
Are you going alone?
I'm worried about you.
Brother Arthit, we're in the hospital.
Nothing will happen here.
Well.
Hurry back.
Okay.
You'll have ten minutes.
Uncle.
Arthit.
Are you okay, son?
I'll go to the doctor now.
I want to make sure you are fine.
I'm fine, Mom.
The only thing is that my wound hurts a little.
I don't believe it.
Do you want me to get up and run in front of you?
No.
Don't get up.
Stay in bed until the doctor allows you to go home.
By the way,
where's Dad?
Right.
He said he was going to talk to the doctor.
Have the police arrested the bad guys?
The police have come to take the statement.
Were you in conflict with anyone?
Why would you get shot?
Does it have anything to do with our farm?
I'm not sure, Mom.
But I think the police will catch the culprits soon.
If it is related to the farm,
just sell it.
It's not worth risking my son's life.
Next time, if I'm still the last one
to be informed
when something serious happens,
I will kill both of you.
There won't be another time, Mom.
Fair enough.
Why would such a thing happen to you?
I nearly had a heart attack,
you know, Arthit?
I'm sorry, Mom.
Can I fall asleep tonight?
The culprits haven't been caught yet.
I don't know if they will come back and hurt you.
The police have stepped in.
I think they won't have the guts.
My son.
Let me
look after you tonight.
Don't worry, son.
You can sleep with peace of mind.
Have a rest.
Auntie wants to look after her son.
So I'm taking you home.
I understand.
If Auntie finds out
that Brother Arthit got injured because of me,
she will hate me even more.
But Arthit survived it
because of you.
If you had run away
and left Arthit there,
I might have lost my son now.
How could I leave Brother Arthit behind, Uncle?
Brother Arthit risked his life to save me.
By the way,
Arthit wants you to move back to our house.
What?
I agree with him.
I'm worried about your safety.
We don't know
why and who is
behind this incident yet.
I think I'd better stay here.
I don't want to upset Auntie.
But Arthit is worried about you.
He asked me again and again.
He is worried about your safety.
He told me
not to let strangers into the farm.
I'm also worried about Brother Arthit.
He will be discharged in two or three days.
You can rest assured.
Yes, Uncle.
Oh, Nang is here.
Hello, Auntie.
Yes.
Brother Arthit.
Does it hurt?
When Auntie told me on the phone,
I was so frightened and I couldn't do anything.
Can I take a look at the wound?
No, Nang.
I'm just taking a look.
Brother Arthit, don't worry.
I have taken nursing courses before.
I promise,
I can take good care of you.
I'm almost recovered, Nang.
No way.
You need more private care
when you're getting better.
It's afternoon already.
Let me wipe your body.
Auntie.
I ask for your permission.
Nang!
Mom!
Mom.
Time for cleaning.
Auntie.
I'll
look after Arthit tonight, okay?
Uh, sure.
What's the matter?
Mr. Dandim.
The police asked to see you.
Miss Paeng, you are here!
Miss Paeng!
Everyone is saying
that Mr. Arthit was injured and hospitalized, is it true?
What happened to Mr. Arthit?
Who was that bald to hurt Mr. Arthit?
Miss Paeng.
How dare they bully us!
Phong!
What are you going to do?
I'll scold them.
Oh, Phong!
Hey, if this is all you can do,
be quiet then!
Let's listen to Miss Paeng.
Or else, I'll beat the snot out of you!
Sape.
Are you looking for a fight? I'll...
Do you want to kiss me?
I'll kick you to death!
I'm sorry!
Listen up!
Uh, Miss Paeng.
Is Mr. Arthit alright?
Brother Arthit
will be discharged in a few days.
Phong, Sape,
you can ask him yourselves.
It must be the people from the mining ground, right?
We don't know who the gangsters are.
I knew it!
Mr. Arthit must have been attacked by them!
I'm sure of it!
Everyone, listen up!
Everyone, come on!
Listen up!
Arthit.
The doctor said you could leave the hospital tomorrow.
Are you happy?
Thanks to Nang's care
so you've recovered so quickly.
You're exaggerating it, Auntie.
I'm only showing my concern to Brother Arthit.
I've chosen the right person.
I've told you, Nang is lovely.
Auntie!
Thank you, Nang.
I'm almost recovered.
You may go home.
I can't.
Auntie told me
to go home with you and continue to take care of you
until your wound is completely healed.
And I
agreed to it right away.
Don't you need to work?
Work?
I have made time for you.
I've sent a leave note to my father.
It's a long leave, one, two, three months!
Arthit, don't worry.
My father has agreed to it.
Mom.
I can take care of myself.
My decision is unanimous.
From now on, Nang will take care of you at home.
Oh.
I'll go back today.
Let Nang take me back.
Then, she will come back to take care of you.
Mom.
Arthit.
Why are you so scared?
I won't do anything to you.
Nang is right.
Why are you so frightened?
Let's go, Nang.
Hello.
Thanon, it's me.
I was about to visit you.
That's good.
Could you help me buy two mobile phones?
No problem.
Also,
I need your help.
What's the matter?
Is it about my sister again?
Alright, leave it to me.
Thank you.
My sister
always embarrasses me before my friend.
Pam.
Where is my car?
Mr. Thanon asked me to send it for repair just now.
Sent for repair?
My car?
Yes.
I only parked it here just now.
Uh, all the cars have been sent for repair.
All the cars at home?
Mr. Thanon said that you wouldn't go out today.
Oh!
Why doesn't he get permissions before doing anything?
Where is Brother Thanon?
Mr. Thanon just drove out.
He sent all the cars at home for repair,
except his?
What a crazy brother!
How am I going out?
Miss Paeng!
What's wrong, Sape?
Mr. Arthit gave us a call
and asked you to go to the hospital right away!
What's wrong with Brother Arthit?
I have no idea, Miss Paeng!
Be quick!
Miss Paeng, hurry up!
Hello.
Miss Paeng has left home, Mr. Arthit.
I saw her take a lot of food with her.
Well done, Sape.
Thank you.
Yes.
Hey.
I should go back, right?
Yes.
Why do you get so close to me?
I lost my value
after bringing you the mobile phones, right?
I want you to give me a little attention.
Go back.
Thank you.
Fine.
I'll go back.
I'll go back to Ling.
You may go.
Bye.
Paeng, thank you.
What are you doing here?
(Pregnancy and Birth)
(Pregnancy and Birth) Why can't I be here?
You know what you've done.
How dare you ask me!
What have I done?
Are you here to see how serious Brother Arthit's gunshot wound is?
I can sue you
for falsely accusing me.
What are you doing here then?
For sure, I'm here to visit my friend.
Visiting your friend?
Mark, my friend
was also injured and hospitalized.
Really?
If you don't believe me,
check it out yourself.
He's in Ward 6602.
I have to leave.
(Patient: Mark Tanikeji)
Mark.
Paeng.
Miss Paeng was out long ago.
Why isn't she here yet, Sape?
I don't know.
You have to know, Sape.
How would I know, Mr. Arthit?
I didn't go with her.
Mr. Arthit.
Would Miss Paeng run back to Bangkok?
Enough.
Talking to you is totally unbearable.
I'll hang up now.
Mr. Arthit! What?
Paeng.
Why are you here so late?
I was going to look for you.
Brother Arthit, why do you get out of bed again?
I'm alright now.
Sape said you brought me something.
I've given it to someone else.
Whom did you meet?
I went to see Mark.
What?
Where did you meet him?
How did you meet him?
You don't have his contact number.
I saw him in the hospital.
Did he follow us here?
No, Brother Arthit.
Listen to me.
Mark is hospitalized.
He was shot, too.
Paeng, tell me.
Why is Mark involved?
I saw him in the forest.
He rescued me.
Then, he went in to look for you and save you.
Did he come to save me?
Why would he pop up in the forest?
Don't you think it's more like an arranged encounter?
I had the same thought at the beginning.
But he explained it.
What did he say?
I saw you being taken into the car.
You looked unconscious.
So I got back to my car
and followed them.
I didn't see where their car was going.
I called you
while looking around.
And then, I found
that the car was parked on the roadside.
I called the police
and got off the car to look for you.
In the end, I found you.
After that, I heard gunshots.
You went to save Brother Arthit after that?
Yes.
But I ran into the gangsters.
So they shot me.
You got shot, too?
Really?
I'm very sorry
for causing you to be shot.
I'm relieved
as long as I know you are safe.
But are you okay?
Yes, I'm safe.
I didn't know you were injured.
How is Mr. Arthit?
Brother Arthit was also shot.
But he's safe now.
By the way,
don't you have anyone to take care of you?
I feel so sorry about it.
If I knew it,
I'd visit you on the first day.
I'm glad that you're worried about me.
In this case,
you can take care of me.
Sure.
Paeng.
Do you know who they are now?
I don't know.
The police have come to me to take a statement.
They looked familiar, as if I have seen them.
But I can't recall.
Do you believe him?
But I indeed saw him
go to save you.
Do you really believe in him?
Will someone like him save me?
Brother Arthit, what do you mean?
I don't think it was a coincidence.
He went there on purpose.
This is all his doing.
Brother Arthit.
I know
you don't like Mark.
He was injured and yet you're suspecting him.
I think you're too much.
Not at all, Paeng.
I don't believe him anyway.
Brother Arthit.
Will anyone be that crazy to shoot himself?
How serious is his injury?
It's almost like yours.
The bullet missed the vital parts.
Paeng.
Before the culprit is caught,
I don't want you to see that man again.
I'd be ungrateful
if I don't visit him.
You'll go with me then.
-But... -Paeng.
Enough, I feel dizzy.
Okay.
Don't call him "that man".
You should be polite.
No way!
I don't believe him at all.
What have you done?
Have you ever considered me?
I didn't mean it.
That was an accident.
You shot Arthit.
Was it only an accident?
I just wanted to frighten him.
He moved to the bullet himself.
Yes, it was my fault.
I didn't ask you about your plan earlier.
Actually, Arthit was not in my plan.
But everything is in a mess now.
It's all because he had a finger in the pie.
What should we do now?
This happened in my place.
Everyone knows that I had a conflict with him.
I'm bearing the blame for you.
Why are you so anxious?
They don't know who did it.
You are overly confident.
You may ruin yourself.
You are asking for trouble.
That's why you've paid a huge price.
This the only way to settle this matter.
And you won't be involved too.
I have sent the people who did this for you
somewhere else.
Stop pestering that woman.
No.
Mr. Mark.
She's just a woman. Is she this important?
Yes.
She is important to me.
That's your business.
But I won't help you again.
Mr. Dandim.
The police are requesting to search
the old warehouse with a warrant.
They won't let me go, right?
They insist on getting the evidence against me.
Mr. Dandim,
why are you so protective of your friend?
I'm repaying his kindness.
He once saved my life.
Take a bite.
Ling, are you ready?
Yes.
Hello, Arthit.
What's up?
Ling and I are going to visit you.
Sorry, we'll be a little late.
Save yourself the trouble.
Why?
I'm sleepy.
Arthit is sleepy.
Okay, then.
Get some rest.
Paeng.
What are you doing?
Oh, you said you were sleepy.
So I'm adjusting the height.
I'm not sleepy yet.
I just
don't want him to be here.
I only want the two of us to be here.
This is my shirt.
Just settle for it.
Should I stay here and look after you, Brother Arthit?
If you don't look after me,
who will?
Brother Arthit.
You have your family
and friends.
But he has no one.
You are thinking about Mark.
You want to take care of him.
Whether I want it or not,
that's my responsibility, isn't it?
Then, I'll ask you to take the responsibility
and take care of me.
Are you willing to do that?
Sure.
I will stay here and look after you tonight.
But I request to take care of Mark tomorrow.
Who are you looking for?
Paeng told me that you were shot.
So I'm here to visit you.
You're here to visit me
or to see Paeng?
Both.
That day,
why were you there?
I think Paeng has told you about it.
Yes, she has.
But I don't believe it.
You don't like me.
That's why you don't believe it.
Do you know
why you got shot?
Did you make enemies?
I've never made enemies.
But it's another story if someone wants
to make enemies with me.
I think you must have gotten in someone's way.
It's good to be careful.
I think
it's just a mad dog's random attack.
I won't be afraid.
Paeng is in the ward, right?
Stop pestering Paeng.
Why should I?
I'm so attracted to her.
And I believe that Paeng wants to come to me
if she isn't stopped by someone.
Then, you should know
I have Paeng's ear.
Well, you have her ear for the moment.
But can you stop her for a lifetime?
I will get the evidence
and find out
who shot me
and took Paeng away.
And I believe
I didn't suspect the wrong person.
Remember to share the message with me.
I was shot, too.
Please tell Paeng
that I am lonely.
Brother Arthit.
Will anyone be that crazy and shoot himself?
He is scarier than you can imagine.
He made it clear that we should stay out of his business.
Paeng.
We've arrived.
Where are we, Brother Arthit?
Brother Arthit.
Why aren't we going home?
Whose house is this?
Wow.
It's so beautiful.
Where is this place?
Paeng.
I want to get some rest.
Go home and take a nap if you want to rest.
What are you doing here?
Do you want to go back to your sleep?
No.
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
Okay, I'll get some rest now.
I'm not feeling very well.
Brother Arthit.
Whose home is this?
Let me sleep a little longer.
Let go of my hand.
Brother Arthit!
I'm here.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't come last night.
Thanon fooled me,
so you had to stay in the hospital alone.
Did you feel lonely?
Can you leave the hospital today?
Where is Arthit?
Am I in the wrong ward?
I'm so sorry.
It's the right ward.
Is it possible that Arthit has gone home?
You're up.
You were asleep, so I didn't wake you up.
I really envy you.
You sleep a lot.
Don't accuse me.
I just took a short nap.
I sat beside you for hours.
Do you want to have your meal or take a shower first?
I want to talk to you first.
Brother Arthit, are you ready for a talk?
Have your meal first then.
We'll talk after,
alright?
Please take a seat.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
It looks delicious.
I didn't expect that you could cook.
There are many things that you've never expected.
Why are you smiling?
Because I am happy.
Brother Arthit!
Yes?
Are you happy when you're with me?
Yes.
You are fooling me!
Brother Arthit.
Why are you doing this?
What's your purpose?
I understand
if you hate me.
I can also understand
if you want to forgive me
and bury the hatchet with me.
But
why are you doing this to me?
What do you want?
Isn't it good
that I behave this way?
I...
I do feel good
when you are good to me.
But I...
I am frustrated.
What makes you feel frustrated?
It's...
In the beginning,
you hated me
and looked like you were going to kill me.
But now,
you suddenly care about me
and you even saved me.
Well,
which one do you like?
Uh...
I don't know how to handle it.
Why?
Because I...
You hate me.
I've never hated you.
So, you're fond of me.
I am not!
You smile again.
Right.
Take a bath after the meal.
Your clothes are over there.
Why are my clothes here?
I asked Sape to prepare it.
By the way,
take this.
It's your new mobile phone and new number.
But you are with me. I don't think you need it.
Just in case
you get lost somewhere,
I can find you.
♪What's wrong?♪
♪What's going on with my heart?♪
♪Never expected I would experience this feeling♪
♪Why am I being soft-hearted?♪
Does it taste good?
♪Why do I feel sad after you've left?♪
Yes.
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪I want to follow my heart so that I no longer feel lonely♪
♪Please come back and irk me, my heart will be full of vitality♪
Brother Arthit.
Brother Arthit!
Brother Arthit, stay here!
Let's talk.
Brother Arthit!
Brother Arthit.
Can you tell me now?
Why don't you go home?
There are many reasons.
Tell me all.
I want to know.
Okay.
First,
I don't want to go back and let Nang take care of me.
If I go home,
she will definitely come and make a mess.
Isn't it good?
Paeng.
What's the second reason?
The second reason is
that I'm worried about you.
I think we are still in danger.
And the third reason,
I don't want to be with others.
I want to be...
Well, I don't want to hear this.
This is the most important reason.
Brother Arthit!
Why did you shout?
I'm right in front of you.
You are fooling me.
Am I?
Look at me.
Then, tell me.
Am I fooling you?
I got it.
You got shot.
You might also be hit in the head.
You may be schizophrenic now.
You surely have a concussion.
You've changed the way you call yourself.
You call yourself Brother Arthit in front of me.
You've been different since you woke up.
Have you noticed that?
Of course, I do.
I'm not as crazy as you.
Brother Arthit.
Listen to me.
Okay.
I'm listening.
I'll explain it to you.
Actually,
you hate me.
I hated you.
Yes.
You hate me.
But I don't hate you anymore.
If I hate you,
I won't do this.
Brother Arthit.
I think you need to see a psychiatrist.
I'm fine.
You're not.
Whatever.
Let me go.
Brother Arthit.
Let me make it clear.
If you remember everything after you've recovered,
you can't blame me for these.
It's you
who have brought me here.
You're holding me.
I didn't take the initiative.
Yes.
If you turn back to who you were,
you must remember what you have done.
I will remember that it's me
who kiss you this time.
You didn't take the initiative.
♪What's wrong?♪
♪What's going on with my heart?♪
Paeng, it hurts.
Why did you kiss me?
♪Never expected I would experience this feeling♪
♪Why am I being soft-hearted?♪
♪Why do I feel sad after you've left?♪
♪Am I crazy? I don't miss you♪
♪You make me mad and you are annoying♪
♪Then why?♪
♪My heart is always moved by you♪
It's me, Dad.
Arthit.
Tell me now, where are you?
Your mother is so worried.
I'm in another province.
How did you get there?
You haven't recovered yet.
Who is going to take care of you?
I've brought Paeng with me, Dad.
You took Paeng with you?
Yes.
I want to take leave for four or five days.
Why didn't you give us a call?
Alright.
I understand it.
What I can't understand
is why you took Paeng with you.
She's going to take care of me.
Are you worried about Paeng?
I'm also worried about her, Dad.
That's good.
You admitted it.
Anyway,
you have to respect her.
Oh, Dad.
You sound like I'm a bad person.
Since Paeng came back,
you have always behaved badly in my eyes.
Please go on.
Now you know it.
Paeng has changed.
She's asking more now.
Dad.
Help me explain to Mom.
Arthit.
I am worried about you.
I didn't expect
you'd fall in love with Paeng.
I didn't expect it, too, Dad.
There will be a lot of trouble coming.
I think we need to talk
after you come back.
Yes.
That's all for now, Dad.
You should ask before opening the door.
What if it is someone else?
There are only two of us.
It'd be a ghost if it weren't you.
I'm telling you
that you have to be careful.
Alright.
Hold on.
Brother Arthit.
What's up?
I want to take a bath.
Go ahead, why do you tell me?
Also, what are you doing in my room?
I...
I can't take off my shirt.
My wound hurts.
Oh.
How did you put on the shirt then?
I don't know. I was too anxious.
Sit down slowly.
Raise your arms slowly.
Brother Arthit, hold your arm.
Ouch.
Done!
Are you happy to manage to take off a man's clothes?
Are you crazy?
Brother Arthit.
You can take a bath now.
What's up?
Are you shy?
Whoever sees a man undressing
will be shy.
You weren't shy before.
What?
Wear your shirt.
Let me help you.
Don't be shy.
I'll wear it myself.
Brother Arthit!
Does fooling me make you happy?
Hey, hold on, I was wrong!
I won't do this again.
I'm sorry.
Does your wound hurt?
It doesn't hurt
when you show me your concern.
I'm glad that you're worried about me.
In this case, come and take care of me.
Sure.
Paeng.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Then,
can you take a bath now?
I forgot.
I can only wipe my body.
Oh, can you do it yourself?
Why?
Do you want to help?
I...
If you can't do it yourself,
I can't only help.
Uh...
I think
I'll do it myself.
Why?
Are you being shy now?
Brother Arthit.
Let me help you.
It's okay. I'll do it myself.
Brother Arthit.
I said I'd help you.
Don't be stubborn.
Sit down.
Hurry up, Paeng.
Are you done yet?
Brother Arthit.
What's the matter with you?
Why have you been urging me?
I'm cleaning your body to make you comfortable.
You should thank me.
You won't understand.
I can never understand
a nitpicker like you.
You're a nitpicker like me, too.
It's because I've been spending time with you.
I surely have to be a good arguer like you.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'll be gentle.
I really want to kiss you again.
I'm kind enough to take care of you
but you're fooling me.
Brother Arthit, your arm
also makes my heart beat faster.
Do you want to kiss me?
You fooled me and I'm getting back at you.
I won't play dirty.
Uh...
You seduced me first.
If you don't play dirty,
you can kiss me back.
♪What's wrong?♪
♪What's going on with my heart?♪
Brother Arthit!
Yes?
Brother Big-Head!
♪Never expected I would experience this feeling♪
Paeng!
It hurts.
You asked for it!
♪Why am I being soft-hearted?♪
Stop!
♪Why do I feel sad after you've left?♪
Paeng, no!
Brother Arthit, have you regained your strength?
No!
Doesn't your wound hurt?
Ouch, it hurts!
Are you fooling me?
No, I didn't.
♪I find it strange without you around♪
You can't lift your arm, right?
Ouch!
♪I feel lonely without you around, right?♪
♪Please come back and continue to stir my heart♪
♪I want to follow my heart so that I no longer feel lonely♪
(Next Episode) Brother Arthit!
You called him.
Do you miss him?
Are you happy now?
You played with my feelings.
Is it fun?
Paeng should be with me,
not you.
Brother Arthit.
You don't hate me anymore?
I've stopped hating you a long time ago.
Do you have any other surprises?
This is just the beginning.
Can you love me again?
If you don't tell me,
I will find the answer by myself.
You don't have to be afraid.
I won't let go of you.
I will be here to protect you.
Tubtim!
I think you've gone too far.
♪When the bonds between us disappear, would you stop being so cold to me?♪
♪You know I love you so much♪
♪I know I'm not good enough to make you fall in love with me♪
♪My words of apology were left here♪
♪I just made one mistake for once♪
♪Are you going to hate me till death?♪
♪Could I ask you a question that has been stuck in my heart?♪
♪I just made one mistake. Can't you forgive me?♪