[English subtitles are available.]
[Unforgettable Love]
Go.
What?
Hurry up!
How dare you sneak pictures!
-Mr. Jia.
Yiyue, let him go.
What are you doing?
This way, please.
Mr. Jia refused to cooperate with He's Group.
The cooperation with Mr. Jia
is a crucial step to
promote bands.
For this cooperation,
He Qiaoyan has been busy
for over half a month.
I'm so sorry.
I never expected
it would happen.
We had had an appointment with Mr. Jia
at 10 a.m. last Monday.
But because Qiaoyan was
concerned about your father's surgery,
the meeting was canceled.
Then, Qiaoyan
made lots of efforts to persuade Mr. Jia
to give us another chance to meet.
But again, you...
Qin Yiyue, don't you think
you've always been making Qiaoyan
a lot of trouble?
I know you're not a real couple,
but merely a contractual one.
How did you know?
Never mind how I knew it.
I had wanted to give you
more time for this show,
but right now, you've
severely affected Qiaoyan's work.
I just can't ignore it.
Even if we're in a contractual relationship,
that's our own business.
Stop deceiving yourself.
You clearly know
my relationship with Qiaoyan.
We have an engagement.
He has told me that your baby engagement
is just a joke.
It's a business of the two families.
Whether it's a joke or not
can't be defined by He Qiaoyan.
Besides, for Qiaoyan, He's Group
is more important than anything.
Do you think
you can compete with the whole He family?
Besides, I can help Qiaoyan run He's Group.
Can you do it?
Keep it real,
you are from totally different classes.
[Ep16]
I'm sorry.
All right, I'll drive you home.
No, thanks.
I can go back by myself.
How can you go back by yourself in this?
Do you want to beat a pervert again?
What were you thinking when
you dressed yourself like that?
Let me drive her back.
Did you come here with him?
I'll take her home.
Let's go, Yiyue.
I'll go now.
What happened?
I want to drink.
Had a quarrel?
No.
It's just...
I did something wrong.
If you do, just apologize.
If you don't speak up,
nothing will be solved.
Ning Fang,
Do you know that feeling?
It's like God suddenly knocking my head,
to make me realize
all the precious things I thought I owned
are nothing but an illusion.
They'll be taken back at twelve o'clock
to their original owner.
You little fool, you are the best.
No one can take them away.
I'm not pretty nor good.
I can only affect his work
and hold him back.
I...
What are they doing here?
My brother must be cheated, isn't he?
I must tell him now.
Bro, what's the matter with you?
How can you allow Yiyue
to drink with another man?
Did she drink?
You've offended her, haven't you?
Where is she?
Inside.
Why are you here?
Isn't it time for you to go?
Ning Fang.
No matter what happens,
I'll make it clear.
Wait for me outside.
You must be Dr. Ning Fang, right?
I've heard of you from Ruowei.
Go, go, go.
I haven't formally introduced myself.
I'm Wen Gu.
Ruowei's boss.
Go home.
Go home?
Go home with me.
Back to our home.
Qiaoyan, where are you?
Since it doesn't work with Mr. Jia,
we have to quickly figure out Plan B.
OK, I see.
Don't be silly,
I'll take you home first.
There's another meeting in the evening.
He Qiaoyan, I have no reason to stand by your side.
What do you mean?
Let's
terminate the contract.
Terminate the contract?
Why do you want to do that?
The validity of our contract lasts for one year.
There's still much time left.
Xiaobao, he...
he's been able to go to school without crying.
His language ability
is also recovering.
He no longer needs my all-time companionship.
I want to devote more energy and time
to my own career.
And I don't want to affect your work anymore.
I think what you need to do now is to calm down.
I'll give you two weeks.
Two-week paid vacation.
It's me who cannot uphold the principle
to be a fake couple with you.
A fake couple?
I'm telling you the last time:
go home with me.
I've told you, terminate the contract.
♫It must be a dream♫
♫The man I loved, where is he now♫
♫The sun just rose, but you still haven't come home♫
♫ The sun just rose, and I'm waiting in tears♫
You didn't ask me to stay at all...
Sit down.
What on earth can't I let go of?
Do you mean
I can't let go of the mansion or limousine?
I'm not superficial, OK?
Am I that kind of superficial person?
Let me tell you,
what I can't let go of is Xiaobao.
Xiaobao and I are good mates forever.
What?
Did you say I can't let go is He Qiaoyan?
You are the one who can't let him go, OK?
He's as cheap as you.
I won't even pay a dime to buy him!
Turn the light off and go to bed!
It's already midnight,
and what are you doing again at my house?
Well, eat melons.
Eat melons for what?
Fruit contains too much sugar.
It's not for bedtime.
Come on,
why did Yiyue burst into temper?
Is she cheating on you?
Do you think everyone else is like you?
You bastard!
I came here to comfort you,
but you are doing nothing but attacking me.
Or it's because of Lin Wei.
It has nothing to do with Lin Wei.
You and Lin Wei
once had a baby engagement.
About that, I've explained it to Yiyue.
I've told her
those were just nonsense from the elders,
so don't take it seriously.
I'm so relieved then.
Relieved? Why?
Neither Yiyue nor you cheated.
What's left is not a big deal.
Women, women.
Find out the cause and remedy the problem.
It's so easy to coax women.
Yiyue, what's going on?
Haven't I told you to declare sovereignty?
How come it was flipped around?
Good news travels slowly;
bad news has wings.
He Qiaoyan also agreed with it?
Maybe he also realized it.
Since Lin Wei came back,
I am becoming unnecessary.
Come on in.
Mr. He,
this is Pediatric Psychology Consulting Room.
Of course I know.
Tell me, why do you want to leave?
I've finished my work!
Besides, for my career,
I have a clearer vision and higher pursuit.
I want to do something extraordinary out there.
OK, I see.
But I hope these are not your excuses.
The title of Mrs. He is no longer what I want.
Pretending to be in love every day
is just driving me crazy!
And there are so many people who like you.
So I don't want to be regarded as
the one squatting on a toilet without...
What did you call me?
A toilet.
Squatting for a long time
would easily numb my legs.
So I'll leave it to others in the queue.
Let's put it this way,
I disagree.
Why?
The contract has made it clear.
Stage three,
Party B should, within the term of the Contract,
help Xiaobao successfully enter the primary school
and adapt to social life.
Yes, I'm doing fine.
Xiaobao is now gradually
adapting to school life.
And he's getting along with kids
without any discomfort.
I think I have finished the work successfully.
It seems that Dr. Qin isn't fully aware of
the definition of social life.
It seems I need to popularize to you
what social life is.
Social life is linked by social relations,
which means building relationships with others.
In the field of psychology,
"interpersonal relationship"
refers to the direct psychological
connection among individuals.
In terms of that,
Xiaobao hasn't achieved it yet.
In simple words,
Xiaobao just peacefully
entered the social environment,
but didn't let down his defense
to make friends with others.
Mr. He,
are you educating a professional
about their profession?
It seems that Dr. Qin also agrees with me.
I, He Qiaoyan,
never fail in business.
How about that: as long as you help Poppet
find a friend,
I'll deem all your work as done completely.
With the contract void and debts cleared,
you'll be free at that time.
What are we doing here?
Meeting parents.
Of course I'm a parent.
I mean,
meeting parents for what?
It's just a casual meeting.
What were you thinking about?
Poppet,
This is...
Guoguo.
Hello, Guoguo.
Hello, Uncle...
Uncle?
Brother.
My name is Cheng Guoguo.
I'm six years old.
I'm an Aries; my blood type is A,
and I live in Xinyang District.
I like painting and dancing.
I serve as the art commissary in the class.
Xiaobao and I have fun all the time.
He takes care of me and helps me,
and he can do the magic of physics.
I really like playing with him.
Okay.
Now that we're here,
if no one opposes,
we'll make an exchange.
Dr. Qin, they are just children.
Don't mess around.
Exchange friend cards.
Friend cards?
Now we can exchange hugs!
Xiaobao, you've done a good job!
Guoguo,
thank you for being good friends with Xiaobao.
The little skirt you are wearing today
is so beautiful!
I love it!
From now on,
You can play with toys.
What's going on with them?
To help Xiaobao,
I made a set of friend cards
to encourage him to make friends in this way.
It was a one-week
challenge of making friends.
Unexpectedly, he succeeded.
By the way,
just now, did Xiaobao say Guoguo's name?
Yeah.
Now he's able to say other names except for "Mom"?
When he encounters a special situation,
or when he meets someone he likes,
he can use very simple expressions.
So far,
the upper limit I've heard is five words.
Then why does he
still need to use cards or
a word-pad in front of me?
That means you should keep going.
After my departure, he'll only rely on you.
Come on, "Daddy"!
All right, I'm leaving.
Let me give you a ride.
No, thanks.
I'll find another time
to come back and pack up.
You've really made up your mind
to terminate the contract.
Our contract is temporary in the first place.
No matter it's sooner or later,
all of it will be terminated eventually.
Even if it's terminated,
we can still sign a new one.
The workload and working hours
will depend on your needs.
In addition,
benefits and the salary can be doubled.
It has nothing to do with money.
It's out of my career plan.
Fine.
If you have a higher career pursuit,
I can arrange a specialized
scientific research laboratory
and the best researchers.
You can do any research you want.
Thank you,
but that's not what I really need.
You should find a chance to explain it to Poppet.
And I should end
this ridiculous experience to start my own life.
Do you think this period
has been ridiculous?
Don't distort what I mean.
In a few days,
Xiaobao' school will hold a Parent-Child Day.
I'll accompany him to take part in the activity.
After this,
our contract will be completely terminated.
Here you are.
OK.
You can leave now.
♫All those mornings, laughing in bed♫
♫I thought laughter can get us far♫
♫It must be a dream♫
♫The man I used to hug, where is he now♫
♫The sun just rose, and I'm waiting in tears♫
I'm so sorry that Qianyan and you have to
make do with a restaurant near He's Group.
I do apologize for your inconvenience.
It's OK.
I know Qiaoyan is busy.
Young people should focus on the career.
All these years, the prosperity of He's Group
is thanks to Qiaoyan.
He's Group is really
striding forward year by year.
Wei is excellent, too.
Young as she is,
she's a famous designer already.
It's just her hobby,
and also her part-time job.
In the future,
she will eventually focus on the family business.
Aunt, Mrs. Lin.
There will be a meeting later.
I need to go first.
Enjoy yourselves.
Wait a minute.
We haven't mentioned the most important thing.
Qiaoyan,
both you and Wei are not kids anymore.
So you should discuss the time to get married.
Get married?
Qiaoyan, we all know that
you've always wanted to
run He's Group well at first,
but marrying Wei won't affect your plan.
It will help you, instead.
Wei is such a diligent girl.
Aunt, you must be aware that I won't
marry for the family interest.
Qiaoyan, you are very smart.
You should know that the marriage between
the Lin and He families means a lot to He's Group.
Of course I know,
but I won't sacrifice myself for the business.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for a minute.
As for Dr. Qin's personal information,
I looked through it again.
Anything special?
We looked up all Qin Yiyue's
experiences from birth till now,
as well as her social relations.
She was born in a working-class family.
From childhood till now,
she is well-behaved and excellent.
There's only one doubt in her experience.
When Qin Yiyue was in the university,
she wanted to be a surgeon.
But then,
she abruptly changed her major to psychology.
Why?
According to her teacher,
it's because Qin Yiyue saved a child in a car accident,
and got her hand injured.
A car accident?
When?
On the same day as Xiaobao's car accident.
Where was it?
It was probably on Huanshan Road.
Xiaobao's car accident
also occurred on Huanshan Road.
Qin Yiyue might be that person.
That's why Xiaobao has a special affection for her.
Does Qin Yiyue know the truth of the accident?
Mommy.
Your Mommy's not here.
Told you, Mommy's not here.
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy...
Can't you say something else?
Xiaobao!
Mommy!
Xiaobao, mommy is here today
to prepare for the show with you
for Parent-Child Day.
So, do you have anything
to show to your classmates and teachers?
I'm here to help Xiaobao
prepare for his performance
on Parent-Child Day.
I...
I know you're busy,
don't worry.
When I rehearse with Xiaobao,
I'll give you a simple role.
You just need to practice
right before the performance.
♫Blows the wind, shines the moon♫
♫Where is the boat floating to ♫
♫Take the long journey with me ♫
♫Blows the wind, shines the moon ♫
♫Where is the boat floating to ♫
♫Take the long journey with me ♫
Secretary Zhong,
Mr. Jia asked me to discuss
the band face to face tomorrow.
Well,
send all materials about the band to me.
All of them.
I'll have further discussions
on your improvement plan with my colleagues
in the R&D Department.
Although there's some difficulty,
it's not impossible.
Excellent!
As soon as your samples are produced,
we can sign the contract right away.
I'm looking forward to your good news.
No problem.
Well then, I'll go now.
There are other arrangements.
Mr. Jia, wait a minute.
May I ask what changed your mind?
Well, I didn't change my mind all of a sudden.
Actually, I've always been
very interested in your band.
But last time...
Last time...
Last time, Yiyue didn't mean it.
No, no, no, you misunderstood me.
Refusing to cooperate with you last time
had nothing to do with Miss Qin.
It was because you and Miss Lin
kept talking about data.
In the end, I just couldn't stand it.
Maybe you don't know much about me.
In the business,
what I value most is the user experience of products,
instead of something like data.
Mr. Jia, you are right.
Now it's because...
Thanks to Miss Qin,
I'm here to meet with you today.
The day before yesterday, she managed to find me.
She convinced me.
How can you go back by yourself in this?
Do you want to beat a pervert again?
If any other accident happens today,
how can you deal with it, Yiyue?
Poppet,
I've recorded the song in it in advance.
You can
just listen to the song in it.
Get familiar with it.
Tomorrow, mommy can't practice with you.
Because I'm going to the villa in advance
with Brother Ning Fang
to set up the venue.
Take it.
Yiyue.
Ning Fang, you are here.
Xiaobao!
Ning Fang.
You should call him Brother Ning Fang.
Brother.
Good boy.
Give me a hug.
Look at the present brought you.
Do you like it?
Take it.
Go and play.
Packed up your luggage?
Not yet.
I'll think about it later.
Can't let it go?
I just can't let go of Xiaobao.
Where's my phone?
It's on this Sunday.
Do you still remember
the concert we missed when we were in college?
I'll make it up to you.
Lin, are you busy?
Do me a favor.
Is there any way to buy
tickets for Xie Ming's concert?
Cindy,
is it possible to get me two
VIP tickets for Xie Ming's concert?
♫Blows the wind, shines the moon ♫
♫Where is the boat floating to ♫
♫Take the long journey with me ♫
Ning Fang, you are here.
Xiaobao!
Ning Fang.
You should call him Brother Ning Fang.
Brother.
I forgot to bring my phone.
Did you see that?
Look for it.
Can't let him go?
I just can't let go of Xiaobao.
Don't be so sad.
You like He Qiaoyan,
which should be a wonderful thing.
Even if you end up with a breakup,
you've also gained happiness while it lasted.
That's enough.
You're right.
Process counts more than the result.
Let's go.