[English subtitles are available]
[CAROL'S]
Be good.
All right.
If he doesn't drink,
we shall.
♫ Do you see the air? She's dancing ♫
♫ just like nobody ever cares ♫
♫ Let it fly. Let it rest.
Where will they be? ♫
♫ Although I got nothing ♫
♫ I wish you were there ♫
♫ So I finally ♫
♫ can't stop finding you ♫
You're so adorable.
How adorable.
Super adorable.
Your eyes are adorable.
But...
Why do you resemble Mr. Ai?
Zeng Li.
We should drink coffee again.
After taking advantage of me,
you're laughing.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 10]
Stop sleepwalking.
Cover for me.
I'm topping the arena's list.
Stop following that dunce.
The Buddhist Wild King Who Doesn't Kill.
Please.
[Wu Ying]
What are you doing?
[Lost in The Forest]
[Brother, the sister is so fierce.]
[Met You In Deep Oceans]
[It's alright.]
[I don't care if we lose this round.]
[Lost in The Forest]
[I'm falling off the rank.]
[Met You In Deep Oceans]
[Don't worry.]
[I'll spend the whole night
winning rounds for you if I've to.]
[Lost in The Forest]
[Brother, you're the best.]
Miss.
If you've energy to banter,
guard the tower instead.
Clear the path would be fine too.
What are you doing?
You're not moving.
Hello.
[I'm lifting the 98K]
and aimed straight at your head.
What are you on about?
[I'm going to shoot if
you do not go to bed.]
I was asleep.
Your phone call woke me up.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
Are you
playing games in stealth mode again?
I was in stealth mode,
how did you know I was playing games?
You were online 20 minutes ago.
I went to collect daily gifts
and went to bed.
When we quit the game at 10pm,
your amount of gameplay
were 2041.
Right now,
it shows 2046 games.
Besides,
it was five consecutive losses.
You...
You're a pervert.
I promised I'd attain
three stars every day.
You promise you'd
go to bed latest at 11:30pm.
You went against your word.
I planned to stop playing by 12am
and go to sleep.
I've been losing the matches.
I wanted to win a match
before I go to bed.
What a stupid game.
Stupid game.
[It wouldn't let me win.]
It's all your fault.
That can't be my fault.
I begged you
to play a few rounds with me.
If you agreed,
nothing would have happened.
I wouldn't fall off my rank.
Be good and go to sleep.
I'll help you earn it back tomorrow.
All right?
[No.]
[I can't sleep without
earning my grade back.]
No.
It's almost 1am.
[Brother.]
[Brother, you're the best.]
Brother.
Please.
What did you say?
Brother.
[Help me regain my rank.]
After that,
I'll go to bed.
[Brother.]
[Please. Come on.]
Sister.
Go online.
All right.
Let's go.
♫ I could feel it all about you ♫
♫ You don't know I was
thinking about you ♫
♫ It makes me feel alone ♫
♫ I never, don't you know? ♫
♫ If I know all that's inside ♫
♫ I could feel it all about you ♫
♫ You don't know I was
thinking about you ♫
♫ It makes me feel alone ♫
♫ I never, don't you feel ♫
♫ if it doesn't matter ♫
♫ You never know how much I love you ♫
♫ no matter you're with me ♫
♫ stars beneath your eyes ♫
♫ waiting for you on the other side ♫
♫ You never know how much I love you ♫
♫ No matter with or without you ♫
♫ stay with you ♫
♫ because I'm here to stay ♫
♫ When I know that I could ♫
♫ sleep tight on your right ♫
♫ When I know that ♫
♫ I could stay in your eyes ♫
♫ and forever hear you say ♫
♫ You never know how much I love you ♫
♫ no matter you're with me  ♫
♫ stars beneath your eyes ♫
♫ waiting for you on the other side ♫
♫ You never know how much I love you ♫
What am I doing here?
♫ No matter with or without you ♫
Wasn't I drinking?
♫ stay with you ♫
Where's Mr. Ai?
♫ because I'm here to stay ♫
♫ When I know that ♫
♫  sleep tight on your right ♫
[I need to leave for work.]
[If your head hurts,]
♫ When I know that I could ♫
[have some honey water.]
[Remember to brush your teeth.]
♫ I could stay in your eyes ♫
♫ and forever hear you say ♫
[Do not be distracted during work.]
Mr. Ai.
Remember to drop off the
patients' information
for today at my office.
Mr. Ai.
Mr. Ai, would you like a kiss?
What did you say?
I said,
Mr. Ai, would you like some cookies?
No.
Mr. Ai.
All right. Let's begin.
Should we kiss?
Mr. Ai.
What did you say?
I asked if the adhesive
would hurt.
Please go easy on me.
It's not going to hurt.
When etch is applied,
your teeth will feel a little sore.
Doctor,
after putting on
invisalign,
would it feel weird
when I kiss my boyfriend?
Excuse me.
I guess you don't have
an experience in this area.
It does feel a little weird,
but it's fine.
Why is it stained?
Thank you, Dr. Ai.
You're welcome.
[Zeng Li]
It happened last night.
It's like nothing happened.
She didn't even reply my text.
[Zhou Wen]
Dr. Ai.
The researches you asked for
the residents in regards to
oral thrush,
I found them.
However, I can't access the files.
I made screenshots
and sent them to you.
Can't you email it to me?
The phone is more convenient.
Is there a problem?
Nothing.
How many more left?
Around 56 photos.
The internet here isn't working well.
If the notifications
are bothering you,
would you like to mute your phone?
No.
I'm waiting for news.
Who are you waiting for?
Mr. Ai.
Pass me your phone.
I'll mute myself.
Mute yourself?
[Mute notifications]
I totally get it.
When you're waiting
for a text from someone,
everyone else's messages
annoy you.
This
is known as the symptoms
of falling in love.
Mr. Ai.
Would you like to head
to the library to read?
You're unusually
talkative today.
Sister Zhou Wen, let's grab lunch.
Let's go.
Mr. Ai.
Are you joining us?
Mr. Ai isn't.
He has plans this afternoon.
How did I end up
at the library?
What did she mean
by her behaviour last night?
Even if I ask her,
she would have forgotten everything.
Forget it.
Come here.
What are you staring at?
Did your Mr. Ai
put on skating shoes?
He has been rolling back and forth.
I think he's waiting for somebody.
Over here?
Who else could he be
waiting for besides you?
That can't be.
Mr. Ai didn't text me.
Hold on.
Since when Mr. Ai
became mine?
He can't possibly be
mine, right?
Mr. Ai.
What are you doing here?
Zeng Li.
I work here.
If I'm not here,
where else would I go?
On the contrary,
what are you doing here?
Are you going anywhere?
I just had lunch.
I was about to buy a cup of milk tea.
I'll get going then.
Let's go together.
Do you enjoy milk tea too?
I've a class in the afternoon.
There's still time.
I'm just taking a walk around.
Let's go then.
You haven't removed your braces.
You're right.
[How should I ask her about the]
[incident last night?]
[Should I...]
[Forget it. I shouldn't ask.]
By the way, Mr. Ai,
I noticed a problem.
The quality of the braces
isn't the best.
What's wrong?
I only wore it for a day
and it's all stained.
[You brought it up first.]
Your braces turned yellow
because you were drinking coffee
last night.
Coffee?
Are you kidding?
Last night, I recall us
drinking wine together.
Also, I clearly remember
removing my braces before that.
When did I put it back on?
Last night after drinking,
you dragged me
to your cafe
and made me a lot of cups of
coffee.
You even demonstrated
your latte art techniques.
Have you forgotten?
I think I did make coffee.
I had too much to drink.
I was really tipsy.
I thought it was all a dream.
Did you drink any?
No.
You took a sip though.
What happened next?
Next, you...
I?
You...
Think about it yourself.
Think about it myself?
Let me recall.
A dog!
A dog?
Yes.
I remember bringing home
an Alaskan Husky
from the skewers' joint.
I also brought it back
to the coffee house.
I also...
You also...
I also kissed the dog.
Come by the clinic at noon tomorrow.
I'll clean the braces for you.
It can't be the first kiss, right?
That depends on you.
It can't be.
It was a
really adorable dog.
What happened next?
Did you help take it home?
I can't let Wu Ying and
Yi Yi learn about this
or they'd tease me
for one whole month.
[I should be able to clean this up]
[before Sheng Ming arrives.]
[This is perfect.]
You're here.
Why are you all dressed up
at home?
Come on in.
Come in.
What happened to your leg?
It's nothing.
I hit something just now.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Be careful.
Are you sure your leg is fine?
It's fine.
Well,
where's your room?
Over there?
Stay here and wait for me.
On the count of three,
you say, turn on the lights, okay?
Three.
Two.
One.
Turn on the lights.
It's beautiful.
Previously, you told me
the bruises on your
legs
were formed
while you head to the
toilet half asleep at night.
With these lights,
you wouldn't hurt yourself anymore.
I was worried you'd find
turning on the lights a hassle,
so I installed a code
in your phone.
Next time, just order your phone
to turn on the lights,
the lights will turn on automatically.
You're so nice to me.
I'll treat you even
better in days to come.
I want a hug.
Yi Yi.
I should go.
I've to work overtime.
Well,
I shall get going then.
Hello.
I'm working overtime.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
I've lived for 26 years.
I'm doubting my charm
for the first time ever.
That means he's a gentleman.
Both of you weren't dating for long.
It's the 20th century.
He's not a monk
from the Great Tang.
You encountered too many players.
You're not used to dating
a normal man.
Wu Ying.
Wu Ying, what are you up to?
Why aren't you speaking?
Please criticise me.
She's probably gaming again.
Wu Ying.
Wu Ying. Wu Ying.
Someone must help her
with her addiction.
Wu Ying. Wu Ying.
Curse these women.
Stop bothering me.
[Defeated.]
Wu Ying. Wu Ying.
Our friendship is over.
Didn't your cutie
urge you to go to bed tonight?
My favourite function
on Mobile Legend
is stealth mode.
I sent a screenshot for Liu Yu Cheng.
Great.
It's exactly what I wanted.
It's 11:30pm already.
Why didn't he text me
urging me to go to bed?
[Liu Yu Cheng is in a sweet duo.]
Isn't this
the girl who has a crush on him?
How impressive.
They are going to spend
the night gaming together?
Go ahead.
[Exit game.]
It'd be best if he doesn't annoy me.
Are you out of your mind?
27 and 21
are not the same.
One is at his prime,
and the other is falling behind.
There is a huge gap in age,
but you're just as pretty.
Yes.
Give it to me.
Give it to her.
That's weird.
When I met her previously,
I didn't find her extraordinary.
However, the more
I look at her photos,
the prettier she is.
She probably edited them.
Don't worry.
Isn't that so?
Yes.
She must have edited her photos.
Come on.
Nobody's eyes could grow this huge.
Is she an alien?
There's another possibility.
What is it?
You're being paranoid.
Previously,
she probably meant nothing
to you.
You wouldn't even
pay attention to her.
Right now, because of Liu Yu Cheng,
she became your love rival.
That's why you'd pay
attention to her.
Love rival?
I don't even like him.
Are you sure about that?
Well, we've never seen you
stare at
another girl's photos
for such a long time.
That's weird.
I counted 100 last week.
How did it
become 96 pieces today?
Several matching spoons
went missing too.
Would people steal
something like that?
Don't they have
something better to do?
Were our goods stolen?
That's possible.
You asked your friend
to purchase
those utensils all the way from Japan.
They can't be found at usual places.
By the way,
I read this post on Weibo.
After eating,
many customers would
pack away the plates, glasses
and utensils home with them.
Would that
occur at our cafe as well?
What do we do?
I got it.
Let's watch the surveillance.
Let's investigate.
Oh my god.
Is this really Sister Zeng Li?
That's juicy!
Fast forward.
Play it again.
Hurry up.
They kissed.
[This can't be real.]
There's another angle.
This is the one.
This is it.
[Goodness gracious.]
This angle. This one.
Which one looks better?
Enlarge the footage.
They kissed!
I lost my first kiss
just like that.
You probably stole
his first kiss too.
Who's cursing me?
Zeng Li.
I've known you for a long time.
I didn't know you
were such an expert.
Mr. Ai, that poor thing.
Not bad at all.
Do avoid spicy and
pungent food.
Okay.
Xiao Fan.
Have you prepared
the ultrasonic cleaner?
I forgot to.
I'll head to storage
and move the antique over.
Okay.
However, Mr. Ai,
if the braces are stained,
effervescent tablets would
do the trick, right?
They could be obtained
at regular pharmacies.
Why would the
patient come all the way here?
Just go if you're asked to.
Stop blabbering on.
I'll go.
The machine is pretty heavy.
What's going on?
The patient who's coming by
the clinic intentionally is Zeng Li.
In order to meet each other,
they are going through a huge hassle.
[Mr. Ai.]
[I've some matters to attend to.]
[I can't drop by to clean my braces.]
What does that even mean?
It clearly shows
how guilty I am.
I dare not meet him.
Forget it.
He probably mentioned
cleaning my braces
casually.
Perhaps, he forgot all about it.
If I do not show up
when I promised to,
he'd find me irresponsible.
He'd think I'm avoiding him.
What do I do?
She went crazy
for an hour.
Go and talk to her.
What should I say to her?
Should I tell her,
Zeng Li, you're great.
That was a sexy kiss, heroine.
Should I say that?
I'm not going to.
Talk to her yourself.
What do I do?
How am I going to face Mr. Ai?
Hello.
[Hello, Zeng Li.]
Why didn't you
reply my text?
Hurry up and take a look.
I didn't read your text.
I'll take a look.
[Okay.]
[Editor in charge: These are samples
of the cover designs. Pick one.]
[You didn't reply me.]
[I'm submitting this
to the editor first.]
It's up to her
to pick the illustration.
Okay.
The book is publishing soon.
We're planning
a few book signing events for you.
The first stop would be at Yancheng.
[Are you okay with that?]
Hold up.
Wait.
I've a problem.
[What is it?
No.
I did not agree to go on public.
I can't do that.
I get nervous easily.
I can't handle major events.
There's a first in everything.
[Isn't that so?]
[If you'd like to sell your book,]
[book signings are a must.]
[Besides, you're an author now.]
[This is a]
[great opportunity to promote yourself.]
At this moment,
Hurry up and cultivate a readership.
The sales of your next book
would be guaranteed.
I haven't thought
that far ahead.
Besides, I wrote the book for fun.
I've never thought of
publishing the book.
If you're reluctant to,
we might have to reduce the
printing of the first book.
[How about this?]
[Reconsider my offer.]
[I'm going to]
[speak to the editor-in-chief.]
[Okay?]
Okay.
[Well, bye.]
It's almost 5pm.
Would Mr. Ai
be waiting for me?
Zeng Li.
Yesterday, you said
you need to head to
the library at 5pm
because a donor came to deliver books.
Mr. Li wants all of you
to help out.
You're right.
How could I forget that?
Mr. Ai, my absence isn't intentional.
My superior had orders.
I'm not going to get my
braces cleaned.
I'm not avoiding you.
Dr. Ai.
Are there any more patients?
There's one more.
The madam who came
for a complete denture
the last time.
She made an appointment at 6pm.
You will have to work overtime.
Okay.
Are you waiting for Zeng Li?
No.
She sent me a text just now.
She had some urgent
matters to attend to
at the library.
She won't be coming to
get her braces cleaned.
That schoolmate of yours
donated a huge number of books.
What was her name again?
Li Qian.
It sounds familiar.
Thank you for donating
the books to us.
You're the reason why.
After we graduated,
the library was recruiting graduates.
My mom insisted me to
take the examination.
Apparently,
it's relatively stable and easy.
I refused to.
I forced myself into the
field of banking.
Over the years,
I never had a break.
Look at you now.
Every day, you could
spend your time with
a bunch of elderly.
Take life easy as you
wait for retirement.
I'm pretty happy
about the decision I made then.
Congratulations.
If I remember correctly,
you're half a year older than I am.
Yes, I think so.
Here's an advise.
You're stepping into 27.
You spend all your
time in the library.
There are no career ladders to climb
nor many men to choose.
You should hurry up and
settle down with whomever.
Honestly, it's really difficult
to juggle both a relationship
and a career.
You should at least
focus on one of those.
In my opinion,
I think life now is pretty great.
It's simple.
I'm just being nice.
My apologies.
I'm hosting a wedding
dinner in six months.
I did not invite you either.
You wouldn't want to come all the way
to send me money either.
Besides,
you don't have a boyfriend now,
do you?
You'd be annoyed if you came anyway.
Junior, was this you?
Goodness.
If I did not know you,
I could barely recognise you.
Your cheeks probably
lost like two to three pounds.
I removed my wisdom teeth.
Of course my face would slim down.
It almost sounded like
I'm accused of going under the knife.
Zeng Li.
During university days,
you'd form a clique
with your dorm mates
to gossip about me.
You're still as annoying as ever.
I...
Zeng Li.
Mr. Ai.
It's been a day.
You haven't texted me.
I told you to drop by the hospital.
You didn't show up either.
Zeng Li.
Hurry up and
introduce him to your
old school mate.
This is a doctor at
Donghu University Hospital,
Ai Jing Chu.
Dr. Ai.
Dr. Ai
is Zeng Li's boyfriend.
They are doing very well.
Perhaps,
they'd get married in a flash.
Li Qian.
You should hurry up.
You can't allow
Zeng Li to be ahead of you.
Hello, I'm Ai Jing Chu.
Hello, I'm Li Qian.
Are you really Zeng Li's...
Yes.
We've been
dating for quite some time.
Which department are you at, Dr. Ai?
My friend is a doctor as well.
He has been complaining
how tiring it is.
The pay is minimum too.
Life isn't easy for young doctors.
The dental department. It's alright.
I hardly work overtime.
Dentists are great.
They make a lot of money.
Look at Zeng Li.
Her boyfriend is
good looking and capable.
I'm so jealous.
That's flattering.
However, as a
professional dentist,
I should inform all of you
some general knowledge,
the size of the face is
related to the mandible.
It has nothing to do with teeth.
Even if you remove all of your
teeth,
your face will not reduce in size.
You came, Mr. Ai.
Why didn't you inform me?
You probably heard everything
just now.
I came to return the books.
I overheard when I was at the door,
so I stayed and listened
a little longer.
Did you really come to return books
or came to cause me troubles?
Why would Mr. Ai
do that to you?
He was rescuing the
damsel in distress.
All right?
Are you satisfied with the way
I resolved this problem for you?
Turn off the lights.
Turn on the lights.
[Liu Yu Cheng: Let me show you.
I haven't shaved in days. I feel...]
[Let me show you.]
[I haven't shaved in days.]
[I think I look like a beast.]
[Girls with a fairy tale dream]
[did not meet their princes in the end.]
[They claim that fairy tales are a lie.]
[However, at this moment,
I believe in fairy tales.]
[Even if the man I was waiting for]
[did not come in a white horse,]
[but when I'm feeling helpless,]
[he's put on the armour silently]
[and fight for me.]