[Episode 8]
How much farther must we go?
I heard it's not far from here.
How are you not tired though?
I climb up a hill every day, remember?
Right, a hill.
I'll take that.
But, but...
Can't you see I need a break?
Who knew that dating could be this hard?
It's blinding.
This is nice.
I can see a lot of stars today.
It was just as starry that night too.
It's the view I see
walking home every night,
but it seems different today.
Because of my company.
I guess.
Okay. Jackpot.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Why must this be my life?
-Are you good?
-Of course. Nothing happened.
Darn you and that smirk.
-Let's go.
-Sure. Hand me the key though.
Ryoc, the key. Hand it over.
This is nice.
I was able to track Kwon Ryoc down,
but who is he with?
I don't recognize her.
Maybe I should stir the pot a little.
Wait. I thought you went home.
[Nam Joo-tae]
Not yet.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
-What?
-Like you caught a big break.
Between Kim Ji-min and Kwon Ryoc,
who's the better story?
The answer's obvious.
[Nam Joo-tae]
Right?
[KBC]
I need to watch the music show.
And I the TV series.
I can't miss this episode.
You're too young
to be watching drama series.
Go to bed instead.
That's how you grow taller.
-I'm already taller than you.
-What?
Even if it's by two minutes,
I'm still older than you.
You only play the age card
when it suits you.
You just woke up an angry lion.
No, that's what you did.
I won't get pushed around.
You... Get over here.
Give me that. Give me!
-No way.
-Why are you so darn strong?
Cut! Okay.
-Good job.
-Nice work.
Good job, everyone.
Guys, that seemed realistic.
I mean...
It looked like a fencing match.
My head's still spinning.
Good job, Ma-ha. Are you good?
Yes, I'm good.
It actually drove the sleep away.
So you're sleepy?
-As if she had time to sleep.
-Right, I get it.
Here. Take your scripts
for the next episodes!
Got it!
I'm too tired to dance.
Can we take a break?
The salad we're forced to live on
doesn't provide enough energy.
I still can picture
the fried chicken from that day.
Cut the nonsense
and fill your stomach with water.
[You just woke up an angry lion.]
Oh. I see you're watching "Love Virus".
Ma-ha now knows
how to look good on camera.
The show gets good ratings too.
She'll soon be a household name.
Are you two still in touch?
It seems like she's super busy.
Of course we're in touch.
What if she cuts you from her life?
There's no need to glare.
I was only kidding.
Come on. Let's take a shower.
A radio show came in for us.
Right. Do a good job then.
We'll get going.
I thought I had moved on
after getting my say.
Just how pathetic am I?
-He's not going to like this.
-I know, right?
-Did you have to work all night again?
-Get some rest then.
-You must be tired.
-Right.
What's that?
Well, Ryoc's a true actor, so...
-He's a pro.
-Want me to run lines with you?
No, that's not it. Well, you see,
-it's just that--
-Yes, I'm tired, but...
What?
Since it's for my beloved teammates...
[Amusement Park, Flashback, Daytime]
Nothing's out of the ordinary.
[Ambush with a kiss on the cheek...]
[Kiss, Kiss, Kiss, Kiss]
-Guys.
-Huh?
Is this why you hid the script from me?
I knew he'd be cool about it.
Spoken like a true actor.
-I got scared for no reason.
-Acting is just acting.
And it's not like they're deep kisses.
Just focus on
the character you're playing.
-It's not my character.
-It isn't mine either.
So when will this scene be filmed?
[Do-jin, Hyuk, no more bloopers.
Kwon Ryoc sends his support!]
Thank you for the coffee.
[Kwon Ryoc will buy you coffee.]
-Please enjoy.
-You're so handsome.
You're so cool.
I should've figured it out
when you said you wanted to see Hyuk.
That's one of the reasons.
You keep getting better
at this dating thing.
Mr. Kwon.
[Do-jin, Hyuk, no more bloopers.
Kwon Ryoc sends his support!]
Thank you for coming here
to show your support.
Please don't mention it.
I just hope you'll look out for my boys.
I doubt they'll need my help.
Can I get you a beverage?
Thank you for this.
I'll catch you later then.
See you later.
Lucky Ma-ha.
Exactly.
It's a good opportunity
to learn from a seasoned actor.
-A good opportunity?
-Why?
I can tell you're lying.
-What do you mean?
-I know you.
I bet you're seething.
Your blood must be boiling.
[Please look out for Do-jin and Hyuk.]
-It's why you've never had a girlfriend.
-What? Why you--
Encouragement and support.
Petty jealousy by me, Kwon Ryoc?
Dae-gwon, love isn't
as simple as that, you know.
Love is...
Just forget about it.
Why would I bother telling you?
Stand properly for the director.
I didn't expect to see you in person.
You're a loyal teammate.
Since you're here,
please stay and watch the scenes.
I'm afraid we have to get going.
Maybe I should.
Really? Come this way then, please.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Right.
[Please look out for Do-jin and Hyuk.]
You've got to be kidding me.
-Hey, Hyuk!
-What?
Don't tell me you're playing hooky again.
-I'm not.
-Of course you are.
I won't snitch on you to Mom,
so give up your allowance.
Seriously? Hand it over.
Ma-ha, is that you?
It really is you.
-Bin, is that you?
-Cut!
Nice job.
You two actually look good together.
So what's the next scene?
He sure is good-looking.
You. I mean, you're good-looking.
Good job.
-Actually, it was all Ma-ha.
-You were both great.
We have one more scene left.
-He's really good-looking.
-Seriously?
-We'll quickly wrap it up.
-Sure.
Bin, is this our first date?
-"Bin"?
-Address me as your tutor.
No way. I'm going to keep
calling you by name.
She should call me that affectionately.
-Stop it.
-I'll someday be your girlfriend.
Why is she making moves
when he's clearly not interested?
So don't you get yourself a girlfriend.
-A girlfriend?
-Okay?
We'll date once I take my CSAT,
so wait for me until then.
You'll date him?
-Focus on your studies for now.
-Unbelievable.
-Promise me.
-What? A promise?
Come on. Promise me.
All right. Will you study hard if I do?
Look at their pinkies.
I bet he's a player.
There.
Anyway, Ma-ha--
My goodness.
A second shot.
Right, a second shot is needed.
-Keep it down.
-Waist shot.
Bust shot.
Stay still, will you?
-Ryoc, don't look.
-Move!
A tight bust shot.
How many times is this already?
Keep it down.
Seriously?
-Cut. Okay!
-Master Silly, you!
It's tough playing the messenger,
isn't it?
This is killing me.
You know how he is when he's obsessed.
I have him in my purview,
so don't worry too much.
Are you kidding me?
Is that the best you could do?
Your expressions.
Here.
The girl you like is with another man
doing... doing that!
How would you feel? Devastated, right?
Show that devastation in your eyes.
Right, in my eyes.
More. More!
Darn, it's hot out here.
Encouragement and support?
Why not stay and keep at it?
Stay out of it, relationship virgin.
Crazy idiot.
Running around like that
is why you're hot.
Darn it.
[Closed]
[Take a right from the set]
[Star Is Born]
[and a left at the equipment truck.]
[Head through the steel door.]
[Take the stairs down.]
[And then make a left.]
[Head through the steel door
and keep walking.]
Ryoc?
You ignored me on set today.
I had no other choice.
That was a deep kiss.
Actually, it was more like a peck.
Bin, I'm going to be your girlfriend.
Seriously?
Are you jealous of him?
No. As if.
Can you get a desk and two boxes?
-Ryoc, I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
You were fine kissing him on set,
but now you treat me like some bug.
Hold on.
You were fine being
in close proximity with him,
so why are you acting
like I'm some pervert?
-Ryoc--
-Forget it. I'm leaving.
I'll get going then.
If you were going to kiss me,
why not do so on the lips?
[Closed]
Where did he go?
[Kwon Ryoc will buy you coffee.]
Let's go, Mr. Kwon.
You have more work to do.
Can you give me 10 minutes?
10 minutes, my foot. Come on.
-Please!
-People are watching! Hurry!
[Kwon Ryoc will buy you coffee.]
-Hang on.
-Be quiet.
Ryoc looks good in there, doesn't he?
-I'm back.
-Welcome.
-One vanilla latte, please.
-Sure.
How did your shoot go?
Yoon Bin's really good-looking, right?
He had a bit of an aura.
No way. I'm so jealous of you.
Good looks are good for nothing.
They're all the same.
Ma-ha had a shoot with Yoon Bin today.
I see.
-Don't you know him? He's an actor.
-I don't have a TV at home.
He's in movies too.
I have no time to waste
before I get a job.
Then do you know who Kwon Ryoc is?
Then do you know who Noh Yang-jin is?
He's a famous lecturer on YouTube.
Our interests aren't the same,
so I don't know who those actors are.
But Kwon Ryoc of SHAX is a top star.
Noh Yang-jin is also a top star
among students
preparing to become a public official.
He can't be compared to Ryoc.
Kwon Ryoc is a famous star
who has a fan club.
Noh Yang-jin also has a lot of fans.
Kwon Ryoc...
To the students who have been preparing
for the exam for years,
Noh Yang-jin is like an idol.
Idol singers don't last for that long.
His fans will eventually
fall for other stars.
His popularity is only temporary.
It's different with Kwon Ryoc.
Those students
spend years on their studies
to achieve their dreams.
Their dreams are more realistic.
After all, aren't we all doing this
to make a living?
But that's...
That's enough.
Ma-ha, why are you so worked up?
No, she's not.
What's with you two?
Hyun-ji.
Actually,
I was at the hospital on that day
to meet Ryoc.
What?
I met him a couple of times more
after that.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
Did you know about this, Ri-a?
What?
Am I the only one who just found out?
Hyun-ji, it's not what you think.
Hyun-ji, we have to...
It's nice to be working
with you alone today.
Right.
Are you upset
that I couldn't get you more work?
-No, that's not it.
-I'm sorry.
I'm not competent enough to be your boss.
That's not what this is about.
Don't beat yourself up.
Then will you smile?
You'll get wrinkles on your pretty face.
Don't think that you were shunned.
[Hyun-ji, I'm sorry.]
[Ma-ha]
She's not answering my calls nor texts.
[Good luck with your work.]
Hyun-ji must be really upset.
She's not answering my calls either.
[Hyun-ji, Mr. Ji]
[Producer Ha-seok]
We've been too careless.
She must've been disappointed.
[Ma-ha]
There.
Does it not look good on me?
It looks too big on you.
Sorry?
Hyun-ji.
-Are you on a diet?
-No.
Or are you stressed?
He must make you work around the clock.
Eun-jin, that's not the case.
You should take care of your health.
You can't do anything
if your health is ruined.
Got it.
[Wishing a big success on "The Killer"]
Unbelievable. Kim Ji-min is on top
of the most searched word list.
-What?
-They're all dating someone.
-Let me see.
It's dark, but it's obviously Kim Ji-min.
Why would she date Lee Sang-woo?
She's too good for him.
But why would her name trend? What a fuss.
People are so interested in stars dating.
Aren't they at the age
to date people around?
Isn't it natural for people to date?
-But what if it was Ryoc?
-Hey.
Why would you mention him now?
I mean, he's at the age
to date people too.
Still, no one can date him.
Ki-hyun.
Kwon Ryoc of SHAX is an exception.
He's not just anyone.
He's a national treasure.
He's someone whom we should
protect and watch.
It's Ryoc!
[Wishing a big success on "The Killer"]
[All right.]
Hyun-ji went home straight after work.
Should we go see her at her place?
Let's give her some time.
-What is it?
-You should be careful
of a romance rumor.
["Are Kim Ji-min
and Lee Sang-woo Dating?"]
Kim Ji-min?
That's Kim Ji-min.
Did you just get home?
Yes. Why are you still up?
I didn't have a shoot today, so...
It hasn't been long
since you got discharged,
so don't work too hard.
Don't overwork yourself.
Okay.
Go and get some rest.
Jae-u.
We've kept SHAX going for six years.
I want to keep this group going
to the end.
You get what I mean, right?
[Star Is Born]
Hello? Ryoc?
Why do you sound so down?
You were full of energy earlier.
I had a lot to take care of today,
so I'm tired.
Is it about me?
No, Yoon Bin.
Ma-ha, you...
-What's wrong?
[-Just a small conflict with my member.]
I should've told Hyun-ji about us.
I can't help but be careful around her.
You must be upset
since she's your team member.
It's only natural since you're a team.
You must be worried
that you might cause a dispute
because I feel the same way.
-You feel that way too?
-But I trust my team.
We've stayed as a team
for six years for a reason.
You should trust the time
you spent with them.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Did you
-read the news?
-Which one?
It's nothing.
What's your schedule for this week?
It's packed with shoots.
Oh, I have some free time
Friday afternoon.
-I'm off on Friday too.
[-Really?]
We can see each other then.
Okay.
Okay, see you.
[We've kept SHAX going for six years.]
Who is he to give advice to me?
We're here, sir.
Oh, gosh.
My, it's been so long, Mr. Kim.
My gosh, Mr. Park. Thank you for seeing me
when you must be really busy.
I'm so overwhelmed.
You must be working hard day and night.
The least I can do
is to treat you to a meal.
Take a seat.
I hear you're busy training trot singers
these days.
Well...
I'm not exactly training them.
You have a nose for success.
-They are getting good responses too.
-Sorry?
You know, those girls you used to train.
Were they called OMEGA-3?
Oh, them?
You put so much effort into them,
but it's not right for them
to work with someone else.
It all turned out this way
because of that incident.
That was in the past.
I think we need to teach him
the business ethics of this field.
But that won't do me any good.
[Seoul Central District Court]
[To Lee Ma-ha]
[A claim for damages]
Ri-a!
-Yes, Ma-ha.
[-Mr. Ji.]
I got a mail.
[Mr. Ji.]
It says we're being sued
for violating our exclusive contract.
Yes, I got the certified mail too.
What should we do about it?
Do you still have
the contract for OMEGA-3?
We threw it away long before.
When the manager ditched Ma-ha,
we tore it apart.
We must have it somewhere.
-Look for the contract first.
-Okay.
[One more thing.]
Is there anyone who can prove
that your previous agency
unilaterally breached the contract?
-Anyone who can prove it?
-Yes.
Who could prove it for us?
Take your time to think of one.
And don't worry much.
Let's solve this one by one.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Girls.
-Hyun-ji.
-What are we going to do?
It's okay. It's going to be okay.
The contract... The contract...
The contract...
[OMEGA Entertainment]
I found it.
Who could prove it for us?
Our manager.
Which one? You mean Go Ba-wi?
The one who ditched you and ran?
He's the only one who can testify for us.
As if.
We don't even know where he is.
No, I'm sure he'll testify for us.
-You didn't throw that away?
-No.
Because it's the number my dad used.
[Manager Go Ba-wi]
[Lee Ma-ha]
Why are you calling me?
Hang up, hang up!
Okay, she stopped.
[Nchicks Chicken]
-Hello?
[-What's taking you so long?]
[We ordered it ages ago!]
I'm so sorry. I'm on my way.
Yes, I'll be there in no time.
I'm so sorry.
[Nchicks Chicken]
Gosh.
[Manager Go Ba-wi]
-Yes, I'm almost there.
-Hello?
This is Lee Ma-ha.
Hello?
Why can't I hear anything?
Hello? Who's calling? Speak up.
-I can't hear you.
[-Mr. Go.]
Wow, I can finally hear you.
Long time no talk, Ma-ha.
Mr. Go.
We need your help.
[CEO Kim Jeong-seok]
[Cliff Edge Entertainment]
Look who's here.
You have nothing
to sponge off of the girls.
Why did you have to sue them?
You know you'll lose the suit.
I know I'm fighting a losing battle.
Yet, you're going to
waste your time and money on it?
That's not my concern.
That means
you have nothing to lose, Mr. Kim.
What else could I have done?
If I want to ride on his coattails,
then I'll have to sacrifice
anyone I can find.
Please leave now. I'll see you in court.
[Cliff Edge Entertainment]
They worked really hard
to make a comeback.
If you're in the business again,
don't play dirty.
[Cliff Edge Entertainment]
["Tea Party's Double Contract,
A Court Case Expected"]
What's that?
What?
["Tea Party's Double Contract,
A Court Case Expected"]
What? A double contract?
That's not even big news.
Why are they mentioning it the whole day?
["Tea Party Struggles
with the Double Contract Issue"]
What do we do? What are we supposed to do?
Let's get going. Mr. Ji can't make it.
We might be late for all of our work.
Gosh, this is giving me a headache.
Let's go. I need to go to the studio too.
I'll get going.
We should get going too.
The shoot will be delayed.
What a nuisance.
What are you reading?
-The news about Tea Party.
-I see.
Those ragpickers want to leech off them
now that their names are known.
It happens all the time.
But they're not big enough
to be on the news.
That's what I'm saying.
It's not even a big deal.
Are they out of news items?
They must be in someone's bad books.
They'll be destroyed.
I knew this would happen
the moment Ma-ha
was sold to another agency.
And it was OMEGA Entertainment
of all places.
She got off on the wrong foot.
Ma-ha was the most diligent trainee
among us.
I also worked as hard as she did.
Of course, Hyeon-o.
You did work really hard.
You worked hard to hit on girls.
[You should get your head straight.]
[Don't be blinded
by the money they offer.]
[You're not big enough
to be traded though.]
[Don't stick your nose
into other agencies.]
[You'll only end up
saddled with massive debt.]
Work hard
when the agency is investing in you.
Don't try to get smart with us, got it?
-Yes.
It'll work out fine.
[Tea Party]
[Yu-jin]
Hey, Yu-jin.
You must've had a long day.
Right. It was total chaos.
But we found our old manager's number.
So Mr. Ji will--
-How is Ma-ha doing?
-What?
She just began to shoot the sitcom,
so I'm a little worried.
Hello?
Are you only worried about her?
-What?
[-I was in OMEGA too.]
I received that certified mail too.
I may not have been as busy as Ma-ha,
but I was busy enough.
Then my pictorial got canceled,
so I'm here trying to pass time alone.
I'm sorry, Hyun-ji.
If you're that worried about her,
you can ask her yourself from now on.
[Hyun-ji.]
[Yu-jin]
I also wanted to be comforted
on a day like this.
[Tea Party]
Hello.
-I'm here.
-You're here.
-Are you all right?
-What do you mean?
I saw the news.
What's not to be okay?
It's not like I did anything wrong.
I knew you'd be tough.
Our CEO will take care of everything.
Ji-hak would do that.
-Is SHAX ever busy?
-What?
You always seem to be here.
Well, a musician should be at a studio.
You're here.
-Does he own a share of this studio?
-What?
He's always here.
I do. I do own a share.
Hey, Fake.
We meet at the TV station pretty often.
Hello.
Sit.
I saw the news.
Fake.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Don't get scared.
I don't get scared
over everything people out there say.
Even if it takes time,
the truth will come out.
And I believe sincerity goes a long way.
What a surprise.
I'm glad you seem to be energetic. Bye.
Ri-ma.
It's rather cold these days.
Please dress warmly.
This is my armor.
I'm always ready to fight.
That's La Ri-ma.
Okay?
See you.
["Tea Party's Breach of Contract"]
[Contacts]
[Crow-tit]
I knew it.
If you don't stay focused,
you'll get hurt again like last time.
Will it be all right?
What's all right?
They're all waiting for you to come.
Come on out.
Get off now.
-Hello.
Great work in this cold weather.
Well, it's always like this
to shoot outside at this time of the year.
Anyway, is that girl, Ma-ha, doing okay?
Why do you ask him?
I mean, they were on set together and all.
I thought they were close friends.
No, they aren't close.
It's not a big deal.
Right, she came to see you
on the day of the accident.
Yes, she came for a morale boost
to root for me on my first day.
She seemed friendly and talented,
so I wanted to tell other directors.
Everything will be resolved soon.
Thank you for your concern.
It's getting cold.
Let's begin before the sun sets.
-Let's do that.
-Let's go, Ryoc.
[NOG Entertainment]
[-Move aside.
-Hey, Ji-hak.]
Move!
[NOG]
[CEO Park Jin-man]
Jin-man. You were behind
all the articles and lawsuits.
It's your plan, isn't it?
Mr. Kim is trying to get his kids back.
Why would it be my plan?
Because Tea Party wasn't the target.
It's me.
That's why this isn't on Mr. Kim,
but you, Jin-man.
Who do you think you are?
Those eyes.
Those are the same eyes
as you looked down on me three years ago
as if you want to beat me.
A kid who used to tag along
like a little brother
betrayed me,
humiliated me, then left.
When you crawled back into this industry,
you never apologized for your behavior.
Try screaming at me again
as you did back then.
Bad news.
The great CEO of NOG is
playing such a petty game,
so I can't seem to get mad.
This is a warning.
Do not mess with my girls.
I'm sorry.
I really don't want to,
but there's another landmine
that hasn't been set off.
What the heck are you doing?
Be consistent with your language.
Don't mess with them!
That's you giving an order.
Please don't hurt them.
And that's you asking for a favor.
Choose wisely.
Should I see you out?
-Are you okay?
[-Yes.]
I think it'll be resolved well.
I'm glad.
If you three are fine, that's good enough.
You must've been worried about me.
Not really.
I'm just checking in
as a senior, you know.
Don't worry about me.
See you on that day.
Okay.
Gosh, what a relief.
All we spent on them was
the key money for their dorm,
rent, food, and gas.
That's about it.
They also made use of old outfits
that other girls used.
We spent the least we could
on maintenance.
They're the ones who suffered.
Their electricity and water were
often cut off
in their dorm,
but the company never made a loss.
It's just that they never got paid.
I never got paid a penny either.
The one who breached the contract
was that jerk...
I mean, Mr. Kim.
I'll tell you everything
for these poor girls.
How could such a soft-hearted guy like you
leave Ma-ha alone in that mountain
and run away all by yourself?
Hey.
I'm sorry, Ma-ha.
Could I trust
that your apology is sincere?
Do you have any evidence to prove this?
I picked up everything from that office
that I can cash out when we moved out,
including the laptop, the tablet,
and the desktop computer.
I have everything with me.
Could you testify
what you just said in court as well?
Of course, I'll bring everything.
This is enough evidence
to wrap up the incident.
It must've been tough, girls.
I cleared out your schedule,
so go get some rest.
Ma-ha, I need a word with you.
Now that we're here,
let's forget the past
and make a fresh start.
-The past? Forget everything?
-Ouch! Hey!
-Give me my money, you jerk!
-Hey! Ouch!
A girl group member is beating me up!
Photos?
You and Kwon Ryoc
were caught.
I could take care of this lawsuit,
but this is out of my hands.
I'm sorry, sir.
All of your decisions
come with a responsibility.
I've shown respect to your opinions,
and I'll continue to do so.
But Ma-ha,
I can't just throw you out there
and let you take the responsibility alone.
["The Killer"]
[Crow-tit]
[The person you have reached
is not available. Please...]
He must be busy.
["The Killer"]
[You have a missed call from Crow-tit.]
[-Ryoc.]
-What is it at this hour?
There's a problem.
Our photos were taken.
Hello? Are you there?
[H Cafe]
Yes.
It's not a big deal.
Lots of photos like those get around.
-Really?
-Yes.
You don't have to worry.
[Bye.]
Hey, over here.
Hey, what's the occasion?
I can't believe you called me first.
-I need to ask you for a favor.
-A favor?
I need you to release an article.
On what?
A follow-up article on the lawsuit
between OMEGA Entertainment and Tea Party.
Oh, that case.
I brought...
[JH Entertainment]
all the materials you'll need,
so you can be the judge.
-Are you asking for a special favor?
-No.
This is the truth.
Most are interested in the problem,
but not many
bother to find out how it ends.
Well, I guess it's not worth
any money or attention.
But I thought
you would do it.
-I'll have a read.
-Thank you.
You know what?
If I do this for you,
it means you owe me one.
Hey, Ryoc. Why did you come here?
[It's the photo of that night
when we ran into Kim Ji-min,]
[so I was concerned.]
What are you two doing?
Mr. Park, you haven't gone home yet.
You two must be having lots of fun.
Hey.
I told you to keep him under control.
He doesn't know anything.
He doesn't?
-You don't know?
-I'm sorry, Mr. Park.
Please wait outside.
She's trying to get her break
by lurking around you.
What good is a petty girl like her to you?
Ryoc.
[Closed]
You should date girls in your league.
Think about it.
Who do you think this story will destroy?
You or her?
You should've known who has more to lose.
Have you gone blind
just because everyone here and there
wants to work with you?
Do you think you got here
because you're that good?
And SHAX?
I can always start over.
I have nothing to lose. Why?
I've made enough money.
Do your members know
that you've been dating a girl?
Do they know?
[Who do you think this story will destroy?
You or her?]
[You should've known
who has more to lose.]
[What a relief.]
[I feel much better
now that you say that.]
[Do your members know]
[that you've been dating a girl?]
[We've kept SHAX going for six years.]
[I want to keep this group going
to the end. You get what I mean, right?]
[Mr. Ji.]
If you were still with SHAX,
what would you have done?
What would you have done, Mr. Ji?
If I was the old Ji-hak
who was a manager for SHAX,
I would've stopped you.
But not anymore.
What's important is your choice.
I would leave it up to you.
Thank you for your advice.
[And I'm sorry for contacting you
over something like this.]
I must've kept you waiting.
No.
How long has it been since we last met?
Has it been a week?
Yes, something like that.
I knew it. I missed you so much.
It looks like something is going on.
Ma-ha.
What is it?
Why can't you just say it?
I can't bring myself
to say it to your face.
Let's
break up.
You probably didn't have to see that.
[Epilogue]
I'm sorry.
Don't say that, Jin-man.
[12 years ago]
I can't believe how cheap they are.
Grab a drink and vent it out.
We'll see a better day soon.
Ji-hak.
I can't live as the powerless anymore.
I'm done living that life.