[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 5]
Brother, Sister-in-law!
It's late. What are you doing here?
I heard sister-in-law is back.
Sister-in-law, this is the fish maw soup I made.
You used to love it.
I really miss it.
Thank you, Fei.
Sister-in-law,
how were your seven years abroad?
Was it hard?
Yes.
But I'm back now.
And your brother is so good to me,
so it was worth it.
Honey,
help me with the soup.
I'll get a bowl.
You sprained your ankle, not broke your arm.
You're trying to give me a hard time, aren't you?
No way.
Sister-in-law, have some soup.
It's so good.
Honey,
try it.
I...
Does it taste good, honey?
Yes.
Sister-in-law, what happened to your foot?
It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
You just act tough.
Come on.
I'll give you a massage.
Thank you, honey.
Honey,
it hurts, doesn't it?
No, honey.
Your hands must hurt
from all the massage you did for me.
I'll give you a massage too.
It's okay.
Thank you so much, honey.
Just get some rest.
It's okay, honey.
I manage Eminence Starlight,
but you manage the whole Group.
You work much harder than me.
Let me...
Does it feel good, honey?
Yes!
Brother.
Sister-in-law, now you have the soup.
I'm off.
Fei, stay.
I have so many things to talk to you.
I'll visit another day.
It's too late today.
I won't bother you.
Go away!
I'm telling you.
I only do this
because there is somebody else around.
Don't go too far!
So you were faking it?
But you looked like you were enjoying it
very much.
Childish!
You're childish and jealous!
I'll say it again.
I'm not jealous.
Alright.
Got it.
I'm going to bed.
Please be quiet when you go upstairs.
You...
Unbelievable!
Hello, Manni.
Fei, you finally answer my phone!
I...
I hit Su Bei!
I just returned from my brother's place.
Sist...
She's fine.
But don't ever
do anything so dangerous again.
After all, she's your sister.
I...
What sister?
I don't have a sister like that.
You're just too naive.
Don't be fooled by her.
Fei, I have a text message coming in.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
[Abortion Surgery Report]
You want to take my brother away from your sister?
Good luck with that.
[Nanxi Eminence Group Co., Ltd]
Here she is. Here she is.
Ms. Su. Ms. Su. Ms. Su.
Tell us about it.
Answer our questions.
Tell us about it, Ms. Su.
Ms. Su. Ms. Su. Ms. Su.
Tell us.
Ms. Su. Ms. Su.
Ms. Su, please.
Was it you who signed for the abortion?
Who is the father of the child?
Please tell us about it!
Yeah. Please!
Ms. Su.
Excuse me.
Here.
Why is there still a file
about my hospitalisation?
Wasn't it removed already?
Someone was behind this.
The medical records are genuine,
but the date was changed.
And fetus protection was changed to abortion.
Now the news has gone viral.
Lu Nan...
Get out of here!
Mr. Lu, what's this about?
Are you going to interrogate me?
Aren't you suppose to explain yourself?
No.
Believe it or not,
I didn't.
You didn't sign this?
Or you didn't
get pregnant with a child of another man?
Su Bei,
I thought you approached me with a purpose,
because you were greedy.
But now I see that
you're dirty
from soul to flesh.
You can call me greedy,
but you can't call me dirty,
because you're even dirtier.
I want a divorce.
No problem.
But apologize to me for what you just said.
Su Bei, I'm warning you.
You owe me that!
Alright.
Then I'll deal with it without relenting.
Please do.
Mr. Lu.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Calm down.
My wife is pregnant
with someone else's child,
and my best friend knew about it and didn't tell me.
How can I calm down?
There's something fishy going on here.
I just wanted to confirm it before I told you.
Who gave you the right
to make decision without informing me?
Do you think you're so powerful
that you can decide everything about me?
Lu Nan.
I'll pretend I didn't hear what you just said.
If you still think of me as a friend,
then calm down
and listen to what I have to say.
I'm sorry for keeping you in the dark,
and I understand how you feel right now.
But you mustn't act out of anger.
Anger?
Do you know how much
this will affect Eminence?
Do you know what the consequences could be?
If you had told me earlier,
I could have dealt with it sooner.
But now
it's too late.
Call a press conference immediately.
I'm going to announce the divorce.
Sorry.
I didn't think it through.
As a special assistant, I failed in my job.
But as a friend,
I must tell you that
I've sent someone to Italy
and we'll have the results soon.
Can you wait a little longer?
Just do
as I say.
Eminence is going public soon.
If you're about to get a divorce, then...
Out!
[Urine Test Report]
[Scan Report]
Bei Bei,
Lu Nan has informed the journalists that
he's going to have a press conference.
Then let's sink together.
[Press Conference]
Here they are!
Tell us about it.
Tell us about it!
Is there really an illegitimate child?
[Divorce, abortion, illegitimate child, scandal. What is real?]
Can you tell us what's going on?
Is there really an illegitimate child?
Tell us, Mr. Lu.
Quiet, please.
Take your seats, please.
They'll answer your questions later.
[Divorce, abortion, illegitimate child, scandal. What is real?]
First of all,
thank you for coming.
I have two things to say
about the negative news.
For one thing,
Ms. Su and I
Sir,
get away!
You can't get in!
were married seven years ago
because we loved each other.
Maggie, Maggie!
Let me in!
Yun, you can't go in there.
I...
We trust
and support each other
all the way.
We never betray each other despite the long-distance relationship.
There are no
separation,
divorce,
illegitimate child
or abortion.
For another,
we will take legal action
against those media
and individuals
who maliciously slander
our marriage
and my wife
Su Bei.
Ms. Su.
Ms. Su, please look at me!
Look here, please!
Thanks, Mr. Lu.
Another one.
Another one, please.
This way.
Good!
Thank you!
Closer!
Ms. Su, please look at me!
Why are you still defending her
after all this?
Why?
Mr. Lu!
Can you answer our questions?
Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu!
Don't go!
Answer our questions, please!
Aren't you going to tell everyone
what you've found out?
[Scan Report]
[Diagnosis of a blood clot compressing a nerve and the occurrence of blindness]
You manage to stay calm
in such a terrible situation.
Don't tell me you don't have a backup plan.
Mr. Lu, you're flattering me.
What do I have to find out?
It's just Kong's endorsement contract.
Is there something
that you're afraid I'll find out?
I don't care what kind of tricks you're trying to pull off.
But if it affects Eminence,
I won't let you off the hook.
I won't divorce you
for the sake of Eminence's IPO.
But you must get out of my house right now.
I don't want to see you anymore!
That makes two of us.
Get out!
Our people came back from Italy.
It's true that Su Bei had an abortion.
Are you going to humiliate me
again with this?
The kid is yours.
When Su Bei arrived in Italy,
she suffered from heartbreak
and found out she was pregnant too late.
The baby was nine weeks old,
so it was definitely conceived in China.
I'm enjoying the wine now.
Mr. Lu,
please mind your own business.
Why didn't you tell me
that the kid is mine?
Tell you?
About what?
If I tell you
the kid is yours,
would you believe me?
You were so mean
and talked so harsh to me.
I didn't dare to tell you!
So? You're not mad now
and know you're the father,
so here you are to see me?
Then
are you here to make fun of me
or to pity me?
Drinking is bad for you...
The moment I found out I was pregnant,
I was already a broken person.
Don't you think it's a bit late now
for you to come and see me?
And I
need somebody to drink with me.
If you're not drinking with me, then leave.
Do you know how much it hurts
to have a baby come out of your body?
Do you know how painful it is
to lie in bed
and not be able to move?
No, you don't.
Sorry...
If you don't want to see me anymore,
I'll move out tomorrow.
I promise you'll never see me again.
Lu Nan, I'm innocent.
You're a bastard.
You're a real bastard!
Lu Nan,
I'll tell you a secret.
Actually,
the kid...
Come on, stop drinking.
I know you're upset,
but drinking won't help.
You've made up for it
by helping her
keep the fuss die down.
You did your best.
No.
We still haven't found out who's behind it yet.
Didn't we already know
it's Su Manni who did it?
There's someone else.
She alone couldn't have done this.
You look into this matter
and find out the person.
Well...
I...
I ordered too much take-out,
so if you're hungry,
let's eat together.
I don't think it's a good idea to wear so little in the morning.
What's wrong with this?
Nice.
But it's our last meal together.
Don't worry.
I'll go pack up my stuff later.
That's not what I meant.
What do you mean then?
It's up to you
whether you leave or stay.
What happened last night
was my fault.
I shouldn't have left you alone
with the kid.
It's all past.
Don't worry about it, Mr. Lu.
I'm full now. I'll leave.
You haven't even eaten yet.
I don't want to. You can eat yourself.
The person who exposed the abortion
was Su Manni.
Then what do you expect me to do,
Mr. Lu?
At work,
you're her boss.
And in private,
you're her sister.
So I'll stay out of this.
Do what you want with her.
What's up?
Close the door.
Just say it.
You think I have time to waste with you?
Do you know how much money Eminence will lose
while you waste my precious time here?
If you don't mind
letting everyone know
how you got to be a top model,
then leave the door open even wider
and let's talk.
What do you want?
[Letter of termination]
[Party A: Su Bei]
You're terminating my contract?
Does Mr. Lu know about this?
I'm in charge of Eminence Starlight.
I don't have to inform him about my decision here.
Su Bei, are you out of your mind?
I'm the top model of Eminence.
Do you know what it means
to terminate my contract?
Mr. Lu won't agree.
What I admire most about you
is your arrogance and stupidity.
I can defeat you
effortlessly.
You're abusing your power.
You're taking revenge on me
for telling the press
about your dirty business abroad, aren't you?
Well, you can take it that way.
But
since you've called me your sister
for so many years,
I'll let you sign the letter and leave.
[Letter of termination]
Dream on!
I won't sign it.
You have the same father,
but you way outsmart her.
I'm more like my mother.
The way you said that
looked exactly like Chris.
Are you all right?
Lu Nan
feels guilty about the kid now.
Now that he relents,
I'll take advantage of it.
But I don't want to see you get hurt again.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
Miss Su!
Mr. Lu is working.
You can't disturb him.
Mr. Lu, she...
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, Su Bei pushes me around again.
She wants to terminate my contract
and says you've agreed.
You're not happy with her offer?
You...
Why?
Do I have to explain to you?
I know.
It's Su Bei, isn't it?
She bad-mouthed me, right?
Don't listen to her!
She's trying to make mischief.
She hasn't said anything bad about you.
No way. It's her!
Mr. Lu,
She's pregnant with someone else's child.
I don't want you to suffer.
Shut up!
One more negative thing about her,
I'll kick you out of the fashion industry.
Mr. Lu,
why is this happening all of a sudden?
There are still many loving pictures of us online.
You gave me a car
and took me to shows.
You...
How can you treat me like this
just because of
that little bitch Su Bei?
You think I did it because I liked you?
I did it
to raise your profile
and boost your fame
for the sake of Eminence.
But
since you've worked so hard
for everything with me,
I'll make it look decent by letting you
leave Eminence on your own.
[8th Anniversary]
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
You look even hotter!
Mr. Zhang.
We come straight here.
Will it alarm him?
What if Zhang Yuan informs Lu Nan...
He won't.
You really have faith in him?
Not in him,
but in money.
Mr. Zhang,
here's your wine. Enjoy it.
Uncle.
Su Bei?
I'm so glad you remember me.
What are you doing here?
Don't be nervous, uncle.
I'm here today
for business.
It's a deal that's sure to pay off.
I...
I'm not nervous at all!
Uncle,
what do you think of Lu Nan?
Good, very good.
Uncle,
it's so nice of you.
Lu Nan drove you out of Eminence
like a piece of garbage,
and you still defend him.
As far as I know, you was with Eminence
since its inception.
You worked so hard for the company for so many years.
Who in the company doesn't respect you?
But you end up like this.
This is outrageous.
I've been married to Lu Nan for seven years
and he wants to divorce me without giving away anything.
That's how he treats his wife.
Uncle,
You must have had a hard time
with what happened back then, right?
Just get to the point. What do you want?
Good!
I'll cut the crap then.
I want to get rid of Lu Nan
and take over Eminence.
You were working with Lu Nan for so many years,
so I'm sure you have what I want.
Lu Nan calls me uncle.
When a junior made a mistake,
I had to cover for him as an elder.
Here are some of my assets overseas.
As long as you work with me,
we can negotiate
[Personal deposit Su Bei total RMB 4,500,000]
about your pay.
She's rich!
That's all I have to say.
Uncle,
think about it.
Uncle, what I say is always valid.
Take your time.
By the way,
how is Su Manni doing
since she left?
Lu Nan has taken
a tough line on her.
He already told everyone in the business about it,
and now no one dares to hire her.
Also,
Su Manni has been
pestering Gu Chengze.
But Gu Chengze is too busy dealing with his father
to care about her.
I said that
I would get back everything
she took from me.
Hello?
What's wrong?
Chris is back.
[Nanxi Eminence Group Co., Ltd]
Why isn't she coming?
She's not here. She's not here.
[Misunderstandings cleared up. What a loving couple]
I've finally found Bei Bei and dad.
Dad!
Chris, what are you doing here?
I'm looking fo dad.
You're not talking to your sis?
What sis?
She's a mean old aunt.
Chris, you're petty!
Please call me Mr. Su.
I was so close seeing dad.
Then you stopped me!
Bei Bei!
Come on.
Tell me
how you get back.
Don't be mad at me
if I tell you about it.
I wasn't mad at you
when you went back to China without telling me.
Being mad not only makes you ugly,
it also gives you wrinkles.
He's really something.
He managed to get the teacher
to change the location of the winter camp to Nanxi.
Sorry, Bei Bei.
I just wanted to see dad so much.
I'm not mad.
I'm just worried about you.
You're only six years old.
This is dangerous.
Don't you ever do it again.
Bei Bei, my bad.
I just missed dad so much.
No. It's not your fault.
It's mine.
Did you apologize to auntie?
She was worried about you too.
Auntie, sorry.
And I miss you too.
Fine. Fine.
Apology accepted.
But
you'll be deprived of a week's worth of desserts and snacks
because of this lie.
No!
Tell me
how you found the company.
I saw a picture
of you and dad on the internet.
There was a big sign
behind you and dad.
So I asked my teacher to send me over
to surprise you.
Bei Bei,
when are you going to take me to see dad?
It's my fault
for putting Chris at such a risk.
[Nanxi Eminence Group Co., Ltd]
Come in.
I promised Chris yesterday
that I would spend the day with him.
Call me
if anything happens at the office.
It's time to spend some quality time together.
Chris told me
he didn't want to go back to Italy.
He kept asking me
why he couldn't stay
with mom and dad.
I didn't know how to explain to him.
Chris is a smart boy.
It's not like he doesn't know I'm lying to him.
He just doesn't want to put me in a difficult position.
It's all my fault.
If he doesn't want to leave this time,
find him a school here
and transfer his student file as soon as possible.
Chris will be thrilled
when he knows about it.
[Zhang Yuan: Meet me tonight at 8:00 at the same place]
So money
does work, huh?
I guess I can't stay
with Chris today.
[Zhang Yuan: Meet me tonight at 8:00 at the same place]
Meet me tonight at 8:00 at the same place.
I'll ask his nanny
to stay with him.
Don't worry.
Bei Bei, are you back?
I'm busy with work today
and
may not be able to go back now.
Can you sleep with me tonight?
I'll try to be back early.
Be good.
What are you doing here?
Who are you going to be with tonight?
A friend.
A friend?
You say "be good"
and give kisses to a friend?
Mr. Lu,
are you being jealous?
Jealous?
No way!
In that case,
why don't you let go?
Don't go anywhere tonight.
We need to work.
Sorry, I have an appointment.
Hey, Yunfan.
Go check on Su Bei's schedule tonight.