[English subtitles are available]
Hu Ying.
How dare you!
Hu Ying. You...
There's something on her.
Search her.
No!
Beat her!
Let her go!
Si Yan.
Anyone causing trouble here
will be punished with being flogged 50 times,
and copying the commandments 100 times.
Your Highness,
Si Yan is a...
Shut up!
I believe her.
Si Yan.
Wake up, Si Yan!
What...
What's going on?
What did they do to her...
Wasn't it your order
to punish Si Yan?
It was.
Then why are you asking me?
Are you satisfied now?
I don't want to bother you.
Si Yan,
I have something important to tell you.
Tell her
when she gets well.
From now on,
I don't owe you anything.
You're not a princess anymore.
The world in the game
may be even more dangerous than outside.
Hu Ying.
Hu Ying, go away!
Don't come any closer, Hu Ying.
Go away from me!
Don't come any closer. I'll kill you.
Go away!
I'll take revenge
twice as much.
Let's forget it.
Yes, Prince Bao is on her side now.
You can follow me or not.
I'll take my revenge.
We'll see.
Si Yan.
Where the hell did you go?
Your Highness,
I just went to check
Miss Min's maid Peach's room.
She has the same earrings.
But it was a pair.
But...
But what?
But these earrings
are sold all over East City.
These double-piercing earrings are really nice.
Things from Treasure Pavilion
are quite different.
Your Highness.
Overnight,
all the women in town are wearing the same earrings.
It's hard for us to follow this clue.
I don't think so.
This is not a good move.
It's quite suspicious instead.
How about
we just go in and ask?
Do you know
who owns this shop?
This is the shop of General Min,
the border defender.
Things
are getting complicated.
Have someone keep an eye on this place.
If there's any sign of trouble,
report to me as soon as possible.
Yes, Your Highness.
What a beautiful day!
The unexpected trouble
gave me a moment's rest.
Prince Bao has saved you.
Do you still want to reject him?
I don't want Lan Miao to misunderstand again.
Please kill
my romance storyline with Prince Bao.
Otherwise, I don't know
how to talk to him.
Why did you act tough in front of Prince Yi?
He...
Don't mention him.
It's all right for me to suffer a little.
I just can't bear this grievance.
Prince Yi has found evidence
to prove your innocence.
I have something important to tell you.
Tell her
when she gets well.
If he had evidence, why didn't he show it earlier?
I knew he was messing with me
and making things personal.
My lady,
it's windy this afternoon.
The sun is scorching.
As you stand on the walls of the city,
your skin will inevitably be dusty.
This Inglemirepharm Prunus mume recovery serum
can help clear the skin
and protect you from sunburn.
It's quite nice.
When I was younger,
I used to love riding the horse on the grassland.
I was young
and didn't know how to take care of my skin.
My skin
is not what it used to be.
Your Highness is so gentle and virtuous.
I never thought
you used to ride the horse on the grassland.
There are gains and losses.
Let's not talk about that.
Just keep these on hand for me from now on.
Yes, my lady.
Let's continue.
Here are air cushions and eyeshadows
for today's live commerce.
This makeup could show...
I don't want to remember any of these.
When I go live later,
you can just write the notes on the side.
Otherwise, what do I need you for?
Okay.
Powder puff.
Here you are.
Try this color.
Thank you.
You seem to have changed.
You...
You know the old me?
No.
I mean
your make-up technique,
compared with that at the Flower Feast,
seems to have improved.
Phew!
I thought Glasses had remembered me.
Since I'm in the Makeup Service,
it's hard not to improve.
This is a bit different than usual.
When I return,
I'll reward you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
The makeup has been kept for a few days.
I'm surprised it hasn't spoiled.
How did you do it?
Do you smell a hint of the clove?
Clove?
You made soup with cloves
and mixed it with alcohol.
It neutralizes the alcohol.
It was all thanks to your book.
Don't mention that book.
Look at my leg, it's still bandaged.
You're the one who made it.
What's the book got to do with it?
What's wrong?
I have an idea.
Since you can keep the makeup from spoiling,
why not strike while the iron is hot
and develop a set of pregnancy-safe makeup?
And then we can sell it at Forever Young.
It'll be a big seller.
You always have business savvy.
What are you selling?
It's confidential.
Let's go.
You're in business.
I can provide the capital.
The envoy has arrived.
Si Yan,
let me do it.
You can leave it here.
I'd hate to bother you.
Let me do the sweeping.
Add some strength.
Here, Si Yan, have some tea.
Good girl.
It's been so hot lately.
My face is always oily.
My makeup is smudged.
I've heard that this UNIFON purifying clay musk
is useful for deep cleansing and long-lasting oil control.
Here, put some on my face.
Okay.
It's so early in the morning.
I thought the lady of the house had arrived.
Turned out it was just a lowly maid.
What right do you have to give orders?
Even if you don't care that
the Second Lady's makeup
allowed her to make a splash,
Prince Yi did say that
if we provoke her again,
we'll all be dragged out of the house.
She's just a lowlife
using her master's powerful connections.
You...
Mind your words.
What's the point of falling in love?
I guess this is the best task for me.
It's hot and the birds are noisy.
Brother Yi, you're still in the mood
to practice calligraphy.
What are you doing?
I've caught two auspicious spiders
and brought one to you.
I heard giving an auspicious spider to your loved one on Chinese Valentine's day
will lead to a happy marriage.
If Min Rui gets the spider from you,
she'll be delighted.
You're so childish.
I don't need it.
Do you not need it or
you just don't want to give it to Rui?
Girls are timid.
I'm afraid
it might scare Miss Min.
Won't the girl you are giving it to
be scared?
She...
She may not be scared.
You should be more concerned about yourself.
There are so many people involved in your affairs.
Giving a spider
may not be enough.
Well...
I'll go and catch a cuter auspicious spider
so as not to scare anyone.
Wang,
tell me.
If I hurt someone unintentionally,
what should I do?
You are so wise, brave,
and intelligent.
How could you do anything wrong?
You are right in everything you do.
Forget it.
Let's put it another way.
If
I have misunderstood someone unintentionally,
how should I make amends?
For me,
it depends on what kind of person they are.
How so?
If they are Bun or Bean,
who are my brothers,
then I'll just apologize to them.
But
for the one I love,
I will adapt to her taste,
and buy what she likes
to please her in every way.
I see.
Today's poems are all with "Yan" in them.
Let me try.
The willow sleeps three times a day.
The peach and plum are competing for beauty.
Brother Bao is right.
It's hot today.
Birds are noisy.
It's not a good day for practicing calligraphy.
I'll go for a walk.
The peach and plum are competing for beauty.
I was right.
So His Highness
is still thinking of that crazy girl.
Your Highness,
the First Lady asks you to go to the back garden.
I've asked the royal doctor.
He said
coming out for fresh air
will help your body recover faster.
But I still delayed in accompanying His Majesty
to meet with the envoy.
Fortunately, the Second Lady took the trouble to
help me.
She accompanied the King up to the city tower.
Otherwise,
it would have been a breach of etiquette.
Are you
the maid who helped the Second Lady with her makeup?
You did a good job.
Come to think of it,
it's been twenty years
since the Second Lady came to the Mansion.
No one has ever said
she looks like me.
It's that maid called Si Yan
who came up with the idea.
My maid has nothing to do with it.
Mother.
You came.
Brother Yi.
I've been sick.
I forgot to ask you.
You've been here for a while, haven't you?
You haven't been out of the Mansion yet.
Alright.
Let Qi Yi
take you out for a walk.
Brother Yi is busy with business.
I wonder
if it'll be too much trouble.
In a few days, we'll be celebrating Valentine's day.
Could I invite you
to enjoy the lanterns with me?
Thank you, Brother Yi.
Oiran competes for beauty.
That's a nice font.
Arrange the flowers later
and tie them around the side.
Keep your clothes tidy.
We'll have an important guest later.
My lord!
You're early.
The girls aren't awake yet.
They are awake.
Girls,
come receiving guests.
Come receiving guests.
My lord,
what's your preference?
I'll get the girls ready.
I want them
to cry.
I see.
Customers are so strange these days.
Exactly.
How can they all be unqualified?
My lord,
are you satisfied?
These are all the girls in your Cloud Brothel?
Yes.
You're still not satisfied?
None of them are to my liking.
We have two more girls.
But as luck would have it,
we have an important guest
who has made an appointment.
Can't you do me a favor?
Let me meet the girls.
I can only tell you
where they are.
Whether you can meet them or not
depends on your luck.
Hu Ying,
you came first in the last monthly exam.
The matrons think very highly of you.
Tell us more.
What are the questions
in this monthly exam?
Even if I get along well with the matrons,
they couldn't have told me this.
This is cheating.
You...
Don't get any bad ideas.
Show your strength.
I hope that the matrons
don't ask any more tricky questions.
What is the question in the last monthly exam?
"The Ten Eyebrows of the Dynasties"
Are we going to take the monthly exam?
Yes.
But
now that you can solve
the Second Lady's problem,
this monthly exam
will be a piece of cake for you.
Even the First Lady is pleased with you.
How did you manage to do it?
It's nothing.
There's nothing to say.
We'll be counting on you, Si Yan.
Please say more nice words about us
in front of the princes and ladies.
Yes.
Okay.
Here are the questions for this monthly exam.
Prepare yourselves well.
Yes.
Get out of the way!
Design a look for a date on Valentine's Day.
One of the makeup items you need
must be handmade.
The judges are the men in the East Mansion.
No way!
Those straight men?
Red.
Come here.
Prince Da,
I haven't seen you for a while.
How are you doing?
Today,
let's have some fun.
You...
He is that important guest.
Sit over there.
Pour the wine.
You...
Have you noticed anything
d...
different about me lately?
There's nothing different.
Your Highness has always been so masculine.
Green.
I think
you can speak more fluently.
Your stammer seems to have improved.
Your Highness, don't be angry.
My lord,
is that enough?
If not, we'll squeeze some more.
Qi Da.
Twenty-five years old.
His mother died when he was young.
He was brought up in turn by the matrons in the mansion.
Though not talented,
he is
studious.
The First Lady arranged for Qi Yi and Miss Min
for a boat trip at Valentine's Lantern Festival.
Brother Yi has the support of his mother.
He really has the upper hand.
I have no one to rely on.
What kind of woman would he like?
If I can't marry Miss Min
to have the support from General Min,
I would not be able to compete with Brother Yi.
With such a vast network of connections,
there is not a single woman
who is close to Qi Da.
Does he stutter when he gets close to women
because he got his heart broken before?
What's going on?
Not a single word of the procuress is true.
It seems we can only wait until the eve of the Valentine's day
to find out who the oiran is.
What do you want to do, Your Highness?
We'll do as planned.
Why did you come here?
I was afraid someone would copy my idea.
Your design
is unexpected,
natural and free.
It's a combination of the form of the Eastern Jin Dynasty
and the grace and elegance of the Tang Dynasty.
I'm sure you can do it.
I don't know if you're complimenting me
or insulting me.
I'm sorry.
I should have believed in you that day.
You may be willful,
but you wouldn't hurt someone for no reason.
But
I had to find evidence
to prove your innocence.
So you left her
and allowed someone else to hurt her.
Why didn't you explain to me?
Have you
never trusted me?
If you had told me why you left the Mansion,
I would never have let them take you away.
If you knew her well,
you should have trusted her.
You've always tried to be brave.
You're so tough.
If you'd just give in,
and beg for mercy,
I...
But then
she wouldn't be Si Yan.
What are you doing here?
Are you taking me to jail again?
It was my fault that day.
I didn't explain clearly...
Let's stay here to get out of the rain.
This place is too small.
Since I'm staying here,
I'd like to ask Your Highness
to go somewhere else to take shelter.
It's pouring outside.
If I get wet and sick,
can you take responsibility for that?
How delicate you are!
Alright.
You stay, I'll go.
Don't go.
Stay with me.
What's going on?
Did you hear
some sounds?
What sounds?
It sounded like
a woman's cry.
A lady of a prestigious house
fell in love with a servant.
Her parents did not approve.
So they decided
to elope together on Valentine's Day.
But the boy didn't come.
The desperate lady disappeared.
The servants went looking everywhere.
Suddenly...
What happened?
Someone saw a white shadow
under the grapevine
floating around.
When he looked closer...
Guess what he saw.
What did he see?
Someone saw the lady's neck
hanging under the grapevine.
She committed suicide.
Since then,
every year on Valentine's Day,
there are men hanging under the grapevine tree.
It is said
they are killed by the ghost of the lady.
Boring.
How can you be afraid of ghosts?
What a shame!
What kind of woman would be so stupid?
When they meet bad men,
is dying the only way out?
Women are always conscious of their reputations.
If they are abandoned by men,
they'll inevitably be criticized.
If a woman's shame is overwhelming,
she may go too far.
Why would they be ashamed
and can't live any longer
when they are abandoned by men?
I think
love for yourself is much more important than love for a man.
If you don't even love yourself,
who else can you expect to love you?
Right.
I can do the reverse design!
What is it?
Valentine's Day
is not just for girls in love,
but also for those who have lost their love,
and who are single.
If they cry, cry proudly.
I've decided on my makeup for Valentine's Day.
I'm going to call it "Pear Blossoms makeup".
No.
Grape Blossoms.
What do you think?
What is it?
What are you lining up for?
We're buying this limited edition gift box.
It's beautiful. I love it.
Open it.
It's not appropriate for me to open it.
Miss Min won't be happy if she finds out.
It has nothing to do with her.
Just open it.
I made you angry last time.
This...
Are you really going to give this to me?
What's wrong?
Isn't this color nice?
Which girl
would like such a dull color?
Take a look.
It's horrible.
I think this color is the chicest one.
Your Highness,
if you don't know how to choose, just don't do it.
If you have no idea,
you can ask me.
What do you mean?
I really suggest you
not give it to me.
If you don't like it, throw it away.
Just joking.
I know you feel guilty.
You bought it for me on purpose.
So...
You've forgiven me?
Not today.
Some other day.
I'll forgive you some other day.
You need another day for that?
I'll talk to you next time.
I have to prepare for my monthly exam.
See you.
Those two dressing girls are quite clever.
They didn't offend anyone.
Especially the girl called Si Yan.
Even Brother Yi, who is usually calm and self-possessed,
becomes ill at ease.
Very interesting.
And brother Bao
is also around her every day
like a bee in the bush.
It's like a big fight.