Unforgettable Love
EP11
We're home!
Oh my Gosh! The villa has changed a lot.
Xiaobao
Go and see what it is.
Look, Xiaobao.
Isn't it like the small house in the fairy tale
I told you yesterday?
It smells good.
Xiaobao, let's go wash our hands.
Come and have dinner after washing your hands.
This is good.
This is your new table?
Didn't you say that
home should enable us feel like home.
Eating is not only about getting food,
but also an opportunity
for family to communicate.
The round table can
draw us closer than the long table.
Sit down, please.
Wait a minute.
Look at these chairs, Xiaobao.
Which color do you like?
Quickly choose one,
and then put on your little sticker
to occupy the seat.
Hey,
This table is my new...
What's new?
Nothing.
Furniture
is for people.
Come on.
It's time for dinner.
Which dish do you like?
I'll pick it up for you.
Eat for yourself.
This is your reward.
The three of us eat together.
Come on.
Are you Miss Yang?
Yeah.
Follow me, please.
Miss Yang, please have a seat.
Thank you.
Mr. Wen
The file you want,
I've already brought it here.
Mr. Wen, Good job!
This is the document you want.
No hurry.
Excuse me,
Please enjoy your meal.
The grilled Japanese Black Cattle in this restaurant
is very good.
Try it.
Don't beat me.
At three o'clock direction,
the person who was secretly photographing
was arranged by you, right?
How can you be kidding?
Why would I do that?
No reason.
Because you want to find someone
to take a picture of us,
so you can tell Chairman Wen
that I am
a person with over-weight scheming
who seduces you.
About Chairman Wen,
hates that there are girls in the company
who deliberately approach you,
so he will fire me.
When I leave,
no one will keep an eye on you.
Why don't you think
I really love you?
Restaurant, violin,
and this.
Premium Japanese Black Cattle.
Big brother, what era is it?
How can you
say that you really love me.
Want to catch a lady?
I suggest you
do the whole set when you are acting.
Otherwise, you lose the woman and your face.
Since Miss Yang is so confident,
dare you make a bet with me?
What's the bet?
If I get you tempted,
you'll take the initiative to leave.
Naive.
Why make fun
of my work?
Or I'll tell my dad,
that night...
we...
Fine.
Just go ahead.
Enjoy
your time
in Wenshi group.
I believe
that you
will leave soon.
What happened?
But I have one condition.
If I got you tempted,
you'll have to listen to me.
Don't you dare?
What do I dare not do?
Deal.
Go!
Yiyue, Xiaobao.
Xiaobao,
guess what
I'll give you?
He is shy.
It's OK. Mommy can help you.
What is it?
Look, what's this?
Here you are, OK?
Let's go. Mommy will take you to play.
This guy,
When did he get on so well
with Xiaobao?
Look,
Try to bounce the ball yourself.
What are you doing here?
I have seriously considered your suggestion
and decided to make a field trip to see
if it is really suitable for Xiaobao.
Welcome, Mr. He!
Let me show you around.
Not necessary.
I've known
all the hardware facilities here.
It's mainly about teachers.
I think it's necessary for me
to know about Mr. Ning Fang.
Xiaobao can't wait to play the ball.
Come on, Xiaobao.
You two brothers, please step aside.
No.
Since it's a parent-child activity,
I think it's necessary
to participate in it together.
Xiaobao,
Let's play basketball.
I'll, by myself,
take turns to challenge Mr. Ning Fang
and your mummy.
If they win,
you can come to this school,
OK?
You against us two alone?
Yes, of course.
Come on, Ning Fang!
Dad scored.
It's a goal!
Dad scored again!
Come on, Ning Fang!
2-2, a draw.
Is it my turn to play?
l have to go.
I'm coming.
Yeah!
Hand hurts.
Mr. He.
Well, I will humor you.
We play positioning shots.
I don't need it.
Yeah!
Goal!
Great!
Come again.
It's almost a goal. It doesn't matter.
It's your turn.
Wow!
Again!
Time's over. Four to two.
We won!
Xiaobao, you can go to school!
You can to go to school.
Are you happy, Xiaobao?
Yeah!
Mr. He, you have to keep your word.
Look,
pencil and eraser,
I've got a lot for you.
At that time,
when some other kids don't bring it,
remember to share with them.
Change and tissue,
I'll put them both
in the side pocket.
Handkerchief.
Xiaobao can go to school finally!
OK.
Let's move on to the next one.
Let's cover the books together.
You know?
When I was a kid,
What I'm looking forward to most
is the book cover before the beginning of school.
It's usually wrapped by my father.
This is
the sense of ritual when school begins.
Is it pretty?
Shall I put something
on your face?
This is the sense of ritual when school begins.
Excuse me,
This is a great next-gen invention.
The prototype of children's smart schoolbag,
combined with our company's latest technology,
can comprehensively deal with
all kinds of emergencies
Xiaobao encounter at school.
Let me show you.
Xiaobao, look at me.
In times of danger,
There is a one button
for help on the left.
When you press it,
it will give out a warning sound.
There's a camera in the middle.
A rangefinder on the right.
How heavy it is!
I've thought about that.
New lightweight design,
in line with the human body mechanics,
can resist the high temperature of 500 degrees
and the water depth of 20 meters.
People who know think he is going to school,
for those who don't know,
they think that he is going to war.
In addition,
Integrated with GPS,
And face recognition to prevent lost.
The data can be synchronized
to the app of parents' mobile phone in real time.
Can it walk on its own?
Is there any need for moving?
You are so powerful,
why don't you just
build a robot to accompany him to school?
Sounds sort of reasonable.
If necessary,
I can arrange
special accompanying staff.
Do you like it?
Come here,
Just save it.
The school
is full of children
of the same age as Xiaobao.
The teachers and the logistics were there all day.
When you make such an exception,
how can he blend in?
Xiaobao is different from
other children.
I have to make sure
he is perfectly safe.
In addition,
This is the first time
for him to face
the strange collective environment alone.
I have to make
a comprehensive assessment and prevention
of this unknown environment.
Think about it,
there are 20 children in a class.
What kind of children
are the other 19?
Will they hurt him?
Are classroom facilities
and school activities safe?
I don't know anything about these.
Stop.
If you want Xiaobao
to become a normal child,
at first,
You have to learn
how to be a normal parent.
So you mean,
I'm not normal?
You are the boss,
How dare I say you're not normal.
It's just that I think,
You're really,
in some ways...
too extraordinary.
It's really hard
for a petty little beauty like me
to understand.
Good Bye.
Xiaobao,
I'll be with you.
So is there
a need for moving?
I'll modify it.
Xiaobao, your father is crazy.
Come on.
Good morning.
Bye-bye.
Come on, Xiaobao. I'll take it for you.
Your bag.
Xiaobao, be good and go to school.
Dad and mom,
will pick you up after school.
OK?
I have another meeting this afternoon.
Of course, it can be cancelled.
Xiaobao,
Mom and I
will pick you up from school in the afternoon.
Don't worry,
our Xiaobao, don't be afraid.
This handkerchief
mom put on the side of your schoolbag for you,
mom will always be with you,
OK?
In fact, you don't have to go.
Come and kiss dad.
Bye, baby. Have a good class.
Good morning teacher.
You can say goodbye
in the way of kiss relay.
Xiaobao kisses his father,
then his father kisses his mother,
and then his mother kisses Xiaobao,
so the family
will be together forever.
You're a little villain.
You're very enthusiastic
about this kind of thing.
Now it's the mother's turn
to pass on the kiss to the dad.
The good interaction between the parents
also indirectly gives the child a sense of security.
No way.
That's not what I want,
but what Xiaobao want.
Please cooperate.
Stage kiss, OK?
Kiss or not?
Stage kiss.
Do you want
to die?
If you're afraid, go.
Xiaobao, we are kissing now.
Kiss.
OK.
I still have a meeting.
Idiot.
Xiaobao,
Your father is a big fool.
Let him go back,
and practice more.
Can we continue tomorrow?
Xiaobao, Yiyue,
Ning Fang.
Good morning.
Xiaobao,
You and brother Ning Fang,
go to school together, is that OK?
Otherwise,
You go in together.
Can I?
Don't worry.
I can tell them.
You're my temporary assistant.
I'll take you in.
That's great!
Thank you.
Let's go, Xiaobao.
Mom will accompany you in.
Be careful.
It's time to go to school.
Mr. He,
I won't go to the company today.
Let all the participants,
go to the building directly opposite
the Sunshine Primary School
and find the floor facing the second floor
of the teaching building.
OK, let me check.
But that place
doesn't seem suitable for a meeting.
I don't care.
That,
is the place for today's regular meeting.
Please slow down, sister.
Excuse me.
I've wronged you today.
Today is Junior He's first day at school.
Mr. He is a little uneasy.
So our meeting today...
I'm not worried.
Yes, yes.
This is called the merger of regular meeting
and group building.
How perfect to eat snail rice noodles for it.
By the way, we will test
the quality of the latest telescope
from the Yi En Company.
Xiaobao's situation
looks normal,
His mood is stable.
The environment is safe, too.
Nothing unusual.
Well.
Today we're going to start
our new course.
We are going to learn a poem today.
First of all, please read this poem
after me.
Farmers weeding...
You're so worried.
Do you think Xiaobao is OK?
Xiaobao is OK.
He will adapt soon.
Don't you think it's good?
Let's go.
Who knows food on a tray,
Thanks to their toiling day.
Mr. He.
Let me report
the sector adjustment in the third quarter.
Jason is in charge of the e-commerce operation
of the Yi En Company.
Now is the profit-making period.
If we take this opportunity,
we can
redistribute the traffic,
reach out to new users
and add value to our products.
Well done!
By the way, Jason...
Why is this guy here?
Jason,
isn't he in the marketing department all the time?
Mr. He,
Do you have a problem with Jason?
Dare you move again!
He didn't listen to the teacher,
and kept playing with handkerchief.
Don't worry.
Teachers in our school
is very professional.
Soon Xiaobao will get used to it.
Mobile phone.
Hello.
Hang up?
Think about where to go later.
It's such a fine day.
Or,
how about we
playing basketball with Xiaobao?
Call and hang up, over and over again.
Why is he so annoying?
Who is it?
Nothing.
Hello.
Are you CEO
and a part-time spammer?
Speak up.
The signal in the meeting room is not very good.
Table 7, one beef brisket rice noodles,
without sour bamboo shoots.
So you're eating rice noodles
in your working time?
What's up?
Go home early.
I promised Xiaobao
to play basketball
with Ning Fang after school,
Is that OK?
Something happened at home.
What can happen at home?
Something serious.
What's the matter?
I'll take you back.
No need. A driver will pick you up.
Hello?
What's up?
Why is he so hot tempered?
He Qiaoyan is really...
Come on, Xiaobao.
Hurry up, There's something wrong with dad.
Something serious happened. Come on.
You're back.
It's urgent, isn't it?
Xiaobao, go back to your room first.
Mom and Dad
have a few words to say.
Go ahead.
What's the matter?
I'm a little hungry.
I beg your pardon?
The seafood noodles you made for Xiaobao
tastes not bad.
I want to try it.
That's what you're talking about.
Isn't that serious enough?
I'm hungry,
which will affect my work.
If I can't work normally,
Heshi Group
won't be able to operate normally.
Heshi's stock price will fall,
employees' income will be affected,
and shareholders' assets will shrink.
Stop.
Seafood noodles, right?
I'll make it for you right now.
If you can't finish it,
you'll be in big trouble.
Tell you what.
I ordered seafood noodles.
Yes.
Instant noodles with seafood flavor.
If you don't think
it's enough seafood,
I'll add some more.
Very conscience,
you see.
You don't think
I've seen instant noodles before,
do you?
Do you want to eat it or not?
There's half
food additives in it.
This is the noodles you ordered.
You have to finish it even if you cry.
Friendly Reminder,
Freshly-made noodles
If you don't eat it,
It's going to be soggy in 15 minutes.
Eat it.
Eat.
Hello, Chairman He.
Mrs. Liu, is Qiaoyan in?
Mr. He is in the kitchen.
Take your time. I'm leaving.
Dare you go.
The noodles are getting soggy.
Suddenly I don't feel hungry.
Qiaoyan.
Aunt He, why are you here?
Aunt He?
Aunt He, this is Yiyue.
She's my wife.
Hello, aunt He.
Aunt He, why didn't you tell me in advance
when you came back this time?
Is she really your wife?
Of course.
It's just that we both
keep a low profile,
so we didn't have a wedding.
What's her family like?
and what's her job?
Her parents are ordinary workers.
Yiyue is a
child psychologist
working at Yade hospital.
Why do you choose her?
Because she's good.
Most of all,
Xiaobao likes her very much.
Just a little psychologist.
What's so good about her?
She...
is very special.
She is unique.
He has a sweet mouth.
Don't forget who you are.
Your wife
is not only your wife,
she is also the hostess of Heshi Group.
Can she bear it?
What's wrong to be the hostess?
Can it be a thousand pounds?
Is she afraid I can't take it?
Since she talks so much,
she must not be thirsty.
I'll drink it myself.
I'll see Xiaobao.
OK.
Go to the fridge,
put a piece of ice in your mouth.
Go.
OK.
Xiaobao.
Baby.
I miss you so much.
Xiaobao,
Do you like
the new mommy dad found for you?
I found Mommy.
Why don't you just
tell your aunt
that we are a contractual relationship.
You don't know my aunt.
She never does things
with a success rate of
less than 75%,
and most importantly,
she values my spouse very much.
What happened to your spouse?
It's not a gold mine.
It's worth more than gold mine.
Narcissism.
Are you ready?
What am I going to do?
Keep your gold mine.
My aunt has doubts
about our marriage.
You should find a way
to dispel her doubts.
Otherwise,
If we're both exposed,
you will pay the penalty.
Boss, what can I do?
Does it hurt?
I told you to be careful.
Look at you, you are so careless.
Aunt.
Blow.
We just need to
show her
something that looks sweet.
You didn't tell me before
that there would be a humanoid monitor at home
to watch us at any time.
My aunt usually lives in the old house
and doesn't come around often.
What kind of job do I have?
Xiaobao still doesn't say anything.
It's served.
The taste of Qin's food is superb.
Mommy.
Aunt He might not know that
Xiaobao had already started school.
It was all Yiyue's credit.
Nothing.
Mainly because Xiaobao is brave.
And Mr. He...
Qiaoyan is also cooperative.
Xiaobao, are you hungry?
Mommy made
your favorite chicken wings.
Let's eat.
OK.
Auntie, please try my specialty.
Mrs. Liu,
Take a pair of public chopsticks to Dr. Qin.
OK.
Give it to me.
Xiaobao also wants to eat it?
Mommy will pick it up for you.
I want one, too.
OK.
I'll go back first.
Auntie, let me see you off.
You eat first.
Xiaobao, you didn't dare to eat just now, did you?
We can eat now.
Well,
I'll feed you.
I didn't expect Qiaoyan
to get married so suddenly.
This marriage is for Xiaobao.
Why?
In order to treat Xiaobao.
You have seen that already.
Why didn't you say it?
The marital relation is fake.
But I found out that Qiaoyan
seemed to have a crush
on this girl.
How about Miss Lin's?
Same as usual.
The marriage of Lin's and He's family
is a must.