[English subtitles are available]
Who is playing?
Grand Tutor,
finally you are here.
I have been waiting for a long time.
Ming Hua?
You are Princess Ming Hua?
Why am I here?
Your obsessiveness brought you here.
Why won't you turn around
so that I can see your face clearly?
It doesn't matter.
When I show up in front of you,
you'll know for sure that
it's me.
Princess Ming Hua.
[Be My Princess]
[Episode 1]
[Lecture Notes on the History of the Ming Dynasty]
[Princess Ming Hua Love of Grand Tutor Mu Yun]
[Xiao Zhao]
[Tingzhou]
Hello,
Tingzhou.
What's up?
Are you reading the screenplay?
Are we going to use classical Chinese language
to communicate from now on?
Don't get stuck in the role
before you start filming.
Let me tell you something serious.
Without any losses, I just peacefully refused
four screenplays, seven endorsements,
and five variety shows for you.
In this case,
when you meet Orlando later, you...
[Xiao Zhao]
Hello? Hello?
[Grand Chief Cabinet Minister]
When I show up in front of you,
you'll know for sure that
it's me.
OK. Ming Wei,
turn around and look at the camera.
Good.
OK. Let's take a few more photos.
That's it.
That's the feeling of misty beauty.
It's so beautiful.
Lower down your arm slowly.
That model looks gorgeous.
Her dress is also beautiful.
Is it possible that she is a superstar?
I think some celebrities
are not as beautiful as she is.
Maybe she is just a model.
Even so, she is good-looking.
That's right.
So beautiful.
OK. Let's call it a day.
Thanks. Good job.
Well done.
My name is Ming Wei.
I'm not a superstar.
This is just one of my part-time jobs.
I'm running out of time.
There is another job waiting for me.
Wait, please.
My Best Actor,
stop reading the screenplay.
Think about the upcoming business discussion first.
[You are my princess.]
I'm Mu Yun,
Your Highness.
[You are my princess.]
Princess Ming Hua.
Will the actress playing the role of Princess Ming Hua
look as fresh and elegant as she?
[Wanda Reign Hotel]
Look at you.
You look amazing today.
What are these clothes?
It's the most beautiful dress I have ever seen.
Thanks.
Great minds think alike.
Maybe.
We will meet a VIP today.
He is Mu Tingzhou, my company's image spokesman
and one of the Best Actors in your country.
Really?
Miss, would you like to have a meal?
We have reserved a table.
I didn't expect a beauty wearing the Han costume today.
Hi,
I'm the interpreter of Orlando.
My name is Ming Wei.
It's her.
So you are the interpreter.
Nice to meet you, Miss Ming.
I'm Xiao Zhao,
Tingzhou's entertainment agent.
Miss Ming, you
look unique today.
You are striking.
Tingzhou, right?
Thank you.
Let me introduce.
Hello, Mr. Orlando.
You actually can speak Italian.
He can speak Italian.
I learned some.
God, this is incredible.
Please.
OK.
I only heard that you are one of the Best Actors,
your IQ is very high,
and you are good at many things.
I didn't know you can speak
Italian so well.
I'm flattered.
It's fine.
I'm telling the truth.
I came to China
to have a further discussion with you
about the contract extension.
No problem.
OK.
Miss Ming,
you look quite young.
Have you graduated from college?
I graduated last year.
Today, it's my pleasure to meet
you and Mr. Mu.
You are being so polite, Miss Ming.
With a beautiful and elegant lady
like you being here,
my job today
is not that boring anymore.
After all, you can interpret for me.
Excuse me.
Mr. Mu,
chatting with you
has given me many new inspirations.
It's enjoyable.
Really.
Excuse me.
I'll come back immediately after answering the phone.
Don't eat all of the food here.
Despite his cold face,
he looks really handsome.
I know I'm handsome,
but she should pay attention to the way
of looking at me in front of so many people.
This is so awkward.
How about asking for his autograph?
Next,
she should ask for my autograph.
Mr. Mu,
could I have your autograph?
You are the fourth one.
The fourth what?
Customers speak highly of the desserts here,
but I think the desserts are not as sweet as you are. Not even close.
Cheng Yao is also here.
Here.
Who are you texting to?
A client.
Female client?
The name is Wei, right?
Fine. I won't ask again.
Xiao Zhao,
hello,
why are you here?
Such a coincidence.
I'm here to accompany Tingzhou to meet a partner.
Is this Mr. Cheng?
Xiao Zhao, nice to meet you.
Hello. I'm Cheng Yao.
Mu Tingzhou is here, too.
Let's greet him.
OK. I will show you the way.
Tingzhou.
Here. Let me introduce.
Hello, Mr. Mu.
Let me introduce.
This is Mr. Cheng from Zhenghua Group.
Zhenghua Group's business covers many areas.
It recently invested in some TV series, too.
This is...
This scumbag.
This is Miss Wang Yingying,
the heroine of
the recently popular TV series Phoenix Fly.
You should know her.
I have never watched it.
This is Miss Ming Wei,
our interpreter.
I didn't know interpreters are so pretty these days.
Who hasn't met
any scumbags?
It's lucky
to find it out
as early as possible.
Wei.
So you are the girl named Wei.
Do you think people with a wealthy background like Cheng Yao
will marry someone unknown like you?
I can tell that
you like him very much.
It must be difficult
to win the heart of an affectionate man
like Cheng Yao, right?
Wish you happy.
Are you leaving like this?
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Cheng Yao,
no matter when you began to be with her,
it is not important anymore.
I'm just glad that
I found it out
so early.
Wei. Let me explain.
From now on,
we go our separate ways.
And we should never meet again.
Wei.
This girl is interesting.
Wait for me here.
I will get the car.
Tingzhou,
you have to deal with this.
You chose the hotel for the meeting.
And it has become a place of sadness for Miss Ming.
Shouldn't you be responsible for it?
She should thank me
for helping her identify that scumbag early.
OK.
As a gentle man,
it is a basic principle for me not to
let girls cry in front of me.
Mr. Mu.
Thank you.
Would you like to take a photo with me?
This is the first time for Mr. Mu
to offer to take a photo with others.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
Here. Smile, you two.
Closer.
Smile.
Three, two, one.
OK.
Have a look.
Thank you.
It's so ugly.
Can we take one more?
It's good.
You can photoshop it later.
Remember. Don't upload it to any social platforms.
Why did this happen?
It's so shameful.
Wei.
I think I have made it quite clear.
Wei,
I have no relationship with her anymore.
I wanted to break up with her
when I first met you.
But she was working all the time,
so I didn't have the chance.
I planned to have the last meal with her today.
I know I was wrong.
I didn't tell you in advance.
I will behave better in the future, okay?
You were arm in arm so intimately.
I don't think you were having the last meal.
It is a fact that you have cheated on me.
You can make your promise,
but I can never believe you.
Let's break up
and make the ending decent.
Wei.
I know I hurt you.
I hope you can give some time
to our relationship and let yourself calm down.
Don't give up easily, okay?
I'm not suitable to
a man who is affectionate like you.
Let me go.
Wei. Listen to me. Wei.
Qiao.
Why did you beat me?
I'm hitting a cheating scumbag like you.
What's wrong?
Stay away from my sister.
I cannot make sure where I will kick you next time.
Get lost.
Sister, let me tell you.
We are from a martial arts family.
You should beat scumbags like Cheng Yao
every time you meet one.
There is no need to be kind.
What if he is hurt?
I know how much strength I use, ok?
Sister,
when will you take photos wearing the Han costume next time?
Can I go with you?
I just worry that Cheng Yao
comes to plague you again.
I'm not going for fun for sure.
The model company didn't
assign me for any new work recently.
The interpretation jobs these days
went quite smooth.
This is the pay of three days.
Guess who I met today.
Who?
Mu Tingzhou.
The Best Actor.
Come in.
I have found it.
I almost promised to be the son-in-law of the director.
Can't he even promise to lend me some books?
What documents can't be found
on the Internet?
And you insist in checking the ancient books.
How can it be the same to read on a computer!
For example, the font
is not time honored.
Look.
The yellowing paper
shows the warmth of the age.
I can only get the rotten smell.
What's more,
Mu Yun was a highly ranked official at that time.
As long as you understand
what big figures did at that time, you should be good.
Why do you check
the small things of folks.
The official history
is only the basic knowledge.
It can only help with framing a person.
Only when you understand
the daily customs of folks deeply,
can you create a lively figure.
How do you think? Is he handsome?
Is he as tall as it is shown on TV?
It's alright.
I don't think he is easygoing.
I intended to ask for an autograph for you.
But he told me that
I was the fourth.
Do you know why?
I read from the tabloid that
he only signs for
three people every day.
It's such a pity that you didn't get it, sis.
It's worth lots of money.
So great.
I write over 30 replies for my fans every day.
[Message]
[Shen Su]
Hello, Miss Ming Wei.
I'm Shen Su from Dongying Group.
We are planning to do a costume drama.
Qiao.
I have seen the photos of you wearing the Han costume on Weibo
and think your image
is similar to the role in our drama.
[Shen Su]
So, I would like to invite you for audition.
Seriously,
this is
the most meaningful role
you got for me in recent years.
Help with the country governance.
Worry about the country and people.
Be honest and clean in the duty.
And even give up his own romance
for the country.
The figure is complex
and challenging.
Speaking of love scenes,
do you remember
I received a call
when we had the meal with Orlando?
They said that the heroine was pregnant.
The crew plans to change her
as she wants to prevent miscarriage.
Aren't you angry?
Sure enough.
She is not Princess Ming Hua.
Who is it?
Hello.
I'm the entertainment agent of Miss Ming Wei.
You have seen the message I sent to you, right?
The place of audition is Dongying.
If Ming Wei can participate,
I will send the detailed address
to you.
We can.
OK. See you then.
[Grand Chief Cabinet Minister]
How was it?
I think it was not good.
Ming Wei. It's your turn.
Be confident.
Come on!
You are here for audition as well?
It's so different to have the support of someone wealthy.
Do you know how to act?
Have you ever acted?
Lack of self-knowledge.
Hello, Cheng Yao.
Are you supporting that interpreter?
Even an interpreter can be interviewed for a heroine.
Does she know how to act?
[Personal Profile Ming Wei]
Ming Wei.
Don't be nervous.
[Dongying Group Board Director Shen Su Dongying Group Production Department Supervisor Cui Xun]
I saw it from your profile
that you know how to play the Chinese zither, right?
Yes. My mom is a Chinese zither teacher.
[Dongying Group Board Director Shen Su Dongying Group Production Department Supervisor Cui Xun]
Great.
In this way,
you can try the scene of
playing the Chinese zither.
Come.
Get prepared.
OK.
Grand Tutor,
you have come to see me.
If you believe in fate,
then all coincidences are destined.
When I show up in front of you,
you'll know for sure that
it's me.
If you don't believe in fate,
then all destined incidents are coincidental.
I believe in it.
Everyone,
these are the four finalists.
Please
share your opinions.
Among the four candidates,
[Song Yao]
Song Yao is the biggest star.
She also has good qualifications and acting skills.
Right.
But she also offered the shortest period,
which means
we have to shoot all her scenes together,
and process it with green-screen technology.
The use of green-screen technology
will definitely affect the quality of our show, right?
What about Yuan Tianying?
I think she's easy to work with,
[Yuan Tianying]
and her acting skills are good.
Acting 17 when she's 30...
While it's not unacceptable,
it only works if she
doesn't look 40.
If that is the case,
we have only two options left.
[Wang Yingying Ming Wei]
About Wang Yingying,
she's a rising actress,
[Wang Yingying]
having played the lead in two web dramas.
Although her acting skills
are not much to talk about,
still,
she's quite average in all aspects.
She's also got the experience of being a heroine,
which is to her advantage
when compared with Ming Wei.
Ms. Shen,
I'm sorry to say this.
I know you recommended her,
but it's too much pressure on the production team
if we use a new actress.
Ming Wei is a complete rookie.
Congratulations!
Congratulations to me!
I never imagined I would get the role.
This good news came too suddenly.
I'm still a little stunned now.
Do you know what this is?
What you lose in love, life will reward you in your career.
With that face and elegance,
you'll be famous sooner or later.
It's too soon for that.
What matters most now
is that I improve my acting skills.
This is what I'm most concerned about.
Now that I've gotten the opportunity,
I have to do my best.
Wei,
it just occurred to me...
are there those type of scenes...
with the leading man
in this show...
I'll get you a tissue.
Bad girl.
What did you want to say?
Is there that type of scene?
Any
kissing scenes?
I haven't got the script yet.
But there are kissing scenes
in the novel.
Really?
This will be Mu Tingzhou's first kissing scene ever.
Did you know that, Wei?
Since his debut,
Mu Tingzhou has never shot any intimate scenes beyond hugs
with those actresses.
He also never accepted any romantic dramas.
Gosh.
My sister is about to
shoot a romantic drama
with the Prince Charming of thousands of girls.
Why does that sound a little creepy to me?
I've also heard that he's never done kissing scenes.
So,
it's still uncertain
if the kissing scenes will be removed.
I bet they won't.
Why?
You are so pretty.
If he kisses you,
he'll be a monster.
If he doesn't kiss you,
he'll be even worse than a monster.
Stop joking around.
I'm really a little nervous now.
If I can't act well,
it will be so embarrassing.
Notwithstanding the kissing scenes,
the whole show will be screwed.
Can you be a little more optimistic, good sister?
I'm just nervous.
It's good news, don't be worried.
Come on, bottoms up!
One, two, three...
-Cheers. -Cheers.
Run slowly, princess.
You're sweating.
This actress got the hiccups,
and she ate garlic.
Replace her now!
So scary.
[Alarm clock]
[General History of China]
[Grand Chief Cabinet Minister]
This scene.
Hurry up.
There's only a few days left before I start filming.
Why this scene again?
He'll find out, awkwardly,
that all the propositions of Zhang Juzheng
were all proposed and done before
by his predecessors.
The only thing he's done better than them is...
So handsome!
Go on.
You go.
Milk tea for you.
And my WeChat.
Thank you.
Can't you keep it more low-key?
I didn't do anything.
I'm just so charming.
What can I do?
Let's go.
[Shenghe Central Library]
Ming Wei.
Mr. Mu. Mr. Xiao.
Call me Xiao Zhao.
Why are you here?
I heard that
there's a lecture on the chief cabinet ministers of the Ming Dynasty.
I thought it would help me to understand the script.
That's why I'm here.
Are you here for that, too?
Not us, just him.
I didn't see Mr. Mu just now.
Good for you, Ming Wei.
You are quite hardworking.
I'm betting on you.
This is my first time acting,
and I'll be working with Mr. Mu.
Of course I have to work very hard.
All the best.
If you have any questions, just ask him.
Don't stand on ceremony.
How do you feel
about this one month of training?
I've learned a lot.
For me,
it's like opening a door to a brand new world.
I want to learn more.
It's a pity that there's no time left.
In the acting industry,
it's very important to keep on learning.
But innate talent is also very important.
After all,
no matter how many books you read and how comprehensive the notes you take,
if you are not a natural,
it won't make any difference.
I'm not sure if I'm gifted or not,
but I believe that
diligence can make up for a lot.
Since the crew has chosen me,
I'll do my best.
I have a bottom line
that is
we can't delay our shooting schedule
for any actor's incapabilities.
I hope that
you won't let the whole crew down.
Rest assured.
If I let you down,
I'll leave on my own.
I won't delay the schedule.
See you tomorrow.
Mr. Chen.
[Grand Chief Cabinet Minister]
Miss Ming.
Hello.
Mr. Chen.
I missed you at the booting ceremony.
I never thought I'd meet you here.
What a coincidence.
Let me introduce myself formally.
Princess, I'm your consort, Chen Zhang.
Mr. Chen,
this is my first time shooting a show.
Sorry if I have to bother you in the future.
It's my honor
to share the princess's cares and burdens.
You've already started flirting.
Director.
Hello, director.
Hello.
Mr. Mu.
Director.
Since I'm about to marry Ming Wei
very soon,
it doesn't count.
It was an expression of sincerity
and loyalty to her.
Alright.
Ming Wei.
You will be shooting your first scene tomorrow.
When you're home,
study the script carefully.
You are the only rookie in our crew.
Remember to learn from Mr. Mu and Mr. Chen.
Don't fall behind,
OK?
No problem, director.
I'll try my best.
Alright, go back and have a good rest.
You will all be shooting lots of scenes soon.
Director,
I have something
I want to talk to you about.
OK.
-See you, director. -See you.
See you, then.
OK.
He's gone, right?
I'll take the elevator after he's gone.
Don't you want to come in?
Oh my God, he's not gone.
Mr. Mu.
What's up?
I'm a rookie.
I hope I can learn from you
in the future.
I can consider teaching you in my free time,
but first,
you have to show me your sincerity.
What are you referring to?
Why...why is he coming so close?
It can't be what I'm thinking, right?
The unspoken rules.