(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Previously, on "The Devil Judge".)
Master Yo Han...
was an abandoned child.
He was a child nobody wanted.
Some humans are born as monsters.
Among them, revenge is an excuse...
to prey on others for fun.
This is fate, everyone!
Arson and acts of terrorism!
Forget all about it.
A powerful judicial reform. It begins now!
There's concern the live court show is unconstitutional.
Who is weak?
I exercise the judicial power delegated to me...
by the sovereign Korean public.
This is a court?
No one else here wants to go against the wind.
You want me to be Judas?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to...
a court owned by you.
He looks just like him,
more than I expected.
You didn't even hesitate to shoot.
Were you going to kill that man?
If I had to.
Why does Judge Kang Yo Han want to raise the stakes like this?
Do you think this is a trial to reveal his crimes...
or the opposite?
We should try to do something no matter what.
The verdict is...
a total of 235 years.
I thought he was going to let him off the hook.
I'm kind of confused.
It was moving. I even teared up.
He might not be tame enough.
Are you looking for this?
(Justice will be done by the judgment of the people.)
Where am I?
Stay put. Don't wander around.
Is there something I shouldn't see?
Curiosity killed the cat.
Who is this person?
Who is this?
Yo Han, go...
I'll come right back.
It's Master Isaac. Master Yo Han's older brother.
I wonder how much you've discovered.
Don't pretend to be tough.
You're not even brave enough to face your pains.
You falter when I speak like this.
Do you know how they ended up gaining their power?
They turned a crisis into an opportunity.
This is how the ones who conquer the world work.
Mr. President!
After the pandemic, the foundation began expanding its charity.
What's your next plan?
Division.
There's nothing we can do if those who have power stick together.
We need to shake them up.
What if I give you a bigger prey?
A rich businessman? The president?
The Social Responsibility Foundation is accepting donations...
for their Dream Home Village project.
But I received a tip that the money...
is being used elsewhere.
To reveal that Kang Yo Han is bluffing,
you must show your hands.
We have Mr. Seo, don't we?
You just picked a fight with the country.
Let's aim for the body first.
I lived on so I could go back there.
As the master of the world...
you kicked me out of.
We have to meet.
Are you...
Hi, Master Yo Han.
Threats are meaningless.
Because I have nothing...
I wish to protect.
Let's see if Master Yo Han really has nothing...
- Soo Hyun! - he wishes to protect.
How dare you lay a hand on Soo Hyun? Soo Hyun of all people!
I didn't do anything to your friend.
Don't ever attack me again.
- Never do that. - How can I trust you?
I have to show you something.
Inmate number 70618, he is Doh Young Choon.
Never once, not even for a single day have I forgotten his face.
It's not him.
This is the system.
A system has no chance against power.
Power can control a system however it likes.
Why did you go in the first place?
You wanted to shake me, someone who kept interfering with your plans.
I wanted...
you to be on my side.
Make your choice.
Will you stand in my way...
or stand on my side?
If there's no justice in reality and it's just a game,
I would like to be on the winning team.
You once asked me...
how I was going to fight against those who run this world.
I make sure I win before the game even starts.
I'll promise you one thing.
The man who stole from your parents.
They will pay for what they did.
Very cruelly.
It's not just about revenge.
I want to fight...
the corrupt world.
(Episode 9)
Did you...
make your decision?
You're the one who forced me to choose.
If there's no justice in reality and it's just a game,
I would like to be on the winning team.
"We worked hard."
"Please pay us."
Put your hands up.
Put the camera down.
Are you a cop?
Will you shoot me?
Shoot.
You can't anyway.
Put that down.
Film me.
Do you regret it?
I'll promise you one thing.
The man who stole from your parents.
And the people who smuggled him away.
They will pay for what they did.
Very cruelly.
It's not just about revenge.
Then what is it?
I want to fight...
the corrupt world.
Elijah?
Yes, what is it?
Yo Han, come quickly.
I'm in trouble.
Where are you?
Where are you right now?
Stay right there.
What's going on?
Kill the video and record the audio.
Are you all right?
Are you watching this, Mr. President?
I am a patriotic citizen of this country.
I was summoned by the president, so I stood up dauntlessly.
But a mere police officer is trying to oppress me.
Step back.
Shoot.
What? Darn it!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey.
Darn it.
No, stop!
No, don't!
Stop her.
- No! - Elijah...
No!
Hey!
Elijah! Soo Hyun!
Go away! Get off of me!
Elijah, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
It's... Kang Yo Han.
It's Kang Yo Han
- We respect you. - It's really him.
- Sir. - Sir. My name is Juk Chang.
Gosh.
You remember me, don't you?
Soo Hyun, are you okay?
I'm fine. How did you come here?
You're not hurt, are you?
How dare you touch my niece?
I didn't know.
I really didn't know.
Stop it. Are you trying to kill him?
Stop it!
Soo Hyun.
I said stop.
Soo Hyun, put your gun down.
You stop too.
Goodness...
You're pointing a gun at me?
You're under arrest for special assault.
This is Yoon Soo Hyun.
I need backup.
Come here.
Say something at least.
Yoon Soo Hyun.
She's out of her mind.
How dare she put you in danger?
- Soo Hyun didn't do anything wrong. - "Soo Hyun"?
I was craving tteokbokki, so she took me out.
And we ran into those scumbags on our way back.
What could I have done about that?
I...
don't even have anyone who I can have tteokbokki with.
Do you know that?
Chief Kang.
I know what you're worried about.
But Soo Hyun is a good person.
Not as an officer,
but as a person, she worries about and likes Elijah.
You're being nosy.
How much longer...
do you think you can look after a teenage girl alone?
I know the church fire traumatized you.
But Elijah is no longer a six-year-old.
You can't lock her up forever...
She's been kidnapped twice.
Pardon?
Many people either want our family's money...
or hold a grudge against us.
And Elijah trusts whoever treats her nicely.
She's hungry for affection.
No matter how much you hate the world and the people in it,
you can never live alone.
You always need someone to rely on.
As long as you're a human being.
Rest up.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
This is my office now.
What a long journey it's been.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
(Contacts)
(Board Chairman Seo Jeong Hak, President Yoon Doo Sung)
(Chairman Lee Jae Kyung, Jae Hee)
(Jae Hee)
Hi, Sun Ah.
What are you up to?
What else?
I'm enjoying my fancy private life after work.
I see. You sound busy.
Is something up?
I can come over if it's urgent.
No, nothing's up.
I was just wondering if we could have a glass of champagne together.
Sun Ah.
Don't tell me the mighty chairman of the foundation...
has no one to have champagne with.
Have some fun. Don't worry about what people think.
Well? Should I send some models over?
No, I'm fine.
Have a good time.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
Models?
That sounds fun.
Chief Kang.
What's the matter?
Soo Hyun just called me.
Everyone from Jukchang TV got released.
They all got released?
It was the police commissioner's order.
I wonder what made the commissioner step in.
So they're not just a bunch of psychos?
Hello?
Yes, sir.
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
The chief justice wants a meeting.
With all three of us.
What?
That's an interesting idea.
Here they come.
Have a seat.
The head of the Live Court Show Operation Support Committee here...
is very enthusiastic.
She wants to make...
live court show promotion videos and posters featuring you three...
by herself.
You need to increase media exposure.
Make the public go wild.
Make them look up to and love Judge Kang.
Make them desire him.
Just like I do.
You're funny, Ms. Jung.
I wasn't joking.
You want us to be clowns in front of the public?
Is that it?
Chief Kang. Don't be so negative.
The foundation wants to support our live court show.
This is our chance to improve the court's position.
Say no more and cooperate.
Chief Justice, you do understand these things.
I'm sorry, but I don't think that's something judges should do.
Getting close to the public.
That doesn't sound bad to me.
Are you sure it's the live court show that you want to promote?
Of course. Why are you asking?
Things have been quite uncomfortable between us lately.
And the foundation suddenly wants to promote our show?
That's unbelievably generous of you.
By any chance, do you have any slogans in mind?
"Strong law and order, a safer Korea."
"The live court show is with you."
Isn't that the slogan the president has been pushing?
Does that make you uncomfortable?
Don't tell me you're against the government policy.
That sounds fun.
Let's do this.
Chief Kang.
What?
Goodness, Master Yo Han. Are you seeing me off?
Was my warning not enough?
I'm pretty sure I told you that I don't have much patience.
Oh, that? It's okay.
It didn't leave a mark.
You'll have to pay for interfering with my plans.
It seems you worked hard to get here.
Would that be okay?
Interfering?
I'm helping you right now.
The survivor of a tragic accident.
The judge who punishes evil mercilessly.
Right. It all sounds good.
People love stories like that.
But wouldn't it be more fun if the stage was bigger?
There are only two more years left before the elections.
Instead of Heo Joong Se or Cha Kyung Hee,
you should grab onto this country.
That suits you best.
Shining brightly at the top.
So?
Use us.
Use the foundation.
How interesting.
You want me to become a sheepdog instead of a wolf...
with you?
There are a lot of cases that draw the interest of people.
Child abusers, rapists, gangsters...
If you get rid of those pieces of trash,
I'll make you into a bigger hero.
The foundation can make anyone the most powerful person in Korea.
We did that with Heo Joong Se, that piece of trash.
If you wait another two years, you and I...
Everything sounds good except for that.
"You and I".
You should take into consideration what I like.
Master Yo Han.
Can you...
be a little nicer to me?
I'll see you again.
I thought you'd like a drink.
Thank you.
They don't have a separate occupational force.
They want to use us for the things that they've started.
It's not a bad idea to make them think we're letting them go.
We could search for an opening then.
You're right.
But they suddenly want us to do promotions? This isn't a joke.
It probably is.
That's the kind of person she is.
Why?
Do you know Ms. Jung well?
Have you known her for a long time?
Yes. I met her here in this house.
Here?
Didn't Ms. Ji say anything?
The story of the maid that jumped.
That was a true story?
How you played with someone's heart?
I knew it. You're just like him.
What are you talking about this time?
The way you judge things based on what you see.
Why on earth did you do that?
That girl could've gotten seriously injured.
She may never walk again.
Yo Han. I'm really worried about you.
This on top of what happened at school?
You could end up in a lot of trouble.
If things like this keep happening, who knows what Father would do?
Yo Han, can you promise me something?
Don't hurt innocent people.
Okay?
This...
When you look at this, think about the promise you made me.
Okay?
My gosh.
Oh, wow.
My brother was like that.
He didn't understand until the moment he died.
There is...
no such thing as an innocent person in this world.
(Republic of Korea, Blue House)
- Mr. President. - Yes. Go ahead.
There has been no progress in the investigation...
on the Violence Gang for the embezzlement of donations.
I know you.
Mr. Park, why are you being so impatient?
A gang isn't a gang for no reason.
A gang is a gang because they do things in secret.
Give us some time.
Our investigation teams are quite capable.
- Yes? - Recently, there has been...
an increase of people who support the internet personality Juk Chang,
and they've been acting as vigilantes throughout the country...
and committing mob violence.
I've heard reports of the police turning a blind eye to this.
- What do you have to say? - That's...
That's all fake news.
Can't you see that?
Who on earth said that?
What newspaper are you from? Are you really a reporter?
Hey, Secretary Choi. What are you doing?
- Did you let everyone in? - I apologize, Mr. President.
What on earth are you doing?
Do your job!
You're out. Got it?
Hey, you. The female reporter.
Are you smiling?
(Republic of Korea, Blue House)
Do you think you're smart?
(Is the country remaining idle as online influencer incites violence?)
(The president vehemently denies it.)
How can that idiot call himself the president?
How annoying.
I think the Blue House is being impetuous.
They're overreaching which is why they're being impetuous.
Putting him in that position was a mistake from the start.
It's all because of that old man, Seo Jeong Hak.
Dear fellow citizens whom I love and respect.
How can you call this a country?
Our precious citizens are dying from a pandemic.
The brats who were born into wealthy families, got educated,
and became successful...
Those people don't care one bit...
about us ordinary people.
I have never set foot in dirty politics before.
I am a fresh face. Someone who came from poverty. Your celeb.
I, Heo Joong Se, who will be chosen by you...
will be sure to make Korea rise up again.
I will put my life on the line...
to ensure Korea's Total...
Change.
Good job.
The Citizens' Choice, Heo Joong Se.
I'm sure ordinary people will relate.
Sir.
Do you really think that I will survive...
in the tough political world?
If you keep it up,
you won't embarrass yourself during the elections.
To be honest, I'm quite good live.
Please trust me.
Okay. Good job.
Thank you.
Salute.
Okay.
Do you think going with that man is a good idea?
I agree with her.
He's just a jester who hosted at our foundation's events.
How can he be a presidential candidate?
He used to be a famous actor.
Is it called "How Refreshing"?
It's really popular. He has six million subscribers.
A jester like him is perfect for such turbulent times.
Don't you agree?
Even if you become president now.
if you don't get the pandemic under control,
you'll be criticized during your entire term.
Why are you offering to be a human shield?
You can control him from the back. Right?
Don't you agree, Assemblywoman Cha?
They didn't want a powerful president.
That wasn't Seo Jeong Hak's idea.
It was the idea of the secretary who hid behind him.
(Strong law and order, a safer Korea)
I apologize. I'm a little late.
That's not a problem. We were setting things up.
Are there only two lights?
Isn't that too few?
Still, our judges look pretty good.
Oh, dear.
Don't.
Okay.
Perfect.
Are you enjoying yourself?
Yes.
Don't go too far.
I won't.
Very nice. Let's do this.
Judges, take your spots.
Crew, back out of the frame.
- Lights, get everyone. - Okay.
- Got it. - Take your positions.
Pose for me, please. Nice.
Okay, 1, 2. Look at the camera.
Nice. Judge Kim, smile brightly.
Cross your arms or something.
- Cross arms? - Yes.
Judge Kim, your face looks a little too stiff.
Put your dramatic good looks to some good use.
Try not to look so awkward.
- Just smile naturally. - Okay.
Our diva doesn't disappoint.
Can I stand in the middle now?
- Sure, you can. - Thank you.
Judge Oh, you know what to do. You're the best.
Sorry, I got a call.
Let's take a break.
Hey.
Did you get what I asked for?
Yes. I have everything on Jung Sun Ah's past.
Do you want me to leak it to Cha Kyung Hee as you asked?
Yes. Hide the sources. And one more thing.
Include one more detail.
That she worked for my family as a maid.
Minister Cha. We got something from the team we put on Jung Sun Ah.
Wow, this woman is very interesting.
Ms. Ji.
Hi, Ga On.
The coffee's...
I'll brew you a cup. Which beans do you prefer?
It's fine, I'll do it.
I prefer convenience.
Okay, then.
[VIU Ver] tvN E09 'The Devil Judge'
"Ga On's Revenge"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Take obscene photos, pick pockets, assault others?
We are here to sentence you!
We will get rid of them ourselves!
- We are... - Power!
How do you like your punishment?
Take it!
Here! You deserve it!
(Jukchang TV, Making Korea Cleaner Project)
What's that? Isn't that the lunatic from that night?
Elijah.
Why are you watching his videos?
He's obviously a loser. What power does he have?
As many as seven copycat assaults...
happened just yesterday.
And...
today this was uploaded.
(I put my life on the line)
Shoot me if you want!
Can a cop...
aim a gun at the heart of an unarmed civilian?
Aren't you ashamed?
My gosh.
He's pretending to be the victim?
This is unbelievable.
Let's put him away.
Shall I help?
No. I'll see what I can do on my own.
Okay.
If you can't manage, come to me.
Okay?
Okay. Thank you.
Ms. Ji. Are you going to cook?
Yo Han told you not to.
I'm going to cook for Ga On.
He never told me not to cook.
I'd be grateful if you'd cook for me.
Elijah, join me.
What? No, it's fine. Leave me out.
- Still, she put in the effort to... - I said I don't like Korean food.
Are you a goldfish? Can't you remember anything I say?
Darn it.
I just...
Sorry, Ms. Ji. I guess I was out of line.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
The truth is, Elijah is much more cheerful than before.
Is she?
She actively starts a conversation...
and offers to do something.
She never did that before.
Not since that accident.
It's all thanks to you.
I'm usually quiet and gruff,
and this is the only way I can show my thanks.
Will it be okay?
Whatever.
You're a great cook.
I just put a few simple dishes together.
Go on.
Thanks for cooking.
I wonder if the food's to your taste.
So, the taste is...
It tastes very different.
It's not something ordinary people eat every day.
I added wild honey so it's even better for you.
Oh. Wild honey?
You put honey in doenjang jjigae.
That's amazing.
That's ginseng kimchi.
I added lots of truffle oil,
so it'll have a unique flavor.
That's the truffle oil...
Isn't it delicious?
The thing is...
- Ms. Ji. - Yes? Go ahead.
Since when did you say Chief Kang banned you from cooking?
He started to eat less and less,
then he told me not to cook.
He used to eat everything without any complaints.
He suspects me.
Without any complaints?
My gosh...
Oh, you should eat.
It's still so hot.
Then have more ginseng kimchi.
Well...
So you don't like Korean food?
Did you finish everything?
You're pale.
Why didn't you warn me?
How could I?
She tries so hard.
She uses whatever healthy ingredients she can find.
What a fool she is.
So that's why you always finished everything without complaining.
Both of you.
Have you leaked the information about Jung Sun Ah to Cha Kyung Hee?
Yes, I did as you said.
She must be digging for information about the foundation.
And we need to get our hands on it.
Elijah, what's the matter?
- When are you coming home? - What?
I said, when are you coming home?
I'm hungry.
- What are you talking about? - Ga On prepared a meal,
but he says we can't start until you come.
Hurry and come home.
What?
- Take me home. - Pardon?
What about the appointment?
Put it off until tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Did you want to see me?
It's time to get them.
Who do you mean?
Your enemy. And...
those who hid him away.
(A safe Korea. I will make it come true.)
Did you catch Doh Young Choon?
Did you find the proof that Cha Kyung Hee hid him away?
Not yet.
But at least I know who we should ask.
Lawyer Ko here.
Lawyer Ko?
He's being a lot of help.
He brings us information from the prosecution...
and leaks ours to them.
There are countless prosecutors who wish to join our law firm.
The only person the careful Cha Kyung Hee...
would trust with such errands...
is her secretary.
He goes on a business trip every month using a government vehicle.
I see.
Is he very loyal?
He's been working for her for years since her days in the assembly.
He's one of her closest confidants.
So it won't be easy to make him talk.
But we should still give it a try.
- We should get hold of him... - That's my job.
I'm already on it.
Then...
I'll try and make him talk.
What's your plan?
Chief Kang, you have a lot of money, don't you?
What?
Money is an extremely powerful motive, isn't it?
You woke up?
Judge Kim Ga On?
What do you think you're doing?
I want a word with you.
About the man in his 50s that you track down every month...
and keep the minister updated on.
What are you talking about?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
His name is Doh Young Choon. He was involved in a pyramid scheme.
My parents committed suicide after being conned by him.
What does any of that have to do with me?
I didn't expect you to have a conscience anyway.
This is pure gold manufactured in Switzerland.
Each bar is worth 500,000 dollars.
So 1.5 million dollars in total.
I said, 1.5 million dollars.
Is that enough to buy your loyalty...
to Cha Kyung Hee?
No?
Two million dollars.
You're wasting your time.
This can't make me betray the minister.
Make that 2.5 million.
You think I serve her for money?
She'll be leading this country.
You're going to regret this.
Whatever you do,
you can't change my faith.
You're still at it?
Judge Kang Yo Han?
You don't know how to make use of tools.
Listen. We have 2.5 million dollars here.
Will you talk?
What do you take me for?
All right.
Two million. How about now?
- Hold on. - 1.5 million.
I'm a busy man.
Hold on. Give me just a second.
I need to think...
One million.
I can't...
Wait!
I'll talk.
I'll tell you everything.
I didn't know it'd be so simple.
It hurts more to lose what you already have.
(Seobu-ro 1901, Danwon-gu, Ansan)
Doh Young Choon is hiding out in a place like this?
Don't have high expectations.
We're just here to check things out.
Once we're done preparing and figuring out what to do,
let's come back.
Right. Over there.
Honey.
Oh, my. Honey.
- It's braised spicy chicken. - Goodness. It looks good.
Honey. You should eat a lot today.
You need to eat a lot of protein as you get older.
I eat well.
You should eat up.
I'm sure you're exhausted from working in the fields.
My gosh. Are you guys a newlywed couple? I just got chills.
Hey. I've made a lot of mistakes and hurt your mom.
- What about me? - The same goes for you too.
Here. Eat all of this.
- My gosh. - Eat up.
Go ahead.
This was seasoned well.
My gosh. This is good. There's a bug over there.
My gosh!
Did I scare you?
My gosh. Does that still scare you?
Gosh, that's good.
Kim Ga On.
Don't be hasty.
That man is the perfect bait to catch Cha Kyung Hee.
Is it because it's not your business?
All that matters to you is the hunt that you planned.
Do you know how I feel right now?
This isn't just about you.
Cha Kyung Hee framed and ruined...
tons of innocent people just to get to where she is right now.
The father of the guy who has been helping me...
was framed by Cha Kyung Hee for accepting bribes...
and being a sexual offender,
and he ended up committing suicide.
Furthermore, how do you intend to face your friend...
if you get blood on your hands?
Execute Doh Young Choon!
- Execute him! - Execute him!
(Emergency Transfer)
I've made a lot of mistakes and hurt your mom.
Don't do it.
Don't ruin your life over a crook like him.
He's not worth it, Ga On.
Ga On.
Soo Hyun.
What brings you here at lunch during the week?
Why are you dressed like this?
I took the day off.
Why?
Because I missed you.
Have you lost your mind?
What possessed you to do something so sweet?
- This is good. - This is good.
- What flavor is yours? - Banana.
Gosh, this is nice.
I wish every day were like today.
- Soo Hyun. - Yes?
If... If by chance...
I did something bad, how would you feel?
Something bad?
Here? Suddenly?
No, not something like that.
Something really bad.
A crime.
My gosh.
Why are you asking me? I would arrest you on the spot.
How could a judge commit a crime?
Do you think I'd sit and watch that happen?
Right?
Of course, you'd do that. That's who you are.
Why are you asking me that all of a sudden?
Is something wrong?
Nothing is wrong. I just wanted to say something weird...
to you.
Did you ride your bike drunk?
Why are you being like this?
Who are you?
Are you atoning?
Who says you can pretend to be atoning?
Don't you know how many people died because of you?
Are you one of the victims?
I've committed a terrible sin.
I'm so sorry.
Give me a break. Did you think I'd fall for it?
I know exactly who you are.
Where did you hide all that money to put on a show like this?
No. It's not like that.
Most of it was seized,
and whatever I had left...
was taken from me by Minister Cha Kyung Hee.
I don't have anything left.
Even if I want to atone for what I did,
I have no means of repaying the victims.
I'm just waiting for the day I die.
Thank you for coming. Please...
Please kill me.
Okay. You deserve to die.
I'll make your wish come true.
Die.
Die!
Honey!
Who are you? What are you doing?
What are you doing? Honey!
Die!
Please let him go. Please.
- Dad! - Don't kill him.
Please don't do this.
- Please let him go. - Please don't do this.
- Please don't kill him. - Please stop.
Who are you? Why are you doing this?
Kill me instead!
- Please don't hurt him. - Please.
Honey. Are you okay?
Dad.
- Let him go. - Don't hurt my dad.
Please don't kill my husband.
Honey. Don't hurt him, please.
Honey.
Who said you're atoned for?
Why won't you even let me get revenge? Why not?
I'm so sorry.
You have no right to be human.
You should be a devil.
You should've stayed evil!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Let go. Let go of me!
Let go!
- What are you doing? - Come outside.
Honey. No, honey!
Honey! Darling!
Honey!
Quit the stupid act.
My money. What happened to my money?
My money! Where is it?
My money! Where's my money?
My money.
Are you looking for this?
My money. It's mine!
Hold onto him.
My money!
My money! That's mine!
Don't do it.
Don't do it. It's my money!
My money. Don't touch it.
No, you punk.
Chief.
- Stop it! There are people inside! - Chief!
- There are people inside! - Stop it!
- Let us out! - No!
Chief!
Save us!
Dad!
There are people inside.
- Kang Yo Han! - Don't do it!
Save us!
Stop it!
Don't do it.
I'm only trying to give him an opportunity.
- Don't do it. - Save them.
- Don't do it. - Don't do it!
No!
- Save us! - No!
No! Don't.
Don't do it.
No. Not my money.
It's my money!
Honey! Get us out of here!
Don't do this.
Save us! Help!
Let me go. Let go!
Calm down and look at him.
My money!
My money.
No! It's mine!
It's my money!
My money!
This is mine!
It's my money!
Help us, please!
Let us out!
What is this? It's all fake!
Darn you!
It's not my money.
It's not mine!
- I must save them! - Relax.
Relax and watch.
Honey.
- Save us! Let us out! - Come with me.
This is... What happened is...
So... This is...
I thought that...
He lied to his family too.
That he'd lost all the money.
Seo Jin.
Seo Jin. Daddy didn't have a choice.
I honestly had to...
Honey, I'll explain everything. I'll...
Darn you!
Don't go! Stay!
Don't go!
Don't go.
Honey.
Here. Get your revenge if you want.
Don't hesitate.
Don't hurt me.
I'm sorry. Let me live.
I'm sorry for what I did. All this isn't...
My money...
Please don't kill me.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have done what I did.
I'm really sorry.
My money!
He's our only bait to get Cha Kyung Hee.
Let's not waste him.
My money!
Darn it!
But where is the real money?
It's right where he buried it.
You pranked him?
I told you.
Humans lose their minds when they think...
they lost what they had.
Have just one spoonful, Mom.
Have just a little more.
(To the victims of Doh Young Choon's scam)
(The Devil Judge)
It would be more fun to topple it all at once.
How dare they put a patriotic young man on trial?
Why did you pick a troublesome case?
Please cooperate.
Why should I care about that?
If you fail to heed the warning,
you must be blown up.
Monsters aren't made.
The monster within is just awoken.
What is this "revolution fund"?
My gosh.
You should've done better.
This plan failed.