Does that feel okay?
Yeah, it feels amazing.
I don't think you
understand how much I love Jules.
How about we hit the hay?
What are you... What are you...?
This may be the greatest
thing that has ever happened to me.
It's also the first time
it's happened to me.
Are you sure this feels okay?
Yeah, it's amazing.
The only problem is,
I took so many Narcos,
I literally can't
feel a fuckin' thing.
Is there anything you want me to,
like, do differently?
Nah, nah. It's amazing.
Rue, you keep saying that.
I know, 'cause this is amazing.
I've been doing it for, like,
25 straight minutes.
Yeah, and it's amazing.
Wait, did I already
say it was amazing?
I'm so fuckin' high.
Don't tell anyone, but she might as well
be going down on my ankle.
Are you, like, close to cumming?
I think so.
Please, God... don't ever let
Jules find out what I'm about to do.
Oh, I'm cumming!
- Rue?
- Yeah?
Did you just fake an orgasm?
What?
No, no. Are you crazy?
That was amazing.
I feel like Rue is too lazy a person
to fake an orgasm.
I'm telling you, Elly,
there's no way she
makes the sounds
I heard when she actually orgasms.
Like what... sounds?
It was like...
it was like...
"I'm cummiiing!"
Okay, yeah, yeah.
- It's awful.
- Yeah.
No, it's bad.
Maybe she's just
not attracted to me.
Or maybe you suck at eating pussy.
That could be it.
Oh, God, that's embarrassing.
No. It's cool.
You're new to the game.
Yeah, but it makes
me feel like a guy.
- Why?
- 'Cause guys don't know how to eat pussy.
Oh, my god. You want
me to show you, bro?
- Bitch, I swear to god.
- All right, so check it out.
- Pretend this is your pussy, right?
- What are you... Oh.
Uh-huh, there's that.
And also...
Wow.
See? Just like that.
Here, try me.
- Try mine.
- You sure?
Yeah. No, it's my hand,
not my pussy. It's okay.
Go ahead. Do your thing.
Just like I taught you.
Yeah, but then point your tongue.
See? And that's how
you make me cum.
And you taste good.
Rue's outside.
I'm just gonna tuck my
dick in my waistband,
and...
You don't know how
much power you have.
I'm not a good person.
I don't like what we're doing.
You seem very much at home here.
Would you like a tour?
I feel like you ruined me forever.
Why does it sound romantic
when you say it like that?
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Why did you love me?
- I still love you.
- But why?
'Cause you're smart and cruel...
but not really.
- Not really smart?
- Not really cruel.
It's funny you say that,
because it's something that
I didn't really realize
until after we broke up.
Did you know that I loved you?
I'm not talking about
obsession or fighting or fucking.
I'm talking about love.
Did you feel loved by me?
I don't know.
But you knew
I had feelings for Maddy.
But I didn't know you were
gonna get back together with her.
How many times do I have to tell you
that we're not back together?
Right, you just hung out
and talked about love.
Oh, Jesus fuckin' Christ.
If I would've known you
were gonna get back together,
- I wouldn't have done this.
- That's a lie!
It's not a lie.
You have this image of yourself
as so fuckin' sweet
and innocent...
but it's bullshit.
If you were a
fuckin' sweet person,
you wouldn't have fucked
your best friend's boyfriend.
You two were broken up.
That is a comfort
to nobody but you.
I can't do this.
What, you wanna go tell Maddy?
- Maybe I will.
- You're afraid that I still love Maddy,
so you're gonna do
whatever the fuck it takes to destroy that.
This isn't about being a
fuckin' good person, Cassie,
or being a fuckin' good friend.
This is about you
getting what you want.
You can fuckin' leave,
or you can get into bed. It's up to you.
You know what you
don't realize, Nate?
Is I don't care what
happens to me.
I don't care how angry Maddy gets.
You two shouldn't be together.
You're toxic.
- How would you know?
- Because she's my best friend,
and I'm in a
relationship with you.
She's not good for you,
you're not good for her,
and I will do everything
I can to prevent it.
Maddy, that's
literally fucking insane.
- Madd-- Cassie, I s--
- See?!
- This is what I'm talking about!
- I said "Maddy" because we're
talking about how
fucking crazy Maddy is,
- which you can't seem to fuckin' comprehend.
- No, what you don't understand,
Nate, is I am crazier!
That's not somethin'
to be fuckin' proud of, Cassie!
No... but it is something
you should be scared of.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
You can't fucking blackmail me
into a relationship with you.
Blackmail means
you don't have choices.
But in reality,
you do have choices.
You just have to own up to
the consequences of them!
That is the literal fucking
definition of blackmail!
- If you don't do this, I'm gonna do that...
- Fine, it's blackmail!
I don't care!
It doesn't change anything!
- It's fucked up!
- You know what's fucked up, Nate?
You telling me that you love me,
and then going and being in a
relationship with my best friend!
What the fuck?!
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
Okay.
Bye.
For fuckin'... C--
Cassie, stop.
I love you.
Did you lose weight?
Do I look different?
- Do I look different?
- I was just wondering.
- Then why would you ask?
- I was just curious.
- Why are you so judgmental?
I wasn't judging you.
You sit on your bed all day
just waiting to criticize me.
That's not true.
Did you lose weight?
Are you depressed?
- Why haven't you cleaned your room?
- Do you ever think about Dad?
- What happened with McKay?
- Where were you last night?
Just shut the
fuck up, Grace!
Shut the fuck up, Lexi!
Fine, I'll stop caring.
You're making me
feel like I'm going crazy.
Like I'm... actually fucking crazy.
Okay, well, thank you. Next.
Any of you snitches
to your parents about this,
your days at the Howard House
are finito burrito.
Never that...
To my beautiful girls.
What, what?
- Where's Mom?
- Asleep.
Not a care in the world.
I would like to make a toast.
To Nathaniel.
The winner of all winners...
the king of all kings,
the big swingin' dick,
Mr. Big Balls, huh?
You are a part of me
I will never understand.
But I take full responsibility.
I think I'm gonna go for a drive.
Fuckin' A.
Wear a seatbelt.
"Okay, Dad."
I gotta go to the bathroom.
I think she has a crush on you.
Should we all just fuck?
I also... have to use the restroom.
That was not 10 seconds.
- Is that a dare?
- Maybe.
We should make her jealous.
- Start the clock.
- Okay... One, two, oh, three,
four, five, six, wow,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
Yep, thank you. Wow, cool.
- That was amazing.
- O-kay, Rue.
Yeah. Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you, are you jealous?
No, no. I don't get jealous.
- Hey, Elliot.
- Yeah.
- Truth or dare?
- Dare.
I dare you to lick from here...
to here.
Wow, your girlfriend is sexy.
Jealous, Rue?
Now, that... was fucking amazing.
You know, I think if
you guys are gonna keep up
with these lesbian power games...
we should steal some liquor.
Oh, I fuckin' love this song.
Whoo, bitches!
C'mon, let's dance.
What's wrong?
C'mon... c'mon.
Do you think Nate's
still coming over?
Yeah, that's
what Maddy says.
What's wrong?
I, like... can't fucking stand Ethan.
- I was wondering.
- I don't know. He's, like, sweet,
and, like, something good
finally happens,
and I'm, like,
a million times more miserable.
Well, there's a difference between
what you think you should want,
and what you actually want.
- How do I know what I want?
- You don't.
Then, what's the whole world
always talkin' about?
People are retarded.
No, seriously, people
are fucking retarded.
Maddy, I don't think
you can say that word.
This shit is hard and confusing.
The last thing you
need is to feel worse
because you're not feeling
something you're supposed to feel.
You do what feels good to you.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
You know what would feel good?
- What?
- Dancing with me on my birthday.
- Okay.
- Come on.
All right, I'm gonna
distract the clerk,
you're gonna steal the beer...
- and you do nothing. Cool?
- Word.
- All right, break.
- Cool.
Oh, my god! Kramer!
Comedian, okay, thank you.
Didn't you get
canceled for saying, like,
the N-word a bunch of times?
- You know what, man?
- Now you work at
- a convenience store?
- What's up, bro?
Twitter is fucked up.
I've always said that.
And they're always
takin' shit too far.
- You know what I mean? What're you gonna do?
- Hey!
Hey.
Kramer, Kramer!
- How much is all this anyway?
- Fuckin' motherfucker!
Motherfuckers!
Get out of my store!
Don't come back!
- Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
- Go, Elliot, let's go!
Go, go, go! Oh, my--
- Oh, my god! Go!
- Oh, my god! Jesus Christ!
Rue!
- Hi.
- Is Maddy here?
Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, baby!
You know, you can't drink on that shit.
It's fuckin' dangerous.
- It's fine.
- Oh, my god.
How are you feeling?
I feel fine.
Do I not look fine?
Come on, motherfucker!
Fuck you, pal!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god!
Yo, could you put
the fuckin' drink down?
- Are you fuckin' drinking?
- Yeah.
- It's just one drink.
- I don't care. Why are you drinking?
I'm not even
into alcohol like that.
- Then why are you drinking it?
- You know, f--
- Elliot, just take me the fuck home, please.
- Wait...
- Rue...
- Nah, I just... I wanna go home.
No, Rue, I'm, I'm just saying,
like, don't drink.
No, I wanna go home.
- Why? Why?
- Just drop me off.
- Drop me off, please.
- Why?
Because I can't fuckin' stand you.
What?
Yeah, I don't wanna fuckin'...
I don't wanna
argue about this shit.
I don't wanna fight.
I'm sick of fuckin' fighting.
I just would rather be home.
You did good, big fella.
Hey, I'm gonna head out,
but happy birthday.
- Why? Don't go.
- Well, I just thought I'd give you guys
- a little bit of girl time.
- That's so sweet.
Nah, you should stay.
Wow, that was certainly a choice.
What are you doing, Cassie?
Waiting for the hot tub to get hot.
Whiskey.
Hey, can I have a cigarette?
Thank you.
Can I borrow your light?
I'm Cal.
I haven't been here in 25 years.
Hi.
I thought I lost you.
She always like this?
No, but when she drinks,
it's just tragic.
Just, just drop me off.
Can you just, just pull,
just pull the fuck over,
and just let me out, please.
- Right here, Rue?
- Yep.
Just fuckin' right up here.
Alright.
Fuck!
Can I take a shower?
Yeah.
Get in the hot tub with us.
I don't...
I don't, I don't
really feel like it.
It's my birthday, come on.
- This feels so good.
- I know.
Can I borrow a shirt?
Hi.
- Hi.
- Are you, are you okay?
- It's okay.
- Oh, shit.
Yeah, it's okay.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
I'm so glad you guys
are back together. Yeah!
- We're not back together.
- You're not?
No.
I mean, I was gonna say no,
but why are you saying no?
- Because we're not.
- I know,
but why do you sound
so definitive about it?
- I wasn't being definitive.
- It sounded like it.
No, I mean, she
just asked a question...
That you didn't have to answer.
- Oh, okay, yeah.
- But you did.
I don't understand
what we're arguing about.
You and your tone.
But we're not back together.
Yet.
I mean, why don't just say,
"We're working it out."
You literally just
said you were gonna say no.
- Right, but that's me.
- Meaning what?
Meaning that when I say it,
it means something totally different
- than when you say it.
- Okay.
It might seem that way in your head,
Maddy, but it's the same word.
Yeah, but it's also the speed
with which you said no.
- Gimme a fuckin' break.
- It was quick.
- It wasn't, no.
- It was like a reflex.
- It wasn't like a reflex at all.
- It was like his natural instinct, right?
- It wasn't.
- It was hasty.
- You see?
You really think she's
gonna disagree with you?
If I disagreed with her,
then I would.
Okay.
What, you don't think
I have a mind of my own?
- No, I'm sure you do.
- He's such a cunt!
What the fuck is your problem?
You see, I'm not crazy, right?
Because he's always
tryin' to gaslight me.
Look, I don't
wanna argue about this.
You see, this is why
I don't believe you
when you make
all these promises,
and you're like,
"Oh, let's get back together.
"You're the only person
in the world I care about.
"You're a goddess, and it's my fault
for not treating you like a goddess.
"I promise, Maddy.
I'll change. I'll grow.
"I'll be better.
I don't deserve you.
"But I love you.
"Please, when I go to college,
move with me.
"Marry me. Have my babies."
I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry, Maddy!
I'm sorry, Maddy.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
It's not fine.
I ruined everything, Maddy.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
- It's not fine.
- You're my best friend, and I'm sorry.
- What's going on?
Sweetie, it's okay.
Oh, god. You threw up.
- Just... get outta the tub.
- I'm so sorry,
Maddy. I didn't...
Maddy, you're my best friend.
Just get out!
- Oh, my god.
- What happened?!
Cassie threw up on all of us.
Can somebody help me, please?!
- I'm sorry, Maddy.
- Use the bathroom!
Nate, get me a fucking towel!
Maddy, I'm sorry!
Are you crying?
- You wanna wrestle?
- No.
- No, no, no. Hey.
- I'm gonna getcha.
- No, I'm good. Stop. Come on, man.
- See?
- And I'm gonna getcha. I'm gonna getcha.
- No, I'm good. I'm good.
What the fuck?!
All right, man. That's enough.
- What, you wanna wrestle, too?
- Come on, man.
- Put your shirt back on.
- I was state champion, man.
- Hey, Mr. Clean!
- Come on!
Oh, Jesus,
you three wanna wrestle?
- You think you can take me?
- Your dance, cowboy.
- Out!
You think you can take me?
Let's do this.
Let's do this, big boy.
Oh, shit.
Yes! Now, it's a party!
Fuckin' out of here.
What?
I was just havin' fun, man.
No, man. I warned you,
like, 10 fuckin' times
not to wrestle anybody.
You didn't fuckin' listen.
You're never stepping
foot in here again.
Hey, hey...
You can't do that to me, man!
Hey, hey! You can't
fuckin' kick me out, man!
You can't do this to me, man!
Hey!
I haven't been here in, like, 20 years!
I have good memories here, man.
You can't tell me
I can't come back in!
Fuck. Okay, all right.
All right.
Okay.
Fuck off!
Juliet, please, please!
You're next! We're in danger!
Please, listen to me!
Something terrible!
- This movie is so real.
- Word.
Yo, who the fuck is that?
Yo!
Yo.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, man. I really gotta talk to you.
Is everything good, bro?
Nah, man.
Nelson's baby mama
showed up
asking all types of
stupid-ass questions.
Fuuuck.
Hey... are you okay?
Hold on.
- Hey, hold on.
- I don't want to talk about it.
I... really have to
tell you somethin'.
Okay...
I lied to you.
Rue's not sober.
She hasn't been since I met her.
She's been doing everything
from heroin to fentanyl to benzos.
And I know that because
I've been doing it with her.
And I'm so sorry.
I just didn't wanna
keep lyin' to you.
I'm sorry I let you down.
Why?
'Cause I'm not a good person.
That's not true.
Yeah, but you don't
really know me anymore.
Yes... I do.
I'm always with you.
I miss you so much.
I just miss you so much, Dad.
What are you doing?
Are you peeing?
Okay, Cal, what is wrong with you?
I think I'm lonely.
- What?
- I think I'm lonely.
Okay, look, could you
please put your penis away?
- No.
- Cal, I'm not gonna ask you again.
- Put your penis away.
- I am who I am.
Oh, fuck.
- Mom, what's goin' on?
- Okay.
- Cal, put your dick away.
- Yo, Dad,
- what the fuck are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
I was just...
I was just telling your mother
that I think I'm very lonely.
Okay, but, like, can you
put your fucking dick away?
Okay, Cal, Cal, this is not funny.
What's goin' on?
Dad's standing in the
foyer with his dick out.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I don't know.
You know what you
three assholes are lookin' at?
The man with no name.
What, what the fuck
are you even saying?
Yo, what the fuck
is going on, guys?
I'm a rogue.
I march to the beat
of my own drum.
You guys should've
seen me tonight.
I don't know if you
would've been proud, but...
ya might've been impressed.
Cal, listen to me.
I think you need to see a doctor.
All right? You're not you.
No, Marsha.
That's where you're wrong.
- I am 100% me.
- Okay, you're scaring me now.
You know why? 'Cause I'm a man.
I'm an animal.
I'm a motherfuckin' Rottweiler.
You know how many
men I've fucked?
- What?!
- Cal, stop it.
- Aaron...
- Cal, please. Please stop.
Do you know how
many men I've fucked?
Dad, why are you saying this?
- Guess.
- I don't understand.
Like, what the fuck
is going on?
I had sex with a man
for the first time...
when you... were in your mama's belly.
Dad, why the fuck
are you saying these things?
Like, have you lost
your fucking mind?
You're talking about fucking men
in front of Mom when I was, what?
Like, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
Who the fuck are you?
Here's the funny thing...
if I said tonight that...
I went to the strip club,
and I...
Picked up a real
grade-A piece of ass...
huge tits, shaved pussy...
and I fucked the shit
outta her in my truck...
you wouldn't be one-tenth as
appalled as you are right now.
You wouldn't be standin' here saying,
"Dad, what are you talkin' about?"
You'd be like,
"Dad, don't say that in front of Mom."
Fuck you...
Fuck you.
You're a bunch of
fuckin' hypocrites.
I'm a man.
I'll fuck whoever I want,
whenever I want.
I'll fuck men, I'll fuck women,
I'll fuck transsexuals,
and I'll have a mighty fine time doin' it.
I eat what I kill.
I'm goin' to bed.
I'm a faggot...
sexist, chaser, pig,
fuckin' creep, and I love it.
Living a double life?
Not my biggest regret.
You are.
But let's be honest,
we all live double lives.
Don't give me that look, Marsha.
You got that shoebox
full of love letters
that camp counselor
used to write you.
You saved them.
Flirting on Facebook...
I get it.
It feels good to know that you were
loved by somebody other than just me.
I'm not standin' here lookin' at you like,
"How could you?"
I mean, we all have secrets.
Aaron?
The porn on your fucking computer...
made my jaw drop.
Marsha, come back! You saw it.
Your mother's the
one who showed me.
Don't talk to me about secrets.
Watching eight people
cum on one person's face,
gang-bangs, fucking cum-funnels,
fuckin' pissin' in
people's asses.
Jesus fuckin' Christ, man.
I got problems,
you got problems.
You know, I was kind of uptight
when I met your mother.
She was a freak...
and a fuckin' fox.
Marsha... you were a fuckin' fox!
Nathaniel...
Your whole fuckin' life's a secret.
A mystery.
Who knows about you?
I have lived with you.
I have raised you.
I am your father.
I know nothing about you.
That's not true.
I know that you're angry.
I'm so sorry I fucked you up
with my double life.
Okay, maybe, I took mine to the extreme,
I'll admit that, but...
I have a problem.
But the reason I have a problem
is this family.
That's why.
I'm not allowed to form
an emotional connection.
And I'm an emotional guy.
You fuckers backed me into a corner.
But you know what?
I think you've set me free.
So...
this is farewell.
I left you with a little...
memory of me here
on the floor of the foyer. You...
two dickwads can draw straws
to see who cleans it up.
I'll see you assholes later.
I love you.
I've always been with you.
From before you were born...
until after you're gone.
Since before we ever existed.