[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[The show is an adapted fiction based on
stories of National Park Rangers.]
[All characters, events, regions,]
[organizations depicted in the show
are fictitious.]
[Are you still afraid of mountains?]
[If you're scared that
people die up there.]
[Save their lives.]
Before they die.
[If I'd trusted you from the start]
[could we have saved
the earlier victims, too?]
You've been saving people.
[Putting efforts more than anyone else.]
This is...
[It's Yi-gang's first love.]
[I must look for Yim Cheol-gyeong.]
[Are you crazy? He's a wanted criminal.]
[That's the opposite of
a humiliating life.]
[You got what you wanted.]
[You too.
You look better with mountains than seas.]
[I can understand why you keep
saying you want to quit.]
Let's both quit.
No, I won't quit.
[I'm going to stay with this mountain.]
A few years ago, someone died
because of a potato bomb.
Have you heard about it?
Didn't know someone died, though.
[That's why I came back.]
[To find out who that person is.]
[Someone is signaling me from
up there on the mountain.]
[If I meet that person,]
I can find out who the criminal is.
[Episode 7]
Yi-gang.
I've finished installing
the sensor camera.
Next is the praying grounds at Baektogol.
If you go past the Magpie Forest
in the 3 o'clock direction,
you'll see a shortcut.
Be careful of the leaves.
They'll be very slippery after the rain.
Don't worry!
I'm a ranger too.
I'm almost past the Magpie Forest.
When you come out of the forest,
turn right and you'll see a rocky path.
[It looks blocked, but keep following it
until you see a narrow path.]
Okay, I got...
Are you all right?
Can you hear me? Say something!
[What happened?]
[Are you hurt?]
[Are you okay? What happened?]
[Da-won?]
[Da-won!]
[Answer me.]
[Can you hear me?]
Are you all right?
Da-won.
[Lee Da-won!]
[Something happened?]
Yi-gang...
[Da-won.]
[Da-won!]
[Da-won, can't hear me?]
[Da-won, can you hear me?]
Yi-gang!
[You can hear me, right?]
[Hello?]
[Da-won, are you hurt?]
Seo Yi-gang!
[Ranger]
What's wrong? What on earth happened?
Tell me.
I saw a guy with a ranger uniform.
It was definitely a winter suit.
His hands and clothes were
covered in blood.
This is him! The ghost.
Who is he?
Why's he covered in blood?
Was it him?
Where is he? Did you leave him there?
Is he still up there?
He vanished...
Seo Yi-gang!
He vanished?
I'm telling you the truth.
I know it's hard to believe.
But it was like some kind of magic.
He vanished before my eyes.
Hello, this is Seo Yi-gang.
Is Hyun-jo
all right?
To be honest,
things aren't that great.
[Sekyung Central Hospital]
His blood pressure suddenly shot up,
and there was internal bleeding.
Actually, I haven't told you
but there've been several
occurrences like this before.
We do every test every time,
but we couldn't figure out the cause.
Every time this abnormality happens,
he gets visibly weaker.
I'm sorry to tell you, but
we must prepare for the worst.
No way.
I swear I saw him on the mountain.
But...
How could this happen?
Everything about him didn't
make sense to begin with.
Yi-gang!
[Seo Yi-gang!]
Sir!
Yi-gang's conscious!
Hyun-jo's pulse has returned.
-Call another helicopter!
-Yes, sir!
Yi-gang...
Yi-gang.
Yi-gang?
Why did they go up there
on this snowy day?
Il-hae!
Gosh.
[Jirisan National Park]
[Korea National Park Service]
[Haedong Ranger Station]
Gosh...
Il-hae!
[Haedong Ranger Station]
No pulse!
[No eye movements!]
-Bring the defibrillator.
-Okay!
[After he'd lost a close colleague
on Jirisan,]
he started to see visions
of people dying there.
He had come to the mountain
to stop those deaths.
[Grass, tree, rock...]
[I can touch what's from the mountain.]
[Yi-gang, look.]
Pretend these rocks are Bidam Cliff.
Rocks indicate the four directions...
and stick a twig in...
[But even after what happened,]
I didn't know
he'd still be on the mountain.
[Yi-gang.]
[Stop them.]
[Please.]
Do you think he's still up there?
Actually, I was scared
when I first saw him.
But then...
How should I put this...
He looked very lonely.
-Yi-gang.
[-Da-won!]
It's me.
[He heard your voice on the radio.]
-Yi-gang...
[-Da-won, are you hurt?]
[And he desperately
wanted to talk to you.]
I think
he's waited a long time for you.
[Ranger]
[No one can do this but us.]
[Someone's killing people
on the mountain.]
[We must stop that person.]
[I don't know why this has happened,]
[but if we can stop it...]
[Maybe,]
[we can go back]
[to the way things were before.]
[Mount Jirisan National Park
Get-Together Festival]
[First Prize]
[All Together...]
-Let's go!
Team Haedong and Bidam. Your theme for
Guess-the-word is endangered species.
-Are you ready?
-Yes!
Start!
-Go, team!
-Let's go!
[Large horse turd buzzard]
Pretty tough!
So, it's...
-It's big.
-It's big?
[Haedong and Bidam]
What is this?
Something out of your body...
Poop.
-Large horse turd buzzard!
-Correct!
Yes!
Quick!
Tummy!
Pregnant!
Santa Clause!
That's not it.
-Bird!
-You're almost there.
A red bird!
Pass!
Nobody could've guessed that!
[Leopard cat]
This is harder!
Sad? Crying?
Old?
Pass.
[Black Woodpecker]
You peel off something.
Peck, peck.
I'm sorry.
[Bigflower ladyslipper]
-Pass!
-Next!
One, two, three.
Trilobe monkshood!
Yes!
Something coming out again?
Chamber pot?
Chamber pot flower!
[Haedong and Bidam]
That's so strange!
Let's go!
Who's the first?
[Hit the bull's eye with backpack pump]
You'd better hurry now.
Not enough time left!
Yes!
Let's do this! Quick!
Team Bidam!
Darn it!
You don't have much time left.
[Run with the youngest on the back]
Gosh, you are heavy.
You don't have much time left!
This is insane.
-Are you good?
-Yes.
Relax!
One, two, three.
Don't get stiff.
-All right!
-Let's go!
-You can do it!
Gu-yeong messed it all up.
How could you come in last in relay race?
You try running with him on your back.
He's almost 190cm. I'm like 169...
-Hey, hey. that's enough.
-That ruined my back.
Cooperation is the whole
purpose of this excursion.
Stop arguing among teammates.
Dae-jin is right. Gu-yeong tried hard.
Oh? Are you making it obvious
you two are dating?
-No, it's not...
-There, there.
We still have the talent show.
Talent show has the highest points.
If we get a first place there, we can win.
Is your ankle okay? You fell pretty hard.
Better than ever!
What are we doing for
the talent show again?
Well...
Our boss will recite a poem.
Hey,
"If You Ever Come to Mount Jirisan"
is a great poem.
We can get bonus points
since it's about Jirisan.
-No?
-Can we?
[Sancheong]
[Baemsagol and Byuksuryeong]
[Haedong and Bidam]
We have to change it.
I agree.
♫ That's how life is ♫
♫ Everyone comes empty-handed ♫
♫ and leave a life story like novel ♫
♫ in this world ♫
♫ Don't be disappointed ♫
♫ You can't do everything well ♫
♫ You only need a better tomorrow ♫
♫ Life begins from now ♫
♫ Age is only a number ♫
♫ Heart is what matters ♫
♫ Do what your heart tells you to do ♫
♫ No more sadness ♫
♫ You only live once ♫
♫ Love is a must ♫
♫ Marriage is an option ♫
♫ You do what your heart tells you ♫
♫ No wasting tears anymore ♫
♫ I'm not afraid of love ♫
♫ Amor fati ♫
Amor fati!
That was something...
-Hyun-jo.
-Yes?
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
It's a painful victory.
You should have said it hurt.
How on earth did you
sprain your ankle from dancing?
I was really fine. It didn't hurt a bit...
We should've just gone with
the poetry recital.
-Gosh.
-No way.
Well...
He got hurt trying hard to win,
so stop bugging him.
And treat him something nice.
I've got something to take care of,
so I have to go.
Actually, Yang-sun and I
have a movie to catch.
My wife and baby are
coming to have dinner.
-Same.
-Me too.
I'll take care of him.
All right.
-Movie date?
-Yes.
You could've picked something fancy.
No. I don't deserve anything nice.
Don't be so harsh on yourself.
I got us to do it.
No.
I shouldn't have got hurt.
Wildfire prevention season
starts next week.
All the more reason to get better.
You said you saw the
wildfire closures banner, right?
[Forest]
It was too dark.
I couldn't see anything else.
I must find out where it is.
But that was all I saw.
This isn't a problem only you have.
Mountains are not like cities.
[Because there are no fire trails,
access of fire trucks is limited,]
[which means it's harder to
directly put out the fire.]
[The helicopter isn't an option at night
or in the wind either.]
So the great damage is inevitable
if a fire breaks out.
Forest fire is something
everyone must prevent.
We'll all be watching carefully,
so don't take on the burden al by yourself.
To be honest,
I was hoping it to end.
Because I hadn't seen
the visions in months.
It's supposed to be a gift
from the mountains, right?
That's how you saved
Seung-hun and Private Ahn.
And you will this time too.
Let's eat before it gets any colder.
Should we add boiled eggs
to celebrate our winning?
And gimbap too.
Sure.
[Kang Hyun-jo]
[Jirisan National Park, Ranger]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
[Haedong Ranger Station, Kang Hyun-jo]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
As you know, wildfire prevention
season starts next week.
Low humidity level warning
has already been issued,
and the wind is speeding up.
In other words,
This is when the chances
of forest fires are the highest.
You must focus on trail patrol
including restricted trails,
especially on prohibiting the use of fire.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
Bidam Team,
-help Yi-gang and Gu-yeong for a while.
-Sure.
Hyun-jo, you're on
ground duty with Yang-sun
until your ankle heals.
Be careful.
I'm your senior.
That's why I care about you.
The prevention season
doesn't start till next week.
So don't be too anxious.
-Shall we check the equipment first?
-Okay.
Are all of these wildland fire gear?
Yes.
There shouldn't be the smallest defect.
They're related to the life
and death of the rangers.
What if there's a report made
while up on the mountain?
We don't have time
to come down to get the gear.
There are fire gear cabinets installed
in places with frequent forest fires.
They have all of these in there.
-Are these fireproof tents?
-Yes.
It's the last resort for real emergencies,
but you can't guarantee
100 percent safety.
Forest fires are just that dangerous.
When a wildfire breaks out,
the temperature
of the smoke itself is 600°C,
and the core rises up to 1,200°C.
-Looks delicious, right?
-Goodness.
We need to boil a little more.
-Well done.
-Here, take this.
Take more.
-You first!
-No, go ahead.
Looks so good.
It's so good.
It's my turn now.
Go ahead.
The rice came out well.
-This one is just perfect.
-Is it?
She gave her a bad review last time.
Have these.
-It's amazing.
-Right?
This one also.
So last time...
[Forest Fire]
[Ranger]
I'll go to the administrations
to get some documents.
Please go to the office and
get the closures banner and the fliers.
Okay.
What?
-What brings you here?
-Oh, hi.
I came to get some fliers and banners.
Wait.
What's that?
What happened to your foot? This is heavy.
[Estimated amount of snow cover]
[Main station, control room speaking.]
[Attention all rangers.]
[Smoke has been detected
on a forest watch camera.]
It looks like Baektogol area.
Report if any ranger can
go check in person.
[Haedong Two, currently at
the Baektogol ridge. We'll check.]
Haedong two. A wildfire confirmed.
It looks like Baektogol,
near Dalgwi Forest.
We're 1km away. We'll mobilize first.
Bidam One, at 1.5km point.
We'll come too.
[Alert, A wildfire detected near Baektogol
on Mount Jirisan. Hikers must evacuate.]
[The trail will be closed
due to a wildfire.]
[Repeat.]
[The trail will be closed
due to a wildfire.]
[Wildfire near Baektogol.
Evacuate Immediately]
-What's that?
-Wait, is that fire smoke?
-Right there.
-Look at that grey smoke.
Just look.
A fire?
Gosh.
[Fire Equipment Cabinet]
Come with me.
-There's something we can do.
-Really?
Arrived at Dalgwi Forest!
Digging fire line now!
[Fire Line: Area where
any inflammable materials are]
[removed to prevent wildfires
from spreading.]
[Mujin 1. Flames detected
from 2km under Baeksil.]
[Creating fire lines.]
[Yiseok 2. Arrived at the northwest
side of Dalgwi Forest.]
[Jangteomok 1.]
[We'll be at the source
of the fire in 10 minutes.]
-How far did we get?
-Hey.
No crown fire yet.
[Crown fire: A wildfire that can burn
tree branches and leaves.]
[As a result, sparks and embers
may be carried by wind and spread around,]
[which is known as spotting fire.]
The wind isn't too strong yet.
We can contain it as long as
we get the fire lines set.
-Okay.
-Hey.
As you know,
we can't use mechanized equipment
because no fire trucks can get near.
[Mechanized equipment: Wildfire tool
which has advanced mobility]
[and convenience as
a compact auto-machine.]
Primarily used in forest where access of
a fire truck is limited.
We'll have to put it out by indirect ways.
Do your best with the fire lines.
We must prevent the fires from spreading
toward southeast to pine tree habitat.
[-Volunteer One.]
-This side!
Flying over Dalgwi Forest with a drone.
The head fire is at
3km northwest of the forest,
[heading toward the peak.]
I think we're lucky.
Dalgwi Forest is a climax forest,
mainly comprising oak trees.
[Oak trees have thick bark
with high moisture content]
[and aren't prone to crown fires.]
If we can only suppress the front,
we'll be able to put it out early.
There it is.
Here comes the helicopter.
Get down!
[We've controlled most of the main fires.]
If they drop water one more time,
along with the ground works,
we'll be able to contain the fire.
Are you all right?
Do I look all right?
Let's retreat to Bidam Shelter for now.
We'll rest up there until we change
shifts with the mop-up team.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
You don't think
there's a wildfire closures
banner near here, do you?
What are you talking about?
The banners aren't even up yet.
Plus, who would put up a banner
so deep in the forest?
You're right.
Get in safe.
Are you going back to the mountain?
Yes. I'll be joining the mop-up team.
How long do you have to do that for?
Are all rangers joining in?
Mop-up is just as important
as initial control.
A tiny ember buried underground
can cause a bigger fire.
We'll have to watch for at least 3 days.
That sounds tough.
-Take care.
-Thanks.
-Get well soon.
-Thank you.
Bye.
Hey, look.
I can barely lift my chopsticks.
Let me help you then.
How dare you eye the leader's cup noodles?
Fine.
-What is it?
-Illegal herb collecting.
I brought them here since it's late
and can't make it all the way down.
Please open up all your bags.
-Why?
-There's nothing.
-I'm sorry, but...
-Hello.
-There's nothing.
-Sorry, it's a procedure.
You came all the way up here?
-We don't have much.
-Please open them.
-Sorry, regulation calls.
-No way.
Sorry, sorry.
[Forest]
-I'm back, sir.
-Oh, hey.
I heard you assisted the
drone team with Sol. Great job.
Yang-sun will finish up
some work at the main station.
What should I do with these?
Well...
Check the inside,
and organize them into the storage.
Yes, sir.
[Fire]
[Forest]
[Forest Fire]
Why?
What's the matter?
The letters on the banner...
Are they always red?
Oh, It depends.
The prevention season differs per year,
so we get new ones each year.
What about the last year?
Last year? Well...
Were they green?
Possibly. Why do you ask?
Where are the banners from last year?
Do you keep them somewhere?
Why would we?
We discard them after the season.
Although,
there are people who take the banners
we leave outside to dispose of.
-Who?
-Herb collectors.
Since the banners are waterproof,
they use them as
cushion fabrics or blankets.
Okay.
-It wasn't this year's banner.
[-What?]
The one that I saw. It was last year's.
What?
-Green letters?
-Yes.
[If we know where that is,
we can find out where the fire started.]
Okay, I'll call you back.
Why aren't they picking up?
The banner in your bag...
Is that the closures banner
from last year?
Why?
Is it illegal to take what's thrown away?
Did you take one? Or were there more?
What if there were more?
Where did you put them?
The storage?
The one where we found the snakes?
Yes. I'll come down too. See you there.
I'll take a shortcut through the
pine tree forest, so it won't be too long.
[Ranger]
Hey, kids.
I'm not a bad person.
Don't you remember me? I'm a park ranger.
No?
[Trails will be temporarily closed.]
[Forest Fire]
Hey! Anyone out there?
Hello!
My phone...
[Haedong Ranger Station]
Hello?
Hey...
Where are the adults?
Mom went to the mountain.
There's no one else.
Pine tree habitat under Dalgwi Forest!
Fire detected! I repeat!
Pine tree habitat! Fire detected!
Hey, hey!
Shoot.
[Mujin one, Pine tree habitat.]
[Hurry! Crown fire's already started!]
Pine tree habitat.
If the resin catches on fire,
we can't control the flames
just by indirect suppression.
We can't even fly
helicopters in this night.
What's more dangerous is
the wind blows
from top to bottom at night.
Worst case scenario,
it could spread to the town.
-Hurry, move!
-Darn it.
Anyone there?
[Jirisan]
[The head fire is heading southwest
towards the pine tree habitat.]
[It's approaching Haedong Village.]
My children are in there!
It's dangerous.
[Why can I only see these cases?]
[They'll be there for sure.]
We'll go up.
[I think he had an accomplice.]
Seo Yi-gang, answer me!
[Someone set fire on purpose.]
[Murders disguised as accidents.]
[We've reached our limit.]
[Haedong-Bidam team.]
[Failed to find any survivor.]