=Please Don't Spoil Me=
=Episode 1=
(Qin Yu, Emperor of the Yin Empire,)
Long live the Emperor!
(inherited the throne at a young age.)
My beloved deputies, as you were.
(Although he reigns supreme,)
(enemy countries are eyeing him.)
Are there documents to memorialize?
(Empress Dowager sits behind the veil.)
Yes, your Majesty.
(Many courtiers are dissident.)
(It is a difficult situation.)
(There are dozens of concubines,)
(each attractive in her own way.)
(But Qin Yu has no interest in them,)
(and has never summoned any of them.)
(Even his servants are all eunuchs,)
(and there are very few palace maids.)
(But do not worry.)
(May my new book be popular)
(Handsome Qin isn't gender dysphoric.)
(He's just focused on and dedicated)
(to the nation's affairs,)
(maintaining peace,
protecting his people)
(and becoming a wise ruler.)
Your Majesty,
you've been approving documents all day.
Why don't you take a break?
I've asked them to prepare the bath
for you to bathe and change.
Okay.
(Qin Yu, Emperor of the Yin Empire.)
This is an aphrodisiac.
Take it.
His Majesty is busy with state affairs,
and has never experienced any intimacy.
Give him some of this aphrodisiac,
and you'll become
the first woman he sleeps with.
By then,
His Majesty will long for you,
and he'll treat you differently.
The title of "Empress"
will of course be yours to take.
(The Empress Dowager brought Yan Yi Yi
into the palace,)
(who was soon named Concubine Rong.)
(She wanted to be favored)
(and be the first women
the Emperor sleeps with,)
(so she planned to
give Qin Yu an aphrodisiac.)
Fu Ling, give me the thing.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
The Empress Dowager asked me
to bring you this pear soup.
(Author, come out!)
(Yan Yi Yi, you nasty woman!)
(Are you really using the aphrodisiac
to sleep with Qin Yu?)
(May my new book be popular)
(I just saw this story too.)
(If Qin falls for it just like that,)
(I'm going to stop reading this book!)
Don't worry, everyone.
Yan Yi Yi is just the cannon fodder.
Qin Yu saw her drugging the soup.
(The Emperor's Harem)
She'll be thrown into the Cold Palace
in the next chapter.
Her father, Yan Da Hai,
will conspire against the country
to save her.
After Qin Yu finds out,
the whole family is beheaded.
Yan Yi Yi is also given white silk,
which she'll use to hang herself
in the Cold Palace.
(Although the plot has been spoiled,)
(I feel better after hearing this.)
(Dear author,)
(I'll reward you
with ten thousand yuan.)
♪Don't be half-hearted toward me♪
Ten thousand yuan!
♪I'm the only one you should love♪
Your Highness, you're awake.
Where is this?
This is Hua Qing Pool, Your Highness.
Why did you fall asleep so suddenly?
Hua Qing Pool?
Your Highness?
I'm so focused on writing in the day
that I even dream about it at night.
I'm such a model writer
who works so hard!
Your Highness, what are you talking?
Oh, it's nothing.
Yan Yi Yi, you're really something.
How dare you dream such a dream.
If novels could be filmed like this,
it would surely cost a fortune.
Not bad.
Such luxurious atmosphere
is to be expected of a royal palace.
(Since this dream is so realistic,)
(let me take a good look.)
He's so handsome!
(Sharp brows and bright eyes,
red lips and fair skin.)
(Exactly how I imagined
a male lead to be!)
Your Highness,
His Majesty is still working.
What's going on?
(Oh, it's too bad it's just a dream.)
(But he's so handsome.)
(He has good chest muscles too.)
You've been in the palace for so long,
but you still can't behave yourself.
I'm afraid when I wake up
from this dream,
I won't be able to touch you anymore.
Don't be shy.
It's just a little touch.
I can't even touch you in my dream.
How mean.
Look!
How dare you!
♪Listen to the sound of tides♪
♪They are saying I do♪
♪The setting sun is listening
to your whispers♪
♪I have told you too many of my secrets♪
♪I am being too sweet♪
♪The whole galaxy is shining for you♪
♪The light in my hand
shines again for you♪