♪Will you be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪Will me be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪You ask me questions♪
♪I want more than
the answers to these questions♪
♪Your questions♪
=No. 1 For You=
(Hey, Zhou Shu Yi.)
(Do you know why being in
first place is so important to me?)
(I push myself forward)
(so that you can see me.)
(Could you please not push me away?)
(Could you please take me to your heart?)
=Lesson 1=
(Let's suffocate!)
(It's a good thing to have childhood sweethearts)
(growing up with you.)
(But sometimes,)
(the three of us can't do everything together.)
(For example,)
(dating.)
(My dad used to tell me:)
("If you fail, it's fine;)
(If you succeed, you're a true man.")
(Back then, he went all the way from Japan to Taiwan.)
(And with this faith, he won my mom's heart.)
(I swear to my lucky necklace,)
(as long as I win first place in the competition
of the swimming club for freshmen ,)
(I'll accomplish a feat of my life,)
(turning this friendship into love.)
(Sorry, Fang Zheng Wen.)
(I'll have a girlfriend earlier than you do.)
(Jiang Yu Xin.)
(Wait for my confession of love.)
(Let's embrace the most important day
before my graduation.)
(Swimming Club Competition for Freshmen)
Come on.
OK, switch sides.
How do you feel? Confident?
What about you?
You'll have the rookie.
Top one of our swimming team.
Champion-to-be!
Senior, your swimming cap.
Senior. Your goggles.
Come on, senior!
Thank you.
So handsome!
You're popular.
Very!
Do you have confidence?
Of course.
I don't even need to bring half of my strength
for this kind of competition.
Don't be too proud.
Come on! I'm Zhou Shu Yi.
Alright.
Just focus.
Relax.
Shi De, in the evening...
Senior Gao Shi De, you are so handsome!
Why are you...
(Why is he here?)
(Does he want to ruin my plan?)
(Cramp!)
(Shu Yi.)
(What a shame!)
(What should I do?)
(Are you OK?)
(Yes.)
(Your feet?)
(I'll get you up.)
(No.)
(Don't be nosy.)
(Go away.)
(Some people say setback)
(is the enemy in life.)
(Failure is the stone in life.)
(For me,)
(whether it's a stone or an enemy,)
(it means three words:)
(Gao Shi De!)
(From primary school to high school,)
(in all kinds of competitions,)
(Second Place)
(First Place)
(be it English or writing,)
(Go, debate or sprint,)
(I was always the runner-up)
(because of him.)
Shi De.
Seniot Shi De, take it.
It's specially bought for you. Please eat it.
You'll love it.
This is for you.
[No.1 Gao Shi De]
[No.2 Zhou Shu Yi]
(I don't like the feeling of losing.)
(But ever since he came into my life,)
(I've always been)
(under him.)
Hey.
What are you doing?
What happened?
Are you OK?
Why did you suddenly fall into the pool?
Why did you suddenly act like this?
Nothing.
Hey.
Shu Yi.
What's his problem?
He didn't even thank you for saving him.
Don't say that.
Not even a thank you.
Thank you for saving Shu Yi.
Put it on. Don't catch a cold.
It's OK.
Safety first.
Don't be sad.
Falling into the pool is nothing.
Don't cry.
Look on the bright side.
Now the whole school knows you.
You're popular.
I'm not crying!
Damn it.
Embarrassed me in front of so many people.
You fell into the pool yourself.
Damn Gao Shi De!
It's his fault.
Why didn't you tell me he would come?
I'm sorry.
I thought the new member
just had the same name as his.
But it turned out to be him.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
You've known each other for so long.
You're good friends.
I'm not his friend.
Absurd!
We were in the same school since primary school,
I didn't expect to meet him in this university.
But he transferred to
the Department of Computer Science
in his sophomore year!
I've been tolerating for long.
I'll never forgive him!
What did he say?
He said he wanted to screw Shi De.
Yeah!
I'll stand by you no matter what!
Let's show Gao Shi De what we've got.
What's the matter?
Bing Wei, is it done?
Wait a minute. Almost done.
They're coming. Come on.
Come on.
All right.
Go.
Shi De.
May I use it first.
OK.
Thank you.
Who did this?
Who is so boring?
Damn it.
Let's find another way.
OK.
Who did this?
Good shot!
Shi De.
That lay-up was a good one.
Good one! Nice capping.
Please drink this.
Free drinks.
Why waste it?
It's a bomb.
You idiot. Why do you give it to me?
It's my new clothes.
(Stupid)
Towel.
I'm in bad luck recently.
-Hi.
That's very nice.
Continue.
I want...
Do I have to play because you want to hear it?
Who do you think you are?
I mean
it's great.
Bravo.
It was you who pulled the pranks before, right?
What pranks?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
Smell like talcum powder.
Stop lying.
I've thrown...
What?
Sprinkle chili powder on his swimming trunk.
Call him and remain silent.
Use wax to remove his eyebrows.
Cut his nose hair secretly.
Put gum on his chair.
(A million pranks to be pulled on Gao Shi De)
Is that enough?
From three o'clock till now, seriously?
Yeah, I'm running out of inspiration.
Are you punishing him or us?
Let's just find some hooligans to beat him up.
Are you stupid?
You study law.
How can you come up with this crap?
They are quite good at it.
He won't find out.
Well.
Just forget it.
We're about to graduate.
Just bear with it for a while longer.
That's why I want a memorial.
Do you remember when we were in Grade Six?
You also said you wanted to do it.
But you ended up falling into
the tree hole instead.
And he saved you.
Every time when you were about to graduate,
you wanted to punish him.
And?
You suffered from your pranks.
What do you mean?
Do you think I'll lose to him?
I've come up with so many ways.
I don't mean that.
We're all adults.
Can't you just talk nicely?
Yeah.
I don't care.
I have to deal with him.
Shu Yi.
It's done?
Remember to take pictures and send them to me.
He's 21 years old already,
still so wayward.
No.
I think being like that at 21
is pretty cute.
Remember to take pictures.
Bing Wei's picture of
the prank plan is totally blurry.
I have to deal with Gao Shi De.
Fang Zheng Wen, be quick.
OK.
What's up?
So mysterious.
I have something to tell you.
Fang Zheng Wen, do you hate me?
No.
You...
don't hate me?
What are you talking about? How is it possible?
So you like me?
Didn't I say that...
Because I like you.
Before I graduate, except for my thesis,
I care about us the most.
If you don't hate me,
would you like to be with me?
But
Shu Yi and me.
The three of us...
I'm talking about you and me.
Why do you mention Shu Yi?
Shu Yi.
Why are you here?
Great!
What good news!
The three of us grew up together.
You two are a couple now.
Wonderful!
Just say yes to her.
I was worried this tomboy
wouldn't get a boyfriend.
Shu Yi, I didn't know...
I'm relieved now that you're the one.
I'd like to celebrate for you.
How about tonight?
-Shu Yi.
-Tonight,
eight o'clock.
-Shu Yi.
-I'll see you then.
Why is he in a hurry?
Is Shu Yi
OK?
What are you doing?
It's dangerous running down the stairs!
Are you OK?
Why Zheng Wen?
Why choose him instead of me?
Zheng Wen is an idiot.
Yu Xin is a fool!
Both of you are idiots!
I tried so hard.
Why do you do this to me?
You said it was a custom-made lucky necklace.
Not lucky at all!
(Next episode)
Did you know how you look just now?
Do you want them to find out
that you love Jiang Yu Xin?
Recently,
I need a page boy.
You take the job.
You have to be on-call
and obey me
until we graduate.
No way!
Wait and see.
I'll defeat you hard.
♪Only half of it will do♪
♪I don't understand why love♪
♪is always replaced by reality♪
♪I'm waiting at the place
where you left, like a fool♪
♪I never expect♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪You're getting further away from me♪
♪Yet I still treasure you in my heart♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I never want you to leave♪
♪Forgive me for never knowing♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪I will no longer be the reason♪
♪for you to be happy or sad♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I'm desperate to make you stay♪