♪Will you be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪Will me be my love?♪
♪Will you be my baby?♪
♪Let me watch over you♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪You ask me questions♪
♪I want more than
the answers to these questions♪
♪Your questions♪
=No. 1 For You=
(Lean on me.)
(If possible,)
(just look at me.)
(Let me be with you.)
(Don't be sad.)
=Lesson 2=
(Let me take you away)
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to die?
Why did you kiss me?
You weren't coming up.
None of your business!
Why do you care?
Do you like Jiang Yu Xin that much?
Seeing her with Fang Zheng Wen
makes you want to die?
How do you know I like her?
Were you stalking me?
Yes, all the time.
So that you can defeat me,
make me a runner-up
and laugh at me, right?
I knew you didn't mean well.
You see it now.
Are you satisfied?
Piss off!
You don't have to pretend to be strong
when you're sad.
I'm not sad.
I'm happy to see them together.
Very happy.
See?
Zhou Shu Yi.
Do you want to be beaten up?
Get lost!
(Some people say that unrequited love
would never fail.)
(Bullshit.)
(When the one you love is with)
(your good friend since childhood,)
(it hurts more than being dumped.)
(You'll feel the pain.)
(You would rather destroy the world.)
(It hurts so much that your world is gray)
(on a sunny day.)
(The turbulent wind precedes the mountain storm.)
(The most painful part of losing your love isn't
that the one you like left you,)
(but that you start to doubt yourself.)
(Am I not good enough?)
(Don't I deserve to be loved)
(so she chose others?)
(To get rid of the pain and save yourself from it,)
(you have to tell yourself
that she is not the one.)
(You have to force yourself to let go)
(and believe someone must like you in this world.)
(So I have to cheer up)
(and find the right person.)
Hi.
Sorry, we're going to rehearse.
Which club are you from?
You're sitting on the chair for our rehearsal.
What are you doing these days?
I didn't see you anywhere.
Shu Yi.
I have something to discuss with you.
Do you mind...
Sorry, I'm late.
I'm late.
The tutor didn't let us leave.
Come on. I'll treat you to lunch.
You two just go and enjoy your meal.
I don't want to be the third wheel.
You know Fang Zheng Wen.
I don't know if he's stupid or putting on airs,
he hasn't give me an answer yet.
But it's fine. I've waited for long anyway.
If you don't give me an answer,
think about the consequences!
(Sometimes,)
(reality could strike you hard.)
(Who does she love?)
(When did she fall for him?)
(Since when have you been loved?)
(All these are bloody cruel.)
Zhou Shu Yi.
I've finally found you.
Did you forget
we're supposed to have lunch together?
You have lunch with him?
Come on.
I have classes in the afternoon.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
When did they become so close?
No idea.
Is he up to any prank again?
Why don't you stop him?
You know him well.
He looks like he doesn't care much,
but he always keeps things to himself.
Yeah.
I wonder who will change him.
Let go!
Why do you grab me?
Will you come with me if I don't?
Did you know how you look just now?
Do you want them to find out
that you love her?
So what if they find out?
Yeah.
Then why did you hide and cry?
Even jumped into the swimming pool.
Excuse me?
Zheng Wen is an idiot.
Yu Xin is a fool!
Both of them are idiots!
I tried so hard.
Why do you do this to me?
What do you want?
Do you want to show them?
Bastard!
I could have done that just now.
What do you want?
Why do you follow me all the time?
Don't you have anything else to do?
What do I want?
Recently,
I need a page boy.
What about this?
You take the job.
You have to be on-call
and obey me.
Why should I?
Well...
Go on.
Do you think I'll be scared?
Cool.
How long?
Not forever, right?
Do you want to be in college forever?
How dare you curse me!
How long?
Until we graduate.
Will I be paroled?
Even prisoners have that.
What are your conditions for a parole?
Alright.
If you beat me once,
you'll be free.
Anything will do?
Anything.
Let's wait and see.
I'll defeat you hard.
You'll admit that you are inferior to me.
I'll send you my class schedule and the venues.
Tomorrow morning, 8 AM. Downstairs of my house!
If you're late...
I see!
Sit in the front.
I'm used to taking the MRT.
I'm used to sitting in a car.
Cool.
Are you satisfied?
It's all your fault.
You'd be late for the first class.
You don't have class until two in the afternoon.
I have your class schedule.
Got my class schedule to pull pranks on me?
Scheming boy.
Let's go.
My class is at 10 AM.
Why do we have to meet at eight, then?
For breakfast.
I have to accompany you in class.
Now breakfast as well?
Come on, we're running late.
Stay close.
OK, students, today we
are going to talk about
what information technology
can be applied to increase
the overall market liquidity.
In fact, through information digging,
we can provide customers with the most
complete, correct, direct, and
effective communication module.
First of all, we can find out
what kinds of customers
we are facing
through overall logical analysis.
We can use big data
to get people to know...
Hey.
Wake him up.
It's embarrassed if the teacher sees it.
It's OK.
No.
He's from Department of Economics and Management.
Why is he here?
And he's sitting next to you.
What does he want?
Shh!
Concentrate.
After we return the books,
let's grab something to eat.
Alright, alright.
There are two more classes in the afternoon.
I'd be free between the two classes.
Gao Shi De.
I'm so hungry.
Let's have lunch first.
Hurry.
I'm so hungry.
Hey.
How come it's your call?
What are you doing?
My feet hurts.
How long do you have to hide from her?
If you keep doing this,
they will find out.
I know.
But...
Seeing her still...
I'm sad. It's my problem.
If she knows about it,
we can't be friends anymore.
Idiot.
You're the idiot.
Why do I tell you this?
You have to face it
so you can let go.
Love is not commodity.
You can't put it back to the shelf
when  you don't like it.
Only the inexperienced people would say this.
I'm not inexperienced.
Really?
Is it Zhe Yu?
Idiot.
Huh?
Are you scolding me, Gao Shi De?
You're so smart.
You're so smart..
You sneak into the enemy's camp to spy on them.
How is it going?
Did you find any of his weak point
that helps us teach Gao Shi De a lesson?
Leave it. I'm quite busy.
Why are you with Zhou Shu Yi
all the time recently?
What happened?
Right?
Yeah.
Shi De.
What are you doing?
I don't want to eat so much meat.
I want it, too.
What?
I don't want yours.
All you know are eating and sleeping.
If you sit on our class again,
take a seat in the back.
You might doze off
and influence me and Shi De.
Even so, Shu Yi would win over you.
I'm talking to him. Why did you interrupt?
So what?
With the criteria of logical judgment,
analyze customers' preference, purchasing time,
properties of the purchased goods
to find out whether they are married
and their social status.
From that, we can tell
the related products they like.
Some people can learn even when they are asleep,
such as me.
You still lose to Shi De all the time.
Zhou Shu Yi  didn't lose.
He lost to Shi De on purpose.
It doesn't sound any better.
I did lose.
I won't deny it.
You are quite honest, though.
No empty seats?
Over there.
I'm leaving.
I'll wait for you outside.
I haven't finished yet.
Not you.
Shi De.
Stop looking at me.
You've decided not to mess with
Gao Shi De.
You two are good friends now?
No way.
I have to.
Why?
Anyway,
leave it.
Be quiet.
But
you hate him so much.
Why are you so close to him now?
Don't ask,
or you'll be scared.
That scary?
Very!
Not bad.
King of the game!
Thank you.
Nice.
This is it!
Huh?
What?
(Taipei City Shi Lin Public Market)
That's what you want to compete?
I've thought it through.
We've competed in everything,
except games.
I thought...
you asked me out for a date.
No way.
Who's going to date you?
Tell me.
In or out.
I don't believe it!
Next one.
Thank you.
What's next?
Next one is...
Zhou Shu Yi.
You have a class tomorrow morning at eight,
just go back.
Damn it!
I'm really your page boy now.
(He fell asleep.)
(Go to hell!)
(A good chance to check his cell phone.)
(Wanna play with me?)
(You are too amateur for that.)
(Why isn't it in the bag?)
(Where will it be?)
(In his pocket.)
(Why is it so hard to get?)
(Almost there.)
(Shit!)
(What are you doing?)
(Let go of me!)
(Come on, let go!)
I'm sorry.
Shu Yi.
Don't get angry.
I thought you and Gao Shi De were together.
How is that possible?
I told you!
But that day,
I saw you...
Bye.
You have to face it.
So that you can let go.
Love is not commodity.
You can't put it back to the shelf
when you don't like it.
So I thought you two...
Even if you really are,
it doesn't matter.
It's the modern age now.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
Listen.
I mean it.
Go after it if you like him.
Otherwise, he wouldn't know, right?
Take us for an example,
I am two years older than him.
But you need to tell him.
Be brave!
So I'm telling you,
I will support you.
We have something else to do,
we shall leave.
They...
are...
Are they really not a couple?
Have more meat.
Why do you make a spicy pot if you can't take it?
Cuz you like it.
How do you know that?
I know you too well.
Thank you...
for just now.
If you didn't take me away,
they'd probably know it.
That's how she's always been.
She never knows what's going on.
A bit bossy, too.
Only Zheng Wen can stand her.
They are a perfect couple.
Is the shrimp ready?
Yes.
It seems that you don't care
so much about Jiang Yu Xin now.
Agree.
Thanks.
Actually,
it's even sadder
when you don't even
have a chance to fight for your love.
It ends before
it starts.
If your beloved one likes others,
what would you do?
Me?
I will
try to separate them
and take advantage of it.
Are you kidding me?
Yes, I am.
Gao Shi De.
Would you allow your page boy
to take a leave?
Where are we going?
Aren't you going to have a class?
Slow down.
Do you want to die?
This week, take light and oil-free food only.
But if you want to die,
have more spicy hotpot.
(Next episode)
Do you like Yu Xin, too?
Will you give Yu Xin to me?
I thought you skipped classes for him
so you can
make him fall for you.
You...
You like me?
You scared me!
Follow me.
Come on!
♪Only half of it will do♪
♪I don't understand why love♪
♪is always replaced by reality♪
♪I'm waiting at the place
where you left, like a fool♪
♪I never expect♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪You're getting further away from me♪
♪Yet I still treasure you in my heart♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I never want you to leave♪
♪Forgive me for never knowing♪
♪that letting go is more painful than a breakup♪
♪I will no longer be the reason♪
♪for you to be happy or sad♪
♪I've said goodbye to you♪
♪But I'm desperate to make you stay♪