Bold
Don't you dare commit the following crimes
Let go
free at kisskh.me
Let go quickly
Let go
If you don't let go, I'll let my father cut off your head
Zihao, I'm fine
You gotta let go
Your Highness Your Highness
You see for yourself
This bowl of boat porridge you just knocked over
In order to preserve the original taste of porridge,
Specially abandoned ordinary food utensils
It was boiled for an hour in a special earthen jar
In the meantime, it needs to be stirred constantly
The kitchen's hands are stiff
It's not just this bowl of porridge
All the meals here
They all need farmers to work hard
It takes countless efforts from the cooks
But how can you spoil it like this
These are all things you should do
In addition to cooking, you cooks
What else will you do
Farmers don't eat for a day
They are unable to cultivate
There is no food in the army reserve
You will lose the battle
What if the granary of the country is empty
Take what to help the people
Without food, the country will be in turmoil
And
This is Emperor Taizu
He has warned his descendants countless times
Food is the most precious thing in the world
Then why should we despise it so much
A kitchen that makes meals
And why defy it openly
What about the ancestral precepts of Emperor Taizu
Emperor Taizu once said
Everyone should perform their duties
The world can maintain long-term stability
The handmaiden dared to ask
We are cooks
Is doing one's duty
His Royal Highness is a descendant of the royal family
Have you done your duty
At your age today
Have memorized a subset of classics and history
Be praised by his ministers
When Emperor Taizong invaded the north,
The Prince is thirteen years old
I have been able to stay in Beijing alone
But what about you
You are presumptuous
No one dares to talk to me like this
Zi Jin
The holy man has issued an order of admonition
Everyone in the world can write a book and give advice
For this reason
Handmaiden only speaks offense
Please abide by your ancestral precepts
Be kind to the kitchen and cherish the food
Don't damage the royal dignity
Big brother, bad woman bullies me
Big Brother, she abused me
You killed her for me
Let's all go down
How dangerous that was
In case Wei Wang really goes crazy
Insist on cutting off your head
Fortunately, His Royal Highness the Prince was present
Do you think that with the personality of King Wei
He will give up.
Did you just get hurt
Xiao Shi
You've been sickly all this time
Everyone indulges you
But what you did today
Big Brother is very disappointed
You are the prince of Daming, the son of Zhu family
How can you be so presumptuous
Brother won't even help me with you
If you lose your temper with your servants in the future,
Go to the wall for one day
Sit down
Xiao Shi
Possessing power should be exercised with caution
Holding a knife and axe should fear life more
A person depends on his origin alone
Can't be respected
What really determines your position in the eyes of the world
It's your words and deeds
Just now, the female official asked you
You are speechless
Why
Just because she occupies reason and righteousness
If you only know how to lose your temper and cut off people's heads
Then no one will ever really respect you
Do you understand
Keep up with her
Your Royal Highness, King Wei, you have been following the handmaiden
What is the intention?
Take down
Stop
Down
Imperial concubine empress Meng Shangshi
Mother concubine
Ayan
You did a good job
Shang Shi
Courtiers choose wise kings to serve
That female official is the same
With all due respect
People like the Imperial Concubine are not worthy of your service
When the water is clear, there is no fish
If the imperial concubine has no intention,
How to win your majesty's guilt and love
Have today's status and power
You saw it with your own eyes
What happened to the weak Zhuang Fei of the First Emperor
Doesn't that really alert you
Meng Shang Shi
Zi Jin
I hope one day you can be a shangshi
How do you look at me
Grow step by step
Until you can support the whole food bureau
Hu Shangshi has lost the favor of the queen
There is no way to match you
I would like to ask
What else do you want
What exactly do you want
In the early years of Hongwu, there were female officials
Assisting Zhonggong to educate concubines
Take charge of all matters of the palace
And formulate the standard of Daming code instrument
Can set an example for women in the world
However, since the first emperor,
Eunuchs are reused
Female officials are losing power
Six innings are in name only
I am loyal to the empress
Is to restore the old system one day
Become the first palace in Daming
You
Bother to create a good opportunity for you
I hope you can firmly grasp it
How is it
Can I trust you
In order to stay in Shangshi Bureau,
I don't have a second choice
The emperor worked hard every day
Only when eating is the most relaxed
Still eat this position
Often have unexpected effects
How did Meng Shangshi defeat Guang Luqing Jing Quan
You remember, don't you
Wait for me to become a still food
I will give you back
I will remember your words
Go ahead
Your Excellency
I told you not to send these things
The room can't fit
This invulnerable soft armor
This is the only thing in the world
The prince himself is reluctant to wear it
I brought it to you
Your Majesty wants to see you
According to the Royal Guards' interrogation
Dai Yuan admitted
Guo Guifei concealed Wei Wang's illness
This matter is of great importance
Involving Wei Wang's health
So my son had to report to my father
Guo Guifei is the biological mother of Wei Wang
Is she concerned about chaos or something else
Please also ask my father to make a clear decision
Tea
Your Majesty
Your Majesty, pardon
Father
Good
Come
One sail
What my father brought you before
Are they all used up
I don't lack anything around me
Father doesn't have to send anything into the palace anymore
You met your own father
I think my father is in trouble
Why do you say such a thing
Father doesn't blame you
That's your real father after all
I am wandering in a foreign land and dying
You found me
At that time, it was unruly
Rather die than go back
You took me in again
Over the years
My literary talent, martial arts, mental strategy
Which one didn't you teach yourself
Except for you
Who deserves to be my father
Shoot
free at kisskh.me
When I secretly took you in
At first, I just wanted to hold more chips for my second brother
Later, I taught it carefully
It is also because you are a material that can be made
After all, my two sons
A sickly man
A dull and stubborn
It's really unbearable
If they have half of yours,
My father remembers when he was thirteen years old
Will you take me hunting
Wolves raid the camp at night
You could have run away from me
But regardless of their own safety
Saved me abruptly from the wolf's mouth
I was seriously injured
Father's Grace
A sail will never be forgotten
Father
I don't know how long I can take care of you
This has been like loyalty since ancient times
Great deception is like faith
My big brother
It is the man who is a big traitor and a big evil
Ever since he ascended the throne,
On the bright side, I am taken care of in every possible way
But secretly, I have been coercing my vassal
When I get to Zhangde,
In less than two years
After all, you can't escape the end of nothing
Our father and son
I'm afraid there is no future goodbye
My father's thoughts for many years
How could my son not know
You can rest assured
One day I will fulfill your wish for you
Good son
Father believes in you
Let this dry in the shade
Yes
What is she going to do
Sister Sue
Has followed your orders
Put the milk skin in a cool place
Anything else
You go get some more clams
Bamboo shoot chicken belly and sea cucumber come over
I want to cook for your majesty
Yes
No need
The Imperial Palace in Nanjing is being repaired
The food of officials and craftsmen needs to be cooked
Guanglu Temple is about to send 200 cooks
You get ready
Let's start tomorrow
Meng Shang Shi
What did I do wrong? You want to transfer me somewhere else
The service of female officials in the imperial court is subject to demand
Go wherever you are needed
Is cooking for the nobles making food
Is cooking for ordinary craftsmen wronged you
Meng Shang Shi
You all hear me clearly
Farmers get barren land
Will work harder to cultivate
Doctors don't distinguish between rich and poor
Will treat patients equally
This is true of all industries in the world
As a kitchen
No matter what kind of people make meals, they should devote themselves to it
If you want to pick on the object
Then you don't deserve to go to the kitchen
Yes
Meng Shang Shi
My father-in-law Liu
Father-in-law Liu, why did you come in person
It's your majesty. What do you want
Miss Su
Why hasn't the milk skin your majesty needs been sent yet
Father-in-law Liu's handmaiden is already doing it
It's just
Father-in-law Liu is going to work in Nanjing soon
What can I do then?
Your Majesty's Oracle
Su Yuehua learned from famous artists with exquisite skills
I will be promoted to the steward on the same day
Specially made meals for Ganqing Palace
Thank you for your grace
Such an exceptional promotion
It's the first time in the palace
That's right. It never happened before
Father
Just now, I sent someone to meet Ayan in your palace
Why stop
I'm talking to you
My father and son said it himself
Ayan is my own brother
I want to protect him
Do you think I will hurt him
Father
The way to stand
Don't precede the words filial piety and loyalty
My son is the prince of Daming
Chu Jun of a country
In addition to the righteousness of the Ming monarch and his son,
The love of brothers should be thicker
Do your best in the order of old and young
I can't let one
A woman in a deep palace with limited vision
To educate and guide my own brothers
This will only hurt him
It's time for the emperor to eat
Why don't you sit down, too
Thank your father
Your Majesty loves tea
This snack is made like making tea
Hence the name tea soup
What you said just now is quite reasonable
What if you are free in the future
Come and spend more time with your father
Yes
Eat chicken
Good
Your Highness has not been so happy for a long time
Is there any good thing
Isn't there no memorial recently
What's going on
Your Highness
Today, there are households who transport grain
And silver cloth to the capital
In case of exploitation by receiving officials,
The so-called method of grain acceptance
Cover the amount of bribes as beauty and evil
The home of the pro-democracy movement is unbearable for exploitation
There are many people who are unable to return home
Begging for the Ministry of Industry to allocate open space to accommodate the households
However, it can't solve the long-term difficulties
It is advisable to send a supervisory empire to each member of the matter
Du Wucheng's military forces patrol from time to time
Dare to extort money from households
Ask for guilt with a play
I secretly heard that the monks and Taoists in the world between Hongwu gave excessive genealogy
Make the monk record department and the road record department make a book
Promulgate the Temple of the World
Whenever you meet monks and Taoism, you should check the book
I heard that all officials in the world can't be virtuous
Repeatedly supervised the empire
According to the inspection department, the assessment is carried out
And the company did not make a detailed investigation
Sosur meal
Are you going to prepare supper for your majesty
I really want to help
Meng Shang eats during the day
I really am
Can't
Get the jar of water I prepared
This meat needs fresh river water
Simmering so slowly all night
Pork will be crisp, rotten and delicious
Extremely delicious
Your Majesty wants to pickle pig's trotters with bad food tomorrow
Would you please go to the cellar and get the ingredients
Yes
Now I'm a steward
You mustn't fall too far behind
Your Majesty likes to eat greasy meat
But these are not good for the health of dragons
Pay more attention when you prepare meals
Yao Ziliao
I've just been promoted to the table
Why don't you say congratulations
Why are you so narrow-minded
Is to remind you
Your Majesty's constitution should be light and his diet should be light
It is not advisable to use more night food
You just ingratiate yourself
Goose gizzard palm presented
Pickled pig's trotters and milk skin
They all hurt the dragon body
Moon flower
This world is very harsh on women
Once you take the shortcut,
The world will ignore your efforts and strength
Every step you take in the future
Can't get rid of the slander of gossip
You are excellent
Just keep your feet on the ground
I can't go to Nanjing
I have unfinished wishes
I can't go to Nanjing under any circumstances
I remember
You made the last vegetarian diet, didn't you
Children
Don't do this side-of-the-road thing in the future
Concentrate on cooking
Shortly after Wang Sishan returned home,
Was found hanging himself
This is her relic
Moon flower
This is the experience of cooking in my life
It's the only thing I can leave you
I hope you will one day
Realize one's long-cherished wish
Become the best kitchen in the world
Master
Meng's and Hu's
None of them deserve to cook food
You have a spirit in heaven
Please bless me
Get one's wish at an early date
Remote clearing
Don't blame me
I'm sorry
Come
Father
Son, it's just in time
Taste delicious food with my father
It's the father
My son has a picture
I want to invite my father to enjoy it
Unfortunately, there was no chance in the past
Events in the world are also waiting after dinner
Yes
It's extremely crisp and rotten
Rare and rare
Father's pork is fat and greasy
It's better to eat less
Not in the way
What the prince said is extremely true
The so-called deficiency makes up for the cold and warms it
Warm the spleen and stomach with mutton in winter
It is timely to treat lung deficiency strain
You might as well try this mutton soup
Good
Have a taste together
Come
Yes
Eat
In the past, mutton smelled too heavy
Therefore, the chef will press it with heavy salt and taste
But this time the mutton
There is no smell of mutton at all
Why
The handmaiden specially added almonds and cooked them together
No wonder, no wonder
Your Majesty has used more meat recently
Why don't you use dandelion tea to get rid of the fire and moisten it
Your Majesty
free at kisskh.me
Scared me
Your Majesty
Father
What's wrong
Bleeding
Who bleeds
Nose nose
My nose
I
Where do people come?
Take these down
Father
Quick, quick, quick
Get these down quickly
Quickly
Quickly withdraw
Withdraw and withdraw
Your Majesty, this is overheating of lung qi
Will qi and blood go up and down
Don't move
Why did the doctor's father suddenly have symptoms
His Royal Highness the Prince
Your Majesty's tongue coating is yellow and greasy, and his nose is hot and dry
And often thirsty
They are all signs of excessive lung fire
It is the thing that clears heat and cools blood on weekdays
Father, can you hear me
Meat and greasy food hurts the dragon body
Don't eat it in the future
Newspaper
Meng Shangshi, Shangshi Bureau
Let her in
Yes
I heard that your majesty is unwell
The handmaiden was deeply frightened
Specially prepare things for clearing heat and moistening lung
After the doctor saw it,
Please take it again
Is it delicious
Sweet
Not as sweet as you
Can you use medicated diet now
Get in
Guiling ointment nourishes yin, moistens lung, clears heat and removes fire
Appropriate to Your Majesty's physique
I wanted to boil this medicated diet before
It just takes about ten hours to cook this turtle shell
I'm really afraid of delaying your majesty's illness
Or is Meng Shangshi thoughtful
It's a coincidence that the food bureau is thoughtful
Add two spoonfuls of honey
Yes
In the past, every summer
The palace always uses this thing to moisten dryness
His Royal Highness King Wei has always said that his throat is sore and hot recently
It was specially made by the Food Bureau for standby
I didn't expect it to come in handy
Father
Do you remember what you said to your son
Xuan Guo Guifei went to the temple
Yes
Zhan Ji
Stand down, everybody
Your Majesty
Bearer
What are you doing
Empress, what are you doing, empress
Empress
What are you doing, Empress
Begin
Empress, I beg you not to
Don't destroy my hand
I beg you, empress
As a kitchen
You don't cook well
Wishful thinking all day long
Read climbing the dragon and attaching phoenix
Your hands
Nature can't stay
No
Just keep me
I don't think of anything anymore
I'm not doing anything
I don't want anything
I beg you, empress
Just keep my hands
I don't want anything
Don't, don't, empress
Handmaiden daring
Please ask the imperial concubine to forgive her
Yao canon meal
Don't rely on small credit to be so presumptuous
This is not your business
Imperial concubine empress, you promised the handmaiden
If the empress of the handmaiden gang sees your majesty again
Can you promise a handmaiden a wish
The handmaiden asked the empress to forgive her
Are your wishes wasted by doing so
Empress
Susi food has the dexterest hands in the world
Doesn't the empress appreciate it too
A sample of her restored Wangchuan map
In this world except her
No one else
Can restore such a delicate picture
Get out of the way
Please keep your promise
Help the handmaiden forgive her
Go
Why do you want to be stubborn
Be stubborn
I treat you as a bosom friend
And you only value that
Yin Ziping is useless
What's so good about her
I follow Master
I want to temper my skills well
She's just like you
For a man who is not worth it at all
Do not hesitate to throw moths into the fire
Whatever I ask and what I want
It's all empty in the end
Why
With what
Moon flower
In any case
I won't even be grateful to you
I never begged you to save me
I didn't save you either
It was your hands that restored Wang Chuan Tu
Moon flower
As a kitchen
You must finally see the real chapter in the skill of cooking
I forgot to tell you
free at kisskh.me
The food list of the burning feast
I have tried it from beginning to end
What about you
How many more medical books have you memorized