[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 37]
Chief.
You finally came.
The superior had informed us to report for duty before the drill.
But the Military Command gave us a special mission
so we came here hurriedly today.
It's not too late.
Though half of the drill has been finished,
the most important part will be conducted tomorrow.
Xia Lin,
seize time to tell
the progress
to Nanzheng and other people.
You should get the hang of it as soon as possible.
Yes.
The situation of the offensive and defensive parties
has been reported to you.
Today's progress of the battle is as follow.
The Red Army
cut the collaborative power of the Blue Army.
The collaboration and supply of Qiaotou Island has been cut.
The Red Army
launched a sneak attack
and four strong attacks in total today.
But they still failed to land on the island.
Both parties suffered loss.
So they're in a standoff?
Yes.
In terms of the battle,
the Blue Army
has been focused on the intertidal zone of the battle field.
They stopped the Red Army from going forward,
but that's all.
For the Red Army,
they have obvious strength in peripheral firepower
and maneuverable power.
Moreover,
their number of troops is four times bigger than that of the Blue Army,
while their wastage ratio
is far lower than the Blue Army's,
which means that
the Blue Army
has been entirely trapped on the Qiaotou Island.
As they have lost the peripheral collaboration,
we can't see the possibility of further changes.
Who are the commanders of both parties?
The commander of the Red Army
is the acting colonel of Regiment 700,
Gu Yiye.
The commander of the Blue Army
is the chief of the Special Operations Battalion,
Gao Liang.
Who?
Gu Yiye and Gao Liang.
Are they in command of the drill or just carrying out orders?
In full command.
That's the idea of the chief of the Military Command.
By the way,
as the head of
the observation team, Chief Zheng
is also on the island now.
However,
his identity now
is Gao Liang's hostage.
Hostage?
We will save this part now.
For the scientific research team,
your main task this time
is to test and verify
how effective the upgraded equipment
of Mountain Net Number Two is in the battlefield.
You don't need to bother
with other things.
Yes.
Chief, have some water.
Our chief isn't free now.
Let's talk about it later.
Ask the logistics to send a few boxes of milk here.
Meals weren't prepared when we went into the island yesterday.
Just some dried food.
Have some water.
Qin,
My Tiger Regiment are not some incapable men.
They haven't showed their true strength.
If they show their true strength,
you would have been captured.
Right.
Nonsense.
To capture the Qiaotou Island in a day?
Are you crazy?
Stop arguing.
You're hostages now so stop arguing.
Just learn how to be a hostage.
Sleep.
Chief.
Sleep elsewhere.
Just sleep.
Don't you think
the way he lies on bed looks so weird?
Yes, it does.
It looks like an ancient tomb.
Pour it on him.
Right.
Report.
Number One,
Eaglet has called.
They have confirmed the coordinate positions
of fifteen targets on the island
including the hidden radar,
the ground-to-air missile site
and the security observation posts.
At six thirty,
the heat directors put on the targets
by Eaglet
will explode at the same time.
Well done.
The situation of the observation team.
Eaglet said
there were only a small number of observation posts on the island.
The observation team has been transferred to the underground fortifications officially.
He has kept us in this hoax
for twenty-four hours.
He has really regarded the observation team
as hostages.
But if that's the case,
he has also put himself
in a dilemma.
Report.
We've caught twenty-seven intruders.
Bring them over.
Lock them up separately.
Interrogate them severely.
Yes.
Take them away.
Stand up.
Don't move.
I'm dead.
Don't think that you can get any information from me.
Take me to the Battle Damage Battalion.
Number One.
Eaglet has missed the contact time.
What about the other person?
Report.
The chief has got into the island successfully.
If they're able to get into island successfully,
and collaborate with Eaglet
to mark
the firepower,
transportation
and supply targets on the island,
[Oriental Tiger]
it will be convenient for me to
organize firepower to destroy them.
Ask the troops
to enter the attacking positions.
Yes
[Chief Director, Red Army Director]
[Integrated Coordination]
[Map of the People's Republic of China]
Report.
The Red Army
reported that they had started attacking.
Inform the chief director
and the scientific research team of Mountain Net Number Two
Inform the observation team…
No.
the hostages
the situation of the battle in real time.
Yes.
How is it going, Wenjing?
All the groups' data are fine.
Track the information.
Start recording it.
Yes.
Cheer up, everyone.
Report.
The radar team has found that many unidentified flying objects
are approaching the reefs of the island rapidly.
How far away is the target?
380 kilometers.
8000 meters in height.
In about ten minutes
they will reach the Qiaotou Island.
According to their flying speed and posture,
they're a group of fighter jets.
Leave observation post team
and the air-defense missile team here.
All the other ground personnel
should retreat to the bunker.
We must shoot down
the fighter jets outside the island.
Yes.
Follow the predetermined plan.
Organize an electromagnetic suppression again.
Meanwhile, ask for two rounds of sudden attacks
to destroy the ground-to-air missile site
of the Qiaotou Island.
Blow it up.
Cancel the launching procedure.
Put down the launchers.
Report.
Our No. 1 missile site
has been destroyed by the enemy's long-range gunfire,
and withdrawn from the fight.
Commander Sun got shot.
The director department has called
to the confirm that the result is effective.
We must shoot down the enemy's fighter jets.
Or it'll become a nightmare.
Yes.
Jiang,
I'm going to the No. 2 missile site.
You're the supreme commander
of the Blue Army now.
Ask our troops
to defend the Qiaotou Island
at all cost.
Don't worry.
I won't leave my position.
Leader of Platoon Two,
shoot those two jets down.
Heavenly Hound discovers the target,
the guided missile.
Aiming at the target.
Aim at the target successfully.
Already aimed at the target.
Please confirm the order.
Confirm the order.
Start to attack.
[AAM SAM THREAT WARNING]
We discovered that the enemy had arranged air defense firepower.
Repeat.
The enemy have started the air defense firepower.
First-class warning.
Heavenly Hound was shot.
Ask for withdrawing from the battle field at once.
Great!
I'm sorry, Song.
I'm sorry.
I was too excited.
Do your duty and be a hostage.
Don't get excited.
Just keep watching.
[AAM SAM THREAT WARNING]
Longicorn was shot. Quit attacking.
Repeat. Longicorn is withdrawing from the fight.
Number One,
nearly all the ground targets of the Blue Army
have been eliminated.
Ask the troops
to go forward at full speed
and land on the island.
Eliminate all the combatants on the island.
Yes.
Chang Mountain, attention.
Go forward at full speed.
Get ready to land on the island.
Teng Mountain, attention.
Go forward at full speed.
-Get ready to land on the island. -Yue Mountain.
What did you say?
There are three landing ships
moving towards us at full speed.
They're six sea miles from us.
He wants to finish the battle before noon.
Inform the troops
to enter the battle field.
I'll be right back.
Roger.
Inform the troops
to enter the battle field.
Yes.
Jiang.
In the northwestern jungle,
there's an infiltrator.
They have started attacking.
Sergeant,
what should we do?
Blow up the commanding ship.
They are so stupid.
Go.
Don't move.
It seems you really love this.
You work so hard.
This is the only
freshwater pond on this island.
I promise I'll make it full of fatal substance.
Little Wangcheng.
Really? Gao.
I had painted my face like this and you still recognized me.
If I had known it, I wouldn't have disguised myself.
That's not fun.
I also promise you that
if you
dare to drop this tablet
into the water today,
from now on,
I'll hit you every time I see you.
It depends on whether you have the capability.
You still think that I'm the little Wancheng I used to be?
Brat,
you've made some progress.
All of you just try to
threaten me with the friendship between us, huh?
You're the commander of the enemy.
If I can stall you for one minute,
I can help our troops increase the possibility to win.
Don't talk nonsense.
Take him away.
Number One,
where are you?
It shows that all the data are fine.
Now no one could stop
the Red Army from landing on the island.
No.
The Blue Army will fight desperately against them.
Observation team,
The director team notifies us that
so far,
all the attacks of the Red Army have been effective.
Over.
The Special Operations Battalion
truly can't hold on for 48 hours.
The Blue Army's countermove
hasn't been reported to the Director Department.
Perhaps the Special Operations Battalion is able to reverse the situation.
I'm the captain of the Yue Mountain.
Our ship was attacked.
Deploy according to pipe damage. Deploy according to pipe damage.
All departments stick to your positions.
The head of mechanical and electrical team will check the flooding water.
Repeat.
Our ship was attacked.
Deploy according to pipe damage. Deploy according to pipe damage
The bombs exploded in four parts.
The bottom and port side of the ship are the key parts.
Mountain Net Number Two
tested the equivalent of the bombs.
The explosion
is strong enough to make the ship
sink within fifteen minutes.
The director department thinks
Yue Mountain has lost its autonomous capacity.
The Red Army's
Operational Command Post,
the First Commando,
the eight cannons
and all the other personnel and equipment on the ship
have to quit the drill.
The command post was blown up,
and quit the drill.
What?
No.
Serve the coke.
My treat.
Don't kick up a fuss.
How did they do it?
What does it mean?
It means
the head of your Regiment 700 has gone.
The Operation Azure
will be ended soon.
Everyone, pack your things at once.
Come on.
Let's go home.
The Red Army is done?
Good.
Inform the troops
to keep on holding their ground.
Before the enemy withdraws,
keep a close eye on them.
Mustn't move at all.
Yes.
Report.
We've brought them here.
Take them inside.
Yes.
How come you're here?
Haven't you been killed in the blast by me?
Shut up.
You're dead.
But…
What?
You thought my command post
was on the Yue Mountain?
Alright.
Say it.
How did you get out of the island?
I won't tell you.
Sergeant,
rest in peace.
Let me do it.
Behave yourself.
Don't touch us.
Alright.
Take them out.
Yes.
Gu Yiye,
why did you tie me up and take me here?
Let me go.
Behave yourself.
Gu Yiye!
Report the position
of our command post to the director department.
Inform the second
and the third commandos
to stop attacking,
and withdraw from the fight.
Yes.
Report.
Director Xia,
the command post of the Red Army has called.
The command post?
Which command post?
The Red Army's.
Transfer the call here.
Yes.
Say it again.
♫ The sun went down. The sunset is glowing ♫
♫ Soldiers were back from shooting range♫
♫ shooting range ♫
How come the result is like this?
We clearly have controlled the situation.
Our Regiment 700
did have chance to win.
Asked four frogmen
to take down the command post?
That's why they're called
the Special Operations Battalion.
That's what they're specialized in.
They just like to do…
Keep it down.
If I'm going to invite the chief and other leaders to a meal,
what do you think we should eat?
Out.
How could you…
…have such an attitude?
Eat instant noodles.
Let's wait for the news after we finish eating.
What news should we wait for?
The Red Army's command post hasn't been blasted.
The director department
is trying to verify the situation.
Wait. Wait..
It hasn't been blasted?
How so?
The commander of the Red Army moved their command post
from the Yue Mountain
to the
to the Teng Mountain.
The Blue Army's frogmen only
blasted the original command post
and their First Commando.
Good job.
Gu Yiye
is really something.
It means Gu Yiye
is still alive.
He isn't dead?
Then why did the director department make a false report about the military situation?
It made me
almost have a heart failure.
Chief,
[Chief Coordinator]
the director department has verified it.
It's true that the Red Army's
command post isn't on the Yue Mountain.
The director department determines that
the Blue Army's Beheading Action is not successful.
The drill goes on.
Is there any point to continue?
The director department also thought so
ten minutes ago.
After the Red Army lost this chance to attack,
it would be hard for them
to launch an attack again before dark.
After it gets dark,
the Blue Army will gain the advantage instead.
But the premise is that
the Red Army's command post
has been taken down.
However, this premise doesn't exist now.
Considering about the materials
sent by the Mountain Net Number Two
about the combat logic of
the Red Army's commander,
the director department has estimated that
within the five hours
and forty-four minutes before dark,
there might be a miracle.
What miracle?
Mountain Net Number Two analyzed that
the commander of the Red Army
has a meticulous logic about combat,
and is good at planning every step carefully.
During
the 997 Action in 1999,
and the Guang 20 Drill in 2000,
he once used irregular approaches
and got victory.
Mountain Net Number Two thinks that
this time
he may also do this.
If that's the case,
the situation
may be reserved.
What's wrong?
Is my order not clear enough?
But there are so many reefs on the east and north sides
of the Qiaotou Island.
We are not able to launch attacks at all.
If we choose to land on the island from those two places,
we'll suffer great loss.
Right.
It's true we will lose some men.
But just think about it.
If we expand one landing target
to three,
the Blue Army's limited military strength
will also be distracted.
Keep attacking them,
their weakness will surely be discovered.
Don't leave any reserve forces here.
All the troops should join the attack.
There are few firing point left on the island
for the Blue Army.
Our number is four times bigger than theirs.
Even if we should fight by the quantity of soldiers,
I would send all men to fight bloodily with them.
It's a strategy to perish together.
Right.
That's what I want.
You might ask
what will be
the cost.
Soldiers
aren't merchants.
No bargain
if it relates to sovereignty.
During the War of Resistance Against Japan,
that island
was occupied by the Japanese.
It was given back
to our country after seven years.
I ask you.
If the island were still
occupied by the Japanese now,
and the country needed us to fight
and take it back,
would you still calculate the cost?
Fight!
Even if I might die, I would take it back.
Action!
Yes.
Comrades,
the last battle
of the Operation Azure will begin soon.
In four and a half hours,
no matter how fierce the battle is,
the sun will set.
The battle
will also end.
[Bayi]
Now we're facing
an enemy whose number is several times bigger than ours.
This is their last chance.
They will also have the resolution
to win like us.
Rush to us
and fight bloodily with us.
At this time,
I want to tell you
we don't have enough military strength
to fight a war of attrition.
So
at this point,
you are chosen
as elites.
Comrades,
ready to go.
Let's
end this battle.
Yes!
It sounds so heroic.
Buddies,
we're special troops.
We always perform
the toughest
and most difficult
tasks among all the troops.
Today,
the twelve of you
have been chosen.
The purpose is to protect our country's territory
and win more time
for our army
so that our comrades
are able to prevent the enemy from landing on the island.
This time
there will be no returning for you.
The instructor and I
are saying goodbye to you here.
For this action,
we only have a few words.
We'd rather go forward and die
than step back and stay alive.
[Integrated Coordination, Blue Army Director, Chief Director, Red Army Director, Chief Coordinator]
We'd rather go forward and die
than step back and stay alive.
Go prone!
Lie down!
Report.
Number One,
the enemy's attack is very intensive.
We've repelled their attack for three times.
The second battalion has suffered heavy losses.
Two hundred and sixty-two people quit the battle,
more than half of our establishment number.
How is it going on the northeastern side?
It's a bit better there,
but there are also some losses.
The instructor and his men
are also have great pressure.
The enemy try to suppress the First Company by firepower.
They operate forcibly
and blow up the reefs.
The instructor applies for
the backup of flat fire guns.
Tell the instructor
to hang in there.
This is the enemy's plot.
Unless there is no other way,
we can't mobilize the reserve forces.
Yes.
The sun will set in an hour.
Inform the Glider Squad
to take off.
Yes!
Number One,
Twelve powered hang gliders
have been released from the island.
What's their purpose?
They're flying towards the landing team.
We're not sure about their purpose now.
Shoot them down.
Don't let them get close to the landing team.
Yes.
Stop them.
Report, Number One.
All the people of our landing ship withdraw from the fight.
He has used up
all his tricks.
Mobilized the reserve forces.
Land on the island forcibly.
Yes.
Everyone,
stick to your posts.
[Sword of the South]
Defend Qiaotou Island to the death.
Jian,
come on.
Report.
Number One.
The southwestern side has fallen.
The enemy have landed on the island successfully.
They've built a beachhead
at the depth of two hundred meters.
The instructor has also lost all his men.
They can't keep their place anymore.
Inform the commander of the Third Company
withdraw to the underground fortifications.
The First Company and the Second Company,
hang in there for another half an hour.
If they build
a supporting beachhead,
there will be more troops landing on the island.
Then
we'll be besieged.
After it gets dark,
the special troops will gain the advantage.
We are not being besieged,
but entrapping them.
It does not depend on the duration,
but the approaches.
Send my order.
Yes.
A miracle did happen.
There are thirty minutes left to end the drill.
It's impossible that the Red Army can defeat the Blue Army.
Does the Red Army have any other predetermined battle plans?
Yes.
But time isn't enough.
The Red Army's predetermined plans
can't be implemented.
Report.
The Blue Army informed us that
their instructor had given orders
to withdraw to the underground fortifications.
Tell the Blue Army that
the director department got it.,
and decides that
the order is effective.
Yes.
It's not effective.
Time's up.
The drill is over.
But
The result hasn't come out yet?
The result isn't important.
What matters is the process.
The drill will be over soon.
The rest of it
will be left to your training department to make a summary.
Inform the observation team.
End the Operation Azure
according to the plan.
Yes.
The drill is over?
Okay.
Alright.
Okay. I got it.
Could you help to
ask the superior
for a few days' off?
We've been
locked up here for over a day.
We all stink.
Assemble on Monday.
Then make a report
for the observation team.
Okay.
I'll report to chief at once.
Why?
What happened?
The directors have ended the drill.
Chief.
The drill is over.
The ship to pick up the observation team
is on the way.
It's over?
Aren't they still fighting on the ground?
They haven't got the notification yet?
[Combat Duty]
Report.
Come in.
Chief,
both the red and blue armies are still fighting with each other.
The drill shouldn't be ended.
According to the plan of the directory department,
the drill
only lasts for 48 hours.
When time's up, it must be over.
A plan is a plan.
But Mountain Net Number Two
needs the overall and complete parameters of the drill
so as to get the final result accurately.
If the drill ends halfway,
there will be a lack of necessary steps and data.
The research project can't be continued.
Your words make sense.
However,
our whole plan of the drill
has been reported to the Military Command for record.
Our troops must
carry out the Military Command's official reply unconditionally.
There mustn't be any alteration.
But chief…
Chief.
Chief Zheng of the observation team has called.
Transfer it here.
Yes.
Hello.
Have you given the order to end the drill?
I'll give it at once.
Stop it.
Don't give the order.
Why not?
He,
this is a critical moment.
Chief, what do you mean?
Think about the predetermined
plans given by both parties before the drill,
and the director department's
analysis of them.
Have you discovered two things?
Firstly,
the Red Army emphasizes stability greatly,
and is not flexible enough.
Except for the first attack
and this offensive with irregular approaches,
they barely have any other tactics.
And the Blue Army
is poorly prepared for handling the transition of attacking
and defending.
They have never changed their attitude from attacking
to defending.
This exposes the problems existing in the troops.
Secondly,
The combat practice of both parties
doesn't proceed according to
the predetermined plans provided by them.
After the start of the drill,
their logic and tactics
changed rapidly.
By now,
the drill has exceeded the old pattern.
I can understand.
At this point of the drill,
the predetermined plans no longer work.
This trend is more like a real battle.
The director department has also discovered these problems
and we are confused.
Chief, your analysis
has enlightened us.
For this circumstance,
even the director department, observation team
and the participating troops of the drill
have never experienced it before.
Superior commanders like us
have never experienced it, too.
However, the drill is getting more and more similar to a real battle.
Not only their tactics
but also their attitudes
are like those in a real battle.
This is a rare chance.
No drill we used to have
can compare with it.
It makes sense.
He, don't stop the drill.
Let them continue
until the final result comes out.
If we persist,
it will be very beneficial for our troops.
But chief,
if we let the drill continue,
it'll be dangerous.
No planning. No prearrangement.
No predetermined plan.
If we continue like this, it might lead to a mess.
It's not safe, chief.
I also thought about the same thing.
Both the commanders of the red and blue armies are young
and inexperienced.
They've never experienced
a drill like this.
Nor have we had such experience.
It's the first time for all of us.
If we continue,
it's not a possibility
but a certainty to become messy and even
have some trouble.
However, He,
the army has a different view
on safety with others.
The army thinks that
we have to make sure soldiers are able to fight in the battle field,
and can win after joining the fight.
We have to make sure they can be useful for the country.
No losing the sovereignty or any territory.
Protect our countrymen from being bullied.
From this perspective,
continuing the drill
is the safest choice.
But if we continue the drill,
there will be a series of new problems.
For example,
the purpose of the battle,
the supply for both parties,
and the ending time of the battle.
The director department must give
a reason to continue the drill.
Moreover, we need to get approval from the Military Command.
Chief,
chief, the purpose of the drill
has been determined previously.
It's to get the control power on the island.
We shouldn't change the purpose.
On the first stage of the drill,
the Red Army defeated the collaborative power of the Blue Army,
blocked their electronic communication,
and cut off their contact with the outside world.
The Blue Army is like being on an isolated island now,
being unable to get any supply.
But the Red Army's supply conditions
haven't been eliminated by the Blue Army.
Wars aren't estimated by time
but the result.
Who is talking there?
Vice director of the research group of Mountain Net Number Two,
Jiang Nanzheng.
He,
the reasons given by Lt Col Jiang are very sensible.
The director department should think about them carefully.
I suggest
to give supply to the Red Army
under limited conditions
and no supply to the Blue Army.
Continue the drill
until the result comes out.
Report to the Military Command first.
Tell them it's my idea.
Then send a report
to the Military Command in the name of our troops.
I'll call Commander Zhao later.
I know the situation here the best.
Otherwise, I would be an incompetent director
of the observation team.
Yes.
Chief,
I'll call the Military Command at once.
Meanwhile, I won't declare the closing of the drill for time being,
and will wait for the superior's reply.
All members of Special Forces
attack them fiercely.
All the Red Army retreat.
Time is nearly up.
[Blue Army Director, Chief Director, Red Army Director]
Chief, the Blue Army has launched a counter-attack.
Director Xia,
shall we inform the participating troops to end the drill?
I'm He Zhigeng.
Yes.
The drill continues.
Chief,
our drill this time has aroused the headquarters' attention.
The headquarters keep a watchful eye on it.
Number One Chief of the Military Command
has asked Vice Commander Meng
to take the combat troops of Military Command
and officers over the division level
to the site of the drill
for watching and learning.
Okay. Got it.
So the Number One Chief intervene personally?
Twenty years ago,
I saw him on the train of new recruits for the first time.
He stole Instructor Lu's uniform.
and tricked all the people successfully.
From then on,
I've been wanting to kick his ass.
For these twenty years,
we've fought with each other for many times.
In terms of victory,
I've won more times than him.
But it's not until today that I realize
I've never defeated him truly.
Number One,
the director department has asked us
to submit the supply list of personnel and equipment.
Take record.
Three rounds of firepower backup by six bombers.
Two rounds of firepower strike by four  Oriental 11.
Number One.
Well,
the Blue Army has sent
more than a team of frogmen to the periphery of the island.
Search the reefs within
ten kilometers' distance from the Qiaotou Island.
Remove all
his infiltrators.
Yes.
The drill director department has informed
to continue the drill
until the result comes out.
But the director department won't offer us any supply.
We also won't get any new soldiers if we lose some men.
Got it.
Fortunately, I've brought
all the resources I have.
Half of the ammunition is left.
But half of the equipment is gone.
All these things aren't important.
What matters is that
we've lost one third of our soldiers.
Now they say they won't add new members to us.
With no supplement of soldiers, how do I continue the fight?
Should I go up the mountains to catch some monkeys
or go to the sea to catch some tortoises?
I just catch them,
and give each of them two guns to charge forward.
Why are you guys so stingy?
You've brought no food at all.
The fight lasted for half a day yesterday.
We didn't have time to eat.
We could only rely on the biscuits,
canned food and sausages we'd brought with us.
Let me tell you what has been left.
Some rice is left as we skipped two meals yesterday.
Two bottle of oil.
And some vegetables.
Almost all of the vegetables have got rotten.
Those old guys of the director department asked me
to figure out some solutions myself.
I figure out some solutions myself?
But how?
What's more, the freshwater
has been poisoned by the Blue Army.
Luckily, the water in the spare pond
wasn't discovered by them.
But it'll be used up soon.
We're discussing.
The Red Army asks for supplement of soldiers.
Even if they don't agree,
they should give us half a day's time.
Ask our troops to take a rest
and re-construct our positions.
After half an hour,
meet with me at the observation pointon on the main peak
to make a battle plan.
Besides,
figure out a way to solve the problem of supply at once.
I'm starving.
Where are you going?
I'm going to check those old men,
to make sure they're still fine.
Chief,
if the troops have no supply,
how does the drill go on?
Despite other things,
our observation team
should get the supplements, huh?
Yes.
Right.
With disadvantageous terrain,
strange combat environment,
extremely tough conditions,
and complicated and fickle situation in the battle field,
it's easier for the troops to discover potential problems
and be tested.
I'm not talking about the troops.
I'm talking about the observation team.
We're hostages now.
The treatment is different now.
No, chief.
The hostages shouldn't starve.
If they get ill from the starvation,
it'll be meaningless to have hostages.
It's useless.
-Gao Liang. -Come on.
Gao Liang.
Well done.
You haven't been defeated by Regiment 700 for these two days.
Good.
I'll put more bet on it.
In the next 24 hours,
no,
30 hours,
if you can still hold on
for the next 30 hours,
I'll take the lead
to ask all the cadres of the Special Forces
to lift you up over the heads
and take a turn around the site of Special Troops.
No way.
Let me lift you up.
What's wrong, Song?
What do you mean?
Anything wrong?
Supplements.
There are still some food in the troops.
I've told them
to give each person two meals and three bottle
of water a day.
Salt will be enough.
Forget the shower. You won't be starved.