[English subtitles are available]
[Nothing But You]
[Episode 9]
This one is so
memorable.
This is the razor blade
that he used.
This is so precious.
I'll check it for him.
[The observation diary for Lai Zhengyi]
[Item collections of Lai Zhengyi]
[Lai Zhengyi's delicate jawline was shaved with this thing]
"Lai Zhengyi's delicate jawline
was shaved with this thing."
What are you doing?
Don't you know it's illegal to
peek at other people's stuff?
Lai Zhengyi's jawline
was shaved with this thing.
So he had a facial surgery, and he told you about that?
Nonsense!
Forget it! Forget it!
You didn't see anything.
What the hell is it?
Don't touch my stuff.
What a mess.
You're so disgusting.
You seem like a pervert.
You're the pervert!
I'm just...
What?
You're just...
infatuated with the angelic Mr. Lai.
I...
I like him.
So what?
It's none of your business.
Get out of here!
I'm not leaving.
I want to check out
what you're up to.
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Stop it!
Give it to me! Hand it over.
What are you doing?
Angelic Mr. Lai.
You know what?
She wrote something in this diary.
What is he trying to say?
It's nothing.
He made a fart.
It's just a fart.
Qin Yanfei!
From now on,
I'm done with you.
What now?
Are you still mad at me?
Let me help you water the flowers.
Don't worry.
I won't tell a word to that angelic Mr. Lai
that you were a pervert...
Shut your mouth up!
I was just joking.
Why are you so furious?
I was messing with you.
Don't get pissed.
When are you going to
tell him that you like him?
I can give you some advice.
I'm not going to do that!
Confess my feelings to him?
It's so embarrassing
for a girl to express her feelings.
What?
So you're waiting for him to take the initiative?
You're pretty good. Jiangjiang.
You know how to turn the tables.
I'm not that childish!
Why do we have to express our feelings to each other?
It is enough that we keep each other in mind.
Besides,
we are now the world's
most recognized couple.
You're so clumsy.
I'm not!
I'm now very content
and very happy.
It is enough.
You're happy for sure.
But what about me?
I was tricked by you to come here somehow,
witnessing your PDA for so many days.
I'm sick of it!
I'm going to find Bi Xiaoran.
No, you can't.
You can't go find her.
Why do you
keep stopping me?
Y-you did everything you could
to keep me from finding Bi Xiaoran.
Are you up to something?
No, I'm not.
I'm your good friend.
Because we're good friends,
I want you to be on good terms with my sister.
You know
my sister's temper so well.
She hates being interrupted
when she's working.
Think about it.
Water the flowers for me.
Aren't you here to give a hand?
Quickly, don't slack off.
There, and those.
I was so scared.
It's a nice day, I feel so energetic
to work with Mr. Lai.
[Best Love]
What is this?
Open it.
Best Love.
[Best Love]
It's so beautiful.
Is this...
for me?
There will be a dance ball tonight.
Come with me.
I understand.
Then this is my reward for going to the ball.
Am I right?
Nope.
It's beautiful.
And that's why I want to give it to you.
It's really beautiful.
But I heard couples
can't give shoes as a gift to each other.
Otherwise, the other side will run away.
These are the shackles.
You can't get away from me.
Shackles.
He said these are shackles!
No one can stand that line.
Why are you wearing high heels at night?
Are you going to be a bridesmaid?
Don't wander around in front of me.
You're so annoying.
Do I look good?
Good, good.
You're being so perfunctory.
These are my shiny
and expensive
new shoes.
So angelic Mr. Lai
gave these to you as a gift?
Yep.
Not only he gave me the shoes as a gift,
he also invited me
to be her partner for dinner.
I wear these shoes,
and I will be
the star tonight.
I will be the prettiest one.
What are you doing?
I didn't tell
that you have big feet.
Your feet must be size 40.
Are you blind?
My feet are size 36!
It must be size 40!
I could fit into it.
Take it off!
Give me the other one.
My shoe!
This...
this shoe's quality
is really bad.
I'm going to sleep.
Qin Yanfei!
Stop right there!
Compensate me!
I need a compensation!
Mr. Lai.
I'm Liu Yue,
Director Wang's disciple.
We met earlier at a dinner party.
Do you remember that?
Yes, I do.
Right.
Are you alone?
I'm waiting for someone.
Who keeps you waiting?
She's so ignorant.
Mr. Lai.
It's time to get in.
Excuse me.
Just in time.
We can get in together.
This way.
[An uninterrupted stream of ink]
-Cheers. -Cheers.
Last time we met each other was six months ago.
Mr. Lai, long time no see.
I wonder if there is any opportunity for us
to cooperate?
We will.
Our company is preparing for some new projects.
Mr. Lai.
Why are you alone today?
You didn't bring your partner?
I'm here.
How could I let Mr. Lai to be alone?
I'm good at drinking.
Do you want to try it?
Enough.
This time, it's fixed.
Try it on.
Take a few steps.
I'll trust you this time.
Help me up.
As you command.
Qin Yanfei.
Are you ready for death?
Do you want a slide coffin
or a flip coffin?
No way.
I thought I repaired it firmly.
It must be that you're fat, and you should lose your weight.
So you're blaming this on me?
You took so long
and look what you have repaired!
You've wasted my time!
[Missed calls Mr. Lai]
Oh, no!
No, I'm late.
Hurry up, fix these shoes for me.
I'm leaving now!
What are you going to do?
There's no time!
I have something to do.
Fix these shoes quickly!
What the hell is wrong with these shoes?
[Shunxing Uber]
Pick up the phone.
-Hope he's not mad at me. -Hello,
the number you dialed did not answer.
-Why didn't he pick up the phone? -Please redial it later.
Come on...
[Xiao He]
[Vienna Hotel]
Lai Zhengyi!
Sir!
Go to Vienna Hotel!
Hurry up!
Got it.
Take it slow.
Mr. Lai.
Hold on.
We're almost there.
We are at the hotel.
We're here.
Slow down.
Thank you, Miss Liu,
for sending our Mr. Lai back.
I'll take care of him now.
Assistant Xiao, you should go back and get some rest.
I'll take care of Mr. Lai.
There are a lot of reporters nearby.
It's not convenient.
Leave him to me.
Thank you.
Take care, bye-bye.
Well, I'll go inside and take a look...
Take care.
I checked my phone.
I still have two take-outs...
At least let me finish my meal.
You can leave now.
I sent you the photos.
I also drove the people away.
And you don't even allow me to eat my take-out?
So basically I'm just a tool for you.
Fine.
Xiao He?
1002.
Lili?
Why are you here?
Where's she?
Where is she?
Show yourself.
Where is she hiding?
I know you're here.
Get out and face me!
Lili.
Who are you looking for?
Playing dumb, huh?
I have the picture.
Tell me.
Were you doing
something illegal here?
I'm alone here.
You refuse to be convinced until you're faced with grim reality.
I have to find her today.
Lili.
Don't you trust me?
You didn't come tonight.
I was alone,
and they were laughing at me
that I didn't bring my partner.
I was all alone.
Then Liu Yue had the opportunity to approach me.
She made me drink a lot of wine.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I didn't stand you up on purpose.
It's because of Qin Yanfei.
He broke the shoes that you gave me.
We were repairing the shoes at home.
Then I forgot what time it was.
So in your opinions,
I'm not as important as a pair of shoes.
No, no.
Of course, you're the most important one.
That's because
you gave me the shoes.
I wanted to wear them.
But you were suspecting me.
I didn't.
I...
Don't be upset.
Okay?
Don't be angry.
Then give me a kiss,
I'll forgive you.
What?
Then...
you won't get angry,
right?
Yes.
What are you doing?
[Qin Yanfei]
Hello?
I'm telling you.
I've fixed your
goddamn high heels.
You can wear this pair of shoes to run a 400-meter obstacle course.
Don't call me to tell me
such a trivial thing again!
What?
Just now...
What happened?
Do you feel sick?
I drank too much.
My stomach hurts.
Stomachache?
Then I'll go downstairs and buy you some medicine.
It's fine.
Just put your hand on my belly to sooth my stomach pain. That'll do.
J-just warm your belly?
What else do you want to do?
Nothing!
I didn't think of anything.
Don't move.
Why is your stomach
grumbling?
Mr. Lai is in a good mood today.
Looks like something happened last night.
You think too much.
Nothing happened last night.
Really?
There's one more thing that I still don't understand.
You've done so much for her,
and you're about to get what you want.
Now you should
ride the wave of success.
I also want to go further.
But this is not the best timing.
Bi Xiaoran hasn't woken up yet.
There are a lot of things between us.
So now,
I can't make a rush.
I really don't understand
you people who are in love.
What are you thinking about?
[First meeting room]
How is the preparation of
Lemeng Night 2021?
Everything is ready.
Now it's in the rehearsal stage.
This is the most important event of Lemeng every year.
Let's keep our heads up,
and make sure we don't make any mistakes.
Understand?
Understood.
Good, I got it.
I understand.
I understand it very well.
Qingyan.
What brings you here?
I'm here to give you
this year's invitation letter of Lemeng Night.
[Lemeng Night]
Is my dress ready?
Yep.
Later today,
we'll send you the dress. You can try it on.
In this year's Lemeng Night,
I will destroy Bi Xiaoran's reputation.
I need to dress up
and give her a hard time.
[Lemeng Night]
I can't reach the zipper!
Lili, we're going to...
be late.
Help me pull this zipper, quickly.
Done.
Thank you.
Something is missing.
I forgot to wear this.
You look great.
Let's go.
Yep.
[Lemeng Night]
Look!
Are they...
It's fine.
It's all for the company anyway.
[Lemeng Night]
Dear lovely
and beloved ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Welcome to
Lemeng Night 2021.
Welcome!
How time flies.
Lemeng has been
established for seven years.
Today,
in Lemeng Night 2021,
many celebrities have gathered here.
And we're going to announce
the new best actor, actress,
best picture and so on.
Those are a series of big awards.
Then, let's wait and see
who exactly
will bring the award home?
Okay, the next award
we are going to announce
is highly anticipated.
That's right.
Next, we will welcome our award presenter.
She's won the Golden Cattle Best Actress twice.
She's Shen Zhimei.
Let's welcome her with applause.
Welcome.
Where is she?
What's going on?
What happened?
Isn't Mei the award presenter?
Why is she on the stage?
What should we do?
-Wait and see. -Sister Mei.
Mei has an emergency
and she asked me to present the award.
The award in my hand
is Lemeng's best actress of the year.
Let's see who's going to
win this award.
The best actress goes...
Bi Xiaoran!
She's not an actress.
She's not an actress at all.
Did she make a mistake?
It's this bitch again,
she's messing around.
I'm going to beat her up.
Calm down!
This is a live broadcast.
Why is it Xiaoran?
She's a producer,
not an actress.
-Right. -Exactly.
How can she receive the award?
No.
I made a mistake.
It's not Bi Xiaoran.
It is...
Jiang Lili.
Who is Jiang Lili?
Who?
It's not the point.
This is a live broadcast.
Now it's a big trouble.
Oh, my God.
Now,
let's enjoy
the wonderful performance
by Bi Xiaoran and Jiang Lili.
What does that mean?
[Emergency hall]
The one who's lying in bed.
Why are there two Bi Xiaoran?
Is that Xiaoran?
Why are there two Xiaoran?
What?
What's going on?
They look so familiar.
[Emergency hall]
That's right.
As you can see,
all this time,
Lemeng has been deceiving the public.
The person who's sitting here
is not Bi Xiaoran at all.
She's her twin sister,
Jiang Lili.
That's Xiaoran?
Sister Xiaoran has a twin sister?
Twins?
She has a younger sister?
Wait a moment.
Your lies have been exposed,
so you don't speak anymore?
Ren Qingyan.
This is the award ceremony of Lemeng,
not your filming site.
Have you thought about
the consequences
of making a scene here?
Justice naturally inhabits a man's heart.
What I said is the truth.
The truth?
Questioning my identity
based on a video clip?
Don't you think it's ridiculous?
As we all know.
Two years ago,
Bi Xiaoran was injured
on her back in an accident,
leaving a scar of ten centimeters.
Do you dare to show it
in front of everyone?
It seems like
you're ready
to bear all the consequences.
You want to play?
I'm here for you.
She has the scar.
What is going on?
[I'm coming for the gossips. My daily happiness is given by you, committee member.]
I heard that Bi Xiaoran
has a twin sister.
[I had to say the entertainment industry is so corrupted.]
And they have swapped the identity.
Is this true?
Mr. Lai, Mr. Lai.
Mr. Lai.
Have a look!
Someone seems to know that
my sister and I have switched identities.
Look at this.
This post is not on viral now.
But what if people see this?
Have a look.
The current "Bi Xiaoran" is not the real one,
it's her twin sister.
What should we do?
Don't panic.
Contact the poster first.
I've sent him
a lot of messages.
He didn't reply to me.
[Make an offer if it's true.]
Will this work?
If he doesn't reply today
I'll ask Xiao He to check tomorrow.
He replied!
[50,000 yuan]
I...
Why am I so nervous?
Don't force yourself.
You don't have to
participate this time.
Just leave it to me.
It can't be.
I can't chicken out.
I have to fight for my sister.
And fight for you.
Let me do it.
Fine.
I'm Bi Xiaoran.
I'll be Bi Xiaoran even if they beat me to death.
For the sake of safety,
I will stop
this live broadcast.
What?
Why?
You don't have to stop it.
I want it
to be a big scene.
Do you see this clear?
Is this enough for you?
You can't spread rumors.
There will be consequences
by saying this kind of thing.
She's literally making it up.
As you can see,
the person who's
lying in bed is my younger sister,
Jiang Lili.
I didn't reveal the identity of us before
in order to protect
my twin sister.
On the day of signing the contract,
I forgot to bring the important file,
so I asked my sister to
send it to me by driving a car.
I didn't expect this to happen.
I'm the one who made her suffer from it.
She's still
lying in a hospital bed.
Now you are the real Bi Xiaoran,
but you weren't before.
She had a severe car accident,
and her legs were badly damaged.
She's impossible to recover this fast.
If you're okay,
just stand up.
Didn't I make it
clear enough?
A mere verbal statement is no guarantee.
I don't buy your story.
How did this happen?
-It's har to say. -That's right.
Lady Qingyan is causing trouble deliberately,
and spreading the rumors all around.
We will get to the bottom of this.
Not let me go so easily?
I think you're feeling guilty.
I don't understand.
Why does Miss Ren have to push so hard?
You have to hit a wall
to stop your behaviors, huh?
Thank you for your concern about this car accident.
The hit-and-run driver has been arrested.
Sooner or later, we'll know
who's behind this.
There's just one thing that I don't understand.
Miss Ren,
Why do you know so much about the details
of this car accident?
She must have something to do with it.
That's right.
Exactly.
How did she know?
Excuse me.
Make way.
Police!
-The police is coming. -Police?
It's the police.
Miss Ren, please come with us.
Officer,
is there any misunderstanding?
It must be some kind of misunderstanding.
[The project progress of The Journey of the Youth]
You kept the whole thing
a secret from me!
You made up a story that Bi Xiaoran
was on a business trip in Australia.
Jiangjiang.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Really disappointed.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I was forced to do it.
Next time,
I'll be the first to tell you.
Next time?
Don't do it ever again!
Or I'll smack you!
Lili did a good job
on this matter.
Do you hear that?
My sister complimented me.
I showed my resourcefulness in an emergency.
Qin Yanfei,
you just don't see the big picture.
It's not even a good job.
This whole thing between you and her
is a ticking time bomb!
If anyone finds it out,
it's over for both of you.
It won't be.
Three days ago,
I found the sidekick of Tian Daren.
Then I knew Ren Qingyan's trick.
Besides, in the nick of time,
my sister woke up.
What does that mean?
That means I'm the God's favorite.
I'm the God's daughter.
And you,
why did you just wake up and go to the site?
And you insisted on standing up.
What if the condition gets worse?
My legs are fine.
It's just a matter of time for me to recover.
Besides, under that circumstance,
if I didn't stand up,
how could I possibly stop the rumors?
But...
Make way.
Sister.
Do you want to eat something?
Do you want to drink something?
Or do you want to do something?
You finally grow up.
I owe you a lot
for your help these days.
Thank you.
You got hurt because of me.
I should help you.
I have to help you more, naturally.
Then you should go home and get some rest.
I'll take care
of the rest.
No!
The doctor said,
if you don't follow the orders,
you'll be living on the wheelchair
for the rest of your life.
You need to rest more due to your injury.
During this period of time,
let Lili continue to do your work.
Don't worry, sister.
I'm not who I used to be.
I'm not a noob anymore.
And I won't
disgrace you anymore.
Right.
Lili is now familiar with
the company's business.
You don't have to worry about work.
Then, Ding Dong,
you should keep an eye on her during this time.
Lili still has something
to learn about.
Keep an eye on her.
Don't worry, Xiaoran.
I will.
Ren Qingyan is suspected of involvement
[Big news happened at the Lemeng Night yesterday]
in the car accident of Bi Xiaoran's twin sister.
Big news!
[Ren Qingyan must gone crazy after acting in so many shows]
[Switch identity? What a bullshit.]
[This is the classic sign of being delusional, hope she can go to the hospital ASAP]
[LMAO. She went for wool and came home shorn, Xiaoran is incredible!]
[It's a great loss for the entertainment industry that Ren Qingyan is not a script writer.]
This is called, "What goes around comes around!"
She's done.
Now the case of Ren Qingyan is closed.
Also, that third wheel, Qin Yanfei
finally left the house.
Now it's finally only him and me.
We're finally back together again!
What a great
and happy day.
We must celebrate it!