=City of Streamer=
=Episode 17=
I don't care if they laugh or sweep.
I don't see any hope
in my own life.
Didn't Mr. Yang
come with you, Miss Yu?
He went to my home days ago.
My mother intimated to him
that we'd decide the wedding day.
I saw his eyes blinking
and I knew
we are finished.
You know,
we'd been dodging his proposal
before
I could find a better man.
But now…
I guess you are
in no hurry to marry, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
But my family
is getting poorer.
You're a college graduate
and you can find a job.
Then what?
Be like you,
bowing before your boss
and getting harassed from time to time
by your young master?
You drank too much.
I'll ask them to take you home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Miss Feng.
I'm sorry. I drank too much.
I shouldn't have said that. Sorry.
Don't be angry at me, please.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
Stop drinking.
Go home, Miss Yu.
I don't want to go home.
I like here. I don't want to go.
No! No!
If you like here,
the door is open to you.
If I go home now,
I'll never come out.
What happened?
Can I help you?
My brother owes someone five thousand.
My family can never afford that.
But the creditor says...
He says
if I marry him,
he'll divorce his countryside wife
and put our marriage on paper.
But you know,
his eldest son
is at the age of Jiashang.
I don't want it.
I don't want to be a stepmother
in that family.
No.
Does Mr. Yang know this?
He does.
He declines to marry me
because of this.
In the past few years,
he helped us pay the debt.
To be honest, I…
I feel guilty about him.
But it's five thousand.
It's a huge amount
even for him.
Last time, he went to my home
and gave us 300,
then
he ran away like a refugee.
I know it.
He will never come to my door again.
In this case,
if you can't go through it,
is it possible to ask
Mrs. Rong for help?
But it's five thousand!
Aunt can help with up to hundreds.
All the Rongs' money
is in my uncle's hand.
Yeah.
Uncle.
Well,
can I ask Uncle for help?
Uncle… Uncle always
shows a poker face.
But I can feel it.
Uncle cares about me.
I said I didn't have a dancing dress
and he let me pick one in the West Hall.
Right?
You know what,
when I lodged here,
I was thinking
why this wasn't my home.
Yes,
I'm going to Uncle for help.
I'm going to him now.
Miss Yu.
You're drunk.
I advise
you don't do anything
before you sober up.
Miss Feng,
please,
could you bring my uncle here?
I can't wait till tomorrow.
Please.
Please, do me a favor.
Alright.
I'll help you.
Do not drink anymore.
Have a rest.
Your decision concerns a woman's fate.
Miss Feng,
there was a Mr. Feng looking for you.
Is that Mr. Feng
your brother?
He's my brother.
Where is he?
He's in the garden.
Thank you, Mr. Meng.
My pleasure.
Dr. Feng,
my baby still doesn't sleep well
at night.
He often wakes up and cries.
I've tried everything.
What shall I do?
Well,
he needs a blood test in the hospital.
Alright.
When will you be in the office?
I'll go for you.
I take night shift this week.
You may visit my colleagues.
They graduated from medical colleges
and are experienced doctors.
I don't want them.
I mean
you delivered my baby
and you know him better.
I'll bring my baby to you.
Shixun.
Shizhen.
Concubine Sun.
I was in the kitchen
and saw Mr. Feng looking for you.
So I showed him the way.
You know it's a huge place here.
I'm afraid he'll get lost.
I appreciate your help.
You're welcome.
You found her. I'll leave you then.
Have a good time.
- Have a good time.
- Mm.
Shixun.
The maidservants
are gossipers.
Behave yourself,
or you'll be a target.
Yes,
I got that.
Mm.
And you,
where were you?
I was looking for you around this place.
I…
A guest got drunk.
I went to help her.
You…
Shizhen,
we are guests today.
Why did you do the host's job?
Note this,
you work here.
You're not sold to the Rongs.
Okay, Shixun.
I got it.
Fine.
It's late.
I'll get back to the hospital.
I'll walk you out.
- Go.
- Okay.
Let's cooperate.
Yes, Mr. Rong.
Nice to see you, Mr. Meng.
You are…?
My name is Wang.
I run Xindong Shopping Mall in the west.
Oh.
We had dinner in Fengyinglou
last month.
You remember?
Mr. Wang.
My apology.
Nice to see you.
I didn't know you're Mr. Rong's friend.
What a surprise.
Yeah,
I've known Mr. Rong
for more than ten years.
We may spend some time together.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Have fun.
Mr. Rong.
Well,
just now I saw a girl
who seemed drunk,
and went to the saloon
with a glass of wine.
Judging from her profile,
she is your daughter.
I'm not so sure.
Maybe she's not her.
Excuse me.
Zhihui.
Are you alright?
You drank too much.
Uncle.
Don't be angry with me.
I drank too much.
A girl shouldn't drink too much.
I was a bit upset
and drank a bit more.
What makes you upset? Tell me.
Uncle,
do you know
why Xiucheng is so cruel to me?
Is it because I'm not good enough?
Xiucheng is too young
to settle down.
Alright, don't cry.
If you cry your eyes out,
your aunt will feel sad for you.
Tell me
why young men
are so unreliable?
Why can't they be as mature
and steady as you?
I've seen the world
because I'm older.
Nobody understands me.
Nobody.
Alright. Alright.
I understand you.
If anything bothers you,
just come to me,
alright?
Don't cry.
Talk to me.
Uncle, you're so sweet.
You make me
fear of nothing.
Zhihui,
Xiucheng let you down.
He doesn't deserve you.
Don't worry,
I will look after you.
Uncle,
I wish Xiucheng is as nice as you are.
You've grown up.
I wish…
I wish I'd never grow up.
I wish
I'd always rely on you.
Uncle,
have some wine.
I'm sorry, Uncle.
Qingzhi,
you're back.
Mm.
Don't go.
I'll never let you go.
I promise
I'll divorce and marry you.
Mm.
You look beautiful.
Fanglin.
Mother.
Your grandaunt is leaving.
I'm busy here.
Walk her out, please.
Yes.
Mr. Meng,
Fanglin is too young
to be a friend of someone like you.
Please stay away from her.
Since Mrs. Rong has asked,
I will
stay away from your daughter.
A man like me
has a bad name,
but
I won't go as far as
to harass a Rongs' lady.
Ah, excuse me,
may I ask about someone?
Who?
Your governess.
Where did you find her?
She?
A friend recommended her.
She's good at teaching.
Is her job teaching?
I think
Mr. Rong likes her.
Watch your language.
Mrs. Rong is angry.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Mr. Jiashang,
congratulations!
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
When did you come back to Shanghai?
Early this year.
Oh.
Ms. Chen.
Yes.
Ma'am.
Did you see Miss Feng?
No,
not when Mr. Jiashang cut the cake.
Bring Concubine Wang here.
Yes.
Go! Go!
Ma'am.
Good to see you.
Bring someone
and come with me.
Hey,
you, come here!
Jiashang,
your father wants a talk with us.
Yes.
Ms. Kang, come with me.
Ma'am.
Mr. Jiashang.
Master, you really can't wait for it.
Miss Feng's brother is here.
If he knows this,
what will…
What happened here?
How dare you! You animal!
You animal!
- Ma'am!
- She's your niece!
How dare you!
She's your niece! How dare you!
I never force a woman!
Did I ever harm you?
I brought you up and fed you!
I paid your debts!
How can you do this to me?
You slut!
Aunt!
- I paid your debts!
- Aunt!
Is this how you repay me?
You slut!
You need a man this much?
He's your uncle!
- You ungrateful soul!
- I didn't seduce Uncle!
- You traitor!
- He was drunk!
He called a name like Zhi!
I didn't seduce him!
I couldn't get rid of him!
Aunt,
I was about to bite my tongue
and kill myself.
Qingzhi?
Open your eyes and look at her.
She's your niece!
We have many guests here.
You want this to go public?
I know we have guests.
You…!
You…you!
What are you doing?
Listen, Rong Dingkun!
I will divorce you.
I can't afford this scandal!
Ma'am, calm down.
Aunt!
Aunt! It's my fault.
If I'm gone,
will you and Uncle be alright?
And I won't be a burden on my family.
I'd better die!
Let me die!
My poor girl!
Why did this happen to you?
How are you going to get married?
Mr. Rong,
Zhihui is an untouched decent girl!
What…
I didn't touch her!
Mr. Rong,
how could you say that?
If this goes public,
how will Zhihui live?
We're a small family though,
we have a decent name.
What…!
A decent name?
A girl under a decent name
doesn't get drunk in other's home.
Be reminded,
your decent name is in debt.
Leave me alone!
Let me die!
Zhihui!
Leave me alone!
Zhihui, calm down!
Out, all of you.
Close the door.
Haven't you heard me?
Out!
Let's go.
Go, go.
Mrs. Yu,
how did you know what happened here?
A gentleman came to me
and said someone was bullying Zhihui.
So I...
Mr. Meng, the latecomer?
Yes.
It was him.
It was the handsome…
Zhihui,
are you alright, Zhihui?
Uncle.
I'm afraid
Mr. Meng planned all this.
And he enjoys the plan.
Zhihui,
what did Meng Xu'an tell you?
He teased me
that I borrowed the dress and jewelry.
Uncle,
you believe I colluded with someone
to frame you?
We're clean of that!
We're not such kind of people
Mr. Rong,
you're a man.
A man doesn't
shift the blame on a woman!
Shall I
send them home now?
No way!
This is not the end.
Our Zhihui
is a clean decent girl.
You stained her name.
You have to make it up.
Stop it.
Let's go.
Zhihui!
We can't go!
Hold on.
Take this.
Take it.
Why?
Will you wear
a borrowed dress throughout your life?
Zhihui!
You're too young
to take care of the money.
Zhihui!
If there's nothing else,
I'll excuse myself.
What a shame!
What a good dog!
Mr. Meng,
you're not welcomed here.
Please leave.
Sure.
Goodbye.
You're really someone,
Zhihui.
Why?
Uncle's check makes you unhappy?
Maybe you're not clear of
what kind of person my father is.
If he knows you used him,
he'll get back at you.
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
I don't mean to make trouble.
You must have done this
out of desperation.
Since you're my cousin,
I should warn you
that you'd better leave Shanghai.
My father won't kill a woman.
He does something worse.
You're smart, Zhihui,
and you know what to do.
The driver will drive you home.
Zhihui.
May I ask a question?
Why did Ma'am think it was Miss Feng?
I don't know.
Perhaps Miss Feng brought Uncle there.
Why was it her?
Jiashang.
What are you doing here?
Get in.
It's windy out here.
Wait!
I have a word with you,
since there's nobody around.
Go ahead.
Congratulations on your engagement.
Miss Du's pretty and has a decent name.
I envy her.
We've parted for half a year or more,
from early spring to late fall.
I miss you every single day,
hoping I'll see you again.
This is not
as I imagined though,
at least we meet again.
Yes.
It's not as I imagined, either.
Jiashang,
I've never asked you.
Did you really love me
when we were in Chongqing?
I thought that
it was love,
but until now did I realize
it was not.
But Jiashang,
I didn't know until now
that I love you.
Shizhi,
please don't.
We are over.
You don't know my heart.
I promise
I won't disturb you.
We may not be lovers,
but we can be friends, can't we?
Jiashang,
you haven't changed at all.
(Shanghai Guohua Bank)
It's good to see you.
Have you heard it?
Yesterday
something happened in Rong's Residence.
What happened?
Don't you know?
What's the story?
I'm not so sure about the details.
I have my work to do.
That's it for today.
Alright.
(VIP)
Hey, Miss,
this is the VIP counter.
For regular business, queue over there.
I'm cashing a check.
Am I
coming to the right place?
Yes. Yes.
You are.
(VIP)
Are you cashing the full amount?
Yes.
All of it.
Alright.
Cash it all.
Oh, yes.
Your 10,000. Take it, please.
Hello.
Open an account
to deposit these, please.
Thank you.
Sure.
Here's your bank book.
Thank you.
It's early in the morning.
Good boy. Good boy.
Come.
What's the noise?
Good boy, don't cry.
What did you say?
Miss Yu
who's always quiet?
Yes.
I was also surprised
it was her.
The maidservants gossiped
that at first Ma'am
thought it was Miss Feng,
but it turned out to be her niece.
The reward
for what she's done!
Miss Feng?
He's not even her type.
No.
I wish I'd seen
Huang Shujun's face.
It's a scandal,
and a shame on the family name.
In no time,
the Huangs will be famous
in Shanghai.
Yes.
She slapped Miss Yu
so hard in the face.
She threw good money after bad.
Oh,
what did Master say?
Would he have another concubine?
Master was embarrassed.
He didn't say much.
He gave Miss Yu a check and let her go.
He just let her go?
He might have done it after drinking,
and doesn't want to
take the responsibility.
It's good to let her go,
or another woman will steal my thunder.
He let her go
and what was she wild for?
She embarrassed Master.
It's not Ma'am.
Master sobered up
and went to Ma'am.
Go on!
The worse, the better.
Wretch!
I noticed something's not right!
Why did she
put on Qingzhi's dress?
She got drunk on purpose
and waited for me in the small saloon.
You have a good niece!
Don't shift the blame on me.
You were obsessed with her!
What?
I was obsessed?
How ridiculous!
Ask your niece
who fell to my arms when I was drunk.
Haven't I kept a cool head,
you'd have seen something worse.
Huang Shujun,
ask your heart and tell me,
have I ever mistreated your family?
I look after
all of your relatives!
And you collude and set me up!
You're always right!
What about me?
I didn't know it was her.
If I did,
I wouldn't have brought so many people.
I wouldn't do that
to stain my own name!
It was you, I knew it!
Huang Shujun,
you kicked Qingzhi out of the house.
Wasn't it for the sake of Jiaxin,
I'd fallen out with you.
And what about now?
Are you destroying the Rongs' name?
I... I… I'm not.
I... I…
Don't say one more word!
From now on,
we two families don't know each other!
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪