Thank you, Mr. Yu
Sponsorship of our program
And participate in this program
What about the theme of our program
Is
Meet people who don't like themselves
What to cook
Close the distance
Dislike
Because I don't understand
Don't understand
Often because you don't like it
And don't want to know
This brewed bitter gourd
Seeding, pickling and cutting
Mix stuffing and brew
Let people know the bitter taste
It can also be delicious
People you don't like
There is also a lovely side
Right
We are
"What to eat next" company
That's right, that's right
Right, right, right
That's what I told you last time
Okay, that's it first. Thank you
Right
Programs attended by Mr. Yu
It's already online
Post in 30 minutes
Is the content of the draft all right
OK, thank you
Hey, hurry up
I heard that the Great Devil
I'll be back in a minute
Don't let him bump into it
We cook
Public relations, that's firing and cooking
That girl's name is Su Kelan
Do not like to work overtime
But sometimes
Everyone works overtime
She'll take her, too
That health pot comes out
Make some overtime meals for everyone
The company atmosphere is really good
Sure enough, our Yu Zong
Is a good boss
Walk young people
Before frying
Will put it in hot water first
Go through it first
After a while
Actually, it can be a little
This is my boss
Yu Hao
People who don't know him
Think he is perfect
Strong and warm
But actually
He is a true bitter gourd
Even with nutrition
But it's too bitter to eat
Yu Zong
Tomorrow at three o'clock in the afternoon
There is a program interview
Will you participate
Control it within twenty minutes
In addition
The program group feels that
The matter of using body double
Communicate with the program group
It's your job
What happened to the media manuscript
Have I ever said this kind of nonsense
Who wrote it
Guo Yu
It was last week
The one who is late every day
Why haven't you been fired yet
Yu Zonghao
Which department
I'm from the public relations department
My name is Guo Yu
What do you think of my participation
"Have a good meal with you"
This program
Our application
Mainly
Deliver fresh and semi-finished products
For people who love food
Like Yu Zong
Good image and good temperament
And love food
Love your family
The cooking is delicious
Don't you know I can't cook
What do you think I can't cook
It is also set up by people with exquisite cooking skills
Participate
"Have a good meal with you"
This program
Can I always cook
Not important
You said
Please traffic star
Endorse company products
Even if it can bring benefits
But it is short-term
It will cost millions of dollars
Yu Zong has a good image and temperament
The fan base is solid
And with the company brand is
Connect in one body
Long-term stability
But if you learn to cook for this
It takes too long
Delay the rest of the total business time
The program is just for effect
There is no need to waste time
Accurate analysis of the market
And user psychology
Provide brand benefits
Maximized public relations scheme
To the image of me and the company
Carry out marketing
It is the responsibility of your public relations department
And you
I can only say that kind of nonsense just now
Do you think you are competent
Go to the personnel department by yourself tomorrow
Yu Zonghao
Yu Zong is here
Here comes the boss
Colan tidy up
Yu Zong
Even eat
It is also considered to be a time waster
Be called the devil by the office
Probably as long as it is
People who know him well
No one will like him
Are you off duty
Why don't you go back first
The devil is back
You can't cook in front of him
We order takeout by ourselves
Don't worry
I thought Yu was always a warm man
Just came to work here
I didn't expect it to be the devil
Overtime all day
I don't even dare to eat a good meal
All right, stop it
Watch the program
Add more barrage
Hungry in the middle of the night
Mr. Yu, are you short of a girlfriend
The kind that can eat very well
When it comes to cooking, it's all close-ups
It's body double, right
Look at my Weibo
There is a comparison chart
How did this happen
Colan
What's the matter
Sure enough, if you have money, you will
You can do whatever you want
True capital comes to an end
Watch the fun and watch the fun
A boss who can't cook
I also advised others to eat well
Cooking scenes are said to be
It was done with body double
Body double is used to do programs
You can't cook at all, can you
Everything on the show is fake
Excessive
To be on the show
Just learn it yourself
Boycott
I didn't know at that time
I'm about to enter the devil's kitchen
Strive to bring bitter gourd
Make a good taste
What about after our company
Will be specially released for this
That's a good statement
Please trust us
It's all rumors
Right
When I trouble you to report,
Don't use the word body double, okay
We Yu Zong
It really doesn't use body double
Hello
Um yeah
"What to Eat" Public Relations Department
OK, thank you
Right, right, right
Yu is always really useless, body double
Yes yes yes
Specific caliber
We'll be later
Will communicate with the media
Thank you
So what you're giving
Solutions
A statement
Second control evaluation
Third, abandon body double
Learn to cook
Jing Chen
You said in the elevator this afternoon
I learn to cook
There is no cost performance
It seems that this time it is really
You can't do it without learning
Things are different now
The matter of using body double has been fermented
If not in time
Fifty minutes
Thirty-seven minutes
Eight minutes
Previous program group
Encounter an emergency
You communicate with the program group
The fastest time to get out of the plan
It's fifty minutes
You were lazy before
Or this time
It's really a special situation
Spend money on hot search
Stir-fry the topic from putting materials
Then go to the hot search
How long does it usually take
One hour
This time from the first barrage
Start a hot search on the Internet
Eight minutes
How
Discuss with the program group
It makes me ride a tiger
Forced me to learn to cook, didn't you
Yu Zong
How about we do this
It's also for the good of the company
If you
Cooperate with the program group a little
It won't be
So it's the program group
Will you be paid
Yu Zong
We have stood on the ground
Company position
Try my best to communicate
But the program group made it very clear
A food column
Use a body double
I have advised you many times
Either you abandon body double
Cook your own food
Or what
Your work
Is to communicate with the program group
Instead of setting up a bureau
To force your boss
This ability to work
None of them
Yeah
I can't go back to working overtime
It's nothing right now
But I just can't go
Bye bye
Hello
You take the baby to eat first
I can't go back today
I can't go back
You guys eat first
It's all like this
Are you still in the mood to cook
Have a good meal
To be in the mood to work hard
Stir-fry a slice of garlic
Add ginger
Stir-fry chopped green onion and small pepper
Put luncheon meat
Stir-fry tofu until golden brown
Add pepper and star anise
Pour old smoke
Soy sauce cooking wine
Add soup to boil
Simple pot
Health pot for office use
It can be finished in three minutes
Be careful of burning
Sister Kelan, I'll have a taste, too
Well, it's delicious
Sister Kelan, I want it too
I want it, too
Yao Qian
Why don't you share it with everyone
Thank you, sister Kelan
Sister Xie Kelan
There is also food here
Uh-huh
It smells good
Can you give us some
Go
We don't have enough to eat yet
There is my braised pork in the refrigerator
OK, thank you
But don't move that fish ball
That's what she did
Feed the stray cats downstairs
OK
I'll get a pair of chopsticks, too
Social animals are only available in
When eating
Will feel that you
Is alive
Sister Kelan
Don't you eat together
I can't
I went home to dinner with my mother
Sister Kelan
You're just because
I have to eat with my mother
I always don't work overtime
Why bother
I think with your ability
Be willing to work overtime
I would have been promoted and raised a long time ago
I prefer to be idle
So I can have more time
Stay with my mother
You can also have more time
Make food for everyone
Thank you, sister Kelan
For me,
Work is to survive
And life
It's with the people I love
Share three meals a day
And those in their leisure time
Warm and happy
Survival
Survival should not be squeezed out
Living space
I'm Su Kelan
A salted fish that doesn't like to work overtime
Colan
Why don't you go back first
Auntie should wait for hunger
It's so late
But here
One more than you, one less than you
How much difference can you make
Let's go
Good
Then I'll go home
Have dinner with my mother
I'll come back
Mr. Jing, they have a plan
It is said that as long as Yu Zong
Cooperate with the next program
Use one's body
The program group will cooperate
Say this time
He hurt his hand
I think
May not be persuaded
Why
What's the matter
Hot search
Don't you think
Are you going up too fast
Go up so fast
It should be designed
Designed
Are you saying
Does the devil know
I can see it all
What do you say
The Great Devil certainly doesn't like it
Others set him up
I can't stand it
I resign
Resign
Right
You think
This world
Is it all around you
My ability to work
It's less than one
Self-righteous
Blindly confident people to judge
I quit my job, too
I don't believe it
Someone will clean up for you
This shit
Yu Zong
Let you find all the people in the public relations department
Is everyone here
Here we are
Who did it
I
Today's company
This happens
You're still cooking here
The company lets you come to eat
Or let you work
For
Work better
Fill one's stomach
Cook in the company
Save going downstairs to find food
Time to wait for food
You can have more energy
Focus on work
Isn't it faster to order takeout
Immerse yourself in the take-out software
It may be difficult to decide what to eat
Waiting time is also easy to be distracted
So
I did it directly
More efficient
Yu Zong
What are the jobs below
Do you want to assign
You guys inside
Who has been in the company for the longest time
In the last program,
Who drew up the copy of eating bitter gourd
Dislike
Because I don't understand
Without understanding
Often because you don't like it
And don't want to know
Who drew it up
Name
Su Kelan
I like delicious food
Yes
Understand
"Have a good meal with you"
Not bad
Starting today
Your promotion to director
The salary is twice that of the former director
Do a lot and double the bonus
Sometimes don't put
It's too important to think about yourself
The company left you
As long as I'm here
Referral
Come to my office
Yu Zong
Is the new version planning meeting still open
Why don't you open it
Do you want to give priority to it
What do you mean
Public relations issues
More important than product issues
It's just a small broken program group as a demon
It's not worth wasting at all
My time
You tell the product team
Tell them to wait for me in the conference room
I'll be there in three minutes
Good
Sue, what was it again
Su Kelan
This is your public relations department
A plan made
Surplus
Page 5, Article 6
Turn around
I need you to go at once
Communicate with the program group
Tell them to cancel
Previous communication results with Jing Chen
They set up a bureau
Just trying to force me to learn to cook
But this is absolutely impossible
The matter of personnel transfer
Angie has
Notify the program group
You go back and look for it
They can communicate
Before nine o'clock in the evening
Give me a telegram report
Does that mean nine o'clock tonight
But it's already off duty
Are you financially free
Without financial freedom
Talking about commuting time
From now on
Your mobile phone is turned on 24 hours a day
This is to get this salary
The most basic conditions
If you can't do it
Just leave
Someone else will do it
This time, let you be right
Communication of program group
Think of it as your positive investigation
Do you remember what time I want you to call me back
Nine o'clock
Yu Zong
Can I do it tomorrow
I'll report back to you
I can't get your report before nine o'clock
Go to the personnel department by yourself tomorrow
Yu Zong
Sit down
Let's get started
Good
To open
The new version has been adjusted
The following failures
First of all, for this
User experience
The coupon problem
We set up a kind of
Coupon exclusive to new members
What happened
Nothing
How do you do
The number you dialed
Is on the phone
Please redial later
Good director
I am
Su Kelan of What to Eat next
How do you do
The number you dialed
Is on the phone
Please redial later
Guide
Don't talk at all
It's not so good, is it
Yu Hao, a bastard
Take Jingchen and all three of them out
Substitution
Change the ghost
Keren is a sponsor after all
What happened to the sponsor
One by one, you
What are you doing sitting there
Lele
Go and put that
"What to eat" materials
Change me to "love freshness"
Get it
This is to change sponsors
What about liquidated damages
They are willing to give
Just waiting for us to sign the contract
Yu Haona made trouble
What to do
Right
Make trouble with the hammer
Use a body double
All kinds of uncooperative black materials
It's all in our hands
Make a fuss about people's designs made with money
It just collapsed
You let him make trouble
You'll see
People who die like Yu Hao
How many people are there now
Waiting to see him fall
Mom
It's okay. I'm not tired
Now work hard and hard
Make more money
Only in the future
Spend more time with you
Then don't earn this overtime money now
You'll have time right away
How can it be so easy
Do you work overtime or not
I'm not in charge either
And don't work overtime
How to make money to see you
Mom
I ordered you takeout
Remember to get an injection before you eat
Got it
Okay, I gotta go
Say no overtime
When the boss talks about promotion,
Fart Dian fart Dian added
Schema
What are you talking about
Has been caught by the boss
I won't do it if I can still say it
Don't I work overtime
That's not watching people serve dishes
We usually let her add
Did she add it
Say what mother should take care of when she is sick
Mother can not work overtime if she is sick
It's not like it's going to be gone soon
Why do you still curse people's mothers
Keep your mouth clean
Yao Qian
What you're eating now
Or did people do it
Don't eat if you have the ability to break your mouth
Have no conscience
Besides
She just doesn't like it
Work overtime in the company
People in the middle of the night
Help you at home
How many things have you done
Don't remember
Speech of the Great Devil
None of you can draw it up
Or someone else did it
I don't even remember it again
Hello
Oh yeah
Who doesn't know they are best friends
And ah
Just live upstairs and downstairs
I also heard that her parents often go there
Colan eats at home
Cannibalism has a short mouth
I can't see anyone talking about her
Wan Shun
Come
Brought you fish balls
Eat it
Come
Let's go eat hot pot later
Ask your boyfriend to join you
OK, I've been wanting to eat for a long time
Let's go
This hairy belly is very delicious
Let me tell you something
And his duck intestines
Extremely fresh
Why work hard
Because I want to have
Life outside of work
The harder you work, the harder you work
The less time you have to live
Hello
I heard something happened at headquarters
Three executives were opened in a row
You have been promoted to director
Maybe it will be opened at nine o'clock
Ha ha
I'm sorry
You have so many things today
I'm still working overtime and can't make it back
Why don't you apply for a transfer back
The company doesn't let the office fall in love
In case they are found
Trouble
And Chengdu and Chongqing are so close
Every weekend
Can't I come back, too
Did you have dinner together
I want to eat together every day
Then I'll change my name to Tiantian
It's too cold
Love you every day
Hello
Express delivery, right
Send it to 3207 for me
I'll cook for you
Guide
Aren't you tired
Tired
As a person
The director of food programs
How can you feel tired of cooking
That's refreshing
Do you know
Doesn't anyone think
Hold the handle of the pot in one hand
The other hand holds a spatula
Stir-fry
There is a kind of
The feeling of reigning in the world
Jin Dao's Express Delivery
Yeah
There he is
Thank you
How do you do
Excuse me, is this director Jin Xuan
Express delivery
Female
Teachers have worked hard
I'm Su Kelan
"What to eat next?" Public relations department
A new person in charge
Here comes the express delivery for everyone
Wait a minute
You made that call just now
But there's a man on the phone
It's like this
The courier brother helped make a phone call
And borrowed this dress from me
I said
It's my friend's birthday
Wanted to surprise him
Golden Autumn Crab Fertilizer
I sent you some
Steamed stuffed bun with crab roe
His family uses crabs from Yangcheng Lake
Three crab peeling masters started by hand
One day can only be at most
Peel two hundred crabs
Steamed 50 cages of steamed buns
This is just 15 minutes
Less unfamiliar
More steamed buns turn yellow
Everybody try it
You are welcome
Jin Dao
Try it, too
I'm not eating this
I've already found a sponsor
You tell Yu Hao
Don't send someone to talk again
Guide
Or
Would you like to have a look at this first
After reading it,
If you still insist
I'll leave at once
This is the basic situation
Just follow this plan
Ensure progress
Good
Brother
Our plan is so easy
It passed
You're new here
Mr. Yu did not give a negative opinion
It means high praise
Your whole group saw the quarterly bonus
Will laugh more happily
Really
I thought Yu was always very
Mean
That's just people who are not satisfied with him
Just mean
People who are satisfied with him
It's just that the face looks mean
It's still easy to get along with
These personnel changes
It won't be bad for the company
Institutional structure
Yu Zong
Boss
That's not the public relations department
Nasukelan
Do you make it to feed the cat
Yu Zong
Xiao Guo, who you are going to quit in the morning
It is more difficult at home
His father is ill
Is the company a charity
Who told you to run around the basement
You don't know, running around the basement
Is it dangerous
What if it hurts
I'm very serious now
I'm warning you
If you run around the basement again,
Go by yourself tomorrow
There will be no delicious food tomorrow
Remember
Go ahead
You put the man's
Send me all performance and weekly reports
Good Yu Zong
Yu Zong
I'm sorry about what happened before
Could you please
Give me another chance
My father is ill in hospital
My family has to pay back the loan
I really need this job
Can you not fire me
Yu Zong
Your private affairs
What does it have to do with the company
Yu Hao
Unexpected
Yu Hao also has today
Peng Xiao
To apologize to Yu Hao, the grandson
Read it again
Good
I thought about it well
Sometimes
I am too self-centered
Where are you?
I give people around me who cooperate
Have caused a lot of trouble
What trouble
Oh, it's about body double
I hope
Can you tell the program group for me
Send an apology
This apology
I still need someone else to convey it
From understanding mistakes
To admit your mistakes
It will take a little time
In the subsequent program recording,
I must
Coordinate with the arrangement of the program group
That's wonderful
It's awesome. It's awesome
Yes
Right
You do as I say
Just do it
I gave you the content
Hurry up
You are too daring, aren't you
Forging imperial edicts
Program Group and Yu Hao
At loggerheads
I can't talk calmly at all
I'll do it this way
At least eliminate it first
The anger of the program group
Willing to talk more
But you're replacing the devil
Be soft and apologize
I'm telling you
It was really discovered
We're screwed together
Jin Dao
You also know our total
He can do this step
It's already a great deal of sincerity
Apologizing is just lip service
I don't want the show
Become his showground
This is not my original intention
But
You're nice
I'm also quite good at doing things
But
There is no need to suffer indignities in Yu Hao
All right
I'll cook for everyone
Jin Dao
Why don't I give it to everyone
Cook and eat
You
Yeah
We Yu Zong have been reflecting
Think he is interested in food
And the program group does not respect
So I want to pass through me
To communicate with the program group
I also hope that through me
To pass him on
A passion for food
Anyway, you don't have to promise anything first
Why don't you try my craft
Yu Hao
You cold-blooded bastard
Balsam pear
Bitter gourd is good. Bitter gourd is on fire
I didn't expect Jin Dao
I also like bitter gourd
My least favorite food
Is balsam pear
I don't like bitter gourd either
You don't like it either
Salted duck eggs with bitter gourd
What kind of dish is this
Can it taste good
Have you eaten
I really haven't eaten it
It's nine o'clock
Haven't called back yet
I'm sorry
The subscriber you dialed is temporarily unavailable
Su Kelan
I told you
The mobile phone needs to be turned on 24 hours a day
It means you don't care
Eating and sleeping
Or are you doing something else
It must be done immediately
Answer my phone right away
Hello, lawyer Shao
About the program group
You send a letter to Love Fresh
They probably want to go public
That's why I risked it
Compensation for the risk of default
I want to be on the show to expand my influence
I guess the hot search is so fast
They should be the ones who did it, too
You take a look at us
The contract for this show
Calculate a maximum amount
Compensation for breach of contract
To scare them
A bunch of program groups
Addition, subtraction, multiplication and division
Art students who don't understand
They also believe in blind accounts
Okay, hang up
Su Kelan
No matter where you are now
Immediately, immediately
Meet me at the program group
Don't take mine
I clipped it first
It's delicious
I thought you said you didn't like it
Do you eat balsam pear
Rob so fiercely
Did I say that
Sister Kelan
How did you do it
Teach us
I'll take yours
Many people don't like the taste of bitterness
So go to the bitterness
Be meticulous
Removing pulp, pickling and blanching water
Crush and stir-fry salted egg yolk
Bitter gourd
Bitter gourd wrapped in salted egg yolk
Can neutralize the bitter taste
But it can be preserved
The effect of dispelling fire
Some ingredients even if you don't like them
But as long as it's good to eat it
Then spend some time
You can conjure up surprises
Are you saying
Yu Hao is bitter gourd
Then he won't fire
I'll fire, I'll fire
Su Kelan
You just made fried salted eggs with bitter gourd
And Yu Hao's last program
Say something very similar
You wrote his copy, didn't you
Can make such a delicious meal
Someone who can tell such a truth
Then why give it to Yu Hao
This kind of artificial mental retardation does things
Is
I think
The boss is like a bitter gourd
A lot of people don't like it
But adults
Who doesn't need to endure hardship
It's not possible
Have you removed the bitterness
You can get rid of the bitterness
But in fact, the bitter bitter gourd has gone
Is soulless
How much nutrition will be lost
I feel
The nutrition of the boss
It's payroll
As a part-time worker
You have to bear hardships
Working soul
I really can't and I don't force it
Go to the toilet and touch a fish
Wait until the salary is paid
The thought of buying a lot of delicious food
Can make your family happy
Eat well
Still very happy
That's true, too
Don't you think it's hard
Because of his fooling around
Big night's
And give us
Cook so hard
Big night is hard work
But cooking is not hard
A pleasing stomach
It's much easier than pleasing people
Jin Dao
That next program
When will it be recorded
It's better for me to go back
Yu Zong is ready to prepare
Recorded next Saturday
Later
I'll send you the program flow
Thank you, Jin Dao
It smells good
Is the soup ready
Right oh right oh
Come on, come on
Do you have bowls
Bring me the bowl
Divide it. Divide it
Everyone has worked hard
It smells good. It smells good
Jin Dao
Come and taste it
Sister Kelan
Or you come
Let's work here
I really want to be fed every day
I don't like it because I don't understand it
Don't understand
Often because you don't like it
And don't want to know
When you take the step of understanding,
How far is it from liking
Slow down and drink it hot
It smells good
Welcome to
Gong Wenxing, come out for me
Gong Wenxing
Didn't do anything humiliating
Why are you afraid of being told
You have to make it clear to me today
When you dream,
The "doodle" called
Who the hell is it
You can just shout once
I dream all day and shout
I've called it twelve times
It is also said that it is the person in the animation
You think someone will believe it
Break up
Ladies and gentlemen
This program
Are you satisfied
Eat well and drink well
Pretty good, huh
Best Actor
It's already the sixth
You broke up with me like this
Why don't you believe it
I said it in my dream
It's an animated character
I see
You're screaming at all
It's not the people in cartoons
Is to watch it with you
Animated people, right
Change the subject
Come
Let's see how my shop is doing
Just so-so
A mess
Don't rely on anywhere
If you don't win for a month, you will win
Your uncle opened my shop today
It is also specially given to your employees
Fold a gift
That's what you say about me
I this
Where's the mess
Chinese small master
You liked it when you were a kid
Shouting to watch it every day
To take me into the pit, okay
Now you dislike it again
It was you when I was a child
Crying and shouting for me to watch with you
Big Brother
Call Uncle
You are a man
Honesty in the past is eaten by dogs
Also
What body double do honest people use
Make what people set up
Profiteers
You made such a big deal about it
What's the matter
Someone is dealing with it
Don't worry about it
You must do this personally
People who even have to read the code for themselves
Let others handle it with confidence
What person
Let you feel so at ease
Don't move your hands and feet
Look at you like that
Let's order
I'm sorry
I'm late
The blind date is still so late
This child is really
Nothing, nothing
Just got back from Chengdu
Sit down
Greet the guests quickly
My son Li Xun
"What to Eat" Chengdu Company
Marketing Director
Extremely busy at work
It's okay, it's okay
A little gift
Thank you
Eat quickly, eat quickly
I'm so embarrassed
Sister Kelan, where is your car parked
I didn't drive
Sister Kelan, you don't drive
Yu Hao's treatment is not good either
Public relations director does not have a car
Sister Kelan
Why don't you come to us
Go to work in the company
Yeah, come and work with us
No
Because I was born
There is no sense of direction
I can't drive a car
People can't drive a car
It's so late
I drive
Let me give you a ride
No, thank you, Jin Dao
My boyfriend will be here in a minute
I
Wait for him
You go first
Then guide us to withdraw first
Bye, Sister Kelan
Good bye bye bye
Colan
I just said
Agree not to change the sponsor for the time being
Is to give Yu Hao another chance
But he can't be like before
Use body double on the show
This is the bottom line
I won't give in
Understand
Jin Dao, you can rest assured
I will convince Yu Zong
Cook in person
That
It must be confirmed by tomorrow at the latest
Good
Go away
Bye bye
Sorry
It's too late to communicate with the program group
The details will be reported tomorrow
Go to bed early
Boss
Don't send it
What's to be delivered, what's to be delivered
In the future
Just ask the children to contact themselves more
Yes
The car I called for you will be here soon
Just one intersection away
How sweet
Isn't that true
Go
This way
OK, then you walk slowly, huh
Be careful
Auntie, I'll go first
Good bye
Bye-bye-bye
Bye bye
Bye bye bye bye
Slow down on the road
OK
Hello
I was in the office just now
The director wants me to have something to do
I knew you were busy
What about you
Are you done with the matter
Something like that
Fortunately, I can catch the last bus
Or you'll have to spend money again
Last bus
Do you take the bus or the subway
It's so late to take a taxi
Don't
Don't waste the money
Reluctant
Also
Your mother's sick to save money
How about this
Where are you? I'll call a cab for you
No need
I have arrived at the bus stop
Stop talking. The bus is coming. Hang up
Give her a taxi
Why spend the money
It's just talk
It's not like she really wants to
That's right
Market report
Can you do me a favor
No
I will work an extra day tomorrow
Then you'd better come back
I'll send it to your email in the evening
I said
What do you think of that girl
Li Xun
How come he's back today
What are you looking at
Let's go. Let's have supper. Let's go
Mom picked it out
Of course I believe my mother's eyes
Welcome to
The handmade lunch box I gave her
I forgot to take it
Is it
Su Kelan is particularly good at this
Immaterial
When I was reading,
A lunch box for her
It's all precious now
Immaterial can be eaten as food
Her father's gone
Mom is a medicine jar again
Your whole life
Do you want to be dragged down by her
But
Don't be in a hurry to split with her yet
You work in Chengdu
Mom needs someone to take care of, too
It's more cost-effective than hiring a nanny
I said I
How can you be so clever
It turned out to be hereditary, mom
The best scum mother and son
Hello
Who is the director of Chengdu Marketing Department
Wang Tingting
Female
Hang up
Pretending to be your employee
Why
In order to lead my opening lo mei
Isn't this wonderful? This
Sorry
It's too late to communicate with the program group
The details will be reported tomorrow
Go to bed early
Boss
Have you eaten almost
Row
Almost
The waiter pays the bill
Do you have fat intestines here
The kind that is especially clean
Understand
How do you do
A total of three hundred eighty-two
Have a look at it
Sweep me
Eat what company employees
I thought I was going to send something
Boss
It was originally possible to send fat intestines
But it seems
Delivered
What's finished
Isn't that what it is
This
You do business
Don't you talk about honesty
Go
Walk slowly
Not bad
And the last bus
Sit down
Feed mom
I'm done
Waiting for the bus
It's so late and it's raining
You get a cab back
I don't
What kind of car do you take
This taxi money is saved
How nice it would be to eat more delicious food
Oh, don't worry
It's okay
Okay, I won't talk to you
Here comes the bus. I hang up
Deceive
I didn't hear the car at all
Send me the address
I'll call you a cab
I didn't lie to you
Really, the car is really coming
Don't wait for me
You go to bed early
I'll be back soon
Bye bye
Recorded next Saturday
Thank you, Jin Dao
Su Kelan is particularly good at this
Immaterial
Her father's gone
Mom is a medicine jar again
No matter can be eaten as food
Hello, a special car is at your service
Excuse me, is this Miss Su
Mobile phone tail number 2725
Yes
Get in the car, please
Mom
Did you call me the car
How do you do, Miss Su
What is your destination, please
The person who placed your order
Let me and you
Determine the destination
Come back
Mom
You're still up
Didn't you get caught in the rain
No
Mom, you haven't eaten yet
Come and wipe it quickly
I've already eaten a little
But I still have to wait for you to come back
Wait a minute
And the soup. I'll heat it up
I think it's raining
Have some soup
Warm and warm
Mom, why are you watching this play again
What again
Just released
Didn't I just finish reading it a few days ago
The finale
You've seen the play five times, haven't you
Is there
I didn't see this the other day, did I
That's it
Overwork late into the night
There will always be fatigue
The Moment of Healing
It's under a lamp
A delicious meal
And family
In the lonely night
Is there any rice fragrance that can cure you?
Feed Yu Zong
It was agreed at 9:30 this morning
Report to the company
Do you know what time it is
Are you going to take Saturday off
Are you financially free
I'm sorry, Mr. Yu
I'll be right there
Mom, why didn't my alarm clock go off
Did you do it
Yelling at me again
Can't you just put
Gentleness towards others
Shall I share some with my mother
Isn't it Saturday
What happened to you yesterday
Isn't it already done
From the end of processing
There is still a long way to go
Mom, I'm leaving
Have you arrived in Chongqing yet
OK, I have to work overtime
Go home a little later
Then come to my house for dinner at seven tonight
Good. See you tonight
Feed Mengmeng
Li Zhi and Aunt Wang
Come to my house for dinner in the evening
You and your parents
Would you like to come along
Sure
You said that the two of us
I live upstairs and downstairs
What can I do for you
What other phone bills are you wasting
Why don't you just shout one voice
Now that you're out of the house
Don't hurry back either
Turn your head and help me buy food
You're not going with me
I work overtime
Overtime
Because of what happened last night
I'll talk to you about it later
If Li Zhi and Aunt Wang
If you arrive first
Why don't you say hello for me
Row
Li Zhi said he would get on the train later
It may arrive at four or five in the afternoon
Wait a minute
Get on the train later
Yeah
He came back from Chengdu
What's the matter
Do you remember before
I told you before
A sweet-mouthed person like Li Zhi
Not necessarily reliable
What do you mean
Li Zhi has come back long ago
Last night
I saw him in the company
Nearby restaurant
Are you mistaken
I went to work
Remember to help me buy food
Your best friend's 5:0 vision
Can't be trusted
You said immediately
How long will it take
Do you want to do it or not
Cats know to go to work on time
Xiao Hei
Time for dinner
Let you work overtime
You feed the cat
Where's Wan Shun
How is Wan Shun today
I'm not with you.
Wan Shun
Li Zhi has come back long ago
Do you remember before
I told you before
A sweet-mouthed person like Li Zhi
Not necessarily reliable
Wan Shun
You can't let little black
Willing to believe you
Just lie to it
If you lie to it,
There will be no fish balls to eat
There may not be time in the future
I cooked fish balls for you
Come and eat more
Eat it
You're not eating
Then I'll leave it here for you
Remember to eat later
Xiaoyi
Can people eat cat food
Yu Zonghao
What happened
Excuse me
Would you please go out and wait for a while
I'll call you later
Yu Zong
You gave it to me
Communication task of program group
It has been completed
The next program will be recorded in seven days
That's good
What about the three chefs
Let you choose one, Mr. Yu
Learn to cook with him
This is what you call
Is the communication result
Learn to cook with them
Your communication result
What's the difference with Jing Chen
Like the program group,
Blackmail demands
Only zero times and countless times, understand
Yu Zong
They're not blackmailing you
It's just that there is something wrong with their method
But they're now
Have realized that
You see
I went to work
Wait
One more thing
We really shouldn't
For the sake of program effect
By such despicable means
Push Yu Zong to the forefront
You come again
We really shouldn't
For the program group
By such despicable means
Push Yu Zong to the forefront
I hope you can convey to Yu Zong
Our previous apologies
I hope your company
It can cooperate for the long term in the future
Make some sacrifices
Jin Xuan apologized, didn't he
That's not possible either
Learn to cook with them
It's a waste of time
Yu Zong
You exercise regularly every day
Two hours
Fitness
Can't increase the turnover of the company
But
Because of fitness
Enhance your image
Savings for the company
Celebrity endorsement fee
Let the advertising budget of the public relations department
Saved 37%
Simultaneously
Fitness is reduced
Your health risks
Lower
In case you get sick
Will bring it to the company
Potential loss
Some things seem useless
But it can produce greater value
From participating
"Have a good meal with you"
The turnover of a company
It increased by 7.352%
Visible
Yu Zong, you are in the program
The image of loving food
Help improve the image of the company
If you learn to cook,
Make you proficient in food
This image is solid
That
Even if the future program is over,
It can also keep the public
Object to the application
Affection and trust
Considering from the time cost
Mr. Yu, you are young, promising and smart
It's so difficult to run a company
You are a cinch
Time to learn to cook during the program
Average to every day
It just takes you
For three minutes
Or
You try it first
Analysis of the first half
That's quite accurate
In the second half, except for kissing up
There is no substantive content
It's all crap
Not flattery
It's a fact
Aren't you clever, Mr. Yu
I made an appointment to walk for five minutes
You can go to the back kitchen of the restaurant
Boss
Move the car
Investigate the chef
Stir-fried kidney flower
Look at the heat
Ironing three wires and watching knives
Squirrel mandarin fish to see seasoning
Let's call it a day
Would you please go back first
Wait for my news
I'll talk to you later
Hard work
Baby, I got off the train
When will you be back
I miss you
After dinner in the evening
Let's go see a movie together
Last night
I saw Li Zhi and his family in the company
Have dinner in a nearby restaurant
Mr. Yu is right about the chef just now
Not satisfied with any of them
Flashy and unrealistic
It doesn't fit at all
"What's next?"
Brand image
Do you think it's appropriate
You don't even think it's appropriate
And asked me what I was doing
What kind of food do you think
Conform to the brand image of the company
I remember
I saw a passage
The matter of eating
It's quite interesting
When you eat alone,
Don't think there's anything
Once you start
Someone ate with you
When you eat alone again,
You will feel lonely
Loneliness
May
What matters is not what to eat
But when you eat
With whom
I hear you're good at cooking
Why don't you try it
This thing needs to be done
Someone will do it
You try it
Make a
When the interview was held
But Yu Zong, I am now
If you can
Tomorrow I'll have the finance
Put the tuition fee on your card
I heard that you usually go to work
I'm not even willing to take a taxi
Should be very short of money
As it is now
Extra money opportunities falling from the sky
Are you sure you don't want it