(Previously...)
We've done everything we could,...
but your son couldn't be saved.
He didn't make it! What should I do?
I'm more confident now that she has
something to do with Aiden's murder.
-That's for sure!
-We don't know that for sure.
Don't defend her
because you like her, Ares.
What if she really did it?
-You killed Aiden!
-Don't! She's a girl!
Hypocrite!
I did all that to ruin Calderioz...
because they put Aeros in a coma.
Lio is behind all this.
He tried to harm me and Ares.
And he pit Retro against Calderioz.
Are you looking for this, Dad?
Stay away from my daughter!
This is your last warning!
Mr. Damar?
Sir, I'm in love with Serra.
It wasn't Aiden who raped me.
In fact he wanted to take responsibility
for a mistake he didn't make.
After killing my baby,
why did you have to kill Aiden too?
Who did it?
Tell me!
I don't know him.
I don't know.
Good afternoon, sir.
My name is Damar.
I want to report a murder
of a guy called Aiden.
Dad...
Dad!
Ser...
What's wrong, Serra?
Who was that, Ser?
Why was there police at your house?
Serra.
Does it have to do with Aiden?
My dad killed Aiden.
♪I believe in second chances
For the broken-hearted♪
♪Now I can take it for granted
Each and every "disregarded"♪
♪I fall apart yet I am still right here♪
♪But broken heart is hard to heal♪
♪It kills me
Everytime I read between the lines♪
♪Love is divided went undecided♪
♪Fade and misguided
Just like another broken-hearted♪
♪Now since you've been gone♪
♪I should carry on♪
♪Cause I'm tired
Of writing songs about you♪
♪I have spent all night♪
♪Just to make this right♪
♪I can't be somewhere I don't belong♪
♪It's time to move along♪
♪Lonely♪
♪For sure♪
♪But I bet I'm not the only one♪
♪It's time to move along♪
Serra's absent again. Is she sick?
Try to call her.
Okay, I'll call her.
She's not picking up.
Should we go to her house? I'm worried.
-I'm coming with you.
-Me too.
Cleo...
-You want to join us?
-Cleo, come on.
Let's go.
Zea.
What is it?
Nothing.
I just wanted to test your ear,...
to know if it's still capable
of hearing.
What? It was Serra's dad
who killed Aiden?
And then?
The police has arrested him?
But, don't tell anyone yet.
Well, Serra had the courage
to reveal it this quick.
So, you knew?
A few days ago,...
me,...
Serra...
We checked the evidence together.
I'm sorry...
that I didn't tell you guys.
Serra told me not to.
She wanted to take care of it
by herself.
Because it was about her dad.
Serra's dad.
My attitude towards Zea was outrageous.
Okay.
To redeem myself,...
I'll clear Zea's name.
I told you.
-Sorry, Res.
-Don't apologize to me.
Serra, don't ever be afraid,
we're all here for you.
I don't think I can bear it anymore.
I don't understand
why all of this happened to me.
I want to follow Aiden
to the other side.
Serra...
Don't say that.
You're allowed to cry.
You're allowed to be weak.
You're allowed to be crushed
and devastated.
But, there's one thing you can't do.
You can't give up.
Karissa's right.
We'll always be there for you.
What if we stay here for a while?
It's okay, my aunt is coming.
We'll stay here until she arrives, okay?
You don't have to think about it.
We're staying, okay?
Love you, Serra.
Thank you very much.
Remember, we also have to apologize
to Zea. She did nothing wrong.
Okay?
Okay.
Wolves?
Maybe you don't know
the meaning of friendship and love yet.
I was never suspicious of Zea.
Because when we love someone,...
we will know their character.
We'll know our loved one is innocent,...
even when the rest of the world
blames them.
Thanks.
Who would've thought
that you could understand love?
Why do you look so serious?
A friend of mine
is going through a misfortune.
God have mercy.
I hope God gives your friend patience.
Amen. Thanks.
Oh, I'm going to Bandung tomorrow
to visit Aeros.
And I'm thinking
to go back there permanently.
But, the end of the semester is near.
Can't Ares make you feel comfortable
at school?
He's annoying.
Okay. So, you're fighting.
Shhh!
I'm sorry.
I'll admit that I did you wrong.
Forgive me if my words hurt you.
I thought you killed Aiden.
If you want to be mad at me
and vent your anger at me,...
I'll take it.
But, don't ever go away from me.
Because I...
Because I want you to be by my side.
You get what I mean, right?
What is Ares trying to say?
He's been typing for so long.
That means he's confused.
That's typical of guys.
They're too proud, but they want it.
Whatever.
Why are you mad at the guy
who hasn't stopped typing, then?
Miss!
(Unknown number.
We can give you a loan. Contact us.)
When you need an assurance,
yet you are offered a loan instead.
Okay.
(To Calderioz.
Have you eaten yet, dear?)
Since when do you talk
to us this sweetly?
Since he got more
than he had wished for.
Aeros,...
aren't you tired of sleeping?
I'm tired.
I miss you.
About Ares, I've tried to find out...
Excuse me. The CT scan result is ready.
Okay, Nurse.
Hold on, okay?
Please.
We need to act immediately.
We don't have much time.
-Do what I told you to.
-Okay. Done.
How are you?
Aeros,...
I promise...
I'll help Zea to find the person
who dared to do this to you.
I also promise...
to always be on Zea's side...
and protect her.
Although she brazenly infiltrated
Calderioz's headquarters.
Get well soon, okay?
I will always pray for you.
Good bye, Aeros.
Keep the evidence you have
in your grave.
Who pulled out the IV?
Your brother!
What's wrong?
Someone pulled out the IV
and turned off the machine.
How can that be?
I don't know.
How is he, Doc?
How's he doing, Doc?
He's stable.
Ares!
Who are you?
(Don't try to reenact this scene.)
We need to apologize to Zea.
Do you have any idea how to do it?
Just apologize, as simple as that.
But, I'm embarrassed.
I feel bad.
You're the only one who feels that way.
I'm not.
Where's Ares anyway?
He is rejecting my call.
What's wrong with him?
Why is he acting like this?
Just forget it.
Maybe he needs some time alone.
And I bet he also feels bad about Zea.
Then we need to get Ares' relationship
with Zea back on track.
Mor...
You were the cruelest one to Zea.
Should I send her a message?
Don't be lame, talk to her face to face.
Don't be a chicken.
Okay, I'll apologize directly to her,
but you come with me, okay?
Whom are you texting?
I'm sharing our location to my driver.
And I'm asking the guys
to take care of my bike.
How's Aeros?
The doctor said he was stable.
Why were you at the hospital?
I was visiting Aeros.
I wanted to tell him...
that his little sister had the nerve
to deceive Calderioz.
And I told him...
that his little sister
has a crush on me.
Not the other way around?
But, who wants to kill him?
He's in a coma, but someone still wants
to harm him even further?
If we connect it to what happened
the other day...
when you were beaten up
by the Wolves at their headquarters,...
there's a chance that today's incident
has something to do with that.
You mean Lio is behind all this?
That's possible.
But, we don't have any solid evidence.
One thing is for sure,...
there's an enemy inside of Wolves.
And you need to be careful.
Especially with Lionel.
Remember, he tried to hurt you.
The best way to defeat the enemy is...
to be their friend,
their best friend,...
and even be just like their brother.
Hello, Bara?
Aeros is stable.
Okay. Thanks.
But, I'm begging you,...
guard him.
I don't want this to happen again.
Okay, Zea.
I'm going to make sure
they're really loyal to Aeros.
Okay.
I gotta go. Bye.
I'm exhausted. I'm tired after fighting
with many people.
I'm going to take a short nap.
With this, I feel my burden's lifted.
You are my sun eternally.
But, that sun is gone now.
How could I live without my sun?
Aiden, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what my dad did to you.
Know this,...
living with guilt and regret...
is much more painful than death.
But, I never regretted knowing you.
And I never regretted loving you.
And it will always be like that.
Aiden forgives you, I'm sure of that.
This isn't your fault.
No.
Regardless, his death is my fault.
This is all my fault.
-I'm sorry.
-There, there.
This is fate.
I'm heartbroken, too.
You know he was my only son.
But, I can't hold a grudge.
I can't do that to Aiden.
Aiden needs to be in peace over there.
The legal proceeding...
is none of our business.
Let the police do their job.
But, you have to know
that I forgive you.
Okay?
Thank you so much. Thank you.
You're young.
You still have a lot of to live for.
You can't live with regret like this.
You need to be tough.
You can do this.
You need to love those who love you.
Got it?
And you need to forgive those
who have done you wrong.
Okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
You said it's a short nap.
I can't feel my legs.
It was short.
It wasn't.
Well, okay.
I'll call you, okay?
Ares, how did you know
where Aeros is hospitalized?
Your maid.
My maid.
From now on, you don't need
to call me like I'm your senior.
Just Ares.
Why, Senior?
Are you in love with me?