Feather magic
Xiao?
Sent someone into the river
Possibly poisoned by the ghost red Yan
turned into stone
Feather magic
Watch at kisskh.me
you become i don't know you
You looked so cruel just now
full of killing
Is your heart made of iron?
But Quan Xian
Just sent spies from the army
to the enemy
Watch at kisskh.me
How to talk about mercy
you want to say
Today's affairs also have my share
Why don't you execute me too
Xiao and you are born and die
so loyal
Remember the past love
neither should you
loyalty
loyalty you say
It's the two of you partnering
Come and lie to me for the antidote
you know the ghost red yan
you say
Why do not you say it
I know you too well
Every time you stop talking
Must have his own reasons
did someone force you to do this
Who gave you the ghost red Yan?
A mere cheap
Watch at kisskh.me
what to do with me
What to do with Cang Liu
but
Since you've come to plead for him yourself
I can give him a chance
I want you
put this in the waterway
Thank you Lord Prey for giving Fei Lian a chance
Feather Magic and Fei Lian
I will do my best to stop Su Mo
you don't have to know
Feather magic
If you don't say I'm Feilian, I'll be with you
parted ways
Fei Lian
The vicissitudes are far darker than you think
Why do I treat Xiao like this
you know
on the mirror tower
in the temple
There is a man of prey
Adult
right
higher than the fifth division
true ruler
Ghost Red Yan
He gave me the last chance
let me find a way
Stop Su G from entering the Sleepy Dragon Abyss
free dragon god
Yuhuan, make it clear
what is the last chance
Yes
from a famous family like you
Of course I don't understand
do you know
in Cangliu
a humble person like me
How hard is it not to be bullied?
only stand out
just become stronger
I have been defeated by Su G many times
Shi Peng regards me as an abandoned child
Shi Luo and Shi Lang wish I would die soon
good to not stop your future
If it wasn't for me to take refuge in the prey
My sister and I are now
I'm afraid I don't know what it looks like
Feather magic
where did you go
sleepy dragon abyss
You can't go too dangerous
you are from childhood
So well protected by the family
too simple
I tell you
As long as my sister and I don't get bullied
I'm willing to pay any price
Feather magic
Major General, you can't go out
It's quiet here
make people feel
a little weird
I can't seem to feel the presence of any living thing
i can feel
There is a strong mind
we should be
stuck here
Those eyes appeared again
Those eyes and these visions
what does it matter
Perhaps from these illusions
Find clues about the sleepy dragon rope
I heard that a man from Yunhuang came to Longxiao Palace
very curious
Just let Chunhuang show me
This is Ya Ran, born to our mother
Hi Ya Ran
Just call me Bai Wei
hello baiwei
How about it
Are you used to eating?
these
They were all just caught from Biluohai.
it's fresh
you try it
taste
How about it
good to eat
then you eat more
put it here
Come
What's this
for you
is fish soup
drink it hot
delicious
I didn't think about it before
Then I asked the elder
Only know the people of Yunhuang
accustomed to eating hot
you caught me
Unexpectedly, Yunhuang and Biluohai
There's such a big difference
Can you tell me the story of Yunhuang
OK
once
Fifth brother took me to sneak off the boat to see the sea of ​​flowers
There is a huge moon orchid there
open under the moon
I didn't expect it to be so interesting
I really envy you
so many interesting things to see
wait till i get better
You can look back to Hai County with me.
there is my hometown
There are a lot of delicious and fun
good
I also hope that
Have the opportunity to go to the outside world
take a good look
drink it
Come
This fantasy is so real
Through the eyes of Queen Baiwei
Not only can you taste the taste of the soup
I can feel her mood
Did you find any clues in the vision?
nothing special
are some everyday
Queen Bai Wei doesn't seem to be abnormal either.
but
even in fantasy
I can also clearly feel
There's a pair of eyes looking at me
to find those eyes
Maybe it's the key to finding the sleepy dragon rope
You just started practicing swords when your body is just right.
I can't stand it anyway
Why are you looking for me?
this is for you
This is
This is water droplets
You Yunhuang people can't breathe freely here
Chunhuang cast a spell on you before
But spells are time-consuming
This water droplet is different.
you put it on
You can move freely in the blue sea
Thank you Ya Ran
no need to thank me
If you want to thank you, thank you Chunhuang
This bead is hard to make
To use Master Minghuo's Bizhu
Plus Izumi's spell
He spent a lot of mana doing this.
He put so much effort into this bead
then I can't
Let's send things to friends first
never mind
if you give him back
he will be sad
then i also need
Just go and say thank you to him in person
Then by the way ask him what he needs
if it can be done
I will pay him back this favor
if you really treat us as friends
You don't have to think about thank you all the time.
good
It turned out to be water droplets
It was when Chunhuang passed Ya Ran
For Queen Baiwei
No wonder it appeared on Ya Ran later
from the situation
The relationship between Queen Baiwei and Ya Ran
It should be very good
But why did Ya Ran appear in Jiuyi Mountain?
Turned into a dodder in the foggy forest again
and from her words
Also full of resentment towards Queen Baiwei
what happened after
we do not know
Maybe the eyes you said
It's Ya Ran
unlike
This phantom deliberately allows us to see
seven thousand years ago
maybe
is giving us a hint
is to imply us
what happened to them
the same will happen to us
girl baiwei
I am Quanxian's Si Shi Ming Huo
On the orders of Young Master Chunhuang
For your friend who died at sea
Held the Spring Festival Ceremony
Thank you Ming Huo Si
Hope the Dragon God will protect you
May your companions return home
hope they
Able to gain peace and stability
Hope the Dragon God will protect you
May your companions return home
hope they get
calm
and stable
Thank you for everything you have done for me
what is this place
This is our forbidden place.
Dragon Cave
Are there really dragons here?
i tell you a secret
you can't tell anyone
Now is the time when the Dragon God is sleeping and changing his bones
So we can get close
change bone
Dragon God changes bones every five hundred years
ten years
Do the math now
It should have just lost one
a what
dragon tooth
I saw you tense just now
thought you were unhappy
Maybe it's the song that Ming Huo just heard.
Then suddenly I feel homesick
It's our poor care
or you don't like it
no no
You take good care of me
I just miss my family.
when can i go home
You now
not healed
Biluohai is in the tide season
The wind and waves are big
It's dangerous to go out
A big wave came
No boat can escape
But he must be worried about me
If you still miss home
you can call this your home
treat us like your family
Different
Why did you bring it here yourself?
i'm just curious
Why pick so many flowers
nice one
you help me get the bud first
Can you take them off one by one?
good
what are you looking at me
nothing
smell it
smell good
this heart flower
It's unique to you
it tastes very special
It must be delicious for brewing
these wines
You made it all for me
One day I'm leaving
so before leaving
I want to leave you some gifts
As a repayment to you and Ya Ran
Take care of me during this time
This is our craftsmanship
The wine we make is especially sweet
you want to go home
I've been away from home for a long time
But before you go
This wine is not ready
what to do
like this
seal it in the vat
You can drink it after a month
drinking alone
Isn't it just to drink alcohol to relieve anxiety?
What did you say
i said i remembered
But I still want to drink with you
OK
Then I try to drink this wine with you
good
you find me
you come, sit down
give you a try
taste
How about it
what is this
why so spicy
It's not water
You do not
You were drinking
so interesting
one more drink, one more drink, one more drink
no no no no no
we were not allowed to drink
Well, I'll try it
It tastes almost like my hometown.
pure brilliance
this as
my parting gift
finish this wine
are you leaving
I can't be here all the time
It's hard work to lead a war.
This is my responsibility to be born into the Bai family
When we meet and part ways
Chun Huang, glad to meet you
Me too
By the way, this wine doesn't have a name yet.
Help me think of a name
And this letter
Please help me send it to Wanghai County
Give it to Langgan
my family will pick me up
good
Bai Wei
Your letter will be delivered
You will be able to reunite with your family soon
Previously in Sleepy Dragon Terrace
I saw how Queen Bai Wei died
Chunhuang was present
And the King of Stars
But the King of Stars has not yet appeared
it's weird
maybe
After the King of Stars appeared
we can leave this fantasy
Look
Those eyes appeared again
Avi
alang
you are really here
pure brilliance
This is Lang Gan who grew up with me
This is the sea emperor who saved my life
His Royal Highness Chun Huang
Thank you for saving your life
you haven't seen each other for a long time
I won't bother
why did you come
I was ten days ago
Let Chunhuang send the letter to you
I thought you all
what letter
did you not receive the letter
no
I am through astrology
Find your trail on the cloud
Just came here
It's not safe here
let's go
unsafe
They are all good to me
very good
I came here a few days ago
trapped by a shark
And she told me
say you're in love with someone else
like someone else
How can I fall in love with someone else?
Yes
Avi
How can you fall in love with someone else
poor care
I don't know if everyone is used to it
I've gotten used to it
but alang
He may not be used to it yet
This bead was given to me by Chunhuang
I can go in the water with it on
Brother Lang
I toast you
This is Bai Wei's own wine
can't you drink?
i drink less
i can hold back
Don't let yourself blow bubbles
Thanks for the hospitality
Right, Ya Ran?
Ya Ran, she is not feeling well
rest in the room
Then let's go see her
it does not matter
She needs some rest
you stay here a few more days
to see her again
Yunhuang's war is complicated
I am afraid
can't stay long
what happened to the cloud
Cangliu people sneak attack on Wanghai County
Your father was seriously injured and is now recuperating
you came to pick me up
instead of my father coming to pick me up
we go back now
to fight off those scumbags
don't worry
Even if the two of us are fast
also to no avail
You two have the people in your heart
The war is so tight
I will definitely assist you
you are still here
Please forgive the Dragon God
Why did the emperor of the sea want to take my dragon tooth?
I have been blessed by the Dragon God for all generations
happy and healthy life
But in the cloudless land thousands of miles away
The people there are suffering from the turmoil of war
This time I met two friends from Yunhuang
They want to quell the war in Yunhuang
Bring peace to the cloud
Although I am Quanxian's sea emperor
But I also want to help them
Therefore
borrow
Borrow Dragon Tooth
I want to make a heaven-defying sword and give it to them
Heavenly Sword
you want them to unravel
The azure lock that seals the sign and protects the power
Do you know
When these two ancient forces reappeared in the world
may cause unrest
I know
So these two forces will be sealed
Neptune
you make this decision now
will be forever
the last time i ask you
do you really want to do this
I believe in Bai Wei
She is the kindest woman in the world
also have the spirit of the common people
i believe her
Will definitely give Yunhuang peace
By the time
Quan Xian is friendly with Kong Sang
world peace
Isn't it the greatest good thing
ok i promise you
But you must remember
The only way to fight against nothingness
Only create and protect
dragon god what does this mean
This is the revelation given by the ancestors to the sea emperor
You have to figure it out yourself
May this prophecy
never come true
There is an island in the middle of Mirror Lake
Sealed with sign and protection
Two ancient powers
As long as these two forces are available
In the cloudless desert, no one is invincible
Why is this power sealed
who sealed it
Someone once got these two powers
unify the cloud
But then out of control
these two forces
Sealed in this small island in the middle of Mirror Lake
no one can get near it
such a powerful force
I don't know if it's a blessing or a curse
In fact, the power itself
There was no distinction between good and evil
As long as the two forces of levy and protection are allowed to
coordinate with each other
will not lose balance
I don't know how to get this power
Open the cyan lock
to break the seal
how to open
go down
please sit
open it
so powerful
This is the Heavenly Sword
It is made with the teeth of the dragon god
The power of the dragon god is hidden inside
with it
open the golden lock
unseal
I want to give it to you
as a cloud
Izumi destination
The gift of friendship
You want such a precious Heaven-defying sword
give us
hope you can find
Protect the power of Yunhuang
The gift of the sword is unforgettable
Hope to see you again someday
Avi
By the way, Chunhuang
Have you thought about the name of this wine?
just call it
recollection
Good name
Chunhuang I will miss you
I miss Quan Xian
if someday
Ah Lang and I can calm down the deserted clouds
we will definitely be back
repay your kindness
the scar on your hand
It was when I went to Jiuyi to pick up the Heavenly Sword.
left over
Chunhuang seven thousand years ago
I have scars like yours on my hands
The two prophecies that Dragon God told Chun Huang just now
Before on the Tianque Snow Mountain
Nasheng also helped me with divination
The only way to fight against nothingness
Only create and protect
Since we entered the trapped dragon
This one thing after another
It seems that there is a certain number in the dark
Not only are we the same as them
This sea shell pearl prays for blessings to protect the sword
And the scar on your hand
those prophecies
There are too many similarities
Even if it is a given fate
we are us
they are them
I never believed in fate
I don't know what will happen after
Turmoil in the cloud
I'm afraid it's all related to sign and protection
These two forces are related
The first year of Taichu
The Queen and the Queen Climb to the Mirror Lake Island
gold lock
Ancient Creation Divine Power Sign and Protection
out of the world
Divine Power Condensed into the Ring of Emperor Heaven and Earth
The Queen
shelter the cloud
The latter two pioneered the world side by side
Nanami Arahira
Dingdu Mirror City
The first ten years
The envoy of Quanxian brought treasures to the audience
alang
This is Ya Ran that I always mention to you
Lord of Langgan
Princess Yaran
I am ordered by the Emperor of the Sea
I came here to congratulate Kong Sang on the unification of the six wastes
Neptune has always respected King Xingzun and Queen Baiwei
The wise god Wu Ze and all sentient beings
Therefore, I would like to form an alliance with Kong Sang.
This is the treasure I brought Quan Xian to show my sincerity
Hope to communicate with Kongsang generation
long history
thank you
This wine is for reunion
I don't know if I'm lucky enough to drink this wine with the king
to congratulate
I got it
Ya Ran long time no see
We didn't see you last time we left
almost ten years
Otherwise, let's go over there and have a good chat
Ah Lang, he should have other things to do
good
Me and Ah Lang have been fighting for many years in Yunhuang
life at risk
Looking at the empty sang now
I can't believe it myself
Of course
If it weren't for you and Chun Huang
Helped in the first place
days like this
I don't know when it will come
I came to the mirror city
see you as a queen
Supported by the people
sincerely happy for you
you are fighting for the common people
It's destiny for you
By the way, I just wanted to ask you
When were you born?
just before
When I am sick
It can make us Princess Ya Ran's favorite
Must be a handsome man
an exotic prince
He used to carry only a sword
Drift to the blue sea
I saved him and healed him
But he has a heart
I was born for him
I've been wrong all my life
you are not from here
inability to breathe underwater
I only have to set up a water formation to heal your wounds
no go no go
not allowed to go
I do not go
If I don't go, let go of your hands
i won't let go
I won't let go
why do you keep going
I only have her in my heart
i'm going to find her
she's already in love with someone else
don't go
you don't go you don't go
Ya burning
you are born
Chunhuang, I did something wrong
i'm sore
why it hurts so much
You are in love with a stranger
I was wrong
I did wrong
The most painful thing in the world
is to love someone who doesn't belong to you
Ya Ran, please tell me
who is this person