(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Number of Voters)
Your Honor.
The Ministry of Justice just issued an emergency stay of execution.
On whose orders?
Judge Kim Ga On just held a press conference.
The live court show...
was all...
a fake.
Can you go into detail?
Are you saying Judge Kang manipulated the trials?
I will speak instead.
It is true that Judge Kang manipulated the trials.
He decided on a conclusion, and to suit that,
he created evidence...
and met with lawyers in advance to clue them into the story.
The counsel was in on it?
- Is that true? - For real?
Is that true?
Judge Kim Ga On here already gave his statement to the Supreme Court,
and a committee will be put together to get to the truth.
What will happen to the live court show?
When the truth comes to light,
all the trials Judge Kang presided over will be retried...
and annulled.
Will the live court show be discontinued?
What will happen to Judge Kang?
(Stay of execution)
As you can see,
the execution...
was stayed.
I will release a separate statement...
on my view of this matter.
Members of the public, I thank you.
(Execution stayed, Kang Yo Han to release statement)
(Stay of execution)
Release the defendant.
You did your job, Your Honor.
I wish you luck...
Defendant.
We'll meet again.
I look forward to it.
What is happening?
They're fighting among themselves.
You'll get your way without doing anything, Mr. President.
A toast.
Cheers.
That kid Juk Chang.
He doesn't die that easily.
What?
Right before he dies,
weren't you going to cut power to save him?
That's just what I told him.
You're more naive than you look.
That's just what I said.
You didn't tamper with the electric chair?
I did tamper with it in a way.
If Juk Chang couldn't handle the pain...
and was going to talk, right before he did,
I was going to up the voltage to the maximum...
and boom.
I bet he'd smoke.
Juk Chang, goodbye forever.
You're something.
That's why you were so relaxed.
I'm impressed, Mr. President.
I just don't get those fools who pretend to be so righteous.
They grab each other at the ankles,
show off,
and then trip up over each other.
Then they bring each other down.
What is that mess? I don't get it.
Fights must be won.
Judge Kim.
I apologize.
Is it true?
Chief Kang really did that?
Yes.
I'm sorry for not telling you.
I had no idea.
Then...
Jang Ki Young, the witness who was bribed.
Is that true too?
Chief Kang's explanation was a lie?
I was for show.
- Judge Oh. - I don't care if I was.
I still believed in what the chief stood for.
I thought he was a good judge, unlike me.
(Handwritten Affidavit)
(Department: Live Court Show Name: Kim Ga On)
(Interview Room, Fact-finding Committee)
I...
first met Judge Kang Yo Han...
(I first met Judge Kang Yo Han...)
Nice to meet you.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Judge Kim Ga On, right?
- Yes, I look forward to... - Welcome...
to the battlefield.
Why are you doing this?
(Making justice isn't difficult. It will be done at DIKE.)
Why am I doing this?
Yes.
- Because I can. - What?
Possibility is like a drug.
Like I said, there's no justice in reality.
There's only a game.
A dreadful unjust game.
(Handwritten Affidavit)
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
Is it happening all over again?
Treating me like a monster.
- Oh, it's a bird. - My goodness!
Are you crazy? Why would you kill it?
From that day, the kids called Yo Han a monster.
That little boy...
will kill his brother one day.
Yo Han. I'm really worried about you.
This on top of what happened at school?
You could end up in a lot of trouble.
You're quite incredible.
You got rid of your foolish brother,
and you rescued his daughter...
so that you wouldn't be suspected and acted like a hero.
Say that again.
Did you kill your brother too?
Yes, that's math.
2 is bigger than 1.
Sir, you seem to really enjoy playing with numbers.
You want to come up with a verdict based on how viewers vote on an app?
Do you think that's playing with numbers?
I call it democracy.
(Over three million votes)
I just choose the fastest way...
for them.
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
Why are you here?
You stabbed me in the back.
So what is there to talk about?
I came to say goodbye.
I told you...
that I didn't want to see you go to a place you can't turn back from.
But while looking at you in the court, I realized something.
Doing it to make Juk Chang talk was just an excuse.
It didn't matter if he talked or not.
You just wanted everyone to have blood on their hands.
And after that,
they'll have no choice but to stand by your side.
That's right.
People desperately want to believe they made the right choice.
That's human nature.
Using the vulnerability of human beings...
is what the devil does.
Say that again.
If you don't attack first, you get attacked in this world.
You don't want me to cross the line in the middle of a fight?
You're being naive.
I...
chose the fastest way.
It's human nature to hesitate.
They're vulnerable.
But they know when to hesitate,
and they know when to stop.
If they don't,
only monsters will be left in this world.
Self-pitying monsters.
Here we go again.
It's something I've heard all my life.
Do you feel the same way?
Are you scared of me too?
You don't want to become a monster like me, do you?
Well?
If you want to kill me,
just do it.
You are a weak loser.
Get lost.
I truly wished...
you would stop.
Since the shocking revelation...
that the live court show's trials have been fabricated,
Judge Kang Yo Han has not responded publicly...
and is just keeping his silence.
The live court show has offered encouragement to the people...
with its aim of making justice.
But the revelation of its fabrication...
put the people in a state of shock.
Negative publicity has been growing against Judge Kang Yo Han.
You see that? That's how good I am.
Yeon Jung, now do you see how brilliant your husband is?
Of course, I do.
You know Chief Justice Min Jung Ho, right?
He thinks he was attacked by Kang Yo Han's supporters...
and he's furious about it.
Yes, is the police not here yet?
I'm telling you it's urgent!
But actually, Juk Chang did it. Isn't that hilarious?
I took more proactive measures...
and sowed seeds everywhere.
And that's why we have beautiful fruits like these.
Of course. Certainly.
You're the best.
You're a genius.
But it's a pity.
It's a real pity.
We should've seen some blood by now.
I would've run over the jerks that go against me with a tank.
Then only the patriots would've been left.
We would've made Korea more powerful...
that will make history.
Honey.
Making history is all good.
But don't forget where we started.
What do you mean?
"Great nation, Korea. Pure-blooded Koreans!"
That was just the concept of our Internet show.
I think you're getting too deep into the character.
I'm worried about you.
Was I immersed too much?
To be honest, we started this to make some money.
I hope you don't forget that.
Money is the only thing that matters in the end.
You're right.
"The first president to turn a nation into a business model."
We did talk about that.
But Yeon Jung.
There is something more important than money.
What's that?
To make sure your name goes down in history.
To etch your name in the grand, splendid credits...
that is history...
as the eternal protagonist!
Yes, that's it.
Yes.
That's exactly it.
I saw the news.
You did?
Are you okay?
Are you worried about me?
Worried, my foot.
If you get arrested,
this house will be mine.
It's been yours all along.
By the way, Ga On is...
never coming back here, I guess.
We're just going back to the way we used to be.
We used to...
only have each other, remember?
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Hello, Professor.
Ga On.
I can't stop thinking that...
Kang Yo Han was involved in Soo Hyun's death.
Professor.
That can't be possible.
Do you really think he killed his own brother for money...
and killed Soo Hyun to cover that up?
He's not that monstrous.
No matter what the world thinks of him,
I know one thing for sure.
He deserves sympathy.
It's not that you don't believe me.
You don't want to believe me.
Professor.
All right. It must've been a long day for you.
Get good rest.
Kang Yo Han is no longer a threat.
You should lift the state of emergency...
and try to calm the public...
That's nonsense.
We should finish what we started.
We'll announce the virus has been found in more areas...
and evacuate more people.
Mr. President, that's not what we planned.
If we evacuate too many people,
there won't be enough facilities to accommodate...
From now on...
From now on,
I'll take charge.
When I make a decision that will go down in history,
all you have to do is follow it.
Do you understand?
And you. You've been getting on my nerves for a long time.
You talk too much. You should know your place.
How dare you, woman?
Most of all,
this is our chance to wipe them all out.
Those who leech off our welfare system...
without making any contributions.
Old people, good-for-nothings,
whiners who protest all the time...
We'll wipe out all those useless people...
and build a new country, okay?
A young and strong Korea.
That's been my slogan since my Internet broadcast days.
Korea's Total Change!
This is a revolution!
A revolution...
to put Korea on the right track!
I'm really moved by your speech.
But have you thought about the aftermath of that?
What aftermath?
By raising the stakes, you'll face more resistance.
What if people pour out onto the streets,
protest, and make a mess?
What else?
I'm the commander-in-chief of the armed forces.
I can sweep them all away.
I'll send all units to Gwanghwamun...
and even deploy airborne troops.
Why can't I?
That's what they did in the old days.
Darn it.
What?
What are you doing?
Oh, my.
Hold on.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Are you out of your mind? You're insane!
Hey...
What?
Did you team up?
What is going on?
There's a limit to my patience, punk.
You're nothing but a puppet.
Didn't you know that?
Did you think you really were a great leader or something?
Hello? Secretary Kim! A coup!
Hey!
Hello? Secretary Kim!
Listen carefully. You have no idea what's going on here.
I'm serious. You have to trust me.
Trust me, you have my permission to shoot them. I mean it.
Trust me, okay?
This is a coup. I'm giving you an order to shoot them.
Pull yourself together. Start with this woman.
Shoot her! Now!
Ms. Jung.
What?
You're scaring him.
It's fine. You may leave.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey! Secretary Kim!
Stand up already, will you?
What?
Go stand by the flag instead of getting in the way.
Honey. Our great leader, Mr. President.
This is all business.
Revolution doesn't make money.
Neither does history.
So why would the foundation support that?
You're so stupid.
I'm sure you have an idea of why I called you here today.
It's obvious.
You must want to talk about someone who's not here.
Like our great leader, Mr. President.
Right. What do you two think?
He seems really excited these days.
He was always a supporting actor, but now he's the lead.
I get how he feels,
but if he keeps overreacting like that, he'll dig his own grave.
I heard he told them to kill Juk Chang if he spoke.
In front of the entire nation at that.
I know. He doesn't think about the after-effects.
He watched too many movies.
I asked him what he'd do if the nation started protesting,
and he said he'd run them all over with tanks.
All he ever does is threaten people.
We want to clean and redevelop Seoul and sell it to foreign investors,
but he really doesn't know anything about the economy.
Do you want me to tell you something even more surprising?
- What? - What is it?
Our great leader, Mr. President,
was planning on spreading a real virus in Seoul.
What should we do about this lunatic?
Has he lost his mind?
How would we sell contaminated property?
He lacks business skills...
because he's an artist.
This is precarious.
We need to come up with a Plan B.
An elite who is a bit safer.
The president and the chief justice of the Supreme Court...
are all temporary employees chosen by us.
Yet they all become delusional.
There are male leads who never change,
but you never got a chance to be one.
Right?
Be quiet!
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han)
You look a bit lonely now.
You're quite brave.
I can't believe you showed up here.
Why? Do you want to get revenge for her death?
Please. I know you're not that stupid.
You would never do something just based on your emotions...
when you have nothing to gain.
I'll give you one last chance.
I want to give you a chance...
because it's you, Master Yo Han.
So stop bluffing.
I'm giving you an opportunity of a lifetime.
A chance to go to the Blue House instead of prison.
Why?
Do you need a new puppet?
Is Heo Joong Se not to your taste?
Are you willing to go to prison for manipulating the trials?
To put on a prison uniform and live among the trash you put away?
Do you think you can handle that?
You're working so hard.
You're really impressive.
You're always working so hard to stay afloat.
To fill a hunger that can't be filled...
and to get something you can't dare to even have.
I feel...
really bad for you.
(Supreme Court of Korea)
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han Holds Press Conference)
I wonder what kind of lies he'll tell this time.
My fellow citizens.
I am a criminal.
- What is this? - What is this development?
(Chief Judge Kang Yo Han Holds Press Conference)
All of the suspicions surrounding me are true.
I have betrayed your trust.
I have abused the law to punish criminals.
As a judge, I came to realize that...
law...
is powerless before power.
Those with money and authority...
got away with committing crimes, and I saw it for myself.
I wanted to do all in my power...
to make them pay the price.
(Kang Yo Han Press Conference)
That's right.
Using my rage that justice is never served as an excuse,
I crossed a line that must...
never be crossed.
Dear members of the public. I am sorry.
I no longer qualify to judge others.
As of today,
I resign...
and will accept any punishment.
I am a criminal.
You may stone me.
Can you face us, please?
Would you be willing to return?
- There he is. - He's coming.
- Judge, no! - Judge Kang.
- Please stay on for us. - You can't resign!
- You must stay. - Please don't go.
- Please, keep going. - Don't quit.
- Chief! - Judge Kang.
- Thank you, Judge Oh. - Chief...
You too.
- You can't leave. - Don't leave.
- Judge. No. - You can't leave, Judge!
- You must stay. - Keep doing what you do.
Get out of the way.
Kang Yo Han for president!
For president!
Kang Yo Han!
- Kang Yo Han! - Kang Yo Han!
The public's support for Kang Yo Han is unchanging.
All over Korea, people are gathering to show their support for him.
He's formidable.
Ms. Jung.
What now?
Mr. Heo Joong Se's so lucky.
He needs to stay a little longer.
Hi, Sun Ah.
Keep tabs on the opposition parties.
After his public statement,
nationwide support for Kang Yo Han has increased.
I thank you for the offer,
but I think it's too soon.
I apologize.
There had been many prior incidents,
but they were all concluded to be groundless suspicions.
According to an emergency poll,
as many as 57.6 percent said they would vote...
for Kang Yo Han if he were to run for president.
Opposition parties don't have a strong presidential candidate,
and they are vying to bring Judge Kang into their midst.
What his next movement will be is the center of their attention.
Ga On.
(Police Notebook)
This is...
It belonged to Soo Hyun.
(Police Notebook)
(Jung Joseph)
(Old house, blue gate, uphill)
Until the moment she died,
she was looking into the church fire.
She'd have come to see you with something to tell.
(Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun)
(Police Notebook)
The detective lady was really persistent.
You have no idea how many times she came here.
When did you last see her?
Not long ago.
About two weeks ago, I think.
She said she'd found everyone...
but Jung Joseph.
She said she couldn't find him. He did odd jobs at the church.
Is this him?
Yes, this is Joseph.
Shortly after she came to see me,
someone said they'd seen Joseph somewhere in Seoul.
What then?
So I called the detective lady to tell her.
Did you say...
old house, blue gate, uphill, this?
That's right. This is what I told her.
- Do you know which area? - Sure.
I have it written down somewhere.
Did something happen to the detective lady?
Well...
No. I just wanted to check.
Is anyone home?
Hello.
Okay.
Thank you.
Mr. Jung.
Hello?
Mr. Jung Joseph?
Is anyone home?
Did you see someone like this nearby?
No, I haven't. What a bother.
Hello?
Is anyone in?
Who... Who are you?
You're Jung Joseph, aren't you?
You work with Kang Yo Han.
Yes. I'm...
Mr. Jung.
Please don't hurt me. Don't kill me.
Why are you doing this? Get up.
Judge Kang told you to kill me, didn't he?
Didn't he?
Can I really trust you?
If Kang Yo Han had sent me,
why would I be sitting here?
If you're that worried,
I'll move you somewhere today.
Chief Justice Min Jung Ho will help.
Can you promise me that you'll protect me?
Yes.
I'll let you talk to the chief justice if you want.
I have CCTV footage...
of the church fire.
I was in charge of the CCTV.
Shortly after the fire,
Judge Kang came to me.
He asked for the file...
and asked me to keep quiet for the rest of my life.
He promised me a new house...
and enough money for me to live on in return.
So I did as he said.
But the thing is...
I'm ashamed to tell you this,
but I had made a copy, hoping I could make money from it.
A few months ago,
Judge Kang sent a man to me.
He tortured me,
asking if there were any copies.
I thought I was going to die.
In the end, I confessed and handed over the copy.
What about these wounds?
A few days ago,
a detective came to see me.
Hello?
Who is it?
Mr. Jung Joseph?
Just a second.
I'm Officer Yoon Soo Hyun from the RIU.
I told her I knew nothing and she should bring a warrant...
and sent her back.
But last night, Judge Kang's man came back.
Asking if I said anything to the detective...
or gave her another copy. Then he beat me up.
About that man,
do you have his phone number or anything?
No. We only talked in person.
He parked his car outside my house last night.
- Here you go. - I appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Sure. You can keep it as long as you want.
That's him. And that's his car.
- This car? - Yes.
First, catch Kang Yo Han's man by all means.
If he killed Soo Hyun,
Kang Yo Han might try to kill him to get rid of any evidence.
Can we look up his car right away?
Yes, one of my old students works at the Police Agency.
I'll find out the man's address and call you back.
Okay.
Just what is in the footage?
I can't tell you that.
Please don't ask me.
Judge Kang said, if I told anyone about it,
he'd chase me to the ends of the earth and kill me.
I know he meant it.
Give me some time.
I'll find out who Kang Yo Han is.
I'm almost there, Ga On.
(Police Notebook)
You've arrived at your destination.
Who are you?
(Call History)
Hello?
Who do you think shot Soo Hyun?
He wasn't trying to shoot her.
They were planning to attack us in the confusion.
If you want to save the world,
you have to cut Yoon Soo Hyun out of your life
You can't help me and be with her at the same time.
You must feel like you're in a fiery pit.
An eternal fiery pit you'll never be able to get out of.
find the people who are responsible for this...
and make them burn in the fiery pit.
That's the only way you can survive in that place.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
I can let you kill me if you want.
But...
you'll regret it...
for the rest of your life.
You killed Soo Hyun.
Ga On.
You're hurting.
You're hurting so much that you want to blame someone.
Shut it!
I saw it with my own eyes.
The evidence that proves that you're the culprit.
I don't know what you saw,
but I'm sure you're aware...
of how futile evidence is.
How easy it is to fool people.
You killed your brother too.
What?
What was on the video you took from Jung Joseph?
You lighting the cathedral on fire? Right?
Did you meet with Joseph?
Did you meet him?
Step away from him!
Step away from Ga On right now.
Mr. Kang Yo Han.
You are under arrest for abetting in Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun's murder.
You have a right to an attorney,
the right to remain silent,
and the right to submit a review of legality for arrest and confinement.
Do you really believe that?
Do you believe that I killed my brother and Soo Hyun...
and that I used you?
Do you believe that everything I said to you was a lie?
Kim Ga On.
This is so moving.
You...
I've never seen this look in your eyes before.
Why are you here?
Welcome, Ms. Jung.
Professor Min.
Do you mean...
Coincidences don't repeat themselves.
It was a coincidence that you resembled Kang Isaac,
but the fact that you started working with Kang Yo Han...
Well, things like that can't be a coincidence.
How dare you...
Oath.
As a judge,
I will make fair and wise decisions...
based on the Constitution and the law.
I will follow the Judicial Code of Ethics...
and be faithful to my duty...
to serve the people to the best that I can.
- To this, I swear. - I swear.
He looks just like him.
One, two, three.
- No. - Hurry.
Gosh.
Okay, I'm going to take the picture.
You should take it together.
No way, Professor.
- My gosh. - I'll take another.
Please smile in this photo.
Okay. One, two, three.
(Communicating with the people)
Who do you think made Professor Min Chief Justice?
Professor Min.
This was all for the sake of the greater good.
You'll come to understand one day.
Ga On.
Professor Min.
You're Master Yo Han's weakness that I planted.
This man...
is really dangerous.
I told you I'd make sure you'd end up lonely. Didn't I, Master Yo Han?
This was all a manipulation.
Kang Yo Han didn't do it.
She did it.
There's no point.
Everyone here has been won over by her.
You were behind everything?
The person who told that old lady where Jung Joseph was,
and the person who told Joseph to lie...
No.
Everything Joseph said was true.
Master Yo Han did everything he could to hide the truth.
The only thing is...
The man who tortured Joseph to get the CCTV footage...
That man wasn't sent by Master Yo Han.
I was the one who sent him.
I, Jung Sun Ah, did that.
Darn it.
No.
No!
This is the thing that Master Yo Han did everything he could to hide.
No! Don't do it. No!
Let go!
Let go. Let go of me!
Don't do it!
Let go!
Don't do it. Stop
Turn it off!
Let go!
Let go of me!
(Verena Church)
The Lord's body.
- The Lord's body. - Did you see Elijah?
She'll be outside. Don't worry.
The Lord's body.
Teddy. Let's pray.
Put your hands together,
bow your head, and close your eyes.
Let Mom, Dad, and Elijah live happily.
Teddy, what did you pray for?
Teddy, do you feel cold?
I'll make you warm.
Pet. I'm petting you.
Let's go, Teddy.
The Lord's body.
Elijah...
I feel sorry for you, Young Master.
For fear she would find out she killed her parents,
you spent your whole life keeping that a secret.
Let me go.
Ga On?
- Elijah. - Elijah?
Elijah.
- Elijah. - Yo Han!
Yo Han!
Elijah.
Yo Han.
Elijah!
Yo Han!
Let go!
Elijah!
- Let go! - Let her go.
Let go!
- Yo Han! - Elijah!
It's time she knew the truth.
Poor Elijah.
No. Don't tell her.
- Let go! - Don't tell her.
Elijah...
Please.
Please!
- Please! - Yo Han!
Let me go! Yo Han!
Please.
Yo Han. Why...
I wanted just one thing.
For you to look at me like that.
Please.
Take him.
Yo Han.
That moment,
I decided to die.
(The Devil Judge)