[English subtitles are available]
Dr. Wu.
Happy Birthday.
You're 27 years old now.
I've spent 27 birthdays
with a heavy heart.
Think about it this way.
This will still be better than
your 30th birthday.
Thank you.
The person to celebrate
your birthday is here.
Dr. Wu,
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
I'll treat you to steak tonight.
Let's celebrate your birthday.
I'm celebrating with
my best friends tonight.
What about this weekend?
I'm celebrating with my
parents this weekend.
It's fine.
It's your birthday.
Is there anything you
want as a birthday gift?
There's really no need for this.
Wang,
you've finished your meal, right?
I'm done.
You two, enjoy.
Enjoy your food.
Dr. Wang
is quite observant.
Dr. Jiang,
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead. What is it?
I heard from Wang Xiao Ya that
a few days ago, in the corridor,
you were talking to Liu Yu Cheng.
Liu Yu Cheng?
Is he that young man
who brings you lunch everyday?
What did you say to him?
Nothing.
I just said you two weren't
suitable for each other
and he should stop
wasting his time on you.
Who gave you the right
to say those things to him?
I thought that's what you think.
So I was helping you
to solve this trouble.
You don't even know me well.
In the future, please don't
decide on your own.
Don't tell me you honestly like him.
He's so much younger than you
and he's still studying.
You two are really not
suitable for each other.
Suitable or not,
I don't need you to tell me.
We're just friends.
You've overstepped your boundaries.
You promised me to go for archery session
and dine at a restaurant.
Within my understanding,
These are already dates.
Now you're telling me
we're just friends?
That's right.
At the beginning, I also considered
to look for someone
who's about the same age
as me to be my boyfriend.
However, after interactions,
I realised
you're the type of person
who's the least suitable for me.
The dates, as you understand them to be,
won't happen again in the future.
Wu Ying, you should consider it.
I'm really sorry!
[Sweet Teeth Episode 15]
[Outpatient]
Dr. Wu, are you clocking out?
Who gave this to you?
Who else could it be?
Jiang Rui, of course.
Do me a favour.
Return this to him
and tell him to stop doing
this kind of meaningless
thing in the future.
Look.
This is the classic design.
Besides, the price has gone up this year.
Wait a minute.
This seems
to be a gift from someone else.
[Dr. Wu, happy birthday.]
[Liu Yu Cheng]
[You're going to be cute this year, too.]
[Dr. Wu, happy birthday. You're going
to be cute this year, too. Liu Yu Cheng]
That guy
must've done it on purpose.
Last time, he grabbed your knee.
This time, it's your face.
It's fine.
He's just an aggressive player.
It's my fault
for not focusing on the game.
Apply it on your face.
Thank you.
You are not in a good condition.
You're in the clouds.
Today is her birthday.
I was going to celebrate
her birthday with her,
but I was afraid she'd find me annoying.
Let me have a look.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Apply it first.
The swelling will subside in a while.
Why did you bring it here?
Don't you like it?
You're a student.
Why did you buy for me
such an expensive bag?
What were you thinking?
Return it to the shop.
I threw away the receipt.
Yes, I'm still studying.
I probably can't give you
what the men in their thirties
can give you
at the moment.
However, I remember it.
I'll work even harder
and dream big.
As for the things that other women own,
I'll do my best to make
sure you own them as well.
Anyway, don't worry.
I bought this using scholarship.
I didn't ask money from my family.
Why do you have to
make life so tiring for yourself?
Great!
Go! Good job!
Look at those girls.
They're pretty and lively.
Awesome!
At their age,
they don't have to worry
so much about realistic issues.
Neither do they face pressure in life.
Isn't being with them
easier for you?
You're the person I like.
I can see and think of
no one else but you.
What are they like
has nothing to do with me.
You said
I was not at the legal age to get married.
However, in Malaysia,
one can get married at 18 years old.
You also said that
we were originally
not meant to cross paths,
but we
still met each other.
The moment
we met each other,
we crossed path with
each other, didn't we?
The only thing is that
currently,
my financial ability is indeed limited.
Perhaps temporarily,
it's going to be a little hard for you.
However, that's also my
motivation to work hard.
I'll work even harder
to study my major.
In the future, I'll definitely
be better than that
Dr. Jiang.
Are you still holding a grudge?
Is Dr. Jiang blacklisted by you?
From the rational perspective,
he's right.
However, in terms of feelings,
it's true that I
dislike him
just a little bit.
We're quite similar in that aspect.
I know, right?
I knew you wouldn't like him.
I can tell by the way you look at him.
Ski resort, we're here!
It's so cold outside!
Let's take a photograph.
One, two, three.
Come and get your luggage.
I'll take it, thank you.
Zeng Li, give me your suitcase.
I'll carry it myself.
Let's go.
It's so heavy.
Is there any kind person
to help me out with it?
You're a grown up now.
It's time for you to face
this world on your own.
Deng Hao Ran,
you deserve to be hit.
Hello, sir.
Here are your room cards.
Thank you.
Come on, let's decide
the room distribution.
Act quickly if you want to
share the room with me.
Otherwise,
you'll lose the chance.
I'll share one with Mr. Ai.
Thank you.
The three of us will decide on our own.
So that leaves us with one another.
I've long heard about you.
Although we're meeting for the first time,
my instincts tell me
you're a born socialiser like me.
Your instincts are very accurate.
I'll be in your care tonight.
I am told that
if three girls go on a trip,
two of them will become
closer than before.
One of them is just there to
be with the rest of the group.
Who do you think
will be the one being left out?
The three of us are very close.
Don't sabotage our friendship.
I'm going to ditch you guys tonight.
I finally
have a free weekend.
I'm going to play games tonight.
You're on a skiing trip.
Why are you still thinking about gaming?
No matter where she is,
she'll only hear one voice.
It's been so long since we had hotpot.
It seems delicious.
Mr. Ai, try this
sour plum drink.
It's very nourishing.
Do you want some orange juice?
Thank you.
This is yours.
You're quite particular
to be drinking from a straw.
Without a straw,
her lipstick
is going to smear later.
I just experienced a breakup.
Do you have to treat me this way?
How did you know I was wearing lipstick?
It's obvious.
Peach colour.
Ma Yi Yi,
didn't you say
it's a nude colour of the no-makeup trend?
Wrong.
One more time.
Why are you so beautiful
even without makeup?
Yi Yi,
I suggest you to switch seats.
Otherwise,
you might get diabetes.
You, get up.
I don't think anyone among us
likes to eat spicy hotpot
more than Zeng Li.
Come on.
Her gums are having problems.
She shouldn't eat spicy food for now.
I've almost recovered.
It'll hurt tomorrow if
you eat a little now.
It should be fine to eat occasionally.
As a dentist,
I won't allow
this kind of thing to happen.
Just let her eat.
What's with you?
Aren't you two tired of it?
This guy
is telling me off just
because he's a dentist.
You can only eat the non-spicy version.
It's fine. Eat this.
I'll get it for you if there's
anything you want to eat.
Let's raise our glasses
to wish Dr. Wu
happy 27th birthday.
It's just a birthday.
Do you have to be so specific?
-It's the 18th.
-Okay.
All right.
In that case, let's wish Dr. Wu
a happy birthday.
Also,
here's
to this unusual group
being together again.
Indeed.
Come on, cheers.
Happy birthday. Cheers.
Between your uncle and Dr. Ai,
who will you choose?
Can I apply for membership
and choose both?
Happy birthday.
Have you finished eating?
We can finally go skiing.
I can't for now.
I'm going to stay in
the hotel for a while.
It seems the hotel's
Internet speed is not bad.
It's my favourite green colour.
I'll keep you company.
It's okay.
Ski with them.
You don't visit here often.
I'm a Malaysian.
I don't have that much interest in skiing.
It's exactly because you're a Malaysian,
all the more you should
cherish this chance.
Dr. Wu,
this Malaysian here
is only interested in you.
Of course he'll cherish even more
the chance to be alone with you.
Can't you just take the hint?
It think after the hotpot meal,
I've figured out
your relationship.
However, I feel
the uncle
doesn't know what's going on.
Not pointing out something you understand
is one of the most basic
moral standards in life.
Are you an immoral person?
Scram.
What?
Did I
miss anything?
Wait.
Your reactions are unusual.
Is something
going on between them?
-How is that possible?
-I'm not blind.
She doesn't have good taste in guys.
Something is happening.
Let's go.
How much is it?
It's fine.
Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
We should pay our own expenses.
Set up a group to receive payment.
Why are all of you leaving?
It's fine.
Come on.
Pay up. Wait.
Xiao Chu,
did you bring GoPro?
That's great.
Later,
when Zeng Li and I have a match,
we'll trouble you
to take more pictures of her
and a few videos.
She's a show-off.
I'm not.
Really?
Come on.
Tell me.
Back when I taught you how to ski,
didn't you tell me
to take more pictures of you
as well as videos?
You didn't learn it properly.
[So, her skiing skills]
[were also taught by Yu Yi.]
How can you say that?
You agreed to bring me
to the advanced ski trails.
In the end, shortly after you brought me
to learn at intermediate ski trails,
you left for the U.S.
Luckily I taught myself how to ski.
I came back now
to make it up to you.
Do you want have a match with me?
Sure. Bring it on.
Mr. Ai,
this person is so arrogant.
Both of us should teach him a lesson.
You two will go ahead and have a match.
I'll be the cameraman.
Then, let's go.
Go, go, go!
I finally got to ski this year.
Go!
Forget it. I'm not going.
You can't. Come on.
Stop wasting time.
It's all your fault.
When I first skied two years ago,
you brought me to intermediate ski trails.
I ended up falling so many times.
I am still traumatised.
How was it my fault?
I suggested to go to
the advanced ski trails.
You said something about
making a compromise
and going to intermediate ski trails.
Did you say those words?
It was my first time skiing.
How could you let me ski alone?
Woman,
you'll just affect my sword-drawing speed.
You know what?
I must go to the advanced
ski trails today.
Don't worry.
I'll go with you to the
beginners' ski trails.
Forget it.
I'll be a burden wherever I go.
I...
I'll swim.
When did you learn to swim?
That's not the point.
The point is
I bought a really beautiful
bikini.
What's wrong with you?
What kind of person wears a bikini
to swim in a hotel?
It's up to me.
♫ I mean, baby, I miss you ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I love you ♫
♫ For you, get online 24/7 ♫
♫ I almost said it ♫
♫ Tough my photo ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I miss you ♫
Play at your full capacity.
Don't blame me later.
♫ I mean, baby, I love you ♫
♫ My heart has been beating
fast for a long time ♫
Let's go!
♫ Calling for a doctor ♫
Let's speed up, Mr. Ai.
♫ Waiting for you ♫
♫ Thinking about the future ♫
♫ A nonchalant greeting ♫
♫ Why do I lose composure
when it comes to you ♫
♫ Linguistic skills become nonsensical ♫
♫ Fortunately, with
the blessing of acting skills ♫
♫ Appear to be calm, when in fact
my heart is beating wildly inside ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I miss you ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I love you ♫
♫ For you, online 24/7 ♫
♫ I almost said it ♫
♫ Touch my photo ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I miss you ♫
♫ I mean, baby, I love you ♫
♫ My heart has been
beating fast for a long time ♫
♫ Calling a doctor ♫
Mr. Ai is really good at this.
♫ Waiting for you ♫
Why are you skiing at such a high speed?
Here I come!
Zeng Li, look out, ahead of you!
♫ Oh, we are lucky ♫
♫ A heartthrob ahead ♫
♫ Induction wave is sped up ♫
Yu Yi!
Don't touch him.
Moving him will make his injuries
even more serious.
What should we do?
Yu Yi, can you hear me?
What should we do, Mr. Ai?
Yu Yi!
He's awake.
Mr. Ai, Yu Yi is awake.
How are you feeling?
My back hurts.
Your back hurts?
My legs feel a little numb.
His back and legs are a little numb.
He might've hurt his spine.
Will I become paralysed?
Paralysed?
No way.
Wait here.
I'll make a call.
What do I do?
There's no signal.
Yu Yi,
Which part hurts? Tell me.
Yu Yi!
Wake up, Yu Yi!
Yu Yi, can you hear me?
Why is there no signal?
Yu Yi, answer me.
Yu Yi!
I was playing with you.
Look, I'm fine.
You're fine?
Yes.
You almost scared me to death.
It was a joke.
Come on, don't be angry.
Look.
I'm fine.
Xiao Chu told me
there're some problems with my spine.
I just want to use it
to play a joke on you.
All right.
Don't cry.
Don't be angry if you're not crying,
okay?
Don't be angry.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're fine.
Go for another check up when we go back.
It's not too bad.
I'm fine.
She's really too adorable.
Before that, when I took
her on a rowing trip,
I fell into the water.
It was also a lie,
but she wouldn't stop crying.
It was really funny,
just like what's happening now.
I didn't cry.
How dare you say that.
It's filled with water.
You purposely threw those pails
into the water.
I really thought you fell into the water.
Look, isn't she really silly
and cute that way?
You're always saying you're 30 years old.
Why haven't you changed at all?
Don't be angry.
Be careful.
Come in.
Why don't we play downstairs?
We'd better not.
If the two of them come back
and see me playing games,
they'll say a middle-aged lady like me
is always playing video games.
You are not a middle-aged lady.
You're like a younger sister.
Come on in.
It's not like I'm going to bite.
Come in.
Close the door.
You look
like an elementary school student
being scolded by your
disciplinary teacher.
This is my first time
entering a girl's room,
other than my sister's.
Then treat me as your sister.
Well,
that won't do.
You're different from my sister.
You're...
What am I?
You're one whom I'll marry in the future.
Come over.
What do you mean?
I bought you a new phone.
Also, you can have this bank card.
Two months ago,
you were grumbling about
switching mobile phones.
You still haven't bought one.
All the money was spent
on buying the bag, right?
There's a balance of over RMB1,000.
The password is your birthday.
Didn't I throw away the receipt?
How did you return it?
There're only two Chanel
boutiques in Donghu.
One of them is near Donghu University
and the other is over 20 kilometres away.
It wasn't difficult to check
the purchase record.
I finally
bought you a gift.
How could you return it?
That's how I'm
different from others.
Other girls
like branded bags.
As for me,
I like stars.
It's the new gaming season.
I want you to use your mobile phone
to play Honour of Kings with me.
I don't need a new mobile phone.
Even with my old mobile phone, I can still
guide you in Honour of Kings.
Later, we'll return it
and buy the bag for you again.
I threw away the receipt.
Then I'll go to the store to check
the purchase record.
Sorry.
I bought it online.
It can't be returned
if it's bought online.
Deng Hao Ran, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Shouldn't you be skiing?
Why are you sitting here?
Look what's going on over there.
My sister,
Yu Yi
and Ai Jing Chu
is a classic love triangle.
If I go over,
won't I feel embarrassed?
What's wrong?
Do you think
you're welcomed here?
I don't care.
I wonder who said this.
"This week, I'm your debtor
and so on and so forth."
Didn't you say that?
Fine.
Lie down.
Get up. Let's swim.
I don't know how to swim.
I don't know how to.
One more round.
Stop splashing water.
Let's go.
Keep going.
Come on, one more round.
No more.
The last round.
Well,
did they
sense anything?
It doesn't matter.
We broke up so long ago.
It's fine.
Of course it's fine with you.
I'm so beautiful.
If they find out,
they're going to say,
"You must've been blind.
What did you see in him?"
I was the one who was blind.
Besides,
my sister is definitely on my side.
She'll definitely feel that
her brother is too good for you.
Luckily I was blind for a while
instead of forever.
I came to my senses just in time.
I came to my sense
very quickly, okay?
I broke up with you.
Deng Hao Ran,
do you still have feelings for me?
Why do
all your girlfriends after that
resemble me?
Ma Yi Yi,
why do I feel that
you're still thinking about me?
After all,
none of your boyfriends after that
is as good as me.
One is worse than the other.
I...
There's no way I'm still thinking of you.
No way.
You're thinking of me.
You're so annoying!
Yi Yi,
where's your mysterious boyfriend?
You've been keeping him
as a secret for so long.
Oh, right.
We'll also be exchanging gifts,
right?
Ma Yi Yi,
yours is cooked.
Come on, hurry.
It'll be overcooked later.
Let's take a photo.
I'm going to take a group selfie.
Three, two, one!
Stop taking. Eat.
I'm not good with my chopsticks.
What are you doing?
No.
We finally secured a series A round.
Didn't we agree to drink
to our hearts' content?
Yes.
Isn't this...
I can't drink anymore.
I'm going to be drunk if I keep drinking.
My girlfriend's class will be over soon.
I have to pick her up.
Come on.
Didn't you and Ma Yi Yi
already break up?
We broke up.
[Ma Yi Yi, I'm so happy tonight.]
[Deng Hao Ran, you're bad.]
[We broke up]
[and you really stopped talking to me.]
[Ma Yi Yi, I'm so happy tonight.]
[Ma Yi Yi,]
[when you broke up]
[with someone unreliable like me,]
[you'll finally be happy.]
[Do you honestly]
[not care about me anymore?]
Should I save you or not?
You're really charming!
Deng Hao Ran,
why do I feel so happy
when I play with you?
I won again.
Deng Hao Ran,
you're really useless!
Look, this is not bad.
Seems great.
Zeng Li!
Come on, let's give it a try.
Coming.
Let's play a game.
Sure.
Wait a second.
Have you played this game before?
I ever.
When I was abroad,
I heard it's Never Have I Ever.
It's improvised in China.
Let me tell you the game's rules.
Sure.
For example, I'll suggest an action.
If you've done it before,
you'll raise your hand with me.
The rest who have never done it
will have to drink
and the two of us won't have to.
If I'm the only one
who raise my hand
and all of you have never done it,
I'll need to drink.
The rules are very simple, right?
Let's begin.
You two,
we're playing a game.
Okay.
We're not playing anymore. We'll stop.
I'm leaving the game.
I'll start.
I read a book,
The Commuter Pig Keeper.
Girl, are you going to keep pigs?
That's not it.
Sister,
you'll end up drinking.
Who will read this kind of book?
Don't be so sure about that.
You've read it before?
I have.
Are you still reading
two hours a day?
Of course.
Has Mr. Ai been this disciplined
since his university days?
I have to learn from you.
Come on, drink.
Drink.
Let's raise our glasses
to the future pig farm owner!
Come on, cheers.
To the future pig farm owner.
My turn.
I stayed up until 3am
to play games.
You're so admirable.
What game did you play?
Monopoly.
You go to bed on time.
Why did you raise your hand?
Which day was it?
Why do you always play on your own
and never ask me to join?
Take a look
at this fake friendship.
It's none of your business.
All right, that's enough.
I lost. I'll drink.
Okay. That's enough.
Stop drinking.
Come on, wipe your mouth.
So it's my turn, right?
Let me think.
The person I like is here with us today.
Can you say something
we don't know?
That's really lame, you know?
We're playing
I ever.
You can say something like
the person you once liked
is here with us today.
Let me think.
So, be it in the past,
now
and future,
I'm in love with this person.
I'm going to vomit.
Why am I the only one raising my hand?
Is no one else going
to raise his or her hand?
I raised mine.
The love rival has taken actions.
You can't lose to him.
Zeng Li,
if you once liked this person,
it also counts.
You...
Deng Hao Ran,
aren't you going to raise your hand?
I...
Why should I?
This afternoon,
when we were having hotpot,
didn't you say
I was your debtor for a week,
and you'd be in love with me for a week,
right?
Fine.
You'll have to raise yours as well.
I have to be in love with you.
Can't you just
be in love with me
even if it's pretending?
That's not convincing at all.
You...
You finally admit that
you're in love with me?
No.
I like Deng Hao Ran.
What?
Impossible. You...
You...
He's not the type of man you like.
What's wrong with my type?
I...
I'm rich.
What time is it now?
Talent.
Dr. Ai,
everyone else has raised his or her hand.
You have to drink.
Drink.
He's drunk.
Mobile phone.
Take a photo.
Take his photo.
Take a video.
From here. Take it from below.
Where?
Take it from below.
That's a good angle.
That's right.
Should we be taking a video
of him when he's drunk?
Yu Yi,
flick his double chin.
You have to film this from below.
Goodness.
Why did he have so many drinks
if he had low alcohol tolerance?
I'll get going.
Don't worry.
Mr. Ai.
Wake up.
Stop pretending. He's gone.
Who did you raise your hand for?
Mr. Ai.
You finally figured it out.
No.
My mind was a mess just now.
So I raised my hand with everyone else.
I really wanted to see
Mr. Ai's reaction
and whether he'd overthink
or get jealous.
I only realised then
that the person I liked
was Mr. Ai.
That's right.
Just now, Mr. Ai
also raised his hand for you.
He was probably drunk.
Look.
He passed out right after
he raised his hand.
I think he was pretending.
Think about it.
Just now, Yu Yi was also present.
It'll be awkward between the two of them.
No way.
Mr. Ai doesn't seem
to be that type of person.
Do you think
he's capable of doing the stuff
he did for you in the past?
Do you mean he also likes me?
Of course.
The way Mr. Ai looks at you
is a man who's hopelessly in love.
That's how he looks like.
Are you going to keep laughing now?
Laugh all you want.
I'm going to take a bath.
It seems you're not going to
stop laughing anytime soon.
Unexpectedly, Mr. Ai,
you're quite cunning
during critical moments.
I'm really a little drunk.
Really?
You should have raised your hand earlier.
Look at Sister Zeng Li.
She's a female,
yet she raised her hand
earlier than you did.
Well,
what if she raised her hand
because of Yu Yi?
Are you jealous?
No.
You're still denying.
You refused to raise your hand
because you thought
Sister Zeng Li did so
because of Yu Yi, right?
No.
Yu Yi is a good friend of mine.
Zeng Li got to know him earlier.
There's no reason for me to be jealous.
Nor should I be jealous.
Mr. Ai,
just face your own feelings
with honesty.
Yes,
you're close to Yu Yi.
However,
if Sister Zeng Li likes
you,
it will be meaningless
for you to give in.
What if
Zeng Li likes him?
It's just a speculation.
If my best friends
and I
fell in love with the same woman,
I'd tell him honestly
instead of keeping it myself.
Let the girl choose.
This way, no matter what the outcome is,
at least it's fair
for everyone.
Wu Ying, are you asleep?
Wait!
[It's the easiest to get her to
confess her feelings in this state.]
[I must help Mr. Ai]
[to get an answer.]
[Who does Sister Zeng Li like?]
I'd been waiting for you.
You're finally here.
Were you waiting for me?
You've had so many drinks.
Why are you still playing games?
They scolded me.
Who scolded you?
My teammates.
They said I kept taking
others' heads in the game.
Look.
You're drunk.
Come on, go to bed.
I'm not drunk.
Why is the door of Mr. Ai's room
opened?
Mr. Ai. Liu Yu Cheng.
Are you asleep?
Liu Yu Cheng,
are you asleep?
Why didn't these two close
their door before they sleep?
Did they leave their room?
They're really drunk
to have left their door open.
Liu Yu Cheng
only thinks about Wu Ying.
He doesn't even have the time
to tuck you in.
You only know how to
criticise me everyday.
You're also the same,
going to sleep without
brushing your teeth.
Let me turn off the lights for you.
I just wanted to
turn off the lights for you.