[English subtitles are available]
[Love Under The Full Moon]
[Episode 16]
[Yao Yang Tech]
I'm working overtime now.
Yes.
About a month.
I promise I'll get it done.
Don't worry, Mr Wang.
Alright, bye.
[Xu Xiao Dong]
Hello?
Xu Xiao Dong.
You were in my office.
What?
You want to talk to me?
Sorry,
I don't have time.
Also,
you're fired.
Stop harassing me.
Crazy man.
How did you get in?
I walked in.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Mr Zhao,
don't you think it's a bit rude to
hang up on me like that?
Xu Xiao Dong,
if you have a problem
with the company's decision
to dismiss you,
you can get a lawyer.
But let me warn you,
if you are coming in here to cause trouble,
you've come to the wrong place.
Please get out,
or I'll call the cops now.
Mr Zhao,
calm down, calm down.
I came here for no other reason than
to talk to you about
the company's
product development.
You see,
Yao Yang Tech
is such a big company,
it wasn't easy to get in.
Let me just grab my phone.
Oh right, Mr Zhao,
I have a question for you.
About
changing the author's prefatory note,
changing underlying protocol,
removing the author's signature,
and then marking these as
your own open-source work,
is that considered plagiarism?
I don't have time
for this nonsense.
Are you leaving or not?
Zhao Yao Yang,
the stuff in that room.
I believe you don't want
others to find out, right?
With just a tap on my phone,
all the major websites,
all the media
will learn
your dirty little secret.
You're a businessman.
I believe
you wouldn't let your hard work
go down the drain.
Even if you manage to grab the phone,
do you think you'll be okay?
Fine,
Xu Xiao Dong,
you are something.
Go on, tell me what you want.
The one who was accused of plagiarism
after you stole
the patent for
his research and development, Xu Wei Yi,
do you remember him?
I don't know Xu Wei Yi.
The person who framed Xu Wei Yi,
please tell me
who else could it be but you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You fired me
because you found out that
Xu Wei Yi is my father.
I told you.
Wasn't it?
I don't know Xu Wei Yi!
I can give you anything you want.
You have 24 hours.
I'll be waiting for you to tell me the truth
about what happened back then.
[Zhao Yao Yang]
Hello.
[Mr Wei,]
[it's me.]
You were right.
I underestimated Xu Xiao Dong.
[The plagiarized code]
[of Family First that I gave you before]
[can't be used anymore.]
[I'm afraid the truth about ten years ago]
[can no longer stay buried.]
Isn't it too late
to shirk responsibility now?
Send some men to get Zhao Yao Yang.
Meanwhile, keep a close watch on Xu Xiao Dong
and
Lei Chu Xia.
Xiao Dong,
are you sure it's a good idea
to confront him openly like that?
You've been investigating in secret for ten years,
and you exposed yourself now
without having any hard evidence,
what if you alert them?
Zhao Yao Yang already knows
that I am Xu Wei Yi's son.
If I keep hiding,
I would only get stuck in a dead-end.
It's time to go head to head with him.
You're doing this
because of Chu Xia, aren't you?
You want to find out the truth quickly,
and to prove Chu Xia is innocent at the same time.
I've always believed Chu Xia,
okay?
Really?
That's enough.
I've started tracking
Zhao Yao Yang with Turing.
As soon as Zhao Yao Yang makes a move,
I'll be able to follow the trail
to catch the people behind him.
Mr Wei,
we didn't find anything
in Xu Xiao Dong's house.
But we got something
on Mr Zhao Yao Yang's side.
Xu Xiao Dong went to Yao Yang Tech
to cause trouble with Mr Zhao.
And he has been gathering information about
the relationship between you and Zhao Yao Yang.
You're saying that
Xu Xiao Dong not only suspected Zhao Yao Yang,
he's also suspecting me,
who has been in contact with Zhao Yao Yang?
Yes.
Have you reached Zhao Yao Yang?
Mr Zhao
has become uncontactable.
[Sorry,]
[the number you dialled]
[is not available at the moment.]
[Please try again later.]
Zhao Yao Yang,
do you really think you can hide from me?
24 hours have passed,
and Zhao Yao Yang hasn't replied yet.
Looks like he's determined to
hide until the matter goes away.
This is a villa that
[Most Expensive Foreclosed Property in 2011]
Zhao Yao Yang bought in the name of others
ten years ago.
It's not on his property inventory,
that's why I didn't find out.
Fortunately, history always leaves a trail behind.
By the way,
don't tell Chu Xia.
Why?
I have a feeling that
I've been followed lately.
My house was broken into.
I've been watching Zhao Yao Yang
too closely,
someone must've found out.
I don't want to get Chu Xia involved.
You can tell her directly.
Do you think after I tell her,
she won't get worried anymore?
After all, it's my father's business,
which makes it mine too.
I want to take care of it myself.
Okay.
This is the place they're coming to.
Jin Xiao Rui doesn't dare
to lie to me now.
Are you really not going
to tell Xu Xiao Dong?
He didn't want me to come,
it must be because he didn't want me
to put myself in danger.
But this is a matter
of my innocence.
I have to take care of it myself.
Come on, let's go and take a look.
Hour maids are not allowed in.
Have you ever seen any hour maids
dressed like this?
You're not hour maids.
All the more reason you can't go in.
If something happens,
who will take responsibility?
Open your eyes and look at us.
Do we look like bad guys?
Why are they allowed
to drive in?
Look at
the brand of car they drive.
So what if they have a car?
So what if they are rich?
Just because he's rich,
does it mean he's not a scammer
or a bad guy?
I didn't mean to tell her.
Yuan Yuan grabbed my phone.
Just go.
You're unbelievable.
Excuse me,
they are
our hour maids.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry, girls.
Please.
What are you waiting for, hour maids?
Ouch, ouch.
[No. 189, 5A]
No. 189, 5A.
This is Zhao Yao Yang's
foreclosed villa.
I just walked around.
The environment around
is really nice.
Looks like Zhao Yao Yang
definitely makes a lot of money.
I've set up
a motion capture system.
Whenever there is movement in his house,
it will alert us.
That's brilliant, Xiao Dong.
We won't have to bother
with surveillance.
Are you upset?
No.
I just suddenly
thought about my dad.
He used to
like to sit under an old tree too.
He told me that
when he shared all his happiness
with the tree,
he would gain strength;
when he shared all his unhappiness
with the tree,
all his worries would be gone.
This is who he is.
He likes to
keep everything to himself.
Every time I hear you talk about your dad,
I can feel that
he is a good father.
You know,
I have
a game console that I grew up playing with.
My dad
carved some words on it for me.
What are those words?
To Xiao Dong,
my son.
But at that time,
I was rebellious and immature.
I always caused him trouble.
So I made up my mind
to find out the truth
and clear his name.
I think
as long as you don't lose
the courage to face everything,
any difficulty
can be defeated.
Why does it
sound so familiar?
The
old fairy lady
said the same thing before.
She said something similar
to encourage me.
You mean the person you told me about last time?
Are you still in touch with her?
No.
Ten years have passed.
I've lost touch with her a long time ago.
Besides, I didn't see clearly
what she looked like.
I think even if we stand together now,
face to face,
we still won't recognize each other.
There are quite a lot of stars tonight.
I guess we'll have fine weather tomorrow.
Oh right, have you heard?
A comet named Neo
will pass by
Earth soon.
Experts say that
if we miss it this time,
it'll only come again
6,000 years from now.
That sounds romantic.
There must be something special on Earth
that it cares about,
that is why it has to come back
to Earth again after 6,000 years.
It's just a cosmic phenomenon.
There are also many comets
that pass through the solar system
once and never return.
Simply passing by and going into
the depths of the universe.
This is just
the trajectory of the comet.
You know nothing.
This is
the trajectory of love.
No way.
Could that be the comet
you were just talking about?
It could be.
Make a wish, make a wish.
I don't care.
Make a wish first, make a wish first.
Hurry.
Sorry.
Did I interrupt you?
Sorry for interrupting.
No, no.
You didn't interrupt anything.
You have a flashlight.
I need to use the bathroom.
You carry on.
Let's go.
Are you seriously using me as a third wheel?
What...
Oh, Xu Xiao Dong,
serve you right.
Now you know how it feels to get interrupted.
You even lit a small lamp.
That's quite romantic.
It's to keep away mosquitoes.
Keep away mosquitoes?
Wait up.
Chu Xia,
there are a lot of mosquitoes inside, look.
Check if there's any mosquito spray
in the bag.
What should I do?
Mosquito spray.
Let me see if they have brought it.
What is this?
I didn't find any mosquito spray,
but I found two bottles of pepper spray.
Jin Xiao Rui!
Jin Xiao Rui.
What's wrong?
Why did you bring
pepper spray?
What's wrong with pepper spray?
Boys need to
protect themselves too.
Are you going to eat me?
Jin Xiao Rui, you're so gross.
How can you be so shameless?
What are you doing?
There are a lot of mosquitoes inside.
I'm sacrificing myself to feed the mosquitoes.
So that mosquitoes
won't bite Yuan Yuan.
Is there any scientific basis for this?
It'll work if you believe in it.
It'll work if I believe in it?
Is there any scientific basis for this?
It'll work if you believe in it.
Xiao Dong,
tell me,
does this count as we are offering blood?
What are you talking about?
We are offering love.
What's wrong with your hand?
Nothing.
How are you feeling?
Did you sleep well last night?
It was alright.
Zhao Yao Yang showed up.
Let's go.
Mr Zhao.
Are you
the assistant of Mr Wei?
What are you doing here?
Mr Wei would like to
talk to you alone.
Please come with me.
I've said everything I needed to.
You guys should go.
I'm sorry for this then.
What's going on?
Seize him!
Let's go.
Come on.
Stop!
Let's go.
-Stop!
-Stop there!
Stop!
I didn't expect
you'd be the one who saved me.
Thank you.
Save your thanks.
I need to ask you about something.
Did I steal the
patent certificate for you back then?
You?
Plus the memorial service,
this is only the second time I met you.
How could it be you?
Who was it then?
Are you still not going
to tell the truth?
Fine.
For the sake that
you saved me today,
I'll tell you.
It was
a woman named Gu Xiao Qi.
Gu Xiao Qi?
Do you know her?
She was my dad's secretary.
His right-hand-woman in the company.
Why would a right-hand woman do that?
About this,
you will have to
ask Wei Xuan He.
He will tell you everything.
Wei Xuan He?
Let me see.
So much blood.
We're going to the hospital.
Come on.
Doctor,
isn't his wound a little deep?
It's fine, it's just a minor injury.
It's nothing serious.
What do you mean by nothing serious?
Your wound
requires at least twelve stitches.
And you need a tetanus shot.
You're being dramatic.
It's not necessary.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
What do you mean "not necessary?”
Come, get ready for suturing.
Sorry, Mr Wei.
We lost Zhao Yao Yang.
And we saw
Lei Chu Xia and Xu Xiao Dong.
We can't find out
their whereabouts now.
A bunch of losers.
Scram!
Did you not hear what I said?
I said scram.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Who is Gu Xiao Qi?
You met Zhao Yao Yang, didn't you?
Nothing he said was true.
But Gu Xiao Qi is real, isn't it?
You're still lying to me at this point.
You were the one who colluded with other people
and stole the patent certificate.
Yet you're pinning it on me now.
Was there anything
you said that was true?
You still don't trust me.
Why do you always
take sides against me?
You are still doing that even now.
Is it hard to tell the truth?
What is the truth?
What is the evidence?
Do you have any evidence?
If you don't,
then there is no truth.
[Cyber Tech]
Yuan Yuan.
Chu Xia, where are you?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I came here to see Wei Xuan He.
All the leads are gone.
Did Wei Xuan He
tell you anything?
I only know there was a girl
named Gu Xiao Qi.
Gu Xiao Qi?
What?
Do you know her?
Not only do I know her,
you know her too.
[I know Gu Xiao Qi too?]
[Who is she?]
[Where will]
[fate lead me to this time?]
This is the machine that
can make Lei Chu Xia disappear?
At least I managed
to bring Lei Chu Xia
back to this dimension last time.
If I want her to disappear again,
can you do that?
The machine has some problems now.
I need some time.
Also,
the bracelet Professor Chen gave her
has stabilized
her magnetic field in this dimension.
I can no longer control
the energy in her from a distance.
I can give you time.
You just need to fix this.
I'll take care of
the rest.
It's a deal.
Mr Wei,
I think there's something you should know.
Without
Professor Chen's bracelet,
I can't ensure that Lei Chu Xia
will return to her original dimension,
and there is a possibility that
she will dissipate into the universe.
You don't need to worry about that.
We'll leave it to the universe.
[Chu Xia,]
[you leave me no choice.]
Haven't I already seen all of these?
No, I'm asking you to look at these.
Do you remember
the last time you
saw these pictures, you asked me
why was a part of this photo cut off?
Yes.
Because the person who was cut out
is Gu Xiao Qi.
The three of us were good friends
for four years in college.
And in those four years,
you and her were close.
After graduation,
you two
shared a place for a while.
Why haven't you mentioned this before?
There was a time
when you two
were pretty close.
However,
before you went missing,
every time she was mentioned,
you would become upset.
Until you disappeared,
she never showed up
nor asked about you.
What kind of good friend was she?
So I just cut her out of the photo.
Keep her
out of your world.
Now that you've lost your memory,
there's no need to
remember this person who upset you.
Besides, over the past ten years,
I've never seen
Gu Xiao Qi.
And I have no idea what she is doing now.
Isn't this the case with
most college friends?
Losing touch after graduation.
Never heard from her since.
Just disappear.
And I don't care.
Gu Xiao Qi was my dad's secretary.
My dad trusted her so much that
she had every chance
to get her hands on the patent certificate.
Why would she help Wei Xuan He?
And how did
the patent certificate end up in your house?
Wei Xuan He told me that
that day before I went missing ten years ago,
I went to your house
and Uncle Xu's company.
My house
and my dad's company?
[Wei Yi Tech forced by investors for rights protection]
[Stop, stop.]
[Please stop taking photos.]
[Quiet down.]
This video is real.
But I'm certain that
before we met,
I had no memory of you at all.
Let's go find Gu Xiao Qi.
Excuse me,
do you know a person
named Gu Xiao Qi,
who lives around here?
Gu Xiao Qi?
Yes.
Do you know?
Gu Xiao Qi?
Isn't that Gu's youngest daughter?
Oh, yes, yes.
She died in a car accident eight years ago.
She died?
At such a young age.
That's such a pity.
That's right.
Such a pity.
We're at a dead end now.
Let's go.
Come back.
Why don't I just stay at your place tonight?
Let's discuss it.
Sure.
[Moonlit Flats]
♫ One word from you ♫
♫ and everything's good ♫
♫ That's all I ask you ♫
♫ No need to be true ♫
♫ You are my pursuit ♫
♫ If only ♫
♫ I could show you ♫
♫ All you need to care about is you ♫
♫ Take you step by step ♫
♫ Hold you hand in hand ♫
♫ Gonna protect you ♫
♫ like a man ♫
This is weird.
I lived with Chu Xia
like this before,
why do I suddenly
feel so awkward now?
Xiao Dong, I...
He falls asleep?
I can see your eyelids moving.
What do you want?
I think I got a new clue.
I travelled back
ten years ago last time, right?
Then I found
the patent certificate at my house.
Why don't
we go back again tomorrow?
Maybe we'll find a new lead.
This is all you wanted to talk about?
Sure.
Okay.
Okay?
But wouldn't we be
a bit too...
Go to sleep.
This one.
The air seems to be filled with
pink bubbles.
What do you mean by pink bubbles?
Are you stupid?
Let me wash it for you first.
I don't mind, hey...
Help me...
I'll help.
I'll help. I'll help. I'll help.
What's going on with Xu Xiao Dong?
Why is he acting strangely?
I can't do it, I can't do it.
Why can't you do it?
Xiao Rui,
we were living together too
before, right?
But after my love confession,
now that we are living together again,
I just have this
awkward feeling, why is that?
Did anything happen between you two?
Nothing.
You really can't do it then.
Does this have something to do
with my rejection last time?
But I know in my heart that I like him.
That's right.
Lei Chu Xia,
have you ever heard a saying?
You may get a moment of pleasure from hurting your man,
but now you'll need to grovel to win him back.
So,
for the sake of your love,
be brave and get him back.
Until I know
how she really feels about me,
I think
we should keep our distance.
So can you do it or not?
[Moonlit Flats]
[Today's promotion, Rainbow Cake]
How did it go?
Any luck
last night?
How's that possible?
A man and a woman being alone in the same house.
As long as you show concern for him,
take good care of him,
everything should've worked out naturally.
How come it didn't work out naturally
for you?
It didn't work out.
I got it.
To deal with an IT geek,
you need to do it in a way that
he can understand.
Play it straight.
Confess directly.
Confess directly?
You can do it.
I like you.
Confess directly.
[I like you]
Say something.
Xiao Dong,
I made you a cake.
Do you want to come over and take a look at it?
I'm almost done.
Give me a minute.
Xiao Dong,
Chu Xia wrote what she wanted to tell you
on the cake.
I'll be right over.
Yuan Yuan.
What are you doing here?
Chu Xia, this cake is so good.
I'm starving.
You owe me?
[I owe you]
You owe me
more than a cake.
What did she owe you?
Ask her.
I owe you, I owe you.
It's not for you.
Why are you so starving?
What do you think?
Don't you think it's too corny?
You've confessed in a western way,
you've tried that,
but did he get it?
He didn't get it at all.
If he doesn't get it,
after
you use such a direct way,
then he's just an idiot.
Yuan Yuan,
miss me?
Why did you have to mess it up?
Blow it.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Please let me out.
What are you doing?
Stop, stop, stop.
Are you going to say it or not?
I really didn't know
you were trying to confess.
We've exhausted
all methods now.
Tell me what more we can do.
You could ask me.
Honestly,
among the four of us,
I have the most experience
when it comes to relationships.
Listen, Chu Xia,
if you want him to accept your love confession,
you need to cater to his liking.
Cater to his liking?
What does he like?
Tickets to technology fair.
[The Future of High-Tech Artificial Intelligence, Technology Fair]
Xiao Dong's favourite.
I was going to save it for myself
for when I want to beg Xiao Dong for something.
I'll let you have it now.
This is something.
What did you just say?
You have the most experience when it comes to relationships?
How many girlfriends
have you had before me?
Hang in there.
Chu Xia!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You've been acting weird today.
You didn't do something wrong,
did you?
No.
What could I possibly do wrong?
I just went through
the tragedy of
filling with regrets after I hurt someone
for a moment of pleasure.
What does that mean?
Doesn't matter.
My friend gave me two tickets
[The Future of High-Tech Artificial Intelligence, Technology Fair]
to some kind of technology fair.
I don't really know much about this
future intelligent high-tech stuff.
Are you interested?
Of course I'm interested.
I've always wanted to go to a technology fair.
And there are two tickets here.
I can go with Jin Xiao Rui.
You can't take it back.
You've given it to me.
I won't take it back, I won't take it back.
But how do you know
if Jin Xiao Rui wants to go?
Maybe he has a date with
Yuan Yuan.
If he doesn't want to go,
I'll force him.
What's so hard about that?
[Moonlit Flats]
You can't take it back.
Qin Yue.
Xiao Dong.
What are you doing here?
Xiao Dong,
I heard you lost your job again.
I found a new job for you.
It's a low-level post,
but I've taken care of everything for you.
You just need to go to the interview
for the sake of formality.
You don't have to worry about
my job.
I'll take care of it myself.
Is that
what you came here for?
I need to talk to Lei Chu Xia.
Go back first.
Be careful.
Alright, I got it.
Go on, go on.