[ Last Episode ]
Excuse me.
Are you Kim Hye-yoon
in Journalism and Communication?
I'm Yeo Jun,
a freshman in business administration.
Yeo Jun? Yes, I've heard of you.
There's something we'd like to ask.
So could you spare us some time?
Sure. Let's hear it.
[ Why Kim Hye-yoon though? ]
She reminds me of you when we first met.
- What?
- Is she a psycho too?
I mean, is she a unique soul as well?
Did she agree to it?
She's like to know the concept first.
The concept will be a bright
and vibrant youth.
Would displaying a fantasy work?
It'll only seem unrealistic.
I also agree that
it should be more realistic.
So you want to go for hyperrealism?
This is a PR video, not a documentary.
Tough reality isn't what
we wish to see in ad campaigns.
That could be true for a commercial ad.
We'd be right to only highlight
the joy of youth.
But this is a school assignment.
Must it be dark and heavy though?
Let's be mindful
of Professor Park's lessons.
Would highlighting
the positive side of youth
speak out to him?
It only has to be fun
and exude positive energy.
There's no need to consider
the professor's preference.
But our grades are on the line.
Although as a freshman,
you probably wouldn't care.
What does being a freshman
have to do with this?
Team leader is right, you know.
As you all know,
I tanked my last group assignment.
I need a good score to make up for it.
Me too.
Still. What's fun to do
leads to a good outcome.
I see we can't get on the same page.
Well, I have a class to get to.
I'll be home late after my shift.
I won't be home anyway.
Is something up between you and Soo-hyun?
No, we're as good as ever.
Jun, you should reconsider
Soo-hyun's opinion.
Wait. Didn't you take my side earlier?
Of course, I'm on your side.
But...
I also think it's better
to have it reflect our reality
and not just the positive sides.
Even in my case,
I'm only happy when I'm with you.
My life's dark too. Actually,
that's how it used to be.
But wouldn't we want
to only remember happy memories
when we look back on this time?
But the one in pain is still you as well.
I'd rather discard him somewhere.
I'll then pick him up
and carry him around in my pocket.
Won't it be uncomfortable at home
with Soo-hyun?
You know I don't let things get to me.
Besides, Soo-hyun may be prickly,
but he's not one to stay angry.
You should go first.
No, you go ahead.
I'm not that desperate, you know.
- Me neither.
- Elders first.
It doesn't extend to peeing.
Right. Since I'm younger,
I'll go first then.
No.
I'll go first.
Just so you know, I really need to go.
I'm craving a late-night snack.
Maybe pizza? Or fried chicken?
Tteokbokki?
Gosh, this looks good.
I wonder how far the smell will travel.
It's too much for just one person.
I guess I have no choice.
I'll throw it away.
What? This is just for me.
It's only one portion.
One portion?
People just love to waste food.
Have some.
If there weren't any food,
you'd pretend to be asleep.
Why are you worked up over the assignment?
I'm not.
Is it the assignment
or are there hard feelings toward me?
I'm against
that dark concept you suggested.
It's weird that you're
this invested in it.
I guess that's true.
But aren't you sick of it?
It's been hard enough for us.
Why must the assignment--
We should view reality as it is.
Can't we escape it though?
Once we run away from it,
we'll one day see that we escaped it.
One should try to overcome hardships.
I don't want to do it right now though.
Will putting it off make it any better?
It could.
As your senior, I know--
You're playing the age card?
- You're a freshman--
- As if that matters,
old man.
Some people can't escape reality
even if they want to.
We're already on an edge of a cliff.
Are you challenging me
to see who has it worse?
- Should we do it?
- Bring it on!
What's with you two today?
What do you mean?
Do I perhaps look more handsome?
What a narcissist.
What did you just call me?
More you than me though.
Don't tell me you argued all night.
Or maybe you drank all night without me.
All night,
we had tteokbokki.
Tteokbokki?
Hey, Koo-hyun.
With his brother,
he's always the sweetest.
Are you jealous?
As if.
We just don't click.
They say that marital disputes
never last long.
Marital?
Gross!
Why is my ear so itchy?
Someone must be talking smack about you.
So be nicer--
Why are you here
when you're probably busy studying?
What's the gift?
My gift? It's me!
Jeez.
I hope you didn't spend too much.
I didn't.
Here.
Mom sent it by post
and told me to hand it to you.
What is it?
Dad's journal.
- But why--
- Mom said
you wanted to be a cop just like Dad.
I had no idea.
You work shift after shift just so that
you can fund whatever dream I have.
Why did she tell you that
when it was way in the past?
Soo-hyun, don't send money
for my rent or Mom to spend.
You even paid back Dad's debt.
Why are you saying this?
- I'm fine.
- Well, I'm not.
You should do what you want as well.
- Koo-hyun--
- I'm an adult now.
You made sure
I grew up with a pretty face.
Want to send me to an orphanage now?
Okay, here we go.
Don't just stand there like that.
Salute to the camera.
[ Nam Yun-woo ]
Yes, looking good.
I'll take it now in one, two, three.
All right.
[ Nam Yun-woo ]
Let's take a look.
Look.
You look amazing!
Gosh, when did you get so big?
In a few years,
we'll be in matching uniforms.
Sure thing.
We'll then take a grand photo together.
Why don't we hang it up on this wall?
[ Nam Yun-woo ]
Where did Ms. Seol go?
She's been taking a lot of time off
since she's quitting soon.
Who's quitting?
Didn't you know?
She's getting married soon.
She's getting married?
With whom?
Her boyfriend I guess.
I hear he's younger than her.
Anyway, I hope you show me a favor.
With what?
Once she leaves, I thought...
You think you'll take her place?
Of course.
Who else could possibly assist you?
- Not you.
- Sorry?
I don't know what you'd lie about next.
What do you mean?
You know exactly what I mean.
What's this? I don't see a name.
Oh, it's mine.
Please utilize it however you want.
But that--
Lies only lead to more lies.
If that's how you get by in life,
it'll stick with you.
Change your ways before it's too late.
[ Father ]
You should head in.
I'll need to take this call first.
There's nothing going on, right?
No, so don't worry.
Right.
Yes, Father.
[ 2021 Myungil University Student Body ]
Soo-hyun, can we talk?
We're late for our team gathering.
It won't matter if we're late.
We made a promise with our teammates,
so of course, it matters.
- You want to blend both concepts?
- Yes.
Darkness will be a character
representing the dark sides of youth
while Light will represent its beauty.
We’ll have Darkness
realizing the light within it
after meeting Light
who lives in a completely different world.
What do you say?
We're out of time, so let's do that--
Then we should all tell our stories.
Regarding the light and shadow of youth.
It's our team project,
so it should be about us.
- While sober?
- My life only knows darkness.
I have nothing to add.
We'll start with the team leader then.
Tell us about your shadows.
Well...
Not being financially stable
took a toll on my life.
And it still does.
I was most depressed
before serving in the military.
Whenever my future seemed uncertain,
I escape reality through video games.
I had too many thoughts and worries
which led me
to lack confidence.
It’s why I gave up things without trying.
Hye-ji, what about you?
Life hasn't been hard for me,
but I've been stuck recently.
It's not completely dark though.
- I--
- Don't force a sob story.
As if you would've had it hard.
- We all spoke, so--
- I haven't yet.
You don't have to since you're
highly against the shadows of our youth.
- I respect everyone's opinion.
- Now you do?
I agree.
I see you haven't read
the article on my father.
Was an article published?
Regarding his wealth and fame?
I lived many years in darkness
due to my father's physical abuse.
Jun...
Don't you worry though
for I'm all better now. I'm in the light.
See? I said we should stick to
the brighter side of youth.
Hey, you didn't have to openly mention it.
Why not?
- It doesn't faze me anymore.
- Take it easy.
Scars don't heal instantaneously.
All I can come up with
are the dark sides of youth.
We'll start working on it though.
Let's work on it together!
What? Unbelievable.
Who are you kidding?
Give it back!
Why should I?
- Hand it over.
- No.
Must Darkness be this mean?
What do you mean?
"Get lost" is a bit harsh,
don't you think?
It hurts to hear that.
Then I chose the right words.
They stirred up emotion.
Then Light should cry upon hearing them.
Why would Light cry?
Who wouldn't?
Did you cry when I said it to you?
Of course not. I'm not Light, am I?
You're the one just like your character.
I'm not as mean as Darkness.
As if. You're Darkness in the flesh.
Why don't we change its name to yours?
You think I'm Darkness?
But this was creative writing.
Check out these lines.
They're what you said to me.
Unbelievable.
My poor old self.
What did I even like about you?
I'm ticked off just by looking at you.
- Let's put it to a vote.
- Put what to a vote?
What do you think?
Of course, it's about Darkness.
You act exactly like Darkness would.
I'm nothing like Darkness.
You so are.
You're not Light or Darkness.
You're Mr. Ambiguous.
Who do you think Darkness is like?
Me?
Shouldn't you play this role?
You'd be a killer in it
since it's just like you.
Aren't Light's lines better?
I'm loving the banter between
Darkness and Light.
Maybe it's because
you bicker all the time.
I just did a good job on the script.
Maybe I should be a novelist.
I didn't know I had this talent.
Don't waste your time
and dream of doing something else.
I only say this for your sake.
No way. I'll be a grand novelist.
Why you...
I'll publish the best novel ever.
- Sorry. I'm late, aren't I?
- What took you so long?
- Nice.
- Soo-hyun!
- This is great.
- Right?
- Jung-ho, here you go.
- No, take one first.
- I'm good.
- I'm good too.
- You should drink one.
- Go ahead.
- I already have one.
So-bin, Kim Hye-yoon's asking for you.
Okay, I'll be right over.
Finish your meal first.
You aren't at her beck and call.
She's taking time out of her schedule
to be in our video for free.
We should tend to her. See you.
Always the Ms. Goody Two Shoes.
Hey, Ki-sun.
- Would you like some gimbap?
- But I already ate.
It's just that you like
the ones with fermented kimchi and tuna.
All right, fine.
It's a gift.
- A gift?
- Yes.
- Healthy fluids?
- Of course.
You should stay hydrated.
This just made my day.
- Sorry about it not being cold.
- It's fine.
Is it?
You have indigestion, don't you?
How did you know?
There's discomfort in my chest.
I know from experience.
Take this.
Where did you get this?
The pharmacy, of course.
Thanks, Hye-ji.
I played my part then.
"The two who represent
the light and darkness of youth"
"are different in every aspect."
"Their background, preference in food,"
"and everything in general."
"Not being able to understand each other
has them always clashing."
Must you act like
you've worked on this project alone?
Should I forget my lines
and tank the project?
I bet you've already memorized your lines.
From what I saw at the festival,
you clearly don't have stage fright.
I was born to take center stage,
but knowing that our team's fate
is in my hands makes me nervous.
Why is our team's fate in your hands?
How about we discuss
whose hands our team's fate is in tonight?
Go to bed, will you?
Being tired leads to under-performing.
"Our elders often say that we should"
"sever ties with those
we don’t get along with."
"Don’t waste time on relationships."
"It won’t matter when you’re old."
"Whether it’s family or friends,
money takes priority."
"When we’re older,"
"we’ll probably say this
to others as well."
[ Myungil University ]
We only have one more team to hear from.
Will the presenter come forward?
I'll be doing the presentation.
Are you sure?
But you're a freshman.
Although, I guess it doesn't matter.
Okay, let's begin.
[ MM, Shopping Mall for the 20-something:
What is Youth? ]
[ Nam Soo-hyun, Kim So-bin, Yeo Jun,
Park Hye-ji, Oh Chun-guk, Han Jung-ho ]
We have created a PR video for MM,
the shopping mall for the 20-something
who respect various styles.
Here's how the story goes.
The two who represent
the light and darkness of youth
are different in every aspect.
Their background, preference in food,
and everything in general.
Not being able to understand each other
has them always clashing.
But then they realize
that the other is only different.
Not wrong or defected.
Two very different individuals
meet in one world,
argue, hurt one another,
but end up falling in love.
Please enjoy the video.
[ Those are the good times. ]
[ Don't talk like you have no future left. ]
Make this happen for you too.
[ It'll never happen. ]
[ Are you sure? ]
You don't come across
decent people that easily.
I'm sure there will be someone for you.
- You're sure?
- Because you're a decent guy.
Because you're a decent guy.
- Only say what you mean.
- Got it.
[ Only say what you mean. ]
[ If I do, would you listen? ]
The decent person beside you?
That'll be me.
What?
[ I intrigue you, don't I? ]
[ Anyway, I'm freshman Yeo Jun. ]
I just want to get to know you better.
I'm more decent than you think.
I don't intend to get to know you,
so get going.
- Do you really hate me that much?
- Yes.
That was quick.
I guess you're being clingy because
I'm not reacting the way you want me to.
But you see,
you can't control everything in life.
[ Here, this is what I make in a day. ]
It's less than how much your dinner costs.
You and I can't be friends.
There's no need for us to be friends.
[ You'd never be able to understand me. ]
Being broke isn't
the only reason you end up in the gutter.
I hope you're not
one of those pathetic losers
who attack innocent people
because they think no one else is
more miserable than they are
when they don't even know
others' situations.
How will you pay me back
for trampling on my heartfelt generosity?
That was the price for being clingy.
I'm going to do what I'm good at
so you do the same.
What are you good at?
Being clingy.
[ Do you know what's really miserable? ]
Being so broke
that you can't protect
those who are dear to you.
How about we turn my lie into reality?
Let's live together.
[ If someone ever says
awful things to you, ]
[ it means that person is hurting inside. ]
[ Do not take it to heart, ]
[ even if it's something ]
[ your parents said. ]
[ Thank you. ]
Our elders often say this.
"Don't waste time on relationships."
"Sever ties with people
you don't click with."
"Don't devote yourself."
"It won’t matter when you’re old."
"Whether it’s family or friends,
money takes priority."
When we’re older,
we’ll probably say this to others as well.
But even they valued relationships
highly in their youth
which led to sleepless nights
being in love,
then brokenhearted, being in love,
and then brokenhearted again.
So this is how we define youth.
A time in our life
when we are brave enough
to befriend just about anyone.
Even though we’ll regret it someday,
we’ll take center stage in our youth
to love, to be hurt,
and then to love again
with all our hearts.
Good job.
Nicely done!
So how was it to work
with your former teammates?
Was it still the worst experience?
Do you find humans to be evil?
- No.
- I'm glad.
Excuse me, professor.
Yes, So-bin.
Could I perhaps play another video?
Of what?
I'll carry that for you.
Hand it over.
Guys, let me help!
I told you to focus on Light.
Please don't fight.
- Did you memorize your lines?
- Yes.
Here.
- Why are you so late?
- I was stuck in a traffic jam.
Traffic jam?
I like this angle.
Here.
Thank you.
- Here.
- No, I'm okay.
- I'm fine.
- Take this.
[ Do you want another one? ]
[ - Yes.
- Here. ]
You have one too.
I already have one.
Oh, this is a nice shot.
The group that won first prize
for this group project is
the group that went last.
Nam Soo-hyun's group.
Nice!
What's the reason?
I want to know what
your scores were based on.
You want to know?
It's their teamwork.
Different individuals came together
and produced an amazing result.
I gave the highest score to the group
who showed what it means
to be in a team the best.
Any objections?
Great work.
Thank you.
[iQIYI Ver]
KBS E12 'Blue Spring From A Distance'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
There's something I want to tell you.
I know you're getting married.
Oh, you do.
Here you go, professor.
You must've had
a hard time hiding it from me.
You weren't just interested in me.
I see you're saying whatever you want,
now that you're quitting.
Ms. Seol, how old are you?
I'm 28.
28...
Na Young.
Yes?
You know my name!
Why are you trying to get married so fast?
I'm only getting married
because I love my boyfriend.
Right. I got married when I was your age
out of love, and it was a disaster.
Can't you just congratulate me?
No.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You seem excited. Why are you in
such a good mood today?
The kids turned in their group project and
I'm happy because everyone did a good job.
They've grown up so much.
I envy how you can be
happy about such a little thing.
Weren't you like that too?
- Me?
- When you were in school.
You were always
so enthusiastic about everything
and you took care of everyone.
You were one of the popular kids.
I always admired you.
That was such a long time ago.
You've changed so much.
Of course, I have.
I'm not that kid anymore.
I'm still the same kid.
I still have hope for you.
I have hope that my super cool senior
will come back.
That's not going to happen.
You're my role model,
so I won't give up without a fight.
I wanted to become like Song Soo-kyung.
Park Si-jae.
What are you doing after class?
- Why do you ask?
- I was just thinking...
Do you want to grab dinner?
I don't know.
I won't ask again.
Park Si-jae, let's have dinner.
I said, let's have dinner.
I guess it's possible
to get the first place.
This is the first time
I came in first place
in group projects since school started.
Oh, who filmed the making?
Hye-yoon.
I sent it to you. Check your phone.
When I worked on projects like these
I always recorded makes as well.
When you look at it later,
it'll be a nice memory for you.
We did really well.
If you do your best while making it,
the result doesn't really matter.
And strangely,
the results are even better.
It was for me.
Thanks.
I always worry too much,
so I really couldn't enjoy anything.
I'm thankful too.
I had fun making this.
I guess you should never
really trust rumors.
The rumors about Hye-yoon
and you weren't true.
So all the rumors were fake?
Some of them were true.
Let's all reveal our Secret Santas.
You go first.
You really don't know?
I've done a lot for you.
What? Really?
Wow, I thought I didn't have
a Secret Santa.
What?
When you had classes in the morning,
I woke you up three times.
- Please!
- You didn't wake up though.
When you left...
Gosh...
I cleaned the bathroom.
It was really hard, but I didn't show it.
And I prayed that you and So-bin
would have a good relationship as couples.
[ Youth Villa ]
I told you ways to get good grades,
but you were barely listening.
Jun, if you want good grades,
you need to learn the basics.
Write down everything the professor says.
And go through them when you get home.
Check the important parts
and when you recheck them
before tests, you'll get good grades.
And...
And I saved you a seat
in the lecture room.
You didn't sit there though.
Thanks.
I had no idea you were so talkative.
Soo-hyun, you were really serious about
this whole Secret Santa thing.
Then let's cheers to my Secret Santa,
Soo-hyun's happiness.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
I didn't hate you because I wanted to.
I hated you because I wanted to be loved.
Hye-ji, have some water.
I started my own YouTube channel because
I wanted to become a film producer.
But I don't have any subscribers
and have lots of hate comments.
I don't have the money nor the skill.
I was living a normal life.
But you were living so diligently.
I was annoyed by it,
but I was also envious.
I felt so pathetic.
It was my inferiority complex.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
What?
Okay.
Guys?
Why doesn't anyone talk about
their problems to me?
Jun! I just don't feel like
talking to you.
You're just too well-off.
Jung-ho, you can talk to me.
Soo-hyun can't really
empathize with other people.
No wonder people call him, "UP".
- What?
Right?
I didn't say anything wrong.
Chan-ki.
What's with that look?
So-bin.
What are you going to say this time?
I'm leaving.
I'm enlisting in the military.
- When do you leave?
- Soon.
This is too sudden.
Are you sad?
We've never been apart.
Right.
Thanks, So-bin.
I realized I had never thanked you once.
Thank you, So-bin.
Why are you talking as if
you're leaving for good?
I'm such a loser, but you always
listened to me and comforted me.
Thanks to you, I always felt cared for
and never felt lonely.
I only realized it
after you became distant.
Why did I think
I could take you for granted?
I was like an immature kid playing
on the lawn you had laid down for me.
Now that I'm standing alone
in a barren field...
To be honest,
I still haven't figured out what to do,
but I'll figure out
how to be myself without you.
I'll find
my true self.
You can do it.
You can do anything you set your mind to.
That's right.
You know me better than I do.
Don't just pack up and leave.
You have to tell me when you're leaving.
Will you throw a going-away party?
I'll take you out for some pork belly,
your favorite.
Just once...
Can I get just one hug
from my friend, Kim So-bin?
- So-bin, close your eyes.
- What?
I'll turn around and run
on the count of three,
so don't look at my face no matter what.
- Why not?
- Just promise me you won't look.
One, two...
Three.
Hey, Soo-hyun.
I'm sensing
something's a bit different today.
Look who's talking. Did you drink?
Yes.
After the group presentation.
- Soo-hyun.
- You've called my name almost ten times.
You know that I have feelings for you,
and yet you're not saying anything.
I know what that means.
I knew
but still couldn't give up.
I've decided to give up though.
I think it became a habit.
Habits are hard to break,
so I kept putting it off.
It sounds like you're saying
you'll never see me again.
I can't cut you out of my life, idiot.
Just cut ties with a loser like me.
You're too good for me.
I know.
But Soo-hyun.
If you ever fall for someone again
when you absolutely can't afford to,
don't let her go no matter what.
A lost opportunity never returns.
You sound as if
you're going somewhere far.
I am going to stay away from you,
but I don't know
if I want to cut off all contact.
Leave the decision up to me.
If I decide to stay friends with you,
you can't go anywhere.
Where would I even go?
Just wait and be on your best behavior.
Hey, you.
- Another coincidence?
- Or is this fate?
I wanted to go for a run,
so I came here and saw you running.
I'll beat you.
I'm an athlete.
And I'm a wanted criminal.
I'm a pro at running away!
Why run in the middle of the night?
What about you?
Because I'd rather run than cry.
So you can say you're sweating,
not crying?
You too?
I kept running on a track
without a finish line.
I never turned around once.
- It sounds exhausting.
- Yes, so I drew a finish line myself.
I'm going to take a break now.
Good.
Rest up so you can run again.
Can I run again?
Of course, you can.
If this is the end,
that's just too heartbreaking.
You see, I'm going to carve a cool path
and walk the path alone.
- Alone?
- You need to master walking alone
to be able to walk with anybody.
You can actually say some useful stuff.
You didn't know?
So watch me
and get up and run.
Really? Then how about a race?
Drinks are on the loser.
Did the talk with Young-ran go well?
Yes.
Did you take So-bin home?
Yes, I sure did.
How about we have another drink?
Go on in. I'll go pick up some beers.
What? I was just kidding.
You'll actually drink more?
Nam Soo-hyun is going for another round!
Be quiet.
- There should be some beers in the fridge.
- No, there's none.
Right, I forgot to tell you earlier.
I deep-cleaned the fridge.
It was filled with leftovers
from the foods you had over-ordered.
I threw them out with my own hands.
Thank goodness we played Secret Santa.
We should keep doing it.
Why don't we extend the agreement?
- No, I don't want to.
- Why not?
Then will you be my Secret Santa?
No, I don't want that.
[ Youth Villa ]
See? I knew you'd say that.
My mother gave me my father's journal
from when he was young.
His journal?
I guess my mother found it
while organizing things.
I read the whole thing.
Is it your father's secret journal?
Then you can't read it
even if you're his son.
I guess you could call it a secret.
Because it's something I didn't know.
I found out that my father
also worried and struggled a lot
and was hurt as well when he was my age.
And he wanted to be a great father.
I resented him all my life,
but to tell you the truth,
but I actually wanted to be a cop
like my father.
I just tried to picture you as a cop.
You'll be too fair and righteous
for your own good.
Police Officer Nam Soo-hyun will never
let off those who break the law.
That's exactly how my father was.
He always made sacrifices for others
and died in an accident.
That's why I had to give up on my dream.
Why give it up?
You can write
your own ending to your story.
Someone's matured.
Don't I say cool things from time to time?
"Gosh, how annoying."
That's all I remember.
I guess that hurt you,
seeing how you still remember it.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Is there anything you want to do?
I'm not sure.
Whenever I was having a hard time,
I tried to do the things I thought
I wanted to do at the time to hold out,
but none of them was
what I truly wanted to do.
It's not too late to find it.
You're good at many things.
Right, that's true.
What should I do first?
When the summer break begins...
During the break--
Why don't we do something fun?
We should go camping together.
I'll spend the summer at my uncle's.
My mother is there.
I want to look after her.
Just during the summer?
I might come back with my mother
and live with her.
Thanks for everything.
I feel dumb this is all I can say.
Am I supposed to cry now?
Are we going to stop being friends
if I move out?
Nothing's forever.
As they say, "Out of sight, out of mind."
You can push me away.
But even if you do,
I'll come and bug you.
I'll be so cold to you.
You just wait and see.
Don't go overboard.
You wish.
I'm totally going to get back at you.
What?
[ I've become an adult
who can share his true feelings, ]
[ thanks to the people
who love me for who I am. ]
- What?
- Come on.
Gosh.
- What?
- What's your problem?
[ Two months later ]
Wake up.
Jun.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
- Did you just smile?
- Wasn't it too cold?
Obviously. Ice is cold, not hot.
- That's a relief.
- What?
I mean,
I'm not relieved that this happened.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
You should go wash your clothes first.
It's okay.
I'm not okay with this.
Then pay me 600,000 won.
- What?
- Just the dry cleaning fee.
And 40,000 won
for the commute and my time.
- Then 550,000 won for a new pair of pants.
- What? 550,000?
You think money grows on trees.
Oh, I get cold easily,
so this iced water is really bad for me.
I should get a medical certificate.
Just think that you took a cold shower.
It's a sweltering day anyway.
- You're mean.
- What? Look who's talking.
Did you two fight again?
I think you guys come to school to fight.
Here, Soo-hyun.
Thanks, So-bin.
My coffee is gone, thanks to someone.
Soo-hyun spilled his coffee on me.
- I should become a judge.
- What?
- You decided on your career path?
- You two fight every day
and ask me to judge who's in the wrong.
I can't do this anymore.
This time,
Soo-hyun is a little more at fault.
- You little...
- What?
[ "Competitive Advantage
Marketing Strategy" ]
There's one left. Do you want it?
I've bought So-bin coffee a few times,
- so I deserve this.
- But I'm older than you.
You can have this. I haven't touched it.
Are you sure?
This coffee is precious.
Soo-hyun bought it for me.
Thank you.
The second semester has already begun.
Time flies, doesn't it?
- Yes.
I always nagged you guys
to be more disciplined whenever I saw you.
I feel bad
because I don't think I ever told you
to think and reflect on yourself.
I've realized that
it's the most important thing in life.
Learning more about yourself.
It leads you to the kind of people
that you like
and helps you figure out
what you want to do.
That being said...
She's going to talk
about an assignment now.
Or maybe not.
Your assignment for this semester is...
I'll only listen to my girlfriend.
This will help you with your job search.
It'll also help you
explore yourself in depth.
[ Portfolio ]
I want you guys
to make your own portfolio.
There's no set format, so you're free
to write whatever you want.
- Professor.
- Yes.
So can we think of it
as a freestyle personal bio?
Freestyle personal bio...
A bio is written to promote yourself.
Well, I will be reading this,
but this is more like... Let's call this
an essay on self-exploration.
I want you guys
to explore yourselves in depth.
Your likes and dislikes.
What you're good at and who you like.
Professor Song has a very humane side.
I'm surprised.
Is she going through something?
[ Student Association Bulletin Board ]
[ Server wanted
at a restaurant near Myungil University ]
[ Designer wanted
for a short-term position ]
[ Student Association Bulletin Board ]
[ Dating? Leisure? ]
[ I still have no time
for stuff like that. ]
[ However, ]
[ I can breathe now, at least. ]
[ "Guide to Teacher Certificate Exam" ]
[ Vitamin Drink ]
[ Drink this and go for a run. ]
[ It's not easy to become a PE teacher. ]
[ I don't have anything new
to add to my resume, ]
[ but I like how things are now.
I'm really happy. ]
[ Youth is like a lush, green spring. ]
[ At a distance, spring is green. ]
[ Look at it closely, and you'll see
that it's lusher and more dazzling. ]
[ Our real spring begins now. ]
[ At a Distance, Spring is Green ]
[ The end ]
[ Thank you for watching
At a Distance, Spring is Green. ]