[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 17]
Let's meet for dinner tonight.
I'll bring your purse to you.
The old place.
See you then.
Don't you wanna eat something?
They are all your favorite.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
You are not feeling well?
I got a stomachache.
I don't have any appetite.
Then let me take you to the hospital.
No need.
Listen,
you may think it's not a big problem,
but over time it can lead to one.
I know a gastroenterologist,
who's very good.
Let's go see him right now.
No need!
Don't bother.
Please take the necklace back.
Since you think we can't be together,
I have to return the stuff
you gave to me.
Otherwise, it'd be inappropriate.
I've got to go now.
I still have things to do.
Shuangshuang!
It's raining! Let me give you a ride!
It's okay. I have an umbrella.
Shuangshuang!
Wait! Wait!
Where's your umbrella?
None of your business.
Wait! What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong!
Why are you angry?
I'm not!
Will you leave me alone?
Qin Hebo,
haven't you used me enough?
I overheard your phone call.
Every word of it!
I was in the kitchen at that time!
So you approached me at the very beginning
and cared about me
just because you wanted to use me!
Then why did you put on such a good act?
I'd let my guard down
when people are nice to me!
Why were you so nice to me?
Leave me alone in the future!
Shuangshuang!
Let go of me!
♪My dear, I'll say goodbye to you♪
Yes.
I used you.
And I lied to you.
But it's true that I like
and care about you!
I still don't know
whether you are lying
or not.
We are so different.
I do like you,
but
I don't want to see you anymore!
Shuangshuang!
♪I ran toward you, and passed by you♪
♪You disappeared in the dark night♪
♪I no longer watched the sunset♪
♪I ran toward you, but you
were nowhere to be found♪
♪I finally understood ♪
♪ I lost you for a reason♪
Judging from his conversation on the phone,
he and Mr. Xue should be behind
all the incidents that happened
to Evergreen lately.
What did they talk about exactly?
I think they've worked together for long.
And if I'm right,
his purpose of joining Evergreen
is to help Mr. Xue of Lihe Captial
to take over Evergreen.
And I think
it's also him who changed
my budget comparison sheet
so we mistook the African log
with termite infestation
as the optimal option.
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
You don't have to feel guilty.
You are also a victim.
Shuangshuang.
You must be tired.
Go take a rest in my room.
Come on.
Mr. Xue.
I think my relation with Lihe Captial
has been exposed.
It doesn't matter.
We've got what we wanted anyway.
And Sheng Zhening doesn't have any proof.
Besides, the 30th anniversary of the hotel
is right in the corner.
I believe
that he wouldn't stir up trouble
at this point.
I got it.
What's imperative
is to acquire the shares
from the rest of the shareholders.
She's asleep?
Yes.
Under the circumstances,
what are you going to do?
It'll soon be the 30th anniversary
of Evergreen.
I can't afford to take any risk
to put Evergreen's reputation at stake.
It's actually a good thing that we know now
what kind of person he is.
At least we can be prepared.
The most important thing for now
is to hold a successful
anniversary celebration.
Good.
This is the seating chart
for the anniversary celebration.
You will sit with Mr. Qin and the heads
of all departments.
I won't sit
with Mr. Qin this time.
Put me on the table of the shareholders.
Okay, Mr. Sheng.
The Dining Dept. wants to know
if they need
to prepare a new menu
for the anniversary celebration.
So, I'm here to ask for your opinion.
I know you are quite busy.
I'll call all the departments
for a meeting later.
They won't bother you anymore
with the anniversary thing.
I see.
Have you sent out the invitations?
The media have received them.
How about the security?
We just hired over 60
security guards from a security company.
And…
where should I
put Miss Xia?
Understood!
I'll put her next to you.
By the way,
bring me Qin Hebo's work record
during the time I was
absent.
Okay.
The anniversary celebration starts
at 9:00 a.m.
I'll go pick you up tomorrow morning at 8.
Okay!
How come you got acute gastroenteritis?
The doctor said
I drank expired, cold milk.
Then can you still
take part in the 30th anniversary celebration?
Who is it?
See for yourself.
[Zhening]
Who is it?
Not important.
Hello?
I was just upstairs,
but you aren't home.
And you are not in the office either.
Oh! I have a meeting with a client today.
I'm with Mu Xiaoyan.
Where are you?
We are at the Live Stream Head Office.
Zhening.
What are you talking about?
Hold on a sec.
Help me!
No!
Mu Xiaoyan.
The projector is broken.
Could you fix it?
Sure! Sure!
Zhening.
I'm so sorry.
I promised that I'd
go with you to the anniversary celebration.
It's alright.
I thought something happened to you.
I was just getting worried.
What's the meeting about?
Nothing special.
I told you before
that we wanted to do live commerce.
But there's a problem
with our equipment.
Don't worry. I can manage it.
Okay! Okay!
I'm coming!
Do you still have a fever?
Fever?
Who has a fever?
Mu Xiaoyan!
I asked him to fix the projector,
but it just
keeps getting hotter and hotter,
as if it had a high fever!
He's all thumbs!
It's okay.
Don't worry, Zhening.
My meeting will start soon.
Good luck today!
I'm hanging up.
I'm sorry about that.
It's okay.
I'm just here to tell you
that you'd better have liquid diet
for the next few days,
in case your stomach gets irritated again.
Okay!
Good for you.
You did very well just now.
Why didn't you tell the truth?
The anniversary celebration
is very important to Zhening.
I don't want to distract him.
Actually, I want both you
and Shuangshuang to join the live streaming.
The three of us all give it a try.
See who got the best reaction.
Me? Are you sure?
Of course!
Then I'll give it a try.
I'm leaving.
You guys chat.
How did you know I was here?
It's a GPS watch.
What did the doctor say?
Nothing serious.
It's just acute gastroenteritis.
Don't worry. I'm fine now.
I wasn't lying on purpose.
I just didn't want you to worry.
Who would've thought it'd become like this?
Do not lie to me if something like this
happens again.
And don't make decisions on your own
without telling me.
Got it?
Yes.
Hello?
Okay.
I see. I'll be there soon.
I'll come check on you
after the celebration.
Go ahead.
They are all waiting for you.
Then I'm leaving.
Okay.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
Take a good rest.
Can we have
a man-to-man conversation?
It's serious.
What's on your mind?
Why do you like about Qian?
Why do you like about her?
How do you know?
Since you found out,
I'll just be straight to you.
Yes. I do like her.
And I've liked her for a long time.
I like her because she's an earnest
hard worker
who's smart and always considerate
of others.
Nothing can beat her.
I don't have a particular reason.
I just like her.
No reason?
Which means you can't think of any.
I think you are not into her that much.
I like her because she likes street food,
she sleepwalks,
she tells lies but always
got caught…
Alright! Alright! Stop!
In a word,
I like everything about her.
Is that all?
But I'm with her every day!
I can be of her help at work,
and I can take care of her in life,
just like today!
Don't you feel threatened?
I think it's a good thing that she has
someone to take care of her
when I'm not around.
So, I don't feel threatened.
Anyway,
thank you!
Thank you for taking care of her for me!
Don't thank me!
I'm not doing it for you.
Listen up.
If you dare hurt Qian,
I won't forgive you!
You can supervise me at any time!
This man-to-man conversation
has to be over now.
I need to go back to work.
Mr. Qin.
The person in charge of the celebration
is asking when you'll come to the site.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Emily.
Tell him that I'm not feeling well.
Let them start without me.
Mr. Qin, what happened?
Sheng Zhening has found out
about my relation with Mr. Xue.
So I don't have to pretend in the future.
Okay. I got it.
Let's give a big hand
to the 30th anniversary of Evergreen Hotel!
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
for coming to the 30th anniversary
of Evergreen.
It's a great honor
to have you with us for all this time!
It's your hard work and support
that has got Evergreen to where it is today.
The theme of the celebration is gratitude.
I'd like to extend my gratitude to all of you
for being with us.
I saw it all!
The anniversary celebration
was a great success!
I'm proud of you!
Just so you know,
I've checked out of the hospital.
You don't have to pick me up tonight.
Take a good rest.
Got you.
By the way,
when will your live streaming begin?
Mr. Sheng,
our anniversary celebrationthis time
has gained positive response from the media.
And they are full of praise for you, too.
Do you know about live streaming?
A little.
I watch it every now and then.
Xia Qian is doing live commerce.
Could you help me register an account?
Sure!
I know you've repaired it once.
But apparently
you didn't do it right!
The pipe is leaking again!
I just tightened it up with a wrench.
When can you come over and fix it?
We'll send someone there
as soon as possible.
As soon as possible?
But,
how soon can it be?
I need a specific time!
Last time you said the same thing,
but I waited for three days!
Tomorrow night, at latest.
I promise someone will be there.
Okay. I'll count on that.
I'll be home tomorrow night.
Please help me fix it!
Alright! No problem!
Okay.
[Meng]
How long has it been?
I'm not sure.
But my stomach ache has lasted
for quite a while.
You missed the last therapy.
You should know
that the therapy cycle is designed
upon careful evaluation,
especially in your case of
owning a large client base.
It could
easily cause problems.
I know.
I had to put it off
due to my wedding last time.
It won't happen again.
Okay.
Now, close your eyes,
and take a deep breath.
Think about the things you've
experienced these days.
You can talk about anything you want.
Actually there's nothing special.
I've always hoped that I could separate
my work from my life.
No matter how much
I'm troubled in life,
as long as I get to work,
I can take my mind off it.
But now, my life and my work
have intertwined with each other.
There's no way to separate them.
You told me
that you wanted me to find a job.
So
I rent this pastry store, which is
right across the street from your hospital.
We can come to work
and go home together in the future!
I don't know
what I can do to change the situation.
So,
it's still because of Ning Meng?
I know she lacks sense of security,
and I know she loves me.
But her way of love
suffocates me.
Xiaotong told me today
that you were so busy at work
that you didn't even have time to eat.
Xiaotong?
The Xiaotong at my hospital?
How did you know her?
you don't have to cook every day
in the future.
The food in our cafeteria is pretty good.
Is it because you don't like eating with me?
I heard Xiaotong will be transferred
because Doctor He's wife
caught her sitting with him
and reporting work.
Have you ever thought
that it could be
your overprotection
that made Ning Meng become like this?
Things have become worse
since our wedding.
I admit that I cared
about her feelings too much.
I thought everything would be fine
and we'd have a good life
as long as I could make her happy.
But at the same time,
I do realize it's an unhealthy lifestyle.
In fact, you don't have
any problem at work.
All your stress is coming
from your marriage,
regarding witch, however,
you haven't shared much.
I know I need to talk about it.
But the things between Meng and me
are quite complicated.
This is your therapy record.
Take it.
I also have a backup.
Moreover,
since your stomach ache
is a physiological reaction
caused by overstressing
and anxiety,
you need to pay attention to it.
No matter how complicated
your relationship with Ning Meng is,
she's after all your wife,
who should be the best listener for you.
Understood.
Thank you!
99% women
out there can't resist
the facial mask!
I've tried this brand.
Look how soft my skin is!
Shuangshuang,
what do you think?
I think
they all have their own advantages.
We have toys and food here.
They are all good in different ways.
The mask Yan just introduced is nice.
Ai, what about you?
I like this robot vacuum cleaner.
It's on a big discount,
which will attract more viewers
to watch our live streaming.
Honestly, my favorite
is this.
It's a story-telling doll.
Why?
I don't think it's special.
Of course it is.
It's not just a doll that tells stories.
The most special part is
that it can imitate parents' voices.
If the parents are too busy at work
to spend time with their child,
they can record their voices with it,
so that the kid can feel their care
and love through this doll.
It's a doll
with soul and love!
I feel touched by it.
And what you just said
was also quite moving.
I think it's something
we can definitely use
during the live streaming.
But we need your professional opinion
when it comes to the order of the products.
I wouldn't say I'm professional,
but I can share some
of my personal experience.
Judging from the choice you made,
I think
you put too much subjective thoughts in it.
As a matter of fact, the order
of the products can be very critical.
Usually, we'd start with
those products with big discounts
and put them on flash sale.
Then we can attract more people
with a lucky draw,
which is like a warm-up.
The night sale usually takes place
from 9:00 p.m. to 10:30 p.m.,
during which time,
we'd usually get the most viewers,
so we need
to save
the best for last
and strive for the highest
selling result possible!
Then the order of the products
is settled.
I think it'll work.
Okay.
Mu Xiaoyan.
Skip your meals tomorrow.
Why?
You'll be in charge of selling the snacks.
The hungrier you are, the more you can eat.
Me again? Why?
I'm on a diet.
I'd rather you gain weight than I do.
Straightforward
and ruthless enough!
As long as
it's considered occupational injury.
And you need to be responsible for that.
Okay. No problem.
I'll buy you a running machine.
Alright.
That's all for today's meeting.
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Let's do it!
Lie'er.
Thank you for your professional instructions!
It's all because I'm truly
impressed by your
never-give-up spirit
and your bargaining skills.
I did invite you for several times.
But after hearing your ideas
and your professional opinions,
I think it'd even worth it
if I had to invite you for ten more times!
Let's do our best together!
You bet!
Okay!
[Account Name: My Summer
Real Name: Sheng Zhening]
This is my account?
What's wrong?
Isn't this name
too obvious?
Is it?
Is it not?
[Account Name: My Summer]
If you think it's too obvious,
I can change it for you.
Forget it. Just leave it.
Take down a few decorative pictures.
Otherwise, it'd look messy.
But an empty wall wouldn't work either.
It'd cause exposure
and make you look pale.
Okay.
This is our main light source.
Put auxiliary lights on each side.
You can turn this on.
That's right.
We can put the ring light here.
I think it's fine.
Turn it up a little.
I'm ready!
Nice!
Do I look okay?
Very nice!
So pretty!
Hi, everyone!
Thank you for watching
our Worth or Not live streaming!
I'm Xia Qian!
This is my first live streaming.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm afraid to make a mistake.
Please forgive me if I do.
So, today,
I invited your old friend,
Lie'er.
She will join me today
for the live streaming!
Let's welcome her!
Hi, everyone!
Dear viewers,
how are you doing?
How about we all come here
and say hi to our viewers?
Okay?
Hi!
You guys do it!
This is Mu Xiaoyan.
And this is Ai.
Okay.
Today, Xia Qian and I
have prepared many good products
for you,
and they are all on a big discount.
Here are a few items.
Hi, guys!
I'm Xia Qian.
Today I'll introduce
a very cute and fun stuff for you.
So,
this is today's highly recommended product,
the story-telling bear!
Those who have kids
will like this product a lot.
We got a message.
“Raccoon 12345” asks
“Is link No. 3 still available?”
I'm sorry.
This product
is completely out of stock.
Don't worry if you missed it.
Tomorrow we'll have a bigger surprise
for you!
Just so you know,
at tomorrow's live streaming,
we'll have cosmetics of famous brands
with 42% off!
Okay.
This's all for today's
live streaming!
If you like our products
and our Worth or Not live streaming,
please
click the
“Follow” button
in the upper left corner.
Alright!
Tomorrow night at 8,
we'll see you here at Worth or Not!
See you then!
I'll unplug this first.
It's great!
Our follower increased dramatically today!
Our pilot living streaming is a big success!
Actually, the reason
we got a big success today
is mostly because
we got Lie'er here to help.
But, if you look at
the statistics of the backend,
14,333 is the lowest number
of viewers we've got,
and the highest
is 48,987.
It is really high.
Qian, it was your first live streaming.
I think you did very well!
And it takes time to attract
more and more viewers.
We got the highest number of viewers
when Qian introduced how the bear
could imitate people's voice
to tell stories.
And it's also
the best-seller for today.
Which means most of our viewers
are mothers.
So I think
Xia Qian's idea of playing the caring card
is working.
Shuangshuang.
What's with you today?
Why didn't you join us
in front of the camera?
I couldn't.
I don't know why
but I get very nervous
in front of the camera!
It's okay.
The first time is always hard.
Just
take your time.
Let's keep up the good work,
okay?
[Sheng Zhening  Are you home yet?]
Are you home yet?
Just got in bed.
Why are you calling?
You'll always be this busy in the future?
I guess.
I've just started,
and I need to improve my sales skills.
By the way,
you are “My Summer,”
aren't you?
No! No way.
An An came up with that name.
I had no idea.
But,
how could he create such a name
without your permission?
I really had no idea.
I'm going to ask him tomorrow
and deduct two months' salaries from him.
Nothing will happen, right?
I'll hang up now.
Let's go to bed.
Okay.
Goodnight!
[Worth or Not]
The wine is a new brand.
As long as you can recover the costs,
reducing the price
is quite necessary.
What do you need the most right now?
Good word of mouth, right?
Once you've gained enough market share,
the profits
will surely follow.
I got you, Miss Xia.
But as for the discount,
I have to discuss with the head office.
If we take one step back,
the customers will take one step forward.
Miss Xia signed an agreement
with the mother company.
She has to reach
the predetermined sales volume
within a month.
Or else, she'll be fined.
See if there's any
festival coming up.
Festival?
Why are you asking?
Every festival we'd buy
gifts for our employees.
Find a festival and buy something
through Xia Qian's live streaming
and distribute them to the employees
in my own name.
In that case,
she can't reach the sales goal easily.
But it doesn't seem like
there's any important festival coming up.
Check again.
A small one will also do.
[International Day
for Natural Disaster Reduction]
There's one!
International Day
for Natural Disaster Reduction
For short,
International Disaster Reduction Day.
This one.
That's it!
It's a very meaningful day.
Remember,
Xia Qian cannot find out about this!
Hello!
Thank you, dear friends,
for watching my living streaming!
It's a little late.
I'm sorry
that I interrupted your dinner time.
But it's only because
that we have something
on a big discount today!
Right?
The product I brought you today,
as you can see, is this wine.
The price is very reasonable.
No matter you'll drink it yourself,
or give it to your friends as a gift,
or take it to a party,
this wine will be
your best choice
for those kinds of
occasions.
I've tried this wine.
When you take your first sip,
it tastes slightly sweet.
And it also has moderate fruity taste,
which greatly reduces the bitter sensation.
In a word, this wine is suitable
for all kinds of occasions.
The number of the viewers
surpassed 2,000 today!
It's a breakthrough!
And most of them placed an order!
Then we should make a toast!
Cheers!
I'm just curious
why we got a big increase so quickly.
Because we are doing a good job,
and our products are of good quality
and big discounts!
So, our viewers are increasing while
the news spreading by word of mouth.
Really?
How about this?
To celebrate our viewers surpassing 1,000,
I'll take you out for barbecue!
Yeah!
I can't go.
The Property Management will
send someone to fix my pipe tonight.
I have to go home.
Then go ahead.
This is Qin Hebo's work record
during the time when you were absent.
Anything abnormal?
Everything looks fine.
But there's one thing that's quite strange.
What thing?
When the Building No. 2 was under remolding,
we were short of some paint.
It was Qin Hebo who paid for it.
Anything wrong
with the paint?
That's the strange part.
As it turned out, he didn't do anything
to the paint.
I see.
First, turn it on.
You all know that.
Then put the yam in.
The power is on.
Next, we'll choose a mode.
This all-in-one machine
Has an automatic steam and bake modes.
Press the confirm button,
and then press start.
[Don't let Mr. Sheng's girlfriend
see these stupid comments]
Mr. Sheng.
I'll talk to the Finance Dept. tomorrow.
I won't take my salary
for the next month.
You must be the first boss ever
who gives the employees gift
on the International Disaster Reduction Day.
I've thought about it.
I think what I did wouldn't
provide you with any practical help.
So, in order to achieve win-win,
I've decided to invest
in your live streaming.
Invest in my live streaming?
What do you mean?
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't make this decision
because you are my girlfriend.
I'm doing this
only because
of the brighter outlook
of this industry
and your outstanding business skills.
Really?
What if you are not
satisfied with our work?
Rest assured.
I've never lost money
in my investments.
Trust me.
That's what I should say to you.
Hello?
Miss Fu.
Your bathroom is leaking again!
- Could you come back and take a look?
- Oh, I'm sorry!
I'll be right back.
Please wait for me.
Where are you going?
The pipes at my home burst again.
I have to go back.
The live streaming will start soon.
I'll be back before it starts.
Please tell them for me.
Hurry!
What is going on with your bathroom?
My ceiling is soaking wet!
I have just painted it a few days ago.
I'm telling you, I won't let you off!
I'm so sorry.
I'm only a tenant.
The landlord is abroad.
The pipes are old.
I think the Property Management
should be partially responsible.
I don't care. I'll only talk to you.
Excuse me for a sec.
Hello?
Shuangshuang.
How is it going?
I'm sorry.
It's an emergency.
I'll be right back. I promise!
I still have work to do.
I need to go back.
Can we talk about this later?
What if you run away?
How about this?
I'll leave my ID card to you.
I won't run away.
Okay.
Hello?
I'll be there in 15 minutes!
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no grudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪