[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 18]
Excuse me.
What's up?
I am the boyfriend
of the girl who lives upstairs.
I'm here to discuss with you
about the leakage problem.
Then come in and take a look.
Look at my wall.
The wall was just painted a few days ago.
Look at all the water.
Look at it.
There is indeed a leakage.
And the bath heater
also leaked.
It's all water inside.
Even the bath heater has water.
Look.
So much water.
Why not ask a maintenance personnel
to take a look?
After the overhaul,
the water will be sucked up.
Well.
Forget about the bath heater.
Tell me how to deal
with the water at the corner of the wall.
Let's do this.
I will pay you 500 yuan first.
500?
1000?
1500?
Here.
Why did you transfer 2,000 yuan to me?
The extra 500 yuan is for you
to keep this a secret.
Don't let my girlfriend know that
I have been here.
Sorry to bother you.
Look.
The flesh is so fresh.
I can't help but eat it.
Let me try for you.
See what's the taste.
I have to say,
this is definitely the best snack
I have ever eaten.
Girls can eat it
for beauty
and weight loss.
Boys watching the live broadcast,
buy it for your girlfriends.
All right?
[My Summer No. 1: Qian, I like you]
I can't stop it.
Thank you, everyone.
I like you.
I love you all.
There is an account
during the live streaming today
named My Summer No. 1.
It seems that Qian has fans.
I think this is good.
Maybe there will be
My Summer No. 2,
No. 3 and No. 4.
But,
I already have a boyfriend.
I don't think we should deceive consumers
for the sake of sale volume
and pretend to be single.
Right?
Are you against it?
Invalid objection.
Thanks to you.
And there are accounts like
My Summer No. 1, No. 2,
No. 8.
You were quite satisfied at first.
What did you say?
I said that
I won't take my salary for next two months.
What's the use of deducting your salary
for one year?
Find a way
to solve this.
Got it.
It's okay.
The Property Management said
they would be responsible.
Really?
Sorry to bother you.
Never mind.
The property would be responsible?
Darling.
Where have you been this afternoon?
I called you many times,
but you didn't answer.
When are you coming back?
[I'll go back in a while]
Have you ever thought that
it could be
your overprotection
that made Ning Meng become like this?
I'll go back in a while.
I am occupied today.
Darling.
Are you working overtime?
I'll wait for you at home.
I don't dare to sleep if you don't come back.
I will go home now.
Do you have something on your mind?
No.
I am just tired.
Then you should take more rest.
Why come to me early in the morning?
I miss you.
I'd like to see you.
By the way,
I watched your live streaming.
What about it?
Is it better?
Much better.
But I think it can be even better
on the current basis.
During the live streaming,
there was a person
named My Summer No.1.
You saw it?
Are you jealous?
Why would I?
Just an ordinary audience.
Besides,
you are an anchor.
You will definitely have a lot
of fans in the future.
This is unavoidable.
Aren't you jealous?
No.
I thought you would be jealous.
I'm still thinking about
how to explain to you.
I didn't expect you to understand it.
He is just
an ordinary audience.
But I don't think
his name
is polite.
Why not?
I am adapting now.
But he is just an ordinary audience.
He just uses that name for fun.
But I think
for an ordinary audience like this,
it is necessary to block him.
Block?
Is it necessary?
You are jealous.
No.
You are.
No!
You are jealous.
Okay, if I'm jealous,
can you block him?
No way.
He is just an ordinary audience.
I am just suggesting you.
Well.
But I'm not jealous.
You went so far.
It didn't do anything wrong.
[Omeprazole Enteric-coated Capsules]
Darling.
What medicine are you taking?
Nothing.
I just have a stomachache.
Darling.
Let me take you to the hospital
to see a doctor.
Not necessary, I am a doctor.
I know my own situation well.
Darling, I mean it.
Go to the doctor.
- It's better to…
- Ning Meng.
Don't force me anymore.
I said I was fine.
Darling, it's my fault.
I just worry about you.
I mean,
if you go…
Don't be like this.
All right, it's my fault.
I will never think too much
in the future.
Darling, just forgive me.
Meng.
Can we live a normal life?
I'm really tired.
After we got married,
I forgot what we were like before.
We just get angry and apologize
every day repeatedly.
Is this the life you want?
I am going to read.
Hello, I am online.
Welcome everyone
to my live streaming.
Before the live streaming,
I would like to explain
my emotional state to you.
I have a boyfriend.
He's very excellent.
I love him so much.
He's the one in my life.
The only one.
So…
So cheesy.
Never mind.
So I am not single.
All right.
No more nonsense.
Today's live streaming is about to begin.
What I want to
recommend today is tea.
The price is quite reasonable.
Just buy it.
Three people unfollowed today.
We lost three fans.
We lost three today,
we are going to earn thirty more tomorrow.
I agree with Qian.
Our live streaming
should be honest and trustworthy.
We should stick to the truth.
Never make any false persona.
Right.
Lies will eventually be exposed.
At that time,
it will bring more damage.
Shuangshuang is right.
All right.
It's enough.
Let's work harder.
Most of Mr. Gao's assets
are with his wife.
If he divorces his wife,
he would surely suffer great losses.
So if he wants to keep his assets,
he definitely doesn't want
the cheating video to be exposed.
He would agree to sell his shares.
Do you need me to send it to Mr. Xue now?
Not necessary.
I'll arrange this.
Okay.
Hebo.
I am planning to transfer directly
the shares of Evergreen held by someone else
to Lihe Capital,
and then formally enter the board
of directors of Evergreen.
Since we have already made it clear,
we don't have to hide ourselves.
I…
Sorry.
Hebo, I have to answer the call.
It's me.
Go ahead.
Okay, got it.
Don't worry.
We are friends.
I will try my best.
Okay.
Hebo.
Is there any progress
with Mr. Gao?
I have no news yet.
I will let you know if there is any news.
Hurry up.
The 30th anniversary celebration
was a success.
Mr. Sheng's abilities
are obvious to all.
I think it is more appropriate
for him to act as the general manager.
Frequent changes in positions
will make Evergreen's management
seems unstable
and impact a bad influence.
Mr. Qin is doing a good job.
There's no need for the change.
Mr. Qin, what do you think?
I have no objections.
It depends on the decision
of the board of directors.
Okay.
Let's hold a meeting next week
to formally discuss today's topic.
If there is nothing else,
I will leave.
Look…
The meeting hasn't finished yet.
He…
They are burning the bridge.
You have paid so much for Evergreen
in the past few months.
They want to take your place
as soon as Sheng Zhening comes back.
The video was sent to Lihe Capital.
Why didn't Mr. Xue
take action?
Should I urge him?
No.
Mr. Qin.
Do you have anything on your mind?
You seem to be absent-minded recently.
Nothing.
I am just tired.
Leave me alone.
Okay.
Meng.
When did you arrive?
I just arrived.
Why didn't you go up to find me?
There's a place I want to go.
Sure.
According to Ai's data analysis,
it is obvious that
the number of live views of clothing
is much higher than that
of others.
But we don't cover this area.
I think it's a chance.
It happens to be a short slab.
What are you doing?
You.
Apply to the head office
for some clothing brands.
Are there any requirements for the style?
No excessive requirements.
But the fabric and workmanship
must be the best.
The finished product
needs to be the same as those in the video.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Why did you bring me here?
We visited here last Valentine's Day.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Zhijun.
I went to see Doctor Zhang.
Professor?
Meng.
What happened to you?
Going back to
the familiar psychological clinic
reminded me of
when we first met.
I am really happy,
grateful,
and cherish the life we have now.
Zhijun.
I know I did a lot
that irritated you.
I will never interfere with your work again.
I will never doubt you,
nor will I be afraid of you
being stolen by others.
I know I can't change it all at once.
But Zhijun, give me some time.
- Meng.
- I will definitely…
Meng.
I really didn't blame you.
You don't have to worry
about my feelings for you at all.
You don't have to worry about
bad things happening
in the future.
Okay?
Zhijun, let's sit here.
Okay.
Why are these all ancient costumes?
It's the Han Chinese costume brand
recommended by the head office.
This month, the head office
launched the activity
with the theme of traditional culture.
Han Chinese costume, jewelry
and cosmetics
all contain traditional elements.
Well…
Who would buy this dress
during the live streaming?
The head office must have given these to us
because of our poor performance.
They are making things difficult for us.
It's okay.
Actually, I found that
the workmanship and quality
of these clothes are good.
The quality is pretty good.
I got an idea.
Shuangshuang.
You like to watch
all kinds of costume dramas.
You can try them on.
I do watch costume plays.
But I can't do this.
You know I'm nervous in front of the camera.
Well.
I…
I can't hold these.
You should try it.
I…
Take a seat.
One for you.
What's this?
Do you remember it?
Why do you still have this?
When I was sick,
I couldn't fall asleep every day,
so you gave me recordings
of the natural environment.
You told me that
the world is big.
I shouldn't be confined
to the little painful world.
At that time, you told me that
you downloaded it from the Internet.
But I know
this must be recorded
by you.
I could hear your breath.
Why didn't I notice that?
Of course you didn't.
I would notice
and feel
everything you do
at every moment.
I will keep all of you
in my heart.
I know.
Zhijun.
Let's travel around.
You said before that
you would take me to travel around the world.
Sure, it's up to you.
Hello.
My house tripped.
Can you arrange for someone to check it?
Okay.
We will arrange it for you tomorrow.
Wait.
Why tomorrow again?
You made the arrangements very fast
for the leakage in my house last time.
Why do you decline with all kinds
of excuses this time?
Didn't you
solve the leakage
with the owner yourself?
Myself?
Yes.
Your boyfriend
asked me to hide it from you.
What boyfriend?
The man
who paid the compensation for you last time.
He is quite handsome,
wearing a suit.
And he seems very rich.
Did you quarrel?
No.
Thank you.
Never mind.
The person in the village
who has the best relationship
with me is Xiao Lang.
Do you watch my live streamingevery time?
This is his home.
But this time…
Not every time.
When I am busy,
I would ask An An to record it
to watch later.
Don't watch my live streaming tomorrow.
Why?
There's no reason why.
Just don't watch it.
Neither can you record it.
All right.
This is the compensation
for the leakage
you paid for me last time.
2000 yuan
in total.
I don't want to owe you anything.
Shuangshuang.
What else?
If I promise you
not to do anything bad,
do we still have a chance?
I don't know.
Why do you keep ironing there?
The clothes would be broken.
What happened?
Anything in your mind?
Tell me.
If a person always serves the devil,
would he get better?
Why asking about this?
I am watching a play.
There is a bad guy
who did much wrong before,
but he wants to get better.
Do you think
it is possible?
No idea.
It depends on the screenwriter.
Let me help you.
Take a rest.
Take care.
So weird.
Why did I agree?
Where are you?
Anyone at home?
[Zhening]
I am at home.
I am getting changed.
Why are you here?
I finished the work at hotel.
So I came to work with you.
I told you last night
not to watch my live streaming.
Why did you break your promise?
I just said not
to watch your live streaming,
but I didn't say not
to watch you work.
You are arguing irrationally.
Are you finished?
You will be late.
No.
Soon.
Hold on.
What's up?
Nothing.
[An An]
Hello.
Okay, I got it.
I will be back soon.
What happened?
There is an urgent case.
I have to go back.
Just go.
I am fine.
I will go downstairs
after I get changed.
Okay, that's good.
I am leaving.
Take your time.
Put this.
Put it in the front.
Man, I…
I'm crooked.
This way.
No, that way.
Here, the opposite direction.
The light.
My face is still dark.
No, aim it at my face.
Qian.
You look amazing in this.
What?
I am uncomfortable.
So weird.
Exactly, Qian.
You can even hold this style.
So nice.
[An An]
All cleaned up.
An An.
Ms. Xia.
Is Mr. Sheng with you?
No, he isn't.
He left after receiving your call.
He didn't return to Evergreen.
And his phone is turned off.
I can't reach him at all.
Really?
He left in a hurry.
Anything urgent happened?
Mr. Gao of our hotel
sold his shares to Lihe Capital.
Lihe Capital is now our shareholder.
Mr. Xue hasn't taken any action.
So I went for him.
But he told me that
you didn't send Mr. Gao's video
to him.
So I…
How could you make the decision
without my permission?
I wanted to do you a favor.
I thought you are concerned
about your relationship with Mr. Sheng,
so you couldn't bear
to send the video to Mr. Xue.
That's why I…
Get out.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is…
The number you dialed is power off.
Sorry.
Power off?
Hello.
The number you dialed is power off.
Sorry.
Mr. Sheng.
You are finally back.
What's going on?
Mr. Gao has always
been a shareholder of Evergreen.
He suddenly sold his shares to Lihe Capital
made other shareholders upset.
Several shareholders asked me
if there is a problem
with Evergreen's operations.
I asked Mr. Gao to record a video statement.
Ask all the shareholders
for an emergency meeting.
Besides,
Lihe Capital not only bought
Mr. Gao's 5%shares.
They also secretly
asked Mr. Xue
to buy the shares of Mr. Lin and Mr. Yu.
They are just not acquired
in the name of Lihe Capital.
So far,
they own at least 10%
of Evergreen's shares.
I got it.
Go schedule the meeting.
Okay.
Excuse me. Thanks.
This way, please.
So strange.
He just told me that
he couldn't reach you.
I was so worried that
I rushed over.
I thought you were with Ms. Xia,
so I…
I went to Mr. Gao's house for a meeting.
And my phone was out of power.
It's okay.
All right.
I am going to have a meeting.
I will be back soon.
Wait here for me.
Is there a problem
with Evergreen's operations?
Mr, Gao has always been a shareholder
of Evergreen.
Why would he suddenly
sell his shares now?
I believe that many people heard
about Mr. Gao selling his shares,
and there are many speculations.
I have a video statement
from Mr. Gao.
I sold the shares for some personal reasons,
but not for Evergreen's operations.
It's a pity that
I will not be able
to work with you in the future.
Wish you success in your work.
Recently, there have been rumors
that there's a problem
with Evergreen's operations.
The expansion of Evergreen
over the past ten years is obvious to all.
The operations have always been
in an orderly way.
Obviously,
someone is trying to take the opportunity
to interfere us
and make a profit in troubled situations.
I hope everyone here
will not be misled.
Come on. Come on.
Xian is here.
Hello, how is he?
Come on.
Is he handsome?
Don't go.
Everyone says you are handsome.
Look.
He is handsome, right?
Come on.
Look at this.
Dignified, elegant and gentle.
So beautiful.
Are you still the anchor I know?
Of course.
Bai Suzhen under the Mount Qingcheng.
Cultivate this body for
thousands of years in the cave.
Great!
We are here to sell the goods.
All the Han Chinese costumes on us
will have
an amazing
discount.
The first 30 orders
will be given
the embroidered shoes
worth 198 yuan.
So nice.
So good, just buy it.
Take a look at the comments.
So many comments.
60 kg is no problem.
Don't worry.
It makes us look slimmer.
Let me see.
Someone asked if it's possible to wear out.
As long as you like. Sure.
You can wear everything.
We can just go shopping like this.
Right.
And take some photos.
Someone envies you.
He is jealous.
They want to buy you.
Xu Xian isn't for sale.
But my clothes are.
I think
everything is for sale.
We can sell him together.
I feel like I went through the veil
of time
wearing this suit.
And I am so elegant.
Am I cool?
- So cool.
- Am I unworldly?
So cool.
It is indeed more intuitive
to show the data in the dynamic histogram.
Right?
It's really better.
You are back.
Take a look.
I made a chart with An An
of Evergreen's turnover
in recent years
according to year and month.
In this case, shareholders can see clearly
that Evergreen is constantly growing.
Just to
set their mind at rest.
But I don't know if it will work.
Diagrams are more convincing
than words.
Is it appropriate for you
to dress like this?
Nothing inappropriate.
I was so busy that I forgot to get changed.
Come with me.
What's up?
Here is the dress.
Get changed.
When did he buy it?
Hold on.
Stop it. I will be okay soon.
Zhening.
Come in and do me a favor.
Didn't you get changed?
This dress is troublesome.
Untie it for me.
You didn't want me
to watch your live streaming
because of this?
Yes, it's so weird.
Not at all.
It's cute.
All right.
Enough.
Well, what happened
to Mr. Gao?
Why did he sell his shares to Lihe Capital?
Hasn't he been a shareholder of Evergreen
for a long time?
Mr. Gao's room was installed with a camera.
Something
was filmed.
Lihe Capital blackmailed him with this video.
Evergreen's security is very strict.
No outsiders can come in.
Is it possible that
Evergreen's internal employee did it?
I was thinking
it might be Qin Hebo.
Last year, he changed
all the coded locks
in the office areas of Evergreen.
The manufacturer of the coded locks
is closely related to Lihe Capital.
Now Evergreen is like
an unlocked door.
Well.
Have you figured out a way?
Don't worry. I will deal with it.
All right. Get out.
I will get changed myself.
The effect of our live streaming
is so great.
All the dresses were sold out.
And all the eyeshadows
and lipsticks you used are sold out.
We got 1000 more fans.
They strongly demanded
another live streaming.
Stop it.
I am flattered.
Are you?
Now that the fans are so enthusiastic,
let's do one more.
And here is my plan.
In the future, the live streaming
will be handed over to Mu Xiaoyan.
Am I capable?
Why doubting yourself?
I am ready to do the behind-the-scenes work.
Because before I was forced
to do the live streaming
by myself.
Through the data this time,
it is obvious that
Xiaoyan is more suitable than me.
You are more open.
And you can lead more people.
I agree.
Me too.
Then I will take a try.
Here you are.
The laurels of honor.
Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Xue of Lihe Capital
would like to invite you to dinner
with other shareholders.
Right at our hotel.
The shareholders are asking
if you would be there.
White Vengeance at my site.
Why not?
Lihe Capital is already a shareholder
of Evergreen.
For Evergreen's future,
we will be in the same boat
and share weal or woe in the future.
Come on.
For Evergreen's future.
Cheers.
Evergreen's food
is so delicious.
Mr. Sheng.
What do you think?
Mr. Xue, I'm glad you like it.
Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Gao sorted out all the hotel's
VIP customer information.
The new housekeeping manager
will on board tomorrow.
Put the materials in his office.
Let him hand over tomorrow.
Got it.
Mr. Qin.
What a coincidence.
Why didn't you come
for the dinner with the shareholders?
I have been waiting for Mr. Xue
for a while.
Great.
I also have something to tell you.
Let's talk in the car.
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no drudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪