[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 9]
[Liping BBQ]
Stop staring at him.
Didn't you ask me
who Sheng Zhening is?
It's him.
You two...
There is nothing going on between us.
The fact is
that he has been courting me.
Didn't I talk in sleep before?
That's because I'm getting
bored with his pursuit.
Really?
Really.
Why would I lie to you?
Please help yourself.
Stop looking at him.
What does he do?
Do you know Evergreen Hotel?
Yeah.
It's run by his family.
Wanna know how he made a move on me?
Take a guess.
Buy you flowers and bags.
Take you to fancy meals.
Mom.
Where is your imagination?
What else could there be?
In order to take me to Iceland
and see the aurora,
he chartered a yacht.
But I was too busy
and too lazy to go.
This one.
What's this?
A credit card.
It's unlimited and you can
spend as much money as you want.
But I remember your instructions
that we don't waste a penny of other people.
I never used it.
Looks at those guys
you found for me earlier.
He is such an excellent man.
Are they comparable?
Just don't worry about me,
okay?
Okay. Okay.
They are not comparable.
Oh my God.
Sheng.
I heard from Xia Qian
that you've been courting her
for two months.
Is that what she told you?
She lied.
- This kid...
- Actually,
I've been courting her
for almost one year.
But
you are such an eligible man.
What do you like about our Xia Qian?
You...
I don't know
what I like about her.
Just saying something.
She
has a bad temper
and a one-track mind.
She does everything without
thinking about the consequences.
She is like a firecracker
that explodes easily.
She plays petty tricks sometimes.
Sheng Zhening.
Don't go too far.
Aunt,
isn't that how love looks like?
Sometimes you can't tell
what's wrong,
but
no one else can replace her.
Yes, yes, exactly.
See.
Come on.
Time for dinner.
Here.
What's wrong?
Did you throw up?
Are you not feeling well?
Well...
Hello.
Shuangshuang.
The kitten doesn't look well.
It doesn't look well?
Is there any symptom?
I think it threw up.
Take it to the pet hospital now.
I'll be right with you.
Okay, okay.
I'll take it to the hospital first.
Thank you for
what you did just now.
Thank you so much.
Don't say that.
You did me such a big favor.
Was I not good enough
just now?
You were too good.
My mom
will urge me to take you.
Then what?
To ask you to keep playing my boyfriend?
Work with me.
Don't mess it up.
There is sunshine in the south facing room.
The view is good, too.
Honey.
I don't like other rooms.
I just like this one.
Is it okay?
Anyway,
actually, I think we can do it.
We can do what?
Nothing.
I just want to thank you.
If you need anything,
just tell me.
I can continue to play your boyfriend.
It doesn't matter to me.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
I will ask you for help
if I need it.
How is the kitten?
The primary diagnosis is indigestion.
They just gave it a thorough check.
We are still waiting for the report.
Indigestion?
Well,
is it because you changed its food?
I changed its food?
The cat food I recommended to you last time,
did you change it all at once?
Well,
am I not supposed to
change the food all at once?
You should change its food gradually,
adjusting the ratio of the new cat food
and the old cat food
so that it will adapt to it.
Different cat food varies in
the protein content and the smell.
The cat will instinctively reject it
and have physical reaction.
I see.
It's okay.
I'll give you some notice and basic facts
about how to keep a cat.
It should be fine now.
It's on a drip now.
It may take a while.
Let's go to the sofa and have some rest.
Come on.
I asked you out in the middle of the night.
You must be hungry.
A little bit.
Have a rest here.
I'll buy something for you.
Sheng Zhening.
You...
What?
No.
Give me your hand.
Put it on.
Why?
You know me.
My mom urges me to get married every day.
I'm going crazy.
You have to marry me.
No.
Don't worry.
After you put on the ring,
you will be my man.
I will be responsible for you.
Get off me. No.
[Mr. Xue]
Something came up in the company.
Please send the kitten to
my house after it's discharged.
The code of the room is
081399.
Mr. Yu has
transferred 2% of his stock
to Lihe Capital.
In this case,
we will have 5% of the stock.
You did a good job this time.
I heard that
a hotel reviewer will check
in building No. 2.
If I remember correctly,
building No. 2 should be an old building.
It has been around for more than 20 years.
The hydro-electric transmission lines
are aging.
It should have been refurbished long ago
if it wasn't for financial constraints.
In this case,
whether Evergreen can maintain five stars
depends on this evaluation.
We can do something about it.
If Evergreen gets less stars
because of building No. 2,
the shareholders might
vote to sell building No. 2.
Sheng Zhening is a nostalgic person.
To sell building No. 2g
is not easy.
Yeah?
But I heard
that the shareholders are not willing to
spend any more money
to maintain that old building.
Whether to sell building No. 2
or lose the support of the shareholders,
let's wait and see
what Sheng Zhening will choose.
I know it will be hard,
but I am very confident in building No. 2.
Are we really not
going to do something about it?
If we can find the reviewer,
then...
Just follow the normal procedure.
There is a gap again.
Hello, An An.
Hello, Miss Xia.
Is it convenient for you to come to
Evergreen Building No. 2 now?
There is a job opportunity
I want to talk to you.
Okay, no problem.
I have time now.
I'll be there right away.
Can I make one small request
before you come?
Go ahead. What is it?
It's fine.
Which floor?
Hello.
Where are you?
I'm in the company.
What's up?
Nothing.
Bye.
Okay.
Come in.
Mr. Qin.
This is the information of
building No. 2 you want.
Mr. Qin.
The hotel hired a new chef
who is good at making Japanese cuisine.
You have been working hard recently
and not eating well.
Would you like to try it later?
Your job now
is not to study the new chef of
Evergreen's Food & Beverage Dept,
but to find the reviewer as soon as possible.
Sorry, Mr. Qin.
You can leave now.
It's too dangerous.
You know what,
I was so close to
being found out,
but don't worry.
Why are you giving that look?
Didn't you
ask me to dress like this?
I haven't asked you about it, An An.
Did you ask me to dress like this
to hide from Sheng Zhening?
Actually,
it's my personal decision.
Mr. Sheng doesn't know it.
This is information of
Evergreen's previous review.
Take a look.
This is your room card.
Miss Xia, before we
find the hotel reviewer,
we need you to live here.
I'll try.
But you are looking for someone.
Why do you ask me to do it?
I'm not a private detective.
That's not right.
Based on what I've been seeing
during this time,
I found that you are smart and clever
with strong analytical skills,
and you are competent.
Mainly because I can't afford
a private detective.
Kitty.
I'll put you here first.
Why is it like no one lives here?
It's so strange.
Do you like your new home?
Isn't this house really big?
It's three floors.
Look.
Do you like this?
Here.
Are you hungry?
Sorry. I thought you were someone else.
Don't go in the chairman's office.
Well, all right, I'll leave right away.
Okay, let's go, Brother.
[Veteran driver]
Tell them that there are some data.
Hello.
Shuangshuang.
You haven't had dinner, right?
Let me take you to dinner.
I know a good Japanese restaurant.
I'm waiting for your treat.
I'm hungry.
I'll pick you up.
Okay.
It's Sheng.
How are you here?
Come in.
You've been dreaming of
Xia Qian lately?
She's all in your head?
Yes.
Everyone looks like her?
Oh no, Sheng.
You have lovesickness.
Really?
Of course.
It's definitely what it is.
But you came at a bad time,
Xia Qian is not at home.
She went on a business trip.
A business trip?
Yeah, she went on a business trip.
Didn't she tell you that?
Well.
Since you are here,
let me give you a hand
and help you cheat.
Xia Qian's favorite fruit is cherries.
Right.
She likes matcha ice cream.
She likes corn,
but she doesn't eat corn candy.
When she gets angry,
she likes to clean.
She enjoys watching horror movies,
but
she doesn't dare to sleep alone
after watching it.
And also...
Okay, stop writing.
I will tell you
when I remember more.
Okay.
Since you are here,
I'll just help you out.
Let me give you a bonus.
Come on.
Come over.
Let me show you something good.
Here.
Look.
This is when she was six years old.
This is
when she was in elementary school
wearing a red scarf.
This is
when she was three months.
And this is
her dad. Don't look at that.
Junior high school, high school
and university.
Look, she changed every year.
This is when she was learning to dance
in the Children's Palace.
Look, she was wearing this.
Pick one for yourself.
Why was she crying in this one?
This is...
It was a Children's Day.
I can't remember which year it is.
One of Xia Qian's good friends got injured
and she asked Xia Qian to dance for her.
Xia Qian promised her,
but she got stage fright.
She got scared.
She was dancing while crying,
crying while dancing,
and I took this picture of her.
Actually, my daughter
has been like this since she was a kid.
She is really stubborn.
Once she makes a promise,
no matter
how much she doesn't like it,
she will do it anyway even in tears.
That's who she is.
Aunt.
I want this one.
No,
not this one.
This is too...
Pick another picture.
It's very cute. I like it.
Okay, okay.
Thanks, Aunt.
The last bite.
Bravo. Bravo. Bravo.
Bravo.
You are really good.
I've rarely seen a girl
enjoy her food as much as you do.
That's because it's delicious.
By the way,
do you have any other plans later?
No.
If not,
can you please do me a favor?
Well,
how old is she?
She
is about your age.
What about her personality?
Just like you.
Very lively and cheerful,
smiling all day.
What about her skin color?
Her skin color?
She is almost as light-skinned as you.
Are you giving me a gift?
Why would I do that?
No.
I'm joking.
Well,
who is it for then?
a female friend
or a girl you like?
Why do you care so much?
No.
I'm just asking,
so I can pick the right gift for you.
It's for Ning Meng.
Didn't you tell me
to cheer a girl up
is to make her laugh?
Then I'll pick a good gift
for you.
Ning Meng.
By the way,
I almost forgot it.
This is for you.
What's this?
Tips for raising cats.
Is it so much trouble to have a cat?
You wrote a lot
on the paper.
Actually,
it's not that much.
Most importantly,
cats need human companionship.
In the world of cats,
it has no idea
what humans do during the day.
When you go to work in the morning,
it thinks you are hunting for it.
When you get off work at night,
it will rush to you
to smell and see
whether you bring back canned chicken
or canned fish.
But if you haven't been home for a long time,
it will think
you got eaten
while hunting.
Got eaten?
I didn't know you know so much about cats.
I had a cat when I was a kid.
But
because
that cat scratched me a lot,
my mom gave it away.
Were you sad
after your mom gave it away?
A little at first.
I really missed it.
After all, I had been keeping it for so long.
But,
I have a cat now.
That's right.
You should come to see it when you have time.
Otherwise it would think
that its owner is eaten.
Yes.
We can't let it feel like its two owners
are both eaten.
Two...
Yes, two owners.
Right.
I'm home.
I'll go up.
Hold on.
This is the gift for you.
Thanks.
You got me a gift.
I'll open it up there.
Thanks.
I'm leaving.
[Ning Meng]
Hello, Meng.
Hebo.
I need to ask you for a favor.
I want to make the vows again
in the hotel.
The vows?
An An said
that the reviewer will evaluate
all aspects of the hotel,
from the hotel administration
to the cleanliness of a toilet,
almost everything.
An ordinary customer
wouldn't pay so much attention to the carpet.
I guess it's him.
He lives across from me.
Room service.
The room service
is also the focus of the review.
[11:45 Room service Lunch: dessert,
fruit plate, one dish and one soup]
I'm the cleaner.
[15:10 Room service Cleaning]
This reviewer works pretty hard.
[18:30 Room Service
Dinner: drinks, Japanese food, desserts]
[21:00 Room service Dry cleaning of suit]
An An.
I need to report to you.
I think I found the reviewer.
Sir.
Here is the lunch you ordered.
Mr. Sheng.
Why are you here?
I passed by
and gave Liu a hand
to deliver the lunch.
Yeah?
I have work to do. Bye.
The reviewer you found...
Come in.
How is it?
The reviewer you found
is Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng?
In that room?
In that room.
Why is he living in the hotel?
I guess he is experiencing the service here
as a customer
to cope with the evaluation of reviewer.
If Mr. Sheng works so hard about it,
why are you still looking for the reviewer?
We still have to find the reviewer.
Who knows what will happen.
Just in case.
Did you give yourself away?
Give myself away?
How is it possible?
Really?
But I have a hunch that it's not going well.
It's just your hunch.
By the way,
the restaurant launched
some new dishes today.
I guess the reviewer
will go there to try the dishes tonight.
You mean
I should go to the restaurant to try my luck?
Thanks. Go to take a look.
My dining car is still outside.
I have to go.
Hebo, just say yes.
The love without making vows
is incomplete.
You don't want my love to be incomplete,
do you?
Why don't you go to ask your brother?
My brother has
way too many rules.
Besides, if I tell him that,
he's going to nagging me for a long time.
I only need the part of making vows.
Just me and Zhijun.
Okay.
I will help you.
I knew it.
You are the best.
Thank you, Hebo.
Have you decided how to do it?
This is my plan.
You even got a plan?
Of course.
Okay.
[Execution Plan]
I'll ask Emily and the others
to schedule it and book the place
as soon as possible.
Okay?
Thank you, Hebo.
I'll go back and prepare for it.
No hurry.
Have some tea with me.
Besides, I have something for you.
Didn't you already give me a wedding gift?
Who said that you have to get married
to receive gifts?
I'm the happiest person when I get presents.
Thank you, Hebo.
As long as you are happy.
Come on.
Hold on.
Excuse me.
Hurry.
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no drudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪