[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 6]
Manager Sun didn't recommend me at all.
Then why did Sheng Zhening say that?
Sheng Zhening is the boss
of Evergreen.
He wants to give you an order,
but because of his ego,
he can't say it directly.
So he took Manager Sun as an excuse.
Why does he insist on
handing over the order
of car group buying to me?
It must be because he did something wrong
and feels guilty,
so he wants to make up for it.
What is this?
Heart?
No.
I mean…
It seems that
Mr. Sheng is pretty good.
It is too hot
to drink.
What's this? Is it yours?
Cat food.
You don't have a cat.
Why buying cat food?
I found a stray cat
in Evergreen.
It looks pitiful.
So I feed it once in a while.
No wonder
you didn't resign.
You are not willing to leave it.
Sort of.
It must be a very cute cat.
Absolutely.
Nice.
Come on.
Let's change a posture.
Here.
Change a posture.
The girl should shake her fist.
And the boy should jump up.
Something like that.
All right.
Three, two, one.
Three, two, one. Go.
Nice.
One more.
Good.
Here.
Three, two, one.
The set of photos
is perfect.
Very good.
Let's change a posture.
What about you carry her?
No way.
My husband just injured his arm.
Just change a…
Your arm!
It's okay.
Bravo.
Nice.
One more set.
Hold on.
You are just going to send a contract.
Why are you so formal?
I am always like this.
In addition to handing
over the contract today,
I also want to thank Sheng Zhening in person.
After all, he gave us
a big order.
Evergreen is really the best party A
I have ever seen.
Nice order, little work.
Fast pay.
Just go.
Come on.
I am leaving.
Fast pay counts most.
Miss Xia.
Are you looking for Mr. Sheng?
I want to give him the contract
for the car group buying.
Mr. Sheng is out.
When will he be back?
I am not sure.
If there is any urgency,
I can give him a call.
Not necessary.
Well.
I will give it to you.
Hand it over to him.
Okay.
I am leaving.
Thank you.
Long time no see.
I didn't ask you.
Have you received the handkerchief
I left here before?
Don't you ask me why I am here today?
I came to hand over the contract
to Mr. Sheng.
But he is out.
I'm unlucky.
You've been in Evergreen for so long.
What do you think of Mr. Sheng?
Do you have a lot to say?
I will give you paper.
Write down all what you want to say,
to scold, and to complain about.
I'll hold it for you.
What is this?
[Handsome, overall good]
Handsome?
Overall good?
Really?
I don't think so.
He is so weird.
He has OCD.
He cares a lot.
He is troublesome
and narrow-minded.
He is totally unreasonable.
All right.
What I said is only part of it.
Generally speaking,
he is a good guy.
Today I am also here
to thank him.
We had some conflicts before.
But he just let go and helped me.
I really want to thank him.
But unluckily,
he is out.
I don't know
when we will meet again.
I hope everything goes well
with Mr. Sheng
and that he is in good health.
Be happy every day.
You work so hard.
I also wish you health
and happiness every day.
All right.
I am leaving.
I will leave you alone.
You want to write more?
[Mr. Sheng would be here. He comes to see the flowers
every afternoon at this time. Please wait a moment.]
Mr. Sheng would be here.
He comes to see the flowers
every afternoon at this time.
Please wait a moment.
Really?
Okay, I will wait for him.
Here you are.
Hebo.
I found out that you haven't
treated me
as kindly as before.
I haven't heard from you these days.
You wronged me.
I was on a business trip.
But I thought about you all the time.
Take a seat.
I asked you here
to give you the wedding gift.
What's inside?
Let me take a look.
Open it.
I asked a designer
to customize it for you.
So nice.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I would wear it
at the wedding.
So beautiful.
Hebo.
I hope that on the wedding day
you and my brother can hold me
to Zhijun together.
How can I do this?
Your brother will be jealous.
He won't.
This must be what he wants.
In the car accident that year,
if you hadn't given me
a blood transfusion in time,
I guess I would be dead now.
I know this is the kindness
of you and brother.
But it isn't in compliance
with the rules.
But I…
Listen to me.
Although I can't hold your hand,
I will definitely witness your happiness
on the spot.
All right.
Mr. Sheng.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
What a coincidence.
Why are you here?
What a coincidence?
It's just time.
I want to tell you that
the car group buying case is over.
I just chatted
with your gardener here.
He praised you.
About what?
He said you are handsome.
And?
And you are a nice guy.
Nothing else?
What else do you want?
I told you last time that
the juice of the blue daze is poisonous.
Your skin will be allergic.
Wipe the wound.
The juice of the blue daze is poisonous.
Your skin will be allergic.
Last time?
When?
Why don't I remember?
Stop pretending.
You've been exposed.
When did you find out?
Not very early.
When is that?
When I was on a business trip with you,
I saw that handkerchief
in your room.
And I knew the gardener was you.
Wipe it.
You will really be allergic.
Thank you.
I look forward to seeing you
next time.
I haven't finished yet.
Actually I want to thank you.
Thank you for comforting me that day.
Nothing else?
I have already told the rest
to the gardener.
You don't need to know.
Seven days…
I am back.
Qian.
You look so happy.
You won the lottery?
Nothing special.
Didn't you say that you hate going
to Evergreen most?
Now I find that Sheng Zhening
is not that annoying.
How can you not hate him that much?
I…
I can't make myself clear.
I will go in first.
What's wrong with you?
Unhappy?
I feel that
Sheng Zhening's relationship with Qian
is getting closer and closer recently.
What does it have to do with you
if they are getting closer?
Of course it has something to do with me.
Hold on.
Look at you.
Do you like Qian?
What's going on, Mu Xiaoyan?
Mu Xiaoyan?
Yes.
I like her.
Really?
It's true.
I actually liked her since college.
But at that time
she was still with He Zhijun.
So I couldn't tell her.
I still like her
until now.
Wait.
You had a crush on her for so long.
I'm always by your side.
Why didn't I tell that
with my intuition?
I got it.
No.
All right.
I won't speak it out.
I promise.
Dear, put it here.
Is it hot?
Not really.
We can just
buy these things
ready-made.
No way.
I have to make the wedding souvenir
by myself.
Give me that packing bag.
This.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Not this one.
This is flawed.
This pattern is not clear.
If you didn't say it,
I wouldn't find it.
I hope that everything
about our wedding is perfect.
I'll leave this one for you.
Does it taste good?
Dear.
Tomorrow we will have
the wedding rehearsal.
Are you ready?
Don't worry.
I want one too.
Feed me.
Tastes good?
Why are you still here?
Isn't your task completed?
The salary will be paid in two days.
I have to wait until I get my salary.
So I am here for my last shift.
What are you doing?
Play with the cat.
I'm afraid it has nothing to eat at night.
So I come to take a look.
I just fed it.
Don't always feed it good cat food.
If it becomes picky,
how could I raise it after you leave?
It's so little
and is growing up.
It has to eat well.
Moreover,
even if I leave,
I will often come back
to improve the food for it.
Remember what you said.
I will thank you for it.
It likes what I fed it.
Right?
Are you free tonight?
I will treat you to dinner.
Why do you invite me to dinner
out of sudden?
Because you fed it.
I don't eat cat food.
Relax.
Cat food is way too expensive.
I am growing up.
I want something expensive.
Then take this.
I!
Sit here.
Here.
Hello, may I help you?
We will take a look at the menu first.
Okay.
I will call you later.
The food is expensive here.
You work in Evergreen.
Don't you know that?
I know.
But it's okay to have a splurge occasionally.
Wait.
Take a look.
I will go to the bathroom.
So expensive.
Will he leave?
Mr. Qin.
When we check out,
you just say that
it's on Mr. Qin today,
and I only need to sign.
Okay.
Madam, would you like to order?
A stir-fried seasonal vegetable.
Spinach with nuts.
Wait.
Is there half a portion
of Yangzhou fried rice?
No.
Then one Yangzhou fried rice.
Enough.
Okay.
Let me check.
Spinach with nuts,
stir-fried seasonal vegetable.
And Yangzhou fried rice.
It's enough.
Just these dishes.
Just these dishes?
It's enough.
I am losing weight recently.
You can only  have the strength
to lose weight after you are full.
I will order two more dishes.
All right.
Well.
Fried yam with fungus.
Fried abalone with XO sauce.
Wait.
Are you sure?
Crispy shrimp balls.
Baked beef short rib with red wine.
It's enough.
We can't eat that much.
Two more.
Ginger kale.
Stewed Dalian mussels with black truffle.
Okay.
Enough.
Sure?
Okay.
I will place an order now.
Are you crazy?
So many dishes.
It will cost you a month's salary.
Well.
To be honest,
I did Qin Hebo a favor.
So he said that
no matter what I order today,
he pays the bill.
Really?
That's why I took you here.
You should have told me earlier.
Is it true?
Yes.
Waiter.
Bring me the menu.
Since it is his treat,
I will add some dessert.
I just chose it.
But I didn't order.
Iced Mochi.
Egg tart.
Two pieces each.
Do you want more?
But you ordered a lot.
One more bottle of watermelon juice.
I can take it away.
Okay.
Are you not losing weight now?
Not today.
I'm so full.
This is your purchase order.
Mr. Qin said that
you just need to sign here.
Okay.
So I should sign Qin Hebo.
Okay, thank you.
No way.
This is the most expensive.
I have to eat it.
I tried so hard.
I don't lose weight today anyway.
This is also expensive.
These two are the most expensive.
And that's also expensive.
All expensive.
Eat more.
Let me help you.
I eat quite a lot, right?
Yes.
You're a big eater.
When I was a kid,
I could eat seven plates of food
at the buffet.
Cheers.
Hello.
This is for you.
Okay, thanks.
Come over and help.
I…
There will be a wedding rehearsal.
Play music for them.
I don't know how to play music.
It's very simple.
Just press a key.
This one first.
Then let's begin from here.
Look, here.
Okay, put it here.
Got it.
Hello, Shuangshuang.
I am in the period and it hurts.
Come bring me a medicine.
Okay.
I'll give you painkillers now.
Hurry up.
I didn't bring the USB flash drive.
It's fine.
An An just said that
the hotel has backup music.
Why am I so careless?
I forgot to bring
such an important thing.
I have already called.
He should be here soon.
I will definitely remind you
to take it tomorrow.
Mr. Sheng.
Sorry for being late.
Let's start.
Okay.
Hello.
This is Wang.
Mr. Guo is busy today.
So I came instead of him.
I am the etiquette trainer
of the wedding company
and the emcee of your wedding.
I am here today
to rehearse for you.
Let's start.
Okay.
One pill should be enough.
Are you okay?
Shuangshuang.
Find a place to rest.
I'll help you with your work here.
All right.
Just over there.
I need to play music for them.
Okay.
Thank you then.
Take the water
and medicine.
You are so nice.
I am going to take a rest.
Okay, just go.
Are you going to play music?
Yes.
I will contact you
via the walkie-talkie.
Choose a romantic and lyrical song
to play.
Hold on.
I would like to ask
what is the content of today's banquet?
Wedding rehearsal.
Just choose one should be okay.
This.
[Violin version, romantic and soothing Canon]
It's your turn,
Mr. Sheng and the bride.
Slow down.
The bride should look ahead
and keep smiling.
Very good.
Slower your pace.
Lift your wedding dress
slightly.
Don't fall.
Okay, right there.
Mr. Sheng.
After sending the bride here,
you can leave.
Projection room. Projection room.
Bridegroom, get ready. Music.
Music.
All right.
[Violin version, romantic and soothing Canon]
Bridegroom.
Walk slowly towards
the beautiful bride.
Meng. Meng.
Turn it off.
Turn off the music.
Something happened.
Who played the music?
Who?
Me.
Let's go.
Meng.
An An.
Brother.
I'm all right.
You don't have to worry about me.
After so many years,
I didn't expect you
to still remember it.
I have been trying hard to forget.
It was my fault.
Brother.
The car accident had nothing
to do with you.
We shouldn't continue to
live in the painful memories of the past.
Brother.
When I met Zhijun back then,
I never thought that
he could pull me out
of such a depressed mood.
I feel very happy now.
In fact,
forgetting the pain of the past
doesn't mean
forgetting the thoughts
and feelings for father.
Brother.
Promise me.
Let's try to let go of the past
and lead the present life seriously.
All right?
Okay.
I promise you.
By the way, today's song
was just an accident.
Xia certainly didn't know.
Don't blame her.
Qian, I am sorry.
I mean…
If I knew that
today was their wedding rehearsal,
I would never let you come.
Sorry.
I just picked a piece of music randomly.
How did I provoke them?
You mean Ning Meng?
No.
It's…
Forget it, it doesn't make sense.
In short, I have no luck
in Evergreen.
Don't let me come again.
I am leaving.
Have no luck?
Xia certainly didn't know
about today's song.
Don't blame her.
Xia Qian.
What's up?
My attitude was not good today.
Sorry.
Well.
Is Ning Meng
all right?
She asked me to apologize to you.
Today
I lost control of myself.
Why does she react so much
to a piece of music?
Because that song
is related to my father's car accident.
When my father
had a car accident,
this song happened to be playing
in the car.
After that, Ning Meng
got a very rare disease.
Every time she heard this song,
she would recall that bad memory.
For so many years,
we have deliberately
avoided this song.
I'm afraid she would be influenced.
I thought she was almost recovered.
I didn't expect that today…
Sorry.
Not at all.
I am fine.
I just thought
you were strange at that moment.
It turns out to be like this.
Sorry.
Well.
As compensation,
I will treat you to a meal.
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
I will book a restaurant.
No matter how expensive it is?
Sure.
No matter how expensive it is.
Wait for me to rip you off.
Come on.
I will not show mercy.
Okay.
When you finish it in a while,
just leave.
I handed in my resignation letter.
But I should be leaving
the day after tomorrow.
Not resign.
You got fired.
Fired?
I haven't got my salary yet.
I won't leave.
Do you know that today is
wedding rehearsal
for Mr. Sheng's sister?
You screwed up
such an important thing.
Do you still want salary?
It's lucky for you
if they don't let you compensate.
Playing music
is not my job at all.
I was asked to do this by you.
Why should I take responsibility alone?
If so,
you are also responsible.
Even if I am responsible,
so what?
Even if the general manager of Evergreen
is right in front of me,
what can he do to me?
Really?
Mr. Qin.
Let's go.
Leave him alone.
Mr. Qin.
I didn't mean that.
Mr. Qin?
Apologize.
Sorry.
I just checked the toilets
of the entire banquet hall.
They're the most unhygienic ones
in our hotel.
If I were you,
I would go and clean it immediately.
All right.
You?
You…?
So you are Qin Hebo.
You lied to me for so long.
I lied to you?
You?
Wait.
You said that
you are very familiar with Qin Hebo.
To tell you the truth.
What Qin Hebo owes me is
debt of love!
Debt of love?
And don't forget,
you arrange me
the job of the driver.
How can you say that I lied to you?
One who wears suit and hair gel
is either a boss or a driver.
Our boss wouldn't keep
a stray cat on the rooftop.
You guessed right.
Just my instinct.
If I said anything inappropriate
to you
during this period,
please don't take it seriously.
Sorry.
What did you say?
Nothing.
You mean
the debt of love I own you?
Well.
No.
That's not what I said.
I didn't say that.
All right.
It's getting dark.
Let's have dinner.
I am not hungry.
I will quit.
I am leaving.
Are you coming to see it again?
Look.
It doesn't move.
This…
I'm glad to meet you
during this time.
But I may not be able
to see you often in the future.
I am here to say goodbye.
I always go on business,
what will it do if you don't come?
If he is on a business trip,
I will come to feed you.
I won't let you starve.
Why is it so spicy?
You should order a mild one.
I always have a question.
Say it.
Why did you become a bargainer?
This profession
is not common.
Of course not.
Well.
I grew up
with my mother.
We didn't have
much money.
Every time we went out shopping
we would try our best to save money.
At first,
I learned from adults
to bargain.
Later, bargaining became my habit.
I get a sense of accomplishment in it.
When I grew up,
I discovered that many people
have a bargaining demand.
Some people are afraid to bargain
because they're not eloquent.
Some people don't understand
the product
so they don't dare to bargain.
So I made up my mind.
I would use my bargaining skills
to help more consumers
buy the most wanted things
at the lowest price.
That's it.
Is that enough?
Don't you eat?
I never ate
at a roadside stall.
I am concerned.
Is that enough for you?
I can make you more.
Not necessary, thanks.
If you don't eat, I would.
Take this.
I peeled for you.
Drink water.
Should I eat or not?
[Mr. He & Miss Ning]
Thanks.
Welcome.
Okay.
Here you are.
Hello.
I took the video and came early.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to
such a happy wedding
in such a beautiful season.
A pair of true lovers
got to know each other
and fell in love.
[He Zhijun, Ning Meng]
They went through a sweet romantic journey.
At this moment,
I believe that everyone
is in the same mood as me,
looking forward to
the bride and groom.
Now, let's send blessings
to them.
It's your turn.
Dad, mom.
I'm getting married today.
Take care.
Let's bless the two of them.
Projection room. Projection room.
VCR.
Please watch the screen.
Isn't this Zhijun?
No one said anything about it.
This is so uncalled for!
What about our Ning Meng?
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no drudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪