[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 14]
How could I get sprained?
Are you old?
The ground wasn't flat there.
Okay. Okay.
Slowly
Go to bed early.
He still got no feelings even like that?
What's wrong with me?
Gosh.
Did he mean he likes another girl?
Any other ideas?
Actually,
it doesn't matter if he likes your friend.
The point is
if your friend likes him.
She hasn't yet asked him.
Then she should.
What a headache.
It's just a few days.
You must hang on.
Or what you did will be in vain.
Hello.
The price comparison and budget are done.
Okay. I'm bringing it to you.
Hello.
This is the menu.
Call me if you need anything.
Sure.
Mom, come and catch me.
Baby.
Slow down.
Excuse me.
Can I order it individually?
Sorry. Sorry.
Pardon me.
Let me clean it for you.
It's fine.
Well.
He didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Go with him.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Be careful, will you?
What should I do?
Take this and cover it.
Thank you very much.
I'll return it later.
Thanks.
Excuse me, are you Miss Xia?
Hello. Hello.
Xia Qian.
Be seated.
Please.
The water glass was turned over.
Alright.
Sorry.
Please take a look.
Sure.
This is our price comparison and budget form.
Sheng Zhening's minion, right?
The handyman from Worth Or Not, right?
I want this book.
This is a set.
26 yuan.
13 each.
13.
Okay.
Wait a second.
I'm bringing you the clothes.
Let me do it.
I have something to do there.
Hi.
Your coat.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
I'd be doomed
if it weren't for this coat.
You're welcome.
I'm leaving then.
Are you a bargainer?
Take a seat.
Okay.
My business card.
This is mine.
[Lihe Capital, Qi Lin,
Senior Financial Consultant]
Miss Xia.
Miss Qi.
I'd like to consult you,
can you bargain for apartments?
I just came back from abroad.
I wanna buy another apartment.
Mr. Sheng.
You should restraint yourself.
I'm not seeing her.
It's for business.
I don't want to be clingy.
Alright.
Don't do this again.
Bargaining for apartments
is difficult,
not like furnitures
or small commodities
which can be bought in bulk.
The more you buy,
the more discount you will get.
There is a balance point in it.
That is to say,
bargainers don't bargain for everything.
Not really.
If you do want to...
What brings you here?
Where is Shuangshuang?
She has business to do.
Zhening.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Let's go.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
What a coincidence.
No coincidence at all.
Do you remember
what was that cafe before?
Stop thinking.
In high school,
we used to buy milk tea there.
Yes.
It was a milk tea shop.
Things have changed.
You remind me of it.
Go.
Don't keep her waiting.
I won't blame you for liking her.
I didn't tell you I like her, did I?
Instead of being a General Manager,
you choose to be her assistant.
Don't tell me
it's more promising to be an assistant.
Okay. I'm off.
See you.
Do you know Qi Lin very well?
Did you know her long ago?
When?
You seems so interested
about her.
No.
I just like her,
and want to learn more about her.
Nothing more.
I'm just asking.
Zhening.
Do you know Qi Lin very well?
You seems so interested
about her.
[Qi Lin]
Hello.
Hello, Zhening.
Do you remember our violin teacher
in high school?
Yes.
It's her 60th birthday
the day after tomorrow.
I want to see her.
Will you be available?
You should go.
Why not?
By this chance,
you can leave Xia for some days.
You can't always stick together.
What?
You don't want to leave her?
Just one day.
Of course not.
Ms. Xia.
[Leave Application of Employees]
Will you go alone?
With Qi Lin.
No.
We've been busy lately.
Turn around and look for yourself.
So many reports yet to be done.
I shouldn't approve it.
But considering your
hard work,
you may go.
Come back as soon as possible.
Does she want to know everything
about their past?
Feel jealous?
The think of them being together
make her feel too anxious to sleep?
Not that serious.
She will be, very soon.
What is going on with my friend?
What else could it be?
She likes him.
She's jealous.
If you didn't come
and we met in street,
I would not recognize you.
You've grown up.
Ms. Chen.
You didn't change at all.
You are still young.
Young?
You are so sweet,
trying to make me happy.
Not like Sheng.
He doesn't talk anything
but violin.
I remember,
when he had questions,
he always told you to ask me.
Did I?
Ms. Chen.
I didn't remember that.
I remember your things
very well.
You know.
You both learned violin.
Qi was smart
and tried every means
to let me teach her
my secret violin skills.
Sheng
is persistent,
devoted to the thing
that he wants to do.
Nothing else can change his mind.
Ms. Chen.
Time changes many things.
Look, we both
have changed.
Why are you young guys
so moody?
I think,
you've got more beautiful
and he's got more handsome.
All other things are still the same.
Ms. Chen.
We come here today
to celebrate your birthday.
We haven't
learn violin since then,
but we've been missing you.
Birthday?
You remember it wrong.
My birthday is the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
Yes.
[Xia Qian, I can't go back
until the day after tomorrow]
Sorry.
I remember the time wrong.
It's fine.
Sorry, I'm late.
But...
Do you wear so little?
Does it look good?
The weather forecast says
it'll be cold today.
Didn't you see
the weather forecast?
No, I didn't.
I randomly picked one
from my closet.
Randomly?
It looks good.
Let's go.
There are wild swans in this park.
Are you cold?
I... I'm not.
- Here.
- I'm not.
Take my coat.
No, no, no.
You wear it.
I am not cold at all.
But you'll catch a cold.
That'll be bad.
Look, they all wear so much.
Here.
How about we go home?
Thanks.
We can't.
We haven't seen the wild swans.
They should be nearby.
Where are they?
- But...
- Wild swans.
Let's see them next time.
Okay?
It'll be bad if you
catch a cold.
Next time?
No.
Why don't we go to eat hot pot?
I've ordered the seats.
Hot pot?
Forget it.
I'll send you home.
Hot pot will keep us warm.
This place is still the same as before.
Nothing changed.
Do you know
why I learnt violin back then?
Why?
For you.
For me?
I didn't like violin at all.
Those years when we studied together
was the happiest time to me.
Would you like some roasted sweet potatoes?
Wait a minute.
Sir.
A box of sweet potatoes, please.
Would you like to try it?
No, thanks.
You didn't eat
roadside snacks before.
Then I found that
these snacks were quite good.
Looks like you've changed a lot
these years.
Is it because of Xia Qian?
Probably.
What are you doing?
Go and take care of it.
Yes.
Mr. Sheng.
What's up?
I want to know things
about Xia Qian,
but I can't contact her.
So,
go and see what she is doing.
Mr. Sheng, I'm at work.
I can't.
If HR goes to you,
let him call me directly.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Ms. Xia.
Thanks.
Mr. Sheng
went for a trip.
Did he tell you anything about it?
No.
You come for him today.
What's the matter?
Nothing important.
I haven't seen him for a while.
I come and take a look.
Mr. Sheng has a friend.
Her name is...
Qi...
Qi Lin.
Do you know her?
Qi Lin?
Mr. Sheng mentioned her to me.
They've known each other
since childhood.
Childhood sweethearts, you can say.
Really?
Miss Xia, why are you asking?
Mr. Sheng,
your boss,
went out for business with Qi Lin.
Not for business.
I don't know what they went for.
It's just...
Are they
childhood sweethearts?
Dating is fine.
But I'm his boss.
He has work to do.
There is much work for him.
What if the work is delayed?
Should I ask him to come back soon?
Yes.
I agree.
He didn't intend to involve
in a relationship.
But they are together on a trip.
It's possible that
they fall in love.
Feelings, you know.
How could you say that?
What if she misunderstood it?
That would be good.
Look.
She'll get nervous
if she really has feelings to you.
Be sure to tell me
before making any decision.
Got it?
Okay.
Hurry, honey.
Dad.
Here.
Come to me.
Do you feel hot?
No.
[Domestic/international air tickets]
Do I really have a cold?
[The man]
Hello.
Let's go see wild swans
if you have time today.
Okay.
Do you have a cold?
No. No.
I choked on water.
Sheng Zhening.
Sorry.
Look.
It's 38.5 degrees Celsius.
You are not fine.
Have some porridge.
[General Manager's Office]
I'll answer the call.
Hello.
Hi, Mr. Qin.
A contract from the Procurement Department
needs your signature.
Are you at home?
I'll bring it to you.
I'm not at home.
Put it on my desk.
I'll sign it tomorrow.
Okay.
You should go to work.
I'll be fine after some sleep.
It's fine.
Don't worry about me.
Take a rest.
I'm fine. Go to work.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Could you please tell me
Sheng Zhening's room number?
Sorry.
I can't tell you.
I know.
But it's urgent.
I'm his assistant.
He forgot to give me the room card.
I need to fetch something.
Sorry, Miss.
It concerns the guest's privacy.
I'm sorry
but I can't tell you.
Pardon me.
What should I do then?
My work is being delayed.
This is the company's rule.
I can't help you.
Go ahead.
Get me a room.
I'll wait for him.
Okay. Wait a second.
Have a drink?
Rui, haven't you gone to bed?
Go to sleep now.
Mom.
Don't stay up late.
Go to bed now.
I'll be back in two days.
Okay. Bye.
Bye-bye.
Why did you move abroad
all of a sudden?
After graduating from college,
I wanted to get a green card.
So I married a local Chinese.
Then I had Rui.
Over time, I realized that
it wasn't what I want.
I got divorced.
You are still
the same.
You put it into action
when you want something.
Actually, it's been a regret
that I didn't choose you.
I wonder if it's too late for me
to make up for it.
Let's
call it a day.
The services of Levend Hotel include
accommodation, catering and entertainment.
Over 100 various suites.
Classic and comfortable rooms.
Exquisite decorations.
The hotel has ultrafast optical fiber,
WiFi available.
You can keep online anytime
for convenient work.
Excellent location.
Cantonese cuisine.
Good night.
Various delicacies
for your option.
Luxurious banquet hall,
with large electronic lighting
for performance
and pro audio-visual equipment.
It offers you
a magnificent feast for eyes.
Levend Hotel.
- Turn it down, okay?
- Accommodation...
- Sorry.
- Catering.
And entertainment.
Over 100 various suites.
Classic and comfortable rooms.
Exquisite decorations.
The hotel has...
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
has activated the call reminder service.
Hello.
The front desk, Evergreen Hotel.
Can I help you?
Hello.
Could you please contact An An,
Mr. Sheng's assistant?
Sorry.
It's beyond our service.
Well.
Never mind
Thanks.
It's your bad idea.
She's turned off her phone.
My fault.
I'm going to Xia and explain it
right now. Alright?
No need.
Book me a flight now.
I'm going back.
The sooner, the better.
I'll talk with her in person.
Now?
It's late now.
You will be very tired.
I'll go instead.
Mr. Sheng,
you are just too nervous.
Maybe her phone
is out of power.
You are carried away
by your feelings for her.
I think you...
You are right.
I'm hopeless.
Fine.
I'll book a flight now.
What are you doing?
I don't want to be like this anymore.
Isn't it obvious?
I like you.
I want to be your girlfriend.
I'm not a good boyfriend.
We can't be together.
Is it really so urgent?
Please say sorry
to our teacher.
Looks like
there's no chance for me at all.
I actually come back
to win your heart.
Sorry.
For the first time, I feel so desperate.
My best wishes to you two.
Thanks.
The flight is at 11:30.
It's 10 now.
It takes one hour at least to the airport.
You need to hurry.
Okay. Got it.
Please wait a moment.
Hurry. Come in.
Wait a second, please.
Wait! Wait!
I'll call you later.
Thanks.
Can you play it a few more times?
Miss.
We've played it for over 20 times.
That's it.
We are getting off work.
You...
Five times.
Five times more.
Alright. Miss.
Mr. Sheng Zhening.
Your girlfriend is waiting for you
at the front desk.
Please come if you hear this.
Mr. Sheng Zhening.
Your girlfriend is waiting for you
at the front desk.
Please come if you hear this.
Mr. Sheng Zhening.
Your girlfriend is waiting for you
at the front desk.
Please come if you hear this.
Mr. Sheng Zhening.
You ask for me?
How come you are here?
♪Teaches me to be honest
to myself and to the world♪
♪Cherish every simple day♪
I'm asking, why are you here?
Well...
♪If it weren't for you to insist on♪
You heard it.
As the broadcast says,
I like you.
I want to be your girlfriend.
Whatever.
I've confessed to you.
Whether you like me or not,
I've already...
♪Love would heat up and walk slowly♪
♪Slowly heat up, ordinary becomes profound♪
♪Slowly we become more and more alike♪
♪Both hearts are clear♪
♪Love has to heat up slowly
to comprehend the experience♪
♪Slowly I found the angel♪
♪Even if the glitter is squeezed
into wrinkles♪
♪It's still the happiness of life♪
♪The hat air balloon near to the sky♪
♪I ever made a wish to the cloud♪
♪And the rain that we got drenched♪
♪Was the way I said I love you♪
♪Love would heat up and walk slowly♪
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don‘t worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no grudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪