[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 12]
Have you eaten?
Have more.
Sheng Zhening.
I got to praise you.
When I read that kind of novels before,
I always think
that the president has nothing to do.
You know,
except for dating the heroine,
what else can he do?
But since I met you,
I've changed my mind.
It turns out that the president
can also be troubled
and there are things that he can't solve.
Sorry.
I burst your bubble about the president.
No.
It's great.
I found it very amiable.
Amiable?
Yeah.
In the novel.
I mean, the character.
This kind of president seems very folksy.
Let's eat.
Have some, too.
I already ate.
[Mom]
It's my mom.
Mom.
Qian.
Ask Sheng to go to work later.
I brought you chicken soup.
She is going to bring chicken soup for us.
Stop eating.
Well,
you go down first.
Go to the company.
I will leave later.
Why?
I can have some chicken soup.
Wake up.
Don't you get bored of
acting in front of my mom?
Hurry.
She talks too much.
Get ready. Stop eating.
No, I want to have chicken soup.
Sheng Zhening!
Qian.
Are you there?
Qian?
Mu Xiaoyan.
I'll take a look.
Qian.
What?
Qian?
Are you inside?
What's up?
I'm changing clothes.
I'm here to send you
the financial statement of this month.
Well,
put it in the office downstairs.
I'll go down and read it later.
Qian.
Are you okay?
Why did I hear a man's voice?
I'm watching TV series.
All right.
I'll put it downstairs.
What?
I'll go down first.
Find a chance to go down, got it?
Aunt Liping.
Let me take it for you.
Here. Take it.
You came just right.
Come on, come in.
Let me make an introduction.
He is Sheng.
Xia Qian's boyfriend,
the General Manager of Evergreen Hotel.
Aunt.
Come on, have some chicken soup.
Okay, let's have some soup.
What does Auntie mean?
You are...
It's fake.
We pretend to be together.
Mu Xiaoyan.
Anyway,
you must keep it a secret for me.
There is no need to live together
since it's fake.
We are not living together.
We only share the apartment.
I don't believe it.
I don't care if you believe it or not.
Don't say anything in front of my mom
and don't ask anything.
It's sweet and delicious.
It's so great.
The chicken soup in our hotel
is no match for this.
Have more if you like it.
Come on, Xiaoyan.
Have some, too.
Qian.
Come on, have some.
How is it?
My mom makes the best chicken soup.
Sheng.
I want to ask you,
when are you and Qian
going to have a baby?
I finally explained it.
I told Xiaoyan
that we are pretending to be together.
Why would you explain to him?
Of course I have to explain to him,
so it will be easier for you.
You don't have to avoid him anymore.
I think the fact
that we pretend to be together,
more people know it,
higher the risk of exposure.
Don't worry.
I talked to him.
He wouldn't dare.
Just leave.
You won't be able to catch bus 11 later.
Go.
I'm leaving.
Hello.
What's wrong?
Something bad happened.
The customs found some pests
in the batch of African logs
we imported.
There are termites, buprestid beetles,
and some seeds of invasive plants.
Did the customs say
what they will do about it?
They will be in quarantine first.
The problematic wood
will be destroyed directly.
In this case,
we won't be able to
keep up with the schedule.
My existing funds
are not enough to buy new wood.
Has the renovation of
Evergreen Building No. 2 stopped?
Why didn't I think of
the risk of termite when I made
the comparison budget?
They probably wouldn't have bought the wood
if I had written it down.
It's not your fault.
That batch of wood was
the most cost-effective choice we had.
Who would have expected such a thing?
But...
I'm supposed to be very sensitive
to these details.
I'll be back later today.
Don't wait for me for dinner.
This is a gift for you.
Sorry, you misunderstood.
We are not a couple.
This is my younger sister.
How much have you drunk?
Stop drinking.
Have some razor clams to sober up.
What's wrong? Are you dumped?
Wait.
You are nodding
and then shaking your head.
Are you dumped or not?
It's a one-sided love. Does it count?
One-sided love...
Sure.
Of course.
So you are dumped, what's the big deal?
You will
find a better girlfriend, right?
Look at Qian.
She found Sheng.
He is good in all aspects.
Qian and Sheng Zhening are a fake couple,
but love grows over time,
not to mention they are living together now.
She will be tricked into
being with him one day.
What did you say?
A fake couple?
Qian doesn't let me tell you.
Don't tell her that.
You're back.
How is it going? Is it okay?
It's fine.
What about the renovation?
Can it continue?
Is there any solution?
Don't worry.
It's a piece of cake for me.
Go to rest.
I heard
your conversation with Mr. Song
outside the door that day.
I know you want to be
the general manager of Evergreen.
What do you think?
I can give you the position
of general manager.
When my dad and Meng had a car accident,
it was you who saved Meng.
During these years,
you've been helping me
become a qualified
hotel manager.
Hebo.
Compared to the position of
Evergreen's general manager,
I think our relationship is more important.
I was just doing what an employee should do.
Honestly,
I've always been grateful to you
over these years.
I didn't rush into
making such a decision.
Objectively,
you are totally up for it.
There is one more thing.
There are termites
on the wood for renovation.
I think you have known it.
My funds
won't be available for a while.
If you become the general manager,
I hope you can convince all shareholders
to renovate Building No. 2.
Is Building No. 2 that important?
Very important.
Is it an attached condition?
It's my request.
Okay, I promise you.
I'll try my best.
Shareholders,
I have one thing to announce.
From today,
I will resign as
general manager of Evergreen.
Mr. Qin will replace me
as the new general manager.
I will serve Evergreen wholeheartedly.
I hope you can support me.
Next, let's discuss
the plan to renovate Building No. 2.
What?
Are you going to help Sheng Zhening
renovate Building No. 2?
Yes.
The shareholders have agreed.
Why are you doing this?
Whether we can acquire Evergreen
mainly depends on
how many shares we have in Evergreen
and how many shareholders in Evergreen
can accept
Lihe Capital's acquisition.
And also,
Sheng Zhejing is a little impulsive
about renovating Building No. 2,
but in the long run,
I think there is a reason
why he persists in doing it.
Have you decided?
All right.
Just do as you said.
Why are you changing the curtains
for me so suddenly?
Didn't you say
the curtains before
can't blot out light well?
So I changed it for you.
Poor boy.
You lost your job.
Who knows how long you will stay in my house?
Barring accidents,
they will invite me back
three months later.
Are you Zhuge Liang?
How are you so sure?
Let's wait and see.
Xia Qian.
Mom.
What's wrong?
You two are not a couple at all.
How do you know it?
How do I know it?
Mu Xiaoyan told me
that he is fake.
Xia Qian, well done.
I'm so worried about your marriage.
You found someone to fool me.
You're even
living with him now.
Yes.
I lied to you
and I hid it from you before.
But I'm in love with him now!
Sheng Zhening is my boyfriend!
Why were you so impulsive?
How should I face him tomorrow
after I did that?
Stop.
What's wrong?
Don't you have something to say
after what happened last night?
I was forced.
You were forced?
By whom?
My mom.
All right.
It's my fault.
I was frivolous and rude.
I took advantage of you, okay?
How are you going to make it up to me?
Make it up?
What do you want?
What do you want to do?
Don't go too far.
What are you nervous about?
I'm not nervous.
Do you think
I'm going to kiss you back?
Of course.
Or what?
You suddenly came so close to me.
There is something on your hair.
Well, thanks.
I want to eat well tonight.
That's how you make it up to me.
No problem.
Xia Qian.
Xu Lu.
Why are you here?
I heard from our classmates
that you opened a bargaining company
and it's doing well.
So I came here to take a look.
This is my company.
Well, it's not that easy.
It's hard to start a business.
I can barely make ends meet.
Do you need anything?
A friend of mine
works for a network technology company.
Their company is moving recently,
and they need to purchase
a new batch of office supplies,
like printers, tables, and chairs,
but the budget is limited.
I'm thinking
that maybe your bargaining company
can help.
Sure, we can.
Thank you very much for coming to me.
If we can work together,
we will go all out.
That would be great.
I'm just on my way out.
Let's talk while walking.
Okay.
It feels different
to sit in this chair.
How does it feel?
Very tired.
I just realize
that Sheng Zhening may be
way smarter than I thought.
It's not easy for him
to manage Evergreen so well
at his age.
Mr. Qin.
You just took over
the position of general manager.
You are not used to it yet.
You will do better than Mr. Sheng.
By the way,
the person in charge of
the renovation of Building No. 2
will come to discuss work.
Are we really going to help Sheng Zhening
renovate Building No. 2?
I promised Sheng Zhening
that the renovation of Building No. 2
will proceed smoothly.
What about lobbying other shareholders
to sell Evergreen shares?
These are two different things.
Just do according to plan.
Okay.
What are you thinking about?
How is your friend
with that guy?
You are right.
They are long-lost siblings.
Really?
How can you smile?
- I'm about to cry...
- What are you talking about?
Don't gossip during working time.
We were not gossiping.
We got work to do.
What is it?
It's very urgent.
Listen up.
I need the comparison budget next week.
Okay.
Are you so busy?
Yeah.
The project plan
is due to finish next week,
but the client wants it three days later.
I must work overtime.
Don't worry about me.
Go ahead and eat.
Does your company need
an assistant?
Assistant?
I can't live in your home for free.
I can work as your assistant.
The salary will be used to pay the rent.
How is it?
Who?
You work as my assistant?
You were the general manager of Evergreen,
but it's different from being an assistant.
It's not at all the same.
Difference in profession
makes one feel worlds apart.
You can't do it.
Why don't you let me try it first?
Okay, let's eat first.
As an assistant,
[Worth Or Not]
you should read the terms of reference
given by Huixin Technology first,
and then get familiar with part of the budget
that Fu Shuangshuang worked out.
This is our meeting room.
If you have more time,
you can find some
cost-effective brands
of office desk and chair online
according to Huixin Technology's budget
and make a
very detailed budget comparison report.
I'll send you
the template later.
After you finish these,
you are ready to get off work.
This is
your desk.
Okay.
When can I
see the plan of Huixin Technology?
It's your first day at work.
Reviewing the plan
is my job.
Where are the other people?
They worked all night last night.
They won't come here today.
They are working at home.
This is your first day at work.
You don't have to force yourself
or pretend to know everything.
Just ask me if there is anything
you don't understand.
Okay.
Madam.
Don't call me Madam.
It sounds weird.
Just call me Xia Qian.
What's wrong?
Is there anything you don't understand?
I've finished my work.
What should I do next?
That fast?
What about the price comparison report?
Do you finish that, too?
I read
our price comparison report.
Huixin Technology emphasized
that they want environmentally friendly
and hygiene office supplies,
but the carpet we picked
may have high levels of formaldehyde.
Yeah?
Here is all the information
on the carpet supplier.
Two months ago,
a company sued them for
excessive formaldehyde in their carpets.
Although the lawsuit
has not been resolved yet,
I don't think we should take this risk.
Therefore, this company
should be delisted
in the final price comparison.
What should I do next?
I've cleaned the glass
vacuumed the carpet
and watered the flowers.
I also tidied the bookshelf.
What should I do next?
Have some rest.
Why did you cook so many dishes?
There are only two of us.
The flowers look good.
Honey, do you like it?
I'll get some new flowers
every day from now on.
There is no need to do that.
We are married now.
Isn't it good to make life simple?
We need a little ritual.
It adds color to our life.
We can't live the same life every day.
Eat, sleep, and go to work.
How boring is that?
Where did you learn this from?
In the book.
Honey, have more.
Today, I heard from Xiaotong
that you've been so busy at work
that you have no time to eat.
You should eat well at home.
She also told me
that you volunteer
to work overtime every day.
You work harder than them.
Meng.
Do you mean the Xiaotong in my hospital?
How do you know her?
She often comes to my shop
to buy coffee and cakes.
Honey.
I think I made a perfect decision
to open my shop
in front of your hospital.
I can see you more
every day
and help you bond with your colleagues.
How great is that?
Meng.
Actually, I don't want you
to meet my colleagues
in our hospital that often.
We are just colleagues.
There is need to get too close with them.
I'm afraid it might affect
my judgment at work if we get too close.
Honey.
I didn't talk a lot with them.
I just want to
know more about you.
I opened the shop in front of your hospital
so that I can see you more often.
Since we got married,
we've been spending less time together.
I see.
Meng.
From now on, except for work,
I'll spend the rest of the time
with you at home.
Have more.
It took me a while to cook these dishes.
Don't worry, Mr. Sheng.
The renovation of Building No. 2
is going well.
I'm keeping an eye on it for you.
Good.
By the way,
There is one more thing.
What is it?
How to be a good assistant?
Assistant?
Are you working for Miss Xia
as her assistant?
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask.
Look,
I finished all the work
ahead of time
and I did it really well.
I even
did the work
that's not mine.
Shouldn't the boss
like this kind of assistant?
Mr. Sheng.
Clearly, you've been used to be
a boss since young.
You have no experience of
being a subordinate.
How come?
In addition to
being adequate for the job,
a good subordinate
should also acquire
a necessary skill.
What is it?
Play dumb.
Play dumb?
Yeah.
Think about it,
if you act very smart
in front of your boss,
what will he do?
He will be wary of you
and feel that you might
threaten his status,
so as to alienate you.
This is when you should play dumb properly
to make him feel
you are under his control
and make him feel safe,
also give him
a sense of accomplishment occasionally
when he instructs you.
You made a lot of mistakes in front of me,
but you were playing dumb?
I didn't, Mr. Sheng.
I really haven't met your requirements.
Look for yourself.
How did you make the report?
It's full of mistakes.
Didn't you finish your work well yesterday?
How did you mess it up today?
It's my first time making a report.
I'm a little rusty.
And I was in a hurry...
I got to criticize you about this.
It's normal to make mistakes
when it's your first time to do it.
It's okay, no problem.
But it is your fault to
put too much emphasis on efficiency.
I'm sorry.
All right. All right.
We all started as rookies.
Now you know your mistakes,
just don't do it again.
How should I make a report then?
Bring your chair here.
I'll teach you.
You are such a headache.
This report is so simple.
Please sit down.
How do I feel that Sheng Zhening
is really cunning?
He is working hard.
How is that cunning?
I mean,
as a general manager of a hotel,
even he comes down in the world,
at least he should have a place to stay.
Now he is even
working in Worth Or Not.
Wait,
didn't you watch the news?
He is also quite miserable now.
Our Qian
just can't bear to see others suffer.
She is going to help him,
and she won't let him live there for free.
Don't worry.
Qian knows how to protect herself.
Are you a man?
What are you doing?
Let's arm wrestle.
If I win,
you will listen to me.
It's a battle between man and man.
Dare or not?
What if I win?
I'll Listen to you.
Okay.
Go ahead
and change the water
in the drinking fountain.
The roasted sweet potatoes are done.
It smells so good.
Roasted sweet potatoes.
Let's eat now.
It's a little hot.
Be careful.
Yeah.
So sweet.
It's roasted so well.
Come here now.
The roasted sweet potato is super delicious.
I left some for you.
No.
I never ate street food.
It's so good.
It's roasted perfectly.
I controlled
the temperature well this time.
I thought about it.
It doesn't hurt to have one.
Here...
I already bit it.
Do you still want it?
Don't be so gross.
It's okay.
I'll buy you one later.
It is so sweet.
Have you got the patient records ready
for tomorrow's appointment?
Yes.
There will be two patients tomorrow.
Here are all the medical records.
One of them
was transferred from Director Lu.
I looked at the medical record.
The patient doesn't like
rooms that are too bright.
Okay.
By the way,
A few patients
have missed their return visit.
Contact them tomorrow.
It's best to make an appointment
for a recent visit.
Okay.
Doctor He.
What day is it today?
Why did you buy such beautiful flowers?
Honey.
During your working days,
the beautiful flowers will
accompany you for me.
Your wife who loves you the most.
How is it, Mr. Wang?
Not so good.
What's the problem?
First, I really don't like
the template of the quotation.
It hurts my eyes.
It's easy to solve, Mr. Wang.
We will change the template
to light green tomorrow.
Then it's the office supplies you chose.
We are a technology company.
The office supplies
should have a sense of tech.
Didn't I send you a reference picture?
We looked at your reference picture.
But we checked it.
The set of desks and chairs you like
is an entry lux.
Your company's budget is limited.
To balance the budget,
we decided to choose
this set of desk and chair
only for the staff
above the vice general manager.
Can't you buy some knockoffs?
Of course we can't.
The quality is not guaranteed.
There will be safety hazards.
Anyway, I don't really like
the office supplies you chose.
All right.
Let's call it a day.
I have work to do.
Give me a new
comparison budget tomorrow.
Hold on.
Did you say tomorrow?
The whole company is waiting for
new office supplies.
Hurry up.
I won't see you off.
Take care.
Can't we
drop this project?
Why not? We can make some money.
There are worse clients
who don't pay the final payment,
steal the fruits of labor
and terminate the contract.
He's no big deal.
It's okay. You will know later.
Mr. Sheng.
Look up
Huixin Technology for me
and see if they are working
with our hotel in any way.
Okay.
Sheng Zhening.
See how sleepy you are.
You don't have to be there with me.
Go upstairs and have some rest.
How can an employee gets off work
before the boss?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's hypoglycemia.
I only need a candy.
Have one.
Well,
have some rest upstairs.
Let's go.
Thanks.
No.
I'm still a little dizzy.
I need to sleep for half an hour.
If I don't get up later,
remember to wake me up.
Hello.
How is it?
Huixin Technology
is not working with us.
But I think the owner
is your college classmate.
You both graduated from
Stanford Business School.
He is called...
Zi... Zixuan.
Chen Zixuan?
Right, Chen Zixuan.
Do you know him?
♪If you don't get it, just let it be♪
♪No need to find out, just be free♪
♪By accident I came to the sea♪
♪So I brought you here with me♪
♪Humans are strange♪
♪Full of  hope no matter it's good or bad♪
♪Giving my heart isn't enough♪
♪The debt of love can never be paid off♪
♪The fun of love, the trick of love♪
♪How speechless, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪
♪May the waiting be worth it♪
♪Patience will never fail♪
♪Every flower needs to be tended♪
♪Slow down and enjoy the journey♪
♪Hold no drudge but only accountability♪
♪Let's live in the moment together♪
♪I bought a whole bag of candies♪
♪The kind that you love♪
♪The effort of love, the simplicity of love♪
♪How terrible, love, love, love♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪Be who you are
and don't worry about the future♪
♪You can be willful and stubborn♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪You can cheat or guess♪
♪No one can change the fate♪
♪You can destroy it and start over♪
♪I'll be by your side anyway♪
♪One who's loved is always a kid♪