[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 36]
Next,
let's welcome Chief Zheng of the Military Command
to do the prewar mobilization rally.
Comrades,
it has been 54 years since the establishment of
the People's Republic of China.
Can anyone tell me
in the past 54 years, before the establishment of
the People's Republic of China,
[Final fight, final victory]
how many wars happened
in our country？
Sir.
117 wars.
54 years
before the founding of the PRC,
big or small,
more than one hundred wars
happened
on the land under our feet.
Even,
half of
our motherland
once fell into the clutches of the invaders
and was invaded cruelly.
This history
is not far away from us.
Again let's talk about the 54 years.
Can anyone tell me
54 years after
the founding of the PRC,
how many wars happened
around the world?
Sir.
206 wars.
According to some political leaders
and historians,
after the second World War,
[Life and death together company]
the world
entered the Cold War.
Then,
what are these 206 wars?
During the 54 years,
how many countries
[Life and death together company]
were destroyed by the war?
How many countries
lost their sovereignty
in the war?
How many countries
lagged behind for decades
due to failure in the war?
How many
people died or got injured
and how many families were broken in the war?
How many children and grandchildren's lives
were changed because of them?
Is this really the Cold War?
Some comrades said,
we are the army that hasn't fight in the war for many years.
This is true.
This is because our country is getting stronger
and our army is getting stronger.
We are not bellicose.
We have never invaded
and will never invade other countries.
So,
we are relatively far away from wars.
I hope this time range
can be longer to last forever.
I hope in this world,
there will never be one bullet
flying above us.
[Oath-taking Rally of "Operation Azure", final fight, final victory courageous, tenacious]
But,
this is impossible.
[Final fight, final victory]
I know this,
and you also do.
War
is never based on our wills.
We have not yet achieved
the complete unity of the country.
The Chinese nation
is building the great cause of modernization.
This army
is not built for
the peace of the 54 years.
But for the infinite peace
of the Chinese nation.
[Oath-taking Rally of "Operation Azure" final fight, final victory courageous, tenacious]
Comrades,
although we live in a peaceful world,
we will be in danger if we forget about the wars.
As soldiers,
what should we do?
♫Go on, go on, go on♫
[Oath-taking Rally of "Operation Azure" final fight, final victory courageous, tenacious]
♫Our troop run towards the sun♫
♫Standing on motherland's ground♫
[Oath-taking Rally of "Operation Azure" final fight, final victory courageous, tenacious]
♫We are the hope the people long♫
♫Nobody can shot us down♫
♫We are the worker and farmer's son♫
♫We are the nation's loyal gun♫
♫Never give up, never end up♫
[Oath-taking Rally of "Operation Azure" final fight, final victory courageous, tenacious]
♫Never shut up♫
♫Till all of enemies are tear up♫
♫The flag of Chairman Mao covers every town♫
[Life and death together company]
♫Listen! Wind blowing bugle song♫
♫Listen! The glory song sounds so strong♫
♫Comrades, we are going to♫
♫The liberation battleground♫
♫Our country border town♫
♫Go on,go on, marching towards the sun♫
♫The final victory♫
♫And the liberation of all our land♫
Dear chiefs,
we have arrived at Qiaotou Island.
The direction my finger is pointing
is the north of Xian Di.
[East, south, west, north]
Qiaotou Island,
has a land area of 2.6 square kilometers.
The northwest sides are cliffs
with the main peak at a height of 125 meters.
The east side is all reefs.
There are many submerged reefs at sea.
The waves are relatively large.
And the island coastline is steep rocky shores
which are rather tortuous and cannot be docked.
There is a wharf on the south side
with a beachhead of about 100 meters.
Boats are all docked there.
Under the cliff in the northwest,
there is an evergreen broad-leaved forest area
of 0.6 square kilometers.
The vegetation condition is quite good.
Even if the vegetation is in good condition, can we hide
or fight at will?
It's such a small area.
Take down this place within three charges.
Check the signals.
Ask the drill director
if the image is clear.
Inform the dispatchers
to enter the command post of the Red and Blue Army
and contact the commanders.
Yes.
Commander.
This is the real-time reconnaissance aerial data
from the drone on Qiaotou Island.
[The dock of the Blue Army]
It seems that the Blue Army
has done quite a lot of work on the island.
You mean the underground construction work?
They took away two days' supplies,
mostly compressed biscuits and canned food.
In addition,
they also prepared some
meat, snacks and vegetables for the observation team.
Commander,
the observation team has got on the island.
Chief wants you to run there and report.
Run there to report?
They are the observation team, not the director department.
Tell them I am busy now.
The observation team is inspecting the shore artillery position
and asks us to move the position.
I know that
we can't let them idle.
It's not a good thing for them to take a break.
Sir,
we have eyes on the observation team.
Are you idiots?
If you put the shore artillery here,
the first wave of firepower
can kill you all.
Withdraw them now.
Change position.
Chiefs.
Chief.
The accommodation is ready,
chief, please go and have a rest.
Chief won't go.
He worries about our shore artillery positions
and thinks we have placed it in the wrong place.
Captain.
The shore artillery positions are set here
with a good view.
By the way.
I thought we have made a deal not to intervene.
You should keep your promise.
Gao Liang.
Sir.
Do you really want to put the shore artillery here?
Yes.
We don't intervene
and give you the power, but look how you have used it.
Not to mention 48 hours,
you cannot withhold for even
48 minutes.
Captain,
it is true that it is quite conspicuous
to place the shore artillery here.
But I have also set up some
powerful insurance measures.
I am sure
the Red Army
will not dare to point its finger in this place.
Gao Liang,
what do you mean?
Chief.
In fact,
you are with the observation team.
So according to the regulation of the drill,
I can't tell you about the details.
But to be frank,
the observation posts of the chiefs
are just behind this place.
It is less than 100 meters from here.
So I place the shore artillery here.
Gu Yiye will never have the guts
to blow this place.
So you want to use the observation team as the shield, right?
But don't forget.
Although we use the
laser simulation countermeasure system now,
the fireworks
can still hurt people.
You have placed all these chiefs
in danger.
If something happens, who can bear the responsibility?
Captain Qin,
this is your fault.
The most important thing is that you have cheated.
Li,
this is not cheating.
Qin, don't fool with me.
Gao Liang, let me just ask you this.
Do you have any idea
of respecting the cadres and love your soldiers?
In thirty minutes,
move 300 meters back.
This is the oder.
Captain.
Gao Liang.
You really don't want to relocate your shore artillery?
Chief.
Yes.
Really?
Then don't change it.
Chief.
I think it is a good idea
to place the shore artillery here.
You should let him command.
Don't intervene.
You should mind your own business.
Chief.
You are making the promise again.
I am the only commander here on the island.
The observation team will not intervene in
anything.
How can we take back what we said.
All orders on this island
will come from you.
You don't need to mind us.
Bring the food and drink
to the observation team
and go fight your war.
Yes.
Thank you, Chief.
Chief.
This way please.
The safety problem is a major issue.
If we don't intervene,
if anything happens...
If nothing happens,
how can we know where problems will occur?
If we talk about safety all day,
how can we conduct military drills
and how can we strengthen our army?
But...
But what? Qin Hanyong,
you really think Gao Liang means what he said?
Do you really think he is going to use us as the shield?
How dare he?
But, just now...
No more buts.
With so many people here, no one noticed it.
Just go and touch it.
Touch the oil on the artillery.
Is this real artillery?
It is just a camouflage.
The whole shore artillery is camouflaged.
Gao Liang's shore artillery position
is not even here.
A group of captains
pretend to be teachers and lecture others.
Gao Liang gets the scores
with his first move.
Seventeen objects on the island,
nearly half of them are fake.
He is messing with us.
The important point is not on the known targets.
Gao Liang is not a cook.
He will not place the fire points in the spotlight
for us to get rid of.
Now we have to find a way
to figure out his real intention.
Otherwise we will definitely be in a disadvantaged situation
when we get on the island.
How is
the deployment
of the Blue Army's coordinated operations?
The intelligence is all collected,
and we are making the defense plan.
Defense?
Be clear of our identity.
We are attacking and they are defending.
At the first sound of the gunshot,
I want the Special Operations Battalion to know
what it means to sit still waiting for death
and what it means to be beaten up.
No, no, no.
No regrets.
You are fooling with us.
[Idea Map of "Operation Azure" Island Capture Drill]
You already started playing.
Your sister-in-law Hongyan brought something to us.
What is it?
Here, have a try.
Sure.
Chief.
What is the director department doing?
We have so many chiefs here.
They didn't even arrange some officials for us.
And we have to run errands ourselves.
Yes.
Here.
Let's keep playing.
Keep playing.
Go, go.
The director group of Red and Blue Army in Operation Azure.
I am the General Director He Zhigeng.
The commanders of both Red and Blue Army, please adjust your time.
Now it is the 15th.
58 past 23.
The drill will begin in two minutes.
Repeat.
The director department will offer no further notice.
The drill will begin in two minutes automatically.
The show starts.
Apart from the air defense post and the observation post,
everyone gets down to the bunker.
Tell them to block their ears
and get a good sleep.
What should we do about the observation team?
They like to see the noisy hilarity.
So let them stay there
and listen to the shore artillery.
Inform the drill director department.
Tell them that
there is no fire point from me
within 100 meters around the observation team.
As long as one cannonball comes out from there,
I will lose.
Understood.
Go and check the air defense post.
I will go meet my guest.
Sure.
Apply electromagnetic suppression in thirty-seven seconds
to shield off Qiaotou Island's
all electronic signals within a radius of three nautical miles.
Open high-frequency radio.
Yes.
Implement Action Zero starts in thirty-two seconds.
At one o'clock,
Dolphin Commando departures.
Yes.
Chief.
The Eagle Squad will be handed over to you.
Don't make any mistake.
Feel assured.
Chief Jian.
Yes.
Notify the troops to strengthen the defense
and enter the defensive position according to the drill plan.
The drill has begun.
Turn on the high-frequency radio and contact the neighboring troops
to let them report the situation.
Yes.
Send two people who are good at swimming
to Hutou Reef and Xingkui Reef respectively.
Tell Zong Hui and Wang Yi,
maybe after dawn,
they will lose contact with our department.
From now on, they can act on their own.
Those who were sent out don't have to return.
Yes.
[Defensive Layout of Qiaotou Island]
Sir.
The Red Army used short-range surface-to-surface tactical missiles.
Strike direction?
No report.
What is Gu Yiye doing?
Is he planning to
blow up Qiaotou Island at one shot
so that he could get on the island before sunrise?
Sir, we got the news.
The B2 target and B3 target of Blue Army
[Comprehensive coordination]
were attacked by missiles at the same time.
[Defensive Layout of Qiaotou Island]
What?
Dolphin Commando, action.
Eagle Squad, action.
Discover the power wing.
Shoot it.
You're lucky that you didn't die.
How many people were captured?
Sir, 25 people.
You are a cadre.
Talk about the purpose of the attack.
Platoon leader.
Take down the enemy's command post.
What if you failed?
Take down the air defense post
and the observation post.
You mission has accomplished.
Get everyone changed to dry clothes
and give them some hot water.
No bastard can be a commando.
We should treat them well.
Commander,
the Dolphin Commando failed to land on the island,
the raid did not achieve the expected purpose.
Report loss.
All three rubber boats are sunk.
Twenty-five people are captured.
Are you sure it is twenty-five?
Yes.
Report the condition of the Eagle Squad.
Among the three powered delta wings,
Two were hit and forced to quit the combat.
One had to make an emergency landing near the main peak of Qiaotou Island.
Who is that?
King of the gliders, Dao Xiaohui.
Repot to the drill director department.
The first raid of the Red Army failed.
Commander, this operation...
Just report like this.
Yes.
The director department has made it clear
that in the raid of your side,
one got killed,
twenty-five were captured.
Out of three powered hang gliders,
two were hit,
one was hanged at the cliff.
What are you guys doing?
You guys
worry too much in places you should not worry.
Even if you have the commanding rights in your hands,
what can you do?
Just the old three axes.
What can we expect to see
in fights between two dummies?
Chief,
you bit so hard.
In your view,
our army does not deserve to be
the main force of the military command.
We are not that bad.
Right.
I have considered this as well.
If an army
wants a bigger development,
it must conduct bold innovation.
We have to let the younger generation
have the commanding authority.
We don't know
how many new tactics they can perform.
He landed here.
He is definitely hurt, so he won’t go far.
Spread out and search.
Yes.
The two planes we shot down are
single-pilot hang gliders.
We have caught the pilots.
Their mission is to
observe the battle situation of the Red Commando
and report to the red command post in real time.
They need three observation planes?
It is the first strike and also a raid.
It means a lot to the battle.
We didn’t use our major force.
If we had used…
What if one plane ran off among the three?
Then they will know
the deployment of troops on the island.
I think something was wrong.
What?
If you want to have a sneak attack, you will definitely choose
a time when defenses are more slack.
But as soon as the director team said the time began,
he started to attack.
There are so many defenders on our island
and heavy weapons.
They only sent 26 people.
They are intended to be killed.
If you say so,
there are some problems here.
What is Gu Yiye
thinking about?
The two powered hang gliders that were shot down are in your hands.
Did the plane that have an emergency landing give off smoke?
No.
It can continue to fight.
No smoke.
So,
he made a forced landing on purpose.
Hurry up and contact Niu
to control the hang glider.
Commander, Niu is caught.
What?
He hid in the dark.
and stunned Niu.
He then pulled him into the powered hang glider
and flew off.
A bird with a broken wing
can take Niu away from
your gang of special forces?
The terrain in that place is particularly dangerous,
and it is impossible for a hang glider to land safely.
But he did make it.
Did you see the pilot?
No.
But I guess
it is the King of the gliders, Dao Xiaohui
Did Niu give off smoke?
Yes, he did. But got captured anyway.
You should shoot him down
if he was captured
no matter life or death.
Commander, drill director department called.
[Defense Layout of Qiaotou Island]
Our airfields, ground-based missile sites,
and sea support ships
were simultaneously hit by red missiles.
Say it again.
The drill director department said
all our air, land
and sea support forces
have been destroyed.
The airfield has been blown up.
[Red Army Position Red Army Command Post No. 1 Observation Point Artillery Position Cliff]
Artillery position was destroyed.
Niu Mancang was captured.
Stop, they are still reporting the condition.
Horrible.
Report the current situation.
Chief.
The enemy's navigation tower, runway,
oil depot, all planes, none were spared.
Nice.
What is wrong with Gu Yiye?
He
really doesn't value our relationship.
He really has something.
Here, give it to me.
Chief.
Call the general director.
I want to have a conversation with him.
Commander.
Three transport boats have fallen into our hands.
[Chief Determination Map of Troop A Qiaotou Island]
The Blue Army's shore artillery positions have also been completely cleared.
Also,
we've deciphered the code of the Blue Army.
According to this code, we can send all-normal signals
to the Blue Army's neighboring army.
Report the commander's situation to the drill director department.
Notify the troops to prepare for attack.
In that case, in the following time,
Gao Liang has no ground-based artillery support.
[Director of the Red Army]
No air-based support,
or sea-based support,
or supplementary supply line.
[General Director]
Then the Blue Army
almost loses all
support.
Has the director department considered this situation before?
We have thought about
electronic warfare in the first round,
artillery attack,
island blockade and control,
and the island's fixed fire clearance,
and then the drill will begin.
[Branch of the Armed Force]
But we never thought
that the Red Army will use all its missals
in the first round.
This is a gamble.
If the Blue Army could withhold this attack,
the Red Army is doomed to fail.
[General Director, director of the Red Army]
I have to admit
that the Red Army wins this gamble.
Chief,
Qiaotou Island is already an isolated island,
this battle will not last for 48 hours.
I understand.
Go on.
We are the observation team and we don't intervene.
Come on, chief.
The airfield is not even in the drill area.
How can Gu Yiye
fight outside the drill area?
The director department allowed him to do this?
Qin, I am sorry.
Isn't the airfield your supportive power?
Of course the director department will judge the attack to be effective.
Half a month’s work
takes less than two hours to finish.
What’s wrong with the Special Operations Battalion?
Gu Yiye didn't play by the book.
How should we fight the following wars?
The real attack of the Red Army
will begin now.
Inform the troop,
be prepared to battle.
Inform the two missile companies
to immediately withdraw into the underground fortifications.
Anti-chemical and engineer units
will be deployed forward.
Enrich the pier position
and connect the beach mines.
Inform the snipers to enter the position.
Yes.
And,
inform all troops.
From now on,
change the title of Red Army
to enemies.
This is not a drill.
It's a war.
Special forces,
we don't have any collaborations now.
We've lost all our neighbors.
Qiaotou Island is an isolated island now.
We are the only people here to defend it.
Brothers,
it's time for you
to become real Special Forces.
How was it?
We didn't get on?
The Blue Army's defense is very tight.
In the direction of the pier and the beachhead,
a large number of mines were placed.
The attacking force is basically exposed to
the coverage of heavy firepower.
We lost more than 50 people,
seven submachine boats and two amphibious tanks.
Report to the director department,
ask them to send us some traffic boats here
and take away all the hostages from the Red side.
Yes.
Instructor.
How many people
were injured?
If it is serious, ask the hygienist to bandage it.
Once the bandages are done,
all the captives must be smeared with flour,
and the wounded must also be smeared, no one can be left out.
And tell them that they are not allowed to wash it off for three days.
This is the order from
Division Commander Song in Division 234.
Yes.
Don't stop.
Immediately launch a second round of attack.
We must open up two beachheads.
Before sunset,
we have to get on the island.
Yes.
Jiang.
We have rearranged the mimes.
Ammo has also been replenished.
Well done.
Gu won't stop.
He will soon start a second attack.
Gao, can we hold on
for 48 hours?
Tell them,
from now on,
if we catch anyone,
don't smear them with flour.
Why?
Stop talking.
I will go check on the observation team.
Gu.
Long time no see.
What?
Want to get information from me?
Six years ago,
I was with Gao Liang
at the Hunter Training School in Venezuela.
Do you know how we two
managed to survive?
It is just two extraordinary people,
in an extraordinary school,
did something extraordinary.
Just like you two
blew up the railway back then.
Really?
The training has more than 30 subjects.
The elimination rate is as high as 80%.
But we graduated
with an overall score
ranking first and third.
Then how about
using some tactics to
let me experience it.
Is there any combo?
Right? What is the Hunter Training School like?
You don't need to be sorry
for missing the course.
As your old comrade,
I'll make it up to you.
Before the drill ends,
you will experience
risky subject training from the Hunter School.
For example,
anti-prisoner training.
Gu, Gu!
Gu Yiye.
Gu, Gu, Gu.
Are you serious? Gu, Gu Yiye.
Gu Yiye, what are you doing?
Commander.
Taking him down from the hang glider
really caused him a lot of trouble.
He is stubborn, he will not tell.
If he really tells,
he is about to transfer to civilian work.
Actual combat drill
needs to look like an actual combat.
Dao Xiaohui,
I am not expecting him to tell,
I just want him to stay in tense.
The tighter, the better.
Yes.
Lightly.
Don't cause any internal injuries.
If his wife wants to divorce him,
I won't spare you.
Gu Yiye.
I am about to have my second child, Gu Yiye.
Tell me, how did I
teach someone like you?
Qin Hanyou.
Will you stop?
If you want to make an conclusion,
[Idea Map of "Operation Azure" Island Capture Drill]
do it
after the drill.
You don't even think about the situation.
Chief is here.
Can not you see how Regiment 700 fights?
They are doing continuous attack.
There's a line waiting for you in the back,
and he won't let you get a good night's sleep.
Can't you do it flexibly?
What are you doing with your weapons?
What is it for to bury them in the soil?
To hatch eggs?
Can't you organize a counter-offensive operation?
Take them out of the reef.
Are you waiting for them to catch your turtle?
Captain.
Who is commanding?
You.
Qin Hanyong.
Are you here to report to the observation team?
Chief.
Now,
this is called...
Yes. Change of words.
Notify the observation team.
Yes.
Tell me.
I would like to give a briefing
to the chiefs of the observation team.
I hope the chiefs of the observation team
can save water and food.
My soldiers are going back and forth.
This is having a bad influence.
♫Unity is strength♫
♫This power is iron♫
♫This force is steel♫
♫Harder than iron, stronger than steel♫
♫Fire upon Fascism♫
♫Let all undemocratic systems die♫
♫To the sun, and to the freedom♫
♫Shine to the new country♫
Gui, don't cry.
I... it's my first time to participate in the drill.
and I got captured.
When I become soldier again in future, what should I tell others?
This is so embarrassing.
No, this is not embarrassing at all.
Firstly, this is just a training subject.
And moreover, we have completed our mission.
We successively brought the eaglet here.
We are the heroes of the Red Army.
A bunch of idiots.
Who is there?
The Red Army is really strange.
They marched forward three times in the morning.
Aren’t they afraid of having their lives shortened?
Have we calculated the life loss?
72 people.
Half of them were left in the tidal flats.
Half were killed by the enemy’s power on the sea.
It really cost them a lot to hit me.
We have searched the whole island
but we did not see anyone.
The captives' confession might be wrong.
Commander.
One fishing boat says that due to mechanical failure,
it asked for docking.
I thought we have agreed to seal the sea and the air.
Where did the fishing boat come from?
Tell them that no docking is allowed.
Already docked.
It is an order issued by the observation team.
These old men.
They have agreed not to interfere in the drill.
Who let the ship dock?
Who?
Who gave the order?
Gao Liang,
the villager’s fishing boat was caught in waves at sea.
The fishing boat lost power
and floated here in the wind.
If you don’t let them get on the island, you want to drive them to the sea?
Moreover, the military-civilian relationship
is a good tradition of our troop.
We can‘t abandon this
just for a drill.
I can not think of traditions now.
I am in a war.
Qin,
did you see?
The soldiers in your Special Operations Battalion,
they forget
whom do they wear this military uniform for.
Anyway, let's put it aside.
Let them get off the ship.
No, I am in a war.
Enough!
Song is right.
Why do you fight in wars?
Isn’t it just for the ordinary people?
Moreover, this is just a drill.
There is no need to destroy the military-civilian relationship.
Alright, get off the ship.
Let’s get off the boat.
Alright, let's get off.
Brothers of the People's Liberation Army, do you have a pit?
I want to take a shit.
We don’t have anything to eat.
Give us some vegetables.
We only have rice and noodles.
Won’t the PLA give us a little?
Don’t try to play with me.
Capture them!
Yes.
Sir.
Chiefs.
[Idea Map of "Operation Azure" Island Capture Drill]
I request the observation team
to get off the island now.
Gao Liang.
Don't act on impulse.
It’s fine if you don’t leave the island.
I will inform the drill director
that the Blue Army admits failure and surrenders.
We can’t fight this war.
Gao Liang,
what do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
What are you doing?
You have agreed to leave the authority to me.
Do you really give me the power?
You give orders and change my plan again and again.
Break the rules of the drill.
How can I fight my war?
Gao Liang.
It is the observation team's fault
to let the fishermen get on the island.
This won’t happen again.
Right.
Chief loves the people,
and follows the principles.
Even if all our soldiers are defeated and killed,
we have to leave
a place for the people.
Right?
This is true.
But are they real fishermen?
Have you seen a boat of fishermen with
all young men in their twenties?
A group of people with flat heads and
speak in
Sichuan dialect and Hunan dialect?
Is there any sea in Sichuan and Hunan provinces?
They were sent by the Red Army
to disrupt the defense system on my island.
They sent me some civilians
to consume food and fresh water on my island.
Fools can see it.
I can deal with all these.
But if the Red Army and the observation team
continue to make trouble,
I can’t fight this battle.
No distinction between authorities.
This is
the mistake of our observation team
and also my mistake.
I promise you
there will be no such problems in the future.
Chief,
can I say something aloud?
Yes.
What can you do to guarantee?
My soldiers are desperately guarding the island here.
You just eat and drink here
and give orders out of your own will.
How will you change? And how can I believe?
Gao Liang.
You don’t know who you are after the drill.
You didn't mean it, right?
He didn't mean it.
Gao Liang,
you know it even if I don't say it.
The significance of the drill is
not only in the grassroots army,
but also,
in the effective operation of the command system.
The observation team cannot go off the island.
You tell me.
How can I make you believe us?
The observation team
should change the identity.
How can we change the identity?
Hostage.
Is there something
wrong with your head?
Sir.
Commander.
Three fishing boats were found five nautical miles away.
They sent a distress signal,
saying that there is something wrong with the boats
and requested to get on the island.
Did you see?
Again.
Tell them
to turn around immediately.
If they dare to continue to drive into Qiaotou Island,
we will send air-explosive bomb,
fifty meters to the ship.
Fishing boats are absolutely not allowed to land on the island.
Yes.
Li Shaobing,
is this really your Regiment 700?
Will this ever end? You play this despicable trick
over and over again.
Why don’t you just change to the reserve force?
How do you know
it is the Regiment 700?
Alright, if it is,
then what?
There can never be too much deception in war.
Is it wrong?
Come on, Chief.
How can it be like this?
Gao Liang really can’t fight in this war.
What’s wrong is not about
the two sides in this battle.
But
about their head office.
Notify drill director department.
Tell them it’s my opinion.
The observation team will change the identity.
We will stay on the island as hostages.
Come on.
Chief.
As hostages,
we have no rights to give orders.
But,
we will keep our rights
to observe the drill.
Sure.
Someone.
Turn right.
From now on,
the identity of the observation team
is changed to hostages.
Take them to the bunker and lock them up.
Yes.
Gao Liang.
This is not necessary.
Chiefs, please.
I said
we only change our identity,
we still have the rights to observe the drill.
You should select a representative.
I will communicate directly with the representative.
Every link and detail of this drill
will be reported.
Take them away.
Chiefs, please.
Let’s go.
I am sorry, Chiefs.
For the drill,
I have to use this tactic.
How's the fishermen team doing?
They were kicked off the island four hours after landing.
The Blue Army filled their water cabinets
and gave them two days' food.
The other three boats failed to get on the island.
In this daylight,
I didn’t expect them to land on the island successfully.
Let’s do this.
At one o'clock in the morning,
send another boat to the island.
Tell everyone on the boat.
If the Blue Army
refuses to let them get on the island,
then they should abandon the boat and swim to the island.
The Red Army has seriously violated the rules of the drill.
Will the director department do something about this?
Put civilians into the battlefield
is against our army’s principle.
But,
the wars in the future
are complex.
The director department believes this tactic works.
Fine.
What will the observation team do?
We do according to the Chief's idea.
The director department agrees
to turn the observation team members into hostages.
The director group will
pass on the information
to the Red Army.
The director department
identifies those who get on the island
as fishermen.
But,
their ships did break down.
It will take some time to repair them.
You should ensure their safety.
Give them necessary supplies.
Shameless.
The integrity in this war
is not that easy to guarantee.
Gu Yiye used civilian-participation in the war.
But Gao Liang
also turned the chiefs to hostages.
According to my understanding of Gao Liang,
I am sure,
he played a bitter trick with the chief.
We can’t blame him.
Regardless of who loses or wins this battle,
the biggest gain is our Troop A.
So the current situation is like
two troubled gallbladders and a pile of experience.
They are enough for us to stay busy in the next half-year.
Sir.
General director,
the Red Army launched the forth attack
onto Qiaotou Island
and retreated again.
They still couldn't land on the island.
Are the residual obstacles at the beach head
cleared?
We opened several roads,
cleared half of the obstacles on the sea.
But this is useless,
as soon as our people retreat
they just made up the gap.
How many beach mines are left for them?
He must have fought a fake war.
But he didn't take much advantage of it either.
He lost quite a lot of people.
It's still dawn.
Shall we organize another charge
before dark?
No need.
We took their whole day up.
The eaglet is ready.
Notify the supporting artillery soldiers.
Ask them to hurry up and replenish the ammunition,
and save the energy until tomorrow.
Notify the troops.
Take some rest.
Get ready to go to the island tomorrow
to catch the turtle.
Yes.
[Information Technology Reconnaissance Bureau]
So there's no winner or loser now.
Sir.
Come in please.
Chief.
Miss Jiang from Mountain Net Number Two arrives.
Come in please.
Chief.
You are finally here.
The superiors notified me to check in before the drill.
But the military command has a temporary duty,
so I came here today.