Aren't you really gonna give in to me?
I can't give in with something like this.
Just give in, already.
If that's how you feel,
try winning against me.
What do we play,
"whoever kisses first loses"?
I've been with you for seven years.
I even let you decorate
the room the way you wanted.
I won't lose to you.
All right, I give in.
I've been with you for seven years.
I'll always lose to you.
I know you wanna lose to me.
Only because I want to drive you
to work tomorrow.
And since I've already lost…
can you…
give in to me, too?
We'll be late again tomorrow.
Please?
Can we do it on the weekend instead?
Okay, darling.
In that case, let's go to sleep.
Shit, I'm late!
Tharn, wake up.
Tharn, we're late.
It's already 7:00.
Tharn, get up.
I'm gonna be late for work.
Tharn, here are your clothes.
Tharn, you ass. You're still not ready?
I'm going to shower now.
If I'm late,
you're dead.
Tharn, you done yet?
Hurry up, Tharn.
-Did you forget something again?
-I did.
I'm late.
I forgot to kiss my wife's cheek.
Tharn.
Come on, I'm late.
Tharn is still the same.
What's changed is,
even though I'm working now,
he's always clinging to me.
If I need a ride, I just tell him.
One call and he's there in a flash.
What am I doing now?
I've been a sports medic for half a year.
I'll give you more details later.
Heard you were almost late this morning.
Yeah, just barely made it.
So, why do you look grumpy?
You got here in time.
Someone gave me hell
about not having an alarm clock at home.
Who?
Dr. Thiti.
Again?
The boss is picking on you again.
Is it…
because you flirted
with that pediatric nurse the other day?
What's that got to do with this?
I didn't flirt with her.
They say the nurse is his mistress.
I never did anything with her.
Besides, I told you I'm taken.
Yeah, but you see,
you've never gone public.
People probably think you're lying.
I've never seen
any of your couple photos either.
Don't trick me into saying it.
I won't do it.
I'll get back to work.
Type, my handsome boy.
Don't get mad at me. I just want to pry.
I just want to know.
We've known each other half a year.
Please, tell me.
Doc?
Type.
I'm spent.
Type
were you late this morning?
Almost.
Then, you weren't late.
You set the alarm wrong.
No, I didn't.
Then, why did it go off at that time?
I accidentally turned it off.
What an ass.
Calm down.
Come here.
What's gotten into you,
giving me a massage?
I guess…
I just want to please my wife.
Are you…
really exhausted?
My boss picked on me again today.
Don't know what I did to deserve it.
Worthwhile job, but a terrible boss.
Come on.
That's how work life is, right?
I'm not like you.
You're lucky your boss is nice.
That's true.
I'm very lucky.
Because I…
have you.
So damn cheesy.
It's been seven years, not seven days.
Enough with the flirting.
I'm…
not only good at flirting.
I can make you feel good, Type.
Go ahead. You've promised now.
What's on your mind?
Work.
When you're with me…
don't think about anything other than me.
Yeah, I know.
You don't know.
I told you, don't think about other stuff
when you're with me.
Tharn…
what do you want
for our seventh anniversary?
Seventh anniversary?
I…
want you and me…
to stay in love for another 70 years.
We'll be really freakin' old.
Then, let's grow old together.
Okay.
Hey.
Why are you happy
this early in the morning?
Last night…
something good happened.
With what? Work? Money?
Or your boyfriend?
-You want to know?
-Yeah.
I'm not telling you.
It's time you introduce him
to your colleagues, Tharn.
I've been working with you for a year.
Introduce me to your boyfriend.
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm possessive.
Man, I'm so jealous of couples.
Here.
Your work.
Why did I have to drag myself over here
to give it to you?
Thanks.
Yeah, I gotta go.
Hello. Thorn.
Hello, Tharn.
Are you free this Sunday?
This Sunday?
I'm not sure.
Free up your schedule and come home.
Why?
Did I forget something?
Just do it. I've got good news.
It's not optional. You must come.
Okay? I'm hanging up.
What's gotten into him?
WHEN ARE YOU COMING HOME?
LATE. I'LL STOP BY AT KHONG'S BAR.
TAKE A CAB IF YOU'RE GONNA GET DRUNK.
OKAY, DARLING.
He said he couldn't be with me.
-He couldn't hurt his partner.
-What's this series?
It's so heartbreaking.
And why is everyone so obsessed
with getting the male lead?
Hey, you're back early today.
Traffic was light.
Today,
Jeed asked about you.
Tell her I'll stop by if I've got time.
I'll tell her.
Tharn, did you drink or bathe in booze?
You smell like
you fell into a barrel of alcohol.
Super stinky.
Aren't you going to ask
about what Jeed said to me?
She probably asked where I was, as usual.
She asked me
why my dear wife didn't come with me.
Quit it. Go get drunk somewhere else.
Can't you see I'm ironing clothes?
If they get wrinkled, I'll kill you.
But this shirt…
is mine, isn't it?
That's right. I'm ironing your clothes.
Why are you ironing them?
I've already ironed them.
Am I not allowed?
Next time, don't do it.
Why are you doing it?
You know I use a laundry service.
It's cheap. Stop ironing. Come on, stop.
You're saying this to me…
after I've been ironing
these damn clothes for an hour?
You wanna do it yourself?
Go on, do it.
And I won't give a shit about you anymore.
Type…
What the hell, Techno?
Some chick's attracted to your man.
What's that got to do with me?
And if he really cheats on you…
you just gotta chop it off
and flush it down the toilet.
I'm hanging up. I'm gonna sleep.
Techno?
Who the hell do you think it was?
Tharn…
I'm warning you.
I'm in a bad mood right now.
If you come close to me again,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Type…
You know…
that I don't want you to get tired, right?
Earlier…
I might have said it the wrong way.
I don't want you to get tired.
You're exhausted enough just from work.
Don't strain yourself at home.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for speaking to you that way.
Are you making me feel guilty
for acting like an idiot?
I'm…
not.
I was mad
because I wanted to do it for you.
We bought this place
with your dad's money.
And you're the one who pays
the electricity and water bills
and the maintenance fee.
So I just wanted to do something for you.
Because I always iron my clothes anyway.
Don't think too much.
I'm happy to do it for you, Type.
You know my money is your money.
Forget it.
I'm going to sleep.
Tharn…
I'm not in the mood.
I'm not going to do that kind of stuff.
Just a hug. Let me hug you.
Tharn…
Please forgive me.
Forgive me, please.
Please.
Please forgive me.
Fine.
You've forgiven me, right?
Yeah.
I forgive you.
And remember this.
If I wanna iron your clothes,
I'm gonna do it.
And if I don't wanna, I won't.
And you.
If you don't wanna get hurt,
don't climb into the bed again.
Thanks for giving me a ride.
Still sulking?
Only 'cause you wouldn't listen
to what I said.
Honestly, you're sulking
like a woman on her period.
I'm gonna do whatever I want, anyway.
And everything I do, I do it for you.
Type.
I'll pick you up this evening.
Just moved in?
I live here too, on the 11th floor.
Which floor are you on?
Since we live in the same building,
it's worth getting to know each other.
That way,
we can help each other in the future.
Do you need my help? That looks heavy.
Cir! Cir, wait for me.
Phugun.
Why are you carrying a heavy box?
Let me do it.
I can carry it just fine.
There's just a bunch of dolls inside.
Pile it on here.
It's okay. I can carry it.
I said pile it on.
-It's okay.
-Pile it on.
Fine.
Well done. Good boy.
Don't flatter me.
You'll call me a naughty boy
if I don't do as you say.
So…
Who's this woman? You know her?
No.
Not a friend?
Not interested.
Cir.
Don't say that.
She'll think you're arrogant.
Let her. Why should I care?
All I care about is you.
You're doing this again, Cir?
I'm not the only person in the world.
In my world, there's only you.
Phu?
Tharn, hello.
You're moving in today?
I'm sorry, I forgot.
It's okay, Tharn. No big deal.
And this guy here is Cir.
-Cir is--
-Phu's boyfriend.
And did you tell him…
who I am?
He did.
And I'm telling you who I am.
Your boyfriend is pretty possessive.
To put your mind at ease,
I already have a boyfriend.
And this, I'll help you carry it.
I'm free today.
Need help with anything else?
No.
-Embarrassed?
-What are you talking about?
Never knew this stoic boy
could feel embarrassed.
Quit it.
Okay, I'll stop teasing.
If my boyfriend comes home early,
I'll introduce him to you.
Okay?
Okay.
Cir. Come on, let's go inside.
Want milk?
No.
I want water.
With lots of ice.
Lots of ice, huh?
Of course, Mr. Type.
I'm going to give you lots of ice.
Your boss didn't ask you to work today?
Don't jinx it,
or he'll call me in.
I rarely get to spend Sundays with you.
I know.
I don't know why he hates me so much.
I don't think he hates you.
He just hates your big mouth.
Don't tease me, Tharn.
I'm way more polite
than I was when I was a freshman.
I bet he'd die of shock
if he met my freshman self.
If he dies of shock,
you're the one who'll get fired.
Type?
If something is bothering you…
you can tell me.
Why should I tell you?
Then, what's your boyfriend for…
if you don't tell him what's on your mind?
Jerk.
Fine.
Remember Champ's roommate
from our freshman year?
No.
The one who studied medicine.
I met him by chance
at the hospital the other day.
His name is Dr. Khunpol, I guess.
Champ used to call him Khun.
And?
I've told you everything.
I'm washing the dishes.
Tharn, you're getting in the way.
Just keep washing.
Tharn.
Let me help.
Stop pretending.
Someone like you
wouldn't think of helping me wash dishes.
But today…
is our day off.
Tharn, stop it.
Please. Please, Type.
Please.
You know that I'm…
a sucker for tank tops.
Yet you still wear it to seduce me.
I'm not seducing you.
You're gonna do it here?
Let's ignore it.
Tharn.
I said ignore it, Type.
I think you should pick up.
This better be important,
or I'll chew you out!
THANYA
Chew her out, then.
Yes, Princess?
What is it?
Why did you call me
so early in the morning?
I thought you were brave.
You forgot that you have to
come home today, right?
Thorn said he'd give you 30 minutes.
You guys have to come as fast as you can.
All right, Princess.
I'll hurry over.
What's wrong?
Let's get changed.
Let's go.
I thought you wanted
to chew your sister out.
All I see is a man who was speeding
to get here in 30 minutes.
You're all talk, Tharn.
She's my sister.
And stop laughing, will you?
Because the handsome Tharn
is afraid of his tiny little sister.
Chopper.
Did you miss me?
Tharn. Type. Hello. You're late.
-Hey.
-We're late because of Tharn.
Who's afraid of her, exactly?
Hi, Princess.
Hurry up, Type. Everyone's waiting.
Okay, Princess.
San…
you really want to get on my nerves?
I said I didn't want this color
for my sofa.
I want a dark color.
Your dad hired me,
so I have to do what he says.
When you hire me, I'll do what you want.
Look who's here.
That should be my line. Why are you here?
This is my house.
Hey, San.
Calm down, this is the house I designed.
I need to inspect it before the handover.
Just admit you're here for free meals.
You've been doing handovers
quite often lately.
I found out my dearest brother
was coming, so I stopped by.
San, don't give me a hard time.
Look at Type's face.
Let me go.
You're an old geezer now,
but you're still
always looking for trouble.
Yeah, the older you get,
the more foulmouthed you are.
I'm your friend.
Have you ever asked
if I really want to be your friend?
Guys, stop fighting.
By the way, why did you call us over?
I was waiting for everyone to be here,
so I could tell you all at the same time.
Here's the thing, everyone.
I'm going to propose to Am.
You call this urgent?
Thorn, you told Thanya to call us over
just because you're getting married?
He's right, honey.
It's not that big a deal.
I even canceled
my appointment with my friends.
I had to cancel my golf game too.
Why is no one excited?
I'm getting married!
Congratulations.
I wish you immense happiness.
So sincere.
My friend's getting married!
Why do you suddenly want to marry Am?
That's my Princess.
The thing is I suddenly woke up
with the feeling that…
I want to wake up beside her every day.
The next thing I knew, I had secretly
measured her ring size and bought a ring.
When are you going to propose?
I'll prepare the dowry.
I can give your inheritance to Am, right?
This Friday, Dad.
As for my inheritance,
you can sign it over to Am.
I'm serious about her.
I hope Am doesn't throw your ring away.
Fork you.
Thorn is getting married.
So when will it be Tharn and Type's turn?
Thanya, let's not focus
on your middle brother now.
Support your big brother first,
or you'll hurt his feelings.
I don't think so.
I couldn't hurt Thorn's feelings, right?
That's right.
I can't wait till Friday.
This is the fourth time you've said that.
That's because I'm happy.
Don't be too happy.
You still don't know if Am will say yes.
Don't be jealous of me, bro.
Since you're getting married,
do something about your sister complex.
Thanya told me you followed her
to movie sets.
And scrutinized all her movie scripts.
I'm a man. I know what men think.
So how can I not worry about her?
Sure, if you say so.
Enough about my relationship.
When are you two getting married?
Did you forget…
that we're a gay couple?
Can't gay people get married?
There are certain limits to it.
What limits?
I'm not worried about my family.
Since there's a white guy who proposed
to my friend in the neighborhood.
But in your family's case, it's different.
Your family has a reputation to uphold.
There are lots of people
at your Dad's company.
And there are your acquaintances,
your friends,
and your bride's family.
Not to mention Thanya's fans.
If they found out that
Tharn was married to a man,
what would they think?
Listen to me, Type.
My family doesn't care what people think.
I'm fine with the way things are.
It's better this way.
If something happens,
we'll just have to break up.
And people wouldn't gossip about us.
You're as stubborn as always.
That's how I am,
and Tharn knows it.
Cheer up.
Guys.
Gather around.
Let's hear your plan, Fiat.
Take the lead.
I'll run down and wait over there.
-Pass the ball to me as fast as you can.
-Okay.
We'd better score fast
before they catch up.
Otherwise,
we're screwed.
Come on, let's crush them.
Let's go!
You're leaving?
-See you later.
See you later.
Fiat, stop practicing.
We won. It's time to celebrate.
Wanna come?
You go ahead.
I'm gonna practice a bit more.
Damn, you've got so much energy.
How long are you gonna practice?
I'm free today,
so I'll just keep practicing.
Don't overdo it.
If Leo finds out you won't take a break,
he'll come after us again.
Are you gonna go celebrate or what?
Because if not, come practice with me.
Dream on. The match was exhausting enough.
We're not hyperactive like you.
Exactly my thoughts.
Then, you'd better leave now.
Or I'll use my position as the captain
to order you, you, and you
to practice with me.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
It's 11:00 already?
We always get home late
when we visit your family.
And we meet your ex there every time.
And my bickering with San will never end.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
Tharn.
I've been with you for seven years.
So how could I not know what
you mean when you say "I'm fine"?
Can we get married, Type?
Not this again.
We've been together
longer than Thorn and Am.
What's that got to do with this?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not being ridiculous, Type.
I just want to move forward with you.
The fact that we live together
is not moving forward enough for you?
-I--
-Tharn.
Enough.
If we keep talking about this,
we'll end up fighting.
We can keep living like this.
Tharn.
Tharn!
What the hell?
FOOTBALL TEAM TACTICS+TYPE'S HUBBY
HELLO.
CROW, CROW, CROW!
HOWL!
THE HELL ARE YOU DOIN', TECHNO?
THIS GROUP CHAT'S BEEN DEAD
SINCE WE GRADUATED.
TYPE. THARN. REPLY AFTER READING.
HELLO, BUDDIES?
OR YOU GUYS…
ARE…
FIGHTING?
GET LOST!