Hello.
This is Thanya, my sister.
You didn't lie to me?
Pops!
Get up, are you okay?
Just admit it, already.
No way.
How can I believe that
this white boy is Thanya's brother?
My old man's so biased.
Uncle, are you okay?
Let me help you.
It's okay, Thanya. Look.
I'm very strong, look.
I'm extremely fit, see?
I heard you were scary,
but I don't think that's true at all.
You look so kind,
so how could you be a bully, right?
You're right, I'm kindhearted
and incredibly generous.
Right, it's not true at all
that you bullied Tharn.
Someone must have lied to me.
It's a lie. Who told you that?
I never bully him.
Right, white boy?
Yes, Dad.
You never bullied me at all.
Who told you to call me…
Dad, it is.
See? I'd never bully him.
Yes, I believe you.
I think the sun's getting hot.
Why don't we get inside?
You're right, Thanya.
Come on, let's get inside.
I'll get you some drinks.
Come on, you must be tired.
Thanya, I'm a big fan of your drama.
Your acting's excellent,
especially that scene…
Thanya.
Your seven-year effort to win him over
can't even compete
with your sister's seven-minute attempt.
I never could've competed, anyway.
My dad is really…
I bet Thanya is gonna be
my dad's new favorite child.
Look how happily they are chatting.
I think so, too.
If I'd known your dad liked Thanya…
I would've took her to see him ages ago.
It's still not too late.
What are you eating?
This.
What the hell?
It's a candy.
Does the sweetness come
from your lips or the candy?
Who're you texting?
Here.
"Strategies for Type's Hubby" group?
How come there's Techno, Champ…
Phugun, Cirrus…
and Thorn's in here too!
And even your sister!
Yeah.
So…
everyone's in the group except you.
You went out of your way
to kick me out of the group?
No.
Come here.
It was Techno's idea.
He said he created this group
to help me propose to you.
So, how'd that work out?
Techno didn't help me at all.
Seriously, I think he…
just wants to hear about our lives.
So, he's nosy?
Here, look.
For me, this group…
is for bragging about my wife.
Which is me.
Do you want me to add you to the group?
It's fine.
We'll let it be your personal space.
In case I'm being a dick and don't want
people to know about us again…
you'll have a place to vent.
If you say so.
In that case,
I'll continue bragging about you.
Suit yourself.
Rick.
Come on.
What the hell?
Shoot, Rick.
A real pro doesn't brag.
Leo?
What are you doing here?
I can't be here?
No, that's not what I meant.
I was going to pick you up at your class.
The professor dismissed the class early.
When are you finished practice?
I'm going to the hospital.
Your knee hurts?
No.
It's just a scheduled checkup.
So, when's practice finish?
-I can go by myself.
-I'm done now.
What?
You said we were gonna
practice till 8:00 today, Leo.
Go sit and wait for a moment.
I'll get changed.
In that case, I'll wait here.
What's on your mind?
Don't you feel that the team
members gave us a weird look?
I don't care.
I can't stop anyone from thinking.
It's enough that you and I
feel the same way.
You could say that.
Leo, what if the doctor says
I can play basketball again?
I won't let you.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
I'll let you play when the doctor says
your knee's completely healed.
But I'm the captain.
So what?
You're just the vice-captain.
You've got no right to boss me around.
You sure…
I've got no right?
Actually…
there's another reason
I don't want you to play…
besides worrying about your knee.
I'm possessive of you.
We look like boyfriends.
That's because we are.
Are you nervous, Type?
Someone like me?
Yeah.
I can't calm my mind at all.
Come here.
Tharn.
I'm glad I've got you here…
with me, right now.
Can you lend me your shoulder?
A month, Tharn.
Even if I can't give my parents grandkids…
I can get ordained for them.
You know, Type…
however long it takes…
I can always wait for you.
Thank you.
I shouldn't, right?
Right now…
this is all I can give you.
this is all I want.
Put it down.
-I'll sprinkle them.
-Add more.
-In every tray?
-Yes.
Add more flowers.
What's up?
Do you need my help?
It's okay, we're almost done.
Are you his friend?
Arrange the lotus carefully.
Why are they wilted?
Don't you have fresh ones?
I told you to cut them in the morning.
You cut them last night, right?
Where is everyone?
Why aren't they helping?
Here he comes.
Honey, do it.
I rejoice in your merit.
Tharn, come here.
-Hello.
Let's go.
But I don't know what to do.
It's not hard.
I think this is what Type wants.
Go ahead.
Honestly, you always turn into a child
whenever you lose confidence.
Go ahead.
Come on, hurry up! Follow me.
Clip his hair.
Honey, the scissors.
Go ahead, clip it and put it in there.
Go ahead, clip it.
Pray and clip.
Put it in there.
Come on, everyone! Get in formation.
Get in formation.
Hurry up.
You stand here, and you here.
Where are the trays? Coming? Okay.
-Come on, Honey! Hurry up!
-Slow down!
-Look, everyone's here.
-It's my first time wearing high heels!
-Let's go greet them.
-Where are you taking me!
Hello!
-Jerk.
-That's it.
-Hurry up!
-Oh, my!
Hello!
Hello, everyone!
-Let's go.
-Why did you make me run?
Really!
-You okay?
-What do I carry?
-You carry this.
-Thank you, darling.
-I carry this.
-I'm going to be a monk's mom!
-Are you ready!
-Don't run, okay?
-Don't run.
-I won't, I'll dance.
Honey, ready?
Very much!
-You sound so confident.
-So, let's do a sound check.
No, it's you who need a check-up.
By the way, why are you so greedy?
You're carrying everything.
The pillow, the talipot fan,
the alms bowl.
Are you crazy?
Greedy.
Tharn, come here.
Come on, come closer.
Speak.
Here, the pillow.
Take it.
So…
Don't say a word.
He hasn't said anything.
-It's a warning.
-Is that so?
So, what should I do with the pillow?
You probably don't know the meaning
behind carrying the pillow.
Listen, in the procession,
they say the person carrying the pillow
can be a sibling or anyone.
But most people think the one carrying
the pillow has to be the lover.
And Type has requested
that you be the one to carry it.
Do you understand why
his dad let you carry it?
He's given in. That's a harsh nudge.
He's finally given in. Understand now?
-Thank you, Mom.
-Sure.
Thank you, Dad.
Like she said.
Honey!
The diamond chipped.
-Serves you right.
-Come here!
When do we start?
Over here!
Over here too!
I haven't gotten any!
-After seeing that bastard Type--
-Techno!
You can't say that, he's a monk now.
Speak politely.
He's a monk? Oh, man, I forgot!
No one heard me. I'll say it again.
After seeing venerable Type,
my eyes still can't get used to the sight.
Usually when he sees us,
he'll run straight at us
and slap my head. Slap! Slap! Slap!
-Yeah, you're right.
-Yeah.
But, Techno, stop badmouthing the monk.
You'll go to hell.
Dude, at least
I'll see a familiar face in hell.
-Who?
-You, of course!
-I won't go there with you.
-Oh, why? Come see me there?
Doc, you done packing up?
Doc, you okay? Are you tired?
Do you feel hot?
I'm fine, it's not that hot.
Doc, excuse me. It is that hot.
Check the weather app on your phone.
Man, it's so hot that if you put
a frying pan on the ground,
and some stir-fry rice in it,
the rice would get cooked.
Ready to eat, tasty, fill you right up.
-You're exaggerating.
-Really?
It's so hot, I can't take it.
Look at my sweat.
Eat this. You'll feel refreshed.
Okay.
What now?
Wear this,
it'll protect you from the heat.
Thank you.
Excuse me, my friends.
This is a temple, not your home.
Be mindful of where you are.
You're at a temple. Take it easy, will ya?
Damn, putting on hats for each other.
Oh, my God, what a sinner.
-So disrespectful--
-Techno.
What are you talking about?
Just wear it, Doc. Don't listen to him.
You usually work indoors.
You might faint from weather like this.
So caring. So lovey-dovey.
I wish you a long-lasting love.
Doc…
we're at an ordination ceremony, right?
Have you ever heard the saying,
"Get ordained before you get laid"?
Even if you're lovers, you've got to wait.
You know that, right?
However…
if you become my friend's boyfriend now…
he's more than ready.
You don't have to wait at all.
Why is that?
-Say it.
-Because I've been ordained.
Now I'm ready to get laid.
I mean, ready to marry.
If you date me now…
I'm ready to marry you.
My heart's all stirred up.
You even made me blush.
So romantic.
Champ, I'm so proud of you.
You've finally made progress with this.
Good job!
What? It's just a joke among friends.
Right?
-Friends?
-Yeah.
Don't say such hurtful words out loud.
Friends? Unbelievable.
Cheer up, Doc.
It's not easy to be you.
Hang in there.
It's not that hard, Techno.
You're smiling.
Seems like you enjoy it.
You're really something, Doc.
STRATEGIES FOR TYPE'S HUBBY
HEY. ANYONE KNOW HOW THE MONK'S DOING?
IN WHAT WAY?
HIS MONASTIC LIFE.
HE'S BEEN ORDAINED ALMOST A WEEK NOW.
THEN, YOU SHOULD ASK THARN.
HE'S PROBABLY TOO BUSY TO READ.
REALLY, WHY?
I THINK HE'S PREPARING.
PREPARING WHAT?
Tharn, you just got back?
Yeah.
Came to get some stuff.
I'll be staying with my parents.
Why?
It's closer to the airport.
Are you flying to see Type?
Yeah.
I said I'd wait,
but that doesn't mean…
I can't go see him.
While I'm gone, watch the room for me.
Roger, I promise I will do my best.
Very good.
-Tharn's really amazing, isn't he?
-Yeah.
If it were me,
I wouldn't be able to stand it either…
if I had to be apart from you
for this long.
Nonsense.
Wait for me.
-Don't be impatient, he'll come.
-We'll be late.
-Hello, Dad. Hello, Mom.
-Hello.
Why do you keep coming here?
I'm so sick of you.
It's normal for old men to act tough.
In fact, he's been waiting for you
since before the rooster even crowed.
Honey, don't tell him.
You're making me look bad.
What are you smiling for?
How long are you going to stand there?
We'll be late for the monk's meal time.
Thank you, Dad.
Hurry up!
-Go, take this with you too.
-Okay.
This one too.
Move on your knees.
Like this, look. Follow my lead.
Put it down.
And mind your manners.
Pay respect to the monk.
Come on, move back.
Put your palms in front of your chest
and do the Benjangkapradit prostration.
-Do you know how?
-Yes.
You spread out your fingers like a map.
Okay, first prostration.
Bend down.
Keep your elbows and knees aligned.
Rise.
Second prostration.
Third prostration.
Go on, make an offering.
Hand it to the monk.
Hand it to the monk,
don't just put it down.
Sit with your legs to the side.
Receive the blessing.
May you receive longevity, beauty,
happiness, and strength.
Sadhu.
All done.
Thank you, Dad.
No problem.
-Just remember the steps.
-Yes.
Let's take our leave.
You don't have to come every week.
Please don't say that.
I wanted to come.
Therefore…
please don't stop me.
You're really stubborn.
Doc, have you been waiting long?
We had so many customers at lunchtime.
It's okay.
Actually,
you didn't have to come yourself.
-Just let your employee make the delivery.
-I can't, you're my important customer.
Tharn, Type, Techno, and you
are all my important customers.
Tharn ordered food from my restaurant too.
But he told me to deliver it
at 5:00 in the morning.
But I know he was gonna
give it to the monk.
If he wasn't my friend, I wouldn't do it.
By the way, I kinda respect him.
He goes there on Saturday.
Returns on Sunday.
He even told me he'd go every week.
Love clearly makes people blind.
Being single is so much better.
Don't you think?
Doc?
Sometimes…
I hate you.
Doc!
Doc, why did you say that?
What did I do to upset you?
No.
You've done nothing wrong.
-Then, why'd you--
-Because you've never done anything.
You don't know.
You don't get it.
Even when I clearly express myself.
What are you talking about?
I like you.
What did you say?
I've liked you since freshman year.
I've liked you all these seven years.
I--
I never knew.
You didn't know.
Because you've never
been interested in me.
I know…
that it's hopeless.
All I can do is dream.
It's a pipe dream.
I want nothing from you.
You don't have to give me an answer.
But from now on…
we have no reason
to see each other anymore.
Doc!
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
It's good enough…
that I got to confess.
Thank you…
for making this heart…
happy for many years.
Goodbye.
What are you doing?
I don't know what love is.
I don't even understand it.
But when you said goodbye to me…
I felt so terrible.
Don't say goodbye to me again.
But you don't like me.
I don't know.
But I won't let things between you and me…
end like this.
Just a little longer, Tharn.
You're going this week too?
Yeah.
Don't stop me, Thorn.
When you're completely exhausted?
It's my happiness.
Besides, the venerable Type
will leave the monkhood next week.
Have you prepared
the offerings for this week?
Mom prepared them for me.
I clocked out early,
so I came to get them myself.
You may not need them anymore.
Good luck, bro.
Type?
You're back?
What's the matter?
You're back!
You're really back, right?
Yeah.
I'm back.
Who did you mistake me for?
You came back to me, Type.
You came back to me.
Thank you…
for waiting for me.
Yeah.
Type, you're going to sleep like this?
Come here.
Tharn.
You bought a new TV?
Thanya bought it the other day.
And the lamp…
you moved it?
I didn't. It's in the same place.
And…
have you seen my black watch?
I couldn't find it.
Type,
if you're embarrassed, I'll talk to you
until you get over it, okay?
I--
To be honest…
I feel awkward.
I'm still not used to it.
I don't know how I should act.
Then…
do you want me to stop?
No.
Don't stop.
Type…
you want a drink?
I'll get it for you.
Tharn…
Shall we make a vow?
I told my parents…
that I might live in Bangkok for good…
because…
you live here.
They understood.
And told me…
to follow my heart.
That's why I've chosen to do this.
Because my heart…
is here…
with you.
Are you…
telling me…
Yeah.
Let's get married.
Are you serious?
I--
Thiwat Phawattakul…
hereby swear…
to have and to hold…
Thara Khirikun…
for better…
or for worse…
for richer…
or for poorer.
I will be by your side forever.
I--
Thara Khirikun…
hereby swear…
to have and to hold…
Thiwat Phawattakul…
for better…
or for worse…
for richer…
or for poorer.
You will have me by your side forever.
You and I…
let's be together.
Okay.
Forever?
Forever.
Doc!
Thorn.
You're about to have your own family now.
From now on, you must be her pillar.
Yes.
You look handsome.
Remember the first day
you wanted her to be your bride.
Whatever happens,
I want you to think back to that day.
Got it, son?
I'll try to have a family
like the one you guys have.
Can you really compete with me?
Of course, he can.
-We should let him get ready.
-Okay.
Thank you, see you out there.
How do I look? Good?
Let me see, turn around.
The suit's pretty neat.
So is the bow tie.
But your face--
Don't worry, you look great.
I'm not confident at all.
Thorn…
you've been saying that for days.
Believe in yourself.
When it's your turn, you'll feel the same.
Seriously, if you weren't my big brother…
I would've gotten married before you.
Good luck, Thorn.
You too, bro.
You still nervous?
Relax.
I'll stay by your side.
Thanks so much.
What's wrong?
I feel sad.
My brother's getting married before me.
But Thorn proposed before you did.
But you and I…
loved each other long before them.
I miss your beanie.
Don't tease me.
Because you wore it for months back then.
Don't know why you were so embarrassed.
You looked adorable.
Then, who was the crybaby…
who got surprised by me
and yelped like a dog?
But, who said that Gil had a crush on me?
Who would've believed
he was using your face to attract women?
Our wedding…
Don't make it this grand, okay?
I don't know about that.
Tharn.
Fine…
do whatever you want.
What can I do about it?
I already said yes.
And you already promised…
to be with me for the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
Toss the bouquet!
I love you.
I love you too.
And this is the love story
of me and Tharn.
From the man I couldn't stand…
to the one…
I love with all my heart.
STRATEGIES FOR TYPE'S HUBBY
THARN, HOW ARE
YOUR WEDDING PREPARATIONS GOING?
STILL STICKING YOUR NOSE
INTO THEIR BUSINESS, HUH?
I'M NOT LIKE YOU, ALWAYS WITH KHUNPOL.
THEN SPEND YOUR TIME
DOING SOMETHING ELSE, TECHNO.
CALLING ME NOSY IS LESS HURTFUL THAN THIS.
I REALLY WANNA KNOW, THARN.
SHIT!
TECHNO, ARE YOU READY TO DIE?
YOU DARED KICK ME OUT OF THE GROUP!
SEEMS LIKE…
I GOTTA RUN.