Tharn…
you're sleeping?
Didn't you tell me
that we should talk things out?
I don't know
what the hell you're thinking.
But if you don't talk to me…
I'll never know.
Tharn…
turn around and talk to me.
Your wife's clever,
but he's not a magical being
who can read your mind.
Turn around and talk to your wife.
Your wife is trying to make up with you.
You should sleep, Type.
It's late.
Will you just get up and talk to me?
It's very late, Type.
We both have to work tomorrow.
And I have nothing to say to you.
Nothing, my ass!
You think I'm that stupid?
You think I don't know what's up with you?
You've been acting like this
since we left your family's house.
Just tell me what you want.
Can you really give me what I want
if I do?
You know what I want, Type.
But you can't give it to me.
You asshole!
This is why I don't want to talk to you.
We'll only end up fighting.
In case you forgot,
you and I are both men.
Or maybe…
you don't want to tell anyone
about our relationship.
You've crossed the line, Tharn.
Why would I introduce you to my parents
if I didn't wanna tell anyone?
Why would I introduce you
to all my friends?
That's why I told you to sleep.
It's late, Type.
Just think I'm an unreasonable idiot.
Then, tell me why
you wanna get married so much.
Because I love you!
Don't you get it?
But there's no need to declare our love
to the whole world.
I know, Type.
Besides close friends,
you don't want other people to know.
Whether it's on Twitter,
Instagram, or Facebook…
you never tell anyone
about our relationship.
I know we don't see eye to eye
on this issue.
That's why I told you to forget it.
As for what happened today,
I'm sorry I was being unreasonable.
Give me a little time.
Just a few days.
I'll try to understand you.
I'll forget about this…
and act as if nothing's happened.
Is that okay with you?
Fine.
You can take as much time as you want!
I just want…
people to know about our relationship.
That's all.
You want time?
Fine, you've got it!
Asshole.
What's with all the racket!
What are you doing?
Making you breakfast.
How many eggs do you want?
You think you can make it up to me
like this?
Put it down.
Come here.
You're a grown ass man,
but you can't even fry an egg.
Any middle schooler could do it.
Does it hurt a lot?
The skin's red.
Why are you smiling?
It was worth getting hurt.
So, do you forgive me?
You think I'd forgive you
just because you got hurt?
Even if you dipped your hand
in the hot oil,
I'd still be mad at you.
What are you doing?
You think I wouldn't do it?
I'm sorry, Type.
Happy now?
Sit down.
I'll do it.
Need my help?
Just don't touch anything. Go.
So annoying.
It's burnt.
Wanna eat it?
-I made it for you.
-Seriously, who would eat this?
Phugun, time to wake up.
Five more minutes.
You've asked for five more minutes twice.
Let me ask a third time.
Okay…
but don't say I didn't warn you.
I dare you.
But give me five more minutes.
Why are you so cute?
Get up.
Will you get up?
Fine.
Not gonna get up, huh?
Come here.
Cir.
Spend your five minutes in the bathroom.
Okay.
What are you doing, Cir?
Making toast.
I'll put jam on yours.
It's dangerous, Phugun.
Okay.
How will I spread the jam for you
if you keep bugging me?
Then, don't do it.
I love plain toast.
You sure?
I just want to hold your hand.
Then, today…
just eat plain toast.
I should stop bugging you
now that I've caught your attention.
I wonder where I put my phone.
You put it on the coffee table
in front of the TV.
There's something on your lips.
Here too.
All gone.
Cir. I'd better find my phone.
What was on my lips?
I haven't eaten anything.
Cir's been sly lately.
Anyway…
I'm about to leave.
Be there in 30 minutes.
See you.
Hello, Tharn.
Hey, you two.
Where are you off to?
University. Phugun has classes.
I have classes. Cir is driving me there.
I said I could go by myself,
but he wouldn't let me.
You graduated, but you go there
more often than some of my friends.
What are you doing? Show some respect.
His older cousin's right here.
Let go, what are you doing?
Tharn, it's too late
to be possessive of me now.
Right, Cir?
Phu, your older cousin's right here.
Show some consideration.
I'm telling you, if I'd been there
when you hit on each other…
You wouldn't have ended up
dating each other so easily.
Got it?
Excuse me, Tharn.
It's too late to say that now.
Where's Type?
Type?
He went to work early this morning.
-So, Tharn--
-Hello!
This is Khlui, your usual host.
What's new is I've moved in
to a new condo.
Today I'll give you a tour
of my new condo.
Stepping out of the elevator,
you'll see the spacious hallway.
How is it? Worth the price, right?
I promise if this live stream
reaches 1,000 viewers today,
I'll show everyone my bedroom.
Gather round, gather round.
How is it? Isn't this beautiful?
Tharn!
Hello, Khlui.
How did you end up living here?
What a coincidence.
I should ask you that question.
Type and I have been living here
for a long time.
So, that means my wish actually came true.
What wish?
You've forgotten.
I made a wish
that you'd grow old together.
And have everlasting love.
What are you talking about?
What were you doing speaking so loudly?
What's this?
-What's this?
-I was being loud?
I didn't realize.
Sorry, next time I'll keep my voice down
a little bit.
There'll be a next time?
Of course!
That live stream should get me more likes.
Actually, your bro here
is the most popular
online merchant right now.
I sell everything.
With my oral skills,
I can even sell old exhaust pipes.
Khlui, you're awesome.
I haven't seen you for a while.
Now you're sucking exhaust pipes?
They do fit in my mouth. What the hell?
What about you? How's couple life?
You've been together for so long.
How many years is it?
-Seven years.
-Seven years!
So romantic.
Romantic?
We're still the same. Fighting every day.
Really, why?
Excuse me.
Khlui, I have a meeting.
Talk to you later.
Wait!
-Hello.
-Tharn, wait!
What?
I haven't gotten an answer.
He's gone.
What the hell?
Since you left me hanging…
I've got to pry
into your love life again, right?
I wanna pry, but I've got to work too.
More hard work.
When will you come home, Squirt?
I just went home not too long ago.
Don't give me that crap, Type.
Look, it's been four months
since your last visit.
Aren't you gonna show your face
to your parents at all?
Or did that white boy
say something to you?
Just you wait. Next time I see him,
I'll chop his head off with a machete.
And your son will be a widower.
What, a widower? Don't talk nonsense.
My son doesn't have a wife yet.
How could he be a widower?
Just accept it, Pops.
How many years has it been, already?
I'm standing my ground. No means no.
Then, keep standing your ground.
I'm going back to work. Bye.
Good, a man must be responsible
with his work.
But remember to come home too.
Okay, Pops.
Damn it!
What's wrong with him?
What's wrong with Fiat?
All he does is practice, right?
I know,
and Leo's only been away for a week.
Yeah, should we ask Leo to come back
from Italy tomorrow?
I've been practicing so much
I don't have time to find a girlfriend.
How long are you gonna slack off?
Go get help.
Hurry up!
Fiat, are you okay?
Damn.
Leo's gonna kill me.
Nurse, go get the doctor!
The doctor's coming. Please calm down.
The doctor's here.
Doctor, I can't give up basketball!
Okay, you must calm down first.
Calm down, you're in good hands now.
Don't worry.
Breathe slowly. Let me examine the injury.
You need to slow your breathing
and calm down.
Lie down, okay?
Doctor, this patient
is pretty difficult to handle.
Looks like he won't cooperate.
Don't worry,
let's wait for the MRI results first.
What if the MRI shows a tear
in the ligament?
Let's not worry about that now.
-Hey, Type! Come here.
-Hello, Khong.
Man, it's been a while. How are you?
I missed you.
Waiting for Tharn's gig?
Yeah. So how have you been?
I'm fine.
But my wife's been ferocious
since she got pregnant.
Congratulations on your baby
and your new bar.
Thanks a lot.
So, what do you think?
Grander than the old one?
Much grander.
It should be, I spent a lot on it.
I'm practically broke now.
-Because of the decorations?
-No.
Because my pregnant wife
has a craving for online shopping.
What's with her cravings
and online shopping?
If she were pregnant for 18 months,
I'd go bankrupt.
-So frustrated.
-Calm down, bro.
Speaking of which, Jeed's waiting for you.
You should go see her.
She's been missing you for days.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
But, I'll go find my friends first.
-Okay.
-Talk to you later. Bye.
-Don't forget to meet Jeed.
-Sure.
-You want another glass?
-Not yet.
Type, there you are. Sit here.
Hurry up. We got a table up front.
What are you having today?
I'll drink whatever you give me.
Look at him. That's my cute boy.
I'll mix a strong drink
especially for my bro here.
-Okay.
-Fake.
Ain't I her bro too?
-Used to be.
-Okay.
Let's add more.
-Take it easy.
-This shot is free of charge.
Heavy and strong.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Does your hospital have
kidney dialysis services?
Just kidding. I meant, liver dialysis.
My mistake.
-You're talking rubbish again.
-Yeah.
Why did you just arrive now?
Sorry, I was busy with work.
Speaking of which,
can I hang my flyers in your department?
Business talk again.
It's not like I'm hanging them everywhere.
Is that so?
Sure, you're definitely
not hanging them everywhere.
You just hung them up all over my place.
It's just a few flyers, Jeed.
Bear with it for my sake.
By the way, what's on the menu today?
Now you're talking about food?
-I'm hungry. Aren't you?
-I'll ask my staff.
Don't go just yet. Let's chat first.
You haven't seen us
for a long time, right?
Yeah, I missed you guys.
Look at us, time sure goes by so fast.
Look at us. Our freshman year passed by
in the blink of an eye.
Next thing we knew, we'd graduated.
-You went to the graduation ceremony.
-Yes.
And then, Type got his master's degree.
Holy shit.
Time flies and all of us
are freaking old now.
Old, my ass!
You looked right at me when you said that.
I meant, me and my friends.
You're still beautiful.
Don't touch me. I'm gonna go check
on my other customers. You piss me off.
-Okay.
-I'm leaving.
Techno, why did you piss her off?
I was just kidding.
Can't I even talk about age?
I mean, look at us.
We're all grown-ups now.
Take me, for example.
Who would've thought
I'd be a civil servant?
And you, Champ, what a total idiot.
Always was and will be.
You forgot to enroll in a class
and ended up graduating after five years.
You would've graduated
with med students at the eighth year.
Shit!
It only takes six years to be a doctor.
-Really?
-Think before you mock me.
-Really? Six years?
-Yeah.
I'm so stupid.
But…
Our friend here is a restaurant owner.
He runs his own restaurant.
You're really passionate about food.
And you'd better stop eating for free.
I'm about to go bankrupt.
What the hell? And you, Type, you bastard.
What?
You always hit my head and kicked my ass
when you were pissed off.
-Want a piece of me?
-Relax, it's not the time yet.
-Bummer.
-Teach him a lesson.
You already did.
You ended up working in a hospital,
taking care of patients.
Seriously, how did you--
Should I kick your ass
and have you treated at my hospital?
Save your energy, man.
Calm down, I'm just kidding.
Wait a sec. There's another.
We have to talk about him.
Who?
Tharn, of course!
Tharn, Type's sweetheart.
He's the best of the best.
Apart from being a music producer,
he helps out at his daddy's company.
Your father-in-law.
He runs an online
musical instrument store.
And he has a part-time job,
playing music at this place.
How many roles does he have? So perfect.
Wait, wait, wait. He's got another role.
What role?
The role you're familiar with.
What?
The role he plays
when he bangs you every night.
Shit!
You do a great job
poking your nose into my affairs.
Good evening, everyone.
This song…
is one I want to dedicate
to everyone who's in love.
Waking up this morning
To a world that seems different
The alarm clock wakes me up
Like it usually does
You are peacefully sleeping
Not knowing what is on my mind
I'm letting you dwell on your sweet dreams
Thinking of the time
We stared into each other's eyes
Without uttering a word
The way you looked at me
Was the proof of our love
With all the good times we've shared
Do you feel the same way I do?
Should I keep it to myself?
Or should I tell you?
I want you to be my last
To be the one
Who shares every breath with me
I will never ever hurt you
Do you hear me, my love?
Please don't let go of my hand
Jeed, here's the thing.
Everyone in our gang is taken,
except for Champ who's still single.
-Find him someone.
-Really?
He's pretty clueless about love.
Champ.
What's up?
Look at his eyes.
What about them?
What the hell?
Look at him. Look!
Look. This is a man in love
who's looking at the one he loves.
Yeah, his world is a rosy paradise.
Do you get it? It's so great.
So what?
Love doesn't make you full.
Having a food buddy
is better than being in love.
Do you agree, Jeed?
-No, I have a husband.
-I am in a relationship.
And you? What are you staring at so much?
My boyfriend.
Yeah, his boyfriend.
-It's his happiness.
-Yeah.
You can rest assured
The two of us will walk side by side
As long as you love me
As long as you don't let go of my hand
Please don't let go of my hand
Have you forgiven me?
You're cunning.
I know that you…
like it when I play music.
If I'd had time for drum practice,
I would've played those instead.
Because I like when you play drums?
You don't just like it.
You…
love it.
Do you know why I agree
to let you work so hard?
Because I know you love to do it.
And?
And I love you when you do what you love.
And do you know…
what I love the most?
Me.
-Holy shit.
-You okay?
Hold on.
There's only soda left.
Damn, I'm totally wasted today.
Champ?
Where the hell are Tharn and Type?
I bet it's happening again.
Only you and me left.
You still haven't gotten used to it?
Those two disappear together every time,
leaving you and me behind.
Let them be.
They're probably "eating"
somewhere around here.
You want it?
No.
What about you?
Sure.
WHERE ARE YOU? I'M ALREADY LATE.
JUST A SEC. MY BOSS CALLED ME IN TO WORK.
OKAY. I'LL WAIT AT THE USUAL SPOT.
Doc, how are you?
It's been a while. Remember me?
Champ!
Why are you so surprised?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
You're still as silly as before.
So, how are you? Been doing well?
Yeah.
What were you thinking,
meddling with the children's OPD?
Meddling?
What do you mean?
Someone told me
you harassed a nurse there.
That depends on
what you mean by "harassed."
I believe talking to a patient
about fitness test results…
means I went there to work.
You're still arguing with me?
Someone confirmed it was you.
If you mean the latest patient,
I went to meet them with Ms. Teng.
She can confirm that I went there to work.
I called you here simply to give you
a warning, but you argue so much.
I guess you have too much free time
if you could do something like that.
They asked for my help
because I'm your superior.
Think about it.
If the nurse informs the board,
our department's reputation
will be damaged.
If you have common sense…
think about that.
Okay?
Consider it a warning.
Don't let it happen again.
Yes, I'll be careful in the future.
If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
So, you run a health food restaurant?
Yeah, that's right.
You didn't believe I could do it, right?
I'm used to Techno teasing me about it.
Says who? I think it suits you
since you always brought me tasty food.
Thanks. I don't often get to hear
someone say something like that.
Sorry, it's a habit.
You always do it to your girlfriend?
You think someone like me
has a girlfriend? I don't.
Even Techno said that with my personality,
I could never find one.
When I said it's a habit,
I meant with you, Doc.
I often rubbed your head
in freshman year, remember?
Not that you were a small guy.
But whenever I was with you,
you looked so tiny in my eyes.
Hey, Type, over here.
Damn it, that asshole boss…
Calm down. What happened?
It's that…
Nothing.
I just haven't had any lunch yet.
Good afternoon, Doctor.
I was planning to tell Champ that
we happen to work in the same place.
Type, you can speak casually. It's fine.
I can't, Doctor. This is our workplace.
Someone might report me
if I use vulgar language.
Let's wait till we're outside.
Type, you should've told me earlier
that you and Doc work in the same place.
I haven't seen him since freshman year.
Yeah. So, what did you call me here for?
Right, it's about this,
the food from my restaurant.
Give them to people in your department
and help me hand out the flyers.
I guarantee
people will like how it tastes.
Even you could easily run a lap
after eating it.
It can't be ordinary food
if it can make me run a lap.
Come on, trust me.
I'm a real expert at eating.
I won't mess up
like when I enrolled in electives.
Come to think of it…
Here, Doc.
Remember to eat. Don't only focus on work.
Thank you.
So…
do you guys still play football?
Not much. I just do the boxing now.
Yeah, we can't run
like we used to anymore.
Speaking of which, that reminds me.
Last week, a college basketball player
was admitted here for an ACL tear.
An ACL tear? Will he be referred for PT?
He'll be sent for rehab first.
What are you talking about?
Techno, start the game.
Easy, man. Don't rush me.
I need to find the right angle.
Hurry up.
No. Just a sec.
Check out my stance. So freaking cool.
Shit!
-Will you just play?
-Okay!
Move if you're not gonna play.
You're wasting time.
Damn it.
Damn, you potted one.
Damn, so cool.
Here, you've got my respect.
Take it easy, will you? Wait.
You've got work tomorrow.
Take it easy. Put it down.
You drank it all.
What's the matter with him?
Did he fight with Tharn?
-No!
-You've got sharp ears.
-It's about his work.
-Really?
When Doc was around,
he hid his feelings so well.
But when we were alone,
he couldn't stop going on about it.
How could I not?
The whole hospital knows
that the bastard is a cradle robber.
And I've got nothing to do
with that nurse.
She's the one who made a move on me.
I already rejected her.
But that shit face keeps picking on me.
I didn't do anything.
He couldn't control his woman,
and he took it out on me.
-Son of a bitch!
-Your boss?
-You!
-Okay!
-Shit!
-It's not time to joke around.
I just wanted to cheer you up.
-Give me that.
-That's mine!
What am I gonna drink now?
-What a jerk.
-Will you play now?
THIS IS KHUNPOL.
-What are you bitching about?
-Nothing.
I'm finding an angle.
You know, a potting angle.
DOC, SORRY.
I FORGOT TO TEXT YOU AFTER ADDING YOU.
IT'S OKAY. YOU'RE PROBABLY BUSY.
JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
THIS IS MY LINE ID.
SEE YOU LATER.
GOOD NIGHT.
Hurry up.
Still as cute as ever.
He hasn't changed at all.
Is he really a doctor?
So curious.
Who are you texting?
Doc.
The one I told you about. He texted me.
What doc?
Khunpol.
Remember? From freshman year.
-Dr. Khunpol, your roommate.
-That's right.
-The one we wanted to switch rooms with.
-Correct.
And he's cute too.
He likes you?
You're crazy.
-Take it and drink.
-Okay.
Type, take it easy.
Yeah, I'm not gonna carry you home
if you're drunk.
You're as heavy as lead.
Go order more. You talk too much.
I've got no more money to split the bill.
-It's my treat.
-Just a sec. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Champ, your turn.
Tharn!
-Type!
-Take him. He's heavy.
Holy shit.
Your wife's acting like he's so small.
Damn, he's heavy as hell!
My shoulder almost dislocated.
Here, your darling's bag.
What did you guys do? Why is he so drunk?
You're asking me?
Like I could give you the answer. Shit!
Tharn, that should be my question.
Did you guys fight or something?
Nothing comes to mind?
When we went out drinking,
we only talked about what happened
with his work and his asshole boss.
Then what?
Tharn, how many years
have we been friends?
You know that every time he gets drunk,
you're the cause.
Am I right?
-Yeah.
-He finally admits it.
So, what's the problem this time?
-It's nothing, really.
-It's just…
-You couldn't get it up!
-Keep your voice down!
Thorn is getting married.
Really? Congratulations!
I'm so ready.
But Thorn didn't invite me.
I guess he hates you.
Really?
Can I come to eat free food, then, please?
Fine, I'll tell him.
Wait, I think that's off-topic.
What's it got to do with Thorn's wedding?
I want to marry him.
What? You knocked him up,
and now you want a shotgun wedding?
You knocked him up or what?
Am I right? Am I wrong?
No!
Right, I forgot.
I'm relieved he's not pregnant.
Anyway, thanks.
I'm gonna bring him inside.
Hold on a sec.
What is it?
I think you need help this time.
Help with what?
Just a sec.
Let me find the Line group.
-What are you doing?
-Be patient, you'll find out soon.
I'm going to kick him out.
-What are you doing, Techno?
-Just a sec.
You always carry him to bed just fine,
and now you're complaining he's heavy?
I haven't complained yet.
What?
Isn't this a cool group?
Strategies For Type's Hubby.
Your wish to get married
will definitely come true.
-Thanks, I guess.
-Yeah.
Thanks for bringing him home too.
Have a safe trip home. Let's go, Type.
Type.
If something was bothering you…
why didn't you tell me?
Even though those guys are your friends…
I still feel jealous.
Hold me.
It's because you're like this…
that I want you…
all to myself.
Why can't I hear anything?
Are they fighting?
What the hell?
This good stuff almost slipped off.
I'll never agree to surgery
even if you doctors say I should.
I won't take any risks.
I'll do the physical therapy
and take medication, but no surgery.
I have to be able
to play basketball again.
Here's the thing, sir.
Surgery is not scary at all.
In your case,
it will be arthroscopic surgery.
Small wounds and fast recovery.
It'll be even more effective
if you do physical therapy afterwards.
Can you guarantee…
my knee will be the same after
if I have the surgery.
Sir, getting the surgery
is better than not getting it.
Because if you decide against it,
your torn ligament might not heal.
Most importantly,
you might not be able to jump again.
Don't try to persuade me.
Those doctors couldn't even convince me.
So why would I give in now?
I'm here to heal my knee
with physical therapy.
And you just need to do your job!
Okay, if that's your decision.
You called me, Teng?
HEY.
YOU KICKED TYPE OUT OF THE GROUP?
LOL
JUST WAIT AND SEE.
TECHNO CHANGED THE GROUP'S NAME TO
"STRATEGIES FOR TYPE'S HUBBY".
IF TYPE FINDS OUT, HE'LL KILL YA.
IF YOU DON'T SAY ANYTHING, I WON'T,
SO HOW WILL HE KNOW?
COME ON, TO HELP THARN PROPOSE TO TYPE,
WE NEED A PLAN.
RIGHT, THARN?
WHATEVER.