Tharn, what time are the musicians
coming to record the demo today?
Tharn.
Tharn!
Hey.
Tharn.
I asked you what time the musicians
are coming to record the demo today.
-Musicians?
-Yeah.
At 2:30.
But only the keyboardist is coming.
It's a good idea to finish
a guide track for the vocalist first.
We can record the full band later
if it gets approved.
And what's wrong with you?
No, nothing's wrong.
Glad you're okay.
Gil.
Do you think it's wrong of me…
to want to possess someone so badly…
that I want to let the whole world know
that he only belongs to me?
What are you babbling about?
It's not wrong because it means
they're important to you.
Stop sulking, stop babbling,
and finish your job.
It's almost lunchtime, and I'm hungry.
What should we eat?
Anything's fine.
You choose.
Yeah, sure, Mr. Thara.
You're not picky at all.
I don't know what's going on with you,
but cheer up, man.
-Gotta go.
-Thanks.
I don't think this case is difficult,
but it'll need continuous follow-ups.
Okay, then, I'm counting on you.
Mr. Thiwat.
Yes?
The boss ordered you to compile
and hand in last month's cases.
But that's not my responsibility.
That's not my problem.
I'm just relaying his order.
Please, excuse me.
What terrible sin did you commit?
I really don't know.
Cheer up.
Thanks.
I'm going home to wash up.
See you tonight.
Hello, what's up?
Off work yet?
No, some work suddenly came up
this afternoon.
So, when will you be finished?
I don't know.
Then… are you working tomorrow?
Want me to buy food for you?
It's fine. Hurry home and rest
if you're done work.
It's okay, Type.
I'll swing by to bring you some food.
It's too much trouble. Just go home.
Going back and forth will tire you out.
Fine, then, I'll just go home first.
Tell me when you finish work.
I'll pick you up.
It's okay, I can go home on my own.
I'll pick you up, it's no bother at all.
It's a hassle.
I'll go home on my own after work.
Okay.
Are you…
coming to watch my gig tonight?
I don't think so.
Tons of paperwork to deal with.
Don't get upset.
-I'll see you at home.
-Okay.
Tell me when you get home.
Okay. I'm gonna get back to work.
Okay.
Yes, come in.
Doc? You're still here?
My shift just ended.
I saw the light on,
so I came to check on you.
Figured you hadn't left yet.
Yeah.
Work suddenly came up.
I wanna finish it by tonight.
Urgent case?
Last month's case reports.
Only your patients?
If that was the case,
I would've finished it ages ago.
It's for the whole department.
Assigned this afternoon.
Deadline, tomorrow morning.
Guess I've got a bull's-eye on my head.
Why do you have to do it alone?
It's not your job at all.
Never mind, I'll finish it soon.
Fine.
So, when can you go home?
I don't know. I'll leave when I finish it.
By the way, do you need anything?
I was going to ask you
to come out for dinner.
Gonna have to pass.
This should take a while.
Champ? In that case, you should hurry.
-But--
-It's okay, there's not that much to do.
Champ will get hangry if you're late.
But if Champ finds out that
you're doing other people's jobs…
he won't let it go either.
You know Champ pretty well.
I know…
that Champ really loves his friends.
-And if Champ finds out--
-Then, just don't tell him.
You're making me feel guilty
for taking up you and Champ's time.
But--
I'm fine.
You'd better go.
Okay.
I'm leaving, then.
Good luck.
TENYA
Doc?
You're distracted again. What's wrong?
Nothing, I just have some things
on my mind.
Is it work?
Not exactly.
Whatever it is, eat first, think later.
Okay?
I'm not like you, eating all the time.
You've got to eat a lot.
You're way too small.
Who says I'm small? I'm not small.
I'm as tall as you.
I guess you're right.
You're as tall as me.
But I don't know why
you seem so small to me.
There is a certain phrase
that my sister often says.
It's…
"so small that I wanna roll it
into a ball and swallow it."
Have you heard that?
What does it mean?
I don't get it, either.
When my sister watches a movie,
she usually uses words like…
"totes adorbs" or something like that.
When she sees a cute guy, she says…
"I wanna roll him
into a ball and swallow him."
Like that.
-Really?
-I don't quite get it, either.
And then?
You're really paying attention.
It's rare that you talk about your family.
Guess I'm practically mute
whenever I'm with Techno.
But the thing about rolling something
into a ball and swallowing it…
I didn't quite get it…
until…
Until?
Until I met you.
Let's eat before I actually roll you
into a ball and swallow you up.
I'm happy to see you smile.
You've been wearing
that serious face all day.
You can always talk to me.
You know that, right?
Actually…
I'm not worried about my work.
But I'm worried about Type.
Type?
What about him?
There seems to be someone in the hospital
who doesn't like him.
I need to deliver these documents
to my superior or I'll get in trouble.
Patient files?
No, my department's operational plan.
Hold on.
But that isn't your responsibility.
Yeah, I know that.
But he's the boss.
I have to do what he says.
When I left, Type was still doing the work
his boss had given him.
It's not even his responsibility.
I don't know if Type has offended someone.
But it wasn't the first time
I saw it happen.
I've seen it several times now.
Type is straightforward
to the point of being blunt.
That can either make people
very fond of him
or hate him to the core.
But I know him well.
He can manage. He's invincible.
Don't think about it too much.
Okay.
You really…
care about all of your friends.
I care about you too.
Really?
So,
what kind of a person am I,
in your opinion?
You're sweet and kind.
Everyone likes you.
See? You're being cute again.
Says who? I'm not trying to be cute.
That's good.
Let's eat.
Before I roll you into a ball
and swallow you for real.
-The food's pretty good.
-Yeah.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Drive safely. Tell me when you get home.
Okay, have a safe trip home too.
Okay, see you later.
Uncle…
I need a favor from you.
Damn,
it's already this late?
SWEET SMILE. PLAYS GUITAR.
ANYONE WOULD FALL FOR HIM.
WHEN WILL YOU STOP FILMING ME?
I didn't go with you.
You must've been very happy.
Damn.
Where have you been?
That's a lot of stuff there.
I went snack shopping for Phugun.
He sure loves snacks, huh?
Yeah.
Then I'll buy some for him later.
-It's okay.
-Why?
I can take care of him.
Did you just get home?
You got back pretty late.
Yeah…
I've been busy lately.
Don't worry.
I don't have time to play with Phu
to make someone jealous.
See you, cousin-in-law.
Tharn, it's cramped.
Tharn.
When should I pick you up?
Type, when should I pick you up?
It's okay, I can go home on my own.
I gave you a ride,
so I have to pick you up.
I told you not to give me a ride,
didn't I?
You were silent all this time
because you were sulking about it, right?
I'm not sulking.
How can I not pick you up
when you're like this?
You worked too hard last night,
you know that?
I played at Khong's bar,
but I still got home before you.
Isn't that a good thing?
You might wanna hang out
with someone else.
Who do you mean?
Which one should I pick,
number three or this one?
I like number eight too.
I like number five.
-Number five?
-Yes.
Okay, then, number five it is.
Thorn, why aren't you asking
for Am's opinion?
I already talked to her,
and she let me make the decision.
Because she knew
that I'd eventually let you choose.
Am always indulges you.
She's not at all afraid
that you're gonna get spoiled.
Here you are. I've been looking for you.
You're finally here, Tharn.
Where's Type?
Busy with work.
Thanya.
-I bought you a cake.
-Thank you.
She's shooting a drama.
She needs to watch her weight.
Just one piece won't hurt.
-I'm going to put it away.
-Okay.
You look upset.
Did you have a fight with Type?
I don't know if you'd call it a fight.
We've been disagreeing
whenever we talk about anything.
We argue more than we talk.
Have you done something wrong?
Thanya, you always side with Type.
Have you forgotten
that Tharn is your brother?
I haven't, but Type
isn't an unreasonable person.
What, are you saying I'm unreasonable?
No, what I mean is,
Type isn't sulky like you.
You're gonna blame me
for being sulky, no matter what, right?
But you're right, I'm really sulky
when it comes to Type.
You're only like that with him.
The same goes for Thorn.
No matter how much he pampers me,
he only loves Am.
But you are our most precious
little sister, Thanya.
HAVING LUNCH AT HOME.
MOM AND THANYA MISS YOU.
Hey, what's wrong?
You've been staring at your phone all day.
What do you mean? It's only noon.
Fine, half a day.
But if that person doesn't contact you,
you'll be gloomy all day.
Let me see your gloomy face.
Sorry, but that person just texted me.
Then, eat your lunch if you're happy.
We have so much work to do.
Teng, can I ask you something?
What?
If you did something wrong and wanted to
make up for it without losing face…
what would you do?
The one who texted you?
Just answer the question.
If it was me, I would…
I don't wanna know anymore.
Just kidding.
What, can't I be coy if you're not gonna
go public with that person?
Okay, I'll be serious.
If it was me, I would buy them flowers.
Flowers?
Flowers work on every occasion.
Thiwat speaking.
Okay, I'm coming.
That's one long sigh.
Boss called?
Close, it's his secretary.
Boss wants to meet me in the afternoon.
What a drag.
What can I do for you, sir?
BOOK THREE (FIVE)
Since you're so competent,
help me with the department's
procurement documents.
But I don't think
that's my responsibility.
You're right.
But I happen to be your superior.
Am I correct, Mr. Thiwat?
Yes, sir.
Therefore, when I, your superior,
give you an order, you must obey it.
Or do you want a warning notice?
-Are you forcing--
-And I have the authority
to sign your resignation letter too.
You have two options.
Follow my order.
Or let me exercise my authority.
If that's all, then, please excuse me.
I want it done in three days.
Type.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
Type.
Type, you got off work?
I've been waiting for you.
But it's okay, I don't mind waiting.
Can you stop following me?
-Let's have dinner together.
-No.
-Coffee's fine too.
-I said no!
But I really wanna talk to you.
Type!
Fiat!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry for chasing you earlier.
No, it's okay.
If you wanna get better soon,
don't do it again.
I'm really sorry.
You're kind, do you realize that?
I'm not kind.
I'm sorry about earlier too.
I was upset about something.
What is it?
Forget it.
It's nothing.
I don't wanna complain to a kid.
But this kid is always ready
to listen to you.
Someone told me if you keep
your problems to yourself,
you could get sick from stress.
Don't make a big deal
out of what I'm about to say.
Okay.
Recently, I've realized
the reality of something.
What is it?
Studying and working
are as different as night and day.
When I studied, everything was fun.
No matter how hard courses were,
the worst that could happen
was failing one.
But when it comes to work,
it's just like they say.
Dealing with people
is more tiring than working.
When people insulted me,
all I had to do was strike back.
But when "superior" and "position"
come into the picture…
even if I meet people
who haven't matured with age…
I can't do anything.
Then…
what do you do?
Endure it.
What if you can't take it anymore?
I'm lucky that day hasn't come yet.
But patience has its limits.
Never mind.
Don't take it too seriously.
Can I ask you something?
How far are you from reaching your limit?
I'm close.
What are you doing?
Nothing, I wanna show
the coffee to my friends.
What are you sulking about?
And what kind of an apology is this?
You think this is the only part
of the apology?
I'm sorry.
This is for me?
Who else would it be for?
I've apologized.
Honestly…
you had me at "sorry."
I don't want to lose you.
When you finish work…
hurry to bed.
I'll text you.
Type is cute, isn't he?
Where are you?
I'm gonna see Type. Why?
Come back right now.
What's wrong with you?
I said come to my house right now.
We need to talk.
Come on, can't I go see Type first?
He's been kind enough to let me see him.
But I said I needed to talk to you.
Come to my house right now!
Okay, fine.
Why are you raising your voice at me?
Fine, I'll go to your house.
Why did you call me here?
I finally got Type to talk to me.
You always ruin my happiness.
Why are you showing me this?
He's got a boyfriend.
So what?
He's got his own man.
You shouldn't mess with him.
I've never interfered with you
when you fooled around.
But this is wrong.
How am I wrong?
They're not married.
I've still got a chance.
I've been your friend for ten years.
I've never known you to be so desperate.
-Leo.
-Am I wrong?
I'm telling you he's got a boyfriend.
You should get the message.
He's got a boyfriend. So what?
-I don't care.
-Fiat!
Don't raise your voice at me.
This time, I'm serious.
You know he's got a boyfriend.
Why won't you just give up?
Because I want him.
Even if he's got a boyfriend
or children, I don't care.
Stop acting like an attention-seeking kid.
That's my problem.
It's none of your business.
I'm warning you, leave him alone.
I won't.
-Then, get out of my house.
-No.
So, leave him alone.
I'm telling you I won't stay away
from Type. Never.
Don't you get it?
Then, get out of my house.
-I won't--
-Get out!
I said get out!
-You're kicking me out?
-Yeah!
Fine!
I'm leaving!
Don't you know I'm doing this…
because of you!
So, why did you chase me away?
You're all I have.
Why are you doing this to me?
What about me?
Don't you ever think about how I feel?
Fiat.
Are you okay?
Leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
Get up. Let's get inside.
You kicked me out, so why do you care?
Fiat.
Let's get inside.
No.
Stay still.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
How can you go home
when your knee hurts like this?
Stay the night here.
You're gonna yell at me again.
I won't.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry…
for chasing you out like that.
I was angry that you didn't listen to me.
Please forgive me.
Don't chase me away again.
I won't do it again.
Why did you pull away?
I brushed my teeth and used mouthwash.
If you don't believe me, I can prove it.
This is how you prove it.
Fine, I believe you.
Are you going to stay up all night?
Yeah, you sleep first.
Type, I think you should rest.
Just do it tomorrow, please.
No, if I sleep now,
I won't wake up to do it tomorrow.
Then I'll set the alarm for you,
and you can go to bed now, okay?
You've got some nerve.
You still turn off my alarm
even to this day.
I won't do it tomorrow.
Please go to sleep.
I don't believe you.
I'm serious, Type.
I think you should sleep. Get some rest.
I know I need to rest.
I love your after-shower scent.
Why?
You mean, I normally stink?
No.
Your scent makes me feel at ease.
You should sleep.
I thought you said you'd rest.
I rested.
The hug earlier.
Come on, Type.
Please, I want you to sleep.
Or is there anything I can do for you?
You've helped me enough
by staying here with me.
Fine.
But I want to do more than that.
It reminds me of that day.
When I was kicked out of my house.
When you were crying in front of my house?
Yeah.
You still think about that?
I'll never forget it.
I remember that day clearly.
The day my dad kicked me out of the house.
Just because I didn't accept the woman
he was going to marry.
Why?
I was just afraid I'd lose him.
He was all I had.
But he kicked me out,
yelled at me.
Said I wasn't his son.
Damn it.
If you hadn't been there for me that day…
If your family hadn't let me stay here…
I really don't know how
I would have lived without you.
But today you kicked me out.
Just like my dad did.
I'm sorry.
I was just angry.
But I never meant to kick you out.
Anyone else can chase me away,
and I won't care.
But don't you chase me away.
I don't care if the whole world hates me…
or throws me away like trash.
But you must stay by my side.
Don't chase me away.
Don't leave me.
He hasn't come home yet?
What are you trying to do?
STRATEGIES FOR TYPE'S HUBBY
IT'S COMPLETE.
BECAUSE YOU RECRUITED
THE WHOLE FAMILY TO HELP YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT. I ALMOST BUMPED
INTO TYPE WHEN I CAME DOWN.
LUCKILY, I HID HER IN TIME.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
DON'T THANK ME, I DIDN'T HELP.
RIGHT, CHAMP?
THE FOOD'S FROM MY RESTAURANT.
THEN I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THIS?
YEAH.
YEP.
YES.