[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 30]
The Clan is making such
a powerful weapon.
What do you think
they are using it for?
For the Ceremony of Light.
The Ceremony of Light?
On the day of the Ceremony,
Her Majesty will kick off candle lighting
and gold painting for the statue of Buddha
at the Heavenly Temple.
If I were from the Clan, that would be
the best time
for me to take action.
Any evidence?
I need more time to look into it.
My lord,
please persuade Her Majesty
into canceling the Ceremony
before I can get evidence.
Cancel it?
Do you know how much
different departments and regions
have spent on and done for it
in the past 6 months?
You can't just cancel it.
Putting it off also works
if it can't be canceled.
Do you want it to be postponed
until you figure out the Clan's plan?
If you can't
find out their plan,
Her Majesty can never
hold the Ceremony, right?
This matters a lot.
We should prepare for the worst.
The Clan already has
the formula of the Thunder.
We can't afford the consequences
once they set it off at the Ceremony.
Our Services works to make our society safer.
We've caught many villains
to protect Luoyang.
We've never asked Her Majesty
to cancel any events.
Now you are saying
we have to cancel the Ceremony
because of a so-called 'weapon.'
It would be so humiliating for us
if people got to know it.
The Thunder is a weapon of mass destruction.
Once it's set off,
It will be devastating for Her Majesty
and people in Luoyang.
How could you still worry
about our reputation
at this critical moment?
Gao Bingzhu,
do you think
you are protecting Luoyang,
but we, as officials,
are always being
indecisive and timid?
Aren't you?
Gao,
mind your manners!
Baitan.
Sir.
Madam.
Careful.
Brother.
Are you feeling worse?
I'm fine.
You're up.
Is your leg still hurting?
Luckily, your bones didn't get hurt.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Don't stand here.
Careful.
Madam.
Sit down.
Madam, Sir Wu searched for you
in mountains the whole night,
[Li Chun, Interior Guard]
so his illness recurred.
Shut up.
Why did you come over
right after you woke up?
You need more rest.
You are the one who needs more rest.
Her Majesty assigned our Services
to ensure the safety and security
at the Ceremony of Light.
We can't make any mistakes.
Now, there is a weapon
called the Thunder.
It's hard to tell what the Clan
will do with it in the future.
I can take the security job.
Siyue,
you nearly died
and I nearly lost you.
Your top priority now
should be your health.
You can't risk your life anymore.
Your illness recurred because of me.
I just want to share
some of your burdens.
I'm fine.
Escort Madam Wu back to her room.
I'm not leaving.
I want to be with you for a while.
You weren't born in a royal family.
You don't understand
my discreetness in the Court.
I'm Lord Chu
and the King of East River now,
but I will be a prisoner
if I make one mistake.
I don't care
about being Lord Chu.
My worry is that our Services
would be controlled by evildoers.
If that happened, you wouldn't be able to
share your thoughts
with anyone in the Services.
I know you care
about people in Luoyang.
I'm proud of you.
I will report to Her Majesty
about the Thunder
but I don't think she
will cancel the Ceremony
based on how much I know her.
What we should do now
is to stop the Clan's plan
as soon as possible.
They got copper from Mount Lian
and the Xuanwu's Pearl.
The Clan has been planning for a long time.
Their leader, Lord Freedom,
is kept in the dungeon
in the Interior Guard Services.
I want to see him.
You should bring enough
people for this operation.
Make sure
to kill Baili Hongyi.
[Gong Yan, disciple of Four Season Clan]
Yes.
[Grave of Baili Kuanren, West Mountain]
My lord.
Hongyi.
My lord!
You...
What are you doing?
It's against the laws.
I know.
Hongyi!
No. Don't do it.
What?
Are you going to report me?
I...
I mean...
Your brother is buried here.
You will be punished by God
for digging his grave.
Uncle Baili.
You can't do it.
No.
Uncle Baili.
Hongyi.
Uncle Baili, please.
Hongyi,
are you sure about this?
Yes.
The cause of my brother's death is unknown.
His handwriting was found
at Tiantong's place.
I have to investigate it.
Hongyi.
Sir, a person from the Intelligence
Services wants to see you.
He is here for work.
Let him in.
Yes, sir.
I am Gao Bingzhu, the Halberdier
of the Intelligence Services.
Greetings, sir.
It's like you're asking for trouble.
Did you forget what I said
to you on the North Mountain?
Lord Chu sent me here.
I'm not scared of him.
Siyue isn't here.
No one can protect you.
Guys!
Are you going to neglect
the security of the Ceremony of Light?
The Thunder
is a weapon of mass destruction.
You saw its power with your own eyes.
Can you afford
the consequences
if the Clan sets it off
at the Ceremony?
What are you here for?
I want to see Lord Freedom.
How come there are rocks inside?
My brother is still alive.
He was born with an extra finger
so he couldn't be an official.
[Baili Kuanren]
It upset him a lot.
He often read
grandfather's books.
My brother must know
the relationship
between my grandfather and the Clan.
He must also know that my grandfather
was studying witchcraft.
Everything will make sense
if he is still alive.
Bother,
learning to read and write
is not fun at all.
Can you play
with me for a while?
Didn't I give you the ring puzzle?
Have you worked it out?
It's so hard.
I tried my best, but still,
they're just separate iron rings.
I can't make a loop out of them.
If I had one more finger
like you,
I might have been able
to work it out.
I've told you a million times.
Do not mention my fingers.
You want to have that extra finger,
but you can't imagine
how much I want it to be chopped off.
Uncle Baili.
Leave.
My lord,
they might come back again.
We'd better leave.
Hongyi.
Let's restore the grave first.
[Lord Freedom,
Leader of Four Season Clan]
The 28th.
Congratulations.
Listen, weeds.
Moral ones
won't be hurt by fire or water.
They can survive cold and hot weather.
Beasts can't hurt them.
The person on the throne should be moral,
but the evil Empress is only a dim light.
She can't shine with the sun and the moon.
Weeds spread widely.
Fire burns them down.
These weeds
will be gone in the fire.
How to set them on fire?
Come.
Come here.
Come closer.
Do you know who I am?
Lord Freedom.
Yes.
Were you sent by the Clan?
Look,
the Clan governs nature.
It burns down all weeds
and makes sure everything is in order.
Once you have fire...
And then?
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
♫Grew in the northwest♫
♫Lived on miasma and grew by rivers♫
♫Flourished to the River Gu and the sky♫
I've told you.
He is a nut.
You're a nut.
You're both nuts.
Lord Freedom.
There're too many weeds in the world.
They can't all be burned down.
They can.
Lowly weeds grow in the wind.
They threaten valuable plants and trees.
They have to be set on fire
and burnt to dust.
In this way, everything
in nature can be in order.
Even so, weeds grow crazily.
They'll never stop
growing even if you
keep mowing them.
Unless you use
the Thunder.
Right.
Good idea.
The Thunder.
Where will the Thunder
be set off?
Luoyang.
Where in Luoyang?
The great rose of Sharon...
-Where in Luoyang?
-Grew in the northwest,
lived on miasma,
-and grew by rivers.
-Stop it.
Where in Luoyang?
Where?
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
♫Grew in the northwest♫
♫Lived on miasma and grew by rivers♫
♫Flourished to the River Gu and the sky♫
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
♫Saw 8 thousand years as spring♫
♫Grew in the northwest♫
-lived on miasma...
-Wait.
♫Grew by rivers♫
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
♫Saw 8 thousand years as spring♫
♫Saw another 8 thousand years as autumn♫
♫The Clan is located♫
♫Where the great rose of Sharon grows♫
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
♫Grew in the northwest♫
♫Lived on miasma♫
They grew in the northwest,
lived on miasma,
grew by rivers,
and flourished to the River Gu and the sky.
Madam, why did you get up?
Is your leg okay?
I'm fine.
It's time for medicine.
I just took some.
Why do I need to take more?
The prescriptions are different.
The doctor asked me to bring this one
four hours after you had the last one.
Any news about Gao Bingzhu?
He just came
to our Services.
He came for work
on behalf of the Intelligence Services.
Sir Wu...
Madam.
Sir,
your work is done.
This way, please.
Thanks, Sir Li.
By the way, do you know
if Madam Wu is getting any better?
She is fine.
We will surely
take care of her.
Please.
Gao Bingzhu!
You can go.
Yes, madam.
Is your leg getting better?
Why didn't you come to see me now that you're here?
I needed to talk to Sir Wu
and
I will leave Luoyang for some time.
Did you find new clues
or did my brother
say something to you?
I'm going with you.
My leg is fine.
At least you can have some company.
Siyue,
your top priority now
is to get recovered.
Luoyang needs you
at such a critical time.
You need to work with Sir Wu
to ensure the security of the Ceremony.
I'll come back as soon as I can.
Gao Bingzhu!
Do you remember
what you've said?
You told me to
stay alive
to find Tan
with you together
and save people
from the Unwelcome Well.
You also promised me
that you'd stay alive and enjoy
the beauty of Luoyang with me together.
Will you
keep your word?
♫In my memory♫
♫My colorful dream was lit up♫
I will, forever.
♫We said goodbye♫
♫I murmured that I'd never see you again♫
♫I'm waiting♫
♫Waiting to wake up from the dream♫
♫Wake up♫
♫Stay♫
Madam.
What's up?
Sir Wu passed out.
Brother.
How is he?
Sir Wu's illness recurred,
and he has been overtaxing himself.
That's why he passed out.
Brother,
wake up.
I didn't listen to you.
You got sick because of me.
Brother,
I'm sorry.
I will
listen to you in the future.
Please wake up.
Don't forget
what you just said.
Brother.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
You scared me.
You scared me to death!
Don't worry, everyone.
Go back to your work.
Yes, sir.
How do you feel?
-I'm fine.
-It's good that you woke up, sir.
You just need to take medicine on time
and let your body recover slowly.
Also,
madam,
you should also
look after yourself.
Thanks, doctor.
Sir,
if you'll excuse me.
Don't cry, Siyue.
Go prepare some ink.
I need to draft reports.
You're in poor condition.
Can't you take a break?
The Ceremony of Light is approaching.
Her Majesty will be present.
We should be
very cautious.
Why didn't you rest in your room?
You shouldn't have come here.
I'm fine.
My injury isn't severe.
You, on the contrary,
should rest your mind.
How could I?
Her Majesty trusts our Services.
We should serve her with our lives.
Even if you don't care about your health,
think about the Services!
You're the backbone of the Services.
How could we serve Her Majesty
if you were too ill to work?
Just let me and Beiqi know
whatever you want to do.
We will do it for you.
We can report
everything to you.
Beiqi and I
grew up by your side.
You can surely
trust us.
I hope he can remember
why I slapped him.
Anyway,
if anything happens,
the two of you shall make a decision together
and let me know.
Do not
be impulsive.
There are two major issues in our Services.
First,
we should ensure that
the Ceremony takes place safely.
Second,
we can't underestimate the Thunder.
I'm afraid that
you can't handle it alone,
so I need to find someone to assist you.
Do you have a name in mind?
I'll let you know.
Uncle Baili,
you kept trying to stop me from opening the coffin.
Did you already know
my brother's body
isn't in it?
We nearly got killed by the assassin
when we were at my brother's grave.
It means that my brother
is probably related to a big conspiracy.
I'm so close to the truth now.
Uncle Baili,
are you still
not telling me the truth?
My lord,
I didn't mean to lie to you.
On the night when your brother died,
your father asked us to prepare the funeral
overnight
and bury your brother the next day.
Your father did everything from picking
the burial clothes to closing the coffin.
He didn't allow others to participate.
After your brother was buried,
he asked us
to vow
not to mention your brother in the Mansion.
People who gossiped
were laid off
by your father.
So,
my father did
everything by himself.
I don't really know any details,
but your father must have
kept it from others
for some reason.
That's why I tried to stop you.
[Baili Mansion]
I said something harsh to you
the last time I came here
because I was worried about Siyue.
Please pardon me.
It's fine,
as long as Madam Wu is alright.
Are you okay, sir?
I'll just cut to the chase.
You're aware that
Her Majesty assigned my Services
to ensure the security of the Ceremony.
It's important,
but as you can see,
my health
is getting worse.
Perhaps, I won't make it.
Siyue could have
helped me
but she got injured.
That's why I came to see you.
You two are friends.
I hope you can
work with our Services
to assist her.
The interior guards are all agile.
I am not as strong as them.
How can I do it?
Hongyi,
don't look down upon yourself.
I thought about it,
but I still think you are the best person to do it.
First,
you understand the power
of the Thunder.
Second,
and most importantly,
you know inside out about the buildings
and streets in Luoyang.
It helps us to foresee
the operations of the Clan.
It's good for security management at the Ceremony.
I'll think about it.
Sir,
I remember that
you studied with my brother.
I did.
Your brother, the King of Zhao,
and I
were students
of Fu Lyuping, the North Gate Scholar.
Why are you bringing this up?
Could you please tell me
the stories between you and my brother?
Back then,
the three of us were just teenagers.
We were of a similar age,
but our family backgrounds
were very different.
Still, it didn't prevent us
from being friends.
We used to
hang out all the time.
We played backgammon
and polo.
The King of Zhao
was very playful.
He often egged me and your brother on
to skip class
and play with him.
In the past,
we enjoyed puppetry
by the Tianjin Bridge.
We also watched entertainers from the West
performing fire breathing in the south market.
We experienced all of the novel and interesting things
in Luoyang.
However, we skipped too many classes
and our teacher finally found out.
He'd question us one by one.
Then, the three of us
would make up stories together.
Your brother
was very honest.
He couldn't lie at all.
He would blush every time
he was questioned
and ended up
telling the teacher
what really happened,
leaving nothing out.
Our teacher hit our hands
with a stick as a punishment.
Your brother was hit
the hardest.
His 11 fingers were swollen
and looked like bamboo shoots.
My hands looked like
stuffed buns while the hands
of the King of Zhao were like steamed buns.
We never felt any pain though.
We would just look at each other
and laugh for no reason.
That was the happiest
and the most relaxing time in my life.
Who'd have thought that
accidents can happen at any time?
Your brother passed away 10 years ago.
7 years ago,
the King of Zhao...
Sir,
is it possible that
my brother is still alive?
You guys can leave.
Yes, sir.
Alive?
How could it be possible?
I checked his grave.
His body isn't in the coffin.
I've failed your brother's trust.
I've heard that grave robbery
is common in Luoyang
and there is a custom to arrange
marriages for the deceased.
I didn't expect criminals
to be so reckless.
They even dared
to rob a grave of the noble.
I was little when my brother
passed away.
My memories are fuzzy,
but I remember that
you and your men came to the Mansion
the day he died.
Hongyi,
your brother
was my close friend.
I wouldn't have recalled
my memory about him if you hadn't
brought it up.
I can lead you
to our Archive
to check the records
if you really want to look into this.
[Maintain Social Order]
Clear the Heavenly Temple
three days before the Ceremony.
Sui Xin.
Yes.
Take some people to guard the Temple.
Don't let other people in without permission.
Yes, madam.
The three areas near the Temple
should start
to be under the state of siege
one day before the Ceremony.
Li Chun.
Yes.
Take people to lock down the areas
and don't let people get in and out.
Yes, madam.
Any suspicious people
got in
or out of Luoyang recently?
Madam,
we've checked the records of people
entering Luoyang recently.
A group of more than ten people
entered the capital.
They are licensed as refugees.
Refugees?
Traditionally,
refugees aren't allowed to enter
Luoyang before the Ceremony.
How did they get in?
What happened?
You can ask Sir Li
after he is back.
Why is he related to this?
[May it please Your Majesty]
May it please Your Majesty,
Baili Kuanren
has been proven
to defame the Court.
According to the law,
he will be exiled
to the northwestern region
and never come back to Luoyang.
Baili Kuanren was terrified
after he pleaded guilty
and eventually died of illness at home.
I, Wu Youjue, took Your Majesty's order
to check his body in the Baili Mansion.
I saw that the right hand of the deceased
had 6 fingers.
It can be confirmed that
it's Baili Kuanren's body.
Show me the license.
[Refugees, licensed by Li Beiqi,
Interior Guard]
Li Beiqi, interior guard.
He let them in.
Where is Li Beiqi?
Is he still out?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen him today.
Li Chun.
Yes.
Go and find out the whereabouts of the refugees.
Yes, madam.
Chen Wu,
tell the doorkeepers.
Once Li Beiqi comes back,
tell him to see me immediately.
Yes, madam.
Take my order.
Yes.
The Ceremony is approaching.
Check everywhere.
Make sure things are in order.
Yes, madam.
My brother
would never defame the Court.
What crime did he really commit?
Actually, he was framed
by Lai Junche, a corrupt official,
and died because of him.
Years ago,
Lai was so powerful
that everyone was afraid of him.
Your brother cared about politics
although he wasn't an official.
He listed Lai's crimes in a letter
to Her Majesty,
but Her Majesty
didn't receive the letter.
The letter was seized by Lai.
Lai then framed your brother up
by saying that he defamed the Court
and insulted Her Majesty.
Her Majesty
thought your brother was guilty.
He got the verdict,
and less than half a month later,
he died of illness at home.
Even so,
such a sudden death
sounds suspicious.
Where is the doctor who treated him?
I felt the same.
I asked the doctor,
but he told me that
everything looked normal.
He only said
Kuanren was depressed
and died
because of it.
The doctor has already passed away.
Madam.
We can't find
the refugees' whereabouts.
The destinations they registered
are all fake addresses.
Fake addresses?
Inform the Grand Court
to help us
find the refugees.
Yes, madam.
Luoyang is huge.
They are like
a handful of salt spread
into the Yellow River.
It's impossible to find them.
Nevertheless, we have to find them.
Li Chun.
Yes.
Send more people to find Li Beiqi.
Make sure to take him back.
I want his explanation.
Madam,
If we find him and he
refuses to go with us,
should we arrest him or kill him?
Take him back here.
Yes, madam.
Kuanren
had an ambition.
If he hadn't had an extra finger,
he could've been an official
and made a difference.
Hongyi,
you're similar to your brother.
You are both persistent.
Now you knew
how Kuanren died.
You must hate the Court.
I won't force you to assist
the security job of the Ceremony
if you don't want to.
I'm in.
Do you really believe
what that crazy old man said?
People tend to be honest
when they are crazy.
Tell me
about the surroundings of the River Gu.
Do you know what the area is
and how big it is?
Even if the Clan is there,
it will take you,
the Grand Court,
and the Interior Guard Services
over months to search it.
Also,
there are many valleys, swamps,
[River Jian, Luoyang, Mount Zhou]
and ancient trees by the River.
People easily get lost in it.
What's worse,
the area releases miasma.
It's poisonous.
The Clan
can't be there.
♫The great rose of Sharon♫
The great rose of Sharon
♫Grew in the northwest♫
grew in the northwest,
♫Lived on miasma♫
lived on miasma.
It grew by rivers
and flourished to the River Gu.
What does it mean?
[River Jian, Luoyang, Mount Zhou]