(Doom at Your Service)
(All characters, locations, organizations, religions, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
Tak Dong Kyung.
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
Then, who are you?
It's cold tonight.
Why did she leave? She could catch a cold. Goodness.
Tak Dong Kyung.
First floor. The doors are closing.
Going down.
- What was that about? - My aunt.
If she sees us, things will get complicated.
If we want to talk, I can't let her catch us.
Talk about what?
Aren't you here because you needed to talk to me?
I doubt that you came back because you missed me...
since we just saw each other.
Why did you ask me who I was?
You even know my name.
Then, what about your question?
I explained to you who I am and what I do.
I don't know.
Something feels weird.
Second basement floor.
- Where are we going? - To the parking lot.
This will be a long conversation.
(Episode 13)
I need to ask you something.
It's cold out here. Let's talk inside.
I can't do that inside.
I'll lose there...
because it's your turf.
- Then, this place works for you? - No.
There isn't such a place.
I picked this place...
because it'd be easier to run away if I wanted.
Let's stop skirting around it now.
- Joo Ik. - Yes.
Did you kiss her?
Did you...
kiss her 10 years ago?
- Yes. - Why?
To get her out of there.
So you two wouldn't get back together.
Why?
She cried there every single day.
If I didn't make her leave that day,
she would have cried, sitting on that step for days and months.
I didn't want her...
to come back again, sit there, and cry.
- That's why I did it. - Did you think about me?
- Did you? - I did.
All the more reason why I did it.
You knew that she was waiting for you.
You knew, but you never went out to see her...
because you were embarrassed.
You left Korea as if you were never going to come back,
but you came back only after a few months because it was tough.
You didn't want her to find out.
Say something.
Curse me out if you want. I'll handle it.
I won't run away.
Why are you brutally honest?
You could have avoided answering it,
apologized, and moved on.
You have a way with words too.
Why are you brutally honest with me?
Because I like you.
You are...
one of a few people I actually like.
I don't want to be a coward in front of you.
I've hidden it for too long.
And all these years,
it had been bothering me too.
This is so annoying.
You still make me feel worthless even in this moment.
You're so annoying.
Where are you going?
- To the cafe. - Why?
I don't think I can sleep in the same house with you tonight.
I regret every moment of it.
Running away, taking too long,
and asking you.
Everything.
I was crying.
I looked in the mirror after I came back.
And I was crying.
But I didn't even know I was crying.
When I looked in the mirror, I was crying.
Why was I crying?
Get in.
Where are we going?
You'll be safe. Get in.
Have you seen...
a girl who's about this tall and has hair coming up to here?
Have you?
A girl who's about this tall and has hair coming up to here?
That description fits so many girls.
Have you met someone like her at the hospital?
- Are you talking about her? - Have you met her?
What did she do to you?
She didn't do anything. I did something for her.
I opened a bottle for her.
What else?
After that, she thanked me and told me to go to the rooftop.
She said the view there was nice.
- Anything else other than that? - No.
Think again. I'm sure she did something to you.
What did she do?
That's what I don't know. So think again.
I don't know.
What do you know then?
What does she have to do with us?
Does she know me?
I can't remember her either?
Perhaps, your brain has just gone bad, not sick.
No need to talk about yourself now.
Right. I'm not exactly kind.
All good, right? It's my turn now.
You weren't crying?
Why won't you answer my question?
I asked if you weren't crying. Was I the only one who cried?
I'm not done with my questions yet.
Who were you calling earlier?
Exactly. That's really weird.
I was crying.
But I couldn't get that thought out of my head.
"I must call you."
- "You"? - But...
I don't know who that person is.
That person's number is saved on my cell phone.
But I have no idea who it is.
Call that number again.
(Call log)
(Human)
Whoever it is isn't picking up. Whose number is this?
"Human". Who's "Human"?
Who knows? At least I know it's not me.
I should go now.
What about me?
What?
Aren't you going to drive me back?
It's nearby.
Walk back. It's only five minutes by foot.
Gosh, if he were human I would've taught him a lesson.
Who could it be?
"Human".
Why do you fall so easily?
Watch where you're going.
I thought you were leaving.
Yes, I was on my way.
My gosh. Seriously.
He must be mad in the head.
(Missed call: Dong Kyung)
(Business proposal)
(Sales and Marketing Plan)
(The Story of Genius Minds, Welcome to Genius)
(Friday, Saturday, Sunday)
(My love confession is either always too early or too late.)
(My love confession...)
(is either always too early or too late.)
(From "The Romantic Egoists")
My gosh, he startled me.
Mr. Lee. Mr. Lee!
Oh, hey. Gosh.
You're here.
Did you sleep here?
- Yes. - Why?
Did you fight with your friend?
No.
Then what?
We're still fighting.
They're always fighting. It's like they're a married couple.
Here's the business proposal you asked for. Take a look.
Did you fight with Hyun Kyu?
What are you talking about? Does it look like I fought with him?
I guess you guys didn't have a fistfight yet.
I'm not going to fight him. Plus, I'd win anyway.
Is that so? You think you'll win? Are you sure about that?
So you lost.
- We haven't fought yet. - Then go ahead and fight.
You won't know who will win until you actually fight him.
Do you want me to go around fighting people?
Do you know why I adore Hyun Kyu so much?
Maybe it's because he grew up as an athlete,
but behind that smile of his, I can tell he's very competitive.
I really like that about him.
Whatever.
You're nothing like him.
When he's in for a competition,
he does everything he can to win, but look at you.
You always just yield as if it doesn't even matter.
I bet he's pretty irritated though.
You always let him win without even putting up a fight.
Things are a bit different this time.
How so?
We're not fighting.
But I need to take something from him.
Really?
Then I guess you'll win this time.
I've never seen you fail to get what you want.
And the same goes with this.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you lose but refuse to admit to it,
that would make you a bad mentor.
But if he loses and doesn't back off,
that would mean you didn't teach him well.
So whatever happens, it's all on me.
If you're going to be the bad guy no matter the result,
you should at least win.
You did this, didn't you?
What exactly is my relationship with her?
You're not going to tell me?
If you don't want to tell me, then don't.
I'll figure it out myself.
I didn't think you'd tell me anyway.
Instead, don't resent me even if something happens.
You kept going on about ghosts,
and now you're even watching ghost dramas?
What? What did you say?
You're awfully energetic for someone who's fasting.
Why are you starting the day watching such a scary drama?
Aunt, I'm not watching this for fun.
I'm studying right now.
I need to study ghosts in order to... Wait a minute.
What? Why does this situation feel so familiar?
- My goodness. - Is it a deja vu?
What? What are you doing here?
Hey, watch it. Why are you talking that way to your doctor?
"Doctor"? Who? Him?
I'm sorry. She's still half-asleep.
It's okay.
She's not very healthy right now.
So that could cause her to become hysterical and rude.
What? "Rude"?
Let me check your condition.
Hey, wait. Wait.
Everything seems fine.
Oh, gosh. Wait a minute.
And that's fine too.
Goodness, thank you, sir.
Aunt, am I the only one who finds this weird? Really?
Am I being strange right now?
Yes, you're acting strange.
We just need to take a few basic tests.
Bye then.
Unbelievable.
What's with you?
But he...
You again?
Stop chatting and sit.
I can't believe this. Why do you keep following me around?
- Hey. - Stay still. Don't move.
Do you even know how to work this thing?
Stop talking.
Seriously, why are you doing this...
Hold your breath.
Good girl.
How many jobs do you have?
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm here to save your life.
What are you talking about?
My gosh.
If you go in there with this, you'll die.
Do you know how expensive it is to fix this thing?
I saved your life.
So you're worried about the machine, not me?
- Lie down. - Hey.
Stop talking.
Why does he keep telling me to stop talking?
Hey. The more I think about it,
I really don't know why I need to take this from you...
Oh my gosh.
Hey. Stop right there. I'm talking to you.
- Hey! - Tak Dong Kyung?
- Yes? - Let's go take your blood sample.
Okay.
Darn it.
Ms. Tak!
(Get well soon.)
You need to bring fruit to someone in a hospital,
so I picked out this and that.
Can you even eat?
- My fasting just ended. - What good timing.
Is the hospital starving you?
You need to eat well when you're sick.
Eat. Eat everything.
Say the word. I'll get it for you.
I'm on standby 24 hours a day.
I'll send you the pictures of hot guys that I collected.
You must be bored here.
I ask because I don't know.
Does it make you less bored if you look at hot guys?
Yes, it makes life enjoyable.
They've gotten close.
I know, right?
I'm so proud. So proud.
- We're not close. - We're not close.
Didn't you bring anything?
You're the building owner's son.
What? Come on.
I'm sure he prepared at least a line.
How have you been?
Not that.
Well... Tell me if you need cash.
- Awesome. - Awesome.
He's so cool.
How is that cool?
Anyways, do you want to try this?
Let's have some fruit.
- Don't open it yet. - Eat with me.
You eat it all. They're expensive.
They are?
I need to go. Something urgent came up.
- What? So suddenly? - Sorry. I'll call you.
I'm going drinking with Hyun Kyu.
Go ahead.
Shouldn't you stop me? You say you like me.
What if I do something bad?
Like what?
Do it.
It won't change my feelings.
I wouldn't have told you how I felt if it were that flippant.
Do you really like me?
- Since when? - Since the beginning.
When was that?
Since the beginning.
You're insane.
How could someone like you make such a stupid decision?
I know.
But losing what I want is what's truly stupid.
Losing what you want is stupid, Ms. Na.
Don't call me stupid.
I thought about it for a long time.
Why did I kiss someone I don't know?
Why did it bother me so much...
to see someone I don't know cry?
The answer was there from the beginning.
I told myself it was wrong, that's all.
Does Hyun Kyu know too?
What?
That we kissed?
Or...
that I like you?
He knows everything. He knew everything.
That's why I can't back down.
What do you think?
Can I win?
I don't know.
Why don't you know anything?
- Like you know? - I do.
Spill it.
I don't know. I'm going crazy.
How did I become the bad girl?
You're no bad girl.
You're finally being rewarded.
- I'm being rewarded? - No, it's an award.
Mr. Cha is an award.
Whatever.
You always complained about him.
I always thought...
that jerk was a real pain,
but he isn't a bad person.
He doesn't give his heart that easily.
That's why he still hasn't opened his heart to me.
That annoying jerk.
It's the end of Ji Na's tearjerker love stories.
Finally, you met a good guy.
That's right. You don't know, do you?
What?
He's...
- mad loaded. - Really?
No, no. It doesn't matter.
Why doesn't it matter?
To be honest, he's pretty good-looking.
And this is a secret.
I never said it in case he'd think I like him.
To be honest,
he's really funny at times.
He really is funny.
I bet he'll make you laugh every day if you go out with him.
I don't know. Should I see a fortune-teller?
A fortune-teller? Should we go together?
- You too? Why? - Some freak...
No, a doctor...
No, no. I don't know how to describe this.
What is it? Is a doctor hitting on you?
Yes. He keeps saying let's end the world together.
Oh my gosh. He says...
he'll love only you even if the world ends?
When did I say that?
- That's not it... - Awesome.
A hot doctor falls for a patient at first sight...
and begs for her love.
What an amazing hospital romance.
It is not!
Hey.
Forget it. Just forget it.
- Sir. - Yes?
Why did you open a cafe?
You were a swimmer.
You even studied abroad.
Why do you ask?
I sincerely like working at a cafe.
You look like you were born to own a cafe.
But I'm not sure about myself.
Well...
After I got injured while studying abroad,
I was completely lost.
I suddenly missed Korea like crazy.
So I stopped by a cafe...
and that was when I realized...
that coffee was the same there or in Korea.
Is that how you fell in love with coffee?
No, that's a lie.
It looks cool to own a cafe.
Don't wait for destiny.
It won't hit you on the head saying it's fate.
I never knew I'd run a cafe either.
If you like it, do it.
Don't make plans and make a big deal out of it.
Just do it.
You'll become good at it eventually.
Then you'll think you were meant for it.
You're good. You're doing well.
Don't you think it was a waste?
What can I do though?
I wasn't good enough to make the national team.
Not that. Your first love.
If you knew you were meant to run a cafe,
you wouldn't have left to study abroad.
Then you may have stayed together.
And you wouldn't be hurt like this.
She's the one...
who was hurt, not I.
I just...
I just kept running away.
It's okay.
Just don't run away anymore.
What? Do I look like a fool to you?
A bit.
You punk.
My gosh. Who put away the beans like that?
It was me. Gosh. I'm so stupid. I'm such a fool!
(Ji Na)
Hello?
Drink with me tonight.
Sure. Let's do that.
Mr. Lee, what do I do with the expired beans...
Let me go and get changed.
You were working at this cafe?
Yes. This is the cafe. But why are you...
Athlete, swimmer, and running away...
I sort of figured it out.
But let me ask just one question to confirm it.
What?
Is my boss number 1 or 2?
You told me you wanted to kill two guys. Which one is he?
- Number one. - Gosh. Mr. Lee.
Lock up for me. Thanks.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- I... - Shut it.
Bye.
Slow down.
You might do something you'll regret.
Sure. Do whatever you want. I'll forget about it.
I guess that's easy for you.
You said you came back to Korea and attended the reunion to see me.
Yes.
Same here.
I went to the reunion to see you every year.
- Let's drink. Drink up. - Okay.
"What if he doesn't come?"
"But what if he really came?" That's all I thought about.
I was disappointed every time,
anticipating seeing you as I sat there.
That's not all.
I couldn't go to your house.
So I roamed around your neighborhood.
I sat at a cafe near your house too.
(Danger, No Entry)
I used to get off at a subway station...
near your house and sit on the bench.
Whenever the doors opened, just in case you got off,
I was nervous and tense.
In case I ran into you by chance,
I kept roaming around your streets.
- I didn't know. - I don't resent you.
Don't look so guilty.
I just wanted to tell you...
that I had been loving you for a very long time by myself.
In my head,
I had always loved you by myself.
But...
seeing you again lately made me wonder...
if the person I loved...
was truly you.
What do you mean?
I don't know anything about you.
I realized it when I started to see you again.
I had been in love with...
the 18-year-old you.
I had been waiting for you on the same spot...
when you had walked away.
It's the same with me.
I don't know anything about you either.
- Yes. That's why... - But I don't care.
I won't run away now.
- Our relationship ended long ago. - It ended?
I had been a swimmer for over 10 years.
Going back to the starting line isn't that hard for me.
I can go back over and over again.
Cha Joo Ik and I kissed.
I know. I don't care.
I care.
I think...
it matters to me.
Na Ji Na.
You're horrible.
You're crying again.
Why...
are you here?
I don't know.
How long have you been waiting here?
What if I didn't show up?
I don't know that either.
Seriously.
You're ridiculous.
I get that a lot.
You never disappoint me with your unexpected behaviors.
You confuse me.
I confuse you?
I don't think so.
Don't be confused.
I came here because I wanted to see you and I like you.
What was that?
I didn't want to drink because if I did,
I might do something that I would regret.
Ms. Na.
Limit your regrets only to me.
Your regrettable action...
could destroy me.
You crazy wench, Na Ji Na!
Gosh. Come on.
- What? My hair? - Yes.
You'll be going through chemo and radiation therapy.
Your hair will fall out quickly.
You've seen it on TV, right?
You might cope better...
if you take care of your hair beforehand.
And that's what I recommend too.
Seeing your hair falling out...
could be harder to watch.
Ever since you were young, you had a nice shaped head.
So whenever I gave you a short haircut,
all the elders in the neighborhood...
would say you look like a cute chestnut...
and give you tons of compliments.
You remember that, right?
Yes, I remember.
Your hair...
will grow.
It'll grow back really fast.
They also sell shampoos that help your hair grow faster.
Right.
Should I also get a haircut?
We can make Sun Kyung shave his head too.
Don't you remember he did that when he went to the army?
He was really ugly.
He looks decent thanks to his hair, so he can't shave his head.
Shaving my head is already enough. Let's not do it to anyone else.
Okay, Auntie?
Gosh, you charming girl. You're such a good girl.
I should go and buy you some hats.
I'll get you pretty ones.
Don't bother. I have a lot of hats.
You even bought me one last time.
Gosh, that's too big.
You have a tiny head.
Let me take a look.
It's about this big.
I'll be right back.
(Absolute rest)
How should I style your hair?
Well...
I want to look like a celebrity.
- Pardon? - Something that celebrities do.
I want a perm that looks really extravagant.
Just like that.
Miss.
That was done with a curling iron.
I want that hairstyle.
There. You're all done.
To be honest, I was a little worried because you came in a patient gown.
We get a few patients from the hospital nearby,
and they come to shave their heads.
This hair looks great on you.
Can we take a photo and upload it on our website?
Your face won't show. It'll just be your hair.
- Just your hair. - Okay.
The curls came out great.
- Are you done? - Wait. Just one more.
I'll take it from here.
It looks so pretty.
You're all done now.
Okay then.
You can shave my head now.
What?
Just shave everything off my head.
I'm sorry. I know you put in a lot of effort to do this for me.
But I wanted to try it one last time.
It won't be your last time. You should come again.
I'll do this for you again.
I'll make sure it comes out even better than today.
Actually, I bet you'll look good with short hair too.
Now that I think of it, it wasn't the hair that came out nice.
You're just pretty to begin with.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
I'll cut it now.
Okay.
- Your nose is bleeding. - My goodness.
- Are you okay? - Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
- Get her a tissue. - I'm fine.
Just a second. Get her a tissue.
Don't cry.
Please don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What's going on?
Where am I?
My house.
Why am I in your house?
Was I kidnapped?
Something like that.
Since I dragged you into this dream without your consent.
Dream?
This is a dream?
What... Wow.
It feels so real.
That's right.
What?
(Les Miserables)
You're giving me a headache.
Is this jail?
Did you lock me up?
Is that all you can say to the person who saved your life?
What?
You saved me?
Wasn't that a dream?
No, it wasn't.
Then that dream... No.
That was a dream. It was definitely a dream.
It was a dream. So why...
That dream?
You were crying in my dream earlier.
It was a dream.
I don't eat, sleep, or cry.
I died and you came to my funeral.
You looked at my picture and cried...
I'm not sad.
I'm not sad no matter how much I look at you.
Hey. You startled me.
- Smile. - What?
Smile at me.
Why should I?
I need to know who and what you are.
Will you know if I smile?
Smile again.
I have no idea.
Where are you going?
Outside.
We need to go somewhere open. It's too dangerous here.
Gosh. Why? Do you think I'll do something to you?
No. I'm afraid I'll do something to you.
Like what?
Who knows? Since I don't know who you are.
Run away if I do.
Run as hard as you can.
Are you sure it's safer outside?
There's nothing dangerous...
since nothing there is alive.
- What is this place? - My subconscious.
Subconscious?
It's like your ocean.
- That was why. - What?
You say this is like my ocean.
So this was how you felt.
That was why you were so prickly.
Don't talk gibberish. Just remember.
Do you really not know me?
No, I don't.
Think before you speak.
Why do I need to think about something like that?
I just know.
I don't need to think to know that you're pretty.
Hey.
Have you been here before?
Obviously, not.
You should think before you talk.
Why? Do you remember seeing me here?
You really must have seen me before.
I have not.
- Then why... - I don't know.
Seriously. You need to learn how to speak again.
You need to make sense. Talk in longer sentences.
What's the use in reading books all the time?
Hey. Be honest with me.
You don't read, do you? You just hold them, don't you?
There's a line that the author wrote.
"Dying is nothing."
"What is frightening is not living to the fullest."
Are you saying that to me?
No. To myself.
Because I'm nothing.
Because I'm not alive.
There's another famous quote by that author.
"The reduction of the universe to one person,"
"and the expansion of one person to a deity."
"That is love."
Remember beautiful things from now on.
Then this place may become...
a little nicer.
Why...
What is this...
Will you choose to do that?
There's not much time.
You need to make a choice.
I'll do it.
(Ask the world to end before dying.)
(Doom, person I love the most)
Oh, no.
I must be going crazy.
I must be really sick.
(Ms. Soo Ja)
- Auntie. - Where are you?
I left something at my house.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
(Human)
Hello?
You...
How could you...
How could you forget about me?
Right back at you.
Even if I made that decision,
you should have recognized me right away.
You should have remembered me.
That's my fault?
Who told you to make that decision?
You did whatever you wanted without talking to me.
You know what? Even when you lost your memory,
your nasty temper didn't go away.
Did you find me handsome even when you lost your memory?
(Doom at Your Service)
We can't escape...
our fate, right?
So we should accept it now.
Will it hurt a lot when I die?
You knew that I would be making this decision, right?
I don't know what I will decide.
We should go.
Bye.
I didn't give up yet.
- Help us. - Accept it.
I love you.
Thank you for loving me.