Our Secret
EP13
Ding Xian
Why don't you
study in Jiangling too?
What have you dreamed about?
You blushed.
It's a sweet dream, huh?
No.
No?
Tell me, what's it about?
Nothing.
Nothing?
What?
Ding Xian
What's up?
Don't talk to me in class.
Your glasses fell off.
Tell me,
what was your dream?
You were so happy.
I didn't.
Did you dream about things
you wish you could have in real life?
Stop it.
You look guilty.
No.
You do.
I don't.
Why don't you get it?
Cherish your high school years!
After graduation,
you two will be far apart from each other.
Draw a guiding line,
then the angle ACD will be...
What's wrong? You've been weird all day.
Nothing.
I'm listening.
Is there anything on my face?
No.
You haven't even looked at me these days.
How did you know there's nothing?
Are you gonna go on or not?
If not, I'll go to bed.
Forget the thing you keep from me,
but my tutoring time is priceless.
After I go to the contest in a few days,
you won't be able to find me even you want.
But you don't cherish this now.
Siyue
The power is off!
I see!
Wait a second,
I'll have a look.
Why is the power suddenly off?
What's up?
Are you afraid of the dark?
No, I'm not.
Here,
now you're not scared, are you?
I like this song, too.
Zhou Siyue
I also want to study in Jiangling.
You're not allowed to go out today.
I'm gonna break your legs!
I'll leave even if you do!
Go ahead!
Leave? Try it!
What should we do?
How did you do your job?
What can I do?
Before I talked to him well,
he was taken away by his dad.
Look how you spoiled him!
Then beat me!
Stop talking!
What' wrong?
You're finally here, look.
Siyue
Jiang, Siyue is here.
You two really are...
What are you doing?
Uncle, auntie!
Siyue
You've come just at the right moment.
You two are best friends.
Help him figure out gains and losses.
Go to the college first,
then think about other things.
You may consider Siyue to be your son!
He's such a good student!
What did you say?
One more word?
Stop it!
-Well.  -Uncle
Let me talk to you.
He's unreasonable!
Yeah.
Siyue, please talk to him.
OK.
Auntie
I'll have a good talk with Jiang Chen.
Right, go ahead.
Don't be so stubborn.
Come here.
Buddy
I owe you once.
So it's okay?
Let's go.
Still awake?
You scared me.
I'm so hungry.
With no slippers,
you might catch a cold again.
Put them on.
That's mine.
You look like a little old man now.
Old man?
You seem to be very experienced.
No wonder you could convince Jiang Chen's dad.
How did you make it?
It's actually
not a big deal.
I said that
the reason why Jiang Chen wants to be a soldier
is that he wants to be a man
as excellent as his dad.
Awesome!
You're good at talking.
It must be tough to prepare for National Olympiads.
Go for it!
I almost forgot.
I heard that your score of math
was only 90-something this time.
It's a tough situation, girl.
It's past two o'clock.
Can't you give me a break?
I see you're not sleepy yet.
Come on, tutoring begins.
I'm sleepy, very much!
Let me go, Mr. Zhou.
Let's go get some drink later.
I know a great milky tea shop,
and it's very cheap.
Okay, okay!
Jiang Chen?
Well, Keke, we'll go first.
Why are you here?
Waiting for you...
Me?
You wear so little.
Tie it on the waist.
No, it's naff.
I have to go to the art class later.
Just tie it on.
What are you doing?
It's cold.
Stickybeak.
Hop on, I'll take you there.
Come on.
Forget it.
Getting a ride
is not bad.
Hold on tight.
You've decided which college to go to, haven't you?
Of course,
the acting department of the Film Academy.
If I fail this year,
I'll try again next year,
until I make it.
I think we are similar
since we won't stop until we achieve the goal.
Who is similar to you?
I have a bright future.
I have one too, OK?
I'm going to be a soldier.
I'm so bright.
Idiot, you are really going to be a soldier?
If we are strong, our country will be strong.
If we are intelligent, our county will be intelligent.
What?
I said,
If we are strong, the country will be strong.
If we are intelligent, the country will be intelligent.
The minimum passing score is so high.
You're going to the same university?
I wish I could.
But Huaqing University won't give me a chance.
I would be happy if we'll be in the same city.
You still have the chance
to go to the same city.
But me, not gonna happen.
You mean
we just break up, right?
This is great news for me.
Bye, I'm gonna be beautiful alone!
By the way,
this weekend,
let's go and see Jiang Chen off.
He's gonna leave.
So soon?
Thanks for watching a movie with me.
Never mind.
Suddenly I thought that
I won't see you again soon.
I feel as if something is missing.
You can call me
or write to me.
You're good at writing, aren't you?
Who said that?
I didn't write that.
Others helped me.
Besides,
why do I write to you?
What a friend!
We are friends?
Well, it's only my own wishful thinking.
It's yours from now on.
What's this?
A parting gift.
I have nothing
but this motorbike.
So sudden.
Take it.
I'll keep it for you.
Wait for your return.
And,
do your best in your test tomorrow.
You will definitely get into your dreamed university.
Of course, I will.
It's not fun for me to play with you.
You do it.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I think she and I are well-matched.
No offense.
Just give you a break.
OK.
Come on.
Teach him a lesson.
You're so...
lucky.
It's just a coincidence.
Why did he do this?
He thought that Little Monster is a soft touch,
but
he got a hard one.
Aren't you leaving tonight?
You still have time to play billiards here?
I just want to have some fun
before I go.
Who knew I may lose so many times.
You guys, come and eat first,
or it'll be cold later.
OK, one more round.
Coming.
Come on, Song.
Come on.
Little Monster
You are so good at playing billiards.
The master taught me.
Well...
keep in touch with me later.
It's better to tell me something about Keke.
It turns out that you have other things in mind,
buddy.
If she goes out with other guys,
you must tell me.
How can that be?
That makes me betray my friend.
Let's cooperate.
I can betray my friend, too.
Just kidding, not gonna happen.
They're my buddies.
That's Keke.
Jiang Chen, why are you not in a hurry?
Aren't you afraid that your dad scolds you?
Wait,
why are you riding Jiang Chen's motorbike?
Don't you have a test?
I got there early and finished it early.
Did... did you do well?
Why do you talk so much?
I'm willing to give you a ride.
Hop on quickly.
Yeah, how can you let a pretty girl wait for you?
Hurry up.
OK, I...
Wait,
you forget your bag.
Well,
I'll go.
I'll drive.
Bye.
Hurry up.
Take care.
Go, go.
Stop looking. Let's go.
We'll meet again someday.
Let's go.
Handsome, huh?
Siyue
The national contest is coming.
Try your best.
I believe that
you definitely can get a place of Huaqing University.
Huaqing University...
OK.
I also think that he will make it.
Siyue can do it.
He has such good grades.
All right.
Stop talking.
The time you pay attention to others
can be used in your study,
okay?
Do you know anything efficacious
that can get one lucky?
For Zhou Siyue?
Keep your voice down. Don't let him hear us.
I haven't seen you care so much
when you have a test.
That's different.
It is of great importance to him.
There are lucky pens being sold near our school.
Why don't you buy him one?
Nothing new.
Lucky bookmark?
Not good enough...
Anything else?
Well...
if you're heartfelt,
make him one by yourself.
Ding Xian
Wait... wait a second.
OK.
What are you doing?
Reading.
Didn't I teach you this one before?
Why is it wrong again?
Is it?
Let me teach you one more time.
That's OK. I'll figure it by myself.
Go to bed, and you have a test tomorrow.
Don't worry about me.
Well, I...
Good night.
You...
-Good luck on the test!  -I tell you...
Oh, God.
Zhou Siyue
Why are you here?
I was supposed to see you off,
but I got up late.
It's just a test.
I'll be back after it.
How could you say that?
It's about your university.
Are you...
nervous?
A bit.
Give me your hand.
Good luck.
This is my first time doing this.
I hope you don't mind it's ugly.
So you didn't do your homework,
and this is what you were doing.
You almost caught me.
Stupid...
Come here.
My hair isn't clean.
That's fine. Absorb some anima.
The final exam is coming.
Go back and do your homework.
When the next semester begins,
I have a present for you.
Ding Xian also came here to cheer for Siyue.
Mr. Liu
It's time to get in.
Siyue
Don't be nervous about the test.
Just do what you usually do.
You'll be fine.
Don't worry.
I'm ready.
Go.
Mr. Liu
If I get admitted to Huaqing,
could you do me a favor?
Even ten is okay.
Zhou Siyue
You must pass the exam.
The road ahead is so long.
You're going to have a bright future.
Come on.
What are you doing?
The winter holiday makes you distract, right?
Mr. Zhou, I'm so tired.
You don't wanna study in Jiangling?
Yeah.
I'd better go to Hangzhou.
Okay,
it's none of my business anyway.
How nice Hangzhou is,
so is the scenery.
And there isn't some guy
tutoring me every day.
What's wrong?
I was kidding.
What are you doing?
Are you making fool of me?
I'm not.
Are you...
Why do you poke me? You always do this.
And you always hit me.
Just tell me if you don't want to do your homework.
I didn't.
This is interesting, huh?
I really didn't.
Stop...
Hello, mom.
OK, I get it.
What's wrong?
Something happened to my family and I have to go back.
Uncle Ding
I'm sorry to hear that.
Thanks.
Xianxian
Su
I thought
you won't be back at the Spring Festival.
I will definitely come back to take a look
after something like this.
How are you?
When I was a kid,
I didn't know what parting is.
When I grew up,
I realized this is such a sad thing.
Yeah.
Growing up itself is a sad thing.
Even the best friends
will gradually become strangers.
There's nothing we can do.
Because everyone
will have a new life of their own.
Then I don't want to grow up.
I still remember in those years
the Keshan Brat
cried three times a day.
When I see you every day,
you cried like a little dirty cat.
Yeah.
In middle school,
those boys were always picking on me.
Do you still remember?
You gave me a bag of toffee,
and they asked me for it.
I didn't want them to find out,
so I hid it under a tree.
Then it rained.
When I went back for it,
there were only the wrappers.
Tell me,
if it's the more you cherish something,
the more you can't keep it?
Xianxian
Here's something for you.
It was for kids during the Spring Festival.
Here.
For me,
you'll always be the same Xianxian.
But I'm not a kid anymore.
Zhou Zongtang
Do you know it's the Spring Festival today?
You still gonna go out?
Yun, I really have something to do.
It's still a school thing.
You haven't been in class for so long.
What things do you have?
Besides,
can it be more important
than the Spring Festival?
Can you trust me?
If you don't even believe me...
I can't explain it clearly
in several words.
Zhou Zongtang
If you leave this house today,
we won't celebrate the Spring Festival!
Aren't you going out?
Take good care of you two.
Xianxian, why are you here?
Go back. It's cold outside.
Dinner is ready.
You eat first.
Daddy wanna stay outside for a while.
It's cold and cheerless this year.
Yeah.
During the Spring Festival before,
your grandma was doing all the shopping
and cooking.
And then she'll gather
the whole family together.
Dad
We can't change it,
but to accept it.
Let's go in.
Are you there?
Hello.
How are
your family members?
They're fine.
Happy new year, happy new year.
Happy new year to you all.
We're singing and dancing.
Do you feel better?
What do you mean?
You know I'm in a bad mood?
Probably because we've been deskmates for a long time,
even if I didn't see you,
I can imagine your expression.
How are you in your hometown?
It's happy.
There's a big dinner at home,
and I was stuffed.
How about you?
I...
I'm watching fireworks at home.
We also had fireworks today.
Do you feel it?
How time flies.
After the festival,
we're gonna grow up.
Yeah.
But that's okay.
We can watch the fireworks together
next year.
Great.
We watch fireworks together next year.
Happy New Year,
Zhou Siyue
Ding Xian
Before the class is over,
I have a piece of news.
Let's congratulate Zhou Siyue
on passing the National Olympiads,
and he's gonna be a student of
Huaqing University!
Awesome!
Besides, those who didn't get recommended,
don't give up.
Where there is struggle, there is hope.
Keep working hard in the new term,
and make progress.
OK, class is over.
Siyue, you become a college student.
Siyue, please tutor us
if you're free.
Siyue, me too.
-OK.  -St... st...
stop it.
Everyone makes an appointment. Siyue is very busy now.
If you have the intention,
come to me to make an appointment first. Thank you.
Just ignore him.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You're really everywhere.
Ding Xian
Pack up and move back.
Move back.
You're too blatant.
I've got aunt's permission.
I don't believe it.
Move quickly.
You'd better stop gossiping. With the time,
you can figure out two more questions.
Quickly.
This is the gift you said?
Why do you want me to move back?
To make tutoring convenient.
No more reasons.
For tutoring...
Are you stupid?
You even believed it.
Why do you always call me stupid?
My whole high school
started from being deskmate with you.
At the end, of course,
I have to be your deskmate.
Otherwise,
it'll be a pity.
Thinking that you have entered Huaqing,
but I was still wandering outside Jiangling.
Deskmate
You're so good at studying.
Do you have
any shortcuts to improve grades?
You wanna play petty tricks?
But I
do have a way.
I made this
college entrance examination countdown schedule for you.
So you had a plan long ago.
Because you make me worry so much.
Make you worry.
Come on!
I won't let you down!