(Previously On Lovely Writer)
Did you come to see me
because you are worried?
Do you think
we should tell our parents?
Don't worry.
I'll be by your side no matter what.
What if the two of us are really together?
You shouldn't be angry about me on this.
If I recall correctly,
you dated boys before you met Mom.
Shut up!
I want you to go upstairs!
Orn.
Okay, the first action is to punch
and back.
And punch like this.
Is everyone ready?
Okay, let's begin.
Three, two, one.
Punch and back.
Punch.
Okay. March on the spot.
Keep your rhythm.
Next action, squats.
Is everyone ready?
Three, two, one, go.
Squat and stretch.
Squat and stretch. Good.
Two.
One.
Okay. March on the spot.
Keep your rhythm.
Next action, back kick.
Use our heels to touch our hips.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick.
Move your arms.
Tuck in.
Two, one.
Hello, Jap. How is everything?
What about your family? Is everything all right?
There are some minor problems.
I don't think it's a minor problem anymore.
Jap.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Well...
What is it?
I was the one who asked
Nubsib and Gene to tell our parents.
But I didn't expect it to turn out like this.
I understand.
It's just that...
I don't want them to hide their relationship.
You don't have to blame yourself.
No one knows how things will turn out.
But, you need to give my parents some time.
My mother likes Gene a lot.
She loves him like her own son.
If it's me, I would be very shocked too.
Seeing both of my sons falling in love
with each other.
It's ridiculous.
What should we do next?
I don't know.
All right. I'll hang up now.
Call me if there's anything.
Okay.
You need to smile more.
Understand?
You are his elder brother.
Gene is troubled right now.
You need to support him.
I'll also take care of Nubsib here.
Okay. I'll leave it to you.
I'll call you again if there's anything.
Okay. Let's keep in touch.
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love, just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
♪I wanna kiss, kiss you♪
♪I wanna love, love you♪
♪I'm gonna kiss you♪
♪1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, and kiss♪
Mom.
Gene, where are you going?
No. I didn't sleep well last night.
What's up?
Go out with me later then.
Take a seat, son.
Mom.
I want to have a talk with Dad.
Dad doesn't want me to be with Nubsib, right?
I don't know.
If he doesn't want me to be with Nubsib,
I want to hear his reasons.
Gene.
Your father has his own reasons.
If you want him to understand you,
you have to understand him too.
I'm not saying that he is unreasonable.
I just want to have a chat with him.
Gene.
Give your father some time.
Have some tea first.
When you said you wanted to be together with Nubsib,
I was shocked.
But how I think of it isn't important.
Try to make this tea.
I'd better not.
The taste is so bad compared to yours.
Gene.
You should understand.
I can't make tea for you forever.
There will be a day
when you have to make it yourself.
If it's bad,
you have to find a way to make it better.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Our family might not speak about love often,
but I want you to know that
we did what we did because we love you.
What's left now is more understanding.
Everything will get better.
I love your father.
I love you too.
I love you.
Why do you look so carefree?
Do you still remember this bonsai plant?
Yes.
Isn't this the Yu Garden Bonsai Plant
I won for you in an auction?
Yes.
Didn't you want to get it badly?
I wouldn't admit defeat.
It's funny now that I think about it.
We met at that time
and no one was willing to give in.
In the end, my flower pot
ended up with your bonsai plant.
Who would've imagined that?
If I knew about the ending,
I wouldn't be fighting with you for it.
If I knew it would still end up with me.
Why are you bringing this up suddenly?
We've been pruning this
bonsai plant for a long time, right?
Do you think
we should let it grow freely now?
Where are you?
Sorry.
My family is still...
It's all right.
I understand.
It's the same with my family as well.
I see. What about you? Is everything all right?
Dad still wouldn't talk to me.
If he doesn't agree with our relationship,
what will you do?
Will you break up with me?
Of course not.
You'll still be my boyfriend no matter what.
Nubsib, come here for a while.
I have to go downstairs.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Sit down.
Nubsib.
Tell me everything honestly.
How did it happen between you and Gene?
Didn't you ask me before?
Why didn't I have a girlfriend?
Don't tell me it's because of Gene.
Yes.
I tried dating someone else
but it's no use.
Why would you be together with Gene?
Actually, Gene didn't remember me.
But I'm the male lead of his adapted series.
Everyone knows about that.
My manager, Tum, is Gene's friend in university.
He asked Gene to take care of me.
To be frank,
I don't agree with this.
Our family is running a business.
Image and reputation are very important to us.
You should know that.
We need to do business with others.
I know.
But you are my son.
I'm also treating Gene as my son.
If it's already like this,
both your mother and I will not say anything else.
Even if we are going to, I'm sure you won't listen to us.
There will only be more arguments
if we don't allow it.
I don't like it too when other people force me.
I've talked to your mother.
From now on, you have to
be responsible for what you do.
I can't stop anything
concerning the love between Gene and you.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Mom.
Look how happily you're smiling now.
What will you do if we don't agree?
That piece of land in Pattanakarn.
Who told you I wanted that piece of land?
Didn't you fail to get it?
Deal.
Get me that deal.
If they are willing to sell it,
I will no longer interfere with anything of yours.
Are you going back on your words?
So what?
Are you going to refuse my proposal?
If Uncle Teep doesn't agree,
you have to talk to him personally.
It's a deal.
Transfer the money to me.
I'll get you the deed.
Okay. Deal.
I wonder from whom NubSib
inherited his personality.
Nubsib, this is your choice.
I love Gene like my other son.
Sorry.
I was just shocked at what happened.
It's fine, Mom.
I need to apologize to you too.
Take good care of Gene.
Have a good relationship.
Yes. I guarantee.
I'll definitely take good care of Gene.
Teep.
Where's our son?
He went to sleep.
Has he eaten anything?
He said he was not hungry.
Teep.
Are you all right?
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that our son will experience
what I've experienced before.
I've been afraid of this.
What is there to be afraid of?
I want our son to have a better life.
A life that's better than mine.
I don't want others to point fingers at our son.
I don't want others to look down on him.
And I don't want them to hate him.
Teep.
Times have changed.
I know you are worried about him,
but if you keep this up,
he will keep feeling that you hate him.
If other people don't understand him,
you should know
who he wants most to understand him.
Teep.
Do you still remember the feeling at that time?
That was the time you wanted most.
Right?
Run.
I'm so afraid.
I love you.
Hello.
That was fast.
Did you miss me?
No.
My phone is just beside me.
What are you doing?
Are you feeling shy?
Shy my foot.
Have you eaten?
No.
I'm not hungry.
How are you doing at the set?
It's still the same.
It'll be a wrap soon.
The shooting has ended early today.
I'm back at home now.
Hold on. Someone is knocking.
Come in.
Dad.
What's wrong?
You're showing me that face when you see me?
Why aren't you eating?
I'm not hungry yet.
Is that the truth?
Or you just don't want to see me?
Gene.
Do you really love Nubsib?
Why are you asking this?
Just answer me.
Yes.
You should know.
Love is not just about two people.
There are many things involved.
Whether it's your job
or Nubsib's job.
If people see you two in a relationship,
they will blame you both.
Even though you say that times have changed,
do you really believe that's the case?
That is why I ask you if you really love Nubsib.
Nubsib is a smart kid.
He can solve any problem.
But you?
Are you prepared to face this?
I really want to be together with Nubsib.
I do envy you.
You are loyal to your feelings.
Be persistent in a relationship like this
and be with him forever.
Because I've never forgotten
about a relationship like this.
What about Mom?
It doesn't mean that I don't love your mother.
Right?
Gene.
You need to stay strong
and overcome any troubles.
Love with all your heart.
Even if you're destined to lose him,
it's fine.
You should know.
I love everyone in this family.
I will always be with you.
Dad, sorry.
Sorry for being rude to you.
I'm not angry at you.
I'm happy for you.
You didn't choose to run away.
Do you remember?
You were stubborn when you were young.
Yes.
You are still together with Nubsib, right?
That's Nubsib, right?
Hello.
Gene.
Yes.
I'm in front of your house.
Can you come down and meet me?
What? What did you say?
Hello, Uncle Teep.
You came as soon as I agreed.
Kids act so quick nowadays.
Yes.
Your father messaged me yesterday.
He has cleared all the obstacles.
I'll leave Gene in your care.
Yes. I'll take good care of Gene.
I hope you keep your promise.
Why are you here?
Sorry.
I was so happy when I heard that
and ran here unconsciously.
You heard everything?
I want to hug you.
Wait, this is my house.
I want to kiss you.
No.
Why?
Can't I kiss you?
Let's go in first.
(Run: Orn, our sons have made up with each other)
(Orn: Let's go to the aerobics class tomorrow)
Sorry, Dad.
You don't have to apologize.
I understand.
You should be better.
Yes.
I'll also work hard to be better.
Do you want to go back today?
I feel like staying for two more days.
You can go back first.
It's troublesome to go back and forth.
I'll wait for you to go back together.
Up to you.
How is it with the land?
I've made another application.
I think it will pass this time.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Don't you believe in my capabilities?
I do.
Nubsib.
If my father doesn't agree with our relationship,
what will you do?
Uncle Teep is a reasonable person.
I'm sure he will understand.
What if it's not so simple?
Where will you get that deed in exchange?
Or will you get your father to talk to my Dad?
No.
Uncle Teep is not like my father.
He is not a businessman.
Uncle Teep will
not exchange his son for anything else.
That's because you are
far more valuable than anything else.
Besides, I think the same as Uncle Teep.
Tiffy.
What do you want again?
I really like you.
Enough, Tum.
I don't think it's funny.
Tiffy.
I'm not joking.
I'm serious.
What are you trying to do again?
Tiffy.
I really like you.
Enough, Tum.
I don't think it's funny at all.
I'm not joking.
I'm serious.
What do you mean?
Tiffy.
Listen to me.
Enough, Tum.
Stop fooling around with my feelings.
Can you?
Enough.
I told you.
I'm serious.
But you are gay!
I'm not.
I never am.
Why do you think I'm gay?
How many times do you need me to say it?
I'm not gay.
How many times do I have to tell you I like you
for you to believe me?
Enough.
I don't want to hate you more than I do now.
You've always been the only person I want.
There were too many things I wanted
to say to you when we were together.
I'm willing to do anything to make you smile.
When you put on makeup or lipstick,
and when you hold my hand or approach me,
I miss every moment.
Even if there's only a slight chance.
What if I'm gay?
Am I wrong to like you?
I only want you to know my feelings.
I like you even though I look gay.
Why don't you understand?
Will you believe me now?
I can believe you.
You rap well.
Me?
I used to go on a program.
What kind of program?
Do you want to watch it? I can take you.
Are you going to behave like that now?
Do you want to?
In a room.
To watch me rap.
Hold it.
Don't you want to?
What?
Gene, what are you doing?
I'm posting a story on Instagram.
The first episode is airing today.
Why don't you dry your hair?
It will dry naturally.
Let's watch the series first.
Watch it later.
Take a picture for me.
Tum wants to help the client promote on Instagram.
Sure.
Can you wait for a while?
Let me finish this episode.
(Is Gene watching?)
(Whose voice is that? Sounds familiar)
(It's Nubsib. So they are together.)
Are you watching the television
or playing with your phone?
Watching the television.
That's your friend, Aey.
I know.
Senior.
What is it?
This male lead is so fierce.
I wonder who played him.
Yes.
I wonder who wrote it.
Why aren't you focusing?
Do you want to watch the re-run?
Why?
It's your own series.
You should watch it.
When my boyfriend is acting one day,
I'll definitely finish the series
without shifting my attention.
You're joking again.
What's wrong?
Are you shy?
You brat.
Sorry.
(Bad Engineer The Series)
Here. It's the commercials.
One, two.
One, two, three.
Here.
Gene.
What?
Help me put on the mask.
Speak nicely.
When wasn't I speaking nicely?
You are so annoying.
Give it here.
Do you want it or not?
♪Do you know? Every time you look at me♪
Apply it well.
Okay.
♪Every time we are close together♪
♪Do you know? You are my dream♪
♪Do you know? Every sentence you've said♪
♪I'll remember all of them♪
♪Do you know? I miss you more than anyone else♪
♪You changed my world♪
Make me look handsome.
I know.
♪You changed my world♪
Why are you laughing?
Say something.
♪You made my heart fall for you♪
Otherwise, the mask won't stick.
Because you are laughing.
♪You made my heart fall for you♪
Your hands are so soft.
My hands didn't even touch your face.
It's the mask.
Don't move.
♪Maybe you are the gift God gave me♪
I'm not moving.
Stop talking!
Otherwise, the mask won't stick.
♪Maybe it's you♪
♪Want to let you know how wonderful this feels♪
All right. You look handsome now.
Are you sure?
♪You love me a lot?♪
♪I love you more♪
Why are you laughing, Gene?
I'm not.
♪I love you more♪
Are you making fun of me?
I'm not.
Do you still want to take pictures?
Are you sure?
Yes.
Here. One, two.
One, two, three.
Another one.
Why doesn't it look handsome as it was just now?
Nubsib, do you want me to hit you?
How can it be handsome
when your face isn't showing?
You look like Casper.
Making fun of me again?
No.
Hey, Nubsib.
Your mask will fall!
My face is all wet!
(Coming Out is Not Honesty)
What are you doing?
I'm writing the setting about announcing
to come out in front of the family.
You're not writing a sex scene?
I want to help you with that.
That's nonsense.
How can you be so cute?
Cute my foot.
I'm working right now.
Nubsib, it's ticklish.
Stop.
Your phone?
Yes.
What is it?
Are you free to speak?
Yes.
It's like this.
Have you seen Twitter?
Yes.
Everyone is saying it's your voice.
Tam is not okay with it.
But I've explained it for you.
I said I was there too.
Okay.
You should be more careful.
You should know how Tam is.
Thank you.
Is there anything else?
If you don't, I'll...
Wait, why are you in a rush?
What is it?
It's about the summer shoot.
It's confirmed for the 6th of this month.
I've already arranged
the flight tickets and hotel.
Thank you.
Can you book an extra room for me?
For Gene?
Yes.
What if someone sees you two
in the same room?
I'm telling you.
Be wary of the staff.
I'll just book a room
that's far away from everyone else.
Sure. That works.
It's safer.
I'll arrange it.
Thank you.
Was that Tum?
Yes.
What is it?
I have a photoshoot at the beach on the 6th.
You should come together.
Me?
What am I going there for?
Aren't you going to work?
I'm not shooting for the whole day.
Let's go together.
Don't you want to play at the beach?
The beach?
All right? Just go.
Let's go together.
To be honest, I'm lazy to go out.
Whatever.
I can go with you.
Nubsib, enough.
Let me finish my work.
Let's go together.
Fine. I'll go.
(Gene: I'm here. I'm waiting for Hin)
(Nubsib: All right)
Hello. It's been so long.
I miss you a lot.
Forget it.
Are you sending the picture to Nubsib?
Mind your own business.
So fierce.
Gene, Nubsib belongs to me.
Just take him away.
You said it.
Don't regret if I steal him away.
You are so annoying.
By the way, how's your draft?
It's almost done.
It's coming to an end.
How many chapters are you
going to write for the spin-off?
What about five to six chapters?
It's just right.
It's about that many, I guess.
But the spin-off needs some sex scenes.
Write a couple in.
What? You want a couple of sex scenes?
Yes. What's wrong?
If you can complete it before the 18th,
you can enter the book fair with your draft.
Okay.
Bua also said
the sex scenes have to be
as hot and juicy as possible.
What's wrong?
Why are you giving me that look?
This is a spin-off.
The sex scenes must be hotter than usual.
All right. I understand.
But I don't know how to write it to good effect
and tie it in with the main storyline.
Try it.
Send it to Bua.
Maybe she can make adjustments for you.
Okay.
Oh, Gene.
Did you receive the draft I sent you?
I'm not confident.
Hin.
To be honest,
I have no time to read it.
Why don't you upload it onto the internet?
What? Upload it?
Yes.
Is that good?
Of course.
I used to do that too.
Don't you remember?
Okay.
I'll try...
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
You are the one who sent the picture.
You know where I am
from the picture of the cake?
This area is close to my university.
I know all of the shops here.
Well, well, well.
You two are sticking together like glue.
Hin, shut up.
Why don't you let Nubsib
help you out with the sex scenes?
Hin!
What?
What scenes?
No.
It's nothing.
Nubsib, finish this cake for me.
Are you going to feed me?
No.
Eat it yourself.
I won't eat it if you don't feed me.
Forget it then.
Pay for me and Hin.
Sure.
Even if you eat a few more, I'll still pay for you.
Miss, give me 20 boxes of cake, please.
I'm sorry, Hin.
You're not Gene.
That's so mean.
I'm just joking.
What did I do wrong?
Nubsib.
Are you done?
We will be late.
I'm done.
Let's go.
We will miss the plane if there's a traffic jam.
Wait.
Did you forget anything?
No.
But you look more excited than me.
Are you mad?
Who's excited?
I'm just afraid of being late.
Wait.
We are going to the beach together.
The sun is bright. Don't forget to apply this.
No.
I don't like to apply stuff like this.
It's sticky.
I might be allergic too.
Trust me.
The things I tell you are good
will definitely be good.
It won't cause an allergic reaction.
All right?
It's done.
You have to use it when I'm not around too.
I don't want the UV rays
to take your cuteness away.
I'm going to vomit.
Let's go. We'll be late.
Hurry up.
Where are you going?
Why aren't you going to work?
I'm going.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the sea.
Didn't I text you?
Can't you wait until it's not so sunny?
I've used sunscreen.
But you are going without me.
So, you won't let me go?
Wait for me.
I'll finish at 5 PM.
All right?
There's that cute expression again.
I've told you not to be so cute.
Seriously.
Come on!
Nubsib. Gene.
Be careful, both of you.
I'm going crazy.
What will you do if I'm not the one passing by?
It's not bad.
Nubsib!
You jerk!
Your actor doesn't allow me to play at the sea.
Are you done?
Yes.
Thank you for paying for my room.
The room is more comfortable now.
You're welcome.
Gene, what did you say?
It's nothing.
Okay. Let's go.
The crew is waiting.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
I'll play with you.
Okay?
Hey, seriously.
Good. Good. Good.
Change another pose.
Very good.
Another pose. Another one.
Okay.
Wait.
Give him a touch-up.
I'll give you a touch-up.
-Nubsib.
-Yes.
What is it?
What are you looking at? Is there anything?
No.
Please look up then.
How is it, Hin?
Have you uploaded your work to the internet?
I haven't seen it yet.
I've decided not to write it.
Why?
I feel stressed.
I haven't finished it yet.
You can just upload it first.
Upload it while writing.
You've uploaded it, haven't you?
Yes.
Did someone criticize your novel?
Not many people read it either.
Most of the readers are criticizing me.
How do you feel now?
I don't want to write it anymore.
Hin.
Think about it.
Do you still want to be a writer?
Yes.
But seeing what's happening now,
I think I might not be suitable to become a writer.
Did anyone praise it after you upload your novel?
Yes.
But it's not a lot.
You see that?
At least there are some people who like it.
-But...
-How about this?
Read your own novel again.
But you need to read it
like how you were reading mine.
Understand?
What do you mean?
When you were reading my novel,
you were from a reader's point of view.
You could see my blind spot.
When you've seen the blind spot,
you won't feel stressed anymore.
Do you still remember
the first time you work for me?
You found many blind spots
when you read my novel.
Thanks to you,
my novel got approved.
But that's different.
I know it's different,
but have you tried it?
Not yet.
See?
Give it a try.
If it doesn't work, I'll help you.
There must be a way.
Okay. I'll give it a try.
Thank you.
Show it to Bua when you've finished.
You might get it published.
You are not an outsider anyway.
It should be easy.
Get it published? I don't think I'm that good.
Don't underestimate yourself.
Give it a try.
Trust me.
Gene.
Do you believe that I can make it?
Of course, I do.
Why did I say it otherwise?
Don't underestimate yourself.
Be confident.
Don't give up.
Bye.
Thank you, Gene.
That's so bad.
Be more careful.
Language isn't stable.
Mixed-up logic.
The first part is too short.
You're here?
Let's go to the sea.
What?
Sunscreen.
Can't you say it nicely?
♪Do you know? Every time you look at me,
every time we are close together♪
♪Do you know? You are my dream♪
♪Do you know? Every sentence you've said♪
♪I'll remember all of them♪
♪Do you know? I miss you more than anyone else♪
♪You changed my world♪
♪You made my heart fall for you♪
♪Maybe you are the gift God gave me♪
♪Are you the one I've been looking for?♪
♪Maybe it's you♪
♪Want to let you know how wonderful this feels♪
♪You love me a lot?♪
Aren't you coming with me?
♪I love you more♪
Nubsib. Nubsib!
Let go of me.
Nubsib!
Don't you want to play?
Not like this!
♪You are a book that I've never read.♪
Darn it!
♪You are a book that I've never read♪
♪But do you know, every page I've read♪
Is it fun?
♪Makes me unable to stop♪
You want to play, right?
♪Although it's not the story I like♪
♪Or the story I expected♪
♪It's the most beautiful story I've seen♪
♪You changed my world♪
♪You made my heart fall for you♪
♪Maybe you are the gift God gave me♪
♪Are you the one I've been looking for?♪
♪Maybe it's you♪
♪Want to let you know how wonderful this feels♪
♪You love me a lot?♪
♪I love you more♪
♪Baby, it's you♪
Come on, Gene!
Didn't you say want to play?
(#Gene isn't a driver #SibGene
#SibAey #Bad Engineer The Series)
(On Next Episode)
Is it because of the #SibGene topic?
I'm worried about you.
If both of them are together,
I will not say anything.
How could you let that happen, Tum?
I was pressured by the
production company of the series.
They want me to take care of my own authors.
There's a minor problem.
My sister wants to have a chat with you.
Mr. Gene is here.
Why did you bring Gene here?
I asked Tum to bring him there.