(Previously On Lovely Writer)
I've talked to your mother.
From now on,
I can't stop anything
between your love with Gene.
You are still together with Nubsib, right?
Yes.
Tiffy.
I really like you.
Will you believe me now?
I can believe you.
Don't you want to play at the beach?
The beach?
I can go with you.
Nubsib!
(#Geneisafool #SibGene #SibAey #BadEngineer)
(Is this the reason why I didn't see Aey
and Nubsib together recently? #SibGene)
(The male lead is indecent and
the writer needs a beating #SibGene)
(The couple I ship is moving fast.
Serve the official couple fans right #SibGene)
(They look like a match. #SibGene)
(How could Nubsib do that to Aey?
I pity Aey #SibGene)
(I couldn't accept this if I'm Aey.
The company should do something #SibGene)
(Young writer taking advantage of his own actor.
How convenient #SibGene)
(Did he know that he has violated the
third law by stealing someone's partner? #SibGene)
(How can the company
allow this to happen? #SibGene)
(I support them. I can separate
the series and the reality #SibGene)
(There's a real-life couple.
How can I still watch the series? #SibGene)
(Stop the broadcast.
I can't watch it anymore #SibGene)
(Nubsib, I'll stop being your fan.
We'll stop supporting you #SibGene)
(While the fake couple earns money,
the real couple is having fun #SibGene)
(SibGene is real!
Fujoshis, please respect them.#SibGene)
(Aey, I hope the series ends now so I can
beat them both for not respecting you #SibGene)
(I'm totally speechless #SibGene)
(There's such a big change to Aey
I couldn't keep up with him #SibGene)
(My SibAey can't end like this.
I'm running out of breath #SibGene)
(Whoever ships this couple,
please block me. So annoying #SibGene)
Nubsib.
What's wrong?
Let's take a picture together.
Are you uploading it to Instagram?
No.
I want to send it to my family.
Look at the camera.
One, two.
Hey, can you stop pretending
that you look better than me?
I didn't do anything.
Are you trying to say that you
look good without even doing anything?
No.
Fine.
Let's make funny faces.
How?
Like this.
Hurry up.
One, two, three.
Put some effort when you make your funny faces.
Hey, Nubsib!
Nubsib!
Hey, that tickles!
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love. Just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
♪I wanna kiss, kiss you♪
♪I wanna love, love you♪
♪I'm gonna kiss you♪
♪1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, and kiss♪
Hello.
Oh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
It's really nothing.
I'm fine.
Is it because of the hashtag, SibGene?
I'm worried about you.
No.
It's not because of that.
What happened on Twitter,
about the hashtag, SibGene.
I saw people scolding Gene and Nubsib.
All of you, please don't scold Gene.
Gene is a person I like and appreciate a lot.
Maybe things are not what they seem to be.
I think we shouldn't come to
a conclusion because of a few pictures.
Actually,
if they are together,
I will not say anything.
But I feel sad
knowing something like that happened.
It's bad for everyone.
To be honest, Gene, Nubsib
and I.
All three of us are getting along well.
What happened between Nubsib and Gene...
I'm not sure
because I'm not the one involved.
Besides, I don't think I have the right
to talk about their matters.
Even if there's something between them,
I won't mind.
I just hope that...
I just hope that none of you
will forget about SibAey.
I just hope that all of you
can keep supporting me.
(Aey, I'll always support you #Aeylive)
(Aey, don't cry #Aeylive)
(They don't love you but I do. #Aeylive)
(He is always around Nubsib. Now I know why. #Aeylive)
(I pity Aey #Aeylive)
(Wait for their statements #Aeylive)
(He is just pretending #Aeylive)
(Beware when you go out, Gene #Aeylive)
(This is showbiz #Aeylive)
(Best Actor in Oscar #Aeylive)
(You are not a real couple. #Aeylive)
(Do your best, Aey #Aeylive)
(If I were him, I'd drown the jerk #Aeylive)
(Aey is too nice. #Aeylive)
(I know why he picked Gene now #Aeylive)
(Gene is much cuter #Aeylive)
(Aey, come home with me #Aeylive)
(He's such a good actor #Aeylive)
(Nubsib escaped!!!! #Aeylive)
(I'll give you a hug, Aey #Aeylive)
(Tiffy: Aey, are you all right?
Do you need me to be there for you?)
(Tiffy: Aey, how are you? I'm worried about you.)
(Tiffy: Aey)
(Tiffy: Aey, say something.)
(Tiffy: How can I help you
if you don't reply to my messages?)
Bua, I'm here to show you the completed novels.
Hin, do you know your position?
What did I hire you to do?
What did you do instead?
You are not doing the job I've given you
but you're doing this.
Do you know what has happened?
Look.
You don't know
because you are not focused on your own job at all.
See for yourself.
The hashtag, SibGene on Twitter.
Do you know how much the sales
have taken a hit because of this?
It gave the publishing company such a bad image.
Where were you?
Were you together with Gene?
Did you remind him?
I don't want to say this, Hin.
If you made a mistake at your job,
I'd have to get someone who
won't make any mistakes to replace you.
Do you want that to happen?
No.
Bua, I'm really sorry.
Hold it.
Apologizing is not enough.
What do you want me to do?
I think you should be able to figure it out.
Otherwise, why do I spend
so much money to hire you?
Am I right?
But this is unfair to Gene.
Whether it's fair or not depends
on your perspective on this issue.
Now that it has happened,
you need to solve it
by all means.
I'll do my best.
Wait.
Bring your things back.
If you can't solve the problem,
I won't help you look at it.
I hope you can understand.
I'm pressured by my superior too.
I understand.
What is it?
Tum, where are you?
I'm on my way back.
I'm at the petrol station.
What is it?
Open the link I sent you right now.
She sounds rush.
(The battle for the male lead)
(Writer VS Actor)
Have you seen it?
Yes.
How could you let that happen, Tum?
Do you know?
The TV station is very unhappy about this.
They called me and chewed me out.
Why didn't you think it through?
What now? Your so-called private life
has affected work.
Can't you be more mature?
I can explain.
That's...
Don't waste your time apologizing to me.
Go and take care of things.
It must be the same thing.
You've seen the news, right?
Yes. I've seen it.
Why did you and your artist behave like that?
I thought you were different
from the other talent managers.
I thought we can communicate well.
-Tiffy, no...
-In the end, it's still the same.
I feel I'm so stupid.
I thought we won't end up like this.
Listen to me.
Enough.
I can't contact my artist now.
Didn't you see his live broadcast?
He looks so sad.
Tiffy, listen to me.
It's over for us.
Tiffy.
Nubsib,
did you go to the beach?
No.
I was sitting by the pool.
When I tried to stand up,
I slipped and fell.
Go take a bath and get changed then.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
Nubsib.
You might wet the floor.
Let me go.
I can walk myself.
Don't move.
You're not as light as you think.
Do you have the right to say I'm heavy?
How dare you say I have no right?
I did so much more than that to you.
Stupid Nubsib.
You should eat less
so I can carry you more easily.
Can you stop talking like a pervert?
I'm not thinking about anything.
That means you are thinking about it.
This room is so troublesome.
An apartment is troublesome for you?
You are the one who's causing me trouble.
The room is so big.
Why do you like to stay
in the small room beside mine?
That's because it's beside yours.
Is this the one in your car?
You like it this much?
You think of it as your family?
You're jealous of a doll?
No.
But I used to be jealous of it.
What?
You were jealous of a doll?
Don't you remember?
We had a quarrel because of the doll.
At that time,
when I entered your room,
I saw how much you treasured it.
So, I wanted the doll,
but you wouldn't give it to me.
So, we had a quarrel and Auntie Run heard it.
So my mother gave it to you secretly.
You finally remember.
Why did you steal other people's things?
I didn't understand at that time.
I understood when I grew up.
That's because I was jealous of it.
Jealous of a doll?
Yes.
You treasured it a lot
so I didn't like it.
I hoped you care more about me.
Are you angry?
No.
Why should I be angry?
That's good.
It belongs to you too.
You can play with it anytime you like.
Just don't care about it
more than you do about me.
Seriously.
You've been so jealous since you were young.
You are even jealous of a doll.
But you don't have to worry.
I care about you more than anything.
What is it?
Gene.
I went looking for you at your apartment
but you weren't there.
Oh, what is it?
I have something to tell you.
Is it important?
Can it wait?
It's very important.
Okay. Wait for me.
I'm going back now.
Who is it?
Hin.
He said he needed to tell me something important.
I need to go back to my apartment.
Let me send you there.
There's no need.
We need to keep our distance sometimes.
Gene.
I'm missing you again.
You are exaggerating again.
Hin, what's wrong?
What is it?
I bought you food.
Don't act weird around me.
Just tell me what's on your mind.
I'm not acting weird.
To be honest, I came here because of you.
You should've seen the news, right?
I've seen it.
Be frank with me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I know it will happen one day.
By the way, Aey is not easy to handle.
Who would've thought he'd do that?
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Have you talked about it with Nubsib?
Not yet.
Why?
Nubsib seems fine.
I don't dare to tell him.
You came to me because of this?
Yes. I'm worried about you.
I want you to consider it.
What do you want me to do then?
I think you should be able to figure it out.
Now that it has happened,
you need to solve it
by all means.
Bring your things back.
If you can't solve the problem,
I'll not help you look at it.
To be honest, I don't know yet.
You came all the way here
just to ask me to consider it?
Yes.
I'm worried about you.
I don't want you to think too much
or get anxious.
Okay.
I'm fine right now.
When I saw you getting so anxious,
I thought you were being chased
by debt collectors.
But you are so nice.
You came to remind me yourself.
Do you love me so much?
Do you?
Do you have feelings for me?
Wait a moment, Gene.
If I don't love you,
who do you want me to love?
Right?
Come on, let me see what you bought me.
It's weird for you to come here.
Shumai.
Gene.
I'll be going back first.
You came all the way here.
What's the rush?
I have to take care of some matters for Bua.
She might scold me again later.
Okay. Hurry up.
Okay. Good luck.
(The Editor Who Risks for Love)
(Mom)
Hin, how are you recently?
Are you busy, son?
No. Are you well?
Why do you sound like that, Hin?
It's nothing. I just had a slight fever.
Hin, can you keep doing your work?
Come home if you can't.
I'm so tired, Mom.
Take a rest if you are, son.
It's still the same even if I take a rest.
My work is in shambles right now.
I just want a better life for our family.
But I couldn't do it.
Hin, I know.
I know you are working
and earning money for the family.
But you have to think about yourself now.
I'm not happy seeing you like this.
I envy the people
who can live a good life without doing anything.
That's life, Hin.
Life won't tell us that we will be successful
because of our persistence.
But Hin, you are already at your limit, right?
I don't know what I should do now, Mom.
I'm proud of you
if you've persisted until your limit.
Just let it be, son.
I trust that you will become an excellent person
if you overcome all these obstacles, understand?
I miss you, Mom. I want you to hug me.
I love you.
What are you doing?
Hey, you scared me.
I'm reading Hin's novel.
It's cute.
I didn't expect him to have a talent in this.
What is it about?
A story about an editor and a writer.
If the novel is cute,
why didn't he show it to Bua?
Well,
Hin told me he had shown it to Bua.
But...
I think I'll show her again.
What about your novel?
Have you finished writing it?
It's almost done.
But...
What is it?
Right now, the character in my novel
is facing his biggest problem in the story.
So, I don't know
how I should continue with the story.
Then, is there anything I can help with?
You are so shameless!
There you go again.
I haven't done anything yet, Mr. Gene.
Stop it, you.
But you have to promise me.
If we are facing a huge obstacle,
we have to overcome it together.
Nonsense!
I'm talking about the novel.
But I'm talking about the two of us.
Okay.
I promise.
Bua, why did you call me here?
Please take a seat.
You know about everything, right?
Currently, our sales are plummeting
and our company is facing a lot of trouble.
You should have known the reason for that, right?
But, I'm just a writer.
I'm not a star.
My private life should not be related to this.
But you are a celebrity in society right now.
Whatever happens to you, whether it's good or bad,
will directly affect our company's sales.
Sorry.
I don't want this to happen either.
I get it. You think love is
a matter between two people.
But the consequences of this matter are huge.
Just take a look at our publishing company.
If things don't take a turn,
it will be bad, Gene.
I am also being pressured by the
series production company.
They want me to take care of my own writers.
Can you find a way to deal with this relationship?
All right? I beg you.
Why should I be the one to bear everything?
When the company asked me to write BL novels,
I did.
How much profit did the company make from that?
But now they are pressuring me?
Do I have to take full responsibility for that?
I don't think it's fair.
Gene.
Nothing is fair.
You should know.
Look around you.
They did nothing but they have been affected.
Don't you think that's selfish, Gene?
But...
Stop. Listen to me first.
If I can solve it for you,
I would've already done that, Gene.
But I couldn't.
You are the only one who can solve this.
Sorry, I hope you can understand me
and also understand it from
the company's point of view.
Whatever.
I don't think I have a choice anyway.
Trust me, Gene.
Go back and think about
the importance of everything.
It all depends on you.
Oh, I brought Hin's novel.
I think you should take a look, Bua.
(@Nubsib_PP Nubsib has a boyfriend?
Why isn't it Aey? I'm not okay. #BadEngineerTheSeries)
(Why didn't you think about your fans?
I'm so disappointed. I won't support you again. #SibAey)
(I don't feel comfortable especially
seeing the beach pictures. #SibAey)
(SibGene's fans, please don't talk
about the novel or series #SibAey)
(I don't care if #SibGene is real,
but Aey is better #SibAey)
(I don't think it's that simple after
watching Aey's live. #SibAey)
(Did Gene write the novel so he can
get a celebrity boyfriend who loves him so? #SibAey)
(Whoever likes #SibGene
can unfollow me #SibAey)
(I pity Aey. Stupid Gene.
Just stop watching the series #SibAey)
Sorry.
I thought you were asleep.
Not yet.
I can't fall asleep.
What about you?
Aren't you sleeping?
I can't fall asleep either.
Why is that?
Sorry. What are you doing?
I'm sleeping. What is it?
There's a minor problem.
I'm at the Entertainment Tower.
Can you come over?
What is it?
My sister wants to have a chat with you.
What? Talk to me?
Yes. It's about Nubsib.
She already called Nubsib over.
But she knows you are my friend.
So she wants to talk to you too.
Then, is Nubsib with you?
He is talking with her.
I come out to call you.
Okay. I'll be there soon.
(Aey: Gene, how are you?)
(Aey: I was called by the
production company too)
Everything will be okay, Aey.
Trust me.
Tum.
Gene.
Where are the others?
They are all inside.
What about Nubsib?
He has talked with my sister for a while now.
Let's go.
Mr. Gene is here.
Why did you bring Gene here?
I asked Tum to bring him.
Isn't it too much to do this?
It's not.
Gene is directly related to this issue.
This is for the sake of the benefits of you,
Gene and the TV station.
But don't forget this.
This is not part of the contract.
Stop using the contract as a reason.
I know what's what.
But you've also forgotten
everything is related.
Didn't you see it already?
What are we talking about?
When Nubsib had his photoshoot at the beach,
you went with him, right?
Yes.
There's nothing in reality.
Every fan knows that, right?
Gene is Tum's friend.
But pictures about their little moment
have surfaced on the Internet.
It isn't weird to have fans
who ship the Nubsib and Gene couple.
The main problem is
that our series is still on air.
The audience will be immersed in the story
while watching the series.
The lead characters
of the series are Nubsib and Aey,
not Nubsib and Gene.
The TV station needs to use sweet moments
between Nubsib and Aey to promote
the series, so as to gain viewership.
When this problem breaks out,
the TV station is angry at us.
They are questioning us for the cause of this.
(Writer gets actor. Fujoshis' BL dream has come true)
I'm not using this to reprimand you.
But I have to use it as evidence
to tell you we really have a problem on our hands.
The TV station is very angry too.
After everything you've said,
how are we going to solve this?
I don't want to say too much.
Since it has already happened,
I called Nubsib here
to tell him what we are going to do.
As for calling Gene here,
I hope you can cooperate with us.
Gene, you should understand, right?
Now that it has happened,
everything will crumble
if we don't solve the problem.
Yes. I understand.
Okay. I'll be straightforward then.
It might be harsh
but both of you are adults.
You should know what you should and shouldn't do.
From now on,
I hope Nubsib and Gene
stay away from each other.
No photos with each other on social media.
No commenting on each other's photos.
Don't go anywhere with each other.
If we do that, nothing
will fall into the media's hands.
We are just going to let this pass?
Yes, the TV station will
do their own promotions on the series.
Regarding the relationship
between the two of you,
this Saturday, the TV station will
have a press conference to clear it.
I can't do that.
Gene is my boyfriend.
How could you separate us?
That's impossible.
Don't you get it, Nubsib?
Everything we've just said
is to solve the problem.
Didn't I say it just now?
You shouldn't be in a relationship right now.
But no terms in the contract
that forbid me to be in a relationship.
We didn't forbid it
but you shouldn't do it right now.
You should know, young actors and models,
especially the ones in BL series,
if you want to have more fans
and keep being popular,
you should forget about
being in a relationship for the time being.
You are clear about this, Nubsib.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I think it's fine as long as
they don't do anything in public.
We don't have to go to that extent, right?
But can they really do it?
They will still meet
behind everyone's back in secret.
Yes.
Meeting in secret
will still be found out by others.
It's like this.
We are not asking you to break up.
We just want you
to keep your distance for now.
When this is over,
you can fall in love with each other
and be together again.
Couples in showbiz are all like this.
There's no problem with that, right?
Exactly.
Yes.
Everyone.
I need to apologize to everyone.
I didn't expect this to blow up so quickly.
It's too late now, Aey.
I'm not trying to reprimand you
but please consider it thoroughly
before you do something, okay?
Nubsib, you should care about
the feelings of your fans.
They are the people
who give you jobs and let you make money.
Don't forget about that.
You can't eat your contract anyway.
I'll terminate the contract then.
Nubsib.
You don't have to
make it so complicated, Nubsib.
Do you have to terminate your contract
just for a boyfriend?
There are only four months left on your contract.
If you terminate your contract now,
you'll have to compensate...
I'll pay any amount of compensation.
Why do you have to do that?
Why?
I want you to stay away
from each other. It's not a breakup.
We are trying to make things better, Nubsib.
Are you willing to give up
your future and end your career here?
You are famous right now.
You should cherish the opportunity
that everyone is giving you.
Don't contact each other
so there are no more rumours.
We'll hold a press conference and tell the media
what they see on the news is not the truth.
You are not a couple.
Everything is just a misunderstanding.
That's all.
We can control the public's opinion...
That's so selfish of you.
Excuse me for being so straightforward.
Ask yourself.
Getting me to break up with Gene,
is it for me, or for all of you?
From what I've heard here today,
there's not a single point
where you are thinking of us.
That's too much, Nubsib.
Enough.
We'll do everything as requested here today.
Gene.
You understand us. Right, Gene?
All right, everyone. Let's calm down.
There's no better way
to solve this problem now.
You should sit down too.
I don't want things
to be like this either, Nubsib.
Please look at it from my point of view.
Why are you scolding me?
Okay, it's decided then.
Don't appear together.
Don't comment on each other's photos.
No interaction on social media.
All right.
I'll do it.
That's all, right?
I'll be leaving now.
Gene!
Nubsib, we still have things to discuss.
What else is there to discuss?
I'm tired from listening to all of that.
Aren't you tired of talking?
Nubsib, come back!
Tum, you need to get Nubsib back
for the press conference.
Tum!
Calm down.
I have calmed down.
Did I talk too much?
I'm going to the washroom.
I think that's too much.
Why did you force them to break up?
Too much?
What do you want me to do, Tum?
I didn't ask them to break up. I just
want them to stay away from each other.
I know your personality. If it happens again,
you'll still force them to break up.
You're good at guessing.
I'm disappointed with you.
You are too selfish.
What kind of person do you expect me to be?
I did everything for our company.
Nubsib still has a selling point.
He has much time to find a partner.
How old is he now?
How could you say that?
You did it for yourself obviously.
Really?
I did it for myself?
You need to understand.
You are who you are today
because of people like me.
Because of my selfishness,
you get to graduate from university.
you possess everything you have today.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Am I not telling the truth?
Don't tell me that you're disappointed with me.
Have you asked me before?
How many times was I disappointed with you?
That is why
I'm not standing on your side.
Can you still feel anything?
Where is your consciousness?
Don't blame me.
You are the same.
Everything turns out like that because of you.
Who can stop that, Sister?
Do you think I don't know, Tum?
You let Nubsib do what he pleases
because you only care about Tiffy!
Is that the personal time you wanted?
Is that it?
You only care about others.
Stop interfering with my business.
Who would want a terrible family like this?
No wonder you were abandoned by your husband.
Tum!
Don't get my private matters involved.
What?
Are you going to hit me?
Come!
Or are you going to beat me up?
Come on!
I am that terrible person in your family.
It's enough to be a talent manager.
I'm not a star.
Stop interfering with my business!
Tum, get lost!
Get lost and don't come back!
Gene.
It's no use to agree with them.
What do you mean?
Not appearing together and
not taking pictures together aren't enough.
They want us to break up indirectly.
What do you want me to do
besides agreeing with them?
They have invested a lot of money in the series.
They are expecting profits too.
No one wants this to happen.
Besides,
I don't want them to say
you are neglecting your career for love.
But it's none of our business.
Being together
didn't make my performance worse.
I can still work as usual.
We don't have to care about what they think.
But the audience care.
The fans care.
You should care about them too,
because that's your job.
Don't you get it?
You should be with Aey, not me!
I know.
I don't wish for an issue with your adapted series.
I don't mind meeting you only at home.
But if we agree to that,
they will find other ways to force us
into agreeing with something else.
Nubsib.
You are a star.
That's what you should do.
You can say that I'm selfish.
But I never wanted to be a star in the first place.
I acted in this series because of you.
If it causes a problem in our relationship,
I don't want to do it anymore.
What do you want to do then?
Like I said,
once the series ends,
I'll tear the contract.
No way.
You don't have to worry about money.
Do you still remember what I told you back home?
You are far more valuable than anything else.
As long as I'm together with you,
I'm willing to pay any price.
Nubsib, listen to me.
You have a job and you have your savings.
How long has it been since you
last asked for money from your parents?
That doesn't have to stop because of this.
Terminating the contract
will cost you a lot of money.
You'd rather we become like that?
Not letting everyone know
that we are together
but that I'm together with Aey instead?
Do you want things to become like that?
There you go again.
Anyone can ask you to do anything
and you'll just agree because you are soft-hearted.
You only care about others' feelings.
Why didn't you care about my feelings?
I care about you.
That is why I did that.
That is your future, Nubsib.
This is not like when we were kids
where the world revolved around us.
Is that what you think?
You should grow in your own way.
I want to grow in my own way too.
You promised me.
You said we would overcome it together.
But you have to promise me.
If we are facing a huge obstacle,
we have to overcome it together.
Okay.
I promise.
Yes.
But it should only exist in a novel.
The truth is,
this is the best way to overcome it.
♪I just want to erase what others said♪
♪Replace them with certain words♪
♪Certain words that I never said out loud♪
Gene.
Don't cry.
I beg you, Gene.
Don't leave. Okay?
Can you not leave, Gene?
Let's end it, Nubsib.
♪Can you stop time?♪
Gene,
I beg you!
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Can it not end here?♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Let us be the only ones in the story♪
♪Okay?♪
Why are you here?
If you come here and just stay silent,
you might as well go back.
Does it hurt?
Why are you so careless?
What's wrong? Why are you staying silent again?
♪If I can read about you♪
♪Like I do in the novel♪
♪I should be reading it slowly♪
♪Every letter and every word
described in the scene♪
♪When we are close to each other♪
♪When both of us have feelings for each other♪
♪I don't want to miss this moment♪
♪If tomorrow no longer exists♪
♪If Earth no longer rotates♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Can it not end here?♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Let us be the only ones in the story♪
♪Okay?♪
♪If we can't have♪
♪The same ending as a romance novel♪
♪If we need to separate in the end♪
♪Can I just remember♪
♪the chapters with both of us?♪
♪Just the two of us together♪
♪Where we don't have to separate♪
♪I just want to erase what others said♪
♪Replace them with certain words♪
♪Certain words that I never said out loud♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Can it not end here?♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
I want to play too.
Give it back.
-No.
-Give me.
No.
Why are you being like this?
If you do it again,
I won't let you play with me anymore.
I want to play with you.
Gene, sorry.
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Let us be the only ones in the story♪
♪Okay?♪
♪I just want to stay in sweet chapters♪
♪Where we're locked in an embrace♪
♪I don't want to flip to the next page♪
♪Don't want to read
the chapter where we separate♪
♪Can we just end the scene here?♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't let others♪
♪Change the last chapter♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Can this be our ending?♪
♪No more next chapter♪
♪Okay?♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Can this be our ending?♪
♪No more next chapter♪
♪Okay?♪
Gene, is there anything that you want to say to me?
I understand what you said now.
Are you all right, my son?
You can cry.
Cry it out, my son.
It's all right.
I'm with you.
I'll always be with you, my son.
Don't cry, my son.
(Four Months Later)
(The Final Chapter)
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Can this be our ending?♪
♪No more next chapter♪