(Previously On Lovely Writer)
Look around you.
They did nothing but they have been affected.
I need to apologize to everyone.
I didn't expect this to blow up so quickly.
I hope that Nubsib and Gene
stay away from each other.
I'm disappointed in you.
You are too selfish.
Don't you get it?
You should be with Aey, not me!
I beg you, Gene.
Don't leave. Okay?
Let's end it, Nubsib.
Gene, I beg you!
Gene.
Are you okay?
Why did you come here?
I'm here to fetch you to the press conference.
What about Nubsib?
Nubsib is already there.
He is doing his make-up.
I didn't see you.
I was worried and came to find you.
Okay.
Get ready.
There's a traffic jam today.
We might not make it on time.
Gene.
Gene, are you all right?
Yes.
Oh. Nubsib was right.
My sister wants to extend his contract.
She has planned everything.
She had a talk with the TV station directors.
She wants Nubsib and Aey to be
the double male leads in the next series.
With that, the TV station
will make a profit for a long time.
Tum, it's too late.
Forget it.
♪Stop thinking, just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love, just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
Nubsib.
-I...
-Aren't you going to celebrate?
I didn't make this happen on purpose.
Someone like you
didn't do it on purpose?
If I still have a bit of strength left,
I would've already punched you in the face.
I didn't expect it to turn out like this.
See?
You did do it on purpose.
Sorry.
Aey, I understand.
You want everyone to care about you.
But do you need to do it to this extent?
What you have today
comes from hurting others.
You are proud of it, right?
Wait.
We are not done yet.
We are done.
Not yet.
I will help you with this.
Thanks.
That's enough, Aey.
Don't worry that I'll hate you.
Don't worry that
I won't be "loving" you anymore.
I can act.
I'm a professional.
See?
I "love" you to death.
How was that?
Is it good enough for you?
Gene.
Gene!
What?
My friend.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
I'll take you to the press conference.
It should be ready.
(#SAGMustSpeakTheTruth)
(Aey, you are the best)
(I won't watch the series
if they can't give an explanation)
(It's trending)
(I support every staff member)
(When is it starting? I can't wait for it to start)
(I'm just curious about the updates)
(Production team, do your best)
(Aey, I'll always support you)
(Everyone can't wait for it to start)
Tiffy, are you all right?
Aey.
Take care of yourself in the future.
Why?
I will not be your manager anymore.
So,
I'm taking care of you for the last day today.
Tiffy, what did I do wrong?
What did I do wrong?
Tell me.
Am I not paying you enough?
I'll pay you 30%.
35% works too.
40%! Please don't abandon me.
Okay, Tiffy?
It's not about the money.
You should know.
Tiffy.
Don't abandon me. I beg you.
Aey, don't cry.
Or your make-up will smear and run.
Don't you hate that?
I'm leaving.
Oh, Aey.
Wipe your tears.
We'll go out together.
It's ready outside.
Friends from the media. Hello, everyone.
Today, the staff members
and cast of "Bad Engineer The Series"
has organized this press conference
because the rumours on social media
have caused trouble for everyone.
The press conference today
is to clarify the situation.
Before that, please allow us
to do a self-introduction.
I am Fah Sirinapha.
I'm the producer of this series.
I am Aey. I play Namcha in the series.
I am Nubsib. I play Kin in the series.
I am Gene, the author
of the novel "Bad Engineer".
I am Tam. I am Nubsib's manager.
Next, we will be hearing
the truth from the three of them.
If you have any questions, you may ask them.
Please take turns so they can hear your questions.
-Let me ask first.
-Sure.
How did the relationship between
Mr. Nubsib and Mr. Gene get so close?
My relationship is close with Nubsib
because I'm the author of the novel.
The production team wants me
to coordinate the characters better
so my relationship is good
with the male lead, Nubsib.
Yes.
We did invite Mr. Gene to help
our actors with character coordination.
Are you only close with Nubsib?
My relationship with Gene is close too.
They are close...
Regarding Aey's live broadcast
that caused a stir on the internet,
someone said you did it to
clear the rumour about SibGene couple.
What do you have to say about that?
Before that,
I want to apologize for doing
a live broadcast due to my foolishness.
I didn't expect things to turn out like this.
It's all my fault.
If I can turn back time,
I will never do that.
There are rumours saying that Mr. Gene
and Mr. Nubsib are staying together.
Is that true?
What's going on?
What happened?
Yes.
We are staying at the same house.
How did Nubsib end up
staying together with Mr.Gene?
I had a problem with the talent agency's dorm.
Allow me to answer that question.
There was an issue within our talent agency.
Due to the increase of our talents,
we didn't have enough dorms
to provide for our talents.
So, we lacked dorms at the time
and needed to find Nubsib a new place to stay.
Fortunately, we were close with Mr. Gene.
That was why Mr. Gene lent Nubsib a helping hand.
That was why Nubsib got to stay
at his house while filming the series.
I hope all of you can understand.
They were staying under one roof after all.
It's not weird for them
to enter or leave the place together.
Right?
Let me ask a question
that everyone is curious about.
What is the relationship
between Mr. Gene and Mr. Nubsib?
What is the relationship? Please answer.
Please answer the question.
There is nothing between us.
Mr. Gene and I
are like brothers.
Yes.
We are just brothers.
Really?
Why did you look so shocked then?
Sorry.
I'm not a star.
I've never participated
in a press conference like this.
Actually,
Mr. Gene and Tam's brother,
which is my manager, Tum,
are friends.
So, we used to be together in public
and caused a misunderstanding.
I wanna say sorry to everyone right here, right now.
That includes the fans of the novel as well.
Don't worry.
No matter what, Aey and I are a couple now.
Gene, please smile at the reporters.
(Four Months Later)
(Bua)
Hello, Bua.
Hin, come over here.
I have something urgent to tell you.
Okay. I'll go there immediately.
What is this?
-Resignation...
-A merit envelope.
Right?
That's definitely what a white envelope is for.
I'm someone who likes to do merit.
Here you go.
By the way, why did you call me here?
Oh, I want to tell you.
The novel you wrote
is going to be published.
What?
The parts where I've marked in red concern me.
Please amend it for me.
By the way, where did you get this draft?
I got it from Gene.
He brought it to me when I called him here.
Thank you for giving me an opportunity.
I'm very happy.
Your novel talks about what
happens in a publishing company.
I like it.
Thank you so much, Bua.
Oh, Hin.
Did you talk to Gene recently?
I didn't talk much to him recently.
Is that so?
Please ask him to send me his draft.
It's been four months
since he sent me a draft last time.
Pass this message to him.
Tell him I understand that he wants
to say something through this novel
and tell him that I'm sorry.
I apologize for the things I did to him.
Okay?
Okay, I'll tell him that.
Good.
Thank you.
Hin, wait! I want that envelope back.
Yes, the envelope.
Bring it here.
Why are you hesitating?
We must put our names for merit.
Bua Bua and Fam.
Amitabha.
I'll send your merit immediately.
Great.
I've fulfilled my merit.
Buddha will bless you.
Have a nice day.
(Hin: I'm heading over to your apartment)
(The Final Chapter)
Why are you so fast?
I was already downstairs when I texted you.
You don't have to text me if you are already here.
My room is quite messy.
I haven't tidied the place yet.
What smell is that?
Don't overreact.
It's not that bad, isn't it?
So, why did you come here?
Oh, it's about your novel.
Bua asked me to follow up on you.
Oh, she also said sorry.
She is sorry for what happened.
She also said you can
write the novel in any way you like.
It's fine even if there are no sex scenes.
As you can see,
I did my best.
I can't write anything.
Why?
Maybe I can't get myself immersed in the story.
Immersed?
You couldn't write it because
you can't immerse yourself in the story?
Are you too free?
It's not funny at all.
I was just joking, Gene.
It's a joke.
-Gene.
-Yes?
I want to drink coffee. Make me a cup of coffee.
Oh, are you my boss now?
Am I your lackey?
But you helped to give my draft to Bua.
I did it as an act of kindness.
You found out?
Yes.
Do you know?
My novel is going to be published soon.
Really?
Yes!
Congratulations.
I'm so excited.
Thank you.
I'm really grateful.
Can you stop looking so touched?
I'm not acting.
Without you,
my novel might not even be published.
Also, if you didn't call me that day,
I would've stopped writing it.
It's all because of you.
Oh, don't cry.
Who is crying? I haven't cried yet.
Hin, do you know?
Actually,
you are the one who didn't give up.
You did this on your own.
I didn't help you at all.
Do you still remember?
You have always been helping me.
If it wasn't for you,
I won't be where I am today.
Both of us
have always been helping each other.
Are you going to give up on this novel then?
Hey, are you lecturing me with my own words?
No.
It was just a random question.
It's not that I want to give it up.
When I think of writing it, I'll...
Then,
do you need to change your environment?
For example, writing at home.
Forget it.
Come on, give it a try.
Maybe it's better.
Try to go back to where the story started.
Are you using my words on me again?
No.
I just want you to give it a try.
Okay, I'll consider your advice.
Okay, I'll be going back then.
What's the rush?
Let's eat together.
My treat.
No. I'll eat with you next time.
I have to amend the draft for Bua.
Oh, you are rejecting my invitation now.
You've really improved a lot.
Of course.
I'm no longer who I used to be.
That's right. You need to get my autograph first.
You won't get a chance otherwise.
If my novel becomes popular,
it will be difficult for you to get my autograph.
You need a beating.
It's a joke.
That's right.
Did you contact Nubsib?
Thank you for your gifts, my fans!
This...
I'll finish all of them later.
Let's see if it's delicious.
Also, thank you for always supporting me
when I'm in pain, when I'm sad
and when I'm feeling dejected.
My motivation to work comes from all my fans.
No matter what, don't forget me
and please don't abandon me.
Oh, it's already so late.
I'll be going off now.
I'll see you guys again tomorrow at 9 p.m..
I'll try my best to be on time.
If I'm late...
If I'm late, I'll receive a punishment tomorrow.
That's all for today. Bye.
(Please do a longer broadcast next time)
(I feel empty after the series ended)
(Aey is so cute. I will follow
@AEY_ATHIKAN forever and be your fans)
(Aey, always be happy)
(Aey, I miss you. Do more broadcasts)
(Mhok has a new drama.
When will Aey have a new drama?)
Come in.
-Sister.
-Yes?
I need to talk to you.
Say it.
Hurry up.
I don't have a whole day's time for you, Tum.
I'm resigning.
No way. Resigning after a minor issue...
We don't have any binding contract.
You don't have to pressure me.
Are you for real?
Just tell me what you want.
It doesn't have to be like this.
I've told you what I want.
Can you stop acting like a child, Tum?
That is why I'm resigning.
I'm a child. I'll forever be a child in your eyes.
Leaving here
will let me grow into an adult.
You can't abandon me like this.
We built this company together.
How can the company operate without you?
Sister, don't try to act
how important I am to you here.
No matter what, you can still
find someone to replace me.
How are you not important?
You have always been important to the company.
No one can be compared to you
no matter what, Tum.
Stop being so petty.
You are lying.
I'm not lying. I'm telling the truth.
If I'm that important,
did you even listen to my opinions?
You have been forcing me.
Since I was in elementary school,
you've been forcing me.
When I started work,
you asked me to resign to help you out in the company
so you could keep forcing me.
I want my own life. Do you understand?
The reason why I'm important
is that I still have to listen to you in the end.
It's because of that, right?
That is why you said I was not like others.
Why did you listen to me then?
Because I love you!
What about you? Can you see that?
I can!
I'm begging you, all right?
I beg you to let me live my own life.
I'm worried about you, Tum.
You are weak.
Both of us are weak, Sister!
Am I right?
Since you dare talk to me like that,
I won't stop you
if you want to resign from my company.
You came here just to say that?
You may leave now.
Wait.
Remember one thing.
You will still be my brother no matter what.
Hello.
I've settled things over here.
Okay.
What are you going to do next?
I don't know yet. Can you give me some time?
Okay. You'll be fine, right?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Take care of yourself.
What's wrong? You look annoyed.
I can't write anything.
What are you going to do then?
I don't know.
Oh, Jap.
Yes?
Did Nubsib come back?
Gene.
What?
Your novel. Where did your inspiration come from?
From my own life.
If it's from your own life,
why don't you go to the places in your memories?
-The places in my memories?
-Yes.
Come on. Maybe you'll find something great.
We have to be quick.
Is the opponent hacking?
I'm sure they are using cheats.
Shoot, there are three of them.
We are doomed.
Get ready to die.
Jap, go to the other side. Why are you hitting me?
Take another route.
I was hiding and got spotted.
I escaped.
Jap, I think I heard footsteps just now.
Something's wrong with your ears, Gene.
Don't disturb me. I'm trying to focus.
Maybe it's Nubsib. If he knows we sneaked out...
It's fine, Gene. It's just a prank.
Besides, he is too young. He can't play with us.
We are not kids.
Do you think we should play
a childish game like hide-and-seek?
Darn. Jap, run.
Careful, on your right.
I know.
The enemy is coming. Hide.
Let him go.
Oh, thank you.
I'm Orn. My house is just over there.
Thank you, Orn. I'm Run.
I just moved here.
How nice it is for us to get to know each other!
Our kids can play together in the future.
I'll go home first.
Sib. Sib. Nubsib, come out.
Sib, where are you?
Gene, come out!
Why are you trespassing?
It's your turn.
Sib.
Gene, close your eyes and count to ten.
Hurry up.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
You...
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I'm waiting for you
at our old place.
Oh.
What is it, Jap?
My face is not as red as yours
even after I drink, Gene.
Stop teasing me.
Why? Are you feeling shy?
Okay. Fine.
I won't interfere with you.
Are you feeling shy?
So cute.
Don't do that, Gene.
Can I sleep in your room tonight?
Can I?
Your parents are not at home.
I want to hug you to sleep
to cure my lovesickness.
That means you won't hug me
if you don't miss me?
Of course, I'm hugging you.
So, you've agreed.
No, I don't want to be
the centre of attention again.
It's over.
My contract with them has ended.
From now on, only our promises are left.
I'm going to throw up if you continue.
Can you promise me?
We will never let go of each other's hand ever again.
No.
Can you promise me?
All right.
Fine.
I can promise you.
Didn't I say I promise?
Why are you still kissing?
I just want to kiss you. Can't I?
Fine. Just kiss me if you want to.
Kiss me until you're satisfied.
Nubsib.
Yes?
Do you know?
When you skipped piano lessons to play with me,
Aunty Orn asked me
to practice with you after she found it out.
That's right.
You liked sitting on that chair.
Do you remember where I liked to sit?
Here.
Why did you like to sit here?
It's because...
I can see your face clearly.
I'm very happy.
You've returned.
I love you, Nubsib.
I love you more and more.
I'll love you
more than you do.
Move.
Nubsib, play a song for Brother Gene.
Sign here.
Sign at the back too.
It's okay.
Wait, aren't you reading the contract, Nubsib?
What's wrong with you? Where are you rushing off to?
I'm rushing off to see Gene.
Were you tired yesterday?
Just now.
That's too much.
I was joking.
Please take good care of my friend.
Just think of it as compensating him
for the times when he was sad.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of every inch of him.
It's done, right?
I can't see you off.
You can go back on your own, right?
-Yes.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Should we do it too?
Do what?
You pervert!
Just a bit.
I'll kick you. Don't.
Tum. Enough!
How's it going?
How's your progress?
Look. I'm writing the ending now.
But I don't know if it's any good.
Piano?
It seems familiar.
I'm wondering
if this ending is good.
Oh, my love.
Who would do this to you?
My true love's kiss will wake your soul.
Your highness.
Did you come to rescue me?
Will you accept my love?
I accept.
Nubsib, I don't think it works.
In that case...
Hey.
That's you, right?
Yes.
It would be my honour
if you would share this dance with me.
Won't you tell me your name?
I have to go.
I have no time to explain.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I thank you for this special night.
Wait, don't go!
Gene, you are good at pretending.
I heard that, Your Highness!
Give it back.
Are you being shy?
What are you talking about?
You're always coming up with nonsense.
My true love.
My soul.
Death has taken away your sweet soul.
Yet, the last breath off your beautiful lips
still remains.
I request to kiss you.
Nubsib.
What is this?
It's poison.
Nubsib.
You drank the whole vial?
Won't you leave some for me?
I want to kiss you.
There might still be poison
remaining on your lips.
Your lips are so soft.
Then, I'm willing to die after this kiss.
Nubsib!
I want to die together with you.
Hey, isn't that too sad?
I think so too.
Let's do it again.
Aren't all your ideas funny?
I really can't think of the finale.
I'm just joking.
But
there's still another type of ending.
What is it?
This is your ending?
No, help me figure it out first.
I don't want it to end yet.
♪1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, and kiss♪
♪Stop thinking, just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love, just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like you want to kiss me too♪
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love♪
(The End)
♪Just say it out loud♪
What are you looking at?
What are we gonna eat?
I don't know either.
What about you? What do you want to eat?
Excuse me.
Are you Nubsib and Gene?
Yes.
Can we take a picture together?
Sure.
I like your novel.
It is very interesting.
I'm looking forward to your next novel.
Thank you.
Thank you, bye.
Come on.
You are more popular than me now.
Should I be jealous?
Why are you jealous?
I'm standing right here. I'm not going anywhere.
Don't you think it's weird then?
Everyone knows you are a guy
who writes BL novels.
There's nothing weird about it.
It's just another novel.
Besides...
I wrote it from our story.
Let's go to eat.
Come on.
(Don't you feel shy now?)
(Nubsib asks his lover)
(Nubsib looks forward to his reply)
("I wrote it from our story.")
(Gene smiles and they hold hands)
(The End)
Hello.
Hello, can you get Ms Rose to answer?
Oh, speaking.
We want to make "Lovely Writer" into a series
but we might make some changes to the content.
Did the publishing company contact you
or tell you about this?
Oh. They've told me.
Let's meet later and
talk about the changes then, Ms Rose.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay, goodbye.
♪Maybe it's true, life is not a novel♪
♪It's not easy to meet a prince♪
♪But the destined one might not be far away♪
♪It might be you♪
♪If someone is confessing to you♪
♪You don't have to think so much♪
♪Just ten seconds is enough♪
♪If you don't answer♪
♪1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, and kiss♪
♪Stop thinking, just let me kiss you♪