Can Nubsib stay for a month?
Okay. One month is fine.
Stay as you please.
The only thing I ask is
to not bother me while working.
Are you an actor?
You've got the wrong guy.
I just moved in with my boyfriend.
What?
Can you help me put makeup on?
Can you help me practice my lines?
But it's a kissing scene.
If you're not comfortable
with kissing then never mind.
I don't want to put you in
an uncomfortable position.
Fine, we can kiss.
Stop, Kin.
Someone might see us.
Kin.
Kiss, kiss.
Kiss!
Cut!
Just kiss already!
This is a Boy Love series.
Kissing scenes need
to be hot and passionate!
If you can't do it
maybe I should do the kissing for you?
I'm sorry
but can we use the camera's angle?
I feel kind of sick
and I'm afraid Aey might catch my cold.
Didn't anyone tell me that my boy is sick?
I didn't know that either.
I found out the exact moment
you did that Nubsib is sick.
That's just great,
maybe I should fake being sick too.
I don't want a camera angle, if we can't
do it today then shoot it another day.
Nope, definitely no camera angles.
This scene requires real kissing only
and we have to do at least 80 takes.
So we'll get the best shots, right?
Yes and this is an important
scene too, we have to do it.
Listen up!
Nubsib is feeling sick so he can't kiss.
We'll move on to shoot other scenes first.
We're not doing it?
Yes and Fah is okay with that.
Fine.
PM, go check if my boy is okay.
Sure.
Let's change the set.
We'll be shooting scene
three of two, next.
Mai, I have something for you.
What is it?
Our sponsor passed this onto me.
Add some scenes for it.
I've used this mask before, it's very
good! Should I make a big scene for it?
Like actually using the masks in a scene.
Let's have it in the whole scene.
Okay.
Everyone please hurry up
or we'll be behind schedule.
There are so many scenes left,
and if we don't finish on time,
I'm not paying you for over time.
Oh, hello Gene!
Hello.
Please take a seat.
Wow, there's so many people.
Where did the acting
teacher from casting day go?
Oh, he's back at Bangsaen.
He's on a vacation?
He's selling Stir-fried Crab and Basil.
What? Why?
He was fired after getting
into a disagreement with Fah...
so he was fired just like that.
Oh! It's that bad?
I don't want to spill the tea
but whoever disagrees with Fah...
and argues with her is doomed.
Too bad that Gene
didn't see the kissing scene earlier...
because Nubsib suddenly told us he's sick,
so he didn't want to kiss Aey but
wanted to use the camera angle instead.
The whole crew was confused!
That must have caused some problems.
A bit! But it's normal.
There's always small
inconveniences happening.
But we can't fake the kiss, right?
In this day and age,
it has to be real kissing!
We can't do camera angles or we won't
be able to compete with other series!
You understand that right Gene?
Mai, could you check this out?
Feel free to hang around, I have to
go check something in front of the set.
Mai!
I know! Geez, can't you
guys do anything yourselves?
Hin, I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Hello, Bua.
Hey Hin, how are you? Is Gene on set yet?
I'm at the set.
I think they're setting up for the next
scene, is there something you want?
Yes! Don't forget that
assignment I gave you.
Ah, the promote stuff again?
Yeah, the book sales
are just off the charts!
So our publishing house needs a lot of PR.
Okay, I'll take pictures for you to use.
That's fabulous! Don't forget.
Sure! Bua?
My novel I sent you...
What...
Where did Gene go?
=Lovely Writer=
Gene? When did you get here?
I got here around noon.
Who are you looking for. Is it me?
No, I'm just grabbing a bite
and doing research for my novel.
I heard that you're sick
so you didn't do the kissing scene.
I have a sore throat,
I don't want Aey to catch my cold.
But before this, you weren't sick.
I think it's the hot weather.
There's no fever.
That's a good thing.
Go find something to eat
and take some medicine too.
Gene...
Would you stop being so polite?
It's gives me the chills.
I'm being respectful to you,
you're letting me crash at your place.
So I want to be good to you.
Whatever! Call me whatever you want.
Are you finished shooting?
Yes.
Can you give me a ride back to the condo?
Tum had to leave early
so I don't have a ride home.
What?
Sure, but I have to tell Hin first
because I gave him a ride over here.
Let's go.
Shit!!
It's okay, Gene.
How can it be okay?
Your shirt is all messed up.
It's okay, I don't have any more scenes.
But it's the crew's shirt.
I'll go get changed and then
let's go grab something to eat.
Won't they get mad?
No, it was an accident.
How about you take the shirt off
and I'll wash it off.
What are you looking at? Take it off.
Take it off here? I'm shy.
I'm just going to go wash it off!
I thought...
Just go change your shirt.
Quickly.
Wait for a minute, Hin's coming soon.
Okay.
Nubsib's also here?
I don't know which is hotter,
the sun or Nubsib.
Just one look and I melt.
Sib lives in the same condo
so he's tagging along for a ride.
Are you trying to show off
that you live in the same condo?
Like hell I am.
Get in the car now, I'm hot.
Stop making that face and hurry up!
Nubsib is hungry.
I know.
Hin, I'm sorry
but can I sit in the front seat?
I get quite car sick.
Sure!
Please?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let me get the door for you,
careful with your fingers.
Come on Hin, stop playing around.
Okay, I know.
So how's your novel coming along?
I'm just asking, no pressure.
I've written some of it.
But if you're not pressuring me
then why the hell are you asking?
So that means you're not busy?
I'm not busy like right now I'm not busy.
Could you take a look at my plot?
When did you start
wanting to become a writer?
I wanted to try writing Boy Love novels.
My plot is about the lead being a writer
while the other is the editor-in-chief!
Why don't you have Bua read it?
I think you might get something
out of talking to her more than me.
We're closer and you're my idol!
Another thing is out of all the
writers I know, you're the best.
Tell me the truth, Hin.
Fine.
She doesn't have the time to read it.
But you being my idol is not a lie.
Why do you want write Boy Love?
It's not easy!
And if you've never written it before,
you'll feel so pressured...
and forced, you've seen what happens.
I know but the Boy Love market
is so popular that I want to try it out.
I want money and fame
so things might become better.
And another thing is
there are hardly guys writing BL novels.
I want to be successful like you.
And I might meet someone
handsome like...
You talk too much.
Do you really need to choose violence?
Nubsib, look what Gene did!
E-mail it to me
and I'll take a look at it.
Really? For real?
Yeah.
Thank you so much Gene! I love
you! I'll send it as quickly as possible.
I knew choosing you as my idol
was not the wrong choice!
(#BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(I ship this couple, I can feel something
there! #SibGene #BadEngineerTheSeries.)
Hey, are you okay?
There's no need for you to overreact.
What are you looking at?
Nothing, just looking at the kimchi.
And what are you looking?
I'm looking at you, looking at me.
When did I look at you?
Right now.
Getting on my nerves again.
I wasn't trying to.
Just eat your food.
(Editor-in-Love.)
(He suddenly choked on his water.)
(Look at the mess you've made,
how did you manage to spill this.)
(I'm was so hungry, if you want to take
care of me then please wipe my lips.)
I just got back to my room, just a minute.
What did you just say?
How was the shoot today?
Did you guys finish all the scenes?
Almost all, except the kissing scene.
Why?
Nubsib said the he had a cold
and was afraid that I might catch it...
so he wanted to use the camera angle but
Mai said no and the whole scene was moved.
That's a good thing,
I don't want you to get sick.
I just find it strange but never mind.
I'm happy.
That's great that you're happy.
I so sorry I wasn't there
to look after you today.
It's totally fine, didn't you have to
go take care of something today?
Next time I won't miss out, so sorry.
Okay.
I need to get back
to it but get some rest.
Okay, I love you.
I love you too,
don't get all sentimental with me.
Okay.
(Aey is so adorable!!
#BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(Even from the side he still
slays!! #BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(That smile! Brb gonna die
#BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(Look at Namcha and Kin playing
together! Too cute #BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(Namcha is always looking at Kin,)
(I can smell love in the air
#BadEngineerTheSeries.)
(These two pics are so sweet that it makes
sugar taste bland! #BadEngineerTheSeries)
(I ship this couple, I can feel something
there! #SibGene #BadEngineerTheSeries.)
They should already kiss in this scene,
just putting their faces close
is not enough.
But that's harassment.
Believe me, it's not harassment!
Write it again.
There's a lot you need to change,
it just doesn't make sense.
But I think it has a main point.
The lead saying I love you
to the other lead...
that's the only man on this earth?
I know but the readers
want to be entertained,
if there's not only one
in this world might make it better.
People won't read it if it's too serious,
they could just read a research paper.
Fix it.
There's not enough NC, 2 chapters
with NC then 1 with none is okay Gene.
Then we're just selling sex now.
No, we're selling ships and
moments for people to sail with!
I want a lead who is always
kissing and horny! You understand?
No more!
I don't want to do this anymore, please.
Please, Bua?
Hey Gene, our university friends...
are having a party, are you free? Join us.
Wait a minute.
Are you sleeping?
Who would know that you're sleeping?
So are you coming?
Sure, but I'm free
only on Saturday and Monday.
Okay, I'll tell them.
Did you know that Jim has a girlfriend?
There's only you and me who is single now.
If you know someone
then introduce them to me.
I'm not picky.
I can't even find one myself,
like I have the time.
I'm always working.
Speaking of work,
did Nubsib leave for class yet?
I think so.
Do you have his class schedule?
I do, why?
I think I'm going to pick him up
and grab a bite.
The kid has got some serious luck.
I was right to leave him with you.
Shut up and send me the damn schedule.
Fine.
Okay, thanks.
I have to get back to work.
-Bye.
(Rice is in the cooker.)
(Eat up!)
(Does bottoming the first time hurt? 18+.)
(You should try but if you're
still under age then don't.)
(The first time hurts so much so
don't expect any pleasure from it.)
It hurts so bad.
(Beginner's Guide to Bottoming.)
(A film for you to research.)
Hello.
It's me.
Hello, Gene.
Are you done with class? Hello?
Hello.
Hello, Nubsib can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
Then why didn't you answer me?
Nothing, I was just shocked
that you called me.
Shocked that I called? Why?
I never thought that you'd call me.
Of course I'd call,
I'm on my way to pick you up.
I got your number from Tum,
I thought we'd grab a bite.
Today?
Today.
I'm very available.
Just wait there and I'll go pick you up.
Pick me up in front of my faculty.
Okay, I'll call you when I get there.
Okay, bye.
Nubsib, get in the car.
Did you wait long?
Not at all, I just got here
and you arrived.
You didn't wait long but
you're sweating all over.
Let's go to Chinatown, I want noodles.
Anything you want.
-What are you smiling at?
-Nothing.
Getting on my nerves again?
I think you're cute
so I was caught off guard.
What?
That's dangerous! Be careful.
It's because of you! Are you crazy?
You don't need to flatter me so much.
Flatter? That wasn't my intention.
It's just a compliment.
Compliment?
Should I be happy
that a guy called me cute?
Has a guy ever said you're cute?
No, only you.
I'm glad that I'm the only guy
who has said that you're cute.
(Here are some more films,
I'm afraid only one is not enough)
(but if you wanna dig deeper,
you might have to try it out LOL.)
What are you doing?
Hey!
A sex scene?
That's just rude.
It's something I'm working on,
I feel like it's not good enough yet...
so I have to change it a bit.
Do you need my help?
Help with what?
We could try those positions.
Are you mad, joking about this stuff?
It's all up to you,
if I help
you might get a better picture.
A better picture? Of what?
Wouldn't it be weird if we...
Just acting out the
positions not actually doing it.
Roleplay! Didn't you say
that you're on a deadline?
Are you for real?
If I help, you might finish early.
What?
You helped me practice my lines
so I want to return the favor.
Don't need to worry,
I learned it in a Workshop.
What do I have to do?
Just stay still.
I'll lead.
I feel strange.
You don't like it?
If you're not okay with it, I can stop.
Wait.
Why? Is this position uncomfortable?
It's very uncomfortable.
How about this?
Because if you're not comfortable,
you might get hurt.
Hurt?
What are you laughing about?
You might hurt yourself,
don't overthink it.
I wasn't thinking about anything.
Fuck! Get off! Nubsib! Enough.
I'm sorry, Gene.
Are you okay?
I understand now how the feeling is I...
I think your NC scenes have gotten better.
I understand that.
But from now,
I want hot and steamy scenes.
I think I want to reduce
the NC scenes in this novel...
and focus on the characters.
Sure, but if you can slide
them it then make it extra hot!
Try reading the western novel
I sent you the other day.
Try to adapt and apply because I think
the sexual tension will be off the charts!
Sure.
Have you ever tried reading Korean novels?
I read on social media that said that
the feedback was very good.
Stop! Hin, I already told you that
it's already been done! Shut up.
Please, Gene?
Add more in the later chapters.
Please? Add more for me.
Okay.
Hello, have you seen Nubsib yet?
He's here, gotta go.
Okay.
Nubsib.
Gene? Why did you come?
Today I'll be the one
taking you to the shoot.
Tum is busy so he had
me help look after you.
Don't worry,
I'll be your guardian for today.
Okay, my guardian.
Sib!
Oh, hello, Gene.
Where are you headed?
The shoot.
Really? Today Aey and Sib
both have scenes to shoot.
So can I tag along?
Sure, we're all going
to the same destination.
Thank you, Gene! You're the best.
Have I told you yet?
I've read your fantasy novel before,
it's really awesome.
You told me last time but thanks so much.
I really like the character, Stephan.
I wish I could be that cool.
When I was writing the novel
Stephan was my favorite character too,
and I did the most
research for his character.
Wow, writing a novel is not easy.
I think it's different for each person
but for me, none of my novels were easy.
Are you hungry? Did you eat yet?
Not yet.
What about you?
Nope.
Should we stop at a gas station?
There's still time, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
Isn't this the women's dressing room?
Excuse me,
there's a man in the dressing room.
I think our customer
went into the wrong room.
This is the women's dressing room.
Oh? Really?
Yes.
I'm so sorry, I thought it was unisex.
It's okay, Gene.
Just take it, if you feel uncomfortable
you can pay me back next time.
Thank you.
Are you hungry?
No.
Do you want to eat anything?
Anything is fine.
Just buy something you want to eat too.
Let's just say I'm feeling generous today
so I'm paying.
Gene.
From now on,
you have to be generous to me only.
That was quick.
Are you and Tum close?
I see you guys together all the time.
We're university friends so we're close.
Oh, it's like that.
So that's the reason
you and Nubsib are close?
I don't think I'm as close to him as you!
Aren't you guys university friends?
Not really, we're not that close.
I just thought that it's strange.
I'm so jealous of you.
It seems like Nubsib likes you.
What? Like me? That's not true.
Really?
You don't need to service me,
I can wipe it myself.
That's so cute,
you guys wipe each other's mouth.
Take it.
The light is almost green,
I'll eat it later.
What do you need me to do?
What should we have you do...
Should we have you ask
Tawan to be your boyfriend?
I'm so shy!
Me too.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Of course it is.
Don't you agree?
Oh, my! That's Kin!
He's so hot.
I know!
Namcha, do you still want my signature?
I do.
Go hug Kin nice and hard
then you can have my signature!
Wow! That's just fab!
Quickly, if you want it
then go hug him tightly!
Kin.
What?
It's me.
Spit it out.
I wanted their signatures...
and they said that I had to...
hug you!
You!
I'm sorry.
Maybe he likes you.
What the fuck are you playing at?
Cut!
Nubsib, can you hear me?
Push Aey's arm a bit slower.
Don't need to rush it?
And Aey, when you hug Nubsib,
I want you to really hug him, okay? Again.
Again, everyone.
Please come to your positions on set,
we're doing it one more time.
Actors are ready, sound, camera,
and action.
(Aren't you coming today?)
(Could you look after Aey?)
(Sure.)
(Thank you so much.)
Hey, Gene.
You look really good today!
I wanted to try a new look,
what do you think?
Very sharp, all the guys
can't take their eyes off you.
Guys my ass.
Oh, our friends are meeting
up on Saturday, 9:00 PM at Hotel L.
Hotel L? I think I'll drive there.
That's great and you can drop me off
on the way home.
Nubsib's become really attached to you,
he's always asking about you.
That's not true, attached like hell.
But you're letting him stay
and you don't have a problem with it.
It's come this far, you should
just let him live with you.
No! We're not close.
And another thing is you only have
one month left...
and then you gotta come
to take him back.
Really? Not close?
That's right.
Hey.
I've been living here so long...
but this is the first time
I've seen you do a face mask.
I found it in the fridge, is it yours?
I remember that you're the presenter.
You remember?
Yeah, I'll be having a small
reunion with my university friends.
I'm afraid
they'll say that I've gotten old,
I've not been getting much sleep
so can I have it?
Have you been sleeping for a long time?
About half an hour.
I think that's okay now.
Wow, time really flies!
It's almost a month.
Is there something you want to say?
Nothing!
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
How do you feel after I moved in?
I feel good.
That's all?
What response do you want?
Living with you is the best!
I don't have to hire a maid!
Are you happy now?
You're so cute.
Cute. Cute. Cute.
Hey.
Shit!
I think you're cute.
That's dangerous! Be careful.
Hey.
Nubsib's become really attached to you,
he's always asking about you.
I'm so jealous of you.
It seems like Nubsib likes you.
Cute my ass!
Have you found a new place yet?
Gather your stuff
and get ready to move out.
Let's go Sib,
go get your stuff so we can leave.
He probably really doesn't
want you to stay and bother him.
You're running your mouth again.
Why are you suddenly so mad?
Cheers!
Don't tell you're...
Gay?
Hey, Sib.
How did you get here?
Gene please behave yourself.
Did your boyfriend buy this for you?
I've been staying with
you for almost a month.
And you still don't know?
You look like you have one.
Because you're so handsome.
I know you're trying to seduce me.