Don't tell me that you're...
Or did you begin
to like guys around that time?
I'm confused.
It's okay.
Can you sleep with me tonight?
Just sleeping.
-Gene?
-Hey.
Ouch!
Gene, you're not being careful.
Sweet dreams.
But why do you want to stay here so badly?
Because I like you.
(Previously)
(Lovely Writer)
(By Wizard)
I've read the latest chapter, Gene.
Oh, my!
My heart is beating so hard!
The NC scenes are good,
like so much better!
I called you
as soon as I finished reading it!
I want to scream!
The lead is just so hot,
reading it has got me...
Like wheezing for air!
But I'm a bit curious.
Why did you change the lead's career
from being an actor...
but into a writer?
You also changed the name
from "LOVE ACTOR"
to "LOVELY WRITER."
Or are you in love?
It's nothing.
I just wanted the character
to be a writer...
because I'd be more in-depth with it.
Another thing is...
I want to write about our industry.
Are you going to throw shade at me again?
But it's okay.
Because it's gotten more fun now
and I like it too.
But don't take it too seriously, Gene.
We're writing it for entertainment.
To make it even better,
I think you need to add more NC scenes.
Guaranteed!
The readers will be so into it!
I'm sure!
Okay, I'm not going to bother you.
Keep working on the manuscript!
I'm going to hang up now,
I'm waiting to read it.
Okay. Goodbye, Bua.
(#Badengineer
They look so cute! Love them #SibAoey)
(#SibAoey #Badengineer
Look at Kinn's hand on Namcha! Dead!)
(There's no need for words
when Aoey looks at Sib)
(#SibAoey #Badengineer
it's all in his eyes, I can see it!)
Don't you ever mess with him again.
Otherwise, don't say I didn't warn you.
Who the hell do you think you are?
His parent?
Or boyfriend?
You're not!
So stop trying to tell me what to do.
In reality, you're just a damn wuss...
who's secretly in love with him
but too scared to say,
and all he can do
is harass the person he likes.
Mind your own damn business!
Just remember
that I won't let anyone bully him!
Cut!
There was wonderful! So real...
But I want another take.
This time, I want it over the top.
I'll keep it
and use it to choose from later.
As for the crew, I want a close-up shot.
Quickly!
Gene.
Oh, Aoey.
You've come today?
I had a bit of free time today.
You should come more often.
I haven't seen you in such a long time.
I also bought your novel.
Could you sign it for me?
Sure, come on.
Thank you.
With you here,
it makes me even more nervous.
You're going overboard.
Don't you have a scene to do next?
I do.
The next scene is where...
Namcha will be felt up by Kinn
in the toilet.
You've got this.
So, I think I'll...
Gene?
It's that...
You know that I like Sib, right?
It's just that...
I don't know what to do.
Should I tell Sib?
And if he's doesn't feel the same way,
I'm afraid I might lose a friend.
And he doesn't seem
to be interested in me.
So I don't know what to do.
You write these kinds of novels
so you might know what to do.
So I wanted to ask for your advice.
Or is it because Sib's a guy?
Well, if Sib likes girls,
then it wouldn't seem strange
that he wouldn't like you.
Does this mean that I'm out of hope?
Well...
Why don't you try writing how you feel
to Nubsib?
To tell how I feel?
That's so adorable of you.
Isn't "Dear John" a bit outdated?
Then...
how about sending a text from your phone?
What do you think you should I do?
I think I'm going
to try going after Sib more.
Go after him more?
Yes, go after him more.
I'll start with asking him out to eat.
It's that...
I think I'll invite Nubsib to dinner
for my birthday after the shooting.
Nubsib is staying at your condo, right?
Then after dinner,
I'll drop him off safely.
Sure.
Then...
Can you help me with something?
It's just that...
Can you help talk Sib into going with me?
Huh?
Please.
I think that you should talk
to Nubsib yourself.
Please, Gene?
-Or else...
-Aoey?
Why are you sitting here?
Shouldn't you be getting ready
for the next scene?
Did you go over your lines?
Okay.
Nubsib.
Don't let it drop this time.
Keep your energy up.
And those of you on set,
quickly change the set.
We're going to go over the schedule.
So little ques and such low budgets.
(Lovely Writer)
We'll take a break now.
I'll see you all after the break.
Let's go.
Crew and extras,
quickly grab your lunch box
and quickly eat.
You also came today?
Yeah.
Sib, here's some water.
I look over and always see you talking.
Why aren't you looking at me
while I'm acting?
I've seen it so much that I'm bored of it.
Unlike me.
No matter how long I look at you,
I can never get bored.
You should get some rest.
Maybe you should join me.
Tum is over there.
It's fine.
I'm fine right here.
Sib...
Can...
we go out for dinner tonight?
It's almost my birthday. I'll pay.
We could go to the same hotel
as last time,
and I'll drop you off at home
at Gene's condo.
Maybe some other time.
Why?
You're not going anywhere after the shoot.
And Gene's busy.
Right?
You're busy?
I...
Hey. Are you guys going to talk for long?
Hey, that group.
Come and eat or we'll run out of daylight.
Come on, Sib.
Let's go.
Kinn...
That hurts.
Good.
So your brain will remember
that you shouldn't make me angry.
You want to tell my business
to Tawan so much, right?
Fine.
Keep roll. Keep roll.
Stand a bit further from each other.
Kinn, can you be more aggressive?
As for Namcha,
like the woman from "365 days,"
act like you don't want to,
but you actually want it.
"I'm ready to be yours."
Do you get it?
Come on, let's do it again
Three, two... Action.
Let go of me!
Kinn, that hurts!
Good!
So your brain will remember
that you shouldn't make me angry.
You want to tell my business
to Tawan so much, right?
Fine.
Keep roll. Keep roll.
Kinn, I want you to be more aggressive.
More touching and more dramatic.
But this is almost rape.
From the script that I read,
Kinn wasn't that aggressive.
And doesn't Kinn become more gentle later?
Just do what I tell you to do.
They're in love.
Don't you understand soap opera vibes?
Don't ask so many questions.
Just do what I tell you.
Come on. Three, two... Action.
That hurts.
Kinn.
Nubsib, slip your hands into Aoey's shirt.
Yep, Slip right in. Slip your hands in.
Yeah, use your fingers.
Aoey, try to pull his hand out,
but you can't do it...
and get seduced by it.
Moan a bit...
Just like that...
Fabulous.
Nubsib, kiss for real.
A real juicy kiss.
Kiss.
Just like that.
Just like that, Nubsib.
Now, Aoey, I want your arms
and legs to go weak.
Act more shyly.
Try to fight him off.
Sib, I want more loving.
How was it? Did you like it?
I guarantee you
that after seeing this scene,
the fans will tear their pillows apart.
Is there something wrong?
Was my directing not good or what?
Oh, nothing.
It's just that I feel a bit hot.
I think I need to sit somewhere
less crowded.
Hey, don't go yet.
The next scene is a highlight.
I ensure you that is scene
will be so heart-wrenching.
I thought you wanted to see it.
It's okay. Please go ahead.
What's up with him?
Or is he hot because the scene I directed
was hot?
Okay, cut. That take was okay.
Is this the cushion
that everyone is saying that's so good?
Do you think it suits me?
This one is suitable for sensitive skin.
The cream is lighter and it's not thick
so it doesn't make you get pimples.
Sib has to use this
because his face is really sensitive.
What about this sunscreen?
What do you think?
This one?
I don't think it's good
if your skin is oily.
Why?
You didn't even try it yet,
so how do you know it's not good?
For some things,
you know with a slight look
and the person using it.
Are you picking on me?
No, I'm just saying the truth.
For you, you're more suitable
for another formula.
Then...
Are you free this evening?
Can you go help pick out
the one that suits me?
Sure.
What time do you want to go?
Today, shooting ends early.
How about we go to a nearby mall?
Deal, right?
See you at the parking lot. Okay?
Good work.
(Arghhhh. My main hardly ever lives.)
(My Kinn.)
(Please get some rest,
both Nubsib and Tum.)
Does Nubsib have lots of work?
(So cute.)
Yes, he does.
There's no time to rest.
Is there anything you'd like
to say to fans?
Thank you for every support.
What are you doing?
Let Tum stop the live video first.
Just a moment.
Are you going to the event
at Siam Paragon?
We'll have to see if Nubsib
is available at the time or not.
I think I can go.
Don't get me in the live.
That's it for today's live, everyone.
Just enough for those who miss him.
When we have some free time,
we'll have a long live session.
Say something before we go.
See you again, bye-bye.
Bye.
Okay, all done.
Why are you guys going live here?
Why don't you go live at home?
I don't live with him anymore.
I'm just afraid his fans might disappear.
You can do the live at my room.
Have I ever complained?
Don't get all angry at me.
Come on, let's go.
Sib.
Are you finished?
Let's go for dinner.
I already told you
that we'd do it some other time.
Can't we go today?
It's almost my birthday.
Please?
Another thing is, if you go home now,
you wouldn't know what you'd eat.
It won't take long.
I'll drop you off at your doorstep.
Please?
Please, can we go have dinner?
I'm going to go pee.
Then, I'm going with you. Let's go.
What do you think?
What?
Do you want me to go?
Gene.
If you don't want me to go,
then I won't.
Wanting to go or not,
that's up to you.
So that means that if I go,
you're okay with it?
Then take a shower and get some rest.
When I get back,
I'll try to be as quiet as I can.
Okay.
See you in front.
Sure.
Gene.
Thank you
I think that...
today, I'm going to confess my love
to Nubsib.
See you.
Hey.
What the hell are you looking at?
Nothing...
Should we go?
Of course, Nubsib's not here anymore.
Do you want to go grab a bite?
Sorry, I can't go.
I'm already going to go see someone.
Fine.
I'll go home and eat by myself.
That's all it takes to help
with how much you missed us. Bye.
Say bye-bye.
Why did you have to push me?
Then what did you just do?
I just took a story. It's for the fans.
Let's go.
I thought you were going to bail on me.
Sorry.
I was doing a live video with Nubsib.
Come on, let's go.
Wear this.
(Tum, come back and take Nick
to Teacher Durian's acting class.)
Haven't you ridden this before?
Uh, yeah.
Not really.
So I'm not really used to it.
You can hold on to my waist.
You'll be safe. I won't crash.
Okay.
Why?
Does it make you uncomfortable?
Or are you secretly crushing on me?
All hell would break loose.
Thank you for helping me choose.
It's that I see the reviews
and I'm scared to buy it.
It's always so over the top.
Actually, it's up to that person's skin.
Some might review that it's great,
while some would say it's not.
It's normal.
I buy based on reviews too.
Some of it, I used and don't see results.
I give it to the kids
in the modeling department to use.
But honestly?
I always use the same ones.
Some brands,
I've been using up to five bottles.
But you're really good at this.
You know more than me.
You're really conscious
of beauty and appearance.
You're almost prettier than a girl.
Today, you're dressing differently.
Are you changing up your look?
Why?
Is it not good?
It's good,
but it's just not like before this.
But do you like it?
Why?
Why would you ask me if I like it or not?
If you like it, then just dress like that.
You don't need to care about other people.
(Sister Tarm is calling)
Hello, Sis.
What are you doing?
What is it?
I'm in the middle of something.
What did I order you to do?
I already took Nick to his acting class.
And what next?
I already had an appointment with someone.
Why'd you order me so suddenly?
Did you tell me first?
No.
But I already did everything
you planned out.
So could I have some personal time?
What do you do with your personal time?
Is that Tam?
Can you stop acting like a child, Tum?
Sis,
I don't understand.
I did everything you told me to do.
What else do you want?
Managing the actor's lives
in a modeling agency isn't fun.
But don't you forget...
that every penny you spend comes
from that work.
You can't even do this simple task.
And that office job
as a graphic designer you want to do?
I don't think you could survive that.
And people like you...
Hey.
You can go take care of your errands.
You've been helping me out all-day.
I don't want to cause you any trouble.
Never mind.
She's always like this.
You know that.
Let's eat.
What do you think?
Do you want me to go?
Wanting to go or not,
that's up to you.
I think that, today,
I'm going to confess my love to Nubsib.
Haven't you had anything to eat yet?
Well?
Do you want to ask me something?
Ask...
Ask what?
You're always looking at me.
You have something to ask me, right?
But if the person asking is Gene...
then I can answer anything.
I wasn't...
Fine.
If you want me to ask, then I'll ask you.
How was it?
I'm fine.
Not that.
Then what?
You just went to dinner.
How was it?
It was good. The food was delicious.
If you want to try it,
we can go together sometimes.
I didn't want to know about that.
Then what else is there to know?
If you're not straightforward,
then it's hard for me to answer.
What did Aoey say?
Are you guys together yet?
Oh, about that.
And why do you think I'd be with Aoey?
Well...
Today, I saw you guys in the parking lot.
Did you see?
Yeah...
It was a coincidence.
It's not like that.
I went with Aoey...
because we had to talk about something.
Talk?
About what?
Today,
didn't I see you talking to Aoey
at the shoot?
I saw your pouting face at the shoot.
And...
did you guys get into a fight?
No.
Aoey and I are just friends.
Nothing more.
If I knew
that you were going to get jealous,
I wouldn't have gone with Aoey
in the first place.
Jealous?
Who got jealous?
I asked cause I just wanted to know.
Don't tell me you saw me and Aoey kissing
and you're overthinking about it?
Today,
I saw you and Aoey on my timeline.
And...
when I went to the parking lot,
I really thought you guys
liked each other.
Gene, you should know...
that the series wants us to promote stuff.
But...
it looks really real.
There it is.
You're jealous.
Sib.
If it doesn't look real,
then who would believe it?
As for the kiss, it's only for work.
But kissing with my feelings...
I don't want to kiss anyone...
except for you...
You don't need to get jealous of me.
I told you I wasn't.
I'll try to believe you.
What are you doing?
When you get jealous,
you like to puff your cheeks.
It's really cute, you know?
I'm going to go take a shower.
"Happy birthday to Aoey."
"I hope you'll be
your cute self forever. From Art."
Nothing tastes good.
Everything sucks.
(Studying Bakery in France.)
(If it's possible
I don't want to return to Thailand.)
(I want to stay and bake there.)
(This Saturday is your birthday.)
(Can you come home
and eat dinner with all of us?)
(Everyone at home is waiting for you.)
Cause love is not a joke...
You want to say it, but can't
Want to listen, but...
Want to listen but can't.
It's not easy and can't you say it all.
The story of love that's there.
Love is probably good
I want to tell you...
I want to tell it to you every day
so you can hear me.
The love inside.
Oh, you also came today?
I've been here since early morning.
I came really early today.
Why? I have to look after Sib.
But you're being strange, waking up early.
What compelled you out of your room?
Sib?
What does that have to do with him?
Then what would it be?
It's because I went to sleep early,
and I have to do some research
on my novel.
-Has Sib seen you yet?
-I don't know.
I don't think so.
Whatever. He'll see you soon enough
because he has an invisible GPS on you.
(Tiffy)
What's that?
I'll be right back.
I need to take this.
Are you a hamster?
You can't keep it in your cheeks.
What are you doing?
Feeding you snacks.
I know that.
I mean, why are you feeding me?
I want you to eat.
If you want to eat,
then just eat it yourself.
I'm not hungry.
But you wouldn't stop chewing on it.
Don't you have to be on set?
Almost.
I have to go change soon.
Nubsib, you can go change your outfit.
Please excuse me.
(I had Waew prepare everything,
please come back this Saturday.)
Aoey, I'm so sorry I'm late.
I was so lost
that I had to have Tum pick me up.
It was so hard to find.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It was just an ad text.
Don't overthink, Aoey.
I know you're under a lot of stress,
but you're going on set soon.
So leave everything behind
and concentrate, okay?
It just so that the director
won't bitch at us.
I'll be right back.
I'm hungry.
I'm so late. I don't know
if there's any food left for me on set.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to get the sheet from my friend.
Where do you want me to wait?
Do you want to go eat cake
in front of my university?
Cake?
Is it good?
I don't eat dessert.
But I've seen reviews
on popular pages before.
Sure, fine.
Send the location,
and I'll go wait at the cafe.
Okay.
When you hear about dessert,
you just can't stop smiling.
I'm going to go now.
Is that the person we saw on Twitter?
-I think so.
-Take pictures.
He's so cute.
Take more pictures.
It's not good to take pictures
of other people.
I'm sorry. It's just that, he's so cute.
So we wanted to take his pictures
to share in our group.
We have no bad intentions.
I understand, and I'm not debating on it.
He really is cute.
But I think you should ask
before you take photos.
Then can we take photos
of the both of you?
Gene, they want to take photos of us.
Can they?
One, two, three...
Can you both move closer?
Sure.
Look at the camera. One, two, three.
Can you take photos from my phone?
Sure.
Look at the camera. One, two, three.
Can you take our photo?
Okay.
Smile, look at the camera.
One, two, three.
Another picture, One, two, three.
-All done.
-Thank you.
You're welcome. Thank you.
-Cute.
-What?
They go to the same university as you?
How cute.
Yep.
What about you?
I hardly see you go anywhere
with your university friends.
Or do all your friends have girlfriends?
Why do you want to know?
Well, I was just asking.
If you want to ask, then ask about me.
Why would I ask
about stuff I already know?
Are you sure?
Then...
Do you know what I like?
I do...
Me.
I know you were going to say that joke.
Very smart.
You're starting to get me.
Aoey...
How are you?
I'm fine.
Is life out there hard?
I'm used to it.
If you're not okay, then come home.
I'm okay, Earn.
Happy Birthday, Aoey.
Thank you.
Mhok...
Aoey, I forgot to tell you.
I also invited Mhok over for dinner.
Our parents miss him.
I saw you're in the series together.
Mhok is always giving me updates on you.
You're still the same as always.
I'm going to go check on Waew's cooking.
Aoey and Mhok, stay and talk
until Mom and Dad get home.
Hey.
You finally came back.
Why are you always trying to run away?
Why am I always trying to run away?
Let me think.
It's because I don't want to talk to you.
And the next time you're coming,
please tell me
so that I don't have to come.
Actually,
Mom and Dad would be so happy...
if their son weren't me,
but was you instead.
And you'd probably be so happy
to part of this family.
I saw you've always wanted
to be part of this family.
Right?
There's nothing good about it.
Say what you want,
but I'm glad to see you step down
from your ego...
to care about others.
Why did you come back?
Didn't Earn tell you
that I was coming back for dinner?
She said everyone missed me so much.
Yes.
I didn't think
that it would be a bad thing,
and we haven't seen Aoey
in such a long time.
Aren't we going to eat?
If you're not,
then I'm going to eat now.
You're probably out of money.
Dad.
I really want to know...
Would you come home
if you didn't run out of money?
This is just what I thought.
But I'm not that desperate.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried about you.
You can sit on your high horse,
but don't think that what you're doing
is going to make enough money.
So you can go learn
and make that damn bakery in France.
Look at your sister.
She's never let us down nor made us worry.
It's you who are stupid...
and like to act lowly.
So?
Being what you want me to be
is uncomfortable!
You already took everything away from me!
My future, my lover, my life!
Aren't you happy yet?
Are you full?
Or if you're not,
what else do you want to eat?
Because all I have left are bones
for you to pick at.
-Aoey...
-Mind your own damn business!
Don't try and argue with me!
You're still as evil as before!
Don't you remember?
That person who said he loved you so much
tricked you!
You loved each other so much that you
tricked me that you needed cram classes.
How did that turn out?
I just gave him some money,
and he carried that money away,
closing his shop to abandon you.
What you did...
didn't fill me.
Honey.
But it embarrassed me.
That's enough.
Aoey.
If you think you're so great,
then don't ever come here again.
And if you hate me so much,
then don't think of this place as home.
Get the hell out
because I never had a son like you.
Dad...
I'll go talk to Aoey.
Aoey...
Is this another one of your schemes?
You knew if I came back
that it would be like this.
Why would you make me come back?
It's not like that.
I just wanted our family
to be together like we used to be.
The same us we used to be?
Do you know when things
were never going to be the same?
It was never the same
since you told dad about Time and I.
My life is like this because of whom?
Are you happy now, Earn?
Is it going according to your plan?
The same as always.
Mark my words.
It's never going to be the same.
Fine...
I hate you!
Back then, I was jealous of you!
Are you happy?
You're the favorite son.
You get all the good things.
I worked my ass off,
but never got anything good.
So I went ahead and told dad.
But now,
I know that I don't want it anymore.
Ever since you left,
dad won't stop pressuring me.
I never knew what you went through...
until I found out for myself.
I'm so sorry, Aoey.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you for at least being honest
with yourself.
But you want me back home...
to get dad off your back?
That's great...
and really selfish of you.
That's enough.
Calm down.
I'll take care of this.
I'll take you home.
Can you stop bothering me?
You're the one who is making this worse.
Come on. Do you want to walk?
It's dangerous.
Let go of me!
I said, let go of me!
Let go!
Let go of me.
Let go! Let go!
Let go of me!
Isn't my day already bad enough?
It's okay.
(#GeneisNotTheDriver)
(#SibGene #GeneisNotTheDriver
My ghost ship.)
(They didn't JUST start being this cute.
It's been a while.)
(I'm glad someone secretly ships them too.
I'm making a fandom soon. Fight me.)
Why did you come to see me so late?
Is there something wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
I just don't want to be alone.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
♪Happy birthday, happy birthday♪
Happy Birthday, Aoey.
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
And I wish for you
to be my cute brother like this forever.
Don't get all sentimental.
At first, I was going
to surprise you at the set.
Come on. Make a wish
and blow out the candles.
Yeah.
You took such a long time
to make your wish.
What did you ask for?
I wished for you
to be my lovely manager forever.
Wow. No doubt.
Don't cry.
Tiffie.
Can I lie on your lap?
Sure. Come on.
Aoey?
Is there something wrong?
Do you want to tell me about it?
I just wanted to lie on your lap.
Just let me lay like this for a while.
(HBD to Aoey)
(They're both so cute.)
(The writer and his actor.
(So sweet, I just can't. My ghost ship)
(#GeneisNotTheDriver
I told you that)
(#GeneisNotTheDriver)
(#SibGene #GeneisNotTheDriver
My ghost ship.)
(They didn't JUST start being this cute.
It's been a while)
(I'm so glad someone
secretly ships them too)
(#GeneisNotTheDriver They are
more real than the main ship. #SibGene.)
Gene, are you at the condo with Sib?
Yeah.
Is there something wrong?
I'll meet you there.
From now on,
be more careful of what you post.
There's something I want to warn you.
I want you to stay away from Aoey.
Thank you for looking after Aoey for me.
It's alright.
Hey. What happened?
What made you come home?
I thought you already forgot
about your family.
Gene, when did you come home?
This is Sib.
Standing right next to his father.
Please excuse me.