You know that I like, Sib right?
Nubsib, kiss for real.
But kissing with my feelings.
I don't want to kiss anyone...
except for you.
Get the hell out
because I never had a son like you.
What did I order you to do?
You can go take care of your errands.
Gene.
Are you at the condo with Sib?
I'll meet you there.
Oh, you are awake?
Lately, you've been waking up early.
I've been sleeping early.
I only slept at 4:00 AM last night.
Four AM? 4:00 AM is not early.
Why don't dry your hair well.
Just let it dry.
Well, what are you doing here manager.
There's no filming set today.
I have a photo shoot.
Do you want to go? Let's go together.
Can I?
Why not. They will capeted you.
You've got more Fan on twitter!
Don't tease me.
Let me get change and put on contact lens.
But Gene, you didn't have breakfast yet.
There's some food in the kitchen.
Nubsib bought one for you.
You can eat first.
I have to talk with Nibsib a little while.
Then, I'll eat later.
From now on, you have to be careful
of what you post.
I warn you
because it's not a big deal yet.
But if Tam know it,
it's bad for eveyone.
I understand but it's hard to do.
How is it hard? Just not too revealing.
Gene is cute. What's wrong
if I want to show him off?
Oh, you are so stubborn.
Why don't people see this side of you?
In front of Gene, you're so polite.
Tum.
I'm just joking.
=Lovely Writer=
Hey, you get jealous.
Jealous? I'll kick you.
I'm so sorry for my friend. So sorry.
I will go grab some coffee.
Hurry up.
If Nubsib doesn't see you
after he finishes his photo shoot.
He will blame me.
We're not together. Don't exaggerate.
They're cute.
They look like a family.
I'm not that old.
I'm just a beautiful sister.
Sure! I see wrinkles on your forehead.
You need more Botox.
So harsh, Tum!
Thank you for taking care of Aey
last time.
No problem. Where did you go?
Gosh. Her face is getting greasy.
Makeup artist, please check her face.
Where is the makeup artist?
They are in the restroom.
Let me get some tissue in my bag.
No, no, I will take care of it.
I'm here. Tum, I'm here.
Makeup artist
ate spicy salad this morning.
So...
Please pick them up
from the restroom. Thank you.
Okay, come on.
Ice latte and ice americano are ready.
180 baht, please.
Sir, sir.
What?
180 baht for 2 coffee please.
There you go.
And may I have one green tea as well?
Hey, you don't need to pay. I can pay.
Think of it as a payback
that you let me in your series.
It's not that big of a deal.
May I sit here?
Okay.
We rarely talk to each other.
That's right. We just cross path often.
How old are you?
I'm almost 26.
Really? You look young.
I thought you are in high-school.
Don't exaggerate.
Are you done with photo shoot?
I'm on a break. Only one more set to go.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you choose the Boy Love series?
My sister urge me to cast.
She is a Love Boy Fans
and she is your Fan.
She wanted me to bring a book
to get your autograph.
Are you okay?
No, I just feel weird.
When someone like my novel.
You don't have to feel weird.
Your novel is quiet popular.
It's ice green tea.
Thank you.
Because I'm a man.
I didn't see it strange.
I will get your autograph next time.
Okay.
Shall we go inside?
I have to give Tum this coffee.
Gene.
I would like to warn you about something.
I want you to stay away from Aey.
What do you mean?
Did Aey do something bad to you?
Never, why?
If Aey did something bad to you,
I'm so sorry for him.
If he really did bad thing to me,
why you have to say sorry for him?
When I first saw you,
I thought you're quiet.
You keep to yourself.
Just like writers usually are!
To be honest, I thought
it's just a stereotype.
Writers are just human.
Not everyone is like that.
But sometimes, I don't like when
someone bother me when I work.
That's true.
Nubsib!
Staffs are looking for you,
didn't you know?
What, I just go get coffee.
Gene, don't forget what we talked about.
Don't forget what we talked about!
Talk about what?
Nothing.
Mhok's sister want me to sign on the book.
Gene, Don't talk to stranger.
It's dangerous.
I'm not 10 years old.
But it seems like it.
I will kick you.
Let me help you.
Don't touch me.
Oh, my gosh.
Ouch!
What's wrong with your car?
I don't know.
The car isn't starting.
Why don't you use oil...
Stop it, that's too old.
Let me see.
Can you do it?
Move.
It's hot.
Tiffy.
Should I sew it first?
You can do that?
You are talented.
You can do girly things too.
It's not weird.
No, its not.
Who would have known.
Don't forget. I didn't have
the car repair skill like you.
That's true.
Okay. Done.
Thank you.
You've been busy
taking care of other's face...
that you forgot to take care of your face.
I often helped my father
fix a car when I was young...
because my family owned the garage.
You like it? Fixing a car is...
Girls don't seem to like.
I like it.
I don't know why.
It's just feel cool.
I envy that your family understand...
and happy of what you like.
It's not like that.
Believe it or not, I used to date a girl.
Maybe it's because
I went to all girls' school,
so I didn't find it strange.
But my mom,
she was not okay when I told her this.
So, I moved to Bangkok...
because I don't want mom
to feel uncomfortable.
What exactly do you like?
I don't know.
I like the one who make me feel good.
Isn't it enough?
How about your mom?
It's not important.
She's not with me anymore.
I just came back from my mom's funeral.
Oh, I didn't know about it.
It's okay.
I didn't tell anyone about this.
I lived with Tam since we were young.
Both my parents pass away by an accident.
At that time, I was still a child...
Tam become head of the family.
For me, I did everything I could.
Sometimes, I think
why did I have to grow up so fast?
I have to be mature.
I just wanted to act like a kid sometimes.
And not have to worry like other kids...
but I could never do that.
The car started. It's time to go.
This is yours and this is mine.
This is also yours.
That's it!
This is not mine.
I did not buy this.
I bought one for you.
For me, why did you buy it for me?
You always drink coffee.
I want you to try something else.
No, you can have it.
Its good. Do you want to try?
You can try mine.
Try.
Try it.
Just try.
This is yummy.
It's like you kiss me.
What? When did I kiss you?
Never mind.
I think, I will go back home
two to three days.
Stay over?
Two nights. Can you stay by yourself?
What if I say no?
Then, I'll ask, how old you are.
I feel lonely.
Can you watch my room?
If I miss you, can I text you?
If its not important, I'll not reply.
Gene.
That's mine and this's yours.
But you can have both.
Because my bottle was yours
since you drink it.
Hey.
Oh, gosh.
You like teasing me. What brings you here?
I thought you forgot the family.
I had a cake recently.
I saw Foi Thong cake so I thought of you.
I have to thank the cake.
Is this Foi Thong cake?
No, it's cereal cake.
I thought you bought it for me.
Your blood sugar will go up again.
It's okay to eat once in a while.
I know you're naughty since the old day.
But our body is not stable,
let me help you take care of what you eat.
I'm so happy. Please take care of mom.
Sure. Let's post a story.
Okay, okay.
So cute. What are you doing?
I'm writing an article.
I have to submit this week
and I've not finish yet.
What is the article about?
It's about gender
diversity in Thai dramas.
This has your Boy Love series too.
Oh, is this Boy Love Fans pioneer.
It's good that you're here
so that I can ask questions.
Because I think you would
understand better than me.
I don't know much about it.
As you know,
Boy Love series is under focus.
Mainly, it doesn't really drive any point.
It's just a fantasy of love.
But what you said, it works.
Let's have dinner at home
so we can discuss.
They all miss you. Especially your father.
I told him to call you
but he's just stubborn.
Of course, please make
me something delicious.
Okay, I'll make a full table.
-Sure.
-Sure
-I will go upstairs to unpack my stuff.
-Yes.
Love fantasy.
Gene, eat up.
These are all your favourite.
You look so skinny.
I want you to see me
when I stay at my condo.
You will say
"Gene, please don't eat anymore."
The frozen food doesn't count!
Don't pretend you know it all.
Come on, mom, look at him.
It's easy to eat.
When I am writing the novel,
I don't like to go anywhere,
my idea will be lost.
Just an excuse! They have delivery app.
Enough, what he said is right.
You have to take care of yourself.
You're getting older and older,
who will look after you?
You seem like it'll be difficult
for you to find the partner.
Right, mom.
You have to think of
yourself when you're old.
Mom and dad will not
stay with you forever.
You're so mean, K. Run.
If you only write the novel,
I think you should come back home.
I saved money for it.
It'll just be deserted.
That's okay. Just leave it there.
You can stay there when you visit Bangkok.
I've been busy recently.
My novel is being made to a series.
Let's decide later.
Gene, who is the actress for your series?
New actress.
It calls "Lead", not actress.
Don't forget mom when you're famous.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
Who can forget you!
-Yeah, yeah, me too.
-Me too.
You forget me for sure.
Let's eat.
(#Nubsin.)
(I agree with Nubsib.
Gene is so cute. #Nubsib.)
(Awww, sweet #Nubsib.)
(Captain takes a lead, crew
members can stop #Nubsib.)
(Are you going to sleep, yet?)
(Not yet. What's up?)
(I miss you.)
(Joking?)
(If you mess around don’t text me)
(I told you I will not
reply if its not important.)
(But you're replying.)
(I thought its important.
I'll not reply anymore.)
(You're so mean to me.)
(Mean? It's late, let's go to bed.)
(I'm not sleepy.)
(Cal I call?)
(Nope.)
(Please don't post your picture so often.)
(You've got a lot of followers)
(I don't want anyone else to see.)
(What's wrong with you.)
(I want to throw up)
(Sleep?)
(Have a good night.)
Gene.
Yes.
Whose cereal cake is this?
It's Auntie Orn.
Why don't you give it to he?
Okay, then, I'll go now.
Is Auntie Orn home?
She's always at home. You should go now.
Gene.
Gene, don't go back to sleep.
Hey, Gene.
Oh, Nueng. Why are you honking?
Sorry, sorry. You come here to see my mom?
Yes.
I just drop her off.
Ah, you're not going to the office?
I stopped by to get some
documents and drop my mom off.
I'm about to go.
Oh, handsome. Long time no see.
Na "Run and Lung" Teep must miss you.
Are you free tonight?
Let's eat at my house.
My mom must be so happy.
I have to ask my family first.
I've plan to stay only two nights.
Oh, Please invite Na'Run
and Lung'Teep too.
Is jab here?
Bring him with you.
I want to meet everyone.
I will ask my family.
Okay, I have to go to the meeting.
See you tonight.
Gene, since when have you been here?
What are you looking at?
This photo was taken
at the end of last year.
Nubsib is the one who
standing next to father.
Nubsib?
Can you remember Nubsib?
Gene.
Nubsib.
He came back from overseas last year.
I remember.
Nubsib is always asking for you.
He is in the university
and staying in the condo.
Otherwise, you should meet him.
He is an actor.
He is super busy
and rarely come back home.
I see him on the internet often.
Have you seen him?
Like I said, you're the same age.
So, you remember.
I'm old, I can't remember anyone.
Nubsib ask me to use his aunt's surname...
because his father doesn't
support him to become an actor,
but I don't want to stop him as well.
Oh, is it Auntie Orn' surname?
Yes, it's my previous surname.
Gene.
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Nothing.
I think I have to go.
Oh, you just arrived.
I realize that I have something urgent.
I have to clear it.
May I give you a hug?
I missed you.
I bought this one for you.
Thank you.
Gene.
Gene, please come visit Auntie often.
I miss you.
(What's wrong?)
(Answer me please. I'm worried about you.)
Gene.
You said you will stay home
for two nights.
Go pack your stuff
and move out of my condo tomorrow.
Why?
You said I could stay with you.
You have several rooms.
You don't need to stay with me.
You remember who I was...
Did you remember from the beginning?
You know, I can't remember you.
Why don't you tell me?
Shit!
I have a reason.
The reason is
you're having fun lying to me.
If you weren't Auntie Orn's son,
I would punch you.
Please do.
Don't challenge me.
I didn't.
I know that I'm wrong.
If you punch me and you feel better,
then go ahead.
But could you please listen to me?
Get out of my room.
Can't you listen to me?
I don't want to hear anything.
I don't want to see your face either.
I don't want to be a stupid
to be fooled by you again.
I never think you're stupid.
Whatever!
Get out right now.
Your stuff will be pick up by Tum.
If we still not talk,
I'll not go anywhere.
What else do you want to lie about?
I'm not lying,
I told you I have a good reason.
Do you think, I still believe the person
who has always fooled me?
If you don't go, I'll call the security.
-Move.
-Gene.
I told you to move.
Gene, where will go you?
Gene, Gene.
Move.
If you don't go, I will go.
Gene, wait. Please listen to me.
(Nubsib Missed call.)
Why are you barking so much?
Gene.