I hope you can stay away from Aey.
(Previously On Lovely Writer)
The car can be started.
We can proceed now.
I need to go home for three days.
The one beside his father is Nubsib.
Gene.
Nubsib.
You remember who I am, right?
You remember since the beginning, right?
Yes.
If you won't leave, I will!
Gene, wait!
(Incoming call from Nubsib)
Ying.
Get the stick.
I'm going to punish you.
You know I'm worried about you, right?
You just disappeared like that.
Do you know how I feel?
Gene.
Hello, Jap.
Hello, Nubsib.
I know where Gene is.
Where is he?
Tell me.
I think he is at the garden mansion.
-Garden mansion?
-Yes, my grandfather's house.
Gene likes to go there
to get inspiration for his novel.
Send me the location.
I'll leave now.
Okay.
Wait, Nubsib.
What is it?
I'll leave my brother to you.
Okay.
I'll take good care of him.
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love.
Just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
=Lovely Writer=
Nubsib.
Son, where are you?
Come out.
Nubsib.
Where is he hiding?
Here?
Nubsib.
Gene! Why are you trespassing?
Let's go.
Do you want to play together?
Do you know how to play football?
Gene, I'm going to tell mom.
What is your name? I'm Gene.
Nubsib.
Nubsib?
Then,
do you want to play together, Nubsib?
Nueng, come here.
Thank you.
Are you tired?
The field is so big and you are so tiny.
But you ran well just now.
By the way,
what were you doing hiding there?
I don't want to attend piano lessons.
Why?
Playing the piano is cool.
My teacher always scolds me and
grabs me when there's no one around.
It's not fun at all.
Have you told your parents?
But Mom thinks I'm naughty and impatient.
Maybe she doesn't know about it yet.
Do you want me to tell her?
Nubsib.
Do you know you are wrong?
Do you?
Ying.
Get the stick.
I'm going to punish you.
You know I'm worried about you, right?
You just disappeared like that.
Do you know how I feel?
Gene.
Aunty, I was the one
who invited Nubsib to play.
He did nothing wrong.
If someone needs to be punished,
you can punish me.
Gene.
I'm sending Gene back.
Did Gene cause trouble?
No.
Gene is a good boy.
I'm just here
to get to know Gene's parents.
Oh, thank you.
I'm Orn.
My house is just over there.
Thank you, Orn.
I'm Run.
I just moved here.
How nice is it for us
to get to know each other?
Our kids can play together in the future.
I'll go home first.
Anyway, thanks for sending Gene back.
You're welcome.
I'll go home first.
Please play with Nubsib again.
-Thank her.
-Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Nice to meet you.
-What is his name?
-Nubsib.
Gene, send your friend off.
Remember to close the door
when you come back.
Gene.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
Come and play again tomorrow.
Nubsib.
Let's go home.
O Noi Ook.
Come on.
Gene, you'll be the ghost catcher.
Turn over and face the wall.
Count to ten slowly.
Go.
I'm starting the count.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine.
Get ready.
Ten.
Hey!
Be quiet.
Let's go and play games.
Let's go. Forget about him.
He won't get angry even if we leave.
He will be fine
after a while even if he gets angry.
Let's go.
It's fun. Let's go and play.
Nueng.
Jap.
Gene.
Walk faster.
Look. Why are you walking like that?
It's like you are going to suicide.
We have to be quick.
Is the opponent hacking?
I'm sure they are using cheats.
Shoot, there are three of them.
We are doomed.
Get ready to die.
I'm going to save you.
Wait for a while.
Jap, go to the other side.
Why are you hitting me?
Take another route.
I was hiding and got spotted.
I escaped.
Hurry, run.
Jap, your left.
Come out, don't get killed.
Jap, I think I heard footsteps just now.
Something's wrong with your ears.
Don't disturb me.
I'm trying to focus.
Maybe it's Nubsib.
If he knows we sneaked out...
It's fine, Gene.
It's just a prank.
Besides, he is too young.
He can't play with us.
We are not kids.
Do you think we should play
a childish game like hide-and-seek?
Darn. Jap, run.
I'm running.
Careful, on your right.
I know.
The enemy is coming. Hide.
Found you.
You're here.
Here, I bought it for you.
You like this, don't you?
Let's keep playing.
Are you angry with me?
Do you want to play in my room tonight?
I have a lot of toys.
Do you want to go?
You're still angry at me?
Then...
I'll count to ten.
If you're still angry, I'll ignore you.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight,
nine, ten.
How dare you enter my lair?
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Take that!
Gene.
Gene!
What are you doing, Nubsib?
Take that.
I want to play too.
Give it back.
Nubsib, give it back.
-I want to play too.
-Give it back.
-No. No!
-Give me.
Why did you do that?
If you do it again,
I won't let you play with me anymore.
I did it
because I wanted to play with you.
What's wrong?
Both of you are so noisy.
I can't even work.
Nubsib tried to take away my toys.
I just wanted to play with you.
Why couldn't you just tell me nicely?
You wouldn't listen.
Gene.
Why didn't you let him play?
I haven't done anything yet
but Nubsib didn't tell me nicely.
I'll take it for you later,
but you need to wait until Gene is asleep.
Gene.
Share it with him. Play with him together.
Look at me.
Play well together.
Go!
That's it!
Gene.
Sorry.
Is something on your mind?
Oh, it's nothing.
Oh, what's wrong with the kids just now?
They were so loud.
Oh, just a quarrel between kids for toys.
Kids are all like that. It's nothing.
Honey.
Do you think the relationship...
between our son
and the neighbor's son is too close?
It's normal.
Don't over-think.
It's nothing.
(Two Years Later)
Gene, why are you keeping your things?
Nubsib.
I...
Gene, you can tell me anything directly.
I have to study at another place.
I have to stay at the school too.
I'll try to come back frequently.
Nubsib, don't be sad.
You can sleep here tonight.
Are you still angry at me?
All right.
Then...
Is this all right?
I'm counting to ten.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Sorry.
Nubsib. Nubsib.
Nubsib, where are you?
Come out, son.
Nubsib.
Dear, hurry up!
All right.
It's getting late. Hurry up.
Wait, I forgot my bag.
-Everything's here, honey.
-All right.
Jap, are you done packing?
-Have you pack up everything?
-Yes.
Gene, it's time to leave.
Dear, what did you forget again?
Is everyone ready?
Yes.
All right.
When will we reach there?
Dear, you didn't forget anything, right?
No. It's all here.
Let's go.
Get ready, kids.
Are you ready, Gene? Jap?
We're leaving.
(Nubsib 31 Missed Calls)
This bottle is yours.
But it's fine, you can take both,
because my bottle
has been yours ever since you drank it.
What's going on with all the barking?
Where did you come from?
Where are you from?
Mr Gene.
I miss you.
How did you find this place?
Aunty Run told me.
Are you still angry at me?
Mr Gene.
I don't want to talk to you.
Can't you listen to my explanation?
I want to be alone.
I like you.
What a funny joke. Happy?
You can go back if you're happy.
I like you.
-I hope you...
-Since the day you left me,
you made me realize that I liked you.
Is it that day
when you didn't even send me off?
I...
Enough. Not another word.
That day,
I waited for you at the old place.
The place where we first met.
I hope you will change your mind
and look for me like you did in the past.
I waited for a long time...
but you didn't appear.
Nubsib.
Nubsib, where did you go?
Why didn't you send Gene off?
Nubsib.
I'm asking you a question.
Why aren't you replying?
Gene.
I missed you.
No.
That's not all.
I wanted you to come back.
I want to be your only one.
I want that you will only be hugged by me,
only miss me and only love me.
Do you believe what I say?
About you liking me?
Yes.
Since then?
Why are you still lying?
You were so young at that time.
How could you like anyone?
I like you and that's the fact.
I don't understand at that time,
but I'm sure about it now.
I told you back then, didn't I?
If you still don't believe me,
I have many ways to let you know that.
No.
There's no need.
What is the reason...
for lying to me about not having a place
to stay and not having a car then?
Because I wanted to be together with you.
If I didn't say that,
could I still live with you?
If you've told me you are Aunty Orn's son,
I would even let you stay for a year.
If I told you that,
how would you treat me?
You should know.
I don't want you to be my brother.
I'm not forcing you to believe me.
You can confess to me...
when you believe me in the future.
Fine.
I want you to prove what you said then.
I'm sure it would be romantic
if this is a novel.
But now,
you should know it, right?
What you did was wrong.
If you still lie to me,
I'll definitely beat you up.
I'm talking about your personality.
Don't pretend to be a good kid.
Just say whatever's on your mind.
Like right now.
Say anything that comes to you.
What does this expression mean?
If you can't say it,
how am I going to believe you?
Okay.
I want to kiss you.
I want you.
Darn it!
What are you talking about?
You wanted me to say it, right?
Well...
You don't have to say everything out.
Hey.
Let me tell you something.
I patted the dog's head just now.
You are kissing the dog now.
Then...
Let's kiss the dog together.
Taking advantage of me.
Gene.
Do you know?
Since you left,
I've been very lonely.
Now that we can be together again,
don't disappear again.
As the car started to move,
he kept looking at the rear-view mirror.
But he didn't see the person
he wanted to see in the end.
He felt sad like he had lost something.
That separation is still memorable
in his mind.
But now,
the time they spent in the past
has resurfaced again.
As for the memories that are fading,
they become clear again.
They meet again
and relit their affection for each other.
Although the way
they meet again isn't considered joyful,
it made him realize...
the part that he lost
for quite some time in the past...
has come back to hold him again.
But you know it, right?
(On Next Episode)
What you did was wrong.
So,
I'll give us another chance to start over.
But I won't allow you
to stay in my apartment.
We can't stay together?
Darn, that's enough.
Hello.
Nubsib, can you take a picture with Aey?
Can you wait for a while?
We are taking a photo
of Gene and Nubsib together.
-You like Nubsib.
-If I...
You knew I like Nubsib
but you still like him too.
You're so bad, Gene.