Gene. (Previously On Lovely Writer)
I like you.
I'm not forcing you to believe me.
You can confess to me
when you believe me in the future.
Let me tell you something.
I patted the dog's head just now.
You are kissing the dog now.
Then...
Let's kiss the dog together.
Do you know?
Since you left, I've been very lonely.
Now that we can be together again,
don't disappear again.
-Hello.
-Hello, Nubsib.
How is it?
Did you talk to each other?
Gene has cooled off, right?
Tell him to talk to me.
Is he angry at me too?
Gene is not angry at you.
Don't worry.
How could he not be angry at me?
I was the one
who brought you into his house.
Gene asked you
to pick a souvenir that day.
You should know that
he was planning to go home.
Why didn't you find an excuse to stop him?
Unless...
You let Gene go home purposely?
I do not need to explain to you.
You just have to know that I love Gene.
Come on.
You should be embarrassed.
Gene is right to get angry at you.
Just wait.
I'll tell Gene that you lied to me too.
I'll tell him you don't usually
stay in the agency's dorm.
You'll say that you are using the room
when my sister wanted to use it.
Also, the casting of this drama.
You knew it was Gene's production, right?
Don't worry.
There's nothing else.
Good to hear.
Take good care of my friend.
-I'll hang up.
-Okay.
Why did you come out?
I'm out to take my clothes.
It's so dark out here.
You should tell me before you came out.
It's dangerous.
Are you worrying about me?
When did you wake up?
I heard the door opened.
You brought me to bed?
Yes.
I carried you.
It's cold here.
It's better if you hug me when you sleep.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
If you're hungry,
what do you want to eat?
We can drive out to eat.
There's a small market nearby.
Can you eat something there?
Yes.
Is this your car?
This?
You fetched me with this at the hotel.
Yes.
Get on.
Are you waiting for the rain?
Okay.
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love.
Just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
=Lovely Writer=
What do you want to eat?
Order for me.
Sure.
Aunty.
Get me Red Pork Noodles
without dumplings.
Also, get my brother special vermicelli.
Sure, please wait a while.
What's wrong?
What's with your expression?
Don't tell me...
You don't like vermicelli?
My brother?
Isn't that right?
I've told you.
I don't want to be your brother.
If it's not my brother,
what do you want me to call you?
Do you still have to ask?
Boyfriend.
Nubsib!
What are you talking about?
We have a 5-year-old gap.
Calling you my brother is right.
I don't know whether it's right.
But if you call me your brother again,
you'll be punished.
Punished?
I'll kiss you.
You wouldn't dare.
Try calling me then.
Brother Nubsib.
What are you trying to do,
Brother Nubsib?
Do you want to be kissed?
-Brother Nubsib.
-Try sating it again.
Enough, Nubsib.
Don't be naughty, Brother Nubsib.
Kids, what are you fighting about?
The vermicelli is here.
Thank you.
It's all because of my brother.
He's so naughty.
Talking back to me.
That's how brothers are.
Just tolerate each other.
But you are the elder brother.
You should be nice to him.
Your brother looks familiar.
Is he a star?
Oh, I remember.
Brother Nubsib.
I'm going to kiss you.
Is it really you?
May I take a picture with you?
I want to put it on my stall.
Lad, help me take the picture.
Sure.
Ready.
Aunty, relax.
You don't have to be so stiff.
I'm very relaxed, lad.
I'm taking the picture then.
One, two, three. Okay.
Another one. One, two, three.
Again. One, two, three.
Okay.
Thanks, lad.
I'll print it out and frame it.
Then, I'm putting it on my stall.
As I've said before,
brothers should tolerate each other.
It's all right, Aunty.
That's how my boyfriend is.
He likes to make a ruckus when he's angry.
Hey, Nubsib!
Lad, don't be so fierce.
Your boyfriend is so handsome.
He's even a star.
You are so lucky
to have such a handsome boyfriend.
I won't bother you two anymore.
Just tell me if you need anything.
Oh, so cute.
Let me pinch both your faces. So cute!
-Thank you.
-Okay.
How's that not bothering us?
You.
Stop saying things like that.
We are not related in any way.
People will misunderstand.
It's all right.
We will be lovers in the future.
Where did you get your confidence from?
You said you like me before.
As long as you admit it,
I'll be your boyfriend.
Actually, I'm the only one
who can pinch your face.
If you come any closer,
I'll kick you off the bed.
Can't I hug you?
If you come any closer,
I'll tell Aunty Orn.
Hey.
Yes?
During the day,
I remember the times when we were young.
Do you still remember that?
We used to have conflicts.
You got angry at me because
you thought Aunty Orn loved me more.
That was so childish.
Really?
What's wrong?
You pretend to forget that now?
I only remember that
you want to marry into my family.
What? No.
Don't you remember?
I don't, because it didn't happen.
It did happen.
You said you wanted to
marry into my family when you grow up.
I was already in fifth grade
when we first met.
I wasn't a clueless child.
Stop this nonsense.
I...
What?
I'm very happy.
You came back.
Since the day you moved away,
Nueng and I got sent to study
in the United States by my father.
I felt lonely.
New friends,
a new social circle and a new place.
You never had
a relationship with someone else?
I did.
But I knew that wasn't the right person.
I didn't know why.
There were many people around me.
But I still felt lonely.
Until one day,
my mom sent me a photo of you and Jap
at Aunty Run's birthday party.
I felt extremely excited to see you again.
You were so cute
wearing the school uniform.
The memories of our childhood
resurfaced in my mind,
including my feelings for you.
After that day,
I found Jap and asked him about you.
I decided to ask my father
to send me back.
Jap!
When I saw you again,
I realized
my loneliness all this time...
was because you weren't by my side.
It was there since you left me.
I missed you a lot. Do you know that?
Can I kiss you?
What?
Right now?
It's just the two of us.
Did you buy food for all the neighbors?
Sit down.
Hey.
Yes?
It's time for you to go back, right?
That's not what I meant.
You need to go on set and study as well.
Why are you taking the trouble
to drive here and there?
It's not a trouble at all.
I'll be wherever you are.
It's just that simple.
Let's go back tomorrow then.
Fine by me. I'll follow you.
Hey,
going back doesn't mean
you get to stay at my apartment.
You can go back to your own house.
Why are you chasing me away again?
I'm not chasing you away.
But you know
what you are doing is wrong, right?
So,
I'm giving us a chance
to start all over again.
Give each other some space.
Understand?
Didn't you say you will wait
until I trust you again?
Do you know?
I don't want
to be separated from you at all.
Hurry up and be a good kid,
so I can trust you again
as soon as possible then.
At that time,
I want you to hold me tight
and say that you love me out loud.
Let me see what you've bought.
Let me know when you've arrived.
Okay.
Drive safe.
Text me if there's anything.
-Gene.
-Yes?
I might change my decision to leave.
Just leave then.
I'm leaving.
Changed your mind?
No.
Return me my key card.
I thought you've forgotten about it.
Impossible.
Your memory is so good.
Of course.
You may leave.
Bye.
(Nubsib)
Have you arrived?
Yes.
Really? Turn on your camera
and show me your room.
No way.
Why not?
It's better
if you are here to see it yourself.
Can't I just see it now?
If you see it now,
you wouldn't feel like coming anymore.
You can come to my room at any time.
Then, when is your shoot tomorrow?
Around 2:00 PM. Are you coming?
I'm meeting the chief editor tomorrow.
I might not make it.
If you can make it,
come and pick me up at school.
Come on.
Where's your million-dollar sports car?
Why are you laughing? Is it funny?
Won't you turn on the camera?
Why not? Can't I have a glance at it now?
Not even if I pester you?
No.
But I'm not hungry yet.
Or, do you want to cook for me?
Gene, please sit.
How is it? Have you eaten?
Oh, not yet.
But I've promised Hin
to eat together after this.
That's good.
Let's finish this soon so you may eat.
About this,
I've marked them in red at the back,
including the details.
Have a look when you go back.
Okay.
Then, near the end,
I think it's quite stressful.
Oh, I wanted to focus on the development
of the characters' relationship.
It's like this, both the characters
knew each other when they were young.
Is it?
I'm worried
it will be too serious for the readers.
And you were on the money
for those sex scenes.
Why did you remove them?
I think the story's development...
is already a romantic one
up to this point.
I don't want to add the sex scenes
because I'm worried it might be too much,
and affects the whole story.
It won't be too much.
It's been a long time since the last one.
Now that there's a development,
just put it in.
Think of it as a bonus for readers.
Right now,
everyone is living a stressful life.
Right?
Make life better, Gene.
Make it better.
Then, I'll add it in the next chapter.
Yes, that's right. I think it's good.
It needs to be juicier.
Get the person
who taught you to teach you again.
There's no such person.
Your reaction proves that I'm right.
I'm sure of it.
Come, bring the things here.
Be careful. Put it here.
This...
Big boss wants me to give it to you.
These are the latest BL novels.
Bring them all back.
I'll be leaving. Bye.
Okay.
See you.
Gene.
How are you recently?
I missed you.
Take me to meet Nubsib.
Did you miss me or Nubsib?
I missed both of you.
How are you recently?
You just had a meeting with Bua?
I'm still the same.
Bua wants me to write more sex scenes.
Honestly,
why should I write so many such things?
Especially when this topic
became so controversial recently.
Perhaps sex is something
that occurs naturally?
Just think of it
as a useful plot in the story.
The readers will understand.
Also, brother, the juicier it is,
the more it sells.
Like the last book
that Bua wanted me to add sex scenes in.
I don't think there's any story at all.
I think you can look at it
from another angle, brother.
Bua is the representative
of the publisher, right?
She knows what readers like.
If that's what the readers like,
she will want to sell the same genre.
But I think it's bad.
Do you know? I feel bad
every time I write something like that.
If the readers like my novel,
I hope they like them for the plot
and not the sex scenes inside.
If I have to say,
you need to balance
the things you want to express...
and mix them together after consideration.
You don't have to remove the sex scenes.
If it's required,
you should write it into the story
and make it more purposeful.
In the end,
I think readers will know what it means.
If you are writing a novel about sex
but there's no sex inside,
don't you think it's a bit weird?
Yes, I understand.
You are right.
Yes.
By the way,
I think you've grown up a lot.
You are more mature too.
What about your novel?
Are you still writing it?
I'm still writing, brother.
But I have a huge problem
with my vocabulary.
I find it hard to write recently.
Be confident.
There.
Let me know if you need help.
No matter what,
you are always my brother.
Okay, brother.
Sorry to interrupt.
Gene, could you give me your autograph?
-Is this the wrong book?
-No.
Can you sign it for me, Gene?
Sign beside Nubsib's autograph.
Right here.
Thank you so much.
I have your novel too
but I didn't bring it.
I'm bringing this magazine everywhere.
I'll bring the novel to you for
an autograph if there's a chance, Gene.
Wait, girl.
By the way,
how did you get Nubsib's autograph?
I met Nubsib coincidentally.
I told him I'll get Gene to sign beside
him and he signed it for me. How cute.
Oh, okay.
Wow. That's impressive.
Gene, can you sign this for me?
But I don't have
Nubsib's autograph beside.
-Gene, can you sign it for me?
-No!
Fine.
You are so famous now.
You can't even take a joke.
Does drinking make you full?
Be careful, Gene.
Nubsib.
Yes. It's me.
Why are you in that unit?
I bought it from the previous owner.
Are you crazy?
Don't worry about my money.
I know. But that's your money.
Don't you feel bad about spending it?
It's worth it to me.
If I knew
you are going to buy the unit next to me,
I'll rent mine to you.
I'll sell this unit then.
You lunatic.
Don't be angry.
I bought this unit a long time ago.
When was it?
Last year. I was planning to move here.
Coincidentally, I found out your novel
was going to be adapted into a series.
You...
Yes.
You wouldn't get angry
about me moving here, right?
I just want to be closer to you...
so I feel more relieved.
Actually, I'm not angry at you.
But you should understand, right?
You understand why
I asked you to move out.
I understand.
Although I've moved here,
I guarantee...
I'll not disturb you.
I'll get your permission
every time I enter your place.
I apologize for everything
that has happened in the past.
I'm happy that you understand.
Can I kiss your face then?
You haven't had any sleep yet, right?
Your eyes look tired.
Yes.
Go and sleep.
Okay.
Good night, then.
Good night.
I'll buy you dinner next time.
No, I'm the one who should buy you dinner.
That's funny.
I'm a grown up.
I'm independent now.
But I'm really happy.
For what?
You've asked me out on a date.
Are you crazy? It's not a date.
Look at you. You're pouting again.
Do you know it's cute?
You're so annoying.
Are you shy?
No way.
You're pouting again.
Get lost!
Nubsib.
Gene.
Nueng.
Did you two go out?
No one picked up my calls.
Is there anything wrong, brother?
No, Mom wants to know how you've been.
Since you've moved here,
I decided to pay you a visit.
What about you, Gene?
Why are you with Nubsib?
Did you get in contact
with each other again?
Why didn't I know that?
Well...
I stay here.
Here?
What do you mean?
Oh, I got it.
You're so sly. Did you get him already?
Don't forget to tell his parents.
Don't worry, brother.
I'll take Gene home when I'm free.
It's all right, Nueng.
I'll go back on my own.
Then, I'll visit Aunty Orn and Uncle Wat.
Understood.
Go home.
I have something to tell you.
Nueng, are you staying here?
No.
I want to eat.
I'm hungry.
Didn't you go out shopping?
Your bags are full.
We are planning to cook rice cakes.
Oh, that's good.
If you want to stay here,
it's really hard to get you to leave.
Fine.
You can stay for a while.
Nubsib.
I'm the only one here.
I won't interfere with anything.
I'll leave after the meal.
Nothing is going on, Nueng.
You are not interfering.
No one is chasing you away.
Stay and eat together.
Yes. That's how it is. Learn from him.
Peel one for Nueng.
Why should I?
He has hands.
Peel one for him.
Nubsib, peel one for Nueng!
Why should I?
Nueng, let me fill your bowl.
Why won't you do it for me?
Why?
You have hands.
Do you have double standards?
What?
I wonder who is the one
that has double standards.
That's enough. Just eat your own food.
Both of you are purposely
trying to annoy me, right?
That's not it, brother.
All right.
Just eat.
I'm hungry.
If you two one some time alone,
just think I'm not here.
I'll eat silently on my own, okay?
Hello, Mom. Yes.
We had a meal together.
Yes.
Okay.
Nubsib's fine here.
Bye, Mom.
What's wrong?
Are you two together?
Not yet, brother.
Then, be kind to him.
He has been waiting for you
for a long time.
When you have confirmed your relationship,
go home and tell my parents.
My mother likes you.
She won't say anything.
She will be happy.
Gene, don't think too much.
Our parents are adults.
Even though my father is someone
who prioritizes the family's reputation,
he is not some closed-minded person.
Otherwise, would he allow Nubsib to act?
If he is the one who finds out,
then it's troublesome.
Even if you're an adult,
you still have your parents.
Just tell them everything
since it's already like this.
Hold on.
There's nothing going on
between me and Nubsib.
Well, there will be sooner or later.
Nubsib is my younger brother.
Do you think I wouldn't know that?
You'll never escape from him.
Gene.
You're here?
I've been looking for you.
Spray some of this after dinner.
Are you all right, Gene?
I'm fine.
I'm just thinking of something.
What are you thinking about?
Can you tell me?
Nueng wants us to tell our parents
about our relationship.
Yes, so?
Don't you feel anything?
Yes.
I want to tell them.
Not just our parents.
I want to tell everyone.
But...
Don't over-think this, Gene.
If you're not ready yet,
I can wait for you.
-But...
-Don't worry.
I'll wait for you to accept my love.
Right now...
♪Maybe God gave me a present♪
♪This is what I've been looking for?♪
You are right.
There's nothing between us yet.
♪Want to let you know
how wonderful this feels♪
Where is it?
Give me the spray.
♪You love me a lot? I love you more♪
("Bad Engineer The Series")
Hello!
Dear guests and everyone from the media.
Today, we are here at the press
conference of "Bad Engineer The Series".
To be honest,
as the announcer of the series,
I'm really happy
to hear your passionate voices.
I believe all of you are here to cheer for
the director, writer and cast, right?
Without further a due,
let us invite the director,
writer and cast to the stage
with our loudest cheers, all right?
Okay? Cheer as loud as you can!
Three, two, one, let's go!
Okay, director, writer and cast.
Please come on to the stage.
Hello.
Okay. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Please.
Hello.
Everyone, please take a seat.
Okay. Take a seat.
Let's have a self-introduction.
Tell us about your name and role.
I'm Mai. I'm the director of...
"Bad Engineer The Series".
A round of applause for Mai!
Next, hello.
Hello, I'm Gene.
I wrote under the pseudonym, Wizard.
I'm the author
of "Bad Engineer The Series".
Okay. Hello.
Next.
Hello, I'm Nubsib Pipatpukdee.
I play Kin in the series.
How nice.
Is Nubsib nice?
Yes!
Okay, that's all for Nubsib.
Next, what is your name?
Hello, I'm Aey Atikan.
I play Namcha in the series.
How sweet is that? Very good.
Both of them are impressive.
Our last guest.
Hello.
Hello, I'm Mhok Metheewat.
I play Tawan in the series.
Keep screaming!
Okay, I want to talk to Mai.
Mai, I want to know how are you inspired
to adapt this novel into a series?
I think this novel is very special.
I picked it up because it attracted me.
I started to talk about it
in the office...
and everyone thought
there are many parts in the novel...
that makes people love them.
It suits the audience.
That is why
I've decided to make it into a series.
I had a chat with Gene recently.
We talked about...
I'm really proud of them.
Right?
Yes.
I'm proud of both of us too.
We never quarreled all this while.
We've broken the curse that every
BL series actor's agent must quarrel.
Thank you.
You always help me.
I'm where I'm at today because of you.
Stay cute.
Don't abandon me.
Are you all right?
It's...
I have something to tell you.
I think...
I like you.
What did you say?
I didn't hear it.
I think I like you.
Can you hear me?
What?
What's wrong with you?
All of a sudden, you...
Louder!
Okay, in that case,
we should have a performance now.
Mai said
they will shoot a scene on stage today.
Wait, let me ask my cast first.
Let's ask them.
Is it okay?
-Yes?
-Okay?
They are so cute.
Okay. Please stand up.
Are you ready?
My actors are ready.
Audiences, fans, are you ready?
-Are you ready?
-Yes!
Louder!
Okay.
That's loud enough.
Mai will say "Action".
We are doing this for real.
Five, four, three, two, action!
You're here?
Why didn't you tell me
about your escape this morning?
You can never escape.
The marks I left on you...
is to remind you that...
you belong to me.
Okay, cut!
Applause!
Okay.
Aey is already blushing.
Chemistry, Physics, Biology, everything!
They can do everything, right?
Yes!
What?
Calm down.
I can't keep it to myself anymore.
I think I like you.
Ever since we went everywhere,
did everything together
and helped each other,
my feelings had changed.
Before I met you, I thought
you were just like other agents...
who were very competitive
and sought your own benefits.
But I have realized
you are not one of them.
You are pretty
and have a nice personality.
Besides, you taught me many things.
You were by my side
when I have no one else.
I'm sure you are the one.
Enough, Tum.
Is this the right time to be joking?
What a waste of time.
I'm going back to work.
Don't you feel anything
after what I said to you?
I'm not joking.
I'm not fooling around.
What I said is all true.
Tiffy!
Have you ever liked me?
Do you need to go back and reconsider it?
Are you really sure
this is what you think it is?
If you are using this as a joke,
I don't think it's funny.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to "Comment Before Sleep".
I'm very nervous today.
That's because
I'm at the launching event...
of a TV series
that is so popular recently.
Many people are waiting to watch it.
The TV series
is "Bad Engineer The Series".
The cast, director
and writer are behind me.
Let's have a chat with them.
Follow me, everyone.
Hello.
-Hello.
Please allow me to stand in the middle.
Okay.
Please hold the mic.
Please hold it
like how you are holding my heart.
Okay, "Bad Engineer The Series"
has been launched today.
How do you feel right now about
the series going on air soon?
I feel very nervous.
I can see many people have come
including the audience and novel's fans.
I'm happy to meet so many fans.
Even the rookies are cute.
So handsome.
We have questions from the audience.
They asked whether Nubsib and Aey
would feel pressured...
for playing as Kin and Namcha
in a BL series for the first time.
We actually feel the pressure.
As you've mentioned just now,
we are all rookies
and we are also acting in Gene's work.
He is a very famous writer
with many fans.
There are so many fans of his,
but we will still do our best.
Is the relationship
between Nubsib and Aey real?
How should I put this?
-Just stay tuned to the series.
-That's right.
Okay, finally,
say something to the audience.
For those audience who want to watch
"Bad Engineer The Series",
-it will be on air on Channel 10.
-Okay.
Please cheer for us, thank you.
When the series starts, we'll invite
everyone to do a reaction video.
Sure.
-Shall we do some actions?
-Okay.
A cute one.
"Comment Before Sleep!"
Thank you.
Please like and share.
Gene.
Yes?
Can you take a photo?
Take a photo with Nubsib.
I think...
Come, Mr Gene.
So cute.
Smile wider.
That's all I can do.
If it doesn't look cute later,
I won't forgive you.
I don't want to be cute.
Brother,
can we ask Nubsib and Aey
to take a picture together?
Can you wait?
We are taking pictures of Gene and Nubsib.
You've been taking pictures for a while.
You should give others a chance.
I'll go to the washroom.
Let's go.
Aey and Nubsib,
please take a picture together.
Okay.
Come, Nubsib. Let's take a picture.
So cute!
He's so sweet.
Closer.
So cute!
Gene.
Who are you escaping from?
The fans.
They want me to take pictures with Nubsib.
That's normal. You are famous now.
Do you think I wanted to be famous?
I want to live a quiet life too.
Really?
I think it's good.
When you were on the stage,
I almost cried
because I felt proud of you.
What are you doing?
Why are you getting so emotional?
It's nothing.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the washroom.
Okay.
I'll be leaving then.
I have to follow up on the three of them.
I have yet to get the draft
after a 3-day delay.
Good bye.
Good luck, brother.
Sure.
Hello, Gene.
Aey.
You scared me.
Are you here alone?
I came here
because it is too crowded over there.
Suit yourself.
Wait.
Why are you in a rush?
It's been so long since we talked.
I saw your pictures all over Twitter.
They are very cute.
Did you get together with Nubsib?
What do you mean?
You're still saying that.
Let me change my question.
Do you like Nubsib?
You like Nubsib.
If I...
You knew I like Nubsib
but you still went and like him.
Aey.
So, it has come to this.
I understand.
You might not be satisfied...
but what you said was wrong.
Are you trying to lecture me?
No, I'm not.
I'm only telling the truth.
A normal person
would've already thought about that.
Are you saying
that I can't figure that out?
Are you taking a dig at me?
I thought you were a cute
and honest person.
Seems like you are naughty too, Gene.
It's fine that way.
I think that's how you are.
You don't look like the honest type.
Aey, mind your words.
What?
Are you angry?
You don't have to.
Because that's how it is. I...
Aey.
Nubsib.
Is the interview over?
Have you forgotten
about the things we discussed?
Oh, the things we've discussed.
I won't forget it.
Don't go overboard.
It's not.
I'm serious.
Hey, did you see the event outside?
It's such a grand event.
Yes. It's very grand.
I wonder which series it is.
I won't say it again.
Let's go back.
Tum is waiting.
Gene.
What?
Stay away from Aey from now on.
Why?
Is there a problem between you two?
It's nothing.
It's just something meaningless.
It's about me, right?
Yes.
So, Aey is unhappy about me?
No.
No?
He even...
He was rude to me.
I don't know why he got angry.
That is why I want you
to stay away from him.
It's better to leave him alone.
What if I leave him alone?
He's not even done yet.
I'm done.
It's still about me, right?
I should talk to him.
No.
Why not?
Are you afraid
that I'm going to scold your friend?
I don't care about that.
I'm worried about you.
Worried?
I'm a grown up.
You don't even want me
to call you my brother.
I don't like it when you get
worried about me like a child either.
Getting worried about you
is not related to your age...
or the fact that you are older than me.
I'm just worried about you.
Okay.
Tell me your reason then.
Why are you worried about me?
Why?
Is Aey going to do anything to me?
Is he going to kill me?
Tell me.
Why don't you tell me?
Why are you keeping it to yourself?
Say it.
Nubsib, Gene, where have you two been?
Do you want to eat together?
I have things to ask you.
No. I'm tired.
I'm going back to sleep.
What about the banquet at night?
I want you to be there.
Sorry. Just go without me.
Okay. Never mind.
Go with Nubsib.
-But I...
-No.
You have to go.
You've promised them.
It's bad to reject someone, got it?
Besides,
the organizer is the TV station.
You'll be in trouble if you don't go.
Wait for me in your room then.
I'll talk with you when I'm back.
Okay.
What are you fighting about?
Who is it?
(Aey: Let's meet.
I have something to talk to you about.)
I knew you would come. (On Next Episode)
You do like Nubsib, right?
Besides getting worried about you,
I'm still jealous of you.
Let's make a promise, all right?
Are you still hot?
Are you allergic to alcohol?
I'm not allergic.
I'm feeling hot.
My whole body is heating up.
Do you feel better this way?