(Previously On Lovely Writer)
Does drinking that makes you full?
Hey!
Nueng wants us to tell our parents
about our relationship.
If you're not ready yet,
I can wait for you.
Can we get Nubsib and Aey
to take a picture together?
Can you wait?
We are taking pictures of Gene and Nubsib.
You like Nubsib.
Seems like you are naughty too, Gene.
Don't go overboard.
I didn't.
I'm serious.
Who is it?
(Nubsib: Remember to eat)
(Nubsib: I'll go back after a while)
(Gene: Okay.)
Who is it?
(Aey: The one beside me is not Nubsib. Don't be jealous.)
How dare he plays guessing games with me.
(Gene: The fact that he is Nubsib
has never crossed my mind at all)
(Aey: Let's meet.
I have something to talk to you about.)
(Aey: Don't you want to know
what happened between me and Nubsib?)
♪Stop thinking. Just let me kiss you♪
♪Don't be afraid of love. Just say it out loud♪
♪Just imagine♪
♪Before I kiss you♪
♪But it seems like♪
♪You want to kiss me too♪
=Lovely Writer=
I knew you would come.
What do you want to drink?
It's on me.
It's all right.
Get the bill. I'll send you back.
Why are you in a rush?
Since you're already here,
why don't you stay for a while?
We can discuss this in the car.
Waiter.
Get me two B-52 cocktails.
I want it to be specially made.
Wait, Gene.
Let's continue our previous chat.
Fine.
Get it over with and go home.
You...
Do you really like Nubsib?
Do you really like him?
You do like Nubsib, right?
I can see that Nubsib likes you too.
How much did you drink?
Are you worrying about me?
I did drink a lot.
The person in the picture I sent you
bought me those drinks.
I didn't think of rejecting.
Where did he go?
Aren't you going to the TV station banquet?
I don't know.
I'm not really interested anyway.
I'm only interested in you.
You...
Are you really gay?
Do you think I'm acting?
Do you think I'm joking with you?
Yes. I don't like girls.
And I think...
I'm cuter than girls.
Your expression looks so funny.
Another glass of B-52 cocktail.
Enough, Aey.
Don't worry.
I can hold my liquor.
I'm just feeling a bit dizzy.
I've finished drinking mine.
But you've yet to drink the drinks I got you.
You'll hurt me.
Well...
You are showing that cute expression again.
Aren't you the cute one?
You said that yourself.
If you're not cute,
why did Nubsib fall for you?
I'm envious of you.
Everyone loves you.
No one cares about me.
That's wrong.
You have many fans
and your family too.
Are you trying to say that I still have my parents?
No one cares about me.
I'm jealous of you.
I want to hate you
but I can't.
You are too nice.
Did you come to see me
because I was drinking alone?
And are you worried about me?
No.
Gene.
Aey!
Sit there. I can't carry you.
You are so kind.
I'm sure you won't hate me.
Aey.
Stop it.
Stop loving Nubsib.
Love me.
I'm cute too.
If you're worried about that,
you don't have to.
I'm good on the bed.
Aey!
Stop fooling around!
I want to go home!
You're so drunk. There's nothing left to say to you.
You don't have to go back.
Stay here with me tonight.
Will you, Gene?
I'm begging you.
Wait.
Gene, you haven't drunk the drinks I got you.
How cruel.
Just drink it for the sake of
the time we spent together.
Aey, what are you planning again?
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Why are you so annoying?
I know what you want to do.
Why did you ask then?
I wasn't asking you.
I just want to remind you.
I don't want you to become like this.
Do you think you are smart?
You like Gene, right?
Do you really want to hear that?
Yes. I like him.
Happy?
Can you stop annoying me now?
Do you know what you've done?
There's no good person who would do that.
-You should know...
-Why should I be a good person?
What can I get from being good?
Answer me.
Do you think that's how you can gain happiness?
When can someone like me
gain happiness then, Mhok?
I've never done anything I like.
Not even now.
Have you ever thought that
what you did will cause people troubles?
Has anyone cared about me at all?
Have they considered my feelings?
You know it too.
You've always known.
-Aey, don't...
-Stop controlling me.
-But I...
-Enough.
That's enough.
You annoy me.
Let go.
I'm telling you to let go.
Let go! I'm telling you to let go!
Let me go, Mhok!
I'm telling you to let me go!
Can you stop acting like my parents?
Why are you always annoying me?
Why are you always teaching me
how to become a good person?
Can't you let me live my own life?
-Aey, I want...
-You want me to become a good person.
Let me ask you then.
Am I really that bad?
Sorry.
I can't become a good person anymore.
You saw that I've already tried.
I really tried.
I've tried too.
On what?
On making you notice me.
Are you so foolish that
you haven't noticed that I like you?
You said no one cared about you
and no one considered your feelings.
I'm the one.
I care about you.
I consider your feelings.
I knew that.
Then, you should also know why I did that, right?
I'm really worried about you, Aey.
But you have to stay away from my life.
I beg you.
I beg you, Mhok.
Why, Aey?
Because I don't like you.
I don't want to hate you too.
You know that, right?
If you don't stop,
I'll hate you like how I hate my parents.
I don't want to do that.
How should I put this?
Do you know your mistakes?
Yes.
I got myself tangled with Aey.
No.
You made me worried.
I was planning to go for just a while.
I didn't expect it to be so long.
Sorry.
Do you know?
Besides getting worried about you,
I'm also jealous of you.
Let's make a promise, all right?
What promise?
From now on,
I'll tell you wherever I go.
You have to tell me where you are going too.
Okay?
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
Aey likes you, so he comes
and fools around with me?
I don't understand.
Don't worry.
Aey doesn't like me.
How do you know?
Actually, our relationship isn't good.
I only know that we like something similar.
Something similar?
You.
Aey doesn't like me.
He likes you just like me.
What?
Then...
I'll call someone to get your car from the hotel.
Don't run away.
Hello.
Yes.
Uncle Tod, I need your help.
(Aey: Gene, I mixed Viagra in the B-52 cocktail)
(Aey: Good luck)
You can contact the staff when you've arrived.
Thank you.
(Tiffy: Aey, are you home?)
I think I like you.
Ever since we went everywhere together
and did everything together,
my feelings have changed.
Enough, Tum.
I'm going back to work.
Tiffy!
Have you ever liked me?
(How should I stop loving a gay person?
Those who had a crush on one, help me)
(Forget it, there's only a 0.01% chance)
(He might like you if you're attractive)
(It's better to become best friends)
(Friendship is the best)
It's so hot.
Gene, what do you think?
Take a bath if you're hot.
Wait.
Take a cold shower. It's better.
But I like to take a hot shower.
No. It's because...
A cold shower is better for you.
It helps to open your pores.
A doctor told me that,
so I don't like to take hot showers now.
Really?
Yes.
Fine.
I believe you.
Mr. Gene.
Hey!
That was fast.
It's just normal.
You should take a shower too.
You...
Are you still hot?
Yes. The heat is still here.
Then, let's go to the hospital.
Hospital?
For what?
What's wrong with you, Mr. Gene?
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
You, on the other hand. Are you allergic to alcohol?
I'm not allergic to alcohol.
Are you okay?
I don't know what's happening.
I'm feeling hot.
My whole body is heating up.
What should I do?
Wait. Let me get you a glass of water.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Nubsib.
Calm down.
Wait.
Be rational.
Nubsib.
Mr. Gene, where are you going?
Don't come here.
Calm down.
Breathe. Get a hold of yourself, Nubsib.
Nubsib.
Calm down.
Nubsib, wait.
Mr. Gene.
Don't come here.
Stop.
Calm down.
Nubsib.
Don't come here.
Nubsib. You...
Breathe slowly, Nubsib.
Nubsib.
Breathe slowly.
Do you feel better this way?
Mr. Gene, you don't have to force yourself to do this.
I'm not forcing myself.
You should know what's on my mind.
What's on your mind?
I like...
What?
Like.
I like.
Happy?
I like you too, Mr. Gene.
If you are not ready yet,
I can wait.
Cut the crap and just do it.
I won't give you a chance to change your mind.
(First Sex Between Males)
(I'm 16 years old. Is it painful?)
(Please share your experience.)
(PS: I rejected because I'm scared.)
Where are you going?
Sleep. It's still early.
Don't you have to go to school today?
It's Sunday.
I can be with you the whole day.
Let me go.
I'm going to the toilet.
Nubsib. Nubsib!
What are you doing? Let go.
I know you're still in pain.
Let me carry you.
Nubsib, what are you doing?
Gene, don't force yourself.
Let me go.
I'm not forcing myself.
What did I do wrong?
I don't like how you're acting.
But I want to take care of you.
Last night, you even did that for me.
I know.
It's difficult for you to take that step.
It should be painful for you, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for understanding too.
♪Maybe God gave me a present♪
♪This is what I've been looking for?♪
Wait.
What's wrong?
I...
Can I brush my teeth first?
Why are you laughing?
I'm just not sure.
Fine.
I have a toothbrush here.
It's new.
Here.
You should brush your teeth too.
Isn't this the same brand as mine?
Yes. It's just a different model.
This has a finer brush.
It's easier to clean.
I bought it especially for you.
Let's brush together.
Why are you laughing?
What are you looking at?
I'll beat you up if you laugh again.
"Bad Engineer The Series" Scene 9 of 10.
Cut 1 Take 1.
And, action.
Can you stop this?
Can you not do that?
But... But I...
I asked you to stop!
Don't you know?
I know.
What do you know?
I... I know I shouldn't...
What do you want from me?
I can't take it anymore.
You are just my senior.
Why are you always troubling me?
You still don't get it?
You still don't understand?
You belong only to me.
All this while,
I've never had such a feeling for someone else.
I love...
I... love...
I...
Cut!
Hey.
You need more emotion when you say you love him.
How can the audience get immersed
if you do it like this?
Right?
Okay.
You've been doing well.
Don't make any mistakes in this scene.
This is the drama's climax. Got it?
You need to believe that Kin loves Namcha.
When you have that emotion, express it.
You know that, right? Love.
Sorry.
Again.
Starting from the confession scene.
Sound.
Ready.
Camera.
And, action.
I love you.
All this while,
I...
Keep shooting. Don't stop!
What's going on today?
Say it with emotion.
Again.
And, action.
I love you.
All this while,
I only have eyes for you.
I...
Cut!
Sorry.
Nubsib, you can try
to imagine that I'm the one you really love.
Okay. I'm ready.
Ready?
Okay, everyone. Actors, get ready.
Crews, in position.
And, action.
I love you.
All this while,
I've never had such a feeling for someone else.
You are the only one for me.
I really love you, Namcha.
I'm not joking.
I'm serious.
It's true. I really love you.
I really love you, Namcha.
Cut!
Next!
I was still thinking that you lack acting skills.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey.
Hello, Gene.
Have you seen Tum?
Oh, both of you didn't come together?
No.
I haven't seen him today.
Gene, why are you looking for him?
It's nothing.
I just have some questions.
Okay. Let me know
if there's anything you need.
Okay.
I'll be leaving.
It's hot today. Right, Gene?
What's wrong, Gene?
Are you ill?
I'm worried about you.
Why do you look like that?
You didn't even reply to my messages.
Gene, are you still angry at me?
I'm just...
joking with you.
Joking?
About the pill.
I didn't put anything in the cocktail.
What?
I didn't put anything inside.
You are nice to me.
If I did that,
I'll be guilty for my whole life.
Sorry.
Aey, lying like that isn't funny.
What if I called the police?
What would you do?
I apologize.
Apologies won't do anything.
Don't prank others next time.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm not sure why I did that.
Gene, do you hate me?
No, I don't hate you.
If I hate you,
why would I still remind you?
Do you know?
I don't want you
to hate me.
Sure.
In the future,
don't prank others like this.
Understand?
Yes.
Gene, are you not feeling well?
Why don't you have some rest at home?
Oh. Don't worry.
I have a slight fever.
I took some medicine.
I'll be better later.
How can I not be worried?
You look pale.
Nubsib is not taking care of you well?
No.
Why don't I take care of you?
No, thanks.
So you are still angry at me.
I really don't like Nubsib.
I'm not angry at you.
But I really like you.
You are doing that cute expression again.
I like you
because of that.
I'll be leaving.
Nubsib.
Yes?
You didn't take the pill yesterday?
What pill?
Viagra.
Viagra?
What Viagra?
Stop pretending.
You said you felt hot yesterday.
I did.
Why are you like that?
You made me worried.
But I'm happy to see you worried.
Are you fooling me around?
No. I'm not.
Why are you laughing?
I'll beat you up.
Remember to hit harder. I want to be beaten up.
You are really...
Keep your voice down.
Otherwise, everyone will hear you.
I'm going back to the set.
Hey.
You're all wet.
What's wet?
Mr. Gene, are you wet?
Nubsib, you jerk.
You are the one who's not clear with your words.
What? What are you trying to do to me?
Give me the towel.
Turn around.
You are so nice today.
I'm nice every day.
Can you dry my hair every day?
You're an adult. Can't you dry it yourself?
Hey.
Yes?
Aren't you bored?
Staying at home every day.
If you're bored, you can go out with your friends.
I'm not.
I want to stay with you more.
No matter where it is
or what we are doing,
I just want to be with you.
I won't be bored.
Mr. Gene.
What about you?
Aren't you bored?
I'm not bored either.
Nubsib, who is it?
I don't know.
Get dressed.
I'll open the door.
Let's do it tonight then.
Nubsib.
Darn it, Nubsib.
It's Aunty Orn.
What?
Aunty Orn.
Who?
Your mother!
Oh.
What do you mean oh?
What should we do?
Get my mom to sit on the sofa.
I'll go and get dressed first.
You should open the door and welcome my mom.
If you look like this,
it'll be more suspicious.
Okay. Hurry up and get dressed.
Okay.
Gene.
Hello, Aunty Orn.
Why are you here?
Oh. My room is just beside coincidentally.
Oh. I see.
It's like that.
What a coincidence.
Yes.
Come in.
Please wait for a while.
Nubsib went to take a shower.
Okay. Come and sit here.
Nueng told me Nubsib has moved,
so I came to visit.
Oh.
Are you two going somewhere?
No.
I'm free so I came to accompany him.
It's been a long time since you last saw him.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Hello, Mom.
Hello.
I called you. Why didn't you answer?
I thought you were not home.
I was taking a shower.
You didn't tell me you were coming either.
Would that still be a surprise if I had told you?
If you hide a woman here,
I'll be able to catch her.
But,
the more surprising thing is
I get to meet Gene here.
Gene is free today
so he came here to accompany me.
Why did you call him Gene? He's your elder brother.
Be respectful.
Are you moving here?
Yes.
It's convenient here.
How fortunate
for Gene's room to be right beside.
Yes.
You are still the same
as when you were a child who stuck to Gene.
In that case,
come home tonight
and stay for a few nights.
If you have class,
just get Uncle Tod to fetch you.
You don't have to drive on your own.
Okay?
Nubsib, you have a shoot tomorrow.
You might not wake up on time.
I don't have a shoot tomorrow.
That's great.
Gene, come back together.
Okay?
Gene.
It's fine if you are busy.
Sure. I'll go.
Pack your things then.
I'll give a call to Aunty Run.
All of us are gathered again.
Aunty Run must be happy.
Wait for a while.
Hello.
Run.
Do you know who I met today?
No.
I met Gene.
It's true.
Nubsib moved to the unit beside him.
Yes.
That's right.
Come to my house for dinner tonight.
Everyone will be here.
Really?
That works too.
We can have dinner at your house.
I'll bring some dishes over later.
Okay.
Sure.
See you later.
What is it, Gene?
Do you think
we should tell our parents?
What?
Is it bad?
No.
If you are not ready yet,
I can wait.
You don't have to rush.
As long as you feel comfortable.
I don't want to hide it anymore.
Don't worry.
I'll be by your side no matter what.
Dinner's ready, kids!
Where are you?
Let's eat?
Let's go.
Jab.
Jab. Eat slowly, kid.
No one is stealing your food.
Eat slowly.
Yes.
Brother Jab, don't choke on a fishbone.
I really miss Aunty Orn's Lemon Fish.
If you like it, come and eat often, Jab.
Our houses are so close.
Okay.
Why are you being so polite?
"Polite" is not a word to describe you.
Right?
I'm very happy.
I feel so happy when I see how Jab eats.
Is that really a praise, Aunty Orn?
Gene.
Enough.
All of you are just like kids.
Eat.
That's right.
Stop teasing Jab.
Eat.
The prawn is so big, dear.
How are the two of you?
Aunty Orn said both of you
are staying in the same apartment.
Gene, you've never told me that.
Yes.
Uncle Teep, the Curry Prawn is good.
Do you want some? Let me get it for you.
Why are you both together?
It's a small world, dad.
Nubsib is the actor of my novel,
the novel that has been adapted to a drama.
That is how both of us met.
That novel of yours where
two boys fall in love with each other?
These novels are very popular now.
What kind of novel is it?
What is that group called?
The one you told me.
Wait, Orn.
Girls who love BL.
Yes. Girls who love BL.
Young actors nowadays are cute.
They are attractive, right?
Yes.
I went to a mall that day
and see the kids gathered around.
They got two attractive boys
to stand on stage and
both of them were hugging and kissing.
They did something so funny
and the fans were screaming so loud.
Wait, Orn.
It reminds me of the time
when we screamed for Bird.
Bird.
-Were you born yet?
-Not yet.
But these are not good people who act that, Run.
I was thinking. How is that possible?
That's so weird.
When I saw them screaming, I didn't get it.
Wat, this is the current trend.
It's popular right now.
I'm working hard to understand them recently too.
Why are you trying to understand that?
These things will pass soon.
It won't last long.
It's an open-minded world now.
There are many couples.
It's a menace.
I couldn't even keep pace with the update.
Exactly.
If Nubsib becomes popular,
he will be making a fortune.
Those fans are all rich.
That's right.
Nubsib.
Are you going to do that too?
That's the genre of Gene's works.
Of course, he has to show that.
Don't tell me...
Dear.
They are close.
They work together.
That is how they help each other.
Work is work, dear.
Don't overthink.
Nubsib, whatever you do,
don't destroy your own personality
and also my company.
I'm not going to say anything
but you should know best
about things that exceed limits.
Yes.
Actually,
in my memory,
these two have been sticking to each other
like twins when they were young.
They eat together, sleep together
and play together, right, sister?
When Gene is going to boarding school,
Nubsib
cried buckets
for so many days.
Really, Aunty Orn?
Yes.
Because I missed Gene.
You are really saying everything.
You're an adult now.
But now,
you don't have to miss him.
The two of you are always together.
Even his fans
are joking about them.
They think they are dating each other in secret.
By the way,
if our sons got together,
it will be really interesting, right, sister?
Yes.
Both of them will wear the groom's suits.
I've seen it on the internet.
Right?
If they got married for real,
Yes.
I'll make Lemon Fish for every table.
You are all joking, right?
How could they be together?
Both of them are our kids.
Honey.
Why are you so serious? We are joking.
Yes. Because they have been close since young.
You are too serious.
Right?
I think both of you
are just like the girls you mentioned.
Girls who love BL.
You are making everything worse.
Gene.
This is your favourite.
Have more.
What if the two of us are really together?
It's time to end this joke.
This is starting to get annoying.
Gene is not joking.
Both of us are dating each other.
If you need a reason
for why we are staying in the same apartment,
it's because I love Gene.
I've loved him for a long time.
Yes.
What Nubsib has said is the truth.
Let me fill your glass.
Do you know about this, Jab?
Nueng?
Yes.
Thanks for the dinner tonight.
I should be thanking you for cooking for the boys.
But, about what happened today...
It's all right. We'll go back for now.
Okay.
Aunty Run. Uncle Teep.
I'll be leaving.
Thank you.
I'm leaving. Goodbye.
Nubsib. Come.
Nubsib.
Dad, but Gene and I did nothing wrong.
That's enough for today.
You are fortunate that both
your mom and I weren't shocked to death.
Dad.
Why aren't you talking to me?
You couldn't accept it, right?
The fact that I love Nubsib.
Just do whatever you want.
I don't want to talk to you.
When are we going to talk if it's not now?
Why?
Is it something serious?
Nubsib and I are only dating each other.
Go up.
No. I'm not going up.
I know.
You and Mom couldn't accept the fact that I'm gay.
But it has already happened.
I didn't expect that to happen either.
Or, do you hate gays?
I have no choice then.
I've already fallen in love with Nubsib.
I want you to go upstairs.
If I'm not sure,
I wouldn't have told you and Mom.
I can keep lying to both of you.
But I don't want to do that.
I'm honest with myself.
I'm honest to everyone.
Is that what I deserve, Dad?
But
you shouldn't be angry about me on this.
If I recall correctly,
you dated boys before you met Mom.
Does that mean that
you hate yourself?
Shut up!
I want you to go upstairs!
Go up!
What you did today was too much.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Have you asked me before?
Am I disappointed in both of you?
Have you thought about it?
A lazy person like you
wouldn't have thought about it!
Go wherever you want.
I don't want to quarrel with another person.
Do you think
you can just do anything as a father?
Fathers are not always right!
Do you know?
What you are doing now
is tyranny!
Jab!
Enough.
♪If I can read about you♪
♪Like I do in the novel♪
♪I should be reading it slowly♪
♪Every letter and every word
described in the scene♪
♪When we are close to each other♪
♪When both of us
have feelings for each other♪
(From Pop to Teep)
(Happy 26th Birthday. This is a present for you, Teep)
♪I don't want to miss this moment♪
♪If tomorrow no longer exists♪
♪If Earth no longer rotates♪
(Nubsib)
(Gene)
♪I just want to stay in sweet chapters♪
(Nubsib)
♪Where we're locked in an embrace♪
(Gene)
♪I don't want to flip to the next page♪
(Nubsib)
♪Don't want to read♪
♪The chapter where we separate♪
♪Can we just end the scene here?♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't let others♪
♪Change the last chapter♪
♪I don't want our kiss to disappear♪
♪Let us be the only ones in the story♪
♪Okay?♪
♪Can this be our ending?♪
♪No more next chapter♪
♪Okay?♪
♪Can you stop time?♪
♪Just let our story remain♪
♪Don't reach the final chapter♪
(On Next Episode)
If they don't allow us to be together,
what will you do?
Are you going to break up with me?
Didn't you ask me before?
Why didn't I have a girlfriend?
Don't tell me it's because of Gene.
Yes.
I don't agree with this.
If you don't want me to be with Nubsib,
I want to hear your reason.
Do you really love Nubsib?