["SCREAM" BY BLACKPAW PLAYING]
MCENROE: After seeing her mom
giggling like a thirsty teenager
in Dr. Jackson's fancy-ass car,
this teenager was thirsty for answers.
Was that what
her mom looked like flirting,
or was it a harmless work meeting
that was taking place
in her street's
most notorious hook-up spot?
[DOOR OPENS]
Whoa, Devi!
Why do you look like that?
I'm guessing you either want something
or did something.
No. I'm just excited to see you.
How was your day?
Did anything interesting happen
at work, with anyone interesting?
You want to know about my work day?
You've never once asked me about that.
That can't be true.
I'm a total derm nerd, a skinhead!
Wait, nope, not that.
I am just trying to be
a little less self-centered.
So, did anything exciting happen at work?
Or after?
You know what? Something very unexpected
actually did happen at work.
Prashant's parents called me.
They're making an impromptu visit
to Sherman Oaks.
Wait, what?
Aiyyo! Adda katavule!
Do you know what this means?
He's going to propose.
No, it's too early for that.
DEVI: Yeah, super interesting stuff.
Mom, you were telling me
about your work day?
Spill it, girl.
You know what?
That does remind me.
I have a couple of work dinners this week.
So you guys, you're on your own.
Or maybe we could all go with you.
Kanna, I really appreciate
this newfound interest
in my professional life.
It's just too much.
Maybe split the difference
with how you were before.
["SCREAM" BY BLACKPAW PLAYING]
♪ I'm a holy fool for you ♪
Hey, Fab. Quick question.
What would you do if you saw your mom
in a car with another man,
but it seemed romantic?
What? She's cheating on my dad?
- Oh no, no. Your dad's dead.
- What?
I'm sorry. This is about me.
I should've led with that.
I think my mom might be dating someone,
but it's way too soon, right?
She should still be mourning my dad.
Maybe she's just expressing her grief
through sex.
Fab! That was very unhelpful and gross!
FABIOLA: Hey, El.
Wow. She's still pissed.
I keep texting her, and she won't respond.
Why are you even trying?
She owes us an apology.
I just miss her, and honestly,
I hate being in a fight.
How do you deal with people
being mad at you all the time?
They're not mad at me all the time. Right?
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
- Scholars, bad news.
My ongoing fight with the school board
has suffered a crushing blow.
I will have to administer a final exam
not a final interpretive dance.
But I already Amazoned a unitard!
However, they cannot stop me
from offering
a more creative bit of extra credit.
The assignment, do an oral presentation
at the end of the week
about one event in the great American saga
that has personally affected you
and your family.
The class is called Facing History.
Who's brave enough
to face their own history?
Anyone else?
Paxton, do you need to use the restroom?
No, I'd also like
to do the extra-credit project.
- What?
- [STUDENTS GASP]
I mean that's wonderful
and not surprising at all.
Okay.
You're making a difference, Lyle.
MCENROE: Devi desperately wanted
to bust her mom
for having a secret romance
with Dr. Jackson,
but given her recent track record
with both Aneesa and Eleanor,
she knew she needed proof
before losing her shit.
Bingo.
[CLICKS]
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, stealing money.
Huh? For what?
I just don't have any because I'm a kid.
Just get out of here.
Thanks for running lines with me.
I bet Tom and Rita do this.
It's so much fun.
Hey, what's up, guys?
Come on, this is crazy!
We haven't talked in almost a week,
and we're best friends.
Well, best friends don't try
to sabotage each other's relationships.
I'm really sorry that I accused Malcolm
of cheating on you,
but it was a misunderstanding.
You really hurt him.
He was so stressed,
he developed a little rash.
I had to take off all of my cool bracelets
I got from Robert Downey Jr.'s Etsy store.
I really am sorry, but I thought
I was just looking out for Eleanor.
Wow, and you think the best way
to look out for Eleanor
is to cast doubt
on the person that she loves?
That makes me think
that you're a damaged person.
Whoa, she's not a damaged person, Malcolm.
That's a little extreme.
You're defending her
when she emotionally battered me?
I am the victim here, Eleanor.
Okay. Jeez!
No, no, no, no.
Not "okay, jeez."
I guess you don't care
about my safety in this relationship.
FABIOLA: Eleanor!
BEN: At the turn of the 20th century,
a vibrant immigrant community
was springing up
in Manhattan's Lower East Side.
My great-great-grandmother
was a garment worker there.
So please allow me to tell you the tale
of Rivington Street's own Ruthie Gross.
You good, bro?
What?
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not. I'm just...
looking for my phone.
Oh.
[SNIFFLING]
There it is.
[SIGHS]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[DR. JACKSON READING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
- NALINI: Goodbye, girls.
- [DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Hey, cuz!
So, I was thinking,
you and me should hang out.
You're basically the closest thing
I have to a sister.
[INHALES] I have three sisters,
so I think of you as a cousin,
but you're my favorite cousin.
Okay. So what's going on with you?
[SIGHS] Honestly, this Prashant thing
is really stressing me out.
You think he's gonna propose?
I feel like some stuff he said to me
about my work recently
made me wonder if he's right for me.
I don't--
Hey, Kamala. You seem tense.
Let me take you out for some froyo,
and we could keep this convo going.
Oh, and grab your keys.
I need you to drive.
That sounds nice.
PAXTON: Okay, think. Ugh.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES]
Ojichan.
[SIGHS]
[INSPIRATIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[READING]
[SCOFFS]
No way.
This doesn't look like a froyo place.
Is it a pop-up?
The zoning laws
in California are too loose.
Kamala, don't be mad,
but you have been duped
for the purpose of hijinks.
[GASPS] Devi! Where are we?
Wait, is that your mother's car?
It is, and this house
belongs to Dr. Jackson,
who I suspect her of dating.
But I need proof.
[SCOFFS]
...but Dr. Everett, you know. And see,
in my family, holidays are crazy.
That wine has a cork.
It's not a twist-off.
This is definitely a date.
My brother, I told you,
called me a fool on Thanksgiving.
So guess what I did?
I got his kid a drum kit for Christmas.
- Can you imagine that kid banging--
- [LAUGHING] You're a monster.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Hmm. Wait, is that a picture of your son?
Yeah, that's him.
Wow, he's really handsome.
- Mmm, and he knows it too.
- [NALINI LAUGHS]
She's basically stripping!
Devi, don't jump to conclusions.
[SCOFFS] Let's see if she answers a text
from her only child.
"How's the work dinner?
Getting a lot done?"
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- NALINI: Just...
My mom just left me on read!
Ugh!
[GASPS]
[THUDDING]
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
No, no. No, it wasn't...
it wasn't anything.
Thank you.
Um, dinner was... was delicious,
and... and so appreciate you cooking for me.
I told you I was a good cook,
and I have something special in mind
for dessert...
No, it's not like that.
- Well, it might be like that.
- [LAUGHS]
But first I actually do have
peach cobbler in the oven.
[LAUGHING]
Oh.
You... You...
[CHUCKLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
Oh. Oh no, no!
My voicemails!
NALINI: Devi, what are you doing?
I'm so sorry, Dr. Jackson.
This trespasser happens to be my daughter.
What am I doing?
What are you doing?
We throw Dad's ashes in the ocean,
and then boom,
you turn around and date another man!
And now because of you,
I lost the only memory of my dad's voice!
Devi, calm down!
I am not dating this man!
This dinner was strictly professional!
A-Absolutely.
Your mom and I are colleagues. That's it.
Can I please get you a towel?
MCENROE: Seeing the pity
in Dr. Jackson's eyes,
Devi felt her rage turn to shame.
What was she doing in this man's hot tub?
Had she totally lost it?
You know what?
There's no need for that, Dr. Jackson.
She can stay wet while she thinks
about what she has done in the car.
Why don't you meet me out front?
Okay, Kamala. You're gonna count to 100,
and then you will get down.
Devi, what am I gonna do with you?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I thought you started dating again,
and I got upset!
I should've known
that you wouldn't do that to Dad,
or wear an all-beige outfit on a date.
Well, you know what?
You have to simply think before you act.
I mean, breaking into Dr. Jackson's property,
splashing around in his hot tub.
It's just... It's just crazy!
MCENROE: It was bad enough
that Devi's phone was broken
and her dad's voicemail
had been lost to Jacuzzi water,
but to hear her own mother call her crazy?
That cut deep.
TRENT: Damn, Crazy Devi!
Wow, you are crazy!
Everyone was right.
You are crazy, Devi.
Where are you going, young lady?
I'm not done lecturing you yet.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Pax. You skipped dinner,
so I brought you a plate.
I'm finishing up
an extra-credit project for school.
Oh, okay.
Hey, did you know
that Ojichan was in an internment camp?
I just found his dad's journal.
Yeah, he... he was a little boy there.
Why hasn't anyone ever told me about it?
Dad, uh, never wanted
to talk about it growing up.
Whenever we asked, he shut down.
I guess I learned
not to talk about it too.
Maybe he should talk about it.
Well, if anyone can get him to open up,
it's you.
He made his license plate "GRAMPAX."
Yeah, I really wish
he had not done that. [CHUCKLES]
But yeah, I'll give him a call.
Thanks, Dad.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
And so, if Ruthie had not lost her leg
in that trolley-car accident,
then she would've gone to work
at the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory
that day,
and I would never have existed.
- Thank you.
- [APPLAUDING]
MR. SHAPIRO: Fantastic work, Ben!
Devi, you're up next.
Devi, your presentation.
MCENROE: Presentation? Damn it!
Because of her family drama,
Devi had forgotten
to write a report on her family trauma.
I didn't do it. I forgot.
You didn't do an extra-credit project?
Wait, are you mad at me or something?
Uh, I can go.
I'm ready for my presentation.
Paxton. Of course, take it away.
Um, so some of you may not know this,
but I'm half Japanese.
I didn't until recently.
And, uh, during World War II,
right here in California,
the government forced
over 120,000 Japanese Americans
to live in internment camps.
My grandfather was one of them.
Now I could rattle off statistics
about it,
but, in an attempt to go above and beyond,
I thought it would be good to hear
from someone who was actually there.
No, he didn't!
[CHUCKLING]
Living history!
We're literally facing history!
This is my grandfather, Theodore Yoshida.
Hi.
So first of all, Ojichan, you were born
in the United States, correct?
Yes.
And even though
you were an American citizen by birth,
you were still considered
a foreign threat.
Which I was not. I was five.
[ALL LAUGH]
Manzanar was located in a farm town
that was abandoned
because the water was diverted
to Los Angeles, which created a desert.
The summers were over 100 degrees,
and the winters were bitterly cold
because there wasn't enough oil
to go around.
Now, Ojichan, what was the hardest thing
about living in the camp?
Seeing my father's heart break.
He was a proud man.
But when they made him a prisoner,
they stole his dignity,
and I don't think
he ever recovered from that.
I'm sorry, Ojichan.
Which is probably
why I never talked about it until now.
But when I see my grandson
stepping out of his comfort zone,
well, it made me want to do so too.
And because I am one of the last people
to still remember Manzanar,
I need to tell my story
so no one ever forgets.
[CRIES]
[VOICE BREAKING] This is exactly
what this class is all about.
[ALL APPLAUDING]
[STUDENTS CHEERING, WHISTLING]
STUDENT: Yeah!
[JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
So, what's going on, Devi?
Nothing.
I am sitting here wearing
a giant turquoise statement necklace,
and you haven't made one crack about it.
Something's up.
No.
I'm okay.
Devi,
tell me what's upsetting you.
Dr. Ryan...
do you think I'm crazy?
Of course not.
[CRYING] I think I might be.
Everyone at school calls me Crazy Devi.
And now my mom thinks I am
after I stalked her,
because I was paranoid
she was dating her work friend,
and climbing onto that man's roof,
and spying on them through the skylights.
And then, falling into his hot tub
with my clothes on.
That's a lot, but you're not crazy.
You're just hurting,
and you might even be a little depressed.
And that's okay,
because I can help you through it.
You had a big loss,
and the hurt that comes from that
can come out in surprising ways.
Like my paralysis?
Exactly.
I know I didn't want
to talk about it before, but...
[SIGHS]
...why did that happen?
If I'm not crazy,
how did I paralyze myself?
Devi, in our field,
it's what we call psychosomatic weakness.
It happens after you experience
a traumatizing event.
Like seeing your father die
right in front of you.
But it doesn't mean you're crazy.
Look at me.
It means you're human.
Devi, you feel a lot,
which means sometimes
you're gonna hurt a lot,
but, it also means
that you're gonna live a life
that is emotionally rich
and really beautiful.
[SIGHS]
Thanks, Dr. Ryan.
You're welcome.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
You're pretty smart
for someone who has Cookie Monster's turd
around her neck.
Oh!
[LAUGHS]
There she is!
[KNOCKING]
[SIGHS]
Chris. Hi.
Hey. Hey, I've been trying
to reach you all day.
Your nurse said you were busy.
Then she asked me to go to the club
with her several times.
Uh, I was actually going to call you back,
but the day just got away from me and, uh...
Last night didn't end great, huh?
I am so mortified.
That... That must have been
the worst date of your entire life.
Nah, I once got stuck
in a rotating restaurant
that kept speeding up.
[LAUGHS]
Chris, I do not think
this is going to work out.
Because of your daughter?
Mm-hmm.
And honestly, me too.
I think it might be a little too soon.
I think I will be ready in a few years,
but you'll probably be
snatched up by then.
Oh, I don't know.
Some people don't like me
when they first meet me.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- Maybe I'll see you in the elevator.
- Hmm.
I look forward to that.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- What the actual fuck?
- [NALINI GASPS]
What were you doing
at Dr. Jackson's office?
I was looking for you
because I stupidly wanted to apologize
for accusing you of dating him,
but I found you full-on Frenching him.
Now I know where my lying gene comes from
because you're the biggest liar of us all!
- What is going on here?
- You wanna know what's going on?
Your daughter-in-law here got a boyfriend
five minutes after your son died!
Guess that's why you didn't seem
too upset about Dad's death!
Was that a slap?
Yes, it was, and she deserved it.
You do not talk to your mother that way!
Did you not hear me?
She has a boyfriend!
You listen to me, child,
your mother is an adult,
and she is the reason
that you have everything you have,
including your life.
She can do what she wants
without your judgment.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
My weather app says
there's a storm coming tonight.
I need the room!
Malcolm's coming over
to run lines with me,
and we go to a vulnerable place!
Of course, honey. We don't wanna
interfere with your process.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[MALCOLM READING]
Sorry, I forgot my glasses.
[SIGHS]
Eleanor, is everything okay?
Malcolm just broke up with me.
[GASPS]
Oh.
I'm so sorry, honey.
Oh, he's just a stupid teenage boy.
Malcolm's a genius,
and you don't understand what it's like
to be in a passionate relationship
because you're with my boring dad.
Eleanor, I'm a dental hygienist.
We are the flight attendants of the mouth.
[CHUCKLING]
So I have dated plenty of Malcolms.
I mean enough. Not a weird amount.
Anyway, you know what I find the sexiest?
Stability.
- Ew!
- Don't "ew" me!
You have the best dad in the world,
and you don't appreciate him at all.
Just give him a chance.
He's a good man who would never leave you
like your mom did.
Or like Malcolm did.
Oh my God.
Malcolm is just like my mother.
I've been trying to date my mother!
- What?
- I should have been trying to date my dad!
- No, I don't think that's the lesson here.
- It definitely is.
Thank you, Sharon.
I'm sorry I've been a jerk to you.
Oh.
Hey, Dad, will you run lines with me?
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [RAIN PATTERING]
♪ Last night all I think about is you ♪
[PHONE CHIMES]
♪ Don't stop, baby
You can walk through ♪
♪ Don't wanna
But I think about you ♪
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- [KNOCKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- [EXHALES]
- DEVI: Paxton?
You're in my house.
Yeah, I guess so.
♪ Heat, heat waves
I'm swimming in a mirror ♪
Look, I just wanted to say thank you
for all your help.
It felt so good
to finally do something well in school.
MCENROE: Paxton was soaking wet,
and he used the adverb "well"
instead of the adjective "good."
He had never been hotter.
So are you here to study or...
No.
♪ Late nights in the middle of June ♪
♪ Heat waves been faking me out ♪
♪ Sometimes, all I think about is you ♪
♪ Late nights in the middle of June ♪
♪ Heat waves been faking me out ♪
♪ Can't make you happier now ♪
♪ Road shimmer
Wiggling the vision ♪
♪ Heat, heat waves
I'm swimming in a mirror ♪
♪ Road shimmer
Wiggling the vision ♪
- That was fun.
- Mm-hmm.
Call you later?
[KISSING]
MCENROE: Whoa, did Devi just tutor her way
into being Paxton's girlfriend again?
Finally, all her studying was paying off.
[SCREAMS]
Ah!
How long have you been there?
According to my Titan,
five to seven seconds.
I need you to come downstairs now
for a family discussion.
- I'm not talking to her.
- Yes, you will.
How could she do that to Dad?
Why don't you ask her, kanna?
You know, the last conversation
I had with Mohan was a fight.
Something to do with my savings
and how I shouldn't keep all my money
hidden in the soil of my plants.
I got so mad at him, I hung up the phone.
[SCOFFS]
I hung up on my darling boy.
Pati...
There is no time for hanging up
or not speaking in this life.
Do you understand me?
- Hmm.
- Let's go. Come.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm going to leave you two alone
to talk this out in private.
If you need me,
I'll be listening from the kitchen.
[SIGHS]
I am so, so sorry I lied to you, Devi.
- How could you move on so quickly?
- I haven't moved on, kanna, at all.
I... I miss your father so much
that it physically hurts.
I guess I just...
wanted a break from that pain.
But I promise you, it is over now.
Are you the only one around here
who gets to make these rash decisions?
It's just I feel like
Dad's disappearing from our lives.
I had all his voicemails on my phone,
but they're gone!
And someone was too cheap
to pay for the cloud.
I refuse to pay for something invisible.
What if I forget what Dad sounds like?
[SIGHS]
You'll never forget that, kutti.
Your father will always be a part of you.
But if you need a little help remembering,
I might have something.
- MOHAN: Ah! Move over, Paula Abdul.
- [CHUCKLES]
MOHAN: Sherman Oaks is about to have
a new celebrity resident.
Devi Vishwakumar is coming to town!
NALINI: Hello, we haven't decided
on that name yet. Okay?
- Sit here. Careful. Oh!
- [GRUNTS]
- Well, whatever your name is, Devi...
- Nope!
[CHUCKLES]
...we are so excited to meet you,
and I already love you so much.
My perfect girl.
[POIGNANT MUSIC RISING]
[KISSES]
[SIGHS]
- Eleanor!
- Guys, we're so-- [GASPS]
I'm so proud of you.
I truly forgot you were my daughter,
and all I saw was this 60-year-old
Southern white lady on the stage.
Thanks, Dad.
I couldn't have done it without your help
and without Sharon loaning me
this unstylish dress
among... other helpful things.
Oh, looks like your adoring fans
wanna talk to you.
We'll meet you by the car.
Bye! Thank you!
You guys came even after I said
those terrible things to you.
Of course, we did. Life's too short
not to speak to each other.
I'm so, so sorry.
I didn't mean any of it.
I think I was trapped
under Malcolm's spell.
Whoa. Wait, so you guys are done?
Yeah. He dumped me over text.
Can't believe I didn't see
what a tool he was.
Makes me think
I could easily be sucked into a cult.
Yeah. We've been saying that
about you for years.
[LAUGHS]
At least, Devi, you won't be
the only one going to the dance alone.
♪ I just wonder what you're dreaming of ♪
♪ When you sleep
And smile so comfortable ♪
Well, actually, I might not be.
♪ That look that's perfectly un-sad ♪
Hey, pal.
MCENROE: Did he just call her "pal"?
That's what you call the ball boy
at the US Open,
not a girl you made out with
for a zillion hours last night.
What the hell is going on here?
Oh shit! Did Devi get played?
♪ Sometimes, all I think about is you ♪
♪ Late nights in the middle of June ♪
♪ Heat waves been faking me out ♪
♪ Can't make you happier now ♪
♪ Sometimes, all I think about is you ♪
♪ Late nights in the middle of June ♪
♪ Heat waves been faking me out ♪
♪ Can't make you happier now ♪
♪ Road shimmer
Wiggling the vision ♪
♪ Heat, heat waves
I'm swimming in a mirror ♪
♪ Road shimmer
Wiggling the vision ♪
♪ Heat, heat waves
I'm swimming in a mirror ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]