Dad, are you all right?
bastard
what to say to you
call you crazy
Free at kisskh.me
almost hurt my brother
damn
bastard
Brother, you can't do it
escort
Grandpa, be careful
The emperor was frightened and the minister was late
free gift
father emperor
Father, don't panic
baby is safe
so brave
That's a crazy horse
Sex is like fire, you dare to go
grandfather
am I not okay?
I ask you to practice more on weekdays
my son
Which one is not literate and good at martial arts?
You are so fat and useless
how to be a man
And let my baby grandson come forward to save you
Father's anger
It's all son's fault
The prince is in danger and none of us can save him
What's the use of waiting
drag it down
Yes
The emperor forgives the emperor forgives the emperor
Those who dare to persuade will be severely punished
from now on
Food Bureau
Daily reduction of too uterine meal
three months later
It's useless if you're still so fat
Unable to ride a horse
see you later
Yes
father
Slower
I'm far away
Then I heard that there is another talented person in Beijing
see you today
Sure enough, Yingwu is far superior to ordinary people
No wonder the Sacred Heart
Exceptional promotion
Han Wang Mizan
ashamed
wait
this this this
Your Highness
What's up
nothing
back to the palace
Slower
What is this Yao Zijin doing sneakily?
His Royal Highness does not want to eat
I can't stand it for a long time
call you today
It is to ask everyone to take turns making meals for the prince
Who can relieve the worries of the East Palace
The princess is rewarded
Otherwise, the prince will be ill
The Shang Food Bureau cannot escape punishment
But the prince has no meat for a day
big appetite
Your Majesty's order
meat is prohibited
How can this make
Yes
Both Hu Sishan and Wang Sishan have tried
Can be cooked no matter how
The prince just can't eat
if we try
Can you beat the two chefs?
you are from everywhere
The best chef selected
Daming land is rich in dishes
Brainstorming may not be impossible
don't try
Free at kisskh.me
Are you going to give up?
look at this
Your Highness
Why don't you try this dish
you
well well
What the hell happened to Lan Cui?
your plate of fried vegetables
How to get the prince's favor
yeah tell us
tell us quickly
Yeah yeah
tell us
it's secret
how to speak
what can't be said
hurry up
why can't you say
win
adult
You, please forgive me
This is the Food Bureau
Why did you break in suddenly for no reason?
Wand
adult
You adult
Hidden set
adult
you
Who do you want to tip off
Say it
Ziping
adult
Jin Yiwei
Power of inspection and arrest
Everyone in the palace is in awe
But here is the inner court
You can't lynch here for no reason
Who are you
adult
What did you say
Adults
The maid made a mistake
It should be handed over to Miya Masashi for disposal
please raise your hand
Adult adult
In those days, Taizu wanted to punish the palace maid because of his anger
Empress Xiaoci fears His Majesty's anger
Insist on handing over to Miya Masashi
Queen Xiaoci is still like this
If adults want to lynch in the harem
It is to violate the rules of the palace and recite the teachings of the ancestors
Your lord is a close minister of the emperor
It should be done more fairly
adult
she just said
I'm obviously trembling with fear, but I still want to stop me
How hard is your neck
I'd love to try it too
Courage is just that
Thousands of poor people in the world
How many more can you manage?
Better take care of yourself first
take it back together
Yes
You adult
What a majesty
Master of Food
Master You, Jane in the Emperor's Heart
preeminent status
But here is the Food Bureau
A place where meals are prepared for His Majesty
really wrong
The lighter ones will be sent to Miyazaki
Serious cases will be dealt with by the supervisor
He Lao Jin Yiwei Intervention
show them
Holy decree
Guards in brocade clothes closely guard the East Palace
It is about the health of the prince
Even if it's a small matter of a tea and a meal
I have to report to the Holy One.
Now you are waiting to serve the prince with meat
is against the decree
take away
wait
They are all chefs who cook meals for the prince
you took everyone away
Prince's dinner today
will you do it
You adult
Free at kisskh.me
It seems today
You can only take one person
Okay
Then I'll be here watching
How did you obey the decree
But I have something to say
There must be no meat in the meal of His Royal Highness
If you dare to disobey the holy will again
I'm afraid that even Meng Shangshi can't afford it
Your Highness
Your Highness is me
Myohyun, what spice did you use?
I know that His Royal Highness does not like the smell of rouge gouache
I deliberately chose the elegant jasmine fragrance
change it
don't you like it
your highness
then you wait for me here
I'll be back in a while
hair
I don't even dare to use osmanthus oil
This is the wandering flower I picked with my own hands
Fragrance bursts if there seems to be no
Your Highness doesn't like it
Then I'm going to take a shower
Don't go and wait for me to come back
Your Highness must wait for my return
Your Highness
Take a bite to moisten your lungs
who has touched this word
Don't miss the prince's meal time
not ready
Sir, what do you mean by this?
Meng Shangshi didn't say it himself
Are these people useful?
If everything needs the help of three female officials
Aren't they all idiots?
Why don't you give it to me
Take it back to Zhenfu Si Prison
no meal
as a cook
Even if the sword is added
Don't forget your responsibilities
from now on
Everyone prepares meals for each palace
As for the prince's dinner
Let me do it
Yuehua
not possible
Okay
here you are
Kuai
Xuelu
Aren't there two best candidates here?
start cooking
Yes
what are we going to do
meal time
to concentrate
If I miss the dinner of the masters of the palaces
Can't wait for Miyazaki
I will punish myself
if we fail
what will be the consequences
Today's Vegetarian Vegetarian
I'm going to make a meal list
Ziping
you make plain noodles
thank you sir
You're welcome
let's go
too much fire
smoked eyes
Does the adult know that woman?
lowly talkative
These little maids
Not long after entering the palace
Is this fish gill made of mushrooms?
Your Highness, try this
Okay
I haven't eaten for a long time
Such a delicious meal
you slow down
how to cook
back to your highness
The shrimp head is dipped in oily skin with ground peanuts
Shrimp body is fresh lotus root with egg skin
Yam mud
Shrimp tail is carrot
look at this shrimp
There are also patterns
back to your highness
Shrimp body pattern
shredded egg skin
Also made of black and white sesame seeds
Finally, seasoning and frying respectively
In the shape of whole shrimp
very clever mind
Your Highness
It's rare that Shang Food Bureau is so attentive
the award
reward reward
come and taste this
first class
what about people
Eunuch Yuan, why are you here?
where did everyone go
They all went to the palaces to deliver meals.
father-in-law
But what did the grandson command?
Who in the food bureau went to the grass house today?
Today is my meal
father-in-law
but what happened
no
you are lucky come with me
You adult
How to remove stains on calligraphy
Your Highness
It is the Huishan spring water that was shipped last year.
bold
How dare you talk nonsense
it is true
The spring water has not been washed by the fine sand
still has a strong odor
One or two more months
Moisturized by night dew
to make tea
When the slaves deliver snacks today
Seeing that the paintings and calligraphy of His Royal Highness Taisun were stained
take the plunge
Please forgive me, His Royal Highness
The prince has eaten dinner
We have nothing against the will of God
what do you think
adult
In this clay pot is the original soup for today's noodles
Really milky white
strong smell
What do you think is the mystery here?
What's the mystery here
It's just a normal soup.
Do you really want me to tear it apart?
what exactly do you use to make the soup
Ziping she has a habit
likes to collect leftover ingredients
especially like
Chicken, Duck, Pig and Fish
Bone after meat removal
even shrimp heads
Collect these ingredients and hang them into soup
white water
The taste is also very delicious
Yin Ziping
Free at kisskh.me
I have a word
disobeying the decree
punished
win
You adult
Adults no longer investigate clearly?
adult
just water noodle soup
No fresh soup to hang
Ziping
adult
White water noodles are boiled noodles
No fresh soup to hang
The adults misunderstood
You adult
goodbye
What other orders do you have, sir?
Pull out the rod twenty
Expulsion from the Palace
Twenty sticks expelled from the palace
come
Your Highness
Slaves are wrong
Your Highness Your Highness
Your Highness
The servant knows that it is wrong, Your Highness
master
you are
a person who takes credit
Wrongful mind should be punished
came back
Your Highness
Where the previous palace banquet
vassals implicated in prison
They have all visited and sent their belongings one by one.
save them food and clothing
Your Highness expected it well
Official salaries are too thin
Several adults are very honest
If the slave does not go
I don't even have charcoal and fuelwood for winter.
How do you know she's impersonating
That's what I've verified myself
decontaminated
Not Hyesan Spring Water
It's the rain of yellow plums that has been left for three years
Nahui Mountain Spring
After the rainy season in the south
Thousands of miles shipped to the capital
Stored for less than two years
There must be some secrets to that person.
This palace maid keeps saying Huishanquan
I don't understand the mystery at all
but dared to pretend
Shouldn't it be punished?
Your Highness
Slaves have eyes but no pearls
The slave is wrong
The slaves will go to the Shang Food Bureau now.
wait
Your Highness
What else do you order
nothing more
let's go
I want to say goodbye to the emperor
Your Highness
Ink researched this painting
Maybe
someone will use
How did you come up with the soup?
Meng Shang food
When I was young, my family lived in poverty
There are often discarded ingredients in restaurants
I see pity
often collected
Later, I found different food combinations
will be ever-changing
different flavors
That
Why are you using water to cook noodles again?
Master of Food
vegetarian meal
Fresh for a day or two
It's been really hard for a long time
I cook noodles with water
The wiseness of the prince
will think of His Majesty's previous decree
will soon understand
How can we make it difficult for us to eat food bureau?
You are new to the palace soon
It seems that he knows His Royal Highness very well.
The sage goes to the prince to guard the country
Annual disaster relief tax reduction
Free at kisskh.me
Comfort people's livelihood
The name of the prince's generosity
spread to every corner of the country
Who in the world doesn't know?
Meng Shang food
Today's vegetarian food thanks to Zijin
can you please not send her away
adult
Zijin is so smart
If you really send her to Shanglin Garden
What a pity
from today
you stay in the restaurant
Learn to cook
Meng Shang food
Adults
to be frank
Boiled noodles is right
but
noodle
I used the magao fish that I sent from Jiaxing earlier.
fish noodles
Although no fish smell
very delicious
I add onion ginger to taste
Covers the original umami of the fish
How could they possibly find out?
but i didn't see you
From the very beginning, you planned to relieve the worries of the East Palace.
It's a good thing for the prince to use vegetarian food
But he needs to adapt
Don't be too hasty
That evil star is just panicking
haunted
He was ordered to monitor the East Palace
I just waited innocently
I've heard it before
The old emperor didn't want to see the fat prince
Even the East Palace has to ask for a sip of tea.
It's really a fight between gods and mortals
keep your voice down
let me see
No
you taught me to read
I help you stay
it's fair trade
do not owe each other
I didn't ask you to save me
OK
Does it hurt?
If it hurts, let me paint it for you
come over
you hurt a little
stop painting
I suddenly remembered
I have something else to do
I go first
this late
what are you doing
I
I'm going to get the food box
put medicine in
Call me a rat who hides its head and shows its tail
Yao girl
Your Highness has left a message
This ink is for you
His Royal Highness Taisun
Your Highness
The moon is bright tonight
go
go to the moon
Your Highness
I almost caught the mouse just now.
there is such a
Friends who have never met and who are not noisy
Isn't it interesting too?
Your Highness does not want to see
This knowledgeable and caring person
what does it look like
gone
Maybe you will be disappointed
better not see
you all know
Both Zhao Dianshan and Bai Dianshan left the palace
There are two vacancies
The palm food and millet work prudently
make up for her
One remaining fair play
Exception this year
The new palace maid passed the examination of the inner school
can also participate
I will also take this opportunity
Choose a direct disciple
teach her what I have learned in my life
Okay so be it
scattered
Yes
Zijin
Do not disappoint me
Your Highness
A clever and skilled cook
someone who is better than painting
Are you really not curious
not curious
Free at kisskh.me
The memorial that Grandpa Emperor gave me has not been delivered yet.
you go ask
Yes
Seems like something is missing