[English subtitles are available]
[Red packet:
Gong Xi Fa Chai, Good luck!]
RMB5.99?
Deng Hao Ran,
can you stop giving
such a small amount of money?
I've grabbed RMB99!
Ma Yi Yi,
reflect on your personality.
RMB3.99?
Deng Hao Ran!
I'm not convinced.
Give me another one!
Ma Yi Yi,
are you ready?
I'm going to start.
Three.
Two.
One.
[You have received a red packet
from Deng Hao Ran.]
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 17]
Xiao Guang
is going to graduate next year.
He wants to work at
the same hospital with you.
You got to help him.
Of course!
Xiao Chu
is young and capable.
He is very caring too.
It's only a small matter.
The same goes for you too.
Come!
Let's have another round!
Cheers!
Come!
You've promised me.
You must help me
deal with your relatives.
No worries. I'm here.
No worries.
[I wonder how Zeng Li]
[is doing in her hometown.]
[She and Yu Yi...]
[Zeng Li,]
[how are you?]
[Ai Jing Chu is a]
[very nice guy.]
[He's worthy of]
[your love.]
I'm not sure
whether he likes me.
I think
he likes you.
[What does the kiss]
[mean?]
[Do you like me?]
[However, he didn't even send me]
[any new year greetings.]
[Does he even]
[Ai Jing Chu]
[like me?]
[How did I get here?]
[It's so adorable!]
[I made this Caramel Macchiato]
[for you.]
[He doesn't want it]
[but we want it.]
[CAROL’S]
CARL'S.
Carol
is my name.
The heart is broken.
It's gone.
The same goes to my heart!
[CAROL’S]
[We’re closed.]
[Zeng Li.]
[Carol.]
[Didn’t you receive the letter?]
[I still can’t keep up with you. Carol]
[This cafe was actually]
[named after her name.]
Mr. Ai!
[Zeng Li: Happy New Year, Mr. Ai!]
[Shall I send him
my greetings first?]
[It's so hard!]
[Ai Jing Chu]
Happy New Year, Mr. Ai!
[Hello?]
[Mr. Ai?]
Zeng Li,
is your heart
still with you?
Hello!
He asked me whether
my heart is still with me.
Mr. Ai asked me whether
Finally, Mr. Ai called me!
I've got to hang up now.
Let's talk for another 5 minutes.
[We can only talk for
another 5 minutes.]
[I want to accompany
my parents too.]
No way!
The countdown is coming soon.
There are another two minutes.
[I need to accompany my parents.]
Alright then.
Happy New Year to
my cutest, attractive,
gorgeous, and gentle girlfriend!
Happy New Year,
Little Boy!
Stop!
Is that what I should get
after giving you
all the compliments?
Bye.
Wu Ying.
What's wrong?
That..
I will always love you.
Bye.
[I will always love you]
[might be the most]
[beautiful words in the world.]
[I don't believe in forever]
[but I believe in]
[Ma Yi Yi: Thank you.]
[every moment that happened.]
[Ma Yi Yi: happy secretly]
[I won't stop them from happening.]
[Instead, I'll enjoy]
[all the joy and tears]
[and remember them in my heart.]
[It has been weeks
since I last met Mr. Ai.]
[I'm a little bit nervous.]
[Zeng Li, calm down.]
I won't advise you
to undergo teeth whitening
because it is not permanent.
After undergoing the treatment,
you might get sensitive teeth.
Sister Zeng,
you're gorgeous today!
Tell me your lipstick colour.
Can you see my lipstick?
Nude makeup
is just a lie.
No worries.
Mr. Ai
won't notice at all.
You look so gorgeous today.
Are you going for a date
after the appointment?
I can't blame you.
Mr. Ai is leaving to
Africa soon.
You should cherish every moment
to date with him.
I beg your pardon.
Africa?
Mr. Ai is assigned to
the medical aid project
in Africa.
Aren't you aware of it?
It's your turn, Sister Zeng.
You're here.
How was your new year celebration?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I heard that
you're going to Africa for
the medical aid project.
I'm not aware of it.
Is it a joke?
No.
I've passed your case
to Professor Wang.
He's my mentor
in Orthodontics.
You don't have to worry about it.
I've confirmed your appointments
with him too.
Am I only a patient
to you?
It's such a serious matter.
You didn't even bother
to inform me.
I'm sorry, Zeng Li.
I wanted to tell you
but I just couldn't
get a suitable chance.
Therefore...
Can you not go?
Each department must send
a representative.
It has been set.
However, Africa is dangerous.
There are Ebola Virus and
and Lhasa Virus.
You might get infected and
lose your life!
Stop cursing me.
The medical aid project
has been carried out for years.
The precaution is perfect.
You don't have to worry about it.
No,
but I read that
Malaria is spreading there.
For instance,
you were bitten by a mosquito
and got infected.
Your immune system would be
destroyed
and...
That's just an exception.
The worse the condition,
the more a doctor is needed.
We're not only
treating the patients there.
We're saving their lives.
No worries.
Since I've volunteered to join,
I'm confident to protect myself.
Did you volunteer to join?
Are you avoiding me?
No.
I've volunteered myself
in this project for years.
It's only a coincidence.
If I didn't come for
the appointment,
I wouldn't be informed
even after you've left, right?
Zeng Li...
Mr. Ai,
the previous patient
has been anaesthetized.
I got it.
Give me a moment.
Zeng Li,
let's have lunch
in the afternoon.
We shall talk about this later.
Is it okay?
Professor Wang wants to meet you
in the afternoon.
Let's have dinner then.
I'll meet you
after the class.
Is it okay?
You've made up your mind.
What's the point for me
to wait for you?
Zeng Li.
Yi Yi,
I'm
a fool.
I thought he ignored me
because there was
some misunderstanding
about my relationship with Yu Yi.
I could explain to him.
He didn't care about me at all.
I was the last one
to be informed of
this matter.
Did you tell Mr. Ai that
you had rejected Yu Yi?
Mr. Ai might stay
after knowing about it.
No,
he volunteered himself
to go to Africa.
Maybe he is afraid
to affect his friendship
with Yu Yi
because of me.
If I told him
about it,
it would be more awkward for us.
He's going to Africa
for six months.
[He's too much.]
Ma Xiao Bing!
I saw Ma Xiao Bing.
I'll talk to you later.
Don't you agree?
Miss!
Let me get you up.
She's badly injured.
What shall we do?
Hello, is it 120?
Someone is injured here.
Shall we
inform
her recent contact?
[Hello!]
[Are you the friend]
[of this phone's owner?]
[She had an accident!]
Stop moving.
Why hasn't the ambulance arrived?
Zeng Li!
Let's go.
I'll send you to the hospital.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Let's go to the hospital.
Mr. Ai.
Don't worry.
We're reaching the hospital.
Stop talking and moving.
Don't look at the mirror too.
Hello.
Hello, Wu Ying.
Are you at the hospital?
[Zeng Li had an accident.]
[She needs a surgery.]
[What's going on?]
[Is she badly injured?]
She hurt her chin.
It's bleeding extensively.
She lost her consciousness.
Did she hurt her bones and joints?
[Her body and joints]
[are fine.]
[However, her chin needs
to be stitched.]
Okay!
I'll get ready.
Don't fall asleep, Zeng Li.
We're reaching.
Zeng Li!
[Outpatient Buidling]
Her wound is deep
but she didn't hurt
her jaw joint.
The wound needs to be stitched.
Do I need stitches?
It's a small surgery.
We don't have to do it
in the operation theatre.
We can do it here.
I should be the one doing it.
However,
your suturing skill is top-notch.
Why don't you do it?
Sure.
I'll get someone to help.
Zeng Li,
we'll clean the wound first.
Relax.
Don't touch.
It'll be infected.
How do I look now?
No worries.
After the stitches,
you'll look the same as before.
I'm here.
[Keep Quiet]
I'll clean the wound.
It might be painful.
Bear with it.
I'll put the anesthetic.
Dr. Wu,
please do the stitches for me.
Sure.
I'll put the anesthetic first.
Relax.
My suturing skill
is good too.
I promise not to leave you a scar.
We'll start now.
Three, two, one.
Shall I pull you up?
Is that
how you brush your teeth?
You should gently brush
two to three teeth at once.
♫ Clear the dust of the stars ♫
♫ To wait for you ♫
♫ And fall in love ♫
♫ If the love can last forever ♫
♫ Don’t let it go ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless love ♫
Mr. Ai,
my skill is good, right?
Thank you.
You sound like
she's not my friend.
Wu Ying.
Fine.
I'll collect the medicine
for Zeng Li.
Don't touch.
It might be infected.
Do you still feel pain?
A little bit.
You're not allowed to ride
a bicycle in the future.
It's safer to walk.
Mr. Ai,
Yu Yi and I...
We'll talk about it next time.
It should be Ma Xiao Bing
that your sister saw.
He's missing.
I think
he's going to take a bus
to his hometown.
What can he do there?
He's alone.
Ma Xiao Bing's parents
have passed away a long time ago.
He lived with his grandfather.
A few years ago, his grandfather
was diagnosed with Emphysema.
Therefore, the village council
sent him
to the orphanage.
I heard that his condition
is getting worse.
He couldn't even make it
to Donghu
for the surgery
for cleft lip and palate.
I'm sorry.
I need to pick up a call.
Hao Ran,
don't worry.
I'll contact
his hometown immediately.
I'll get a car
to fetch Ma Xiao Bing
in two days.
I saw it too.
I just don't get it.
Why are they so free
to spread rumours?
I know.
However, we've tried
all the stuffs and
think it is good
before introducing them
to others.
This is very important.
If the condition worsened,
you must hire a lawyer.
Did you get it?
Why can't you get it?
I...
Let me tell you.
We are
in the same boat.
You must settle it
by this afternoon.
Did you get it?
It's difficult for bloggers
to uphold our rights now!
-If I say it, I feel uncomfortable.
-Hello.
If you don't say it,
I feel uncomfortable too.
-I don't know how to explain it to you.
-Miss.
Anyway,
that's what I mean.
Did you get it?
I'm hanging up, bye.
Miss.
What's wrong?
Please look down.
Is there anything on the floor?
Didn't you see that
I was mopping the floor?
[Does he have OCD?]
I'm sorry.
Since you are the culprit,
you should clean it.
It's okay.
Lift your arms.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
It doesn't matter.
Don't be scared.
You
still look nice
in the pink dress.
Am I right?
It's okay.
Let's go.
What's wrong with her?
I'll bring her to the teacher.
I'll come back later
to mop the floor.
Let's go.
Don't go there.
You'll dirty it again.
Come.
Where did you get it?
I took it from
the principal's office.
It was the donation.
Brother,
this is for the children.
We shouldn't take it.
It's for the children
but
I was the one who bought it.
Are you a volunteer?
Let's add a WeChat.
Keep in touch.
No need.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean
since we are in
the same organization.
Okay.
Great! Come.
Are you done?
Let's go.
See you next time.
Bye.
Ma Yi Yi,
I'm
speechless.
You don't have to say anything.
Shut up and drive.
If you break up,
don't ever ask for my comfort.
Let me tell you.
Based on
your speed to fall in love
with a stranger,
serve you right
to date all the bad guys!
No worries.
With
your advice,
I won't be cheated easily.
Why did you peep at my phone?
Let me warn you for the last time.
Let me tell you.
Not all the volunteers
at the orphanage are nice.
Of course I know about it.
Didn't you always
volunteer yourself
at the orphanage?
Walk slowly.
I only hurt my chin,
not my legs.
How can you still be talkative
after hurting your chin?
How do you feel?
Are you still feeling pain?
I'm a bit drowsy.
It's because of the anesthetic.
It's normal.
Why don't you take a nap?
I'll leave after preparing
the medicine.
Thank you, Mr. Ai.
My body is aching.
[Oh my god!]
[When did I take off my pants?]
[He must have seen everything.]
[Will Mr. Ai think]
[I'm too liberal?]
[What's going on?]
It's warm!
[You might not from New York,
let me tell you the story.]
[Why am I still reading]
[the same line?]
[Ai Jing Chu,]
[what's wrong with you?]
[Stop thinking.]
[Zeng Li shouldn't]
[get me wrong.]
I thought you had left.
I'm afraid you'll be hungry
when you wake up,
so I've fixed something for you.
The soup is ready.
I'll turn off the stove.
Here you go.
Enjoy the soup.
I'll go back to the hospital.
Mr. Ai,
I have something to tell you.
It's
about Yu Yi and I.
I know you read
my letter to Yu Yi.
I must admit that
I used to like him.
I thought
I would never fall in love
with anyone else, except him.
However, I realized that
I've changed
after graduating from
the high school.
I wanted to tell you
during the appointment
this morning.
I've made it clear to Yu Yi.
He is not the person that I like
but..
I thought
I had turned off the stove.
Maybe you had turned the fire
to the maximum.
It's possible.
Let me do it.
Are you okay?
Let me have a look.
Don't move.
Luckily
it's fine.
However,
you must walk carefully recently.
You must be careful
when you eat too.
Zeng Li,
I asked you
whether your heart
is still with you
in the Chinese New Year
phone call.
If it is still with you,
I'll take it away.
♫ Have you ever dreamed
about me before? ♫
♫ Two hearts that are close together
hiding under the stars ♫
♫ Gradually getting used with
the courage you send in whispers ♫
♫ Every single time
I find it hard to breath ♫
♫ You are the star of mine
I see you in the dark ♫
Did he kiss you?
He's inhuman.
How could he kiss you
knowing you're injured?
No.
He only
gave me a gentle kiss.
The effect of anesthetic
is not over.
My chin and lips
are still numb.
I can't feel much.
Hold on.
Did he confess to you?
His phone rang
when we were kissing.
There was a patient
waiting for him at the clinic,
so he left.
What is the relationship
between both of you now?
He kissed you
before he confessed.
How could he do that?
Shouldn't he confess
before he kisses you?
What kind of behaviour is this?
He's taking her advantage.
He's taking your advantage.
He's taking your advantage!
The tofu is tender.
It tastes good!
Take more then.
Aunt,
how did you make the tofu?
Why do you want to learn
how to cook
suddenly?
Nothing.
The tofu
tastes good,
so I want to learn
how to cook it.
This is not the first time
that I cook the tofu.
Why did you want
to learn it suddenly?
You just teach him.
Why do you have to talk so much?
I only said a few words.
Since when I talked much?
Let me tell you.
It's simple.
Cut the tofu into pieces.
Boil them in water
for three minutes.
[Bean curd with crab roe]
Remove the water and let them dry.
Then, fry the crab roe.
Use a small fire first
and use high heat when
it is almost ready.
Did you get it?
I'll try it out tomorrow.
Am I blessed enough
to enjoy your cooking?
You should learn
to cook more dishes.
I can stop cooking
after that.
That's great!
I'll be able to enjoy
brother's cooking!
Your brother's cooking
definitely tastes better
than your mum's cooking.
Xiao Chu, don't only eat the tofu.
Take some prawns.
Yes, help yourself.
[I'm wondering whether]
[she has finished the chicken soup.]
[It won't be fresh
to leave it overnight.]
[Don't eat snacks for dinner.]
[Ai Jing Chu]
[Wait for me at home.]