[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 24]
Why didn't you say anything to me?
Recently, I wrote letters to you
and called you,
but you made no response.
Gu Yiye.
Do you want to break up with me?
Gao Liang, your kick's
amazing!
- If you were not there, we wouldn't win.
- Awesome!
Of course you wouldn't win.
Do you know how amazing I am now?
- Gao Liang. Gao Liang.
- Do you know?
Hurry up. Let's...
Sergeant Han.
You know what?
Thanks to your cheer of encouragement,
we won the game.
We almost lost.
We only scored one more goal than them.
You're amazing.
I didn't even shout.
Although you didn't shout,
I felt like I heard it.
If you shouted, I would get very excited.
You know what?
When I was in the new recruit company,
I could always hear your cheers.
Your cheers encouraged me.
Why are you so funny?
No kidding. I'm serious.
There are a lot of male soldiers
in the Communication Academy, right?
Yep.
Among all the female soldiers,
you're the most beautiful girl, right?
Just kidding.
What do you mean?
I've written a letter to you.
Have you received it?
What letter?
Gao Liang!
The unit leader wants to see you.
OK. I'll be right there.
- I...
- I gotta go.
It's going to rain.
Take my coat.
I gotta go. Bye.
Well...
Nanzheng.
Have you ever thought about a question?
What is it?
Do you think we are a good match?
What do you mean?
Sit down.
No.
I feel nervous when you stand here.
I said no.
I have a question for you.
We were under strict control
when we were in the company,
but
you were always on my mind.
Strict discipline was imposed on us,
but it couldn't prevent
our feelings for each other.
Now we're students of the military academy.
We're allowed to be in a relationship.
Why have you been avoiding me?
You shouldn't have asked me this question.
What's wrong with you?
Did you
fall in love with someone else?
I don't want to keep guessing.
Then stop guessing.
Nanzheng,
I wanna break up with you.
Why?
Gu Yiye,
look into my eyes and answer my question.
Why don't you look into my eyes?
Because...
Because you're the division commander's daughter.
I can't accept it.
Liar!
I don't think it's the reason.
Do you think I'm a fool?
Did you
get into trouble?
I got it.
You still
can't forget about that battle, right?
It's okay. I'll wait for you.
Or
do you think...
Do you think I'm not good enough?
No.
I've already made up my mind.
I said I disagree!
You know how much I like you.
You know how important you are to me.
Why would you treat me like that?
What is our previous relationship
to you?
Tell me, Gu Yiye!
♫ Yearning for me, looking at me. ♫
♫ Time turns into flowers,
like you, like me. ♫
Jiang Nanzheng.
What happened?
He hurt you, right?
Let's take revenge on him. Come on.
Let her go!
Mule Gu.
Will you feel uncomfortable
if you don't hurt Jiang Nanzheng?
You're happy to see her crying, right?
Are you really a man?
I'm not happy.
I'd rather die than live this way.
Then commit suicide. Don't hurt her.
I broke up with Jiang Nanzheng.
I don't care.
Anyway, you don't understand.
I don't understand?
I can't understand you.
It's not true that you can't understand me.
It's just that you can never see it.
I don't want to see anything.
I don't want to see anything!
Why do you look at me this way?
Did anything happen?
What happened?
Say something.
Because of a child.
Which child?
Stop guessing.
I'm asking you who the child is!
The child
of Xiu and Platoon Leader Zhang Fei!
Zhang Fei has a child, huh?
He's 4 months old.
He likes me so much.
Zhang Fei didn't know he has a child, did he?
I decided to raise the child
for our platoon leader.
Who do you think you are?
And then?
Both Xiu and the child need me.
I've already made up my mind, Gao Liang.
I chose Xiu
instead of Jiang Nanzheng.
I don't know if I should beat you.
You...
Do you feel sorry for Jiang Nanzheng?
Do you feel sorry for Xiu?
Do you feel sorry for yourself?
Listen!
Only in this way, can it be fair!
You hurt Jiang Nanzheng.
Where's the fairness?
You want to talk about the fairness with me, right?
You left Jiang Nanzheng and decided
to marry Xiu.
Is it fair to Jiang Nanzheng?
Is it fair to Xiu?
What about you?
Don’t you love her anymore?
Are you going to give up?
She loves you
instead of me.
Listen.
Xiu needs me.
Jiang Nanzheng also needs you.
That's different.
Jiang Nanzheng can still make choices
but Xiu can't.
More important, the child needs me.
That's what you think.
Will Xiu accept?
I'll try.
I'll try to make her accept.
Stop it!
Gu Yiye, listen.
If you do that,
two people's life will be ruined.
Look at the school where we stay every day.
We stay at such a beautiful school.
Every day we think about
how to achieve our ambitions,
how to make our life
better
and how to improve our relationship.
Do you know where Xiu is?
Xiu is in the mountain.
She lives in the rural area.
Every day she thinks about
how to earn a living,
how to support the elder
and how to raise the child!
Enough!
Gao Liang.
Sergeant...
Sergeant died on my back.
I have to carry him.
That's my fate.
I don't have to worry
because Nanzheng has you on her side.
How could you organize others' life?
Who do you think you are?
I did organize your life. So what?
Take care of Jiang Nanzheng.
Otherwise, I'll kill you.
That day,
Gu Yiye told me
the last words of Platoon Leader Zhang Fei.
When our platoon leader died,
the rest life of Gu Yiye was organized.
[Army Academy of People's Liberation Army]
One, two, three, four.
[Tutors]
I wanna make a call.
Hello.
Please put me through to
Jiang Nanzheng of the Sixth Squad.
Where are you from?
Infantry college.
She's not available. She said
male soldiers of
the infantry college are all jerks.
She's never available for them.
Well, you...
Hello?
Hello.
Please get me through
to Han Chunyu of the Third Troop.
I didn't expect that it's the reason.
I have the greatest respect for Gu Yiye.
He plucked up the courage
to make that choice.
A lot of people can make promises
but few of them
can keep their promises.
Nanzheng didn't choose the wrong mate.
But
why don't you tell Nanzheng
the real reason?
We think hatred is better than
sorrow.
Do you agree?
That's what men think.
Actually, it's still painful.
It's he. He.
Instead of men.
Gu Yiye is a jerk.
But you and Gu Yiye
conspired together.
Fine. We conspired together.
Don't tell Nanzheng about it.
You have to keep it secret.
Since you told me,
why do you want me to keep it secret?
You're Nanzheng's confidante
and my good friend, right?
Only you can comfort her.
She'll only listen to you.
OK.
I'll comfort her.
Your coat.
Take it back.
You washed it for me, huh?
Well, I'm going to return to the army soon.
I want to talk with you
about us.
Us?
What's wrong?
You... Sit down first.
Sit down.
What's wrong? Why do you want me to sit down?
Tell me.
Well, actually...
Actually, to me,
you're no longer
just a friend
or someone from the same city as me.
Do you remember the time when you were in
the new recruit company?
When you took me away from the river,
you became different to me.
I already
told you that in the letter.
Which letter?
I haven’t received any letters.
Forget it.
Maybe it went missing halfway.
Anyway, that's not important anymore.
Actually,
I've been in a pickle for a long time.
I...
I've asked myself again and again.
Why would I have a crush
on a new recruit
who's younger than me?
But after I convinced myself,
my feelings for you became stronger.
I couldn't resist.
It's inevitable that we have
to face ourselves.
Am I right?
Yes, you're right.
I like you.
What about you?
I...
Well,
Sergeant Han,
I think...
To be honest,
I don't think we're a good match.
Why?
Every day I...
Well, I like a lot of people.
There are so many female soldiers.
I like every of them.
If I keep my mind
on all of them,
I'll be exhausted.
So many girls?
I think you only have a crush on Nanzheng.
Nanzheng...
Did I guess right?
Yes.
Actually...
I was touched by Gu Yiye's choice.
I think
we all need courage.
I always know
your feelings for Nanzheng.
However,
because of you three's relationship,
I saw what you did for Nanzheng.
So
I'm concerned about you.
Anyway, that's all in the past.
Go to visit Nanzheng.
I think she needs you now.
It's a chance for you.
I don't need this chance.
Ask her out
when she just broke up with her boyfriend.
I will never do anything like that.
I don't want to humiliate myself.
Brat.
Both of
the process and the result are important.
You're right.
Sergeant Han.
Thank you for treating me as your friend
and
being honest with me.
Therefore,
I want to be honest with you, too.
I'm sorry.
I really
can't accept it.
Gao Liang.
You're waiting for Nanzheng
but I'm waiting for you.
Don't wait for me.
We can never be together.
Sergeant Han,
tell Jiang Nanzheng
that
from tomorrow onward,
I'll officially chase her.
I gotta go.
Take care, Sergeant Han.
Sorry, Sergeant Han.
I dare not turn around.
I know you're upset.
I really want to go back, comfort you
and tell some jokes.
I want you to laugh
instead of crying.
Besides Nanzheng and my brother,
you're the closest person to me.
But this time,
I dare not make you have illusions
or feel hopeful.
I'm afraid that you'll be more upset
so I'd rather pretend to be a bad guy.
I really don't want you to be sad.
I want to call you sister.
Sorry, Sister Chunyu.
[6 months later...]
[Create a new situation in
the revolution and modernization of the army]
Comrade.
Come on. Let me help you carry the suitcase.
Give it to me.
Come on. Give it to me.
You broke up with Gu Yiye.
He's like the United States.
It's right for you to break up with him.
But I'm like Cuba. You shouldn't have
avoided me.
We have a strategic alliance.
Why can I see you everywhere?
Our troop came here for training.
It's just a coincidence.
You know what?
It's fate that brought us together.
You can never avoid it.
Really?
Sergeant Han is also here.
Did you see her?
Why do you seem to be confused?
Are you pretending to be confused?
I don't know why you are so lucky
to have our wonderful sergeant's admiration.
You really changed.
Now you care about others.
Really?
Left, right, left.
Both of them lost some weight.
That means they didn't slack off.
Sergeant, are you okay?
I'm good.
All right. Go back now.
OK.
Go back for training.
Bye-bye.
Chunyu.
Deputy Company Commander Xia.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Why are you in the division?
My vacation just began.
You didn't go home, huh?
I missed the army so I came back.
What are you doing here?
We're teaching soldiers in the division.
A member got injured during the training.
He was hospitalized. I'm going to visit him.
Why didn't you reply to my letter?
I don't know how to reply.
I think
I've already made it clear.
You don't have a boyfriend.
Why did you give that reason
for refusing to be my girlfriend?
Don't look at me this way.
No one told me anything.
Your eyes
betrayed you.
Actually, you're good.
Many of our female soldiers
have a crush on you.
I believe you.
Are you so confident?
Of course.
Otherwise, I wouldn't chase you.
Honestly,
I had to pluck up the courage
to chase you.
Chunyu.
I have to
tell you something.
I know
it may make you
misunderstand me,
but if I don't make it clear,
I'll never forgive myself.
Tell me.
You wrote a letter to Gao Liang.
But I thought it was for me.
I opened it by accident.
When I took the letters
for me and him on that day,
I had no time to give him his letter.
There was an emergency muster.
And when we finished the training at night,
we were exhausted.
And then?
Then
I'd like to admit
I read the whole letter
due to the curiosity and jealousy.
Chunyu.
I always...
I always want to give it to you.
Luckily, I met you today.
Let me return it to you.
Why do you want to return it to me?
I wrote it to Gao Liang.
Because if I give it to Gao Liang,
it's likely that he'll misunderstand me.
But if I return it to you,
you won't misunderstand me
because you're an upright person.
You never misunderstand anything.
That's the reason why I trust you so much
and I confessed at the risk of
being refused and despised.
Soldier is a profession
that has a long history.
After your compatriot dies,
take care of his wife and children.
People who lived thousands of
years ago already did that.
It's pretty common all over the world.
To a large extent, classical armies
depend on the ancient tacit agreement
and brotherhood.
It's about the kindness
and responsibility.
Since Xiu and her child live a poor life,
you want to sacrifice the rest of your life.
What is the People's Army?
Why you?
When the sky falls,
you’re the tall one.
This is the mission that only you can accomplish.
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ the rivers that we crossed together ♫
♫ the songs we sang in tears ♫
[New recruits company, comrades friendship.
Go hand in hand for a bright future.]
♫ When you leave ♫
♫ the sunlight is gone ♫
♫ The mountain breeze blows away ♫
♫ the enthusiasm in my mind ♫
♫ When you fall ♫
♫ the world is gone ♫
♫ My persistence is scattered ♫
♫ on the ground ♫
♫ I miss the vows and legends ♫
♫ that you left quietly ♫
♫ and the immortal red flame in your eyes ♫
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ the timidity falling like a meteor ♫
♫ the trembling that is as lonely as a wave ♫
Xiu.
♫ I still remember ♫
Make contributions to our country.
♫ the rivers that we crossed together ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
Nanzheng,
♫ the songs we sang in tears ♫
the moment Platoon Leader Zhang Fei died,
the burden of responsibility fell on my shoulders.
Your companionship and inspiration along this journey
will be buried deep in my heart.
Nanzheng,
I’m sorry.
I know what I’ve done here,
with you.
I do not pray for your forgiveness.
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ the timidity falling like a meteor ♫
♫ the trembling that is as lonely as a wave ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ the rivers that we crossed together ♫
Nanzheng,
♫ I still remember ♫
I feel like I owe you a lot.
♫ the songs we sang in tears ♫
I like that you owe me.
Owe me for life.
Then I will never forgive myself.
Yiye,
I will look for the answer
until I find it.
There you go, daughter.
Eat.
Why don’t you eat?
I told you I don’t want to eat.
Look at you.
No matter how sad you are,
it is a bowl of rice noodles.
You can hate the guy,
but you don’t have to hate the rice noodles.
What did Gao Liang say to you?
Do I need Gao Liang to tell me?
It’s written all over your face.
The thinner you are, the more you look like your mom.
Your mom
was different from you.
She hated me and ignored me.
But she ate meat
and rice noodles as usual.
It takes physical strength to hate a person.
Only when you have eaten enough can you hate a person.
What do you say, daughter?
I don’t hate anyone.
Then I’m going to criticize you.
Why not?
If you had told me earlier,
I would have kicked his ass.
There’s no chance for him to go to the military academy
and be an elite. It's all bullshit.
I’ll send him to the farm to feed the pigs.
What are you doing?
You investigated me.
Otherwise, how do you know
so much about me?
I’m telling you,
this is my personal business,
and I can handle it,
without your interference, Division Commander.
Interference?
Well, sit down.
Did I intervene?
That’s a serious crime for me.
Did I interfere with you?
But when you fall in love with someone in the future,
I have to intervene.
I don’t believe it.
Who dares to bully my daughter?
Who dares to bully me? It’s you.
What did I do to you?
Do you know why he broke up with me?
Why?
Because I’m your daughter.
He doesn’t want to be the son-in-law of a Division Commander.
Well, this guy
has moral integrity. I like him.
Comrade Zheng Yuan.
Don’t you have your own principles?
You said you wanted him to feed the pigs,
and now you like him.
Do you love your daughter
or admire your soldier?
My beloved daughter, you know nothing.
A man
must know self-respect,
self-confidence.
That’s not self-respect and self-confidence.
That’s selfishness.
If you don’t tell me these bullshit reasons,
I won’t think about it.
After hearing what you said,
I think this guy must have something to suffer from,
or it doesn’t make sense.
You should understand him.
When your mom and I…
Dad, I don’t want to hear this.
Do you think I’d be happy
if you told me that?
Why can’t you learn
how to care about others?
You always feel that you are right
and impose your own ideas on others.
You’ve left everyone
around you scarred.
And
I won’t be like mom.
I won't live with hate.
Don’t worry about that.
You don’t have to defend yourself,
and you don’t have to tell me.
What a naughty daughter,
you really blocked me.
I have to knock down this wall.
I must tell you what happened in those days.
[Carry every red flag.]
♫ The south wind blows gently ♫
♫ Blows away the fog ♫
♫ Blowing me to you ♫
♫ The north wind comes quietly ♫
♫ It's plucking away the wheat ♫
♫ Let me find you ♫
Commander Gu.
Why are you willing to meet me today?
What’s up?
Cut it out. Have a seat.
Sit down and I’ll talk to you.
You’ll know when you read it.
♫ I’m willing to do everything about you ♫
♫ I’ll leave you the place in my hand ♫
Finished it?
The contents of these three letters are similar.
Xiu is rejecting me.
I’ve really thought of all kinds of ways,
but I can’t convince her.
I’m the one who gets the best
in the academy exams.
So why is it that when it comes to Xiu,
I feel like I’m never going to pass.
Those of you
who come from cadre families,
all of you
have learned a lot
and are full of knowledge,
how come you can’t understand the letter?
Shame on you.
Read it.
Why?
Just read.
Hello, Comrade Gu.
I’ve received the money you and Gao sent.
Thank you.
I’ll take the money.
But I don’t agree with the idea
you put forward.
I firmly disagree.
Fei boy won’t agree.
Don’t think like that again,
and don’t write any more letters.
Say hello to Gao.
Xiu.
Keep reading.
What do you want?
Do you want to solve the problem?
Read.
Gu,
[Xiu]
hello.
I’ve received the money you and Gao sent.
I can’t trouble you anymore.
Stop sending money.
Mom is in better health now.
She can hold the baby
to chase the chickens back to the nest.
The baby can crawl.
Don’t mention that again.
Like I said, I disagree.
You’ve trained hard.
You don’t have to write letters.
Say hello to Gao.
Xiu.
Well, next.
Your mom
is the only woman
I ever cared about in my life.
I owe her a lot.
Dad,
this is the first time
you’ve told me about mom.
Dad,
you are much older than before.
Nonsense.
I was in my twenties then,
and I was young
and handsome.
Dad,
you and mom
have a romantic story.
And I envy mom so much,
having a man like you to care about her and love her.
Mom doesn’t know how lucky she is.
Why didn’t you tell me before?
Would you listen to me when I told you?
Daughter,
I know you got two comrades on your side.
One is Gu Yiye, and the other one is Gao Liang.
They are all excellent.
But
they are two different
types of men.
Do you agree?
Gao Liang is enthusiastic and motivated,
brave and tenacious, exhausting all efforts.
Even the most critical Song Jianshe,
cannot say he is not good.
However, he only completed the life of an ordinary soldier.
For girls,
he is ordinary, down-to-earth, responsible,
and worthy of girls’ trust.
Gu Yiye, on the other hand,
is arrogant, confident, and unruly.
He will show superhuman courage
and strength in do or die,
and will not hesitate to burn himself and the people around him.
This is destructive to girls.
The girl who falls in love with him will be hard.
If Gao Liang fights all his life to become a hero,
then Gu Yiye is a legend.
But it’s too hard to be a legend.
Legends have the great risk of falling
and burning into ashes;
the risk of struggling through life
in the mire of mediocrity.
For ordinary people,
ordinary life is good.
But for people like Gu Yiye,
every minute and every second are a torment.
They will also vent their anger at the people
who love them because of the suffering every minute.
How do you know?
How could I not know?
I am the one
who is struggling in the mire of mediocrity.
I don’t want my daughter
to be such a worthless fuel
in that person’s life.
You mean,
mom is the worthless fuel, right?
Because your mom left me,
she lived up to her value.
Dad,
tell me that,
does someone like you
ever change?
I’d like to say yes.
But I can’t lie to you.
Come on.
Dad,
what happened to your hand?
It’s been a long time since I cooked.
Eat slowly and don’t choke, daughter.
Do you see the difference?
The content is the same,
they are all rejecting me.
Your stupid head. You’re killing me.
I’ll give you an analysis.
Three letters.
Do you see
what the names are?
Comrade Gu.
Gu.
Brother Yiye.
What does that mean?
That shows that her mind is changing.
Right?
Look at the content of the letter.
She has already started to talk to you about the family
and she’s going to send you the bacon.
What does this mean?
She misses you and cares about you.
And then what?
And then present yourself well.
I think the door is about to open.
No way.
What if Xiu says no to my face?
Forget about it and do what you have to do.
Yiye,
why are you getting so unsure of yourself?
Where is
your unruly attitude before?
I don’t know what happened.
When it comes to Xiu,
I feel nervous.
There you go.
You’re in character.
Cut it out.
Let me tell you something.
I think you know that
I
am quite popular
among the female soldiers in the Communication Academy.
They admire me.
So as far as this matter is concerned,
I’ll give you three secrets.
First,
insist on.
Second,
being shameless.
- Third…
- Come on.
I knew the third one.
Just like you,
insist on being shameless.  Is that right?
You seem to understand.
You know everything.
I can’t talk to you seriously.
Okay, fine.
Let me tell you something serious.
The root cause is that
those of you who came from cadre families
do not understand the sufferings of the world.
What does love
mean to Xiu?
She can’t even think about it.
What environment does Xiu live in every day?
All kinds of life pressure are on her.
She’s like
a drowning person.
What about you?
You’re the rope in the water.
Doesn’t she want to hold on to you?
That’s nonsense.
Xiu is not that kind of person.
Yeah, right.
I didn't say she was either.
Let me tell you,
what do you mean to Xiu
and the people in the village?
You are a PLA,
a Bodhisattva soldier
and a Chainbreaker
who can save Xiu from the hot water.
You
chose Xiu
because of your responsibility,
but that was only the beginning.
If you want to go on with Xiu
in the future,
you have to love her.
You have to let her feel the love
that she couldn’t even get from Zhang Fei.
That’s fair.
You should think about this matter carefully.
Love her. Can you do that?
Got it?
I will do my best.
I’m gonna make it happen.
Okay.
Then today’s lesson was not in vain.
Gao Liang.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Alright.
I have to go.
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
You stole all my knowledge,
and you just want to run away, huh?
Gao Liang.
Why didn’t I think
you knew so much about love?
I’m a late bloomer.
Jiang Weixing and Niu will be here soon.
Say hello to them for me.
[Carry every red flag.]
Don’t shine the flashlight on me.
I’ll kick your ass.
There you go.
Well, the smell.
Are you ready?
Not bad.
Shouldn’t we sing a song before eating?
No singing, no eating.
Cut it out.
This is a small gathering. We’d better keep it low-key.
Don’t bring Song here.
Come on.
Did you bring the rules?
Rules.
Of course.
Come on.
Cheers.
To the Ninth Company.
[Zhujiang Beer]