=City of Streamer=
=Episode 31=
Shizhen,
how will I ever let you know?
I'll keep the secret
forever and ever.
The new teacher Miss Feng is awesome.
She easily enlightened me
on math problems I couldn't solve.
Hope I can be as great as her someday.
She's such a good and beautiful woman.
What kind of man on earth
can be good enough for her?
Stop guessing.
She's already spoken for.
Look over there.
Miss Feng, someone is waiting
for you downstairs.
According to students,
a handsome rich man is chasing you.
That's him?
He looks handsome and amiable,
unlike other rich young men.
Shizhen, you have to hustle.
When are you going to get married?
Get married?
I haven't decided yet.
Seriously? What a good man he is!
He's one in a million.
You can't even find a better man
in romantic novels.
What a pity!
We're already lucky to be together.
There's no pity.
Life is short for women.
You should think for yourself.
Life is short.
We'll enjoy every day we spend together.
I'll take my leave.
See you.
All right.
Why did you suddenly come?
I missed you
and I came to pick you up.
I got paid today.
Shall I invite you
to watch Shang Xiaoyun's new opera?
As soon as you have money,
you're trying to support a man?
But considering my figure
and appearance,
I deserve a higher price.
In my heart,
you're very valuable.
Even all salaries of my life
can't be enough for you.
But I need the money
for another purpose.
You're rich, Mr. Jiashang.
You can wait, can't you?
What do you need the money for?
I want to buy a house.
Are you going to stay in Peking?
Mm.
If it's because of Meng Xu'an,
I can solve the problem.
When I'm around,
you don't need to be scared.
It's not all about him.
Actually,
I've always wanted to settle down
in a place
and think carefully
about our future.
What will our future hold?
It depends on how you treat me.
Let's go.
Mm.
I asked you not to buy them,
but you insisted.
Why did you buy so many things?
I can't use them up.
I don't care.
What other girls have,
my girl must have it.
What other girls don't have,
my girl must have it, too.
What if you spoil me?
My pleasure.
- Rock Paper Scissors.
We won.
I won.
Wait for me, brothers!
What happened?
Don't cry.
Are you hurt? Stand up.
Let me check.
Where did you hurt?
Your knees?
Mm.
Your brothers are just ahead.
Come on. Go play with them.
Mm.
They're waiting for you there.
Stop crying.
She looks so lovely when she stumbles.
You like children?
Mm.
Of course I do.
Or why would I be a teacher?
Look at their eyes.
Pure
and vigorous.
What's wrong?
Miss,
my brothers refused to play with me.
How come?
Why don't they play
with such a lovely girl?
Go. Let me take you there.
Mm.
Let's go.
Be careful. Mind the snow.
Come on.
Rock Paper Scissors.
- Rock Paper Scissors.
- Brothers!
You play the eagle.
All right. All right. Come on.
Come on.
Come over.
You come this way.
You can't catch me!
Come and catch us.
Hold tight.
Here. Here.
Hello?
Hello? Jiashang.
Father woke up.
Just now,
he asked where you were.
I said you were in Peking
for some business.
He woke up?
How's he doing now?
He's clear-headed.
But he's unconscious
from the waist down.
The doctor is checking on him.
It's preliminarily estimated
that the bullet hurt his spine.
I'm afraid he can't accept such a fact.
You're right.
After Father knew that,
he became furious.
He smashed all the infusion bottles.
The doctor had to ask the nurse
to inject him
so that he would calm down.
What about the others?
Mother and Aunts are
accompanying him in the room.
Fanghua was informed, too.
She said she would come back
as soon as possible.
Yunchi is keeping her company.
Where's Uncle Zhao?
Ah?
Why do you ask about him?
When Father woke up,
didn't he come?
Oh. He's also here.
Do you want to talk to him?
No.
Tell Father
that I'll be back tomorrow morning.
All right.
Jiashang,
what plan do you have
for you and Miss Feng?
It's none of your business.
Do me a favor.
Don't bring her up in front of Father.
All right.
I won't.
Look at here, please.
Get closer.
Have a bigger smile.
All right. Get ready.
Hold on. Three, two, one.
♪What is bitterness♪
♪What is pain♪
(Huamei Photo Gallery)
It's so cold in Peking.
It's getting warm in Shanghai, I guess.
♪It's dim in the distance♪
♪My faint uneasiness♪
Perhaps.
The temperature
makes no difference
when you're not around.
It makes a difference.
Whenever I think of you,
I don't feel cold.
♪Who's there to share joy and sorrow♪
In next spring,
let's fly a kite in Beihai Park.
All right.
♪I'm destined to use up my luck
to meet you♪
♪I'm destined to use all my strength
to look for you♪
♪I'm destined to spend the rest of my life
Protecting and accompanying you♪
(Huamei Photo Gallery)
♪We can't control ourselves♪
♪I'm destined to use up my luck
to meet you♪
♪I'm destined to use all my strength
to look for you♪
♪Our love is destined to be long♪
♪Life is too short♪
♪The story won't be over♪
You're back.
Your father has been asking about you
since he woke up.
He's living in the West Hall.
Go to see him.
Mr. Jiashang.
Father.
Don't be angry.
Or it'll harm your health.
What do you want to do, then?
If you don't want
to take care of me, get out!
Get out!
Out!
Jiashang?
Jiashang.
It's all right.
I'm back.
I'll take care of everything.
Father became irascible
after he woke up.
Mother doesn't want to take care of him.
Jiashang,
be very careful.
Don't worry.
I'm going upstairs.
Father.
You've found the way home?
Did that woman
finally allow you to come back?
How did you know?
Don't think I knew nothing
just because I was in a coma.
You loser.
You broke off your engagement
to Du Lanxin
and lost the paid bride price!
Now everyone in Shanghai is
laughing at our family!
It's my engagement.
I'll handle it in my way.
It's a family engagement!
What makes you think you'll handle it?
Look how poorly
you're running the company.
Meng Xu'an is at the door,
and you?
You shirk and step back.
Here comes something interesting.
Meng Xu'an
has got my half-brother.
If I killed Meng Xu'an,
should I kill my brother, too?
If I killed him,
how would I explain
after you woke up?
What are you talking about?
You don't know about it?
Meng Xu'an's sister
gave birth to your son
and he was raised in the Meng family.
He's 17 years old now.
What?
Qingzhi...
She had a son for me?
I met him at the auction.
He looked weak.
But apparently,
he's my biological brother.
Father,
when you meet him,
will you be happy?
Meng Xu'an has
brought my son up.
What on earth is he up to?
What else do you expect?
He'll certainly kill us
and make his nephew
the master of our family.
Fortunately,
Shizhen saved me.
You should be grateful to her.
Without her,
I wouldn't be standing here.
We owe this to her.
That woman
worked for Meng Xu'an, didn't she?
I told you that she was fishy.
I kept warning you.
But you were enchanted by her
again and again!
Such a kindhearted man like you
doesn't deserve to be my son!
Right.
I'm indeed weaker than you.
I'm not merciless enough
to kill my own brother.
Shut up!
Give my seal back to me.
From this day on,
don't interfere
with any family business.
Go continue your education.
Give my seal back to me.
Give it back to me!
I've got an idea.
Father, you're in poor health.
You'd better rest for recuperation.
And I'll take care of the company.
With the help of friends,
I've found the best neurologist.
I hear he's in New York.
I've contacted him.
I'll take you to see him personally.
What do you think?
You...
You heartless creature!
Are you going to grab power from me?
In less than one month,
you cut the apron strings
and tried to be independent?
What do you think you are?
You're nothing,
but a childish puppy!
After assisting me for a couple of days,
you want to take the wheel?
I'm... I'm not dead yet!
It's not your place to be the master!
Give my seal back to me.
Give it back...
Give it
back to me.
Give my seal back to me!
Give it back to me!
My... my seal...
Scamp!
I don't want you.
You're just like your mother.
Stupid
and cowardly.
I would rather give my family property
to Qingzhi's son
than you.
Get out of here.
Get out of here!
Father, you must be tired.
Have a good rest.
Mr. Jiashang.
Give him an injection.
- Yes.
Come on.
You heartless creature.
Don't touch me.
It'll be done soon.
Just a second.
Our family and the Meng family are
well-matched in strength.
Neither of us can
annex the other at one stroke.
If we keep fighting each other,
we'll both lose
and the third party will benefit.
Father,
you don't own the Rong family alone.
I can't let you
ruin our family
for your personal grudge.
Fanghua has paid a terrible price
for the mistake you made.
I must protect other innocent people.
Father,
you know it.
I'm not interested
in Rong's businesses.
But from now on,
I'll take the wheel for the Rong family.
This is the best choice for the family.
Father,
your time has gone.
Take a good rest.
Jiashang?
Did Father beat you?
He's being unreasonable.
Whenever he feels unsatisfied,
he maltreats us,
saying that we try to hurt him.
Father was just back from the hospital
and he's paralyzed.
I'm afraid he can't face up to it.
He can do nothing
but vent his anger on others.
Don't take it personally.
Father used to be spirited.
He always strode
and was full of beans.
Jiashang,
when do you think Father can recover?
Considering the current
medical technology,
we can't find a cure for him.
I just hope
he can accept the reality soon.
Mm.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
Mother.
Jiashang,
how was your trip?
Not bad.
Uncle Zhao, did you come
to visit my father?
After taking the medicine,
he fell asleep.
Ma'am said you were back
and she invited me to dinner.
Besides,
several documents
need your father's signature and seal.
I'm keeping the seal.
Since my father was injured,
he's been mentally unstable.
Considering he's irascible,
he can't handle any business.
I'll manage the company
on his behalf.
You don't mind, do you?
I'm loyal to your family,
whether alive or dead.
If you need anything,
I'm at your service.
Only when you
shoulder the main responsibility
can your father recuperate
without concern,
right?
I'm glad to hear that.
Mm.
Let's have a talk in the study.
All right.
Ma'am.
Mm?
Excuse me.
Mm.
Mother, are you all right?
One more thing.
The war is critical in the southwest.
Local crimes are rampant.
Our goods from the south
(Contract for Market Storehouse)
have been robbed twice.
(Party A: Rong Jiashang, Party B: Huatai Company)
Commanders are too busy with wars
to attend to us.
Suspend the transport, then.
It's the end of the year.
Let our men have some days off.
How's it going with the Meng family?
Nothing big has happened.
They just keep an eye on us
with open hostility.
Avoid head-on confrontations
as far as we can.
They're evenly matched with us.
Once we get into a big fight,
we'll both suffer.
Then others will benefit.
But your father can't let it go.
We mustn't harm the family interests
because of his personal grudge.
Besides, you developed
our subordinates.
If they're killed in such conflicts,
won't you feel sorry?
Uncle Zhao.
Mm?
I'm young
and not very experienced.
Now, I can take the position
simply because
I'm Rong Dingkun's son.
I know.
Some seniors in the company
don't obey me.
I manage to hold on to my position
because you support me.
I'll keep in mind
how you've helped me.
Don't say that.
Since you worked in the company,
you've handled
every case properly.
To be honest,
times have changed.
We established the company
with your father.
However,
we still depend on young men like you
to make it prosper.
Uncle Zhao, you're reading my mind.
To tell you the truth,
I've always wanted to discuss something
with a senior.
I'm all ears.
Some of Rong's businesses
should be rearranged.
Some businesses are murderous.
They make evil money.
They should be
cut down,
then closed down.
Uncle Zhao,
what do you think?
What businesses are you talking about?
Opium.
Opium?
I know.
Selling opium
laid a solid foundation
and has financially supported
our company for years.
But it's not a long-term business.
And it's too wicked
and guilty.
If we don't rearrange our businesses,
we will be bound
and forever stuck in illegal businesses.
Once we stop selling opium,
we'll suffer heavy losses.
The profits are considerable.
How can we stop it just as we wish?
Haven't we done
enough wicked things?
My father is paralyzed now.
No offense,
but he deserves it.
I want to do this
so that I can perform good deeds
for my father
and my family.
It's easy to stop selling opium.
But then how do we support our men?
It's not easy
to disband men in this industry.
Where there's a will, there is a way.
Even the best of friends must part.
Uncle Zhao, you assisted my father.
You made the greatest contributions.
I won't treat you shabbily.
Thank you for taking care of my family
when I was away.
I heard that Ma'am was unwell.
But when I saw her today,
she looked good.
You and your sisters call me Uncle Zhao.
Then we're a family.
We should take care
of each other.
Cheers.
Shiori,
news just came
that Mr. Rong woke up.
In recent days,
routes of Rong Company
have had repeated failures.
A few days ago,
one of their batches was reported
and detained.
Mr. Rong has woken up,
but Rong Jiashang still takes the wheel.
What's your point?
Shiori,
this is vital to taking Rong Jiashang.
If you marry him,
you'll be the mistress
of the Rong family.
Our brother just died
and we're still in mourning.
If I offer to marry him,
even Father will not approve.
Besides, do you think
Rong Dingkun can still force his son?
We have to
come up with a more careful plan.
Send someone to spy on the Rong family.
Let me know if there's any news.
Rong Jiashang
will be mine.
He can't get away.
Sir, here's your newspaper.
(Rong Dingkun of Rong Company
Woke Up Last Week)
Rong Jiashang has been back for days.
What has he done?
Mr. Meng,
Zhao Hua'an sold opium secretly.
When Rong Jiashang knew that,
he used an excuse
to have fired
Zhao Hua'an's subordinates.
He even gave a pay raise
to regular employees.
No legal businesses are neglected
and directors have no reason
to complain.
They hate Rong Jiashang,
but don't dare to say so.
He punished Zhao Hua'an as a warning
and won popular support.
Rong Jiashang
can be capable.
I also got wind
that Rong Jiashang issued a new order.
All businesses of Rong Company
can't be implemented
without his review, signature or seal.
In this way,
their channel of opium smuggling
will be cut off.
We can hardly get anything on them.
What about Rong Dingkun?
He's been staying in his residence
without coming out even once.
The Rong family is offering
five times the salary
to recruit a nurse.
Rong Dingkun
never dreamed
that he would be paralyzed at this age
and that his son grabbed his power.
It's not enough. I want more.
I'll make him watch it
when his family is broken up and ruined.
One more thing, Mr. Meng.
We've figured out
where Miss Feng is living.
Do you want the address…?
No.
As long as I know she's all right,
I'm contented.
Come on in.
Mr. Meng, you've got a visitor.
He asked to meet you alone.
Meet me alone? Who's he?
He didn't leave a name, but a note.
He said you would know
upon seeing it.
(I know all Rong Dingkun's secrets.)
Get him in.
You may go.
- Yes.
Mr. Meng.
Mr. Yang, long time no see.
Mr. Meng,
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I had no choice
but to come and beg you.
Please save me.
I heard about your affair with Miss Du.
I also heard
that you decamped
with a lot of Rong Dingkun's money.
What?
Trying to come back now?
Decamped?
How could I?
Mr. Meng, you know very well
what kind of man Rong Dingkun is.
He has woken up.
He'll certainly hunt me down.
Throughout Shanghai,
Zhao Hua'an's men are everywhere.
Even the Du family won't let me go.
I'm...
I'm driven to the wall.
I know you're looking for me, too.
I indeed know
many of Rong Dingkun's secrets.
As long as you keep me alive,
I will
tell you without reserve.
I have to see how valuable
the secrets can be.
Come and have a look.
How much is this?
Have a browse first.
If you want any,
you can bargain.
Come and have a look.
What about this? How much is it?
You have good taste.
- This one looks good, too.
- This is a new product.
Shizhen?
I can give you a discount.
Shaoqing?
Shizhen.
Come and have a look.
I should say thank you to you.
Without your help,
I would still be living
a hell-like life.
It's you
who gave me a new life.
I didn't expect
to see you again.
How was your life in Japan?
I got married.
I'm back in Peking with my husband
because he is on a business trip.
He's a diplomat.
Why are you in Peking?
I resigned from the Rong family.
Now I'm a teacher in a local school.
Were you implicated in my case?
After you left,
a lot more things happened
in the Rong family.
Fanglin and Fanghua were admitted
to McTyeire School for Girls.
I completed my duty
as their governess.
Then I got the job in Peking.
Do you know
how my sister is doing?
I was so keen to run away
that I didn't consider
how she would end up.
Shortly after you left,
she gave birth to a son.
I guess
the Rong family will be nice to her.
She indeed has a son.
That's what she was expecting.
Later,
she straightened out her ideas.
She managed to understand you.
She also thought it was good for you
to run away.
She asked me
to tell you
that she missed you a lot
if I could meet you again.
If possible,
I'll visit her in Shanghai.
Let me give you an address.
Her son is in poor health
and he's staying in the hospital
where my brother works.
If you miss your sister,
you can write a letter
to the address of the hospital.
All right.
My brother will give the letter to her.
Shaoqing,
take care.
So do you.
Father,
time for lunch.
You unfilial son!
How do you have the nerve to come?
I... I spent most of my life
establishing the family business.
This is what I earned!
But you ruined it all!
I don't want the meal.
I want opium.
I want...
I want... I want opium!
According to the doctor,
if your waist hurts,
you can have some opium.
It hurts.
It... It hurts.
It...
Give it to me.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Father,
did you have a wife and children
before you married my mother?
Who are you?
I'm your son,
Rong Jiashang.
Jiashang?
You've grown up.
Father.
Before me,
did you have a son and a daughter?
No.
You're my only son
of your generation.
When you were born,
you weighted 3.4kg.
You indeed tortured your mother.
Your crying
nearly raised the roof.
You indeed
made me proud.
Father,
I heard
that you had another family.
Who told you that?
Ma'am and Uncle Zhao.
They also said
that they died of illness.
No.
They were my brother's family.
Why did you never mention
that I had an uncle?
Why do you ask?
I'm just curious.
You said I was your first son.
Do I have an elder sister, then?
No.
You're the only son I have.
You're my only son.
Father.
Father?
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪