Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ♡♥ Unraveling a Heart Team ♥♡ @ Viki.com
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold, the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend, we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world, a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 2]
Go, bring 2,000 taels.
Wait
2,000 taels was the price before.
It's changed now. 5,000 taels.
You!
You raised the price on the spot.
When we saved Lord Ning
since we saved Lord Ning.
Now, with interest, it's at least 3,000 taels.
The other 2,000 taels is for angering my Grandmother. I'm not happy about it.
What? Lady Ning feels wronged?
Or...do you not think Young Lord Ning isn't worth 5,000 taels?
You!
Mother, you can't!
Enough. Stop with the attitude.
Mother! Why should you give it to her?
Tell her you're not giving her anything and to get out!
If we drag this out it'll hurt your brother's prestige.
He's about to take his government tests.
Spend a little money for peace.
Madam
Mother, I'll give this to her!
Here's the 5,000 taels you wanted.
Here!
If you dare throw it, I'll add another 5,000.
Here.
Miss, I never thought you'd actually get anything
but you really did it!
5,000 taels!
I just wanted to get justice. I don't have to have this money
but I don't want Grandmother to suffer over this.
You're returning favors and giving justice to injustice.
Miss,
what are you going to do with all this money?
Go to the Capital.
Zhen Zhen, you really cancelled the engagement?
Yes, cancelled.
It was the fault of the Ning family for insulting me first.
We're in the right.
But since you did this,
this engagement is really cancelled.
Grandmother, it's not sad and I don't regret it.
This type of family, even if I marry into it, it may not be a good thing.
You cancelled this engagement for a moment of anger.
Before doing this, you should have discussed it with us.
They slandered Uncle and angered Grandmother.
I must get justice.
Zhen Zhen...there are other ways to cancel the engagement.
Exchanging it for money is really...
This money is to teach them a lesson.
Grandmother, I won't lower my head to make peace with the Ning family.
This engagement...let's just end it here.
This bracelet is for you.
I can't, Grandmother. This is precious to you.
Take it as...wearing it for your mother.
The bracelet went with her
so she owes you one. I'll give it to you.
It looks pretty on you.
Take it as a token from me.
In the future, Fang Mansion will be your home.
You can live her peacefully.
Thank you, Grandmother.
[Lord Cheng Mansion]
Zan'er is still unwilling to give up his armor.
Zan'er.
Father, mother, you came.
This time going to the capital to meet the Emperor...
have you thought how you're going to handle it?
You know why I'm doing this.
His majesty suspects me of selling the roadmap of capital city and leaking our military plan.
This is not trivial.
You can't let your guard down.
Zan'er.
How can we let you go to the Capital like this?
Mother, I'm already grown.
And plus I've been fighting battles with Father over all.
What problems have I not encountered?
What should I be afraid of?
Of course it's other people's intentions.
You and your father know how to fight and kill on the battlefield.
But the people in the Capital are conniving.
Rest assure
Father has so many people in the Palace.
They'll be sure to protect me.
What I worry about
is Father managing the military by himself.
He'll be too busy.
Don't worry about the issues here.
As long as you come back safe and sound, everything will be fine.
Zan'er, you're fate after returning to the capital is unpredictable.
You must be cautious.
Have Baotang return with you.
You can take care of each other on the road.
If you need something, follow the old rule
let the Sky Pavilion handle it.
Sanbing will stay in the north
to take care of military affairs/
Zan'er.
His Majesty has already bestowed marriage to Jiuling.
Why go through all the trouble as his official?
Mother, this is...
my wedding present for Jiuling.
I'm an adult now. I won't mess around.
Enough.
Our son has to get on the road.
Let him keep packing.
Let's go.
Father...Mother...
Your son is leaving,
please accept your son's bows.
Fulai Hotel
Here, Second Brother.
This wine is pretty good.
Pretty good, right?
Second Brother.
They're staring at us so hard their eyes are about to fall out.
Waiter, more food! I'm hungry!
Have another cup, Second Brother.
Here it comes.
Customer, your noodles!
Customer...
I'm so sorry!
So sorry!
Valued customers, so sorry! This waiter is new.
He doesn't know the rules. If you have any issues, please tell me.
The people of the Sky Pavilion are still so embarrassing.
Get away!
Thank you, Sir!
Eunuch Li, I will clean up myself.
Is the master fine?
So careles.
Everyone, sit.
What is it?
It's nothing. Let's talk about it after we eat.
Give it here.
It's really nothing. Let's talk about it after we eat.
Give it.
The news may not be accurate.  You need to verify it later.
Princess Jiuling was imprisoned after the wedding. A fire in the prison killed her beyond recognition.
Princess Jiuling was burned beyong recognition.
Let's eat.
Second Brother.
This...
Jiuling, she...
passed away.
That is what the letter says.
Second brother, don't worry.
Officials, he drank too much.
I will check him now.
Fulai Hotel
So are you a young hero?
Of course.
After all, I will guard the border with my father.
Now that I am leaving, you compliment me.
Then will you miss me?
Of course not.
I am joking with you.
You will be the only one I miss from the capital.
What difference is between me and others?
You are different with any others.
You are the one and only Princess Jiuling of this world.
Jiuling, once I go,
I don't know when I can come back.
Perhaps one year or perhaps two years.
Perhaps three or four years. Or even longer.
No matter when you come back, I will wait for you here at the capital.
Second brother, don't worry.
The news is not verified yet.
Besides, it is doubtful that it is true.
Although the letter said that Princess Jiuling died,
it also said that she was burned beyond recognition.
Is it possible that it might not be her.
Baotang, what you say could be right.
Continue.
Right, the letter also said,
The old friend of the late emperor, Jun Yingwen, appears
when Princess Jiuling was imprisoned.
Is there any connection between these two events?
There is something else there.
Where is Jun Yingwen?
His whereabouts is unknown but his daughter, Jun Zhenzhen,
went to her maternal grandmother at Zezhou.
Jun Zhenzhen?
Zezhou?
Let's go to Zezhou.
Second Brother!
Eunuch Wei, I gave you more than 10 people to watch Zhu Zan.
You let him escape.
It is all my fault. Please spare me, Your Majesty.
- Drag him out.
- Yes.
Please spare me Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Please spare me, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Say, why did this Zhu Zan run away?
Maybe it's because he was worried that he would be punished
for the roadmap of the capital city, so he fled the capital.
If you were Zhu Zan
and you wanted to run away,
would you choose to run away when outside of the capital
or escape to the northern lands?
Look.
Go look for him. No.
Capture him back.
Yes.
What do you
think about Princess Jiuli?
Princess Jiuli has a pure heart and is gentle and respectful.
She is the example of the imperial court.
Will she become a second Jiuling?
On the wedding day, the two princesses did not meet. Jiuling...
After Jiuling passed away,  Princess Jiuli was grieving over her loss.
So I think that she does not know about the late emperor.
That is what you think.
People are unpredictable.
I petition to marry Princess Jiuli.
Take your time. Wait after the 100th day of Jiuling's funeral.
Yes.
[Wu De Si]
Family Lu's Ancestor Temple
A girl named Jiu Ling is being blessed by heaven.
Jiuling, did you just leave us like this?
Jiuling, I stopped you at the temple,
to save your life.
I brought people to the celestial prison
to also protect you.
I'm sorry, Jiuling.
I came late.
I calculated the right moment to save you.
Yet I didn't expect
you to die in a fire.
Now,
Chu Rang fears Princess Jiuli and Jiurong.
I can only marry Princess Jiuli
to protect you better.
Now that you are no longer here,
you will protect everything you care about on your behalf.
The third year of Taiyan
The third year of Taiyan.
That year, your grandfather was captured by the people of the Northern region.
This silver was created to pay for his ransom.
We sent this government silver to Zezhou to hand over to the people of the Northern region.
However, they became hostile, broke the agreement and said that we were not trustworthy.
They refused to release your grandfather.
In the end, your grandfather and several uncles
died in the hands of the people from the Northern region.
This was a humiliation.
Government silver? Seal?
Is this the seal to instruct the delivery of the government silver during the third year of Tai Yan?
If I join Fang family to gain experience, perhaps, this is a good opportunity for me to investigate.
[Fang Mansion]
- You both are...
- I'm looking for Miss Jun. Please report to her.
What's your family name?
It's Ling. Please report immediately.
Miss, someone out there is looking for you.
- Looking for me?
- Yes.
He mentioned that his family name is Ling and he's looking for Miss Jun.
Ling?
Will you meet him?
No. How can she casually meet a man?
Alright. I'm going to reply him.
Hold on.
Perhaps, I remembered wrongly. I will meet him.
Alright.
Second Brother.
Where is the Mister Ling?
Ba Cheng, you lied. Check first next time before you call our Young Mistress.
Liu'er, he must have made a mistake.
It's fine. Let's go back.
Take a look at the colorful umbrellas.
Buns, just out from the pot.
Let's go.
Second Brother, why isn't she out yet?
- I have already...
- Is Fang Mansion a place for you to mess around? Leave now!
He...
One shouldn't visit with an anonymous name.
I was too abrupt.
We can only wait till Miss Jun goes out.
Second Brother, what about...
that trick?
That trick was used against the soldiers from Northern region. Using this trick on a young lady?
Alright, I'm wrong.
Fine. If we don't use that trick, do you have any good tricks?
Alright. Be there soon.
I heard a female cousin went to De Shengchang shop a few days ago.
I wonder if this is true.
You checked in such details. Are you trying to join the Fang family?
Don't, don't.
Fang family is a dead man's curse. I dare not offend it.
Come, let's drink our tea.
[De Shengchang]
These are the accounts for that year. It's useless to read them.
Miss, take a look.
If there anything you need me to explain?
It's not necessary.
I'm leaving.
Zhenzhen,
familiarize yourself today with these. If you are tired, go back and rest.
Thank you, Older Sister. I'm leaving.
Grandmother was kind to let her learn the accounts. In the end,
she's not interested in De Shengchang at all. She's merely dealing with Grandmother.
Older Sister.
Third year of Taiyan was a long time ago. We must plan to obtain the accounts of that year.
Miss, I think you are not interested in De Shengchang at all.
It's fine.
You are obviously reluctant.
Why don't you go back to the old  lady and do stuff that you like?
Grandmother is doing this for my sake too.
What's going on?
How did you drive the carriage?
Miss, a hand cart was damaged
and blocked the road.
Come.
What's going on?
The wheel of this hand cart is damaged. Take a detour.
Miss, this is bad.
Let's walk. We can take a stroll.
Miss, this is not appropriate. If any mishaps happen along the way,
I can't undertake this responsibility. It's better that I escort you...
It's fine. Don't worry.
Our young mistress came from the capital and didn't get lost. How could she get lost in a small place like Zezhou?
Let's go, Miss.
Liu'er,
it's the job of the carriage driver to escort his passengers safely.
Talk to him nicely in the future. Don't use such attitude with him again.
Miss, you will be bullied by others with your good temper.
No. You are definitely that kind
who treat others politely when they do the same to you.
When others treat you in an arrogant manner, you will retaliate, right?
Why do you say that?
Because you treated Mrs Ning in this way.
Miss, I just passed by a pastry shop.
They looked delicious. Do you want to have some? Want to take a look?
Go and buy them. I will wait here for you.
Miss, are you alone?
Remove your dirty hand from me.
How could such a beautiful lady with a good temper be so irritable?
Don't blame me for being impolite.
Impolite? I'm so scared.
She's being impolite to me. Everyone, take a look.
How could she do this? This is too much. In broad daylight too.
What is she doing?
- Release me.
- Fine.
How insulting.
Stop!
Look.
Let go.
Brat, mind your own business.
Are you alright?
Apologize to her.
Impossible.
I was wrong.
Firstly, your apology was too soft.
Once more time.
Your so-called apology was because
I'm highly skilled in martial arts and you were helpless in this situation.
What do you want then?
Miss, what is your wish?
I want to report him to the official.
Miss, I think today was a misunderstanding.
Why not reduce this major problem into a trivial matter? Miss, you are magnanimous.
He escaped.
This little thief was rather formidable.
Don't bother about me. It's fine.
Miss.
I helped you.
Shouldn't you help me too?
Miss.
I forget to bring my wallet. The account is not settled yet.
Can I please know your name?
I will pay my debt tomorrow.
No need.
Take it as a repayment of your assistance today.
It's right and proper to repay debts.
I must pay my debt.
Mister, do you know that person?
You must be joking.
The hand cart which was damaged and blocked the road was arranged by you too, right?
I think you have misunderstood me.
I have seen this type of trick before.
Miss, since you know,
why would you pay for me? Why not just leave?
I just want to come see what other tricks you have.
I indeed have another thing.
Is your father Jun Yiwen?
Do you know my father?
I heard of him.
You are...?
I'm Ling Jiu. "Ling" as in "rule" the kingdom. "Jiu" as in "when all's said and done".
Ling Jiu.
No matter when you come back,
write me a letter in advance and I'll wait for you at the city gate.
Really? You will wait no matter how long it is.
When have I ever lied to you?
But...
But if I'm gone for too long
and many years pass,
what should I do if you don't recognize me anymore?
When that time comes, if someone impersonate me,
Don't be deceived.
I got it. I'll gift you a name so you will be the one and only.
I'm called Jiuling so you'll be called Lingjiu. What do you think?
Jiuling and Lingjiu?
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
I like it very much!
Lingjiu?
- Miss Jun/
- It's you, Zhu Zan.
So it's you.
Miss Jun, are you all right?
Miss Jun, I was abrupt today because of someone.
Princess Jiuling.
I know your father and you just left the capital.
Have you seen Princess Jiuling?
I will never harm your father and Princess Jiuling.
Please believe me.
I do not know where they are.
The princess and I have known each other since we were young.
The princess's whereabouts are very important to me.
Where is the princess?
I really do not know.
If you do not believe me, you may ask others.
I shall leave now.
You're back?
Second Brother, how was it?
Your acting is too awful that people see through you.
Can people see through my acting?
This Miss Jun is very discerning.
What happened afterwards?
Have you found out anything related to Princess Jiuling?
Nothing?
What a waste.
I keep feeling like she hiding something from me.
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
Try it.
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable cause and effect ♫
It tastes very good.
Miss Jun, I was abrupt today because of someone.
Princess Jiuling.
♫ With many tomorrows to come, I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
Zhu Zan,
Zhu Zan, the previous innocent and bubbly Chu Jiuling
is now the Jun Zhenzhen who's irrelevant to you.
On this journey of revenge, I must not implicate any innocent people.
If I'm careless, everyone in the Duke Mansion will be consigned to eternal damnation.
For Imperial Father, Zhenzhen, and Master,
I have no other choice.
However, you are not the same. Zhu Zan,
you don't need to go through all this for a dead person.
Although Princess Jiuling is dead,
you must live well.
Forgive me.
for not recognizing you.
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
[Blue Cloud Rundown Inn]
Jun Zhenzhen knows Jiuling's whereabouts for sure.
Is she afraid to tell me?
Scattering rose petals in the tea,
did Jiuling teach her that?
Second Brother, don't think any more about it. Rest.
Eat this. Try it. It's very fresh.
There's no meat in this. Replace it.
Looking at the closed shell, I didn't know it's empty.
What is it?
Achieving one's aim by underhanded means to save the princess is a crime of deceiving the monarch.
Even if I reveal my identity to her,
we are not close with each other.
She will close up like this shell.
Then what should we do?
If Mr Jun and Jiuling are safe and they can't show themselves,
they will have problems with food and clothes.
If Jun Zhenzhen knows their whereabouts, then she will surely go there.
Miss, he seems to be Fang Chengyu,
the eldest son of the Fang family,
Are you the rumored female cousin, Jun Zhenzhen?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ♡♥ Unraveling a Heart Team ♥♡ @ Viki.com
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come, I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come, I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers, I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫