♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 12
Capital city
Guanghuamen
Danfengmen
Mansion of Prince Huai
Tomb of Beloved Wife Princess Jiuling
By Husband Lu Yunqi
Be patient
and listen to me.
All this begins with the origin of Miss Jun.
You only know that Miss Jun
is the granddaughter of the Fang family.
But do you know
her family
has practiced medicine for generations and inherited medical skills
for several hundred years?
Her father,
Jun Yingwen
was a famous doctor in Runan.
She is Jun Jiuling,
the highly skilled doctor
who learnt the medical skills at home
and took over her family business!
Miss Jun is a highly skilled doctor.
How can a girl
become a highly skilled doctor?
Yes.
Your story
is far off the mark.
Miss Jun wanted to
take over her family business
and reopen Jiuling Drugstore in Runan.
After hearing the misfortunes of the Fang family,
killings of her grandpa and uncle
and her dying cousin,
she was determined
to help the Fang family through the crisis
and think out a wonderful plan.
Miss Jun
detoxified and cured
Young Master Fang
under the guise
of marriage.
To find out the plotter behind
Li Changhong,
Miss Jun even
risked her life.
With the sick and weak
and the old and disabled,
she returned to Runan
after a long and arduous journey.
She met ambushes,
broke through traps
and stumbled through
various dangers.
She revealed
the big case that Li Changhong and officers and soldiers
had been in collusion for over 10 years.
She broke off
an engagement and thought out a wonderful plan
under the guise of marriage.
The highly skilled
doctor Miss Jun didn't return overnight to help her grandma,
a royal businesswoman, turn the table by a written instruction.
I'm not good at storytelling.
This is a story fabricated by storytellers.
Good.
It must
have been fabricated by the Fangs.
You don't know.
The storytellers in the whole city
like to tell the story that
the highly skilled doctor Miss Jun
saved the Fang family from danger, fought with bad guys
and treated the sick people most,
followed by the story that Great-grandpa Fang
obtained the imperial decree
of establishing Deshengchang.
I'm not good at storytelling.
I'll take you to a teahouse tomorrow
and you can listen there.
Zan,
we've almost finished
our investigation in Zezhou.
Where will we go?
Go back to the capital city.
Don't forget
how we escaped from the capture of the men of Arm Moral Department.
If we go back to the capital city now, we'll be caught.
If we don't go and ask for punishment,
how can I dispel Chu Rang's suspicion of me?
And
I have something more important to do.
I know what you want to do.
Go on.
Uphold justice for the late emperor and princess,
right?
Have your meal.
After that, go to bed early.
We'll go back to the capital city tomorrow.
Your Excellency,
our men chased her the whole night,
but she still escaped.
She went to the capital city.
The capital city?
Yes.
If she knows who we are,
she won't escape
to the capital city
and fall into our snare.
Your Excellency,
our men have entered the city.
Do we
strike the Fangs now?
Their daughter-in-law
didn't go home the whole night.
A girl
served water and food in the inn.
She's
kicking up a cloud of dust.
Leave it alone.
Let's first go back to the capital city
and report to His Majesty.
Yes.
Jun.
Chengyu,
where is Jun?
She left a letter to you.
Ling Jiu,
thank you for helping me
find out the plotter behind who framed up the Fang family.
To keep my word,
I'll figure out the secret of Zezhou
and tell you all about it.
I learnt from my grandma
the official funds in the third year of the Taiyan period
had really been
secretly handed over
by Chu Rang to the Fang family
as their start-up funds
to support Chu Rang.
Now
only my grandma knows this past event in the whole family.
The Fang family has been taught a lesson
because of their mistakes.
The rest are innocent.
You promised me to let the Fang family go.
Please keep your promise.
Don't baffle them
at any time.
See you,
Ling Jiu.
I don't know when we'll meet next time.
Take care.
Dispel the grief of losing the dead
as soon as possible
and look forward to your future life.
Jun Jiuling.
You don't need me,
so you abandon me,
with only a letter left.
Where did she go?
She left.
She only said that
she had some private things to deal with.
I also don't know
where she went.
Do you
like her?
Do you actually like her?
Jun,
you haven't answered my question.
Why did you leave?
Leave it alone.
I'll go back to the capital city first.
It turns out that
I have so many memories in Zezhou.
I have a new family.
I found out the secret of Zezhou
and met Zhu Zan,
but
I still had to say goodbye to him.
I go back to the capital city
to find the way in my heart this time.
Even if it is extremely dangerous,
as long as I survive,
I will firmly go on.
Jiuli,
Jiurong,
I'll go back to the capital city to protect you.
Chen's sugar figurines.
Sir.
Would you like a sugar figurine?
OK.
Five coins per one.
Here you are.
Chen's sugar figurines.
The specialty of Zezhou,
Yes, yes, yes.
Chen's sugar figurines.
Unexpectedly,
Madame Su of the Fang family
is so cruel.
Yes.
She has a daughter.
Does she?
How can Miss Fang
-continue her life? -The specialty of Zezhou.
How, indeed?
She must feel terribly ashamed.
Is the woman
surnamed Su in collusion
with Shopkeeper Song…
Yes.
She is just my mom.
What a nuisance.
Miss Fang,
have a sugar figurine.
You'll feel better
after having it.
No need.
Try it.
Try it, please.
No need.
My sugar figurine…
Only several coins.
I pay you.
Sorry.
I don't have any money with me.
But I'll keep it in my mind
and pay you next time.
It doesn't matter.
I can make them.
Never mind.
Were you driven out by the Fangs?
Good.
You're free.
I wasn't driven out.
I just want to leave there.
Where will you go?
It's none of your business.
Not exactly.
Fate makes us
meet here.
I think
you were like my long-lost friend at our first meeting.
I'll treat you
to a meal today,
OK?
The fried boiled pork ahead
is very delicious.
Would you like to taste it?
Let's go,
Miss Fang.
Go.
Come on.
Miss Fang,
quickly.
Your Ladyship, look.
Here we are.
Let me support you.
Was my father killed by you?
Yes.
What do you want to do?
Chu Rang,
I'll regain everything you seized from my father
and put the matter in the right light.
The capital city,
I'm back.
Your Ladyship,
where will we first go after entering the city?
The Map of Capital City is very detailed.
Where do you want to go?
Can we first
find something to eat?
We ate solid food all the way,
and my teeth can't bear.
OK.
Well then, let's go here.
Let's go.
Here we are, Miss Fang.
This restaurant.
Please.
Let me tell you.
Like my sugar figurines,
the fried boiled pork of this restaurant
is also a specialty
of Zezhou.
You'll know after having it.
Boss,
I want
a bowl of fried boiled pork.
OK.
I just began my business
and sold several sugar figurines today.
Let's just order one bowl of pork.
Don't refuse.
We
both know
each other well.
As friends,
it's common for us
to sit and have a meal.
Don't shed tears
over the changes of seasons.
And don't mention my kindness,
repayment to me or the like.
Without doubt,
I'm not sympathizing with you.
Don't sympathize with me.
I just think
you, alone,
have a hard time.
Fortunately, you meet me today.
I have nothing to say
and I don't think as much as you said.
Just shut up, will you?
Here comes your dish.
It's hot.
OK.
Thank you, boss.
Be free.
Have a taste.
Don't bother.
I ate.
You said you're hungry.
Then I'll eat.
Where do you
stay now?
I stay in an inn.
It's good
to stay there,
but it costs a lot.
I don't think
it's a good place to stay in the long run.
To survive here,
you still need to make a living by some craft.
I have a good idea.
Why not learn to make sugar figurines from me?
Let's go over there.
Yunzhao,
we've devoted ourselves to preparing for the exam
in the capital city for a long time.
We rarely have time to go out and have tea.
Stop reading, OK?
Taste it.
It's good tea.
Young Master.
Young Master,
your letter.
From whom?
Sorry,
Wenming.
Forgive me for leaving for a while.
Go ahead.
Miss,
buy one.
Your Ladyship,
look.
It's so nice.
Your Ladyship,
look at this.
Do you think I don't even know the time of day?
No.
Do anything you like
and buy anything you want.
You have our money bag.
Well,
I'm a bit hungry.
What good food can we eat here?
Dong's dried meat.
Miss,
it's very fresh.
Dong's dried meat.
I remember it's recorded in the map
their dried meat is very tasty.
Why not have a try?
OK. OK.
Let's go.
Dong's dried meat. Boss,
I want a portion.
OK.
Liu'er,
I'll go out
to handle something later.
Wait for me in the inn.
OK.
Please hurry right back.
How much?
Three coins per portion.
OK. Thank you.
See you.
The marriage of Miss Jun and Young Master Fang
is just a strategy.
Where is
she now?
Can we meet again?
Your Majesty, calm down please.
Due to your incompetence,
the Fang family gets rid of their unpresentable identity
and becomes imperial businessmen in just ways.
It's hard for us to deal with them later.
How can I calm down?
Though they showed their identity,
they didn't mention anything about the official funds,
nor do they
suspect it was done by Your Majesty.
They firmly believe
Li Changhong and the evil Madame Su were in collusion.
This plan must have been designed
by someone clever.
The reason why they didn't mention the past
is to protect themselves.
Having always been
in the palace,
I'm known by no one outside,
so
no one suspects
Your Majesty is involved in it.
Now the Fang family only knows
there must be someone
behind this matter,
but they don't care
who he is.
If
we do anything to them rashly,
it'll cause
all the people's speculations
of us.
If they know how to behave in this delicate situation
and don't cause any trouble,
I'll spare their lives
for some days
and decide whether to keep them or not
after it blows over.
Your Majesty, you're wise.
Jiuli,
Jiurong,
I'm back.
Are you sure he is His Lordship?
Yes.
As soon as he entered the capital city,
our men have targeted him.
His Lordship?
Boss,
another plateful of meat
and another beaker of wine.
OK.
Zhu Zan.
Enjoy yourselves.
OK.
Although you've been here for a long time,
I'm sure you don't know
the marinated meat in this restaurant tastes best.
Why do you still have the mood to eat?
Don't
you know
who the most wanted person
of Arm Moral Department is?
Yes, I know.
So eat
before they come.
If they come,
they'll spoil our mood.
I have no mood.
Eat quickly.
Enjoy your food.
If you eat worriedly,
you don't think anything tasty.
Have this.
You still have the mood to joke with other
at this critical moment.
Go back.
Don't you go with me?
I have something important to do.
After that, I'll go to the palace.
Go to the palace?
Why does he go to the palace?
Does
he want to confront Chu Rang
about the secret in Zezhou?
What's the last thing
he wants to do?
Let me go with you, OK?
Go back.
I know when to stop.
Don't flaunt your superiority.
OK.
Then I'll go back.
Don't you need my help?
Wait.
Pay.
Boss,
here you are.
OK.
See you.
Take care.
It's
my tomb.
It turns out I was buried
in the ancestral cemetery of the Lu family after death.
I was bound by this marriage
when I was alive and after I died.
I'm coming.
I'm back.
I bring the flower,
northern manjusaka,
you want.
What is
he doing?
Outline in my dream
can be carved on your face
Time interlaces in the eye waves
For unspeakable cause and effect
Let me weigh every word
Life is full of twists and turns
So hard to be free and easy
Tomorrow always comes
I'd like to entrust myself to you
to enjoy stars and the land together
In long silence
We are far separated by a sea of faces
What else can I do except for a sigh?
The rest of my life is bumpy
You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind
I'm be eventually be passed by
The wind is in hot pursuit
to stay with nature
If memories can tell
It will make me shed tears
Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes
Tomorrow always comes
I'd like to entrust myself to you
to enjoy stars and the land together
In long silence
We are far separated by a sea of faces
What else can I do except for a sigh?
The rest of my life is bumpy
You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind
I'm be eventually be passed by
The wind is in hot pursuit
to stay with nature
If memories can tell
Every of its words will make me shed tears
Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes
You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind
You shuttle through the bottom of my heart
Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?
If my longing for you can be written down
Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down
You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again
Tears well up in my eyes
Let me perform magic for you.
Wait a moment.
I have a wish.
Can you help me realize it?
What wish?
Go ahead.
I can help you realize it.
It's heard there's a kind of flower called manjusaka in the north.
It looks very pretty in its flowering.
Bring one flower back with me
when you come back.
OK.
I promise you.
Is it pretty?
I think you look good with it.
Jiuling,
let me tell you a secret
which has been hidden in my heart.
I thought to tell you about it
when you called me Ling Jiu again.
But I had no chance anymore.
I like you.
I came immediately
when I got the news of your marriage.
But it was late.
Late.
Chu Jiuling already died,
but now Jun Jiuling knows
you covered 1,000 li
to pick this flower from the north,
during which you escaped from escort,
changed your name,
risked your life entering the capital city
and acted in black at night.
You just want to put this flower
before my tomb.
You cheat me.
You aren't buried inside.
Do you know?
I met a girl
who is exactly like you.
But I know she isn't you.
What should I do?
Lu Yunqi.
Your Lordship,
this is the ancestral cemetery of my family.
It's improper for you
to come here.
Because Jiuling's tomb is here.
She's my dead wife.
Lu Xiaozao,
listen.
How did Jiuling die?
She died of an acute illness.
The imperial doctor felt her pulse
before marriage.
Why did a healthy girl
die suddenly
at her wedding ceremony?
Human affairs are hard to predict.
But
it has nothing to do with you.
Your harassment is useless.
Stop cheating me.
Since it's useless to say more,
let's do something useful.
I'll teach you
a lesson
with my sword
for Jiuling.
Save it.
You dirty brat,
I'm afraid you've forgotten
why you're called Lu Xiaozao.
Let me remind you.
You were
black, small
and as thin as a rake.
If my dad hadn't taken you in,
you would have starved to death at the roadside.
Now
you begin to steal.
Dare you steal again?
Tell me.
Dare you steal?
Dare you?
I dare you.
You…
Zhu Zan.
Catch him.
Make way. Make way.
Get out of the way.
Eunuch Yuan.
I'm going to present myself to His Majesty.
Why do you stop me?
Eunuch Yuan,
he wanted to kill me here.
Your Lordship,
you're an adult.
Don't run wild again.
OK.
Look.
Your Excellency Lu,
His Majesty asked me
to take His Lordship to the palace.
Why do they take him to the palace?
Your Lordship,
please.
Please.
Your Excellency,
will we just let him go?
Go back to Arm Moral Department.
Let's go.
Zhu Zan,
you're so clever
that you can expect that your public appearance in the capital city
will cause an uproar.
So
entering the palace
is also your plan to get out,
isn't it?
I hope everything goes as you expected
and you can return safely.
Miss Jun.
Mr. Ning.
Miss Jun,
long time no see.
Long time no see.
You helped the Fang family
get rid of danger,
which is admirable.
You know all?
Yes, my family mentioned it in a letter.
Why do you come here?
I'm,
I'm here for something.
But no one knows I'm here
except my family.
So…
OK.
I'll keep it a secret for you.
If you need any help here,
please find me
in my uncle's mansion.
OK.
Do you have anything on your mind?
The metropolitan exam is drawing near.
You'll have good grades for sure.
Let it be.
You're determined to be an official.
It's my inescapable duty
to continue and develop my family.
You're good at reading,
but the official circles are full of danger.
I know
you're honest.
My uncle also reminded me of that.
Do you also know the law of the official circles?
Anyhow,
I hope you can pass the exam
and get what you want.
See you.
Miss Jun, let me
send you home.
No, thanks.
It's just ahead.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫