♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 5
Show Your Skills
Yunmengze Inn
Chengyu, look over there.
Chengyu.
It's cold at night.
Would you like a hand warmer?
No, thanks.
Jinxiu,
Chengyu has got better,
so he isn't afraid of cold.
Much heat may chafe him.
OK.
I'll listen to you.
Chengyu,
it's Fire God Temple
ahead,
which is the most lively place
at the Lantern Festival every year.
Yes.
Does my Mother worry
I'm seen by others?
You doesn't do anything wrong.
Don't worry.
Relax.
There's a constant stream of visitors
tonight.
So many people.
Yunzhao.
Fortunately,
you're here today.
You should thank me.
Yes.
It's crowded ahead.
Are the best lanterns displayed?
Yes.
It's heard
there're unique and novel lanterns
in various styles
this year.
Let's go
and have a look.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Go and have a look.
This year's lanterns are really nice.
Do you like
to watch lanterns in the daytime?
Watch lanterns in the daytime?
I think
it's another kind of pleasure
to watch lanterns in the daytime.
I don't like it.
I just like
the colorful lanterns
on the night of the Lantern Festival.
You're still unchanged.
Yunzhao,
what if you meet
Miss Fang
at the lantern show
today?
What if,
indeed?
Let it be.
Let's just
have a good time.
Even if others laugh at
and talk about me,
I don't care.
You indeed have
a detached attitude.
Yes, yes, yes.
There're so many lanterns.
Grandma, look over there.
Grandma,
may I leave
for a while later?
Over there. Over there.
It's the Lantern Festival today.
Enjoy yourselves.
Don't accompany me.
Go and watch lanterns.
Let's go.
Let me push, Your Ladyship.
OK.
Chengyu,
is it fun to come out?
Yes.
Look over there.
Novermber-15th day.
He's surrounded.
Wonderful.
Good move.
Four seasons-15th day.
Person-15th day.
Your Ladyship,
where's the lantern you made?
Why haven't we seen it?
Don't be anxious.
We're almost there.
I just saw there're nuts for sale.
Would you like them?
I'll go and buy some.
Go ahead.
I'm waiting for you here.
Please hold it.
I lost.
Everyone,
does anyone want to challenge?
You wait
and see.
After we enjoy ourselves
to the full,
you can go and challenge,
which will amaze all the onlookers.
Me.
Be careful.
Don't lose,
or you'll lose face.
Five elements-six palaces.
Six palaces-five elements.
Wrong.
First attack the middle route.
Seven dippers-six palaces.
Seven dippers-five elements.
Six palaces - six palaces, long.
Six palaces - four seasons.
Seven dippers-six palaces.
Eighteen stars-eight directions.
Eighteen pines-seven dippers, connected.
15th day- eighteen pines.
Fourteen pheasants- sixteen phases.
Five elements-nineteen guests.
Miss,
please.
Slowly. Slowly.
December-10th day.
December-six palaces.
Nine states-nine states.
Eight directions-eight directions.
Nine states- eight directions.
Eight directions-seven dippers.
Heaven-seven dippers.
November-earth.
Four seasons-heaven.
Person-heaven.
Six palaces - heaven, connected.
Nine states- six palaces.
Eight directions-five elements, connected.
Sixteen phases- nine states.
Seventeen stars- 10th day.
Nineteen guests-seven dippers.
Nineteen guests- nine states.
Six palaces- fourteen pheasants.
Heaven-six palaces.
Heaven-five elements.
Heaven-eight directions.
Four seasons-fourteen phases.
Five elements-15th day.
Seven dippers-thirteen intercalary days.
Seven dippers- 15th day.
10th day-heaven.
Nine states-heaven.
November-heaven.
November-person.
15th day-six palaces.
15th day-five elements.
Earth-person.
Earth-eight directions.
Heaven-earth.
Sixteen phases-heaven.
Thirteen intercalary days-earth.
I admire your superior skills
in the game of go.
I bow to your superior skills.
Childe, you're modest.
That's
what I should
say to you.
Decisive
and thoughtful,
you thought it over before every move.
Your skills are indeed
better than mine.
You didn't win by luck.
But why
didn't you
drop the last piece?
Did you worry about me?
No.
The victory or defeat is obvious.
I didn't need to make an unnecessary move.
I can know your character by your go moves.
I'm impressed with your elegant go style.
I'm glad to play the go game with you.
I'm Ning Yunzhao.
May I
have your name?
Are you Childe Ning?
Yes.
Who is
your teacher?
My deceased father.
Where is your home?
Can I
have another chance
to have a competition with you?
You have superior go skills.
You are also better than I thought.
Here is for you.
Are you comforting me for my failure?
Happy birthday to you.
He was engaged to Zhenzhen.
If Zhenzhen were still alive,
she would be satisfied with the marriage.
I gave the lantern
to him for Zhenzhen.
Yunzhao.
I lost.
When did you accept a lantern?
Who gave you it?
I met a girl
who won me in the go game.
Won you?
You played a go game?
When did you play it?
No.
You're a child prodigy
who could remember every move at 8
and be well versed in go skills at 20.
Who could
win you in the world?
Who is she?
I also want to know.
Your Ladyship,
wait for me.
I finally saw you.
I thought I lost you
in the crowd.
Where's the lantern you made?
Over there.
"Show Your Skills".
Why is the lantern dim?
The lantern is the chessboard
and lanterns on it are pieces.
Now the black player
can win the game by one move.
Whoever makes the right move,
the lantern will light up.
Try. I'll try.
Wait.
Listen to me
before you try.
The 5,000-tael note in the glazed cup
is the prize.
5,000 taels.
Anyone who can let this lantern light up
can win the prize.
5,000 taels.
10 taels for each try.
If you have no money,
get out of here.
Your Ladyship,
Is the 5,000-tael note…
Yes.
You take the engagement annulment money of the Ning family…
You take the engagement annulment money of the Ning family as the prize.
If we lose,
we'll suffer.
Don't worry.
Few people can crack it
in this world.
That's good.
Then I'll be a looker-on with ease.
Zan,
the streets are crowded with visitors
when lanterns are lit.
I think the Lantern Festival of Zezhou
is as lively
as that of the capital city.
Zan,
you've been tired lately.
Relax yourself.
Let me tell you.
There's a go game today,
with 10 taels of silver for a try.
The winner
can win a 5,000-tael note.
I'm determined to get it.
Determined to get it.
Zan.
Baotang.
Zan, look.
I'll get down to my work.
Don't lead me
to these irrelevant places later.
Zan, here we are.
It's just ahead.
Don't, don't go.
Don't go.
Accompany me to have a try.
Sorry.
Miss Jun of the Fang family sets a go game ahead.
Let's go and have a look.
Go, go, go.
A go game?
With 10 taels of silver,
you can just buy a bottle of top rouge
in a top rouge shop of Zezhou,
buy a set of famille rose teacups
of the Ding kiln,
a tableful of first-class feast at Luyang Restaurant
and a writing brush
made of north wolf's hair.
Your Ladyship,
did you teach him to say that?
No.
Having been in Zezhou for such a long time,
we're indeed short of money.
Zan,
you've changed.
Have I?
No, no, no.
You haven't changed.
Don't hesitate.
You can have a chance to win the 5,000-tael note
with only 10 taels of silver.
It's
a god-given chance.
This keeper
knows a lot.
It seems he must often travel widely.
I, a businessman,
would like to try.
Your Ladyship,
we earned 10 taels.
Look.
Quickly.
I'll try.
It's interesting.
Yunzhao.
It's so difficult.
Yunzhao,
you've been skilled at go games since childhood.
Go and try.
Of an extraordinary mood,
the setter must be clever
and skilled in go games.
But I can't
crack it.
Can't you?
Go and have a try.
It's
a rare chance.
If you don't go,
I'll go later.
It can't be cracked at all.
Chengyu,
this year's lanterns
are much nicer than those in previous years.
They look joyful.
Yes.
Grandma,
that lantern is pretty.
Look at that.
Is it pretty?
Grandma,
do you know
where Zhenzhen is?
Why hasn't she come?
The lantern show is very bustling.
She must enjoy herself a lot
and forget us.
Do you know
where her lantern is?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Grandma,
I'm sort of tired.
Let's go home.
Chengyu,
are you alright?
Yes.
Having been here for a long time,
I'm also tired.
Let's
go back.
Go back.
Grandma,
I haven't enjoyed myself.
Let's go back, Jinxiu.
That lantern is very pretty.
Quickly.
Let me try.
It's a wrong move.
No one wants to try.
Yes.
Me.
I've watched here for a long time.
It isn't
a big deal.
It's important to be happy.
It's wrong.
He lacks self-knowledge.
Me.
No one can crack it.
As a sugar figurine seller,
you're a layman in go.
Don't make trouble
here.
Leave there.
Yes.
I'll show you
my real skill.
He's so confident.
Lay your piece.
Can't you crack it?
You're baffled.
Lay your piece.
Take back your silver.
Can you make it?
Can you, indeed?
Lay your piece.
Lay your piece quickly.
It's hard to make money.
Lay your piece.
Yes.
Can you make it?
It lights up.
5,000 taels.
I cracked it.
Yunzhao.
He really made the lantern light up.
I cracked it.
Where is the note?
No matter whether I can play the go games or not,
I cracked it.
Send the rest small bits of silver to my house.
Return our silver to us.
Your Ladyship.
We lost all our silver,
5,000 taels.
How long will it take
to earn so much money?
Your Ladyship.
I was kidding.
Just 5,000 taels.
You're so clever
that you can earn it quickly.
I'm not thinking about the lost silver.
Watch out.
Your Ladyship.
Butler Gao,
this is the keeper of your lantern last night,
Lei Zhonglian.
Why are you seated?
It doesn't matter,
Butler Gao.
I saw you last night.
You did a good job.
Did you also go to the scene last night?
I should see
who could crack my composition.
Do you know
who won the prize
in the end?
I heard others call him
Chen Qi.
Yes,
he's Chen Qi,
a sugar figurine seller.
In fact, he…
He can't play the go games.
Really?
Then he won so much silver
by luck.
Mr. Lei,
today I invited you here
to ask you a question.
Did you find something suspicious
after he cracked my composition?
Pay me for guarding your lantern.
Liu'er.
Last night…
Can I ask you a question?
What question?
5,000 taels is enough for you
to spend your life.
Why didn't you take it away?
Childe,
don't look down upon me.
We reached
an agreement.
If you hadn't reminded me,
I might have made a wrong move
and lost the chance to earn several thousand taels of silver.
You're true to your word.
Pay me.
Why?
I lost a sugar figurine.
Zan,
he is so mean.
Two childes of about 20
and one called the other brother,
right?
Since you know it,
why do you still ask me?
Um…
Well.
Lei Zhonglian.
You…
What did he do before?
He took care of carriages in a bank.
He has been in our family
for years.
Your Ladyship,
are you angry about
losing so much money yesterday?
No.
They cracked my composition by their skill.
I don't care about who the winner is.
Yunzhao.
No.
Yunyan,
you're so naughty.
Yunzhao,
is it worth pondering?
You've watched it
since you came home last night.
I tried to crack
this ancient composition.
You're well versed in go games.
I'm sure you can crack it.
Yunzhao,
the lantern looks good.
I'll take it
and put it together with the one in my room.
No.
I don't have it,
and I'll give it back to you
after placing it in my room for several days.
If you like this kind of lantern,
I'll buy you a new one.
Why do you
come to me?
Our Mother wonders
whether you fix the date of going back to the capital city.
I'll leave in several days.
I'll go and tell our Mother personally.
Yunzhao,
I'm leaving.
OK.
Why didn't you
tell you
before entering?
Santao asked me to come.
Seeing you're
in a good mood,
I didn't disturb you.
Did you have a good time
last night?
Yes.
No wonder
you didn't come to us.
I didn't trouble you,
so surely you could have a good time.
Are you angry with me?
Come on.
It's all my fault.
I watched who could crack my composition
most of the time
and failed to accompany you.
I know
you lost
a big sum of money.
Do you know all that?
Yes.
Grandma told me yesterday
and asked me not to mention it before you.
Then why do you mention it?
I'm glad to do it.
Give me your hand.
You've recovered quickly.
You can take a medicated bath soon.
Don't bother you with it.
Let Santao take care of me.
She also needs to listen to me.
And you and I
will get married.
Don't be shy.
You…
Childe,
you have a visitor.
Miss Jun,
what brings you here?
You managed to crack my composition last night.
Don't you wait for you?
Miss Jun,
what do you mean?
Does the sugar figurine taste good,
Zan?
Miss Jun is extremely intelligent.
I wonder
how you cracked my composition.
I can answer you,
but you should answer me a question first.
OK.
Go ahead.
How did Deshengchang start to go up?
Why do you ask this?
I find
its business is booming,
so I want to learn how to do business
and make some money.
So you came to me
in the lantern shop
and managed to ask me to visit you by winning my 5,000 taels by trick
at the Lantern Festival?
Yes.
I haven't finished.
The customers' information,
such as destinations and names, is recorded
as for the transport of general cargos.
Deshengchang has lots of customers,
so there must be documents.
He's indeed investigating the secret of Zezhou.
You really overestimate me.
I, one beyond the Fang family,
can't know
such a secret.
So can you
answer my question?
Because I am
extremely intelligent.
You…
Come on.
I'm not kidding you.
In fact,
my dad told me it.
When my dad taught me
how to crack this composition,
I listened
very carefully beside.
I'm extremely intelligent,
so I got it soon.
The people beside us
praised me loudly.
They said
I was very clever,
I was a matchless hero
and I was extremely intelligent.
I…
So I'm indeed extremely intelligent.
Zan,
the Sky Pavilion figured out the medicinal materials.
What disease can they treat?
This prescription is used
to treat a stubborn disease.
But such a prescription
with so many detoxification medicinal materials
is rare.
Only one
in the Fang family
suffers from a stubborn disease.
That dying Childe Fang.
Put all medicinal materials aside.
Handle it.
OK, shopkeeper.
Hello, Miss Jun.
Yes.
Have the medicinal materials
I booked last time come?
Yes.
Wait a Motherent.
I'll fetch them for you.
Thank you.
Miss Jun,
would you mind me asking you a question?
Who made the prescription
for you?
What's wrong with it?
No,
it's sort of strange.
Each of these medicinal materials
is effective,
but it's strange
to mix them
in a parcel.
Most of them are used for detoxification.
One or two medicinal materials can work,
but why do you use dozens of them?
As the saying goes,
every medicine has its side effect.
Many of them may accomplish the very opposite.
Miss Jun,
they may not remove the toxins
and even hurt the patient.
Thank you for your tips.
I know about it.
Never mind.
OK.
It's good that you know it.
Please take them.
Thank you.
Miss Jun, see you.
It is a small world.
Is it hard
to meet me?
Do you want to
remove Childe Fang's toxins?
Don't always think yourself clever.
Why did you
buy these medicinal materials?
I'm ignorant.
I wonder what disease can be treated
with dozens of detoxification medicinal materials.
As a doctor,
is it improper for me
to do research with some medicinal materials?
It makes sense.
Miss Jun, listen to me
and think
whether my idea also makes sense.
The Fang family has had the only son for three generations in a row
and been cursed evilly.
It's said Childe Fang
can't live to 16
as he suffers from
the hurt of toxins.
It's an accident if such misfortune happens to one generation
and it's a coincidence
if such misfortune happens to two generations.
Is it strange
if such mischief happens to three generations?
I can't understand your words.
Maybe it's predestined.
Let me make a guess.
In fact, the curse of men of the Fang family
are caused by others, fabricated
and Young Master Fang
was secretly poisoned.
You're so smart.
But it's my duty
to treat Chengyu,
and it has nothing to do with you.
So please don't stop me.
Miss Jun, don't worry.
I won't tell others.
But please
do a favor for me.
Find the list of freight customers
of the Fang family over the years
by virtue of your identity for me.
Your Ladyship.
Here is a letter for you.
Where does it come from?
The Ning family.
Miss Jun,
there was a misunderstanding between the Ning family and the Fang family.
Please go to
Room 3 of the sky level in Jinyun Restaurant
on March 3 for a chat.
Ning Yunzhao.
Jun Zhenzhen,
you'll be tricked definitely.
Yunyan,
your idea is wonderful.
With Childe Ning's letter,
she'll definitely go.
By then
she will be blemished
and won't bother
Childe Ning anymore.
Yes.
But,
do we
go too far?
Aren't you afraid…
So what?
It's her fault.
She shouldn't have blackmailed our Ning family
and humiliated us
again and again.
What I did
is to get even.
Yes.
Your Lady,
drink tea.
will you go to see Childe Ning by appointment?
This letter was sent by Childe Ning's manservant,
but it doesn't mean that it's written by Childe Ning.
Why?
Childe Ning was born from a scholarly family
and acts magnanimously.
If it was really inconvenient
for him to say something at home,
he probably wouldn't invite me
to a private room
which may stump girls.
Of course, it's just my guess.
Cousin, why didn't you let Mujin send a message as usual,
but let me meet here?
There are so many people in the mansion.
It's too risky to do so.
This matter is very serious.
So we'd better agree on many things ourselves.
In case of mistakes,
even if Mujin can afford it,
can you afford it?
Then let's get to the point.
If it takes a long time, I'm really worried that
Mujin can't cope.
At the  lantern show last night, I checked carefully
and found that Chengyu's condition had not improved.
He was still half dead.
It seems that a wedding can't help.
It can't save his life.
But now the only mistake is that
in case Jun Zhenzhen is pregnant with the children of the Fang family
after the wedding…
What do you mean by that?
If Jun Zhenzhen dies,
where can the Fang family find
a woman to marry him voluntarily
in such a short time?
Are you going to kill Jun Zhenzhen?
No one wants to kill her.
She is just unlucky enough
to have an accident.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫