♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 6
Tomb of Beloved Wife Princess Jiuling
By Husband Lu Yunqi
Jinyun Restaurant  Drunken Steps by the River
Cousin, why didn't you let Mujin
send a message as usual,
but let me meet here?
There are so many people in the mansion.
It's too risky
to do so.
This matter is very serious.
So we'd better
agree on many things ourselves.
In case of mistakes,
even if Mujin can afford it,
can you afford it?
Then let's get to the point.
If it takes a long time, I'm really worried that
Mujin can't cope.
At the lantern show last night,
I checked carefully
and found that Chengyu's condition
had not improved.
He was still half dead.
It seems that
a wedding can't help.
It can't save his life.
But now the only mistake is that
in case Jun Zhenzhen is pregnant with the children of the Fang family
after the wedding…
What do you mean by that?
If Jun Zhenzhen dies,
where can the Fang family find
a woman to marry him voluntarily
in such a short time?
Are you going to kill Jun Zhenzhen?
No one wants to kill her.
She is just unlucky enough
to have an accident.
I'm afraid
it's inappropriate to do so.
You see, the Fang family
has come to this point now.
Jun Zhenzhen is a little girl
and can't make waves.
Cousin, do you think
it should be discussed in the long run?
Are you afraid?
Now we have no way back.
Even if you don't think about yourself,
shouldn't you think about
Jinxiu?
Moreover, the success or failure of the plan over the past ten years
depends on this action.
I know you are sensible.
As long as you work hard,
Jinxiu will be safe and sound.
Just now Madame Su went out
to see a man.
That man was very cautious.
His cloak covered his face.
He took a carriage
and made a long detour
to get rid of the people we sent.
I thought she was gentle.
Unexpectedly,
she was a poisonous snake beside the master.
The Fang family is supposed to be
picky about concubines.
How did she marry into the Fang family?
It's because of Shopkeeper Song.
She is the distant cousin of Shopkeeper Song.
When something happened to her family,
she came to Zezhou to seek relief from her cousin.
At that time, the master
encountered bandits
during the escort,
when Shopkeeper Song risked his life to save him.
Because the master was grateful for Shopkeeper Song's kindness,
he took her as a concubine.
Shopkeeper Song.
Our family feels indebted to Shopkeeper Song.
Even if Madame Su did something stupid,
it should have nothing to do with him.
Do you think
she went to see Shopkeeper Song tonight?
I'm not sure.
However,
only someone who has been with the Fang family for decades
like Shopkeeper Song
will not make you suspicious.
Now,
Madame Su has repeatedly sent soup
to check Chengyu's condition.
They must be impatient.
But the more impatient they are,
the more they will give themselves away.
Miss Jun even promised to give you
the guest list of the Fang family's freight.
That's not right.
Miss Jun has always been very cold.
How could she help you so much?
How did you do it, Zan?
Could it be…
No, no.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
5,000 taels.
You made a deal with her with the 5,000 taels
you earned from her.
Great.
That's great.
Awesome. Awesome. Awesome.
I'm flattered. I'm flattered.
Awesome. Awesome.
How is everything going in the Sky Pavilion?
Any news from the capital city?
Go ahead.
Lu Yunqi
is getting married again,
and his fiancée is still a princess.
Which princess?
Zan,
don't get mad when I say it.
Go on.
Princess Jiuli.
And their wedding day
is the birthday of Princess Jiuli.
Zan,
we agreed not to get mad.
Send more people near Prince Huai's residence.
Be sure to ensure
the safety of Prince Huai and his sister.
Don't need to ask me for instructions
and don't need to care about the means.
OK.
Then I'll arrange it now.
Go.
OK.
I came to see you again.
I brought you
your favorite
eight-treasure cake this time.
This is what I just learned.
I may not
have done a very good job.
But it doesn't matter.
I'll
do better next time.
When I first saw you,
in fact,
you certainly didn't know
it was me,
and you'll never know.
That's my ball.
It's not yours.
No.
Hit him.
Kick him.
Stop it.
Come on.
Are you OK?
Yes, I'm OK.
You know what?
I've been thinking about you every day
since that day.
Finally, our wedding came.
I didn't expect that I had time
to say thank you for saving me.
Jiuling,
don't hate me.
I'm getting married again soon.
The bride
is Jiuli.
I'm sorry.
The most regretful thing in my life is that
I didn't save you.
So the only thing I can do now
is to take care of them two.
His Majesty has doubts about them.
Only by marrying Princess Jiuli
can I dispel his concerns
and protect them.
If you knew it,
you would forgive me,
wouldn't you?
Come and have a look.
Have a look.
Look at the flowers.
Your Ladyship,
everything you need to get married
is almost ready.
The wedding dress will be delivered later.
In fact, I really can't figure out
what you think.
Why do you want to marry Young Master Fang?
Make way.
Be careful. Be careful.
Hold on to it.
Your Ladyship.
Make way.
Don't come out.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, be careful.
Make way.
All the escort agencies
and merchants in Zezhou have been verified.
None has suspicion.
Now
only Deshengchang of the Fang family is left.
The Fang family?
Jun Zhenzhen.
Liu'er, don't come out.
Make way.
Excuse me.
Zan, hurry up.
Make way.
Look out.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
Your Ladyship.
That was dangerous.
Fortunately, that childe saved you.
Your Ladyship,
you know
that man.
Why did you two pretend
you didn't know each other?
We should hide
something from others.
Are you worried that
people will notice it
and you will be misunderstood to be involved with other men
since you have been engaged?
All in all,
he is not a bad man.
Don't think too much.
Your Ladyship.
Do you like him?
Why do you ask so?
Then I don't understand.
You don't like him.
He is mystery
and not pleasant at all.
But you still protect him
and say he is not a bad man.
If you don't like him,
why are you protecting him?
Protecting him
doesn't mean I like him.
Maybe it's because I admire him.
What's the difference?
For instance,
because of the cancelling of marriage,
I dislike
all people of the Ning family,
including Childe Ning.
However,
occasionally,
we played a game of blind chess
without knowing each other's identity.
Then I change my view on
his character and chess character.
This is called admiration.
But I don't like him.
So you are
admiring Childe Ning,
but you don't like him?
Yeah.
So you admire that person
but you don't like that man?
Almost.
Let's go.
May I come in?
Why not?
Please.
Thank you for your help today.
Forget it.
But did you offend anyone?
On the hip of the horse which had been alerted,
there is a silver needle.
I guessed it.
Looks like someone
doesn't like the marriage of the youngest son of the Fang family.
So they also
poisoned the young master
of the Fang family?
Maybe.
By the way,
I brought you this.
You give me medicine provided by others?
Sort of.
How are you?
Does your wound still hurt?
It's all right.
Let me see.
What are you doing?
I can do it myself.
I'm a doctor.
What are you thinking about?
After you leave,
I can do it myself.
Okay.
Then I'm leaving.
Miss Jun.
please pay more attention to
Deshengchang.
I won't stay in Zezhou for long.
You have something important to do?
Lu Yunqi wants to
marry Princess Jiuli.
The emperor has promised him.
When?
On the birthday of Jiuling.
So I have to hurry
to the capital before his wedding.
Lu Yunqi, you are mad.
Okay.
I see.
Then I'll leave first.
Grandma, aunt.
I'd like to discuss
something with you two.
Go ahead.
I was thinking whether
my marriage with Chengyu
can be completed after March 3.
Is it in such a hurry?
I'm afraid it's too late to prepare.
After marriage,
I can do
give Chengyu medicine baths as soon as possible.
Then I can repair his meridians
with gold needles.
After a period of time,
Chengyu should be able to stand up soon.
Sir, please come in.
Welcome.
This is Jinyun Restaurant?
I've heard that they have many rules.
On March 3,
no one is allowed to go in.
It's said that
this is the condition
for descendants of the Chen family to give up this place.
The descendants of the Chen family are really interesting.
Go.
Let's go in and have a look.
There are fine seats.
Come in, please.
This way, please.
Upstairs, please.
Come in, please.
Sir, please come in.
Sir.
Please come in, Your Ladyship.
It's lively here.
Come in, please.
Miss Jun.
Childe Ning has arranged it.
In Sky Room No. 3.
Please follow me.
Come in, please.
This way.
I knew she would come.
Look at her dress.
She must have come to seduce Childe Ning.
Take it easy.
Don't worry.
As long as we succeed,
when my brother finishes the spring exam
and chooses a girl for engagement,
I would speak good
of you.
With you, my best friend
to be my sister-in-law,
I'll be much more relieved.
I'm just trying to help you,
I didn't think so much.
I've arranged
my subordinates.
Look.
Miss Jun,
please have a seat.
This is a good new tea.
Please have a taste.
Is Childe Ning here?
He will arrive later.
Please forgive him.
Okay.
I have nothing else.
You can leave now.
Yes.
See you, Your Ladyship.
Ning Yunyan?
There is overpowering drug in the tea.
Liu'er.
Go.
Yes.
Are you clear?
Don't worry.
It's on me.
I promise
to complete it well.
Just wait to see her
be discredited.
Good.
Do it well.
After you succeed,
I'll give you a great reward.
I'm good at it.
Good.
Come with me.
OK.
Do I have to dress like this?
Zan,
it's March 3.
We are trying
for a prize.
And Jinyun Restaurant has the largest prize today.
Let's go, let's go.
Just take a look.
It's boring. I won't go.
Zan, please.
Just take a look.
You're almost there.
Go.
We'll be right there.
That's it.
Fan.
Just take a look.
It's really her.
Your Ladyship.
Why don't we just go?
What if that scoundrel
comes in?
Even if we avoid it this time,
we would meet with other tricks later.
Why don't we take this opportunity to deal with her?
What are we going to do?
Long time no see.
Yeah, yeah.
How is it?
Look around.
How lively it is!
Let's go, let's go.
Look. How nice it is here!
Haven't you seen a pitch-pot game before?
You've been too tired lately.
Don't you know we have serious business to do?
Let's relax
before we get back to business.
You can't do business every day.
Come on, let's go this way.
I'll be with you this time.
The last time.
Okay.
Be with me for the last time.
Okay?
Childe Ning.
Nice to see you.
This way, please.
Why does Childe Ning come?
What are you panicking about?
Since my brother is here,
we can let him see
how shameless Jun Zhenzhen is.
It's pretty lively.
Yunzhao.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I know.
You are looking for
that girl who gave you a lantern that day.
Yeah.
I knew it.
I figured it out
because you keep an unusual attitude
toward that lantern.
Don't make fun of me.
I just think that girl is smart.
I want to know her.
We understand.
But Yunzhao,
be patient.
Fate is something
we can't ask for.
Maybe one day,
she will naturally appear in front of you.
Is that so?
Yes.
I think so.
Everybody.
Everybody, be quiet.
Be quiet.
Today, many
beauties and talented men gather here.
On such a grand event,
how can we lack
some elegant activities?
It's said that in recent years,
the pitch-pot game is popular in the capital.
So our restaurant
makes bold
to introduce this game
to today's event.
And the pitch-pot game…
The pitch-pot game
has simple rules.
I'm good at this.
However,
in addition to betting on winning or losing,
our restaurant
has also come up with an idea.
That is,
to determine the winner
in accordance with
the number of bamboo arrows
thrown into the pot.
If any
childe
or lady
breaks the the record
determined by our restaurant,
he or she will be
our VIP later
to get our best services.
In addition,
all his or her expenses in our restaurant
will be all free.
Great!
That's nice.
Interesting.
Free food and drink.
Zan.
Is there anyone
willing to sign up
to take this challenge?
Yunzhao,
I've heard a long time ago that
you are a master in this game.
Hurry up and show us.
Yeah.
Try it.
No.
Wenming.
Is there anyone willing to take the challenge?
I won't go.
Your Ladyship, Your Ladyship.
Ning Yunyan's name has been signed up.
Do you think
she will attend it?
Based on my understand of her,
she will surely attend it.
Then we can take this opportunity
to make a fortune.
We can't miss this golden chance.
Your Ladyship,
how much do you think we can make?
50 taels?
5,000 taels.
5,000 taels?
But,
but Your Ladyship,
can you throw arrows into the pot?
I didn't expect my childhood pastime game
can be useful today.
Are you willing to take the challenge?
We can discuss it.
Ning Yunyan in Sky Room No.6
and Jun Zhenzhen in Sky Room No. 3.
Next, let's invite
the first challenger.
Sky
Room No.6,
Miss Ning Yunyan.
Yunyan?
Is she interested in
such an elegant activity?
And
Sky Room No. 3,
Miss Jun Zhenzhen. –Zan.
Zan, look!
Jun Zhenzhen?
Is that girl
who cancelled the engagement with Yunzhao?
Good!
It's her!
Yeah, yeah.
You signed me up?
Who signed me up?
Is she qualified
for competing with me?
Who made this trick?
Don't go then.
No way.
My name has been reported.
If I don't show up,
it would defame my family.
Besides,
I'm good at it.
I'm not afraid of her.
Go.
It's her.
Yunyan.
Yunzhao.
Interesting.
Childe Ning.
Yunzhao.
Since you are interested in this game,
why didn't you tell me in advance?
It's just a whim.
I just heard
your name just now.
I don't know who's so shameless
to sign up for me.
Yunzhao.
Now that you're here,
play the game for me.
Show those who overestimate their strength
your excellent pitch-pot skills.
Forget it, Yunyan.
Yunzhao. Be good.
Yunzhao.
Go, Childe Ning.
Stop it.
Yunzhao, come on.
Yunyan begs you.
Stop it.
Go.
Go ahead.
Don't make people wait.
Yunzhao.
No, Yunyan.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Next, let's welcome Childe Ning
to replace Miss Ning Yunyan
to take the challenge.
Go, go, go.
Come on, brother.
Good!
Come on.
Go, go, go.
Childe Ning.
Good!
I'd like to see
how she wins this game.
Do you think Jun Zhenzhen is a master?
She knows nothing about it.
My brother
must defeat her.
Let's go upstairs to enjoy the show.
Go.
Sorry.
Miss Jun.
It seems that
you have an elegant interest today.
So you are
Miss Jun.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Childe Ning.
I thought
I would meet many people for once only in my life.
And now I see you.
I think
meeting you again
is more joyful
than seeing you once only.
Yeah.
What a coincidence.
You also know how to play a pitch-pot game.
I wonder
if you're as good at it
as playing go.
You have flattered me.
Instead,
it's my honor
to catch a glimpse of
your skill in this game.
Sorry to trouble you,
Miss Jun.
As long as you don't mind
the rumor off the stage.
They may say whatever they want.
It has nothing to do with us.
Miss Jun Zhenzhen will play
against Childe Ning Yunzhao
in the pitch-pot game.
All bets will go to the winner.
The loser
will return double
the wager's money.
OK.
Yunyan,
your brother is going to play.
Shall we bet?
Certainly.
Clearly,
he will win.
Excuse me.
Please.
Miss Jun,
what would you pitch?
I bet on the first arrow.
OK.
Bet on the first arrow.
There are 3 rounds in total.
In the first two rounds,
each player gets 6 bamboo arrows.
There are 12 pots in total.
In the last round,
each player gets 12 arrows.
The winner is the player with more arrows into the pot.
Best of three.
I bet 100 taels on my brother.
I bet 100 taels on Childe Ning.
I bet 500 taels on Childe Ning.
I bet 500 taels
on Childe Ning.
Great.
Miss Jun,
please.
Please.
You know what, my brother is good at it.
It's great.
Great.
Yunzhao is still so great.
Look.
Isn't it?
He is so great.
Let's wait and see Jun Zhenzhen making a fool of herself.
Miss Jun,
please.
It almost fell in.
I knew she couldn't make it.
Childe Ning got all 6 arrows in the pots.
Miss Jun got 5 of the 6 arrows in the pots.
Childe Ning won
in the first round.
Well done.
So great.
Miss Jun,
when you were about to pitch just now,
your wrist inclined by half inch.
Keep steady this time.
Thanks for reminding.
Please.
You first.
Well done.
Amazing.
Not bad.
She is great.
Yunzhao didn't play honestly.
Yes.
Alright. Alright.
My brother won't lose.
Miss Jun got all 6 arrows in the pots.
Childe Ning got 5 of the 6 arrows in the pots.
Miss Jun won
in the second round.
Well done.
Miss Jun,
we tied.
You gave me the chance.
I admit defeat.
You also gave me a chance.
Miss Jun,
how about playing at full stretch in the last round?
That sounds great.
I will.
Ladies and gentleman,
it's the last round now.
Do you want to
increase bet?
I'll increase the bet on Childe Ning by 300 taels.
I'll increase the bet on Childe Ning by 500 taels.
I'll increase the bet by 500 taels.
We'll increase the bet on Childe Ning by 1,000 taels.
1,000 taels.
Bet on Miss Jun.
Increase the bet.
I bet Miss Jun will win.
1,000 taels.
That's interesting. So busy.
I'll increase the bet by 2,000 taels.
I bet my brother will win.
Guests in Heaven Room No. 6
increase by 2,000 taels.
They bet
Childe Ning will win.
Go on. Go on.
So Miss Ning is going to battle with me.
Miss Jun is outstanding.
I'll increase by 1,000 taels.
Another 1,000 taels.
4,000 taels.
4,500 taels.
5,000 taels.
It's so interesting today.
Why are 5,000 taels again?
Why is the Ning Family
always related
to 5,000 taels?
It's still them two.
And
still 5,000 taels.
It's hard to tell who will win.
If I get the double amount of silver,
don't be jealous.
Please bet for me, host.
I bet 5,000 taels
on myself.
5,000 taels?
Miss Jun...
She spends the money on making a fool of herself.
Go ahead.
Go bet.
Miss Jun
bets 5,000 taels.
She bets that she will win.
Well done.
So awesome.
Players,
you may begin.
Great.
Yunzhao,
well done.
Well. Well.
Great.
I,
I told you that.
He's so great, right?
He got all arrows in the pots.
Childe Ning got 12 arrows in the pots.
Next, let's invite
Miss Jun.
You're really excellent.
Miss Jun,
please.
Jun Zhenzhen,
with a false marriage contract,
you cheated 5,000 taels of silver of my family.
Now in the public,
how are you going to cheat?
Yunyan.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫