♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 2
Ning Mansion
去
Go.
Bring 2,000 taels.
Wait a moment.
2,000 taels was the price just now.
Now it's different.
5,000 taels.
You?
How dare you raise the price?
My grandfather saved Master Ning
many years ago,
which deserves
3,000 taels, doesn't it?
As for the other 2,000 taels,
it's for you irritating my grandmother,
and I'm not okay with it.
So what?
Mrs. Ning, you don't want to buy it?
Or do you think
Tenth Childe Ning
isn't worth 5,000 taels?
You?
Mom, you can't do as she said.
Come on. Just stop.
Mom.
How could you promise to give her the money?
You should have let her go
without giving her a dime.
And what could she do?
Her causing a scene
would affect the fame of your brother.
He will take the exam next spring,
which matters more.
We just pay the money
for his fame.
Madam.
Mom,
I'll send the bank note to her.
Hey.
The five-thousand-tael bank note you asked.
Take it.
If you dare to throw it to the ground,
I'll ask for another 5,000 taels.
Your Ladyship,
I thought
you were kidding for asking them to pay a hundredfold or thousandfold price,
but I'm wrong.
It's five-thousand-tael bank note.
I was just trying for the justice we deserve.
I would rather not get the sum of money
than have my grandmother suffer that.
You've tried your best.
And Her Ladyship will understand.
Your Ladyship,
what will you do with such a large sum of money?
Go to the capital city.
Zhenzhen,
do you really want to break off the engagement?
Yes.
The Ning family was wrong for humiliating me.
It was their fault for sure.
But what you did
would entirely ruin the engagement.
Grandma,
it's not a pity.
And I don't regret it.
I wouldn't be happy
if I were to
marry into such a family.
How could you
break off such a good engagement
due to sentiment?
You should have discussed it
with us before you made up your mind.
They slandered grandfather,
and grandmother got sick because of them.
I couldn't just
let them go so easily.
Zhenzhen,
you could have figured out another way to break off the engagement
if you really wanted it that much.
It was just so unwise of you to do this
by asking them for money.
They deserved to
pay us the money.
Grandma,
I won't compromise with the Ning family.
Let's just forget
the engagement.
This bracelet is for you.
Grandma, I can't take it.
It's yours.
Just regard it as
my present for your mother.
She died with the bracelet
which is supposed to be yours,
so I gave you this as a compensation.
It looks so good on you.
Take it.
It's my good will.
Don't be that starchy here.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you, Grandma.
Lord Cheng's Mansion
Lord Cheng's son Zhu Zan
Zan'er still doesn't want to take off his armour.
Lord Cheng Zhu Shan  Zhu Zan's mother Ms. Yu
Zan'er.
Dad.
Mom.
You came.
Zan'er,
have you prepared well
to meet His Majesty?
You knew why I did that.
His Majesty suspected
me of selling the mileage chart of the capital city
and divulging military secrets.
These are huge charges.
You have to deal with them carefully.
Zan'er,
you'll go back to the capital city.
Your dad and I are
so worried about you.
Mom,
I'm an adult.
And
I've been fighting wars with dad.
I've experienced a lot.
I know how to deal with the situation.
Man's heart is incomprehensible.
Your father and you
are good at fighting wars,
while those who are in the prosperous capital city
are so good at plotting against each other.
Don't worry about me.
Father has so many friends in the imperial government,
who will protect me for sure.
In fact, what I worry about the most
is that father will be
so busy with military business alone.
Don't worry about military business.
All that we want is you coming back safe.
Zan'er,
we don't know
whether you'll be safe this time.
Remember not to drop your guard.
Let Baotang go back with you.
He can protect you on the way.
If something happens,
let the Sky Pavilion take care of it
as we used to do.
Sanbing will have to stay
in the north backland
to deal with military business.
Zan'er,
His Majesty has granted a marriage to Jiuling.
What else can you do
as an official of His Majesty?
Mom,
this is the present I prepared
for Jiuling's wedding.
I've grown up.
I won't cause a scene.
Okay.
Zan'er will set out soon.
Let him package his things up.
Let's go.
Dad.
Mom.
I'm leaving.
Please allow me to bow to you.
Go.
Cheers, Second Brother.
Cheers.
Drink it.
It tastes good.
Yeah.
Second Brother,
Zhu Zan's sworn brother Zhang Baotang
those flunkies of the Arm Moral Department
are watching us
so firmly.
Waiter.
Bring us dishes.
We're hungry.
One more shot, Second Brother.
Come on. Try this.
Cheers. Cheers.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Sir, here's your noodle.
Sir, I'm so sorry.
Sir.
I'm so sorry.
Sir, I'm so sorry.
The waiter is a new comer.
He's a green hand.
Please tell me
what I can do for you.
The one from
the Sky Pavilion is still that mysterious.
Back off.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Thank you, Sir.
Eunuch Li,
I'll go clean the mess.
Sir, are you okay?
The waiter was so careless.
Everyone, sit down.
Okay. Have a seat. Let's sit down.
What's up?
Nothing.
Let's just enjoy the meal first.
Give it to me.
It's nothing. I mean it.
Let's just enjoy the meal first.
Give it to me.
The information I got might not be true.
Let me go confirm it, will you?
Enjoy the meal.
Second Brother.
I mean…
Jiuling
died?
The letter says so.
But don't be that sad, Second Brother.
Maybe…
Sir,
he drank too much.
He drank too much.
Sir,
I'll go check him.
You're a teenage hero, aren't you?
Chu Jiuling Junior
Of course.
I'll go
garrison the frontier with my father.
Zhu Zan Junior
How come you remember to praise me
when I'm leaving?
Will you miss me?
Of course not.
I was just kidding.
Of course I'll miss you.
You're the one and only one
I'll miss
in the capital city.
Am I that different?
You're so different.
You're unique, the only Princess Jiuling.
Jiuling,
I don't know
when I can come back.
Maybe one year.
Maybe two.
Or maybe three or four years.
Or longer.
No matter when you come back,
I'll be waiting for you in the capital city.
Second Brother,
don't be that worried.
The letter hasn't been confirmed yet. Right?
I'm suspicious of its authenticity.
The letter says
Princess Jiuling…
But…
But the letter also says
her body can't be recognized.
Is there a chance that
it's not Princess Jiuling?
Baotang,
you're right.
Go on.
Well.
The letter also says
Jun Yingwen, an old friend of the deceased emperor,
appeared on the day Princess Jiuling was locked up.
So is there a connection between the two things?
Something might be behind it.
Where is
Jun Yingwen?
He's missing.
But his daughter, Jun Zhenzhen,
went to Zezhou.
She went to her grandmother's place.
Jun Zhenzhen?
Zezhou?
Let's go to Zezhou.
Second Brother.
Eunuch Li,
I sent you a dozen people
to watch Zhu Zan.
How could you let him run away?
It's…
It's all my fault.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Drag him away.
Yes.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I mean, why did Zhu Zan
run away?
Maybe he was afraid
that he would be
punished for
the mileage chart of the capital city thing,
so he ran away from the capital city.
If you were Zhu Zan,
when would you choose to run away?
When you've been
close to the capital city
or you're in the north backland?
Find him.
Go find him back.
No.
Arrest him.
Yes.
What do you
think of
Princess Jiuli?
She's pure,
kind, gorgeous and thrifty.
She's really a model
of the girls in our country.
Could she become
another Jiuling?
The two princesses didn't meet
on the wedding day.
Jiuling…
When Jiuling died,
Princess Jiuli was immersed
in the deep sorrow of losing her relative.
So
I think
she shouldn't know the thing of the late emperor.
That's your point of view.
It's hard to know a person's real thought.
Your Majesty,
could you please marry
Princess Jiuli to me?
Don't rush.
It can wait until
the 100th day of Jiuling's death.
Yes.
Ancestral Temple of the Lu Clan
My daughter, Jiuling
went to heaven.
Jiuling,
did you go to heaven?
why I stopped you in the hall
was to protect you.
Why I led people to the imperial prison
was to save you.
I'm sorry, Jiuling.
I arrived there too late.
I had figured out the best timing of coming to your rescue.
But I didn't expect
you would die in the big fire.
Now
Chu Rang is alert to Princess Jiuli,
and Jiurong.
I'll be able to protect them well
if I marry Princess Jiuli.
You died,
but I'll protect the persons you care about
for you.
Fang Mansion
The third year of Taiyan.
Your grandfather
was caught by Beiqi people.
We made the taels
to save him from Beiqi.
We sent these official taels to Zezhou,
and gave them to Beiqi people.
But they broke the promise.
And they accused us of breaking our word.
They refused to release your grandfather.
In the end,
your grandfather and your uncles
died in Beiqi.
The third year of Taiyan National Treasury
It's a huge humiliation.
Official taels?
A paper strip for sealing?
Is this the shipment paper strip
which was used to seal the official taels in the third year of Taiyan?
Working in the commercial house of the Fang family
might be a good chance to figure the thing out.
Flower umbrellas.
Come and have a look.
This one is good.
Please take your time.
It's fresh. It's fresh.
I want this. I want it.
Okay. Sure.
Who are you?
I'm looking for Miss Jun.
Could you please
report it for me?
What's your surname?
It's Ling.
I'll be back soon.
Your Ladyship,
someone is looking for you.
Me?
Yes.
His surname is Ling.
He said
he was looking for you.
Ling?
Well,
will you meet him?
No. Of course not.
How could Her Ladyship meet a strange man?
Okay.
I'll ask him to leave.
Wait.
Maybe I know him.
I'll meet him.
Yes.
Second Brother.
Second Brother. Second Brother.
Well, where's Childe Ling?
He must be a liar.
You'll have to confirm his identity
when you report to Her Ladyship.
Liu'er.
You might mistake him.
That's fine.
Let's go back.
Have a look at the flower umbrellas.
Flower umbrellas.
Steamed buns.
Fresh steamed buns.
Let's go.
Second Brother,
how come she hasn't appeared?
I've…
How dare you knock at the door of the Fang Mansion again?
Hurry and leave.
I wanted to meet her but refused to reveal my name.
It's so impolite of me.
We can only meet her when she goes out.
Second Brother,
shall we
try that?
That trick is for the Beiqi soldiers.
How could we use it on a lady?
Got it. Got it. Got it.
I'm wrong.
I'm so wrong.
Okay.
We won't use that.
Then what else can we do?
Okay.
I'm coming.
I heard a lady, a new comer,
was working in Deshengchang.
But I haven't confirmed the news.
Why do you care about it so much?
Do you want to be a matrilocal son-in-law of the Fang family?
No. No. No.
Men of the Fang family won't get a good ending.
I don't want to be one of them.
Come on. Have some tea.
Okay. Sure.
Have it. Have it. Have it.
Deshengchang
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Please take your time.
These are the account books of this month,
which are useless for me.
Your Ladyship.
Do you need me
to explain it to you?
No need.
Well,
I'm leaving first.
Zhenzhen,
you just need to know something about how the commercial house works today.
If you get tired,
feel free to go back and have a rest.
Sister, thank you so much.
Then I'm leaving first.
Grandmother let her learn to read account books out of kindness.
You know what?
She's not interested in the business of Deshengchang at all.
Instead, she's giving grandmother the runaround.
Come on, Sister.
The third year of Taiyan is a long time ago.
I have to figure out a way to get the account book of that year.
Your Ladyship,
I mean you're not interested in
the business of Deshengchang at all.
I'm not.
You look reluctant.
Why didn't you just refuse the requirement of the dowager?
Then you would be able to do something you really liked.
Grandmother asked me to do this for my sake.
What's up?
How did you drive the coach?
Your Ladyship,
a handcart broke,
which blocked our way.
This way, please.
Please.
What happened?
The wheel of the handcart broke.
You'll have to choose another route.
Your Ladyship,
what should we do now?
We'll walk.
And we can wander around.
Your Ladyship,
it's not a good idea.
If you come across an accident on your way,
I can't take the responsibility.
Let me send you back.
That's fine.
Don't worry about that.
We came all the way to Zezhou
from the capital city safe.
We can certainly
take care of ourselves here.
Let's go. -Your Ladyship.
Liu'er.
A carter's duty is to fetch people safe.
Be nice
to him. Okay?
Don't talk to him that rudely.
Your Ladyship,
you might be bullied
if you're so nice to everyone.
No.
I think you'll be nice to
those who
are polite to you,
while you'll treat the impolite people
the same way as they do.
Right?
Why do you think so?
Because that was how you treated Mrs. Ning.
Your Ladyship,
I passed a cake shop just now.
The cakes there look pretty good.
Do you want to try it?
Come here and take a look.
Go buy some.
I'll wait for you here.
Miss,
are you alone?
Take your hand away from me.
You look so gorgeous.
But how come you're so rude?
You'll regret for what you did.
Will I?
I'm so scared.
Miss, I'm looking forward to what you'll do.
How could he do that to a lady?
It's too much.
How could he do this in broad daylight?
What's he doing?
Let go of me.
Okay.
He's so rude.
Stop.
See. See.
Brat,
it's none of your business.
Are you alright?
Apologize to this lady.
No way.
I'm sorry.
First,
your voice was too light.
Second,
you making the apology
was because you were overwhelmed
by my excellent martial arts.
Then what else do you want me to do?
Miss, what do you think?
I'm going to notify the local government.
Miss,
it's merely a misunderstanding.
We can deal with
it by ourselves.
Miss, I know you're generous.
He's running away. He's running away.
That brat
is kind of powerful.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Miss,
I helped you.
So, could I ask you for a favor?
I don't have my purse with me.
And I haven't paid the bill yet.
Could I know your name, Miss?
I'll pay you
a visit tomorrow.
And I'll send the taels back to you.
No need.
You can regard that
as my appreciation for your help.
I have to pay you back,
which is necessary.
I have to send the money
to you.
You know that man, don't you?
Miss, are you kidding me?
Of course I don't know him.
The goods dropping from the broken handcart
which blocked my way
were also arranged by you.
I think
you got me wrong.
I've seen so many tricks
like what you did before.
Miss,
you've known everything.
How come you still paid the bill for me
instead of leaving?
I wanted to know
what else you'd like to do.
There's really another thing that I want to do.
I do want to know
whether your father is Jun Yingwen.
You know my father?
Sort of.
Who are you?
I'm Ling Jiu.
Ling means ruling the world
while Jiu means the end of everything.
I'm Ling Jiu.
Whenever you come back,
you should write a letter to me in advance.
Then I'll be waiting for you at the gate of the city.
Are you sure?
No matter how long it takes?
I've never lied to you, have I?
But…
But if I would be away from you for so many years,
you wouldn't be able to
recognize me after so many years.
What would you do?
If someone would
pretend to be me,
you couldn't trust him.
I come up with an idea.
I'll give you a name.
Then you'll be unique to me.
My name is Jiuling.
Then yours can be Ling Jiu.
Okay?
You're Jiuling
while I'm Ling Jiu.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Ling Jiu.
Miss Jun.
It's you.
Zhu Zan.
You're Zhu Zan.
Miss Jun,
are you okay?
all that I did today
is because of a person,
Princess Jiuling.
I got to know your father and you have just left the capital city.
Has your father met Princess Jiuling?
I won't do anything to hurt your father and Princess Jiuling.
Please trust me.
I really don't know where they are.
Princess Jiuling and I have known each other since childhood.
Where the princess is means so much to me.
Then where is your father?
I really don't know.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask someone else.
See you.
You came back.
Second Brother,
how is it going?
Your acting skill is terrible.
She knew everything from the very beginning.
How could it happen?
That Miss Jun is
far smarter than I thought.
Then…
What happened later?
Have you known where Jun Yingwen
and the princess are?
You haven't?
Then
we did everything in vain, didn't we?
I feel she hid something from me.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
Try this.
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
It tastes so good.
Miss Jun,
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
all that I did today
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
is because of a person,
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
Princess Jiuling.
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
Zhu Zan,
♫In long silence♫
the childish and lively Chu Jiuling
has died.
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
The Chu Jiuling, who's alive now,
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
is Jun Zhenzhen. She's irrelevant to you.
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
I have to take my revenge,
but I can't implicate anyone who hasn't done anything wrong.
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
Even if I make a minor mistake,
the whole Lord's family will be implicated.
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
I have to revenge for father,
♫If memories can tell♫
Zhenzhen
and my master.
♫It will make me shed tears♫
There's no turning back.
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
But you're different from me,
Zhu Zan.
You don't need to
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
go through this for a dead person.
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
Princess Jiuling has died,
but you have to live your life.
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
Please forgive me
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
for not telling you who I really am.
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫
Jun Zhenzhen must know where Jiuling is.
She doesn't dare to tell me the truth, does she?
Was it Jiuling who taught her
to splash rose petals on tea?
Second Brother,
don't think about it anymore.
Take a rest.
Enjoy the meal.
Try this.
It's so delicious.
It's empty.
Try another one.
See. When it's closed,
I don't know whether it's empty.
What's up?
Saving the princess
and keeping it a secret would be a huge crime.
Even if I told her who I am,
she wouldn't let her guard down since
we don't know each other well.
Then what should we do?
If Mr. Jun and Jiuling are safe,
and they can't show up,
then daily necessities will be a big problem.
If Jun Zhenzhen does know where they are,
she will definitely go to their place.
Your Ladyship,
that one seems to be Fang Chengyu, the legitimate son of the Fang family.
You're Jun Zhenzhen,
the so-called cousin of me. Right?
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫