♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 7
Dawn Moon and Good Wind
Assistant of Arm Moral Department  Jiang Baihu
Fang Mansion
Ning Mansion
The Heavenly Maids Scattering Blossoms.
All arrows in the pots.
Miss Jun,
how wonderful!
Amazing.
Zan, she got all the arrows in the pots.
5,000 taels, Zan.
Look, we didn't come in vain.
All arrows in the pots.
Ladies
and gentlemen,
the winner
is obviously
Miss Jun.
In just a few days,
I lost to you again.
Thank you for giving the chance.
I'm not as calm as you.
Zan,
you haven't taken the money yet.
I didn't expect you
to be good at the pitch-pot game.
After you showed your skills today,
you beat the crowd.
You made a huge amount of money
from your previous bet.
Please wait here.
They'll send someone
to deliver the money later.
Your Ladyship,
there's so much money.
I'll keep an eye on them.
Liu'er.
After the pitch-pot game,
you must be thirsty.
Miss Jun,
here you are.
Jun Zhenzhen,
are you…
Wait a minute.
Yunyan,
it seems that Jun Zhenzhen
has been on guard.
But
I've already made all the preparations.
I arranged for a man
dressed in the clothes of Jinyun Restaurant
and gave him some money
to help me cheat Jun Zhenzhen first.
The tea I sent this time has been filled with
another overpowering drug.
And I tampered with
both two cups of tea.
That man
has taken the antidote.
So,
so once he is in the room, the plan is perfectly safe,
right?
Yes.
Let's wait and see.
I looked at that girl.
She's the girl who gave you the lantern the other day.
Honestly… She's that girl.
…did you just throw the game on purpose?
Miss Jun is so good at the pitch-pot game.
I candidly admit defeat.
You spent so much time up there talking to her.
What did you talk about?
I wonder too.
Tell us about it.
Don't let it go wrong this time.
Lord, you can rest assured.
This time we have made all the preparations.
There can be no mistakes.
Yes.
Why hasn't there been any movement
for so long?
I wonder too.
Shall I go and have a look?
That's OK.
Go and have a look.
What's the matter?
Jun Zhenzhen,
what are you shouting for?
I think Miss Ning is mistaken for someone else.
I'm here.
Let me go.
Come over.
Jin'er.
Isn't that Miss Lin?
Let me go.
Who sent you here?
Jun Zhenzhen.
Let's talk about it later.
Miss Ning,
I don't know this lady surnamed Jun.
It's none of my business.
Don't talk nonsense here.
I don't even know you.
How could you do that?
I…
Miss Ning,
are you trying to hurt my lady
or destroy her?
Don't talk nonsense.
This is clearly the trap you set.
Ning Yunyan,
how am I supposed to live?
You want to plot against my lady,
but you hurt her by mistake
and still bite back here.
It seems that
she hurt
herself
by her own doing.
Don't talk nonsense.
It has nothing to do with me.
You all wronged me.
Indeed.
So wicked.
She's gone too far.
Why is she like this?
How could she do that?
Go.
Miss Jun.
Yunzhao. Young master.
Yunzhao.
Watch out.
Go.
Don't run.
I hope it didn't scare you.
No.
Ning Yunyan,
did you do it?
You're talking nonsense.
You obviously designed all this.
You just want to take this opportunity
to make a big fuss,
so that you can cast the load on the Ning family.
Yunyan,
stop it.
Miss Jun,
sorry.
I'll solve it.
Everybody. Everybody.
Sorry, guys.
Sorry.
Come out.
It's all right now.
Today is the big day of Jinyun Restaurant.
I didn't expect
this to happen.
It scared
all of you here.
Jinyun Restaurant
apologizes to you all.
Today's expenses
are halved.
But
the immediate priority
is to ensure your safety.
So
our Jinyun Restaurant
will be temporarily blocked.
I hope
you will bear it.
Please bear it.
Yunzhao.
It's all Jun Zhenzhen's fault.
Otherwise Jin'er
wouldn't be like this.
Our Ning family wouldn't
spend so much silver.
Yunyan,
why don't you think about
why she lied to you
and why you were deceived?
You framed her
in such a mean means first.
It's all your choice,
your decision.
What reason do you have to resent her now?
Yunzhao,
I'm your sister.
Why don't you speak for me
but for her?
Yunyan,
don't you think you were wrong?
I wasn't wrong.
It's all her fault.
To blame her is to shirk your own fault.
You will continue to make mistakes in the future.
What's wrong with me?
I just want to retaliate against her for the Ning family.
It's all her fault.
She just wanted to frame me.
Ning Yunyan,
you won't
be lucky
every time.
And in this case,
your stubbornness
has ruined Miss Lin's life.
Don't you feel sorry now?
What's wrong with me?
I wasn't wrong.
Yunzhao, I wasn't wrong.
Come on. Come on. Come here.
All right. All right.
Mr. Ling,
are you
all right?
Thank you for saving me today.
I don't know
when you came.
I happened to see
your skill in the pitch-pot game.
Well,
you were the one
who just betted on me, huh?
I have a question.
The Heavenly…
Zan.
The men of Arm Moral Department are coming.
Let's go.
Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Right now.
Make way.
Who's in charge here?
Come here to talk to me.
Your Excellency,
the person in charge is usually here.
He is absent only on March 3
in accordance with the usual practice.
What do you want me to do,
Your Excellency?
Let everyone
gather downstairs
and leave the front door
in turn.
Your Excellency,
our Jinyun Restaurant
is open to all the people today.
There are many people coming and going.
It's really difficult for me
to meet your request.
I'll arrange it right away.
Sorry,
guys.
I'm really sorry.
According to his request,
line up
to get out of Jinyun Restaurant in turn.
Sorry, guys.
Please.
Go.
Let's go.
It's full of twists and turns.
Zan,
we are so unlucky.
We can meet
our enemies accidentally every time.
Now Jinyun Restaurant
is surrounded everywhere.
It's hard for us to go out.
Come here. Wait.
Stop.
OK. No. No.
No. Go.
Go. Be quick. Be quick.
Wait.
Stop.
No. No.
OK. Go.
Stop.
No. Go.
No. No. No.
Go.
Leave. Leave.
Stop.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You guys
search upstairs one room by one room.
Yes.
Go.
Make way.
My money.
Stop it.
She's covering us.
Zan,
why don't we run in chaos?
I'm afraid Arm Moral Department is going to pick on her.
Mine.
Stop it.
If you go on,
I will kill you all.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Arm Moral Department is handling a case.
Get the hell out of here.
I'm Ning Yunzhao from Zezhou.
You're from the mansion of Lord Ning Yan.
Yes.
Childe Ning,
Arm Moral Department's action
was secretly ordered by His Majesty.
I'm afraid
you'll lose your head after listening to it.
Your Excellency,
all the people who came to Jinyun Restaurant today
are civilians.
There must be no key criminal you want to catch.
Why should you bother them?
Childe Ning,
this is not the time for you to be a hero.
Hurry back to home.
Send my regards
to your dad.
Did you
drop
the silver?
Answer me.
Your Excellency,
please forgive
my maid's timidity.
Zan,
what should we do?
Keep calm.
You look very composed.
I think
the maid
dropped the silver deliberately.
All of you,
search carefully upstairs and downstairs
and don't miss any corner.
Yes.
Let's go.
Make way.
Make way. Make way.
Zan, terrible.
It seems we can't avoid fighting with them.
Don't expose our identity.
We still have more important things to do.
Let's go.
Drink.
Stand aside. Stand aside.
Sorry.
Sorry, everyone.
OK.
Go.
Stop.
Let me check. Wait.
It isn't me.
Go.
Miss Jun,
let's go now. Miss Jun.
She's safe.
Prepare to act.
Is there anyone?
No.
Zan,
will we act?
Follow me.
Search carefully.
Yes.
No one.
Withdraw.
They left.
Thank you so much today.
Thanks. Thanks.
How do you know there's a secret door here?
I'm very familiar
with the structure of Jinyun Restaurant.
Each separate room here has a secret door
and all these secret doors are connected.
Chen Qi.
You're surnamed Chen.
Are you the descendant of the Chen family
who sold Jinyun Restaurant?
Don't slander me.
It's my dad, a compulsive gambler, who sold it,
not me.
Well,
how do you know
they want to catch us?
As soon as the men of Arm Moral Department came,
I saw you slip away.
If they didn't come to catch you,
you weren't afraid of being found out.
Thanks. Thanks.
Your Excellency,
we searched upstairs and downstairs
and didn't find anyone suspicious.
A bunch of bums.
See you, Your Excellency.
They already left.
Who are you?
Why are you standing at the gate of my mansion?
It turns out to be Miss Fang.
I'm Ning Yunzhao.
Miss Fang,
I want to see Miss Jun.
Please tell her.
Childe Ning,
do you think
it's proper
for you to see her
at this time?
Please tell her
about it.
Whether she wants
to see me or not
depends on her.
OK.
Just wait.
I'll go and ask her.
The assassin today
is likely to be the one
who framed up the Fang family.
As the assassin escaped,
I have no clue again.
After I cure Chengyu,
I should figure out the guy behind quickly.
Jinxiu.
Ning Yunzhao wants to see you.
Ning Yunzhao?
Decide whether
you see him or not.
If others see
him waiting at our gate,
it'll damage my brother's reputation.
OK.
Miss Jun,
were you frightened
by what happened at Jinyun Restaurant today?
No.
Thank you for your care.
It's good.
It turns out you played a go game with me
on the night of the lantern show.
The one who could make such an exquisite composition
must be an openhearted person.
You're
the same as I thought.
I'm flattered.
Why do you want to see me tonight?
I apologize to you
for Yunyan's cheating you into going to Jinyun Restaurant.
Childe Ning,
you shouldn't be to blame.
It wasn't caused by you, either,
so you don't need to apologize to me.
No.
I asked Yunyan and learnt
she hated you for quitting the marriage.
So I should
be to blame.
Since Miss Ning
told you the real reason,
please tell her
I don't want more people to be involved in it.
So I hope
she can conduct herself well
after this matter.
Miss Jun, don't worry.
They'll be given a lesson.
Miss Jun,
I also want to ask you something
today.
Please go ahead.
How do you know
it was my birthday date
on the day of the lantern show?
I learnt it
from the marriage contract.
Miss Jun,
is it really
a coincidence?
Childe Ning,
you think too much.
I didn't plan to meet
and play the go game with you
intentionally.
Do I
think so much?
Yes.
Then why did you
give me a lantern?
You knew who I was back then.
Didn't you think
it's improper?
Childe Ning,
I was indeed thoughtless.
If what I did
perplexes you
and makes you misunderstand me,
I'll apologize to you.
Miss Jun,
no need.
It seems I really think so much.
See you.
Childe Ning,
I know
our engagement
displeases many people.
But
I have put it down.
Let's put an end to all this.
I had no idea you would come today,
so I didn't prepare tea for you.
Take this pear
as tea.
It turns out
she doesn't adore me.
Our engagement was annulled.
We won't
have any relationship later.
Ning Yunzhao,
she has expressed her meaning
by giving you this pear.
It means
separation.
Don't think that much.
She can do it,
and so do you.
Good pear.
It's sweet.
It's a good gift for other.
But it means
separation.
Did you hear our talk?
I heard it accidentally.
I happened to pass by.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for saving me today.
I promised you
I would protect you
and ensure you're not hurt.
I asked Zhang Baotang
to investigate the assassin's movements.
It should be the one who framed the Fang family.
I also think so.
Now they're determined
to perish the Fang family.
How are you?
I'm fine.
It was dangerous
at Jinyun Restaurant today.
Did those men of Arm Moral Department come to catch you?
For the sake of
your safety,
please leave here as soon as possible.
Our deal ends.
Stop investigating this matter again.
Why do you care about me so much?
Do I?
Don't worry about me.
I have a sense of propriety.
Can I ask you a question?
Do you want to ask about the movement of Heavenly Maids Scattering Blossoms?
How do you it's called
Heavenly Maids Scattering Blossoms?
Princess Jiuling once taught me it.
When did you learn
to play the pitch-pot game with her?
In the winter of that year when she was 15.
What about the way of drinking tea?
Why are you
exactly alike?
Princess Jiuling and I were together morning and night,
so she taught me much.
What else did she teach you?
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫
Who are you?
Who are you actually?
I'm Jun Zhenzhen.
Go to the accountant's office with me
tomorrow afternoon.
Mother,
I have something to talk with you.
I know
you'll leave for the capital city.
I've prepared luggage
and carriage for you.
Thank you, mother.
You're welcome.
Mother,
fix Yunyan's marriage
before I leave.
But you'll leave in three days.
Do you mean
we fix her marriage
in three days?
Yes.
She did make a mistake,
but Jun Zhenzhen
should also be to blame.
She's the initiator of evil.
If she hadn't come to break off the engagement…
Mother,
she isn't the initiator of evil.
I vaguely heard something about it.
You know the rights and wrongs
better than I do.
But
it's unnecessary
to fix Yunyan's marriage
so soon.
Mother,
I don't want to let my marriage
be others' bargaining chip anymore.
Yunyan should also
learn to be mature
and know what to do
and what not to do.
We shouldn't allow her
to wantonly enjoy youth
and delay her life.
OK.
I've planned
her marriage
and thought to fix it
in lunar December this year
and let her marry next year.
Since you can't come back during the Spring Festival this year,
I'll fix her marriage,
so you won't miss it.
Thank you, mother.
Ning Yunyan
will get married soon.
Really?
I heard that
it's Childe Ning's proposal.
They've seen the matchmaker,
and she will be engaged later.
Don't you know it?
Miss Jun, don't worry.
They'll be given a lesson.
So this is the lesson that
he gave Ning Yunyan.
Your expression tells me that
you've long known it.
Zhenzhen,
the wedding day of you and Chengyu is near at hand.
Have you tried
all the wedding clothes sent to you?
Are they the right size?
Thank you, aunt.
They fit well.
Do you believe that
she didn't try them at all?
She talked nonsense
and didn't take the marriage seriously at all.
Jinxiu,
stop talking.
Go on eating.
A doctor will come
at 13:00
to check Chengyu's condition again
before the wedding day.
After lunch,
let's go together.
Grandma,
I have something to deal with at 13:00.
So I'm afraid
I can't go with you.
What are you going to do?
Is it more important than Chengyu's condition?
Why must you go
when the doctor comes?
Before the wedding day,
I want to get everything ready.
OK.
Do I need to ask the doctor
about anything?
Can you ask the doctor
to prescribe something more
to supplement Chengyu's physical strength?
In this way,
he can successfully complete our marriage.
Jun Zhenzhen,
you're shameless.
Chengyu is in poor health,
but you still,
you still want him to take tonics
for your wedding night.
You
are shameless.
Jinxiu,
you misunderstand me.
I do so
to hope
Chengyu can
complete our wedding ceremony,
which is also a major event of his life.
You misunderstand me.
You were talkative.
Grandma, I'm full.
Then,
I'm leaving first.
OK.
Mind your own business.
Then come back early.
Jinxiu,
as an
unmarried girl,
be reserved
and don't talk
thoughtlessly.
Mother,
I didn't educate her well.
Grandma,
I see.
Go on with your lunch.
Deshengchang rose in the third year of the Taiyan period.
There're records of accounts in the previous years
when they earned less money,
but why aren't there any records
in the third year of the Taiyan period,
when they earned
more money?
Are there any other account books?
The freight records over the years
and the account books
of Deshengchang branches are all here.
Maybe they were lost
or destroyed.
Destroyed?
If they're really destroyed,
it'll be troublesome.
As many years have passed,
there must be no witnesses and material evidence.
Deshengchang's history of that year
seems to be erased.
Miss Jun,
you've been in Fang's mansion for so long.
Have you seen this pattern?
How did he know this seal pattern?
I've never seen it.
What is it?
Previous shops,
pawnshops and banks
all had their own symbols
to differentiate each other.
I don't know
what this pattern represents, either,
but I feel
it has something to do with what I'm investigating.
But this is not the seal of Deshengchang.
I know it.
The less related the Fang family
and the third year
of the Taiyan period
is to
this pattern,
the safer they will be.
If you see this pattern
in Fang's mansion,
please tell me at once.
OK.
This matter is serious.
Thank you for your help.
Last night,
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
OK.
See you.
What's wrong?
I just can't understand
why you gave up
the engagement with Childe Ning
but marries Fang Chengyu instead.
What did others say?
Someone said outside that
the Fangs hold
such a grand wedding
to spend some money
for Young Master Fang for the last time.
They said it isn't a wedding at all
but a funeral instead.
Bah, bah, bah.
It's too harsh.
Let them jeer.
After Chengyu gets better,
they will also come
for congratulation.
Wash hands!
In 10-odd years,
I've been engaged three times,
with Lu Yunqi who seemed to be from a dream,
with Childe Ning who's destined to miss me,
and with my cousin in depression and despair.
However, all these three engagements
do not truly belong to me.
Can I have an engagement
that truly belongs to me
in the rest of my life?
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫