Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ♡♥ Unraveling a Heart Team ♥♡ @ Viki.com
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold, the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend, we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world, a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 5]
Chengyu, look over there.
Chengyu, it's cold at night. Do you want a handwarmer?
No need.
Sister, Chengyu is a lot better now and not that afraid of the cold.
- Too much heat may cause dryness for him.
- Okay, we'll do as Zhenzhen says.
Little brother.
The Fire God temple is ahead.
- It's the most lively there every Lantern Festival.
- Yes.
Will mother worry about other seeing me sick?
You didn't do anything wrong. What are you scared of?
Relax.
- There is an endless stream of people here to see the lanterns today.
- Many people.
Yunzhao, you'd be missing out if you didn't come today. You should thank me.
Exactly.
Why is it so lively ahead? Are they showing the best lanterns?
Right. I heard
that the lanterns this year are of various styles, unique, and novel.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go take a look.
The festive lanterns this year are really nice.
Does Brother Wenming like to see lanterns in the daytime?
Seeing lanterns in the daytime?
I think that seeing lanterns in the daytime is a different kind of experience.
I don't have such refined interests. I only like
the grand view
of the many colors and bright lights.
You're still the same as always.
Yunzhao, look at that.
What should we do
if we encounter Miss Fang here today?
Right. What should we do?
Act naturally. It'll be fine as long as we enjoy the view.
Even if people joke and talk about me,
what does that have to do with me?
He's indeed from the Ning family.
He minds his own business!
Grandmother, look over there.
Grandmother, later, I want to leave for a bit.
We're celebrating festivities today. Spread out, you don't have to stay by our sides.
Go see the lights.
Let me help you, Miss.
- Chengyu, isn't it nice to be out here?
- Yes.
Look over there.
Eleventh month, fifteenth day.
He has good skill.
Four seasons, fifteenth day.
Person, fifteenth day.
Miss, where is the lantern you made? Are we there yet?
Don't worry.
We're almost there.
I just saw someone selling nuts. Do you want some? I'll go buy it.
Go ahead. I'll wait for you here.
Here you go.
I lost.
Everyone, is anyone else up for a challenge?
Chess master, don't challenge him just yet.
Wait for all of us to have had our fun.
Then you can take up the challenge and impress everyone.
I'll challenge you.
Do well, don't lose.
It'll be embarrassing.
Five elements, six palaces.
Six palaces, five elements.
That's a mistake.
Seven dippers, six palaces.
Seven dippers, five elements.
Six palaces, six palaces, long.
Six palaces, four seasons.
Seven dippers, six palaces.
Eighteen stars, eight directions.
Eighteen pines, seven dippers, connect.
- Fourteen pheasants, sixteen phases.
- Five elements, nineteen guests.
Miss, please step out.
Twelfth month, tenth day.
Twelfth month, six palaces.
- Nine states, nine states.
- Eight directions, eight directions.
- Nine states, eight directions.
- Eight directions, seven dippers.
- Heaven, seven dippers.
- Eleventh month, Earth.
Four seasons, heaven.
Person, heaven.
Six palaces, heaven, connect.
Nine states, six palaces.
Eight directions, five elements, connect.
Sixteen phases, nine states.
Seventeen stars, ten days, connect.
Nineteen guests, seven dippers.
Nineteen guests, nine states.
Six palaces, fourteen pheasants.
Heaven, six palaces.
Heaven, five elements.
Heaven, eight directions.
Four seasons, fourteen phases.
Five elements, fifteenth day.
Seven dippers, thirteenth intercalary day.
- Seven dippers, fifteenth day.
- Tenth day, heaven.
Nine states, heaven.
Eleventh month, heaven.
Eleventh month, person.
Fifteenth day, six palaces.
Fifteenth day, five elements.
Earth. Person.
Earth. Eight directions.
Heaven. Earth.
Sixteen phases. Heaven.
Thirteen intercalary days. Earth.
Your Go skills are excellent and admirable.
I admit you outdid me.
Don't need to be modest.
"Don't need to be modest." I should say it to you instead.
Decisive and thoughtful, you thought twice before making every move.
Your skills are truly superior than mine. It wasn't just a fluke.
But why didn't you move the last piece?
Did you try to avoid embarrassing me?
Of course not.
It was obvious who had won. Why would I do that?
You can tell someone's personality by how they make moves. Your style was elegant.
I had a good time playing you today.
I'm Ning Yunzhao. May I know your name?
So you are Young Master Ning?
That's me.
May I know who your teacher is?
My teacher is my deceased father.
Where do you live?
Will I have another chance to play you?
Your Go skills are quite good.
You're more impressive than I thought.
This is for you.
Are you comforting me since I lost?
Happy birthday.
After all, he once had a marriage contract with Zhenzhen.
If Zhenzhen was alive, she would definitely be satisfied with the marriage.
I gave him the lantern for Zhenzhen.
Yunzhao,
I lost.
When did you receive the lantern?
Who gave you this?
I just met a lady who beat me at Go.
- Beat you?
- You played Go?
When did you play Go?
That doesn't sound right. A child prodigy, you remembered all the Go moves you'd seen at the age of eight
and ranked level four, Understanding Changes, at the age of twenty.
Which woman in the world could beat you at Go?
Which family is she from?
I want to know too.
Miss! Wait for me, Miss.
I finally found you. I thought I'd lost you in the crowd.
Where's the lantern you made?
It's right there.
Why is it dim?
This lantern is a Go board, embellished with pieces all over.
Now Black is just one step away from winning this game.
If someone can make the right move, the lantern will be lit up.
- Give it a try.
- Let me try.
Hold on.
Not everyone can give it a try.
Look.
The 5,000-tael note in this Chinese crystal cup is the prize.
- 5,000 taels–
- Whoever lights up the lantern can win the prize.
- 5,000 taels?
You can give it a try for 10 taels.
If you have no money... get out of here!
[Hit the Ground Running]
Miss, do you think the 5,000 taels is...
Exactly.
The money the Ning family gave you for breaking off the engagement...
Did you use the money the Ning family gave you for breaking off the engagement as the prize?
Does it mean if we lose, we'll lose everything?
Don't worry. Very few people in the world can solve it.
Good. Good. Then I can sit back and watch.
What do you think, second brother?
Isn't it crowded with lanterns lit up at night?
Even though Zezhou is small,
the Lantern Festival here can compare with the one in the capital.
Second brother, you've been exhausted lately. Just relax.
Also, someone set up a Go game today,
where you can give it a try for 10 taels.
If you win, you can take 5,000 taels home.
I think I can win it for sure. I'll win it for sure.
- Second brother.
- Baotang.
Second brother, look.
I have something serious to do. Don't take me
to irrelevant places like this.
Second brother, we've arrived. It's right there, second brother.
Don't. Don't go. Let's give it a try.
I'm sorry.
The Fang family's cousin set up a Go game over there. Let's take a look.
- Let's go.
Go game?
With 10 taels,
you can only buy high-quality rouge from a high-end cosmetics shop in Zezhou.
You can only buy a famille Ding ware tea set.
You can only pay for a table of a top-notch feast at Luyang Restaurant.
You can only buy an ink brush made with wolf fur from the north.
Miss, did you teach him to say that?
No.
Now we've been in Zezhou for a while, our money's tight indeed.
Second brother, you've changed.
Have I changed?
No, no, no. You haven't changed. You haven't changed.
What are you looking at?
With 10 taels, you have a chance of winning 5,000 taels.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
This keeper is knowledgeable.
It looks like he's always traveling.
I'm a businessman. I'll give it a try.
Miss, we've made 10 taels.
Look.
- Hurry.
- I'll try.
Yunzhao.
Yunzhao, you've excelled in Go since you were little.
Why don't you give it a try?
Whoever set it up is a clever person with brilliant Go skills and in an extraordinary state of mind
But this game... I can't solve it.
You can't solve it?
Just give it a try first.
This is a chance of winning 5,000 taels with 10 taels.
If you don't go, I'll go in a bit.
This game can't be solved.
Chengyu, this year's lanterns are more beautiful than ever before.
How joyful it is.
- That's right.
- Grandma, you see how pretty that is?
Look at that.
Right?
Grandma, do you know where Zhenzhen is?
Why hasn't she come back?
It's so crowded and she's probably so happy that she's forgotten it.
Then do you know where her lantern is?
I don't.
I really don't.
Grandma, I'm a bit tired. Let's go home.
Chengyu, are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're tired indeed. We've been browsing for a while.
Go. Let's head home. Let's head home.
- Grandma, I haven't had enough fun.
- Let's head home, sister.
You see how pretty that is?
Hurry.
I'll try.
- Nobody wants to try now.
- Exactly.
I'll do it.
Only 10 taels.
That's fine as long as we have fun.
- He's not good.
- He dared to give it a try despite his caliber.
- I'll do it.
- Nobody can solve it. You're just a sugar figure seller. What's the point of trying?
- Somebody's playing. Don't disturb them.
- Why give it a try?
Exactly.
If I light up this lantern, you'll be impressed.
He seems quite confident.
- Make a move.
- Just take the money back.
- Can you do it?
- Exactly. Can you do it?
- Hurry up and make a move.
Make a move now.
- Do you think it's easy to make money?
- Just place it somewhere.
Can you do it?
It's lit up! It's lit up!
He is so good.
Yeah, so good
I figured out the chess gameplay.
I did it. I did it.
I did it.
I figured out the chess game.
Where is the money?
Does he know?
That's right.
Whether I know how I play or not? I am the one who got it nevertheless.
What is he saying?
Deliver the left over small taels to my house.
Return our money to us.
Miss.
Our money is all gone.
Five thousand taels.
How long would it take to earn that back?
Miss.
I was only joking before.
Its only five thousand taels. You are so brilliant.
Will earn that back very soon.
I wasn't thinking about the money.
Watch where you are going.
Miss.
- Manager Gao.
- This is the person watching the lantern, Lai Zhong Liang.
What are you doing?
It's all right, Manager Gao.
We met last night. You did well.
Miss, you were at the scene yesterday?
Since I made the lantern, naturally I need to take a look.
Then did Miss know who won at the end?
I heard people calling him Chen Qi.
Right, his name is Chen Qi.
- He is a candy selling peddlar.
- He doesn't know how to play chess.
He...doesn't know to play chess.
Then he scammed us?
Mister Lai, we asked you here today to check with you as well.
Yesterday did you see anything suspicious at the end.
I am only paid for watching the lanterns.
Liu'er.
Last night,
- Can I ask you a question?
- What question?
This five thousand taels is enough for your entire lifetime's spending.
Why didn't you just directly take it?
This young sir, who are you looking down at?
It was agreed on who gets it.
If you didn't advised me just before, I would most likely placed wrong.
Then I wouldn't even be able to earn those couple hundred taels.
You actually keep your words.
Give me the money.
What money?
I am missing one candy there.
Look at this person.
Two man in their twenties.
One call the other Second Brother, is that right?
Since you know already, why did. you ask me over.
- This...
- No...
Lai Zhong Liang, you...
Where did Mr. Lai used to work previously?
He watches the vehicles at the money exchange.
He's been at the Fang Family for quite a number of years.
Miss, you lost so much money yesterday.
Aren't you angry?
What is there to be angry over?
They used their true ability to win the chess game.
Doesn't matter who figured it out.
Brother.
It's not right.
Yangyang, you are mischievious again.
Brother,
what is interesting about chess game? You've been pondering it since last night.
It's an ancient gameplay. I was trying to solve it.
My brother is so brilliant. You surely can solve it.
Brother, this lantern is pretty.
I will take it to make a pair with my own.
You can't.
I am not taking it.
I will just borrow it for a few days. I will return it.
If you like this, I will buy a new one.
Is there a matter you need me for?
Mother asked me to inquire when you plan to return to the capital?
I'll leave in a few days. I'll go tell mother personally.
Then I'll get going, Brother.
All right.
You come in here without prior notification.
What is that about?
Santao asked me to come.
I saw that you were in a good mood. So i didn't interrupt.
Did you have a good time last night?
It's not bad.
No wonder, you didn't return.
Of course you had fun without my annoying presence.
You are mad?
All right, it's my fault. I was too focus on the lantern.
I missed the time. Didn't come back to be with you.
I also know that you lost money. A large amount.
You know all about it?
I know it. Grandmother told me yesterday.
Told me not to mention this matter in front of you.
Yet you brought it up?
I wanted to.
Come.
You are recovering well.
You will soon can do a medicinal soak.
I don't need you for the medicinal soak. Let Santao do that.
Santao also has to listen to me. In addition,
- I will be marrying you soon. You needn't be shy anymore.
- You...
[Yunmengze Inn]
You have a guest.
Miss Jun, why are you here?
You spent all night trying to solve my game to wait for me to come over, didn't you?
What do you mean?
Do sugar figures taste good, second brother?
Miss Jun is very smart.
I came to ask you how you figured out the chess gameplay.
I can answer you after you answer my question.
OK. Ask.
How did Deshengchang start making a fortune?
Why do you ask this?
Deshengchang's business is booming,
so I want to learn how to do business and make money.
You came to the lantern shop for me.
You managed to win my 5,000 taels at the Lantern Festival and trick me into coming here. Is it worth it?
It's worth it.
I'm not done asking. When it comes to cargos,
there's a list of customers
showing their destinations and names.
Since Deshengchang deals with many customers,
there should be documents.
He's really digging into the secret of Zezhou.
You think too highly of me.
How could an outsider like me know about such confidential information?
So can you answer my question?
Because I am smart.
-You. -Forget it. I will stop teasing you.
Actually, my father told me.
When my father taught me this chess gameplay,
I listen very, very carefully to him.
Only becaseu I am smart. I got it right away.
The audience who watched us playing all praised me.
They said, "Wow! You're very smart!
You're an invincible, extremely intelligent hero."
I...
So, I am really smart.
Second brother, Sky Pavilion has figured out the medicinal herbs.
-What is it for?
-This prescription is for chronic disease.
But it was rare to put so many herbs together.
Never seen anything like this.
In Fang family, there is only one person
has chronic disease.
The dying young master Fang?
[Fuxiang Medicine Shop]
Put it all to the side.
- Place them.
- Got it shopkeeper.
-Hi Miss Jun. -Hi shopkeeper.
Is the prescription that I reserved ready?
Here it is. Wait for a moment.
-I will get it for you. -Thank you.
Miss Jun, can I ask you
who prescribed it for you?
Antying wrong?
Nothing wrong. It is just weird.
Seperately, each herb is good.
But I don't know why mixing more than 10 herbs together
They are all detox herbs.
One or two detox herbs should be sufficient.
But mixing more than 10 herbs
is an overdose of medicine, like the saying said.
It can backfire.
Miss Jun, it not only cannot detox,
it may harm you.
Thank you for your concern. I know what it is. It should be fine.
Since you know,
please take it.
-Thank you. -Have a good day.
[Satin Silk Fabrics]
I meet you wherever I go.
Is it difficult to bump into me?
You're detoxifying the young master, right?
Why do you always think you're so clever?
How do you explain the purpose of the prescription?
I am ignorant.
What disease needs more than 10 detox herbs?
As a doctor, I get it to research on herbs.
Is it not right?
It sounds good.
But see if what I'm thinking makes sense as well.
Family Fang has only one son for three generations.
They've been cursed.
I heard that this young master won't live past 16 years old.
It turns out that he's been deeply intoxicated.
If it occurs to one generation, it is an accident. Two generations, coincidence.
If it happens to three generations,
isn't it weired?
I don't know what you are talking about.
It could be destiny.
Guess what?
The male curse on the Fang family is actually artificially created.
The young master Fang was actually secretly poisoned.
You are smart.
But it is not inappropriate for me to heal Fang Chengyu.
It has nothing to do with you. Please give me a break.
Don't worry. I won't leak it.
I need a favor from you.
Use your identity to help me check the list
of the Fang family's freight guests over the years.
Fang Mansion
Miss Jun
Your letter.
-Where is it from? -Family Ning.
Miss Jun, there is a misunderstanding between the Fang and Ning families.
Please come to Sky Room 3 of Jinyun Restaurant on March 3rd for a chat.
Ning Yunzhao
Jun Zhenzhen, I don't believe that you won't play the game.
Yanyan, your idea is wonderful.
She'll definitely show up with Childe Ning's letter.
At that time, she'll lose her innocent reputation.
Will she still dare to put her hopes on Childe Ning after that?
That is right.
But, do we go too far?
- Aren't you afraid—
- So what?
She offended us first.
She first cheated my family of silver and then embarrassed us again and again.
It is tit for tit.
Right.
Your lady, your tea.
Will you go to meet Ning Yunzhao?
To Jun Zhenzhen
Although the letter comes from Ning Yunzhao's personal servant,
he might not the one who wrote it.
How so?
Ning Yunzhao was born into a gentry family.
He would act openly and appropriately.
Even If there really was something that couldn't be talked about at home,
he still probably wouldn't have invited me to a place that would make girls uncomfortable.
This is just my guess.
Why didn't you let Mujin pass me a message as usual, but ask me to meet you here?
There are so many people watching in the residence.
This is too risky.
This is serious. We should talk in person.
If anything goes wrong, even if Mujin can afford that, can you?
Then please say it quickly.
I'm really worried that Mujin can't handle it on her own if this takes too long.
I checked carefully at the Lantern Festival last night.
I realized that Chengyu's condition was not improving.
He still looked half-dead.
It seemed that the marriage wasn't of much help. It won't save his life.
But the only thing that could go wrong now is if Jun Zhenzhen is using the marriage as an excuse,
to get pregnant with a male offspring of the Fang family...
What do you mean by that?
If Jun Zhenzhen dies,
in such a short period of time, where is the Fang family
going to find another girl who will willingly to marry for the sake of warding off his illness?
You're going to kill Jun Zhenzhen?
Nobody will kill her.
It's just that she got unlucky and had a little accident.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ♡♥ Unraveling a Heart Team ♥♡ @ Viki.com
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come, I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come, I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ If memories could speak, I wouldn’t stop shedding tears  ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers, I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫