(Do Not Attempt To Reenact This)
Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
Moreo.
-Why didn't you fight back?
-I did.
But...
You know how it is.
Wait up, my leg hurts.
Oh, my gosh. You're ruining the moment.
Come on.
What was that?
I think it came from the front.
Let's go check it out.
Why are you just sitting there?
Come on, Ser!
Hey.
Where are you going?
You're supposed to take responsibility
but you're running away.
Hey, who do you think you are?
Use your eyes!
This is crazy.
It took me months to order this.
-Now it got scratched.
-It's okay.
Let them solve this problem
by themselves.
-But...
-It's okay.
-No!
Your motorcycle
got the most damage, Ares.
This is crazy.
Oh, my God!
When someone's talking to you,
you have to look at them.
Do you think the asphalt
is more handsome than me?
"Handsome"?
How much money
do you need me to transfer to you?
This girl thinks she's so rich.
Just send it straight to my account.
-570...
-Stop speaking nonsense. Hey!
Do you know who I am?
The money that you have
and the money that I have...
You have more money than me.
But it's okay.
If we combine it together, we...
You're not funny.
Do you want to input
the number yourself?
I don't need your money.
-I need your apology.
-I was going to do that...
before you roughly pulled my hair.
Who is that girl?
Oops.
Apologize to me right now.
Not that easy.
Okay.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Not that easy.
Wait.
-I really am sorry.
-What do I get if I forgive you?
I'll do whatever you wish.
I'll ask five wishes.
-Two wishes.
-I'm not interested.
Okay. Three wishes.
Deal.
Girls.
Here we go.
You're so cool.
Until now, no one has dared
to go against Calderioz.
Let alone a girl. You're the only one.
That means...
you deserve to join our group!
Congrats!
Okay, I'm Karissa.
-I'm Zea.
-Selina. But you can call me Selin.
I'm Cleo.
Hi.
I'm Serra.
I'm Zea.
From the ABC triangle,
we know that angle A is 120 degrees.
Angle B is 30 degrees.
From A to C is 5 centimeters.
We're looking for the length
between B to C.
-Does anyone know the answer?
-Widows really are more tempting.
(Widows really are more tempting)
Anyone?
Hello, everyone.
My name is Zeanne Queensha Bratadikara.
You can just call me Zea.
I've just moved from Bandung.
She's from Bandung.
No wonder she's pretty.
Zea, you can sit on the empty chair
over there.
Please move to the other seat.
Hurry.
Zea, you can sit here.
Good morning, baby.
You're so beautiful today.
Did you sleep well?
Wake up! Wake up and solve
the problem on the board!
What's the answer?
(Trigonometry)
Ares is also sleeping.
Ares, wake up.
Ares.
Why were you sleeping?
You must have been studying
till late at night, right?
That's why you're sleepy.
No wonder you've got the highest grades.
Moreo, you should be like Ares.
He's got the highest grade
in this school...
because he's the most enthusiastic
when it comes to studying.
Come on, come to the front now.
Come on!
Miss...
I can't solve that problem.
Okay, fine.
Then, I'll give you a punishment.
Go to the other classes now
and apologize to everyone.
That includes your juniors
so that you'll stop sleeping in class.
Do you understand?
Then I should receive
the punishment too.
I also fell asleep.
-Are you being serious?
-It's okay, to make it fair.
We both came here to apologize...
because we both fell asleep in class
during the lesson.
It's okay if you fall asleep
in class, Ares.
We still like you. Right?
Especially if you dreamt about me.
But I also want to...
Ares. Stop!
I'm a human being!
-Do you see?
-No.
Ares and I want to apologize
because we fell asleep in class.
Ares, let's take a photo.
Take a picture with Moreo, okay?
Let's take a photo.
We have to hurry
because I'm really busy today.
Smile!
Oh, my gosh. This is so entertaining.
I want to apologize because Moreo and I
fell asleep in class during the lesson.
I also want to apologize.
I fell asleep in class
too just like Ares.
I think apologizing
is really important...
because there are three stages
to apologizing...
Meet me at the cafetaria...
in the second break.
I didn't know, so I'm apologizing.
Because I didn't know.
But the point is,
apologizing is really important.
I'm apologizing. That's how it is.
Looks like someone wants
to join our gang.
No, thanks.
Zea.
Come here.
Sit down.
I was the one
who told her to meet me here.
Because this new kid...
wants to treat us
in order to get to know us better.
Thank you!
Ares, why are you doing this?
Zea already apologized to you.
It's okay, Ser. Let's just say
this is us getting to know each other.
So, what do you guys want to order?
Not just us...
but also all the students
in the cafeteria.
Do you understand me, new kid?
What do you guys want to order?
Just tell the cafeteria lady.
The new kid.
This will be sold out
in an instant, Mang Oji.
Zea.
-Don't get too close to them.
-Yeah.
They're members of the Calderioz gang.
You must have heard of them.
There are so many members in it.
And the six most powerful members
are in this school.
I'll tell you about them.
The one sitting at the edge.
His name's Megan.
(Date of birth, April 3, 2003.
Zodiac, Aries.)
He's one of the members of Calderioz
who is the coolest and talks the least.
And the one over there is Laskar.
(Date of birth, November 2, 2003.
Zodiac, Scorpio.)
(Character, the toughest
who is good at melting people's heart.)
He's the strongest member of Calderioz.
He's a fighter, also known as the guy
who beats people up.
And that one sitting on the table.
That's Moreo.
He's the weakest member of Calderioz.
(Character, class clown, but not cute.)
They're all handsome except him.
Just look at how ugly he is.
Now, the one using his phone is Aiden.
(Date of birth, July 4, 2003.
Zodiac, Cancer.)
(Character, nice, humorous,
has the sweetest smile.)
Calderioz wouldn't be fun without him.
That one is my baby, Ardhan.
He's handsome, isn't he?
(Date of birth, May 27, 2003.
Zodiac, Gemini.)
(Character, flirty,
but his heart is for Karissa.)
He's mine.
Now...
last but not least, him.
Antares.
Or you can call him Ares.
(Date of birth, August 4, 2003.
Zodiac, Leo.)
(Character, got perfect charm,
smile, and gaze.)
He's the leader of the Calderioz gang.
Just like the God of War, he's
well-respected by a lot of people...
and admired by all the girls
in this school.
My advice is if you want
to have a safe life here,...
don't get involved with them.
Here's your drink.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Miss, where's Ares's food?
-It's being prepared.
-Please wait a bit, okay?
-It's fine.
-Just give it to someone else.
-Okay. Wait a bit, okay?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Where's the food I ordered?
You haven't got yours?
All right. Then order it yourself, okay?
♪I believe in second chances
For the broken-hearted♪
♪Now I can take it for granted
Each and every "disregarded"♪
♪I fall apart yet I am still right here♪
♪But broken heart is hard to heal♪
♪It kills me
Everytime I read between the lines♪
♪Love is divided went undecided♪
♪Fade and misguided
Just like another broken-hearted♪
♪Now since you've been gone♪
♪I should carry on♪
♪Cause I'm tired
Of writing songs about you♪
♪I have spent all night♪
♪Just to make this right♪
♪I can't be somewhere I don't belong♪
♪It's time to move along♪
♪Lonely♪
♪For sure♪
♪But I bet I'm not the only one♪
♪Just like a broken hearted♪
Drink first.
Hey.
Can you not be so lovey-dovey
in front of Laskar?
-Why me?
-Of course, you.
Why me?
Why?
-How much is the total?
-The total is 2,050,000 rupiah.
-I'll pay for my own meal.
-Okay, please wait a second.
I'm not used to eating free food.
I'm usually the one treating people.
-Thank you.
Your card, please.
Seriously, that new kid is so annoying.
She's being such a snob and she's
so bravely getting close to Ares.
We really can't let her do this.
We need to teach her a lesson.
Hey.
Wait.
-Come here.
-I want to go back to class.
Back to class?
What did you hear?
I didn't hear anything. I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
Get over here.
Come here.
-What are you doing?
-Stay still.
Stay still.
So pretty.
Don't clean it up, okay?
Bye.
May I know the reason you moved
from Bandung to Derlangga High School?
I know the answer!
I know the reason
you moved to this school.
I'm sure it's because...
-Because I'm here, right?
-Oh, my gosh.
-I actually...
-She's speaking sweetly.
We just met. We need to get to know
each other more...
That's not how it is.
It's my habit.
Be strong, Mor.
I want to talk to you.
Come with me.
She's the only one who's like that.
No one's here.
Zea just treated everyone.
Maybe everyone's still at the cafeteria.
Do people still do that?
Being a secret admirer?
You should just talk to him directly.
For the sweetest person,...
I need to use the most romantic method.
Whatever.
Excuse me, Ares.
Why do you keep avoiding me?
I want to you to keep your promise.
I needed to go to the toilet.
I'm not done talking to you!
Zea!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
Why didn't you bring me along
to watch the girls dance from the start?
I also didn't want to
because of Karissa.
-And then?
-But after I saw my baby,...
I got excited.
Lame.
What's Ares doing?
I just knew that Ares
wants to join the dance.
Zea's pretty good at dancing.
What's wrong with that person?
He's asking for trouble.
Zea.
Why did you laugh at me?
You're such a sensitive person.
We weren't laughing at him, right?
-You were clearly laughing at me.
-What?
-We weren't.
Now, dance.
You're always talking nonsense, Ares.
-Me too?
-Do you want to?
-I don't want to. Just you.
-Hey, you two!
You too, Ardhan. You should dance too!
Sorry, Ares. But seriously,
I wasn't laughing at you too.
Me and Megan were playing games, right?
And Ardhan too.
You're in trouble again.
Mang Oji would say,
"Not your loyal friends."
Not your loyal friends.
-"Not loyal."
-I'm playing the song now.
-Are you serious?
-Whatever.
I'll treat you at Mang Oji later.
Come on.
Karissa would love this.
Zea, wait.
Zea.
I want you to join the dance club.
Usually, if someone wants
to join the dance club...
they have to take the test first.
But since I'm the club president,
you can join right away.
Okay?
I'm really sorry.
I was just dancing along
because I was running away from Ares.
I see.
So, you don't want to join
the dance club?
Okay, then.
Why are you like that?
I'm passing over!
Ares!
Hey!
Over here.
Come on! You're so noisy! What?
Where are you going?
I'm so embarrassed
because the girls saw me.
-Now I'm like a...
-And the color is yellow.
-And it had cartoons on it.
-Did you like it?
You're sick.
Hey.
-So arrogant.
-Oh, you.
What is it?
I think someone moved my bag.
Seriously?
If x is 5...
You took your time
going to the restroom.
Can I borrow your notes later?
Which is 2 times 125...
plus 4 times 25...
plus 2 will give us the total of 337.
Hey, guys.
Have you tried the new shumai
at the cafeteria?
It's the most delicious shumai
I've ever tried in my life.
-It's really...
-You're exaggerating.
-Just take it easy.
-Seriously.
-It's so good.
-Okay, girls, I'm heading back.
My ride's here.
Bye.
But it's really good.
The meat is like...
Can you introduce me to her?
-Her?
-Her.
Zea.
Someone wants me to
introduce you to him.
Hi.
I'm Zea.
I'm Fino.
Zea, can I have your phone number?
Sure.
Thank you.
I'll send you a message sometime.
-How sweet.
-What is it?
It's your first day here
and you already have a fan.
Stop it.
Okay.
-Sel, are you coming with me or not?
-Let's go.
We're going home, guys.
-Bye bye, I love you, guys.
-Love you.
Is she kidding?
Babe, let's go home.
Are you sure you want to go home?
Are we going somewhere?
You don't want to go
somewhere else first?
Of course, I do.
Where are you taking me?
-Let's go to a cafe.
-Sure.
Hold on.
Is it going to be the two of us...
or are the others
going to be invited too?
Of course just the two of us.
You know it yourself
that they're all single.
-They'll be jealous.
-What are you saying?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Wait up.
Hey, babe. Put my cardigan
in your backpack.
My bag's heavy.
-What is that?
-It's for you.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
Babe.
You always know how to make me happy.
Wait. You didn't do
anything wrong, right?
Of course not, babe.
I just want to remind you
how special you are to me.
Very smooth.
I'm going to open it, okay?
-There's a letter? That's rare.
-There's a letter?
Hold it.
Why is there a letter?