Our Secret
EP07
Siyue
Let's play billiards this Sunday.
What are you planning?
Count me in.
I'll think about it.
The math competition is approaching.
Xianxian, you can join us.
I can't play billiards.
Neither can I.
Anyway,
you just aim at the billiard ball and poke it.
That's so embarrassing. I don't want to go with you.
Oh my!
I don't want to go with you, either.
Well, let's go with them.
I can teach you how to play billiards.
Yeah!
How about asking Jiang Chen to join us?
Forget it.
He's too good at it. We don't want to embarrass ourselves.
If you can't see clearly, just tell me.
I can take the notes for you.
You need to focus on your competition paper.
I can finish it on time.
Dinner is ready.
I'm coming.
Hurry up.
Here you are.
Mom
I want to discuss something with you.
I want to change a pair of stronger glasses.
Your nearsightedness has gotten worse?
Yeah.
Xianxian, it was just pseudo myopia before.
Wearing glasses is to correct visual acuity.
How could it get worse?
I have no idea. I can't see clearly sometimes.
Which row of seats are you in now?
The fifth one.
Then you can talk to your teacher
to move your seat to the front row.
You'd better
not depend too much on glasses.
If your nearsightedness keeps getting worse,
you have to wear glasses all the time.
If you don't want to talk to the teacher yourself,
I can talk to him about it.
No. Forget it.
You dad told me that
the science-arts division is coming.
It comes just in time.
When you are in the arts class,
you can sit in the front row.
All will be settled then.
But I may choose science, too.
You are a girl. How can you learn science?
Why can't girls learn science?
I don't mean that girls can't learn science.
It's just girls are usually not good at learning science courses.
You must think that
there is little difference between your academic performance on the two courses.
The science courses will be much more difficult in the junior and senior years.
But ......
That's enough.
I have made the decision for you. Choose the arts class.
How can you say that?
This is my own business.
Don't I have the right to
make my own choice?
You don't know how to make a better choice.
I'm only telling you this for your own good!
And you dad can help you with the courses.
So you can go to a better college.
We did this all
for your own good!
Stop arguing with me.
That's enough.
Calm down.
It is a very big deal.
We should talk it over.
Xianxian
Don't talk to your mom like that!
I'm full.
You can't educate children like that.
You are good at educating.
You really did a good job,
and she just left the table like that.
Xianxian, come online quickly.
Accept my friend request online.
Welcome Little Monster.
Put down your cell phone and do your homework carefully.
Xianxian
You told mom that you want a phone
a few days ago.
And we bought you
this one.
What's wrong?
Sorry, dad.
I lied to you.
About what?
Zhou Siyue lent me this.
I saw it this morning.
Well,
just return it
to him later.
Xianxian
Since we have bought you this mobile phone,
I'd like to make some rules for you.
First,
don't bring the phone to school.
It will distract you.
Second,
I hope you can think about
what your mom said to you just now.
She had a point there.
Dad, you also think
I should choose arts?
I have the same idea as your mother.
It's just that girls may suffer more
to learn science courses.
And we don't want you to go through this.
How about you, dad?
Why did you choose to major in politics?
Me?
I was not good at science courses.
And it shows exactly that
girls are good at arts courses
while boys are good at science courses
is not a correct theory.
By the way,
I get angry not because you don't want me to learn science.
I'm angry because you don't let me make the choice myself.
Xianxian
We did this because
we are afraid that you will make a wrong choice
and can't bear the consequences it may cause.
If you've made your determination,
I'll
respect your decision.
Thank you, dad.
And, yeah,
don't be angry with your mother anymore.
Her bark is worse than her bite.
You know that.
And
I think she may be going through menopause.
Okay.
I'm not mad at her anymore.
Honey.
You may do your homework now.
Hello, senior.
Could you please do me a favor
to give me some exercises and materials
of science for junior students?
This is the composition topic of this year's college entrance examination.
Finish it
in two classes.
These are exercises of science for junior students.
It's not that difficult.
Yeah.
I can handle all these now.
If I choose science
and work very hard,
maybe I can get better grades than you.
Miss...
What are you doing?
I've finished the composition.
Come to my office
before the noon self-study course.
Your composition is pretty good.
Your writing skills are not bad.
You'll choose the science class?
Mr. Liu
What's the matter with these girls of your class?
Kong Shadi said she wanted to choose the science class yesterday.
And so does her.
Have you handed in your application form for the science-arts division?
Not yet.
Think it twice.
May I come in?
Yes, please.
Mr. Liu
I want to participate in the math competition, too.
The Placement Test is about to come.
Can you handle all these?
Chinese is a very important lesson.
He Xingwen
Attending the competition is not the only way to go to a good college.
Your academic performance of all courses
is pretty good.
You can go to a good college by attending the college entrance examination.
Zhou Siyue can participate in the competition.
My academic performance is better than his.
Why can't I participate in the competition?
Very well.
Then you may
finish this paper first
and give it to me tomorrow.
Ding Xian, are you listening to me?
Yes, I am.
I'll think about it.
Well,
don't
do anything irrelevant to Chinese in my class.
Did our Chinese teacher criticize you?
Not really.
Zhou Siyue
Do you think that girls are more suitable to learn arts courses?
I don't see any connections between them.
Neither do I.
But my parents and our Chinese teacher all said
that girls should learn arts
and they don't want me to learn science.
Then do you think
you are good at arts or science?
On choosing arts or science,
you don't need to care about others' thoughts.
You just
make your own decision on the basis of
your interest.
I'll support you no matter what decision you'll make.
Really?
Will you support me
if I choose arts?
Of course.
Forget it.
I'll take a nap first.
Deng Wanwan, what's wrong with you?
He Xingwen, are you the only one who has homework?
I don't have homework?
Don't you feel embarrassed
to make me do the cleaning
outside alone?
No one force you to do so.
And it's my own business to do it or not.
I'm busy preparing for the math competition
and have no spare time.
Don't be mad.
He Xingwen
How could you say that?
Zhou Siyue also participates in the competition.
And he never takes it as an excuse.
No wonder Mr. Liu likes him,
not you.
Everyone knows that you like Zhou Siyue.
What are you saying?
It's ridiculous.
Mr. Liu treats him so well just like his own son.
Maybe he will be recommended for admission to college.
He's the future student of top university.
I can't afford to offend him.
He Xingwen
I used to think that you're able to go to top university, too.
But now,
I think you can just go to an
ordinary college at most.
You can just mind your own business.
Why do you judge others like that?
If my friend can be recommended for admission to a prestigious university,
I'll be happy for him.
Yeah.
This is just sour grapes.
It's dangerous to have thoughts like this.
Not bad.
Our good girl knows how to lash out at somebody.
Thanks to you.
Silly girl.
Zhou Siyue
Actually, I'm not silly.
I know.
12 to 12.
You did scare me when
you lashed out at He Xingwen.
You are so brave!
I didn't think much of it at the time.
It's just that He Xingwen was way out of the line.
You begin to defend Zhou Siyue, now.
13 to 12.
Do you remember last time Mr. Liu said I violated the rules?
He was the first one that
defended me since I came to this city.
So now,
I'll defend him, too.
Shadi
Come with me to have my hair cut after the exam, okay?
What?
I want to have my bangs cut.
I want to look pretty.
I'm so happy to hear it.
You know what?
I know a good hairdresser.
It's hard to get an appointment with her.
I'll take you to see her after the exam.
Ding Xian
Xianxain, are you okay?
Ding Xian, I didn't mean it.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Let me take a look.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
May I take you to the school infirmary?
You go to class first, and I'll take her to the infirmary.
All right, let's go to the class.
Go to the class.
I've examined your eyes.
I suggest you
go to the hospital for an X-ray
to check if the retina is injured.
All right.
Let's go to the hospital.
I think it won't be that worse.
We have classes later.
Fine, then you just stay here and go blind.
Okay, let's go to the hospital.
Then do we need to ask for a leave first?
Finished?
You can get some sleep.
We need to wait half an hour to get the results.
Your eye is injured.
Why are you talking so softly?
Zhou Siyue
You don't need to take notes for me.
I'm afraid that
it may waste your time preparing for the math competition.
After the exam,
I'll ask my mom to take me
to change a pair of glasses.
You can focus on your own stuff.
Okay.
Zhou Siyue
Thank you.
There's no need to thank me for this.
I don't mean this.
It's just that
when everyone was against
my choice,
only you told me to
choose what I like.
So,
I appreciate it.
As long as you have made your determination, everything will be fine.
Ding Xian, hurry up.
I'm going to be late.
I've got to go, now.
Hang on a minute.
When will you hand in the application form of science-arts division?
Just these days.
Then remember to hand in it on time.
Okay, I got it, mom.
I have to go now.
Okay, be careful on the road.
Zhou Siyue, did you lose your mind?
May I come in?
Ding Xian, what's the matter?
Mr. Liu, may I come back later?
It's okay. Come in.
Mr. Liu, this is my application form of science-arts division.
You can put it here.
Anything else?
No.
Then you can leave.
Okay.
You chose the science class.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I want to show everyone that
I can work very well
on science courses, too.
Why did Mr. Liu scold you just now?
Did you do something wrong?
I haven't been doing well in the competition papers lately.
So he's mad at me.
He's too strict with you.
You already have so much to do.
How could he keep putting on you
so much pressure?
Don't worry.
I can handle it.
Zhou Siyue
No matter what you do,
I'll support you, too.
I know.
By the way,
my dad bought me a new phone.
Thank you for
lending me this.
Spend more time on your study and less on the phone.
You, too.
Two girls were peeking at you in the examination room just now.
Did you notice that?
Really?
It seems that you did very well in the exam.
You can even notice what others are doing.
Yeah, not bad.
I did well in Chinese, English and comprehensive liberal arts tests.
And the math test was okay.
As for the comprehensive science test, I finished it anyway.
You are still talking about the exam?
Don't you forget
what we've planned to do after the exam?
Of course not.
I'll see you in the billiards room after dinner. Let's go.
Come here.
You don't forget what you've promised me, do you?
Of course not.
I'll see you at your house after dinner.
Okay.
Shadi
How do I look?
Very good.
Just wear this.
Ding Xian
-I have prepared some fruit.  -Mom...
I'm changing clothes.
Don't come in, please.
Even mom cannot come in?
Okay, fine.
I'll pick up your brother.
The place is all yours.
Okay.
After my mom going out,
let's go to the hairdresser instantly,
or we'll be late.
Don't worry. We won't get late.
You are the hairdresser,
aren't you?
You...
You're kidding!
Don't worry.
Believe me. I'm an expert in cutting bangs.
No hairdresser can do better than me, okay?
Slanting bangs. Straight bangs.
European and American style, Korean style and Japanese style.
I can cut all styles of bangs
as long as you name it.
Select one.
Maybe we should just forget it.
No.
Select one.
This one.
It's not good enough.
It's not stylish at all.
How about this one?
This is a stylish haircut.
Stay still.
Are you sure it is used this way?
Trust me.
Tonight,
it'll definitely amaze you.
Shadi
I'm a little scared.
Don't be.
You have a small face,
so all I need to do is a little
touch up.
According to my experience,
bangs in this length are
the most suitable for you.
Well,
be careful.
Okay, we've finished.
How does it look?
It seems that
I have made a mistake.
What do you mean?
Shadi
It is just
too rustic.
Not that bad.
In fact, it is okay when getting used to it.
It's just that
when you first see it,
you'll feel it's a little weird.
Then
can you come up with some methods
to make me get used to it at the first sight?
Let's sever our friendship.
Slow down, I can't see the way.
You have covered your face with this hat
and you certainly will walk this slowly.
It is your masterpiece that should be to blame.
Bye!
I'm so thirsty.
I'm going to buy something to drink.
Be quick.
Okay.
Give me a bottle of drink, Mr.
Isn't the clerk there?
No.
I'm coming.
Mr.
Girl, mind your own business.
What do you want?
Come here. Come.
What happened?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm back. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's go.
We'll take a billiards table, Mr.
Okay, wait a minute please.
Do you smell something?
What?
Zhou Siyue used hair gel.
Wait.
He began to use hair gel.
What does this mean?
Let's get started.
I'm going to put down the drinks.
What are you laughing about?
Nothing.
Why do you wear a hat in the room?
Don't look at me.
What?
It's kinda cute.
Do you mean it?
No need to wear that.
It does no good to your hair.
If two men ride on a horse, one must ride behind.
We two celebrities of Shen Hai High School must duke it out today.
I'll show you.
What kind of celebrity are you?
Zhou Siyue is a celebrity indeed.
Stop bragging.
Let me have a try.
Here. Here.
I'll do this.
It seems not that difficult.
You can have a try.
I can't play it.
I'll show you.
You'd better just give it up.
There is a hemispherical method in math.
Do you know it?
It's a waste of time to teach you.
The correct billiards hit point
should be on the extension line
connecting the center of the bag and the center of the ball.
As long as you can aim at the point,
it will get into the bag in most cases.
Have a try.
Your hands cannot be like this.
Like this.
What are you laughing about?
Your bangs
split.
Zhou Siyue
I got it.
I'll have a try myself.
You lucky dog. Novices are always so lucky.
Awesome.
Ding Xian
You didn't practice this
behind our backs, did you?
No, I just learned it.
Siyue, do you notice that
this girl is barely satisfying in study
while she's so good at these stuff
just like in the game hall last time.
It's hard to explain.
She is a gifted player.
And she has a good teacher.
I'll have a try.
You're too protective of her.
How do you do? Are you Ding Xian's mother?
Yeah, I am.
I'm Ding Xian's head teacher, Liu Jiang.
How do you do?
Mr. Liu, how are you?
Please come in.
Okay.
Sorry to bother you. Do I need to change shoes?
No. No. No.
Sit down please.
I'll get you some water.
Don't bother. I won't stay long.
That's okay. Sit down, please.
I know that
you two are partnering to bully me today.
You can only blame yourself for your poor skills.
You skills are good? You don't even touch the cue.
That's because
you are not a good teacher to teach me this.
Give me the wallet.
I'll foot the bill.
It's in my pocket.
Did Ding Xian do something wrong in school?
Or did she fail the exams?
No. No. No.
Don't worry, Mrs. Ding.
I come here to
complete a task of the school.
It is just a common home visit.
The holiday classes just finished.
And they'll be junior students soon.
Do you know the science-arts division?
Yeah. I asked her to choose arts.
Arts?
Yes.
But Ding Xian chose science.
It can't be.
I asked her to choose arts.
Well.
I'll show you here.
This is the application form filled by Ding Xian
and she chose science here.
She didn't tell me this.
I can change it for her. Give me a pen.
Mrs. Ding, stay calm.
I think
we should listen to
Ding Xian's opinion about this.
She'll be mad at us
if we change her choice like this.
-Yes.  -Do you think so?
Yeah.
And I
have analyzed the situation
about her choice.
You can listen to me and see whether my analysis is reasonable.
-Okay.  -I think
the students in science classes
are all well-performed students.
Most of them are
top students.
Compared with these students,
Ding Xin is
obviously mediocre.
No. Mr. Liu
Ding Xian was
a top student
in her previous school.
I never worried about her studies since she was a child.
And the grades of the latest exam are not released, right?
And she is very resistant to pressure.
Since she came back,
she never complained that she had trouble in study.
As her teacher,
you should encourage her more.
How could you say that?
Don't get me wrong. Mrs. Ding, calm down.
You misunderstood me.
Sorry, Mr. Liu.
I've got stuff to do.
So, shall we ......
stop here......
Okay, then I'll go now.
Okay, okay. Thank you for coming.
Mrs. Ding
You really misunderstood me.
Goodbye, Mr. Liu.
I ......
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
I ... I wanted to tell you ......
See you, Mr. Liu.
See you.
Here is your change.
Okay, thank you.
You are welcome.
Let's go to KTV.
Okay, I can go.
Maybe some other time. My parents are about to go home.
It will be so boring if you don't.
Come with us, okay?
Shadi, I'll come with you next time.
You may go now.
I'll walk her home.
Okay. Go.
Let's go.
Okay.
It's cold outside. Put your clothes on.
Your bangs are pretty.
That's a lie.
I know what my bangs look like.
By the way,
when will you attend the competition？
This October.
So soon after the school starts,
I'll go to get confined training.
For this period of time,
you have to be on your own.
Be careful.
Don't worry. I can make it.
So confident.
Since I've made my decision to learn science,
I'll work very hard in the future.
Even if without your help,
I can get good grades myself.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Let's see your monthly quizzes grades.
What are you looking at?
I'm home!
Xianxian, you are back.
Mom
You cut your hair?
It looks awful.
Don't talk nonsense.
It's time to go to bed.
No.
Who allows you to cut your hair?
Mom
I don't even have the right to cut my own hair?
Yeah.
She has grown up
and has her own idea.
We should respect her choice.
I work hard to take care
of your daily life.
What's your return to me?
One didn't listen to my opinion and chose science,
and the other knew clearly her choice
but didn't tell me a word.
You take my words as garbage, don't you?
I deserve to suffer all these
and should keep my mouth shut, right?
I see.
You've grown up
and want to make your own decision.
You won't listen to me anymore.
But will you still listen to me?
I don't care.
No matter what method you'll take,
she has to be transferred to the arts class.