I couldn't finish speaking
in front of the division commander just now.
From Zhangmu
to the division headquarters,
you are my best comrade.
We used to climb walls,
hide from boars,
and shun the provost together.
But what about the future?
I can only see you off the stage
during your performance.
Gao Liang,
the art troupe will always follow
the soldiers wherever they go.
Whether at the sentry post at remote places,
or on the top plateau,
and even on the battlefield,
I will visit you
and sing for you.
The distance between soldiers and our actors
is always the closest.
That's not true.
You will be everyone's Jiang Nanzheng,
not my own.
We will be far away then.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland, be strict with requirements, and make solid preparations.]
Hey, Gao Liang.
I want to
ask you for help.
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
Gao, well done!
This jeep
is awesome.
I borrowed it for a month.
Hurry up!
Don't forget to take notes.
Thank you.
Do you make up your mind?
Have you asked the sergeant for leave?
The sergeant doesn't have time for Gu.
All the sergeant is thinking about
is wearing the cadre uniform
and he wishes to give everyone time off.
You're finally here.
Let's have dinner before you leave.
No way.
Gao was specially transferred
to perform the task assigned by the platoon leader.
So you know it.
Let's go.
Stop being cool!
I borrowed it from the division commander.
Why are you more anxious than Gu?
Well,
you don't want Jiang to leave, do you?
Yes.
But I'm not like him.
He keeps everything to himself
and will regret it when she leaves.
No. I heard
Gu and Jiang
broke up.
Why are they now...
Niu,
it's not what you think.
Yes,
Why is your thought so complicated now?
Mule Gu is a playboy.
You just need to
care about me, your fellow.
OK?
I do care about you.
Think about it.
Gu and Jiang
broke up.
Here's your opportunity
to go for her.
Am I right?
Nonsense! Niu.
I don't want it.
I am telling you
I'm going to
drive Mule Gu to meet Jiang today.
Why will I do that?
You think I'm dignified.
No!
It's contempt for my rival in love.
- Don't talk nonsense.
- Got it?
How are your driving skills?
I tell you,
I'm here for business today.
It's not easy for you two
to calm down.
Just let it go.
When you see her later,
don't make a foolish thing.
Got it?
Don't ask why.
The only reason is
that she doesn't love you anymore.
OK?
You talked a lot.
Get in.
[Fear Neither Hardship nor Death]
Gao Liang.
Gu Yiye.
Sergeant.
It's great that you got a jeep.
So I don't need to send him by bike.
Hongliu's sister is ill.
She's pretty sick.
The notice of critical condition has been issued.
He's in a hurry to the railway station.
Give him a ride.
Let's go.
Bye, sergeant.
Get in.
Hongliu, take it easy.
One, two, three, four.
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
Be careful.
Bye.
Nanzheng,
when are you going to report?
Tomorrow afternoon.
OK.
I'll congratulate you later.
I think
it's the art troupe's honor
to choose you.
It's their loss
not to choose you.
By the way,
all the guys
in the art troupe of the military district
are very handsome.
But
they are all smooth-tongued.
Stay away from them.
You care so much.
- Hello.
- One ice sucker, please.
- OK.
How much?
Five cents.
OK.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Under the sun,
there was a little boy
who finally got an ice sucker
he longed for.
But when he was just about to
take his first bite,
the ice sucker fell to the ground.
That's how I feel now.
What a pity!
You still laugh at me, huh?
You're the ice sucker.
You are.
Enough. Let's get to the point.
Nanzheng,
I came here
with an important task.
I need your help.
Follow me.
So beautiful.
Let me try on this one.
OK.
Here you are.
Hello.
Hurry up.
Our store is going to close.
I've decided.
I'll buy this one.
- OK.
- How much is it?
Sixteen yuan.
Sixteen?
Do you bring enough money?
Sure.
The sergeant gave me twenty.
The dress is so expensive.
He is a thrifty person.
Why will he buy such an expensive dress?
Nanzheng,
you
go outside and wait for me.
I'll see if I can bargain with her
to save some money for the sergeant.
If you're here,
she won't lower the price.
OK.
Fine. I'll be done soon.
Hello.
I have thirty yuan.
How about thirty yuan for two dresses?
Well,
I can't decide.
Think about it.
Just two yuan short.
And I'll buy two dresses.
Here is the money.
Let me wrap them for you.
OK.
Nanzheng,
I'm done.
How much is it cheaper?
Two yuan.
Look at your smile,
I thought you cut six yuan.
Let's go.
Comrade,
wait a moment.
I'm really sorry.
Our manager doesn't accept your price.
Please make up the difference,
or give the dresses back to me.
Comrade,
I gave you all my money.
Can't it cover the expense?
Why don't you
ask her for help?
No way!
How could I ask her for help?
How much does he owe you?
Thirty-two yuan for two dresses.
Two yuan short.
Two yuan. Here you are.
OK, thank you.
You're welcome.
Nanzheng, I'll repay you when I get back.
May I ask
whom the other dress is for?
It's for you.
When you tried it on just now,
it looks good on you.
So I want to buy one for you.
Then you don't need to repay me.
I bought it myself.
I'll give you the rest of the money
when I go back.
No.
I give it to you.
Comrade Gu Yiye,
we're now ordinary comrades.
The dress is too expensive.
I can't take it
unless you let me pay for it.
When I tried on it just now,
I thought it's very beautiful.
Thank you.
I'll give you the money
when I go back.
[Five Yuan]
What's up?
Lend me some money.
Let me see.
Here you are. That's all I have.
Aren't you going to live?
No.
Here, this is my money.
Thank you.
You're rich. So rich.
One yuan fifty cents.
Write it down.
- Write it down first. Hurry up.
- Don't worry.
Make sure I can get my money back.
Don't worry.
Don't forget. I mean it.
Gu.
Why are you here?
Nothing.
I just stop by.
Bye.
[Xinxing Clothing Department]
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
Get off the bike.
Everyone must get off at the gate.
Platoon Leader Zhang,
is that your wife?
Just call her Xiu.
Nice to meet you, Xiu.
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
Really?
You saw Zhang's wife.
Look at all of you,
behave good.
Today is Gu Yiye's first day as a sergeant.
You behave like this.
Do you still want to be in the Ninth Squad?
Yes, we do.
This is my first squad meeting
as your sergeant.
We all know each other very well
and have lived together for nearly a year,
so I don't put on airs.
Let's go straight to the point.
The former sergeant
treats everyone like brothers.
All of us in the Ninth Squad
are his soldiers.
The Ninth Squad is like home to him.
His fiancée came.
Tell me, won't he bring her to us?
Am I right?
So I think
he will bring his beautiful fiancée
here to show off.
It’s said that when a solider is promoted,
he will assume great airs.
The former sergeant has just been promoted
to the platoon leader.
Should we test him?
He got promoted and shouldn't forget about us.
Why would he forget us?
Look at you,
you only deserve to throw grenades.
For family visit,
soldiers can have about 10-day leave.
We have been training during the day,
he must be very busy.
In the evening,
the company will give him leave.
Then let's keep him with us,
so that he won't be with his fiancée.
Let's see
who is more important to him,
his fiancée or us.
Jiang is smart.
That's what I mean.
But let's make a deal.
We only test him for two days.
His fiancée came all the way to the army.
We can't be too cold-blood, right?
What if he doesn't bring his fiancée?
Let me tell you.
If he doesn't bring his fiancée,
as sergeant, I...
I...
He's coming.
Why did he come back alone?
Sergeant. No, platoon leader.
Are you alone?
Where is your fiancée?
All rise!
Applaud!
We warmly welcome you!
Here is water.
You must have a long journey.
Drink some water.
Don't be ashamed of our poor condition.
Do you have any other girls there?
Are you hungry?
Are you exhausted?
Comrade Xiu,
here is the situation.
Platoon Leader Zhang Fei
was our sergeant.
So he has to take care of
all the things in the Ninth Squad.
If he doesn't do that,
we will decline in performance.
So he has to
accompany our soldiers in the Ninth Squad
and ask me to
take you back to the guest house.
Is Zhang Fei really an officer?
Of course. It's just announced.
Then why he still dressed
as an ordinary soldier.
He hasn't received his cadre uniform yet.
But he'll get it soon.
Why do you keep coughing?
Do you catch a cold?
[Maintenance Platoon]
[Prepare for War]
Jiang Nanzheng.
Why are you here?
I came to make a report to you.
Did your platoon leader's fiancée receive the dress?
Does she like it?
Does she like it…
She likes it very much.
She was so happy.
It's all of you who must be happy.
Finally, a woman visited your squad.
Come on,
she is also happy.
I heard she was crying with joy.
I'm glad she likes it.
Jiang Nanzheng.
What's up?
I have
a small request.
May I speak freely?
No.
Why did you refuse me?
You should say "OK".
OK, you can say it.
[Maintenance Platoon]
Well, you see.
It's Gu Yiye who accompanied you to buy the dress.
You put it on when you bought the dress.
He saw you in the dress, right?
I waited for you two in the jeep,
so I saw nothing.
When I went back, the more I think about it,
the more uncomfortable I am.
Then I thought
after you go to the art troupe,
you'll have lots of beautiful clothes.
Then you wear the beautiful clothes
to perform for many comrades.
I want to see it, too.
Show me, OK?
Only for me.
Gao Liang.
I've always regarded you
as my comrade.
Can you...
I see.
What's up?
Wait for me.
I'll get changed.
Jiang Nanzheng.
[Activity Room]
I changed my mind.
The dress was bought by Gu Yiye for you.
Let me give you something, too.
No need.
Don't waste money.
Well,
I'm an orphan, you know.
I have no burden.
I lent all my money
to those poverty-stricken comrades.
Let me buy you a dress.
You can wear it
when you go to the art troupe.
It's not a gift from Gu Yiye.
Jiang Nanzheng.
I beg you.
I can't salute you for this.
But it's really my biggest plea.
Jiang Nanzheng.
Before you leave,
let me run with you once.
Please grant my request.
I don't know why I always think of
my elder brother these two days.
I have a hunch that
the army
is going to make a big move.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland]
Gao Liang.
Come out.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland]
Gao Liang.
If you don't come out, I'll leave.
What's he doing?
Jiang Nanzheng.
I'm here.
What are you doing up there?
Come down. It's too dangerous up there.
Look,
the new clothes I bought for you.
Do you like it?
♫ We are comrades, as close as brothers ♫
♫ The revolution has called us together ♫
♫ You are from the frontier ♫
♫ And he is from the mainland ♫
♫ The smoke of war is telling ♫
You don't listen to me.
You waste money.
♫ My youth is burning ♫
You're so stubborn.
My comrade Jiang Nanzheng,
♫ Say goodbye to you at that moment ♫
from tomorrow on,
you will become a singer
of many people.
♫ In and out of my dreams, you were there ♫
I'm Gao Liang,
your comrade,
and a soldier
from the countryside.
♫ The mountains and rivers are telling ♫
I will always look at you
and hope you will be young,
beautiful,
♫ Green youth inspires me ♫
full of revolutionary passion
and be my comrade
forever
and ever.
♫ Side by side with you at that day ♫
♫ It's hard to part. You keep me warm ♫
Jiang Nanzheng.
I'm coming.
♫ Yearning for you, watching over you ♫
♫ Yearning turns into winds. Read my mind, read your mind. ♫
♫ Yearning for me, looking at me. ♫
♫ Time turns into flowers, like you, like me. ♫
Platoon Leader Zhang,
what are you doing here so late?
Li, my fiancée is here.
Really?
[All heart for the Four Modernizations]
My marriage application was approved.
Just wait for my wedding invitation.
OK, I'll wait for your news.
Have you...
Have you eaten yet?
What did you eat? Is it delicious?
Rice noodles with shredded pork.
Gu is very considerate.
Is it from Gu Yiye?
Rice noodles with shredded pork. Great!
I've been in the army for several years.
But I only ate for several times.
It should be specially cooked by the kitchen.
Gu Yiye
is really observant.
I've been worried that you can't eat well.
I'm afraid of you...
Are you going to keep standing?
Zhang Fei.
Yes.
So beautiful.
Like a bride.
You look more beautiful than the dress.
Why don't I
wear it tonight?
Not tonight.
It's too late.
Put it on tomorrow,
so everyone can see it.
Let everyone see
how beautiful
my fiancée is.
My comrades were all eager to see you
when they knew you were here.
They were scrambling to deliver food to you.
Do you mean Gu and others?
Yes, Gu Yiye.
You know,
Gu Yiye is my soldier.
He is the best in the platoon,
the company, the battalion,
and even the regiment.
Really?
Of course.
What are you laughing at?
He's really great.
As the child of officers,
he's smart and loves reading.
He does a good job in training.
Didn't you tell me
you were the best-looking man
in your army?
That's right.
I am.
You see, the army stresses
orderly procession,
neat tactical actions
and excellent
war drills.
Besides,
I'm darker than them.
You go to sleep.
I'll ask the company commander for leave.
I'd like to
accompany you to the county town tomorrow.
Then we can hang out
and stay a little longer.
Where are you going?
I'll go to the platoon.
My bed is there.
I have to sleep there.
The door is locked.
It must be done by those boys.
I can't get out.
Fei boy,
I don't mind your poor family.
I want to marry you
because you're a soldier.
You don't live a good life
like others,
but you take responsibility for others.
A man like you is a real man.
That's why I want to marry you.
I can see that
the army is busy
and you have made progress.
I'm not here to hold you back.
I'll leave tomorrow.
Xiu,
isn't it appropriate to go home tomorrow?
Besides,
our letter of introduction...
Take it easy.
I have two requests.
Tell me.
First,
take me to your chief tomorrow.
Why?
I want to thank them
for cultivating you.
If they agree,
I'd like to invite them to
be our marriage witnesses.
Second,
stay here tonight.
Don't go.
Take me to the station tomorrow morning.
I'll wait for you at home.
If you don't go back and marry me,
I'll keep waiting.
Xiu.
Hail, Platoon Leader.
Platoon Leader.
Comrades, what are you doing?
Platoon Leader, something happened to the Ninth Squad.
It's true.
If you're not busy,
please go and take a look.
Xiu,
I have something to deal with.
Good night.
My comrades, it's three o'clock.
Go to bed and stop horsing around.
[Create a new situation in the revolution and modernization of the army]
There'll be a big move.
Stand up.
Our division is ordered to
complete the assembly
within 12 hours,
carry all weapons and equipment,
prepare two cardinal numbers of ammunition,
march to Zhangmu Railway Station,
and go to the border.
In a word,
prepare for war.
That is all.
Everybody, go back immediately
and take action according to the order.
Yes.
Our division has already turned to
Level II readiness,
with all soldiers assembled,
equipment replenished
and relevant operation plans improved.
I asked the security section to investigate.
Those who violated confidentiality rules
by spreading gossip
were criticized and educated.
My opinion is to
freeze all transfers immediately.
No one is allowed to leave.
You can rest assured that at this moment...
Section chief.
I'll stand firm.
Report.
- Your lunch.
- OK.
Gao Liang.
Yes.
Go to the Communication Company
to see if Jiang Nanzheng leaves.
Chief, she has left.
Drive to the railway station now
and bring her back.
Zheng,
what do you mean?
I just said that we'll freeze all transfers.
This rule applies to both other soldiers
and my daughter.
Our purpose is to
stop those who want to be deserters.
Jiang Nanzheng doesn't have that problem.
And her transfer order
was issued 20 days ago.
Nothing happened at that time.
No matter when the order was given,
my daughter can
only move forward at this time,
but not step back.
Go.
Yes.
Attention!
Dress right!
Eyes front!
At ease!
Listen.
Tonight,
do your internal affairs.
Stop knocking on my door.
- Disband.
- Yes.
Platoon leader, have you met yet?
Get a clear picture first, right?
Yes.
Inform the cooking corps
to serve the meal in advance.
After lunch,
assemble in 20 minutes
and prepare to march.
Yes.
Clerk, what happened?
The lunch will be served early.
Pack up in twenty minutes
and go to the frontline.
I didn't say anything.
Get off! Get off!
Go back with me.
Gao Liang, stop it.
The train is leaving.
I'm in a hurry to report to the art troupe.
I'm not kidding.
The division commander asked me
to take you back.
What's going on?
Report.
Come in.
Staff Officer Sheng.
Yes.
The division headquarters is going to set off in ten minutes.
Tell Leng Rui to arrange a command van for me.
I'll set out with Regiment 700.
Yes.
Chen Dashan.
This time,
your Regiment 700
responded faster than
the last maneuver
and didn't lag behind.
I called you here to remind you
that your problem has just been corrected.
You should maintain vigilance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
On the battlefield,
2,500 officers and soldiers of Regiment 720
are both soldiers
and lives.
They need to complete
the mission of defending national territory.
Their families
are looking forward to their safe return.
Do you understand the great significance?
Yes.
Go.
[Create a new situation in the revolution and modernization of the army]
Chief,
I have something to report.
You want to go to the subordinate unit, right?
Yes.
Get in!
Division Commander, I can't be a coward.
I ordered you to get in!
Yes.
Come on.
The Third Platoon, hurry up.
Stop hanging about.
Come on. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Everyone, hurry up.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come on. Hurry up.
Go inside. Come on.
The Third Platoon, hurry up.
Come on. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Get on.
Zhang Fei.
Why hasn't Xiu come back?
Hurry up.
Come on. Hurry up.
She wanted to
thank you and the commissar.
She should go shopping for gifts.
Zhang Fei.
You made me speechless!
At this important moment,
why did you ask her to buy gifts?
You have one hour
to wait for her.
One hour later,
manage to get to the railway station
and meet with the Company.
No, Commander.
I can't be separate with
my soldiers.
Execute the order. Stop talking.
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
[August First]
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait for me.
Sergeant, I get on the truck.
Come on. Give me a hand.
Didn't I tell you to stay?
What are you doing here?
You all go to the frontline.
Why should I be left behind? I won't accept it.
I was approved to join you by the battalion.
You've been feeding pigs for months.
One year later,
you can get third-class merits.
What are you doing here?
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
How is it going?
It's done boarding.
Let's go.
OK.
We ruined
their chance of being together
by clowning around.
It's hard to
know
when we're supposed to be back.
Stop looking.
Didn't you join us last night?
Platoon Leader.