"A factory break-in,"
that's what you said.
We should never have got into this, Tom.
On the night of June 21st,
a general strike will be called
across the city.
How do we know this foolish man
will hand over the diamonds
when we're done?
We don't. But that's another business.
When this business is done,
it will all be over.
And afterwards,
you and Arthur can begin your new life.
So there are three cellars
underneath the house.
There's a tunnel here that runs
from the house, underneath the river,
to an underground strong room.
We need our tunnel to run from here
and hit the strong room, direct.
I need to speak
to you about the Priest.
I will shoot him myself, Tommy.
I swear to God,
if my son pulls the trigger,
I will bring this whole organisation
down around your ears.
Ripped By mstoll
Welcome to the opening
of the Grace Shelby Institute
for non-insured children of the poor.
I would very much like you to
join me in thanking the man
that made the founding of this
establishment actually possible.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr Thomas Shelby.
Speech!
Come on, speech!
Aw!
Say it, Tom. Say it to 'em!
Erm, I didn't come here today to
make a speech, but I will say this.
These children are now safe.
In our care, they will be safe.
Because we are from the same
cold streets as they are.
And in our care, they won't be
shipped away to the colonies,
or separated from kin,
or made to work for men
in their various ways.
They will grow up here, at home...
loved...
in Birmingham.
Because this is our city.
By order of the Peaky Blinders.
Hail!
Now let us sing Immortal, Invisible.
You hear that, Grace?
The absence of my invitation
for this event
was obviously an oversight
on your part, Mr Shelby.
Look, I have the keys.
I have allocated myself an office.
Just there,
two doors in from the street,
it's the one that already has the stove
and the crucifixion on the window.
Mr Shelby?
It is the one that has the crucifixion
on the window in orange and red,
that will be my office.
And I will take them to
Saint Aloysius for confession.
You do understand these keys are
part of our broader arrangement?
In the next 24 hours, you will do
exactly as you have been instructed.
You will not deviate, you'll not fail.
Come on, little fellas.
Ow!
The, uh...
The Lord Mayor would like you to
come and eat cake and drink some tea.
Tommy says, "Mingle and smile."
It must be the trains.
No Ruben?
Do you know any other guests
from London who have not turned up?
Some, I think. Yes.
Pol, I'm paid by the company now,
so I have to talk to other people.
So you have moved from horses to
automobiles in just four years?
When you ship to New York
you pay a higher dock duty.
You should consider coming with us
through Boston.
I just spoke to johnny Dogs.
He said the tunnel's hit heavy clay.
- It's slowing him down.
- How long?
Two days before they hit the wall.
Tell him to dig a sinkhole
to drain the clay.
He's asked if you could go down
and have a look yourself, Tom.
I told him, wild horses
wouldn't get you down.
- Hmm.
- Yes.
Mr Shelby, I'd just like to say that
I wish I had met your dear wife
before she was taken from us.
And I would like to allocate
an hour a day of each of my lady's time
to make winter clothes
for the little ones.
Speak to my secretary, Ms Stark,
in the grey hat. She knows my diary.
Fuck me, Tom.
I don't know how you do it.
Incoming.
- Mr Shelby?
- Yes?
Aw. Your little boy
looks so much like you.
He does, yes.
He's a little rascal, isn't he?
Mr Shelby, would it be too inconvenient
to steal you for a moment?
No, no. No inconvenience at all.
Tommy, I am sorry. He wants you.
- Aw, come here, Charlie.
- There's Daddy.
Oh, little boy.
So lovely to see a man
willing to hold his child in public.
From the members of
- the Moseley War Widow's Institute.
- Ooh, watch this!
Made by Mr Winslow himself
of Winslow Castings.
Look at that!
From a photograph of your
horse that ran at the derby.
Oh, that is very kind.
- Thank you very much.
- Grace's Secret.
Charlie.
Would you mind holding it for us
so that we can have a photograph
for the gazette?
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr Shelby.
- Not at all.
- Thank you.
Thank you for your time, ladies.
Thank you. Thank you for your time.
Thank you. Thank you.
Where's Charles, Ada?
I gave him to you.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
Boys.
- Have you seen Charlie?
- Eh?
- I haven't seen him.
- I don't know.
He is playing, ain't he?
Pol, where's Charles?
Lizzie, where is Charlie?
- I don't know.
- Where is he?
Back Door. Kitchen.
Get to Blake Street, where the cars are.
Tommy! Someone said they saw a nurse
take him through the back door.
- Fuck.
- What nurse?
I don't know. Go.
- Arthur.
- What?
Somebody said they saw a woman
and a kid getting into a car.
Ah, fuck!
Charlie!
John.
- Where is he?
- John.
- Arthur.
- Go find Moss.
- Arthur, where is he? Where is he?
- Junctions, block them all off.
- Tell me.
- Someone took him.
All right.
Hey, listen to me!
They put him in a car.
They put him in a car and drove south.
We've got roadblocks and spotters.
I'll set up shop
and put every man we have
- on the junctions from here to Maypole.
- Yeah. Yeah. Right. You do that.
- But you have got to go to the office.
- Yeah.
You've got to sit by the phone.
- Whoever took him is going to call.
- Right. Of course.
Polly!
Let's go, Pol.
Stay by that phone.
Me and John will cover the roads.
I need Michael
at the Maypole junction.
I need Moss to block
all the roads south.
Give me Moss. Gone where?
- Tommy...
- It's them.
- Who?
- It's fucking them.
Look, it might just be
some random woman.
- Because sometimes women go mad...
- No, it is them.
Did you break the phone?
He broke the phone.
It's all right,
we have got another phone.
- Tommy?
- Ada?
There's someone outside, a priest.
Stay here, Pol, stay here.
Don't do anything.
We have your son.
Get in the car.
First.
Is he safe?
Of course he's safe.
All children are dear to me.
You have all the cards.
Tell me what you want me to do
and I will certainly do it.
You ever drive one of these beasts?
I am asking you to conduct business.
Of course, I borrowed it.
Lent it by a Lord
for the duration of this business.
I will certainly do what you
need me to do with no complaint.
We were forced into
doing this awful thing.
We did warn you that your son would be
in danger if you deviated from the plan.
It was you who made a mistake.
- You understand?
- Yes.
What mistake did you make?
Do you even know?
Tell me what you want me to do.
- You made a deal with our enemies.
- I will do what needs to be done.
You went behind our backs to stop
the Soviets from blowing up the train.
But it's all right. It's all right.
We've rectified your mistake.
You ask me, "What do I need to do?"
Well, here is what you need to do,
you fucking mongrel, you...
Since the Bolsheviks will not
be blowing up the train,
you will blow up the train yourself.
It has always been about the explosion
from the beginning.
The bang. The outrage.
Understand?
Those are notes and fragments
for you to scatter in the wreckage,
implicating named officials
from the Soviet Embassy.
I will scatter them. It will be done.
Good.
Our friends at The Times and
the Daily Mail will do the rest.
And once the British government
cuts diplomatic relations
with the Soviet Union,
that will be our mission accomplished.
You would have been
part of a fine adventure.
To help with the outrage,
we need people to die in the explosion.
How many?
Let's say... six.
Rail workers, perhaps,
men from the factory.
And I want my son returned to me
within an hour of the explosion.
Oh, it's conditions now, is it?
We need to fix the
handover in advance.
I haven't finished
with you yet, Mr Shelby.
We also hear
that you are digging a tunnel.
Mining for precious stones
under Wilderness House.
I'm told they have a Fabergé
in the strong room.
The Lilies of the Valley Egg
made in 1898.
One of the Odd Fellows has a wife
who's obsessed with Fabergé.
He wants to give her the egg
for her birthday.
Then he will have it.
And the Economic League will take
all of the jewels that you steal,
to cover our considerable expenses.
The fight against Communism
is not cheap you know.
- So if you want to see your...
- I will give you all the jewels.
A bang first.
Then bring everything that you
have stolen to your office at dawn.
No. No, I'm, uh...
I'll not be able to get the
jewels to you by dawn.
The tunnel has hit clay.
If the St. Andrew's clock strikes
5:00 a.m. on the night of the robbery
and we don't have everything
that we asked for,
the bell will be tolling for your boy.
Now get out of my fucking car.
- Where's Linda?
- With Esme.
Esme's water broke.
I was just with her. Running around,
fucking broke her water.
- Where is Finn?
- Out with the young ones,
looking for the Riley.
We couldn't reach him.
I need to know who spoke.
Our enemies know everything. Everything.
I need to know who spoke about business
outside of the family.
I need to know who spoke
and who they spoke to, now.
- Tommy, listen, uh...
- Your wife, Arthur?
I am going to tell myself that
you are not thinking straight.
Your mind is not clear.
Or Esme getting cash
for cocaine, eh, John?
Fuck!
All of a sudden,
back in the family, Ada.
Eh? That is a surprise.
Out of the blue.
On whose orders?
Tommy, this is
not helping find him.
And you and your painter.
You said he knows you.
Things developed. You talked.
If anyone has talked about
the tunnel to anyone else,
I need to know,
and I need to know this second.
- What about your clay kickers?
- Hmm.
Drunk in a pub.
I'd trust those men with my life.
- More than you trust us?
- Yes.
As of an hour ago, yes.
Why is Michael not in
this fucking line-up, anyway?
- You leave Michael out of this.
- Oh, yes?
- No, he should be here.
- I fucking don't even know him.
And I have only fucking known him
for fucking three years.
No, he is not going
to be your whipping boy.
I don't even fucking know the boy.
I never told Michael
about the Lilies of the Valley.
The only people I told about
the Fabergé eggs are in this room.
Tommy, I want you to know
that I came back for love...
and common sense.
And Esme's got no need for extra cash.
And you bring my wife into this,
means we speak
when this business is done.
John, Arthur,
I need 50 sticks of BSA dynamite
and 300 yards of cable
and six detonators by midday tomorrow.
And this is evidence.
I need you to scatter it.
We're blowing up a train,
and people are going to die.
Ruben and I talked about many things.
But not that. Not ever.
Tommy, I'm sorry I'm late.
We looked everywhere,
all the way up to Hay Mills.
We saw nothing.
Put four cans of petrol in the boot
of my car and bring it round.
Put cigarettes and a lamp in the box.
And fetch Michael. I need him.
Ada told me he gave you red wine.
I imagine you can't remember
half of what you talked about.
He was never interested in business.
He came to you at my wedding.
He pursued you. Sought you out.
Why would an educated man of his
standing do something like that?
- You mean, to a woman like me?
- Yes.
I've done the odds on all of you.
Even's it's him.
There is another possibility,
but even's it's him.
Bloody hell.
I asked that you come alone and unarmed.
Yeah, well, alone I ain't
never gonna do, am I?
And as for the cane,
don't worry about it.
That is just my sciatica.
It always plays up around the
winter and the summer solstice.
What have you got for me, Alfie?
What did you
bring me out here for?
This is on the way
to somewhere I need to be in a hurry.
- Mmm.
- What have you got for me?
Well, seeing as you were prepared
to pay such an exorbitant amount
for this information, I decided
to give you value for money.
So here are the names
of all the men in England
whom I would approach, right,
if I had a Fabergé egg for sale.
Here you go.
And then, here's all
the men on that list,
you know, who would buy
the old Fabergé egg,
even if they knew that
that item was stolen.
Here.
Then comes your curious
fucking gyppo question.
I won't ask but, erm...
Here is a list of the men
who would buy a Fabergé
because of their wife's obsession.
Ah, yes. Thank you, Mr Shelby.
It's lovely doing business with you.
You left a name off the list, Alfie.
- Did I?
- Yeah.
I've already spoken to my people
in the jewellery quarter.
Experienced dealers.
They tell me there are only
three men in Britain
whose wives are obsessed with Fabergé.
Makes them good customers.
You missed the richest one off the list.
Yeah, well, if you knew already
how come you dragged me all the way
out into the fucking oggin, mate?
Two reasons. Reason one.
By withholding a name
that you most certainly know,
you've proven to me that you have
done a deal with the Odd Fellows.
It was you who told them
about the tunnel.
You who told them about the
fucking deal with the Soviets.
Reason two.
The name of the man that you're
withholding must be my enemy
otherwise,
you wouldn't be protecting him.
He is now a man I can use.
Listen, sweetie, you can't take a man...
You gave information
in exchange for a share.
Tommy... Tommy there were
things in that treasury, right,
that God himself, He spoke to me,
and He said, "Alfie, you are
meant to have these things."
You crossed the line, Alfie.
- You fucking what?
- You crossed the line.
- "The line"?
- They are using my boy!
Did you fucking know?
Yeah, I knew, you know.
But damned as I am, it made
no fucking difference to me, mate.
Fucking hell, Tommy!
Oh! Crying out loud.
What the fuck is going on?
What is the matter with you, Tommy, eh?
Eh? You've gone fucking angry,
ain't you?
- Yeah, I got fucking angry...
- It's in your fucking head, man.
- Come on, man!
- This bastard deserves it!
He's nuts!
It's in your fucking head, son.
I know this bastard deserves it.
I fucking know.
But if you kill him now,
the truce with the London outfits
will be blown to
fucking pieces, all right?
- Michael. Michael.
- Don't worry about that truce, kid,
right, because it fell apart.
You got nothing to worry about when it
comes to the ol' scary London boys.
Which fucking side are you on, Alfie?
I do not give a fuck right now, kid.
All right?
I do not want him to spare me
because of some fucking peace pact.
I want him to acknowledge that
his anger is un-fucking justified!
I want him to acknowledge
that he who fights by the sword,
he fucking dies by it, Tommy.
So what, they took
your boy did they, eh?
They have got your boy?
What fucking "line" am I
supposed to have crossed?
How many fathers, right,
how many sons, yeah,
have you cut, killed, murdered
fucking butchered, innocent and guilty?
You are going straight to
fucking hell, ain't ya?
Just like me!
You fucking stand there,
you, judging me,
stand there and talk to me about
crossing some fucking line.
If you pull that trigger, right,
you pull that trigger
for a fucking honourable reason.
Like an honourable man,
not like some fucking civilian
that does not understand
the wicked way of our world, mate.
Look, Tommy,
the killing of Alfie Solomons
is not going to help.
This will be very bad for business.
Michael,
go and call Inspector Moss.
Tell him it's Palmer.
Well said, Alfie.
Well said.
I did not know about your boy, though.
I know.
I saw.
Hello?
Good Lord.
Polly...
Why didn't you come?
I was going to get on the train
last night but then I...
I realised I simply I wasn't
ready to enter your world.
Good God. I'm shaking.
Good.
But now, I am ready.
I have been searching all night for you.
Polly, whatever you have been told,
it is not true.
The painting was wrong.
She was too sure of herself...
and I'm not.
Not any more.
I can paint another.
Oh, Polly.
What the fuck am I doing?
I want a dull life.
I want you. I want you. I want you.
I want you to paint me in a dress
that I bought in a shop.
We have a life?
I think so.
Hello?
I demand to see my solicitor.
I have a right to have him here.
Gilbert Palmer.
I want to talk to you
about a missing kid.
We are Peaky Blinders.
Where is he?
Deep breath.
johnny! johnny!
What the fuck are you doing here, Tommy?
They've taken my boy, johnny.
Everything's fucking changed.
I have the hole dug before midnight
or he's gone.
Do you hear me?
Are you not going
after Charles yourself?
Tommy?
Well, I was at...
This morning, I was out
on the road with Tommy.
I killed a man.
Well, he needed cover.
I was all he had.
So what did he give you?
He said it was good for close range.
You're better with my Smith & Wesson.
No, no. This is mine now.
It feels part of my hand.
Where'd you hit him?
I hit him in the side of the head.
How was you when he went down?
Tommy said I did all right.
This is where we think Charles
is being held.
They're not expecting anybody,
so he should be alone.
There is two good men there.
You do what they say.
But I fire the bullet. All right?
Yes, you can be there.
But it's better if they do it.
See, these are experienced men, Michael.
When you're sure the kid is safe,
you call Finn.
All right.
Come on, boys.
Hello there.
There you go. How's that?
Like a spoon? A shiny spoon?
Do you want to hold the spoon there?
All out, boys! Wild cat strike!
This locomotive
couples in 15 minutes.
If we don't hear word by 10:00,
we blow it up.
There are men on board, Arthur.
Yeah. Six men on board, Charlie.
Driver, stoker
and four men
I hand-picked myself.
Me and John picked those men.
So it is me and John
who will pull the switch.
The rest of you men can go home.
Tommy. Tommy.
He has got the shakes,
help me with him.
Get him out. Get him out.
We are bringing him through.
We need to move. Now.
You wait here.
I'll do the killing.
That is a fucking order.
You move too fast, Thomas.
We need more timber.
Make it safe. I will go on.
Thomas, it is too fucking wet.
It's sludge.
Make it fucking safe,
and I'll go on!
Okay.
What do you think you are doing, boy?
Please don't.
Please don't shoot.
Please don't. Please.
You fucking rat!
What do you think you're doing?
You know who you're
fuckin' messing with?
We don't have much time.
I'll take your fuckin'
life from you.
Let's go!
You are a gypsy bastard.
Who wants to be in heaven, eh?
Who want to be in heaven when you
can be sending men to fucking hell.
Hey.
I will do it, Arthur. Eh?
I'll do it.
I will take him.
No, this bastard is mine.
Go call Finn.
I told Tommy I'd do it...
so I'll do it.
Arthur, wait!
Charlie is safe.
It's all right.
- Oh, God!
- Oh!
Let me speak to him.
Hello, Charlie?
Hello, Charlie.
Can you hear me?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you go to bed.
Good boy.
Where the hell have you been?
I've been out in Maypole.
There has been some trouble.
I can't stay.
You can't stay?
Tommy needs my help.
It's family business.
- No, no. Please.
- I am sorry.
Please.
- Where is he?
- He is upstairs.
Mr Shelby,
this is Monsieur Silk.
He is here on behalf
of the Parisian buyers.
He needs to verify the value.
It was a pleasure doing business
with you these past few months.
You would never steal
from your family, would you?
The collection was mostly
my mother's, anyway.
It is more mine than theirs,
and they would never have sold it.
They would have wasted it
on a lost cause.
You needed a tunnel.
I need your signature
to make this sale legal.
Confirmed.
The original Duke Alexander
Petrovich's collection.
To raise a legal bill of sale
and get this across the border,
I will need an authorisation
signed by yourself in the family name
in my presence.
As we agreed.
Half for the tunnel,
half for the signature.
Where will you go?
Vienna.
There is a man waiting for me.
Poor man.
You?
Birmingham.
I'm going to buy a racehorse
and have it trained.
Also, £5,000 for the sex.
And five for helping you
through the grief of losing your wife.
You didn't even come close.
The papers are in order.
Now I just need your signature
for the provenance.
Of course. I have a pen.
At home, these jewels saw way worse.
That is why they are all cursed...
as are we, Mr Shelby.
If you are ever in Vienna, look me up.
Yes, yes.
Before I begin,
I want to let you know
I made a mistake.
I made a mistake,
and I want to apologise
to all of you.
Arthur,
you warned me against getting
involved in Russian business,
and you were right.
Mmm.
I doubted your wife,
for that, I am sorry.
Linda, I have added 3,000 here,
in the hope you will forgive me.
Apology accepted.
Esme, I doubted you as well.
Now John has got innocent lives
on his conscience.
- Ordinary working men...
- Yeah, all right.
- Esme, we got it.
- No. She is right.
You and Arthur are going to
have to share that burden.
But I hope the house
that you can buy with this
can become a place of...
contemplation
and perhaps, redemption.
Charlie, for lost tools
and dangerous goods
and Curly's wise words.
Johnny, for board and lodgings.
Lizzie.
Michael,
for the killings.
Five for cutting and five for shooting.
- No, Tommy.
- What?
Tell me, eh?
This is who I am!
And this is all I can give you
for what you have given to me.
For your hearts and your souls.
Yesterday, I nearly lost my son.
You should fucking understand that.
For what, eh? For what?
For this? For this?
And I know that you all want
me to say that I will change,
that this fucking business will change.
But I've learnt something
these last few days.
Those bastards. Those bastards
are worse than us.
Politicians, fucking judges,
lords and ladies.
They are worse than us.
And they will never admit us
to their palaces
no matter how legitimate we become.
Because of who we are,
because of who we fucking are
because of where we are fucking from.
Is that right, Ada?
Our Ada knows.
She got smart about revolution.
And she knows you have to get
what you want your own way.
Lizzie, I want it known, that money
was for you
because some nights it was you
who stopped my heart from breaking,
no-one else.
And the rest of you,
you took the King's shilling.
You took the King's fucking shilling.
When you take the King's shilling,
the King expects you to kill.
Right, Arthur?
Yeah.
That is how it works. Right, John?
That's right.
That's right, Pol.
That is fucking right.
Tommy...
You've had a bad time.
We understand.
So at an alternative time,
when we have all recovered...
I would like
to put before the family
an alternative view
of the future
of the Shelby Company Limited.
A more hopeful view.
Which I, for one,
would quite like to hear.
As would I.
Come on, Arthur.
The train for the dock
leaves in one hour.
Then we'll get the boat to New York,
and it'll all be in the past.
I will be off then, Tom.
I will see you, eh?
I will see you, Brother.
Bye, Curly.
You can go,
but you won't get far, Arthur.
Uh, all right, Tom.
I spoke to Moss last night.
He told me that the
Chief Constable of Birmingham
has issued a warrant for your arrest.
Murder, sedition,
conspiracy to cause explosions.
John, they're coming for you as well.
Murder, conspiracy to cause explosions.
Michael...
- What the fuck?
- ...for the murder of Hughes.
Polly...
Wait a minute,
what the fuck are you...
...the murder of
Chief Inspector Chester Campbell.
Why didn't you
fucking tell us, Tom?
The people we betrayed last night,
they want to bring us down.
They control the police,
they control the judges,
the control the juries,
they control the jails.
But they do not control...
- Look what they did to us.
- ...the elected government.
- Why didn't you tell us before?
- You are my brother.
Listen to me.
So I've made a deal.
- They will hang us!
- In return
for giving evidence against them.
We will fucking hang.
It is all taken care of.
Lizzie, collect up the money
and bring it to the cellar.
You will all get your money
in due course.
When the police gets in, do not resist.
You go with them,
and you do not say anything.
Arthur,
I have made a deal with people even
more powerful than our enemies.
- Arthur!
- Trust me, Brother, eh?
Trust me.
- No, Linda...
- You did this deliberately!
You made this happen to keep us!
Come here. Come here.
Come on now, we
have to run. We have to run.
Fuck you!
Ripped By mstoll