♪I want to get closer♪
♪I walk lightly♪
♪Yet accidentally♪
♪Walk into your trap of love♪
♪Oh no, no, no♪
♪You cannot simply confess
your love when you are drunk♪
=Campus Ace=
=Episode 11=
(A day as an intern)
Although you haven't graduated yet,
since you come out to work,
you have to keep professionalism.
Respond promptly to work messages
and solve problems independently.
Don't keep asking me
when you will be able
to participate in the design.
I don't like an incompetent person
with high ambitions.
If you can't stand the pressure,
you can go back to your campus.
Don't waste each other's time.
Yes, miss.
I got it.
This is your workplace.
If you need anything,
you may ask directly
from the administration.
Also,
don't call me "miss".
Call me Amanda.
Yes, Amanda.
Thank you.
Amanda.
Are you briefing the interns?
I really envy you.
Unlike me who has to
work hard every day.
Ladies.
Later, let's have a meal together
to welcome you two.
You are unusually efficient.
People would think
that they're working for your studio.
Martin is asking for me.
I need to go.
See you.
Listen, both of you.
You'd better not
play tricks under my nose.
I hate incapable people
who only create troubles.
You're free, aren't you?
Here.
Here are two copies of design sketches.
I want you to complete the sample today.
If you can't make it,
you don't have to come tomorrow.
I will do my best.
Okay.
Can either of you
help me get the parcel?
I've completed the sample.
I'll go.
Go ahead.
(Who moved my sketch?)
(Oh, no.)
I got the last piece of fabric.
Qiao Nuanfei.
Give me back the fabric.
Tang Momo.
Are you a robber now?
You stole my sketch
and deliberately took
the fabric I was going to use.
How dare you say I'm a robber.
Qiao Nuanfei.
Aren't you afraid
I'll report to Mr. Martin
if you use such dirty tricks?
I'm going to use
the same fabric as yours.
First come first served.
Why do you blame me?
You came late
and accused me of stealing your sketch.
I think
you're used to throwing mud
at people, aren't you?
You!
Anyone there?
(Amanda, I'm trapped in the warehouse.
Can you come and open the door for me?)
Keep an eye on the runway.
Make sure the lights and music
are exactly as I said.
Nothing can go wrong.
All right.
Why are you here alone?
Where is Tang Momo?
I have no idea.
She probably is slacking off somewhere.
(Amanda, I'm trapped in the warehouse.
Can you come and open the door for me?)
Looks like she's locked
in the warehouse.
♪You love bumping into her♪
♪On every sunny day♪
♪Approach gently♪
♪My letter of love confession♪
♪I chat shyly with her♪
♪While avoiding her gaze♪
♪I predict our destiny♪
♪We are not lovers yet♪