Unforgettable Love
EP21
Mommy
What are you doing here?
Sit here.
Have a seat.
See what you want to eat.
What's this for?
I have told you
we will have dinner together every day.
What's up?
Eat while it's hot.
I like eating it this way.
Any problem?
If you don't like my way,
you can go back,
and leave me and Xiaobao alone.
You eat first,
I need to take a call.
Mr. Rong
Qiao Yan
I have a terrible news for you.
I need to inform you that
our contract
can't be signed.
Why?
I was just informed from headquarters that
three days ago，
Linshi Group and our headquarters
signed a long-term contract.
And in China this contract
is exclusive.
In other words,
in China our company
is only allowed to cooperate with Linshi.
OK, I see.
Thanks.
Well, sorry for that.
You are born with a silver spoon,
so you may not have much feeling
for the problems of other families.
But don't be self-righteous
to interfere in others' lives.
Do not come here for no reason and disgust me!
Our relationship
is pure superior and subordinate.
What's in your mind?
I'm stupid.
No,
I'm not stupid.
but you a douchebag.
Am I, Wen gu
a douchebag?
I am not a douchebag.
I'm not going to the party tonight,
and you guys have fun.
Besides,
Don't call me for
any party this month.
And don't introduce
new girls to me.
They all look the same.
I don't want to play Linkup?
I got a girl in my mind.
It's not about a playboy becoming a good man.
but a good boy showing determination.
No eating in the office area.
One hour later,
all business departments come for meeting.
Assistant Yang had a fever,
and asked for leave today.
What, what happened？
Is that true?
Today our Boss comes to the office
at ten o'clock a.m.
Did I hear it wrong?
he said all the departments what?
He will preside over the meeting,
and let us
inform all business departments.
Does he know the business scope
of our company?
Forget it, just forget it.
Inform them, inform!
Hurry up!
Get busy, get busy!
Xu, you came just in time
I checked the
financial report for the first half of the year.
Combined with market and industry trend,
our growth rate fell 12%
from that of last year.
The company now
is in the important third stage of development,
but the benefits are not satisfactory.
In this case decision makers
need to make changes.
I'll make an appointment with the board of directors.
You come up with me.
No problem.
This quarter is the key to development.
From now on,
I will fix a daily process.
Before ten o'clock a.m.,
Make sure I receive
the executive report from middle managers.
and the handling process of key affairs.
In the noon,
I will discuss plans
with branches and agents.
Time for lunch break
can be utilized to deal with minor problems.
In the afternoon, we will take stock
of financial data of the day
as well as key projects.
And we will have a meeting with
core executive departments
By the way,
Before knocking off work,
ask the Department of Administration
to report the company's system.
It needs optimizing.
One more thing,
sort out and bring me
a big channel data
for the last year.
Did Chairman Wen press you again?
I'm not a toddler,
who need to be pushed
to walk.
I don't do something,
but it doesn't mean I can not do it.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Wen
This is the strategic cooperation agreement of products.
Please have a look when you are free.
OK.
Get to work.
Seriously?
He Qiaoyan hasn't taken a stand?
Right.
Your father has
spread the message.
He shouldn't be so calm.
Heshi Group
is the whole world of He Qiaoyan.
He will compromise.
This time,
you asked your father
to make such a big movement,
in order to capture He.
In this case,
if he's still
that much into Qin Yiyue,
then he literally
look down his nose at
our family.
In the appreciation banquet tonight,
everyone in business connection
with my father
will be present.
I'll bring He Qiaoyan there,
and let him make a statement.
Good.
The German hospital
could be so supportive
to our project,
and offered to invite
all members of our research group
to their country,
which is much beyond my expectation.
We have reached an agreement that
you and
your two senior sister apprentice
can work there with me.
In due course,
when we are settled down,
I'll be busy working both at home and abroad,
and business in the German hospital
will be in charge of you three.
Sign the contract now,
and we will go to Germany soon.
Why is it so sudden?
It's said that Heshi Group
has Cooperation with the German hospital.
And Heshi gave us a strong recommendation.
Yiyue
before I was worried that
you may not able to work
after marriage.
Now it seems that
the He family treat you well.
You have to be there for a year,
which didn't trigger their opposition,
but won their supports.
I am so sorry.
I let all of you down.
I failed to introduce the bracelet
to European and American market as scheduled.
And now for various reasons,
the project was shelved,
leaving considerable products overstocked.
Later on,
the board will certainly
hold accountability.
But all of you here
have no need to be anxious.
Because the whole matter
and the subsequent consequences
will be shouldered
by myself.
I know exactly the significance
of the bracelet to you.
It represents the hard work of us.
I will never
give it up.
Even if the board of directors
depose me as
the Chief Executive Officer,
I will not give up or transfer
my shares.
Instead I will apply
to work in R&D Center
and forward the bracelet project.
It's the Clinic of Children's Psychology.
Miss Lin, you've grown up, right?
You may already know about
things happening between me and Qiao.
With all due respect,
you can never
win his heart
in this way.
I don't need his heart.
All I need is the person himself.
Specifically,
I just need
the position he represents,
CEO of Heshi Group,
the sole son of He family.
Linshi Group
has an appreciation banquet tonight.
As long as he shows up,
I can have an account with my father,
no matter if he will marry me.
It's none of my business.
But you're the only one who can make him
show up there.
Miss Lin, you've come to a wrong person.
I'm not qualified or capable.
You are, and only you are.
At nine o'clock p.m.,
on the second floor of this hotel.
I know it's hard for you to do that.
But only in this way
can he give up
thoughts of you.
Once he makes it,
he can make a wise choice.
What he will face
in the following days,
is all up to you.
Come on.
Take some medicine.
Ah, Get up, come on.
That's good.
Treating cold and having sauna,
I did both at once.
Can you tell me now
what's going on between you two?
He brought my mother and brother here
without informing me first.
Who is he to get involved in my family
and decide things for me?
It is his fault
to do this.
However,
It's not the first day you've known him.
You should know that he didn't mean to hurt you.
I know he meant no harm,
but he really hurt me.
What are you doing?
Let me have a touch.
Touch of your heartbeat.
Dong dong, dong,
dong dong dong dong dong...
I've diagnosed it.
In your rage
hides a trace of anxiety;
in anxiety hides a trace of uneasiness;
in uneasiness,
hides a little bit doubt;
In doubt hides a trace of...
What is it?
Love.
How's it possible?
You are into Wengu.
Impossible.
What do you want to do?
Make a phone call.
No.
I said it that
I'm not going to call him.
I took an oath yesterday.
No.
See, see, see.
Did I say who I will call?
Qin Yiyue, you take advantage of a patient!
I've known you for such a long time,
and I never saw you
in such a big mood
in front of outsiders.
Anger signals concern.
Disappointment arises from expectations.
It's uneasy to meet someone you like so much.
Have a try, or you would never know.
Understand me？
You're willing
to be bullied by Lin?
It's not bullying.
She came out on top,
and I should admit defeat.
Have you ever thought about
obedience.
Connected with Linshi,
you'll be a winged tiger.
Didn't you
brush your teeth today?
Fine, my mouth stinks.
Lin's move,
is disgusting.
I can never stand it.
But,
isn't Qin greatly touched?
What's in her mind,
I really don't know.
What are you doing?
Lie down.
Although you called me a douchebag,
I still answered your call.
How generous I am.
Ruowei is ill.
Yiyue
You, as Ruowe's boss,
whether or not
should come
to visit her?
You won't come?
OK, I see.
Pissed off?
Badly pissed off?
He will come.
Qin Yiyue, you are so annoying!
Does a boss have the duty
to take care of sick staff?
Of course.
Pseudo pure makeup, maiden makeup,
Red-lip makeup...
are all lame.
I'll show you
what patient makeup is.
Snot, snot, snot.
He's coming.
I drove him here.
Could you two please, leave us alone?
Or I can't play it well.
Let's go.
It seems that you are very ill.
I don't need your care.
What are you coming for?
I'm here to prove it to you that
I am a
magnanimous person.
No need to have psychological burden.
Have a good rest for recovery.
Although you call me a douchebag,
but
I'm not going to fire you.
Besides,
drinking hot ginger decoction
may cure a cold from wind.
I'll cook it for you.
You can make ginger decoction?
Slow down.
This is He.
Hello, Mr. He.
Just now Mr. Li's and Mr. Ou's assistant
called me,
saying tomorrow's meeting will be cancelled.
For what?
It may probably
for rumors about your
leaving the group.
I see.
Get in the car.
Are you really going to leave Heshi?
I just stepped down
as Chief Executive Officer.
In another position,
I'll still push forward the bracelet project.
That's nice,
for I can save more time
for you and Xiaobao.
You always said that
I was occupied with work
and ignored you.
Now I can make up lessons I missed.
Please, do me a favor.
I didn't expect that you can really cook this.
Of course I can.
You thought I was kidding you?
Watch out.
It's burning hot.
And, tell you a secret.
My mother was worried
that I can't find a girlfriend when I grew up,
so
she wrote down
all methods
to coax girls.
So your mother told you
to make a girl's heart chill first
and then make ginger decoction to warm it
so that you can capture her.
Is it?
No, What's wrong with you recently?
You're acting like a hedgehog.
Get out.
Yang Ruowei,
Cancel it.
What?
Release my hand.
Our bet, cancel it.
I don't want to bet anymore.
Why?
Because I found that
I'm kind of...
Alright!
No bet, alright.
Come here.
Assume that you lose.
You have to accept the defeat
and keep your word.
Get out.
Yang Ruo...
Yang Ruowei.
Room 888 on the second floor,
you'll know when you get there.
Qiao Yan
don't you want to know
why Dr. Qin
ask you to come here?
The banquet hasn't started yet.
Let's have a rest here.
I have arrived.
I'm going to study abroad.
It's tentatively one year.
If it goes well,
I will stay there and settle down.
You know,
it's my dream
to study in Germany.
You are my term
for qualification
of studying in Germany.
It doesn't make sense.
If you want to study abroad,
I can help you.
I can also take Xiaobao
to accompany you.
Forget it.
I'm tired of dating you.
I don't want to live like this,
and I don't think it worthy.
I don't worth it,
or Xiaobao not?
Both of you.
So do I.
Thank you for your sacrifice to me.
And for the reason I broke up with you,
which you've been eager to know,
let me tell you.
The reason is,
my love for you
is not as much as you think.
That's it, bye.
On the appreciation banquet tonight,
you just need to show up
and take a stand.
It won't take you long time.
I know that I have no position
in your heart.
Don 't worry,
I won't push you too hard.
Lin Wei
You know I used to be like you.
To get something,
I used to do anything I can.
But now I know
what are the things
that truly worth guarding.
I'll offer to quit the job
on the meeting of the board.
You will renounce Heshi
just for her?
Right.
Unexpectedly that the president of Heshi,
He Qiaoyan
is such a childish person.
I know you.
Only real benefits
and success in career
can satisfy you continuously.
Qin Yiyue
is just a passer-by in your life
with freshness.
You don't know me at all.
She has given up on you.
Are you still going to be crazy for her?
Love
can make one lose all dignity, right?
That's between me and her.
It's none of your business.
Everything you own,
plus me and the whole Linshi Group,
fail to amount to her?
Right.
What are you up to?
Don't you say that
all over the world,
you only care about one woman,
Qin Yiyue.
I'd like to see,
if you have no feeling
toward anyone else.
Miss. Lin, please respect yourself.
Chill yourself.
Medicine.
Hello.
Medicine, medicine.
Where are you?
Come and save me, hurry up.
Send me the address.
Are you all right?
Can you walk by yourself?
I cooked porridge.
Come out and have some,
after you changed your clothes.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Let me bring you there.
Thanks, but...
Do you have a place to stay?
Well, I mean,
you came out with a cell phone only.
You have no ID card,
so you can't live in hotel.
But of course,
if you went to your friend's home,
that's okay.
I have no friends.
I don't know
what happened to you.
But you can stay in my home,
if you don't mind.
I can stay at the clinic these days.
Have some porridge while it's hot.
Have an early rest!
It's me.
Mr. He
You asked me to check
if something happened
over the golf course.
I found It.
What happened?
Surveillance shows
your wife Ms. He and Mr. Zhang
walked into an alley together.
Few minutes later,
they went out of the alley separately.
Is there
anything else?
Not yet.
Mr. Zhang has been hiding himself well.
There must be someone supporting him
in this city.
You are right in your analysis.
This person not only supports him,
and probably
he also knows me well.
So over the years,
I have not
found any clue.
From tomorrow,
check Ms. He
for me.
No problem.
Qiaoyan
I thought you were with Lin Wei.
Aunt
Why didn't you tell me that
you've been in touch with Mr. Zhang
in recent years.
What are you saying?
You were captured,
outside the stadium
the night you met him.
If it is related to him
that you are so strongly against
me being together with Yiyue?
If it is because she knows
the secret between you two
so that you threatened her
to break up with me?
I do have connection with him,
but it is normal
for he had worked in Heshi for so many years.
And the reason why she left you
is that she didn't want you
to be entangled in the past anymore.
No further investigation,
just for her sake, okay?
Qiaoyan
Qiaoyan, no.
After all these years,
I found you finally.
Bastard!
The other way round, Mr. He.
You were the driver that day.
Shut up, you!