♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 23=
Stand still!
Stop fighting!
Jiang Mengmeng,
come out.
I know you are in there.
She is practicing the fourth level
of Blood Moon Power,
transcendence.
No matter how you cry,
she can't hear you.
Master,
please forgive him.
I beg you. Let go of him.
Forgive him?
I have forgiven him once,
so now he can only blame himself.
He broke into
our Jing Yue Sect,
and hurt my disciples.
Do you think I can forgive him?
Mengmeng,
you have achieved the fourth level
of Blood Moon Power.
Congratulations, Goddess.
Did you just leave?
How come you are back?
Mengmeng,
come back with me.
Late love is not valuable.
(No matter how many times you forget,)
(I will make you love me again.)
Put him in jail!
Wait!
Leave him in Xi Xi House
to be a slave.
(Xi Xi House)
Mengmeng, listen to me.
When will you stop fooling me?
Murong Chen.
I trust you,
forgive you,
and spare you a chance every time.
But you,
every time
you lied to me and abandoned me.
Do you think
if you put on a show
by hurting yourself this time,
so that I could forgive you,
and pity you again?
This time I come to you
not for your forgiveness,
but to see you. I miss you.
I want to stay by your side.
I will kill anyone who tells this.
Mengmeng.
Murong Chen,
why are you here?
You are saying
you want to see me,
and stay with me every day, right?
Yes.
Then don't regret it.
♪If you didn't want to
get back together♪
♪Why did you give me hope♪
♪And leave me waiting alone♪
Today
is the day I achieve
the fourth level of Blood Moon Power.
I wonder whether all of you want to
share the joy with me.
Of course...
Good.
Come.
Sister!
Well,
no wine left.
Bring me the wine.
Not you.
You!
Go and bring the wine.
Bring us the wine.
Why do you stand still?
Go, go, bring the wine.
Hurry up.
Be careful. So clumsy.
Be careful. Hurry up.
Can't even bring the wine.
Let me ask you.
Does he look like a dog?
He is a dog.
- Is he?
- Yes.
Let's drink.
We'll drink a lot.
Well. Let's drink.
Let's drink.
♪I will still be here♪
Come on, let's drink.
Let's drink. There, there.
I caught you.
Watch out.
The one who is caught by me
will have a drink.
There, there.
Goddess, catch me.
Sister, come and catch me.
Here, here.
Don't run.
Sister, here.
You almost caught me.
Sister, you are weird.
Yes.
You almost caught me.
Goddess.
♪Once blessed hands of us♪
♪But see him off on board♪
♪Is this relationship rare♪
♪Be a normal person is hard♪
♪I’m revisiting the old haunt alone♪
Come, close the eyes.
Here I am.
♪If you can come back for me♪
Here, here.
♪I’ll hold your hand♪
I catch you.
Who do you think you are?
You, an inferior servant,
aren't supposed to touch me.
How dare you?
Mengmeng, Mengmeng,
it's just a game.
There's no need to be furious.
Sorry, Goddess.
It's a joke.
I don't expect that you are mad.
Well,
put him into the wood house.
No meal for him.
Your Highness.
Why do you stand still?
Yes.
Get up.
This Jiang Mengmeng
is ridiculous.
But I like her.
The more she
hates Murong Chen,
the happier I am.
My cold poison attacks me again.
Mengmeng.
Cold poison has been treated.
Blood?
Is it...
Serve some tea.
Serve some tea for Goddess.
Hurry up.
How do you serve tea?
I had nothing last night,
and I am weak now.
He is careless.
Drive him away.
(The wound is not on her wrist.)
Just go.
Can't even serve tea.
Could you work harder?
Goddess, don't be mad.
Do you hear that
Murong Chen was driven away by Goddess?
He pisses Goddess off every day.
In my opinion,
Goddess is good-tempered.
Why is she in a mood
when seeing Murong Chen?
He cheated on her,
so she surely will torture him.
As far as I am concerned,
Murong Chen is nasty.
She humiliated him like that,
but he is still flattering.
I think,
the attitude of Goddess
toward the toy boys and Murong Chen
is quite different.
Is it true?
It's true.
(Go away!)
Goddess.
Go away!
What's the matter?
I just reminded her to
drink more hot water.
How did I piss her off?
Besides, why were four of us
driven out?
Indeed.
It seems Goddess's anger
is indiscriminate.
All of you get away.
A bunch of stupid boys.
Hateful guys.
Did I just drive you away?
Why are you back?
As they are gone,
I help you clean up.
It might hurt you.
You come here.
Stay closer.
I am fed up with
these men.
Maybe you are different.
Isn't this what you are fighting for
by forcing yourself to stay here,
and bearing all humiliations?
- Again?
- Well...
- How exciting!
- She has become truly obsessed
by practicing Blood Moon Power?
Murong Chen,
you are so ignorant.
I give you a chance to serve me.
It's your fortune.
How dare you bite me?
How cruel!
I feel that
Goddess
looks more like Master.
It's good that you three are here.
Put him into the dungeon.
It seems that your nightlife
has to last for a while.
Aren't you getting tired?
Not enough.
I want to revenge Murong Chen.
It is never enough to
humiliate him beside me.
I think the reason
he broke into Jing Yue Sect
is not out of love,
but to change my mind.
He doesn't want me to
practice Blood Moon Power,
in case I threaten the world,
and the royal court.
The more he doesn't want me to do,
the more I want to achieve.
I will make
all his concerns
and all his fear a reality.
That is my ultimate revenge.
Sorry.
I will listen to you from now on,
and will not let you worry anymore.
I didn't expect that
you said these to me.
I am proud of you.
Great.
Since you are determined,
let's work harder.
Next,
I will pass on you
the fifth level
of Blood Moon Power.
OK.
Infinite.
Infinite?
Endless moonlight
generates
boundless and weightless state,
and infiniteness.
When you reach that state,
it triggers
the light of blood moon that
emerges into heaven and earth.
At that time,
be it the royal court or the world,
everything in the universe
will be ruined and gain rebirth.
Everything
is under your control.
Really?
It's a pity that
I didn't achieve the fifth level.
But now,
I will teach you the spells.
Whether you can understand or not,
it depends on your intelligence.
Don't worry,
I still have one thing to say.
Say it.
It will be my 18th birthday,
and I want to hold a birthday party.
Of course.
At that time,
I want Murong Chen to witness it.
Murong Chen?
Our wedding was set
on my 18th birthday.
So...
- I think...
- Stop.
You can say no more.
I agree.
Leave your birthday party to me.
You work hard on the Power.
How is it?
I'm fine.
Don't be disheartened.
The fifth level is hard to achieve.
Let's continue.
(Invitation)
(Yu Qingzhu invites Murong Chen to
Jiang Mengmeng's 18th birthday party.)
I need to go to some place first.
Why are you here?
You wanted to stay by my side,
and see me every day.
Well,
after a while,
you have changed your mind?
I am a prisoner now.
You can do everything
as you wish.
I am here to invite you
to my 18th birthday party.
It seems you remember this day.
Then I will say no more.
I know you are clear.
I am clear.
No one is clearer than me.
Jiang Mengmeng,
come here,
I have some blessings for you.
Stay closer.
I only want to talk to you.
It doesn't matter.
A locked man
does me no harm.
Stay closer.
Murong Chen.
Dear families and friends,
thanks for coming here
to attend my 18th birthday party.
I am much honored.
I attach great importance to this party.
Before I was seventeen years old,
I was the princess of Ruo Shui Kingdom.
In the last year,
I've been to many places,
made a lot of friends
and experienced a lot as well.
All these
helped me grow up
from a headstrong
and spoiled princess
to a
self-dependent
and proactive
heroine.
In the process,
one person
has played a major role.
He has changed
how I understand the world.
The seat beside me is
left for him.
Some of you
have known him.
Some have not.
It doesn't matter.
Today let me reintroduce to you
the 5th prince of Cang Yun Kingdom,
Murong Chen,
as well the owner of Tian Ji Pavilion,
Yun Ya.
Tian Ji Pavilion owner?
- Indeed.
- Really?
- That's Murong Chen?
- Murong Chen.
The owner of Tian Ji Pavilion
looks like this?
He is the owner of Tian Ji Pavilion?
Today I am here
all because of him.
Let's make a toast to 5th Prince.
Today is the best day of my life.
I want to ask
5th Prince
to dance for us.
Look at him.
He is never a dancer.
If Goddess wants to see,
- I am willing to dance.
- Right.
- Come on.
- Normal dance...
may have been watched by everyone.
But I think you have never seen
dance in chains before.
Yes.
Mengmeng,
stop humiliating the 5th Prince.
I will dance.
Lend me your sword.
Today is
the birthday of Goddess.
I didn't prepare any gifts.
Nor I could dance.
Thus,
I can only play
with the sword.
Hope Goddess can appreciate it.
♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
What hell is the dance?
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
I can't stand it.
I need to go to the bathroom.
I'll go with you.
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
Are you fine?
- Your Highness.
- Murong Chen.
Which side should we pick?
How about we pick the side
with more people?
Ok, that way.
Let's go.
Jiang Mengmeng.
I didn't expect that
you chose him at last.
Do you remember
how I treated you?
How he took advantage of you
and hurt you?
And you?
Aren't you taking advantage of me,
and lying to me?
(Jing Yue Sect)
This is Jing Yue Sect?
It should be.
It looks normal.
I'll clear
this place in
a single moment.
Dong Kui wants to know
why Your Highness took the initiative
to rescue 9th Princess
as she was stuck
in Jing Yue Sect?
It was all because of that letter.
- Soldiers!
- Yes.
Charge!
We need to wait for
the crown prince of Cang Yun Kingdom.
Right.
Murong Yi
requested in a letter the assistance
from Ruo Shui Kingdom.
How come he is late?
Your Highness, he is here.
What a handsome and charming man!
Master!
Something is wrong. Master!
Murong Chen with soldiers
of Cang Yun Kingdom,
and Jiang Sisi with soldiers
of Ruo Shui Kingdom
are besieging Jing Yue Sect.
What?
They are saying that we kidnapped
and tortured 5th Prince
and 9th Princess.
They united to fight with Jing Yue Sect.
Let's go.
When did we kidnap them?
It's you, Murong Chen.
You broke into Jing Yue Sect
to get hurt,
so that
Murong Yi and the royal court
will send soldiers here.
Right?
You finally understand.
Come on.
Bring me the poisons
and the weapons.
Let's go.
Chase them.
- Let's go.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪