Look! Over there!
Enemy's aircraft! Enemy!
Look!
Hurry up!
Run away!
Hiroshima will be attacked!
Hurry up!
Danger!
Where are you going?
Help me!
Here!
Over here!
Stop fire! Stop fire! Stop fire!
Run away!
Go!
That's a B-29, bub.
There's no outrunning, what's coming.
Yashida!
Takashi Yashida what are you doing?
Hurry up!
Yashida! Hurry up! Come here!
You're better off down here.
Yashida!
Yes.
I'm coming...
I'd hurry if I were you.
Run. Now!
Stay down!
No, wait!
No, no. Wait.
No. No.
It's not safe.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Wake up.
Where were you?
Nagasaki.
That far back?
You're here.
Of course.
Can you stay?
You know I can't.
Jean, I'm so sorry.
I know.
I'll never hurt you
or anyone ever again.
I made a vow.
A solemn vow?
You're making fun of me.
It's too late.
No!
No, Jean!
No, no, no, no! Please!
You can't hide.
No, no, no! Please!
You can't hide!
No, Jean!
No!
Whack all of that on store credit.
Thanks, honey.
Got the arrows?
Yeah.
Remember the arrows?
Yeah, yeah, Eddie, we got them!
Yeah!
Hey, boys!
What are you doing?
Man, you almost blew his foot off!
You're not a hunter, are you?
Not anymore.
What the hell?
Don't make me do this.
It must have been
damn near 12 feet tall.
We didn't hear nothing,
except twigs.
Then it just came upon us.
It got Riley,
just gutted him.
It got Eddie.
Ripped through the tent, knocked
over the snowcat like it was a toy.
You the one was attacked
by the grizzly?
I'm the one that survived.
I'd like to buy this man a drink.
What's your name, mister?
It's Logan.
And that's a poison broadhead,
which last I heard was illegal.
Go ahead, ask me where I found it.
Ask me.
Where did you find it?
Well, funny you should ask.
I pulled it out of the back of a grizzly.
Whoever shot it,
didn't have the wind or the balls,
to track the animal properly,
and put it out of its misery.
Instead of dropping
a lethal dose of the poison,
it bled into the bear,
made him crazy, killed five people.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Because I don't dip
my arrows in anything.
In that case you got nothing
to worry about.
Damn.
That hurt.
Sorry, Jean.
I would not bother with them.
Most of them will die soon anyway,
without your help.
Three of them, a week from now,
in the same truck.
This sword is hundreds of years old
and was named Danzan by the
first samurai who used it.
Danzan means separator,
in Japanese.
The ideal weapon for separating,
head and limb,
from body.
Like so.
I'm parked in back.
Get in.
Sorry, it's a rental.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Yukio.
And?
I've been trying to find you
for over a year.
Why?
To give you that.
My employer wanted you to have it.
Who's your employer?
Master Yashida.
He said it belongs to you,
and that he's paying all debts.
Master Yashida is dying.
He wants to say thank you for saving
his life all those years ago.
He knows that you are a...
busy man.
But he very much wants to say
his goodbye in person.
Alright, where is he?
Tokyo.
Wait I'm not going to Japan.
It would be dishonorable for
you to refuse his request.
Well, apologize to Mr. Yashida,
I'm not going to Tokyo.
Alright?
I've got things to do.
Do not apologize.
It's been an honor just
to meet the Wolverine.
That's not who I am anymore,
you understand?
Interesting.
Why did you go into that bar,
if not to seek justice?
I don't know.
You don't know.
No!
I think you know.
Pull over.
You are a soldier.
No, I'm not. Pull over.
Pull over, now!
Now.
You are a soldier,
and you seek what all soldiers do.
And what's that?
An honorable death.
An end to your pain.
Who says I'm in pain?
A man who has nightmares every
night of his life is in pain.
One day.
I say goodbye to Mr. Yashida
and I come right back.
Ok.
Fifteen hours.
Depending on the wind.
Fifteen hours?
You don't like to fly?
I love it.
Kuzuri.
What does that mean?
Monster.
No pain?
You have no...
Oh, yeah. Pain.
Plenty of pain.
How old are you?
It's been a long time.
Many wars.
Understand?
Too many fucking wars.
We are almost there.
So, you can see the future?
I can read a map.
You said you knew the future
of those assholes in the bar.
I know they are going to die.
We are all going to die.
You said they would die
in the same truck, in a week.
If you're right, that's quite a talent.
We don't all have claws.
So, do I die on this plane?
No.
Not on this plane.
Don't let the lights fool you.
These are dark days in Japan.
Some believe when
Master Yashida got sick,
a shadow fell upon us.
Do you think he's a god?
No.
A man.
But a great one.
After the war,
he helped rebuild the nation.
And the family business
became Japan's largest.
Did they give you
a little card to memorize?
I owe Master Yashida my life.
Don't be a dick.
A lot of guns.
There have been attacks.
Attempted kidnappings.
Attempted assassinations.
By who?
The Japanese mob,
the Yakuza.
They've grown strong as the
government has grown weak.
Weapon reaction!
Like I said, I'm fine.
Show me the weapon.
I told you we're ok!
Hip replacement.
Please wear it
Too small.
Hey.
This way.
Who's that?
Shingen,
Master Yashida's son.
He's good.
He's alright.
Long time no see.
So, what happened
to the badass in boots?
Master Yashida is traditional.
One eye on the past,
and the other on the future.
Grandpa you're still alive,
I don't want.
This must be done by you
That's Mariko,
his granddaughter.
Mariko?
What? What happened?
It's ok. It's nothing.
You haven't answered my emails.
I can't explain now.
Why did you tell me cnow?
Who is that dirty person?
The man Mr. Yashida is looking for.
Don't let grandfather meet this dirty
man like that.
Shizu and Saki are going
to disinfect you.
Give you a shave.
Like hell they are.
Get in the tub.
Really?
Sit down.
Alright.
Sit down-don't move anymore, hey
Ok. Ok.
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
I can do. I can do myself.
What?
You look nice.
I feel violated.
Prepare two more suppressors
for Master Yashida.
And check his blood pressure.
Lord Yashida.
As per your request.
Kuzuri.
You look the same.
But then, that is no surprise.
Dr. Green.
Leave us, please.
Five minutes, no more.
My oncologist.
Well done.
Oh, forget the etiquette.
I'm past such precautions.
For many years,
I have wanted to thank
you for saving my life.
Yeah well.
You were kind to me.
And you were kind to many people.
I saw that even from that well.
The painting is from
the village of my birth.
It depicts the bravery
and skill of the Black Clan.
Ninja warriors.
They served my family
for seven centuries.
I didn't send for you
only to thank you, Logan.
I wanted to repay you.
To offer you something
no one else can.
A gift to equal the life you gave to me.
I don't need anything.
Not a thing.
Eternity can be a curse.
It hasn't been easy for you,
living without time.
The losses you have had to suffer.
A man can run out of things to live for.
Lose his purpose.
Become a ronin.
A samurai without a master.
I can end your eternity.
Make you mortal.
What they?
What they did to me, what I am,
can't be undone.
Yashida Industries can do anything.
We have reason to believe your
ability to heal can be passed.
Passed?
From you to another.
You have struggled long enough, Logan.
I'm confused.
I came here to say goodbye
to a man I once knew.
I am the same man.
I was not ready to die then.
I am not ready to die now.
But you are...
aren't you?
Are you offering to kill me?
No.
Not right away.
You can live a long and ordinary life.
Fall in love,
have a family, grow old.
And one day,
die an ordinary death.
It can be done.
Yeah look,
nice to see you again.
Sorry you got sick.
Please, Logan-san.
I need you again.
I fear for my family.
I fear for everything I have built.
Enough.
Please, Logan-san.
You should leave.
They're going to kill her.
Who?
Mariko,
my grand daughter.
She is my treasure.
She must be protected.
You don't want what I've got.
Kuzuri.
Kuzuri!
Lord Shingen,
Your father is asking for you.
The time has come.
Father! Father!
Father, please let me go.
Step aside.
You cannot go in the room.
Let me in, father!
You cannot go in the room, Mariko.
Let me to speak with him
before he meet my Grandfather.
Go away! Father?
Why should I do?
Lord Shingen, will talk to you
tomorrow morning...
I will talk to him now. Father!
Not now, Mariko!
Please, father.
Leave me alone.
Please wait father listen to me.
Did I say, not now Mariko?
Please, father.
Do it later!
Please listen to me.
My father is living his last moments!
That's why you must listen to me now.
Don't stop me, leave now!
You're always like this.
That's why Grandpa is so sad.
Mariko!
Careful, careful.
It's slippery out here.
Let go.
You about done?
Let go of me.
He just wanted to say goodbye?
You two grew up together.
Yes.
But you're not her sister.
No.
Master Yashida found me
on a trip to the South.
He brought Mariko to see
a factory he was building.
I was digging through
the garbage for something to eat.
So they just took you home with them?
It was always difficult for
Mariko to make friends.
I'll see to it the plane
is ready in the morning.
Sleep here.
Don't look so disappointed, Shingen.
I'm not dead yet.
I'll be in my office,
if you need me.
It's not easy to say...
But dialogue between us has always
been difficult, right?
I have been honorable.
You probably did your best.
You have always been
my assumed successor.
So the past few years as a test,
I allowed you more control.
It has been an honor.
And I now realize that was a mistake.
You have brought this
company close to ruin.
When I die,
someone else will take
my place as chairman.
Father,
I'm sorry if I have disappointed you.
Let's not insult one another.
You are not the man to lead Yashida.
You cannot bring
in someone from the outside.
In that you are correct.
I will never allow
this kind of thing to happen.
Eternity can be a curse
Kuzuri.
You have no pain,
Kuzuri?
How old are you?
Interesting offer.
What are you doing
turning the old man down?
I thought you wanted to be with me.
Come here.
He's dead.
I didn't foresee it.
You are a great observer
of the society, can I ask you,
what do you think about the death
of Yashida Ichiro?
What can I say...
Who's that?
With Mariko.
His name is Noburo Mori.
Minister of Justice, a rising star.
He's Mariko's fiancé.
You need to bow.
Bow!
Lord Shingen, this is Mr. Logan.
I know who he is.
Your father was a good man.
He would often say
the same about you.
But then, he was always
fascinated with your kind.
Tell me, why do you think he sent
our little Yukio to fetch you?
To say goodbye.
And now you have.
Time for you to go back to your cave.
Anyone else you want me to meet?
I pledge to you,
Master Yashida,
to be vigilant,
to protect Mariko,
and dedicate my life to.
That armor belonged
to Shiruba-Samurai
the Silver Samurai.
It will stand watch over
the old man forever.
Logan?
Hey.
Something's not right.
Let go.
Can you come here!
Come here!
Step back!
Do it!
Logan!
Let me go.
Don't take a video!
Stop that!
Smart foreigner!
Please take her!
Let's go!
Move!
Do you think you can escape!
Go!
Kuzuri.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go!
Yukio!
Mariko!
Where are you going?
Go!
Mariko!
Don't run away!
Wait!
Let's go!
Here we go!
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait!
What are you doing!
Here, here! Here!
Move!
In here! Move!
I'll kill you, Gaijin!
No escape!
Keep moving, keep moving.
Keep moving! Move!
You're bleeding.
You need help.
Just keep moving.
Thank you for what you did back there.
Those were Yakuza.
I'm fine.
Why are they after you?
I can make my way from here.
You should go.
Get yourself a doctor.
That's nice.
This is one of those bullet trains, right?
I told you I don't need your help.
So what do they do,
ike 300 miles an hour?
Excuse me.
Would you say something!
This cowardly attack was,
the work of Yakuza thugs.
It's a violent response to my efforts,
to try to destroy me,
but I will continue to fight
and put down the organized crime.
According to witnesses,
she escaped by the north gate.
The foreigner was with her.
Your gaijin friend,
where is he?
Last I saw he was
protecting your daughter.
You are a toy doll.
A companion for a child
who has outgrown you.
Keep that in mind.
Kayo.
Are you ok?
So, where are we headed, Mariko?
Where are we going?
I'm going to the end of the line.
My family has a home in the South.
That's stupid.
No offense, but they're gonna know
to look for you there.
Not this place.
But you want to be left alone.
Yes.
I understand.
Do you?
Oh, yeah. Trust me.
Problem is, if I do that,
I don't think you're gonna live
to see the end of the day.
You can't pretend shit isn't
happening when it is, princess.
Unless you want to die.
In that case, you're playing this perfectly.
What the hell?
What the hell is happening?
The foreigner.
Just do it!
What happened to you?
We get off here.
Let's go.
Just listen to me, will you?
We need to find some place safe.
I don't understand.
How do you know
they were Yakuza?
They were the same guys
from the temple.
How do you know they were after me?
Look, we need to find some place safe.
We need to get off the streets.
I don't understand.
Shut up! Listen.
Do you know this place?
Where's downtown?
Straight ahead.
So, where's the nice part of town?
Another eight blocks that way.
Good.
We're staying here.
Let's go.
This is a love hotel.
A what?
A love hotel.
For couples,
understand?
Right.
Hey.
Two rooms.
Adjoining rooms, on the same floor.
I can not speak English
Right next to each other.
Very close No.
Same floor. Same floor.
No English. No English.
No English. English.
No. No. No. No.
I want to ask you two rooms,
Is it next to each other?
It's crowded now.
Now empty room.
Underground cell.
Nurse's room.
Mars expedition.
What did she say?
She has no rooms available
next to each other.
She's asking if we prefer,
the dungeon,
the nurse's office
or the mission to Mars.
This'll do.
Lift off! We have a lift off!
Kind of homey, actually.
Where do you plan on sleeping?
I don't.
That's a lot of blood.
I thought you were done being the hero.
But these guys were...
trying to kill her.
Just let it go.
It's not hard to die.
Come to me.
Logan
You're slipping.
You hide but you can't escape.
What are you?
Kill him!
Do it!
Logan
Look at him!
Wanna say something,
What?　What happened?
Who?
He was killed.
I'm talking because I'm worried.
I'll do it later.
No worries. No.
I'll do it.
I'm worried.
He woke up.
This is Mieko,
from the hotel
and her grandson, Hitoshi.
Is he a doctor?
In a manner of speaking, yes.
He's a veterinarian
student.
Large animal.
Thanks.
You may have cut him once or twice
while he was stitching you.
Ok, ok.
Ok. Ok. Ok.
I'll take care of it.
Please take a break.
I understand.
Hey.
Thank you.
I never needed this before.
What? Help?
That doctor, the...
one who helped your
grandfather, the blonde.
Who is she?
He met her last year when
he was in America for treatment.
Your grandfather told me my
healing could be taken from me,
passed on.
I'm not getting better, not like before.
She did this to me.
Blondie!
Miss Blonde, wait a minute.
Blondie! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look here.
How beautiful!
How much?
How much, yeah?
How much...
You kept me waiting two hours.
You have no respect.
So you haven't found them?
Don't play with me, bitch.
I could kill you.
If you could make me
feel something, Harada,
that would be sublime.
I can slit your pretty mouth open,
before you open it
to say one more stupid.
I asked you to do one thing, little man.
Bring me the mutant.
I don't work for you.
I work for the House of...
You work for Yashida,
I get it.
Yet you cannot fulfill his dying wish.
My God, if you had any idea
how much you have failed him.
Where is Logan?
I am not done with him.
The mutant has powers.
He's just a man now.
His flesh is weak now.
I did that.
I suppressed his power
so he could be taken.
You see, it's me you should respect.
Just find them,
before the Yakuza.
We get off here.
Where are we?
Just outside Nagasaki.
This way.
This is the guy from the funeral,
the archer.
He was your boyfriend.
That's Harada.
We were village champions
that summer.
He with the bow
and me with the knives.
Harada and I were planning
to get married.
What stopped you?
Grandfather.
He said we had to wait until
we were at least 15.
From the mountain,
from the sea.
I will take it!
Chopsticks upright are a bad omen.
It resembles incense at a funeral.
Nothing is without meaning.
So, the other night at the house,
when you...
ran out in the rain
what did that mean?
My grandfather was dying.
You knew he was gonna die.
He'd been sick for a long time.
It wasn't his death I feared.
So what then?
What did he tell you that night?
Mariko, why did your father hit you?
I was trying to warn him.
About what?
What did your grandfather tell you?
He told me...
that...
in three days,
when they read his will...
I will become the most
powerful person in Japan.
He gave it all to me.
The company?
I didn't want it.
He knew that.
I don't understand
why he gave it to me.
It was all my father dreamed of.
Well, that's why.
What about this fiancé of yours?
Nostromo.
Noburo.
Does he know about this?
No.
Why are you marrying him?
He seems like kind of an asshole.
My father arranged it last year.
What?
It gives him a better access
to the political theater.
To disobey my father
would be to dishonor him.
I don't expect you to understand.
You're not Japanese.
Can't find my daughter yet?
Our island is long and thin.
Trains only run in two directions.
You've only to go up and down.
Lord Shingen, please don't worry.
My men are working hard
and give their best...
Then they're just idiots.
You've wasted to much my time.
I have my father's affairs to deal.
Get out and find her!
Go!
Tell me you have more promising
news from your contacts.
They open the will in three days.
We are running out of time.
Soon, I hope.
I'm sending men to the South.
That's where we found the bodies.
The fact, the Yakuza was at the funeral,
it means they had someone inside.
Alright, they can't find me here.
It's dangerous.
I'm coming there right now.
No.
They'll follow you.
Don't worry.
Please.
Only next few days.
I'm fine.
Logan is here.
But he is hurt.
Mariko-chan?
Someone's here.
Mariko?
I've to go.
Hello?
Mariko?
Mariko-chan?
What happen Grandma?
Mariko-chan,
a big tree fell on the road.
The boys tried to get away,
but it was hard to get out
Uncle, please drink tea
Thank you for your hard work,
please be careful
Are you ok?
Tired.
Do you need something?
No.
Hello.
Apple?
Apple? Have.
This will help.
It's time.
What?
Please.
Take it.
Thank you.
No.
Two hands.
Japanese sword...
require two hands.
Like that?
That's it.
It's beautiful, Yashida.
But I can't take it.
Please.
Thank you.
Keep it safe.
Keep it safe for me.
Someday, I'll come get it.
It's time.
I was here,
when it happened.
It's how I met your grandfather.
We hid in there.
I heard the stories.
My grandfather would say,
what happened here was proof that
everything in the world finds peace.
Eventually.
That man can recover from anything.
Maybe you, too.
You don't sleep very well.
You call out in the night.
Who's Jean?
We should go back.
There's rain coming.
I'll make tea.
For you.
This isn't right.
You need this tied like a proper samurai.
Your grandfather called me a ronin.
A samurai without a master.
He said I was destined to live forever,
with no reason to live.
Was he right?
Yes.
Still?
Hey.
What are you doing?
This isn't going to end well.
Everyone you love dies.
Kuzuri.
Do you know what that means?
An animal.
A fierce creature,
with long claws and sharp teeth.
It fears nothing.
When I was a girl,
I had nightmares.
I'd wake up and run to my parents.
My father would get angry.
Go back to sleep.
Face your fears.
My grandfather was different.
He told me stories about Kuzuri,
his friend.
Who he met at the bottom of a well.
He said the Kuzuri was magical,
and saved his life.
He said Kuzuri
would protect me, too,
as I slept in my bed.
Who's Jean?
Is she like you?
What happened to her?
She died.
I killed her.
Along with the Kuzuri.
Logan.
Mariko?
Logan!
Mariko!
No! Logan!
No!
Logan!
Hurry up!
No!
Mariko!
Logan!
Logan! No!
No!
Logan!
Mariko! Mariko!
Where are they taking her?
Where, you piece of shit?
I no talk, gaijin.
I never talk.
Who hired you?
Take me to Noburo.
Logan.
Take me to him.
I need to tell you something.
Do it. Now.
You wait in the car.
Logan.
What?
I saw you die.
When? Just now?
A while ago.
But it's not like
I get a complete picture.
More like looking through a keyhole.
But I'm always right.
All I can see is one part
of a person's life,
their death.
And I saw yours.
So, what did you see?
I see you on your back.
There's blood everywhere.
You're holding your
own heart in your hand.
It's not beating.
I don't have time for this shit.
When I was five,
I knew how my own
parents would die.
Then I watched it happen
from the back seat.
Look at me.
A lot of people have tried to kill me,
and I'm still here.
Yeah
but you're different now, aren't you?
They can hurt you.
They can kill you.
Just wait in the car.
I said, wait in the car.
You need backup.
You're not safe, not in your condition.
Just think of me as your bodyguard.
Sexy.
Come on!
I'm coming.
Wait a minute
Ok, round four.
Here we go.
It's a nice butt.
Drink for you, my lady.
Get out.
Not you.
Now call me old-fashioned
but I thought being engaged meant
you were done with this kind of bullshit.
I am the Minister of Justice.
Do you have any idea
what I could do to you?
Really?
You're gonna try and talk tough,
standing there in your red underwear?
You have ten words,
ten words...
to explain to me,
why you, the Minister of Justice
would want your fiancé
killed by the Yakuza.
And if I don't like what you say,
you are going through
that fucking window.
You don't have the faintest
idea what's going on
How many words was that?
Nine.
You have one word left.
Really?
Shingen. Shingen!
Keep going.
Since he got sick,
old man Yashida spent billions
on doctors, healers.
Stockpiling adamantium
at his lab in the North,
secretly trying to prolong his life.
He brought the company
to the edge of bankruptcy.
He was obsessed with you.
Tobe's executives are already...
English!
Shingen lied,
protected the old man,
concealed the debt from
stockholders and the board.
He tried to be a good son
and thought he'd be rewarded.
And then the old man left
everything to his granddaughter.
If Mariko got all that power,
she would dump his ass.
It's true.
Mariko would have never gone
through with the wedding,
not once the will was revealed.
She never took to me.
Oh, really?
A class act like you.
Shingen promised me
a fortune for my help.
So, you put a hit on his daughter.
Is that it?
Political careers don't last forever.
That's right.
Wait! Wait! No!
You wanted the truth.
I told you the truth!
I didn't like it.
How did you know
there is a pool down there?
I didn't.
Thank you.
Did you know,
that I studied biology at university.
Genetics.
There are genes that skip generations.
Recessive genes.
Eyes.
Hair.
Talent.
Temperament.
Not all children can inherit equally.
My father is not inside me.
But inside you.
He faced a mirror.
I was finding myself
How can you control
the Asia's largest company?
I persuaded my father.
Crazy.
No.
Just woke up.
If you kill me father,
you'll lose all honor you have left.
Stop.
Don't worry Mariko.
I don't want to hurt you.
I want to protect you.
I'll stop your pain.
Let me go.
I will fulfill your wishes.
Things I couldn't do that day
that were disturbed by the monster.
I didn't want to die.
Let me go.
It's alright, Mariko.
Come with me.
What's going on?
It's more than you can imagine,
You.
Me.
Sorry to interrupt,
but I need your daughter alive.
What are you?
A chemist,
a nihilist,
a capitalist,
a mutation.
A viper.
Where is the security?
Yakuza.
Shingen?
Logan.
This.
This here.
Where is this?
Master Yashida's birthplace.
The company built a facility
into the mountainside.
How far?
500 kilometers from here.
I got to get that thing out of me.
How?
Stop Logan.
I saw you die.
I'm never wrong.
You're not always right.
You didn't know the old man
was gonna bite it.
I saw you die in a room like this
with your heart in your hand.
I can't leave her
with those freaks and killers.
I'm the only chance she's got,
but not with that thing inside me.
You're going to die, Logan.
Maybe that's ok.
No, listen to me, Logan!
No, stop.
Logan!
You're not gonna want
to watch this part.
No! Listen to me!
Please, no!
No, stop.
Listen to me.
Logan!
Move!
Stay away from him.
He killed your master.
Put hands on your sister.
And now you want him?
Oh, no.
I can't see.
You'll always be a beggar.
You're crazy.
Oh, no.
Yukio.
Logan!
Don't hit my friends.
Where's Mariko?
She's gone.
That Viper bitch took her.
It was my father's obsession,
with mutation,
with God's mistakes,
like you and her,
that ruined this house.
You tried to kill your daughter.
Live with that.
What kind of monster are you?
The Wolverine.
Hey, come here, come here.
That's it.
I was wrong.
I told you.
Let me have a look at you.
It's nothing.
Hey,
thank you.
It's a trap, Logan.
What is this here?
What are you hiding?
It's easy to understand, Mariko.
Welcome, Mariko.
It's alright, Mariko.
She also serves
the House of Yashida.
She serves herself.
She infected Logan.
And what about Grandfather?
What did you infect him with?
I granted his dying wish.
I helped him to rest.
Now, it's your turn.
Lend a hand?
Listen to me, mutant.
She will not be harmed.
She will be fine.
So long as you do your job.
Logan will be here soon,
you should prepare.
It was easy to lure him here.
It's another thing to capture him.
We're ready.
He's never faced the Black Clan.
Yes, well...
Dip your arrows in this.
It won't kill him,
but it will slow him down.
Keep your potions.
He's no challenge for us now.
He's weak.
Ok.
But when you fail...
you have this.
Did you have a nice rest?
I don't know what you said or did
to deceive Harada or my grandfather
Now calm down.
Your grandfather sought me out.
I am the head of this family now.
And why do you suppose that is?
Why do you think the old man chose you?
Because you are strong?
Or because you are weak?
I see you've come to fight.
It's pointless.
You're weak.
You're out numbered.
The Black Clan has protected
the House of Yashida,
for 700 years.
Is that all the men you brought?
I'm gonna get her.
We are grateful for your
protection of Mariko.
But there is one more sacrifice
you must make for her family.
Go fuck yourself, pretty boy.
Come!
Markines, let's go!
Go!
Yukio, run!
Logan.
Kayla.
I love you.
Kayla!
Logan.
Logan!
Mariko!
Jean.
Save me.
Stand back.
There is no need.
Where is she?
Where's Mariko?
Where is Mariko?
Still pining away?
That's so sweet.
Impressive, no?
He is made of adamantium,
just like you.
Oh, Logan, you know what, I get it.
You're frustrated.
I know she's here.
I want to see her.
You want answers.
Yes, I want answers!
I'm sorry,
I wish I could say more,
but I was hired in part
for my discretion.
I'm sure you were.
That,
and a certain talent for combining
biochemistry and metaphysics.
High-grade toxins are my specialty.
It helps to be genetically immune
to every poison known to man, as I am.
And immune to the toxin
that is man himself
as I am.
I'll tell you what,
you twisted mutant bitch,
why don't you open these bracelets,
and we'll see who's made of what?
The claws.
Now we can begin.
I know you have feelings for him.
But you must forget him.
You are a member of Yashida family.
That woman betrayed Grandfather,
and so have you.
No Mariko.
Are we childhood friends?
You have to believe me.
Hanada.
I have to leave, let me to meet him.
Did he do anything to you?
He saved my life.
Forget him, Mariko.
I am not willing to do this.
I obey, I'm following
your Grandfather's plan.
The suppressant bug you found
inside of you was mine.
You took it out on your own.
I didn't see that coming.
Viper is a dangerous.
I know, but she is just a piece,
until your grandfather's
wishes come true.
Where is she?
Don't worry.
You are strong.
You have courage.
Real courage.
But that won't help much now.
What the?
Believe me .
Is it difficult?
We are destined to be together.
Even now.
Perhaps.
Stop!
Seriously?
Let's go.
Go!
Run!
Come on.
Mariko, come!
Go!
Run!
Mariko, get out!
Come on.
This is not the way.
Two hands.
Master...
Hey!
Bub!
Harada.
I'm sorry.
Now, you die.
Today is not my day.
Hey!
Logan-san.
Don't look so shocked.
With you at my side,
I survived to Nagasaki.
Surely I could survive this.
It's alright.
It won't take long.
Dr. Green and I have been waiting.
It's only this armor that's kept me alive.
We built it to make me strong,
so I can take what
you would not give.
And transfer your unwanted healing
to my body.
My legacy must be preserved.
Your mistake was to believe
that a life without end
can have no meaning.
It is the only life that can.
Hold on.
We are almost there.
The peace,
the peace you've wanted.
Your reward.
You know,
I'm giving you the very death,
you longed for.
This feeling
to be invincible
like you.
You are a real monster.
Mariko.
It's me.
Your grandfather.
I buried my grandfather.
You asked me to come say goodbye.
Sayonara.
Are you alright?
Logan.
You're here.
Of course.
Can you stay?
I can't.
Yes, you can.
This is what you wanted.
Not anymore.
I'm all alone here.
You put me here.
You were hurting people, Jean.
I had to.
I love you, Jean.
I always will.
I will be lonely.
You are my only family.
Take care, sister.
Am I wrong to think
you might visit me soon?
Stay.
I can't, princess.
I'm a soldier,
and I've been hiding too long.
In our business profile tonight,
Mariko Yashida.
A two-generation passing of the
torch in the Yashida family
as Mariko Yashida takes the
helm from her grandfather,
who built this tech giant.
I know it will always be the purpose
for a corporation to make a profit
but Yashida Industries believes
we can also work with our community.
So, have you decided?
What?
Mariko says we can go
wherever we want.
Just say where.
What are you doing?
I'm your bodyguard.
So, where do you want to go?
Let's just start with up.
And then?
We'll see.
Interesting.
By IESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections May 2020
With cutting edge technology,
and the world's leading minds
we are on the frontlines
keeping you healthy,
keeping you safe.
Trask Industries.
Solving tomorrow's problems, today.
I'll take the pat-down.
Opt out.
You can go ahead, sir.
I'll wait.
What do you want?
There are dark forces, Wolverine.
Human forces building a weapon
that could bring about the end of our kind.
What do I want?
I want your help.
Why would I trust you?
You would not.
Hello, Logan.
How is this possible?
As I told you a long time ago
you are not the only one with gifts.
By IESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections May 2020