♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 35=
Dad.
Are you busy?
Yes.
Mr. Lei is back.
I am preparing some materials for him.
You are very thoughtful.
You are also difficult.
Dad, I have to take care of Fanlv now.
So, about my work,
I don't have enough time for it.
After now, Yutian is managed by Mr. Lei.
Don't worry.
Just let it out and let it in.
Xiangyuan,
I have something to discuss with you.
About the company?
No, about our family.
Come.
I want to transfer my shares to you now.
Dad.
The divorce didn't work out that day.
That is not my thought.
I didn't force her to do anything.
I know.
Fanlv has told me everything.
If I don't divorce with Lin Xiangyuan,
is it possible to transfer our shares
to him?
Daughter, this is a big deal.
You have to think it over.
I'm not asking you to do it now.
I am thinking about,
if he has got the shares,
he will feel reassured.
He will feel that we treat him
as our real family member.
Xiangyuan.
The doctor has told me everything.
You don't have to keep it from me.
She was actually very sick.
She got better so soon,
thanks to you.
During this period,
you've been working hard.
I used to watch out for you.
It is my fault.
During this period,
I've been thinking a lot.
Fanlv is right.
Money comes and goes.
We are a family.
No matter you are divorced or not,
these shares are yours.
Dad.
Xiangyuan,
it is not easy for you
to fight for your career outside.
By giving you these shares,
I want nothing from you.
I just hope that you can have strong position
in the company,
so that you can apply your talents.
This is what you deserve.
(Miss Xu You,)
(you were photographed
not coming home that night.)
(Anything good to announce?)
(If I can meet the right person
at a right time)
(and have future plan,)
(I will definitely let you know
as soon as possible.)
(Is Lei Yuzheng your boyfriend?)
(Please answer.)
(When did you get together?)
(When will you get married?)
(Please answer.)
Your medicine.
Thank you.
Qunfei.
Please give Siqi a call.
I call her?
I don't want to get scolded.
Please ask her
how Du Xiaosu is.
Ok.
(Zou Siqi)
Nobody answered.
(Du Xiaosu)
Excuse me.
The patient in this room,
how is she?
The flu causes an inflection
in her lungs.
She has a serious fever
and dehydration.
When she goes home,
let her have a good rest
and not get too tired.
Mr. Lin,
Hengshan Fund seems to have a sure bet
this time.
We've been working on "the plan"
for a long time,
is it time to make a "profit"?
Mr. Lin,
you have so many shares.
If you work with majority shareholder
and vote for Hengshan Fund,
we will...
Go. Take it to Mr. Lei.
Mr. Lin, why?
This is what we've worked hard for.
As soon as Lei Yuzheng is back,
you give it to him and give up?
It's not like you.
Xie Li, let me tell you.
Though I have shares of Yutian,
Yutian is neither mine
nor yours.
I have no idea what you mean
by "profit" and "plan".
I can't understand either.
I have nothing to do with Hengshan Fund.
I have no right to get involved,
and neither do you.
I've finished.
Go out.
Lei Yuzheng.
Please, don't leave.
Xiaosu, you're awake.
Mr. Liu.
How come it's you?
I heard that you were sick.
So, I came to see you at once.
You worked too hard.
Let me help you.
I'm really sorry.
You are also quite busy,
and I'm bothering you.
Don't say that. We are home fellows.
Let me take your temperature.
All good.
Go home and have a good rest.
Don't get too tired.
Ok.
Nurse.
I wonder if I can
go through the discharge formalities.
Yes.
Let your boyfriend settle the bill,
and then you can go.
Let me do it.
Stay.
You're afraid that
I will pay for the bill for you?
You can return the money to me later.
Thank you.
You boyfriend is so nice.
He took care of you all night yesterday.
Yuzheng.
What is S.G.'s opinion?
They are still
performing the assessment.
They let us
wait for further information.
Yuzheng.
Within such a short time,
how come the price of Yutian's share
has raised a lot?
Obviously,
Hengshan Fund
is absorbing and raising money.
Someone buys in,
then someone should sell.
This is how the stock market works.
No one wants to pass up the opportunity
to make a profit.
How do the majority shareholders react?
They all can't wait.
Some of them began to sell their shares.
Now, what I'm most worried about is
the reaction of S.G.
Call from S.G.
Hey, Linton.
Yuzheng.
For our beautiful "date",
only Mr. Liu came?
Have you met him?
Of course.
Mr. Liu is a tough guy.
His capacity for liquor
and his courage were wonderful.
I'm afraid that,
to do business with you in future
should be not easy.
You are teating me as a stranger.
Next time,
I'll fly over to make an apology
to you.
Yuzheng.
I know the situation of Yutian.
What do you think?
Yuzheng.
I have to tell you.
At the same time
that Mr. Liu arrived in S.G.,
the representative of Hengshan Fund
abroad also arrived.
The board is still evaluating.
There will be an answer tonight.
You also understand
"the law of the jungle" in business.
The weak one is never welcomed.
So, let me tell you in advance that,
if the result is not good for Yutian,
there is nothing I can do.
An old Chinese saying:
willing to help but unable to do so.
Linton,
your Chinese is much better.
Ok, I can understand.
But there is also
another Chinese saying:
friendship can be established
even the business fails.
I hope you won't
do something like kicking people
when they are down.
Yuzheng, how is it?
What's the attitude at S.G.?
Uncle Jiang, what we can do now
is to assemble all forces
and inform
those majority and minority shareholders
to hold tightly
their shares.
Speaking of shareholders,
Yuzheng,
there's something I have to tell you.
I have given the joint shares
of Lin Xiangyuan
and Fanlv
to Lin Xiangyuan.
Fanlv gets depressed
after she lost her child.
It is Xiangyuan who has been with her.
I believe that
he is not the same as before.
I also believe that you can forgive him.
Ok.
Uncle Jiang,
I respect your decision.
Thank you.
(Memory Corrosion)
Yuzheng, what are you doing here?
Have a seat please.
Sit, please.
I just got back from a business trip
and heard everything about you.
I came here just to see you.
Feeling better?
I'm good.
That's good.
Are you reading?
I'm looking at the photos.
What kind of photos?
You were only ten at that time.
In my heart,
you will always be the same as
when you were ten.
But, Fanlv,
everyone has to grow up
and go through something.
No matter what,
you are always my lovely sister
in my heart.
No matter where I am,
if you need me,
I will definitely be with you.
Yuzheng,
even if you just want to
make me feel comfortable
and say that,
I'd like to believe it's true.
It is true.
Seeing you like this,
I'm relieved.
On the way here, I was thinking that
you have to get better.
You
should not care about me right now.
You have to care about Du Xiaosu.
I saw a photo of you and Xu You
on the Internet.
Are you really seeing each other?
On that night,
you were with Xu You.
I saw Du Xiaosu was really sad.
You must have really hurt her.
So,
to be my lady is hard.
Tell me about it.
How is it going, you and Du Xiaosu?
Ok, fine.
Save the time to question me next time.
I'm relieved to see you
getting better now.
I'll come again in a couple of days.
I have to go.
Yuzheng.
Can I hug you
like I did when we were kids?
There is something
that I finally got,
but the price is too high.
I wish you wouldn't be the same as me.
Kai, is it ok?
He can't get away from us.
Handsome!
Why are you here drinking by yourself?
Do you have something in your mind?
Would you want me to chat with you?
Since our meeting is fate,
would you like a dance?
Of course.
Who are you? What's wrong with you?
Who are you? How dare you touch my wife?
You wanna go to hell?
You wanna die?
What happened, Kai?
Why are you fighting?
Ye,
this guy was bullying my wife.
I wasn't.
She volunteered.
You…
Take it easy. Take it easy.
We are buddies. We can't go so far.
We come here for fun, right?
Kai, don't do that
for my sake.
You leave with your wife first.
I'll pay the bill today.
I'll treat you to dinner
some other time.
Ok. For Ye's sake,
I'll let you off this time.
Don't let me see you again.
Go.
Don't leave!
Buddy, this is your fault.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
Ladies! Come on! Dance!
Have fun!
Buddy.
A toast to you.
Thanks for helping me out today.
We are friends now.
Isn't it just a little thing
between men and women?
I can understand.
Buddy, I have to say.
Today,
you owe me one.
No problem.
From now on, if I can be of any help,
just tell me.
Cheers.
Ye?
You are a man of righteousness!
One more.
Cheers.
Buddy.
I have been fighting against injustice
all my life.
About what happened today,
never mind.
I help you today,
and maybe someday I'll need your help.
Buddy.
Did you know me before?
I knew you?
Let me tell you.
I've been doing business
in Southeast Asia for years.
I just came back this year.
I've been speaking Vietnamese
for longer than speaking Chinese.
If you insisted that I knew you,
you must have been to Vietnam.
Vietnam?
You don't believe me?
Should I
talk to you in Vietnamese?
Buddy. Just joking.
Look at you.
How come I don't believe you?
Come on! Cheers!
Look at you!
I don't know what you do,
but I do know that you must be somebody!
Somebody?
I'm going to be an outcast.
You know what? People like you
all have a shortage.
Shortage?
With too strong ability,
you easily overshadow your higher-ups.
Am I correct?
I'm correct, right?
Now your boss
doesn't like you. I'm sure about that.
You're right.
(Lei Yuzheng)
I have been following him
and working for him for a long time.
When it was time to get the profit,
he suddenly stopped.
He doesn't listen to me.
I can't understand.
Buddy, I can't understand.
(Xu You's calling)
Xu You.
Yuzheng.
You didn't even tell me
when you came back?
You've been busy dealing with
the reporters all day.
I don't want to bother you.
Are you angry?
Why?
For what happened last time,
I'm still looking for a chance
to thank you.
You don't have to look for a chance.
If you want to thank me,
why don't you come to me now?
Here.
You usually take a private room.
Why did you decide to sit outside today?
Even for a dinner,
I have to avoid people.
I'm tired of that.
Aren't you afraid of being photographed?
Are you afraid?
What have I to be afraid of?
I'm not a super star
and I don't have fans.
I'm just afraid that
you don't feel comfortable.
I have to say.
Now, the domestic entertainment industry
is not what it used to be.
A small thing
can make a big splash.
Good.
To experience a big splash with Mr. Lei
is what I really want.
I hope they pay attention to me.
So, I can be in the news more often.
Ok then,
if you insist.
Try it.
Thank you.
You don't like it?
No.
I like here.
It is not because of the food here,
but the feeling here.
I don't need to hide,
and I can sit here with you
to have a dinner.
I've been thinking about
this kind of life for a long time.
Xu You.
I'm sorry
to cause you trouble.
If you want to be so polite to me,
I'll be polite to you as well.
You did cause me some troubles.
Big troubles.
An actress has to be mysterious,
so that more people can pay attention.
Once she's photographed being
accompanied by a man,
I'm afraid no one wants her
to act as a dream lover again.
Xu You, I'm really...
Save it.
I was expecting all of that.
But I'd like to perform it with you.
I've performed so many roles.
But I've never performed myself.
The longer I perform that I love you,
the more difficult for me
to get out of it.
I'm not going to lie to you.
Because of
Du Xiaosu, right?
You are pretty sure
that you love her in your heart.
But why are you so cool toward her?
You're not protecting her.
You're hurting her,
and making her feel painful.
Xu You.
Excuse me.
I think I need to calm myself down.
Mr. Lin, wait, please.
I've read all the materials you gave me.
It is helpful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's my job.
About transferring shares to you,
Uncle Jiang has told me.
What do you mean?
Are you trying
to remind me of something?
You took me wrong.
I just want to
congratulate you.
Congratulate me?
Congratulations
on becoming a shareholder of Yutian.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Now I got it.
I got a big chunk of shares.
Now, I can also have a say in Yutian.
These were all that
I had been dreaming of.
I thought I would be happy,
but I am not.
Because that's not what I really want.
So, what exactly do you want?
I just want to know
what the gap is between us.
Just let it be.
You can't give me the answer.
Because I don't think
you are that noble and upright.
Because you're my kind.
Lin Xiangyuan.
Did I hear it wrongly?
You said we were the same kind?
I thought you were a true man.
I thought
you would cherish it more than I do.
However,
you chose to run away.
You don't even
have the courage to face it.
Am I right?
Lin Xiangyuan.
What's up?
Nothing.
We haven't seen each other
for a long time.
So, I drop by to see you.
How are you these days?
Quite good.
I heard from Qunfei recently
about Miss Jiang.
How is she? Is she ok?
She is quite good.
I go shopping with her when I'm free.
Chat with her.
Though she hasn't recovered,
she is much better than before.
I'm here today,
because I want to say something to you.
In my heart,
you are always a strong girl,
whether in love or in business.
You've learned to heal yourself
and overcome it.
Am I?
I didn't even see it by myself that
I am so strong.
I think I need to
look at myself again.
It' true. I'm telling you the truth.
I know that over the years
you have had something against me.
But I never blamed you.
Because it was my fault.
Actually, Fanlv is right.
I was always
mindful of personal gains and losses.
Lin Xiangyuan.
If that's what you're here
to tell me,
would you please...
Xiaosu.
Please let me finish.
After I've been through this with Fanlv,
it seems
I've understood something better.
There is something
that cannot be forced.
that you should fight for.
There is also something
that you have to insist on.
What are you trying to tell me?
I know I made a lot of mistakes,
especially
what I have done to Lei Yuzheng.
Lei Yuzheng…
Excuse me.
If you come to me today
just to tell me about him,
save it.
And I have something to do.
I have to go.
If you don't want me to mention him,
I will not mention him.
Then,
let's talk about us.
Us?
Xiaosu.
From today, I hope to
give you a chance
to get to know me again.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not going to push you.
I am thinking that
we are still friends.
After what we have gone through,
can we still be friends?
That's exactly the reason
why we can be friends.
What kind of friends?
Less than lovers and more than friends.
We are confidants.
I am not pushing you.
You have time to think about it.
I also give myself time
to test myself.
Ok, I agree.
Friends.
Don't you have something to do?
Would you
give me a chance to give you a drive?
Ok.
Let me check what the time is.
May 17 to
May 11 in 2019.
Yes, that's OK.
Regarding the position,
please wait.
If there is any question,
you can communicate with me in time.
I don't think
there is much of a problem.
If any adjustment needed,
just feel free to contact me.
Ok.
Thank you for your support and trust.
You can rest assured that I will do it
very well.
Ok.
We have to go. Bye.
-Ok.
Bye. Bye.
We have to go.
Waitress.
Check, please.
Miss, a gentleman over there
paid for it just now.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I always feel that
there is someone following me.
Oh my god.
Don't scare me! In broad daylight,
someone can follow you?
I really feel that
someone is following me all the time.
Dear, don't you have persecutory delusion?
Just joking!
Get your head out of the clouds.
Let's go.
I really feel that
someone is following me all the time.
Xiaosu.
Why aren't you eating?
Are you worried about something?
Nothing.
You don't have to tell me.
I know already.
It is because of your boyfriend, right?
Fight?
Fight…
We just don't
even have a chance to fight.
He disappeared.
He is completely out of my life.
Disappear?
No contact at all?
No.
I always feel that he is by my side.
But I'm afraid that
it is just my illusion.
Although I don't know
who your boyfriend is,
I think he must have troubles
and is forced to part with you.
So, he can only choose
this kind of particular way
to care about you and protect you.
No matter what,
I believe him.
No matter what happens,
I'm willing to believe him.
You love your boyfriend very much,
don't you?
Love is quite strange.
In the beginning, you care about everything,
but in the end,
you can forgive anything.
I am really afraid that
my insistence
will be defeated by time.
I don't know how long
will this kind of life last.
I'm sorry, Xiaosu.
There's something
I shouldn't have kept from you.
I don't take you as
a sister only.
I also like you.
How can I not be tempted
by a girl like you?
How can I not care about you?
I want to apologize that
it wasn't me who was with you
at the hospital that night.
I think, it might be him.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪