"Previously..."
(Episode 6)
(Cheong A Arts Center Director Cheon
Inauguration Performance)
Thank you.
(Cheong A Arts Center Director Cheon
Inauguration Performance)
Congratulations, honey.
Director Cheon,
first of all, congratulations.
Many are praising
your comeback performance...
at your inauguration ceremony today.
How do you maintain your voice
in such perfect condition?
Even after I retired,
music is everything to me.
I'd like to dedicate
today's performance...
to all my fans in the country.
From now on,
I'm going to commit myself...
to raising Korean classical singing
to a world-class level.
Your daughter recently had
an unfortunate experience.
Is it true that the kidnapper is
your old rival?
Rumor has it that...
she's also the ghost singer
who forced you to retire.
Sir, you seem to be starting
a rumor yourself.
The kidnapper is just...
one of my wife's classmates
who admired my wife.
I do sympathize with her wish...
to get her incompetent daughter
into Seoul National University.
But I can never forgive her...
for committing such a horrible crime
out of a sense of inferiority.
Not all students should strive
to get into Seoul National University.
To prevent this tragedy
from occurring again,
it's time we reformed
our education system.
One second, please.
(Cheong A Arts Center,
Director Cheon Seo Jin)
(Cheong A Art Center Director Cheon
Inauguration Performance)
Didn't I say you didn't
have to attend the ceremony?
This is prima donna Cheon Seo Jin's
comeback performance.
Her husband should,
of course, be there.
Come to think of it,
you're one lucky woman.
With Oh Yoon Hee dead,
the truth of the ghost singer
is buried forever.
I feel sorry for that poor woman.
You must know why Cheong A Group's
stock prices have skyrocketed.
Cheong A Arts Center has attracted
500 million dollars from abroad.
Out of which, how much is
from Oh Yoon Hee?
I have a question.
How come Oh Yoon Hee's shares
have become yours overnight?
It's almost as if you've been
waiting for her to die.
What about you?
Why did Jin Bun Hong lie
at the press conference?
You think I don't know
who's behind her?
I'll never forgive you for messing
with my daughter using her.
Be prepared.
If you know that,
why are you letting it slide?
The worse Oh Yoon Hee looks,
the more beneficial it is to you.
Is that it?
We're in the same boat now.
As the shareholders
of Cheong A Group,
we have no choice
but to help each other.
You don't want the boat we're in
to sink, do you?
You crazy jerk.
Who's calling who crazy?
Eun Byeol!
You're here. Everything seems fine.
Her memory has returned, too.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Eun Byeol, are you okay?
I'm so relieved that you woke up.
You have no idea how worried I was.
I have great news.
You...
got into Seoul National University.
It was proved
that Bae Ro Na cheated,
so the professors unanimously agreed
to accept you back.
What's wrong? Aren't you happy?
Seoul National University
has been your dream.
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore.
Leave all the bad memories behind...
Those eyes are haunting me.
What eyes?
Ro Na's mom's eyes
right before she died.
If you make eye contact
with a dying person,
you're supposed to lose your soul.
That means, soon,
I'll either go insane,
die, or become a monster.
What do you mean?
Where did you see Ro Na's mom?
Why did you do it?
What?
You killed her.
You pushed her off the cliff
with your car.
Eun Byeol! Wake up!
Eun Byeol! Please wake up!
Stop it!
She's still in the car!
Ms. Oh. You can't leave me.
Please save me.
Eun Byeol!
I got you.
Here...
Seo Jin! Help...
Goodbye.
She tried to save me.
She kept trying to wake me up
and never left me.
How could you kill someone
who was trying to save me?
How could you?
No! You're mistaken.
You must've had a nightmare.
I'll ask for a sedative.
Thanks to Ro Na,
I was finally able to get free
from Ms. Jin.
But I've betrayed her again.
I killed the woman who saved me!
I did it for you.
For me?
You killed Grandpa and Ms. Oh for me?
Life isn't that easy.
You win some, you lose some.
How long will you throw tantrums
like a child?
Do you know what I did
to get back here?
Do you know the humiliation
I suffered?
I was treated like garbage in prison
for the first time in my life.
I was insulted
by scums of the earth.
But I hung in there and survived.
That's what you need to do!
You can do it!
I can't do it. I just can't...
What if Ro Na's mom follows me
for the rest of my life?
What if I go crazy?
I'm scared.
I'm terrified.
Stop being weak!
If you can't handle it,
turn me in yourself.
If you want me to go back to jail,
turn me in!
Mom... I want to live.
Get me that drug.
You remember that drug from before
that erased my memory.
Get that for me.
Then I'll forget everything.
That's the only way I can live.
I want to go to SNU.
I want to get a boyfriend.
I want to be happy.
I'm begging you.
Please get me that drug...
that will erase my memory.
Please save me.
Get it together!
Beat it on your own.
Everyone has a hardship
that they have to live with.
You have everything!
You got into SNU.
I'm the director of Cheong A Arts Center.
Your life is all set now!
So...
shouldn't you bury a small flaw
that your mom,
who did the best she could for you?
Isn't that a given?
A flaw?
You are...
a monster!
It sickens me
that I'm your daughter!
- Eun Byeol!
- What if...
I become a monster like you?
Don't come near me!
Eun Byeol.
You killed Grandpa...
and Ms. Oh!
You make me sick!
Eun Byeol!
Please come quickly.
Give her a sedative. Please.
What is it?
Mr. Do.
Remember the drug
Eun Byeol took before?
- Get some for me.
- What? But that's...
Don't say anything. Just get it.
As soon as possible.
No!
No, don't.
No more... No more drugs.
That's insane.
I must've lost my mind.
I'm sure Eun Byeol will beat this.
She'll beat it on her own.
She's my daughter after all.
My mom made it.
She wanted to give it to you
for your birthday.
She knitted it every night
without taking a break.
She wanted to see you happy.
It's so pretty.
I'll cherish it forever.
I have to show you something.
(Joo Dan Tae)
(Was comatose
when she gave birth to Seol A)
What is all of this?
I don't know either...
why Mom made this.
I thought maybe you'd know.
Not at all.
I can't even make a guess.
I don't know what she did,
but she was always busy.
She was on the phone often.
She barely slept.
She worked so hard all the time,
but she didn't have a single
nice outfit in her closet...
or any valuable jewelry.
Although she gave me everything.
I'll take Ro Na to the hospital.
She hasn't even had any water for days.
I need to get her an IV.
Okay, good idea.
Are you okay, Mom?
Of course. Take Ro Na.
See you later.
Seok Hoon. I'm terrified too.
(Mirae OB-GYN)
(Park Sang Mi)
You said...
Joo Dan Tae switched
Seol A and Hye In, right?
Which hospital was it?
Why are you asking?
I'm wondering if I could find
Hye In's biological mom.
Why would you find her?
She gave up her baby
after getting paid by Joo Dan Tae.
Who knows if she regrets it?
I'll ask around quietly.
(Never Stop Digging,
CEO Oh Man Sik)
She came here, didn't she?
What did she ask?
I'm the child's mom.
You should know
what the ramifications are...
for sharing personal information
with third parties.
Tell me everything you told her.
(Mirae OB-GYN)
(2004 Mirae OB-GYN
Treatment Record)
(Kim Mi Sook, Kim Hye In)
Is this everything?
Did you talk about anything else?
She asked if you had given birth
to twins.
So I told her that you gave birth
to just one girl.
Twins?
(Mirae OB-GYN)
How did she know
that I gave birth to twins?
Why did she suddenly
look for Hye In's birth mom?
This much money...
should be enough
to get what you have elsewhere.
Just a moment.
My goodness.
Bring it over.
Yes.
This is the exact same information...
I gave Oh Yoon Hee, ma'am.
(Cheongpyeong Dam No-Body
Murder Incident Record)
(Kim Mi Sook,
born September 28, 1986)
Hye In's birth mother is dead?
(Cheongpyeong Dam No-Body
Murder Incident Record)
(Incident Log)
Yoo Dong Pil killed her?
Why would Jenny's dad
kill Hye In's birth mother?
Stop!
Let me see.
What's this?
Gosh, it's abalone samgyetang.
Two whole chickens?
What's in here?
Wait a minute.
This is the abalone porridge
meant for your dad.
Who are you donating all this to?
It's not that punk Min Hyuk, is it?
Are you crazy?
Who are you associating me with?
Then where are you taking
all these expensive health foods?
They're for Ro Na.
She looks half-dead.
Seok Hoon said the nurse
couldn't get a needle in her.
What if she were to get sick?
You're so considerate,
just like your mom.
Why don't you bring Ro Na over?
She can eat and sleep here.
- Really? Can I do that?
- Yes.
- Okay. I'll get her quick.
- Sure.
No, don't go!
- Don't you mind them.
- Dad.
Don't bring her here.
There are many others
willing to look out for her.
Why are you so mean?
You've been oddly cold towards them.
I told you not to go, so don't!
Nothing good will come from
getting involved with them.
Do as I say.
Don't you dare bring her.
Why can't I?
Ro Na's my friend
and Mom said yes too.
I said don't go!
Do you want your life
to go down the drain too?
What do you know about Ro Na?
Ro Na saved me. I owe her my life.
When Seok Kyung called you
a murderer and badmouthed you,
I really didn't want to live.
So I went up onto the roof
so I could just jump.
Ro Na stopped me.
If it weren't for her,
you wouldn't have a daughter.
Jenny.
When I was being bullied,
Ro Na's mom was the only one
to side with me.
And you want me to stay away
in case I ruin my life?
Why have you changed, Dad?
Rather than when I heard
you had a record,
I'm more disappointed in you
right now.
Jenny.
Jenny. Wait.
Why did you yell at her?
Something's not right.
Tell me what it is.
Honey!
- Where are you going now?
- To the gym.
Don't lie.
We've been married for 20 years.
You can't dupe me.
Why are you acting out of character?
Leave me alone.
Yoo Dong Pil!
Don't suffer on your own
and talk to me!
I got bit...
well and truly by Joo Dan Tae.
- What?
- I think...
Joo Dan Tae killed Oh Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee was murdered?
But I took the blame for it.
He knew I hid Kim Mi Sook's body
in the fountain...
and trapped me.
He could frame me
for Oh Yoon Hee's murder.
So I disposed of her body
in the lake.
Oh, no. My gosh.
Honey. No one knows
what Chairman Joo will do to Jenny.
You know what he does
to people who betray him.
He said after Yoon Hee, we're next.
No. I can't let that happen to Jenny.
Even if I rot in prison
for the rest of my life,
I can't let him touch Jenny.
We must protect her.
I will kill that punk.
No, honey. Don't go.
Think only of Jenny.
We must lie low.
You're less of a person than her.
You should be ashamed.
If it means I can protect my family,
I'll side with not only Dan Tae
but the devil too!
I would willingly give my heart!
No. We won't side
with the devil again.
That won't happen.
I was pretty famous
in Jincheon myself.
("Paradise Lost")
(10 billion dollars)
Shim Su Ryeon
had Logan's 10 billion dollars.
Did he love her enough
to give her all that money?
What is she to him?
Hi, it's me. What are you doing?
Oh, thanks. That's enough.
That'll do. Cheers.
I was bored. I'm glad you called.
Hera Palace has been weird lately.
I'm too scared to drink
even at home.
Because someone
called Oh Yoon Hee died?
Oh. You won't know the full story.
Oh Yoon Hee was
Hera Palace's troublemaker.
There never was a quiet day
since she moved in.
All the residents disliked her.
All but Su Ryeon.
The two seemed pretty close.
It was no joke.
She coddled the woman
who killed her own daughter.
Shim Su Ryeon had a child
before she was married.
Oh Yoon Hee pushed the girl...
and she fell to her death.
The fountain was covered in blood.
It was such a dreadful sight.
It must've been hard on Su Ryeon.
Bad things kept happening
to people around her.
That must be just her luck.
Her mother died
as soon as she got married,
then her father died of heartache.
Then the great Simoon Construction
went belly up.
I think Chairman Joo and her
just weren't a good match.
Hey.
Are you interested in her?
What man wouldn't be interested in
a woman as beautiful as her?
Our parents were very close,
and she was my first love.
Hey. Traitor Ha, Seo Jin,
Joo Dan Tae, Shim Su Ryeon, and you?
That's the worst kind of mess.
Plus, you said you and Dan Tae
were closer than brothers.
We're really tight.
Enough to share everything.
How cool.
Then tell me a little dirty secret
from Dan Tae's past.
I really won't tell anyone
that I heard it from you.
Look at me.
I'm really good at keeping secrets.
He's interested in Shim Su Ryeon?
I'm sorry, Su Ryeon.
I need you to save me.
I don't even know where to start.
It began...
with a woman called Kim Mi Sook.
Let me ask something first.
Why did your husband
kill Kim Mi Sook?
You knew about that?
Jenny's dad had no reason
or motivation to kill her.
If he took the fall for murder,
there's only one answer.
Joo Dan Tae.
You're right.
Joo Dan Tae killed her.
My husband took the fall
and did time in prison.
He made a deal with that punk...
so his daughter
could have a nice house.
Now he might have to take the fall
for Yoon Hee's murder too.
What are you saying?
Yoon Hee fell foul with Joo Dan Tae.
Dan Tae had put Yoon Hee's body...
in the fountain downstairs.
And now he's saying that
my husband killed her.
Dan Tae killed Yoon Hee?
It wasn't an accident?
I guess so.
Though I have no proof.
I'm sure it involves
Yoon Hee's death.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yoon Hee's body
was pulled out of the water.
Yoo Dong Pil, that dummy,
disposed of Yoon Hee's body...
by throwing it in the water.
He had to because Joo Dan Tae
was blackmailing him.
Everyone is insane!
Everyone's gone insane!
I know I did something
that cannot be forgiven.
I am not going to make excuses.
I am begging you.
But not for my husband's life.
What I want...
is to kill that scumbag Joo Dan Tae
with my own hands.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Please let me help you uncover...
the truth behind Yoon Hee's death.
I'll help you.
I'm not afraid of
humiliation or death.
I can't live...
in such a submissive manner anymore.
If it's true that he got rid of
Yoon Hee's body,
how am I supposed to believe you?
When he did something
so animalistic?
Your husband's an animal.
I can't believe it.
What will it take
for you to trust me?
What should I do?
The one and only card
I have in my life,
I will use it for Yoon Hee.
Will you trust me then?
(Ma Ri Sauna)
It's been a while.
I thought you closed permanently.
Are you open again?
Well...
There's something important
I need to tell all of you.
Chairman Song.
That promise you made that
you would one day help me out.
It still stands, right?
Have you seen me break a promise?
What do you need it for?
I...
I have a sister whom I owe a lot to.
A little while ago,
she was murdered by someone.
Murdered?
Did you catch the culprit?
I have a feeling as to who it is,
but I can't do anything because
I don't have evidence against him.
Please help me catch him.
Are you sure that's what
you want to use it for?
It's not your own issue.
I want to help her get revenge.
Only then would I be able to live.
Please help me.
I beg of you.
I knew I made the right
judgment on character.
Now you are living up to your name.
What is it that you want?
Tell me anything.
The accident took place near Gimpo.
Supposedly the murderer
drove around for hours,
but there is not a single
camera footage of him.
How does that make sense?
If it doesn't,
you should make it make sense.
- Gimpo, you said?
- Yes.
I have full control of that area
since my logistics company is there.
Yes. Call all our kids now.
I have someone I need to find.
(Haeyeon Logis)
(Haeyeon Logis
Emergency Special Meeting)
Anyone who finds the scumbag
in that picture...
will get a special bonus.
If you find him in 24 hours,
100,000 dollars.
If within 12 hours, 300,000 dollars.
If within an hour,
you get 500,000 dollars.
- We'll do our best!
(Haeyeon Logis
Emergency Special Meeting)
Isn't the reward too much?
You think I can't spend
that much on my person?
Thank you.
I'll never forget your grace.
Don't worry too much.
I'll use anything my company
can afford to find him.
Thank you.
(I will make Cheong A Arts Center
an international stage.)
(Director Shim Su Ryeon)
I heard this is the best area
in Cheonsoo District?
And since it's a business district,
if you build some buildings with
a loan of up to 800 percent...
how much is all this?
At least 500,000 dollars.
Dang.
Can't you see I'm working?
Since I'm an adult now,
I feel the need to start
getting into real estate.
You know this is mine now, right?
Don't you have
anything better to do?
I don't think you can afford
to be so smug right now, Mom.
Since dad changed it to my name,
I'm asking you...
to vacate the place soon.
Don't you understand me?
Do I have to call the police
to help you think straight?
Do you know how
big of a crime it is...
to steal someone else's
seal and identification card?
"Someone else?"
Did you really just say that?
I told you I've never
had a daughter like you.
Tell your father this.
I will change the name that
the penthouse is under,
even if it leads to litigation.
Same with this company.
You get your mind straight.
Act...
only after knowing...
whether your so-called father
really cares about you.
(Name Change Certificate)
(Joo Seok Hoon)
Joo Dan Tae.
Joo Seok Hoon?
Explain yourself.
Why is the penthouse
under your and Seok Hoon's name?
Why is my name not there?
You told me the penthouse
and mom's company were all mine.
Did you lie to me?
You stupid brat.
All you want is money.
What?
What did you just say?
Were you talking to me?
Your ears seem to work perfectly.
Why couldn't you use them to study?
I'm tired.
We'll talk about this later.
You better answer me.
You told me to steal the seal,
and now you're ignoring me?
If mom sues me for theft,
I might get arrested.
Are you that scared to get arrested?
Why would you tell her
that you stole the seal?
You should have
denied it till the end.
You ruined everything,
you stupid brat.
Mr. Cho, come in!
Take her to the cottage.
Yes, sir.
Let me go!
How can you do this to me?
I did everything you told me to!
You were using me this whole time?
You coward. You think I'm just
going to stay put?
I won't take this from you.
Take what? You little...
Don't be so loud.
Just stay quietly in the cottage.
If we lose that land again,
you're done.
Take her out!
Dad... Dad!
Let me go!
Dad!
Perhaps it's time to get rid of her...
since I've used her for a while.
What else is left under her name
that I can use?
(Cheong A Arts Center)
How dare you show up here?
You're shameless.
Can't I be here?
I thought you'd be grateful to me.
Eun Byeol got into SNU thanks to me.
How could you say that?
What was your plan
after kidnapping Eun Byeol?
Kidnapping her? Me?
When did you start
working with Joo Dan Tae?
What did he want from you?
Did he tell you
to turn her into a fool?
Or to stop her
from getting into SNU?
You put that cell phone
in her pocket, didn't you?
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Is that what you think?
Then why don't you go ahead
and say that to the police?
Tell them that the person
who tampered with the test...
wasn't Oh Yoon Hee, but me.
I can tell from your face
that you want this buried.
Once the truth is out,
Eun Byeol will suffer
the consequences.
- Shut it.
- Admit it.
I care about Eun Byeol
as much as you do.
Let's face it,
you weren't even there...
when Eun Byeol was
taking the entrance test.
You didn't do anything.
It's because Oh Yoon Hee
died a kidnapper...
that Eun Byeol got into SNU.
What do you want from Eun Byeol?
I love Eun Byeol.
Unconditionally.
That's what sets me apart from you.
Can I visit Eun Byeol
when she wakes up?
Jin Bun Hong.
Jin Bun Hong!
Jin Bun Hong, don't you ever
show up in front of Eun Byeol.
Do you think I'll fall for it again?
Answer me, you crazy wench!
You're out of your mind.
You're insane!
She's letting the woman who abused
her daughter off the hook?
What does the woman have on her?
Hello, Ms. Kang.
Have you found out anything?
I found the jerk.
There.
That's him. It's Joo Dan Tae, right?
He was driving Yoon Hee's car.
There's not an area not covered
by Chairman Song's business.
Gimpo, Incheon, Paju...
They scoured the entire region.
Joo Dan Tae was in Gimpo that day?
Does that mean...
Jin Bun Hong teamed up
with Joo Dan Tae...
and made a false statement?
That's right.
Yoon Hee was killed
by Joon Dan Tae, wasn't she?
Well, what now?
Do we bring this to the police
right away?
We should take action before
he can destroy any evidence.
No.
Legal punishment doesn't mean
anything anymore.
We've already done that before.
After all our efforts
to put them behind bars,
they all got released one by one.
We let them get away
with what they did ourselves.
I trusted the useless law...
and lost so many people
in my life as a result...
while the guilty ones walk free.
Then what's your plan?
Only a demon...
can handle a demon.
You don't have to die
to end up in the pit of fire.
(Joo Dan Tae)
(Yoo Dong Pil)
(Gave birth to twins?)
Yoon Hee made this?
That day, Yoon Hee told me she had
something important to tell me.
And she was followed by Joo Dan Tae.
To stop her
from telling you something?
That's the only possible
explanation for now.
What was she going to tell you?
Why did he have to kill her
to shut her mouth?
Why go that far?
I don't know.
Everything's tangled up right now.
But I'll untangle it by all means.
On Yoon Hee's behalf.
To me, Cheon Seo Jin seems
just as suspicious as Joo Dan Tae.
But she's a victim in this case.
She also benefited more than anyone.
That's right.
See how Cheong A Group's
stock prices skyrocketed today.
Those scum.
So there is more than one person
to go after.
By the way, who's the person
in the red circle?
"Baek Jun Ki?"
(Entered Korea with Logan Lee)
Baek Jun Ki. I'll start with you.
I need to find out who you are.
I lost again.
Seo Jin told me to come over.
She said she'd be here soon.
Please have a seat.
I'll get you some tea.
(Baek Jun Ki)
(VIP Dealer Yoon Jae Pil)
Ms. Cheon, you're back.
Eun Byeol will be discharged soon
so get her room ready.
What were you doing here
without me?
You wouldn't pick up your phone,
so I had no choice but to come over.
Is Eun Byeol coming home?
I heard she was too ill
to be questioned by the police.
She must be feeling better now.
Her treatment isn't over.
Are you going to sit back and watch
Yoon Hee lose her reputation?
Eun Byeol has to open her mouth
for the truth to come out.
There you go again. Please stop now.
Only Oh Yoon Hee knows the truth.
Ask her when you see her
in your dream, or...
leave right now.
It wasn't a coincidence.
You becoming the director
of Cheong A Arts Center...
or Eun Byeol getting into SNU.
It's become clear now.
What are you implying?
You know my alibi
better than anyone.
I was with you the entire time
on the day Eun Byeol was kidnapped.
No. You were away for ten minutes.
Are you saying...
I killed Oh Yoon Hee
during those ten minutes?
I don't believe you.
Wake up Eun Byeol
so that the police can question her.
Leave the sick girl alone.
Oh Yoon Hee hurt my kid
to get back at me.
She even killed a person
for her kid.
Her criminal record proves it.
Watch your mouth.
You'd do anything
for your kid as well.
I'm a victim.
I still can't forgive Oh Yoon Hee
for what she did to Eun Byeol.
My only regret is that I couldn't
put her behind bars myself.
But I do feel sorry...
for her untimely death.
She sure was good at sweet-talking
to you and Logan.
I'll give her that.
Mark my words.
Even though Yoon Hee
can't be brought back to life,
I'll get to the bottom of why
and how Yoon Hee died...
by all means.
I'll risk my life to find out...
who made her end up
in that freezing lake.
Go ahead.
Whatever I say,
you won't believe me, Shim Su Ryeon.
Is that why she came here?
What does Baek Jun Ki have
that she's looking for?
Did you want to see me, sir?
Yes.
My offer regarding Baek Jun Ki...
Have you given it some thought?
I'm still thinking.
Have a seat.
I'll make the decision
easier for you.
I've come up with a way...
to take care of it
without getting blood on our hands.
What is it?
Baek Jun Ki is crazy about gambling.
He used to empty out his parents' safe
before he was 20...
and blow it all on gambling.
Even while he was locked up,
I made sure
he could play now and then.
His addiction should be
much more severe by now.
He has a tendency to lose it
if he runs out of money.
If you use that well,
it'll be much easier than you think.
Ten.
Eight.
Banker.
Insufficient funds.
Bring me some money. I'm all out.
What?
You won't do that for me?
You don't care if I talk,
is that it?
You brought me to Korea,
so you need to take care of me.
I hate waiting, so make it quick.
- Ro Na.
- Eun Byeol.
I hear you're going home soon.
I heard you've recovered a lot.
I'm so glad.
What is it?
I've been waiting for you
to wake up.
Let's go to the police
If it's too hard for you,
you can just fill out a statement.
That I took you to my home
to help you,
and that my mom didn't kidnap you...
What are you talking about?
You helped me?
I'm speechless.
Since when were we so close?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you remember?
When Ms. Jin hurt you at the school,
Seok Hoon and I got you out.
Did you hurt your head or something?
Or are you making stuff up
because you're desperate?
I saw it on the news...
that your mom kidnapped me
and tried to kill me.
That's ridiculous.
Why would my mom kill you?
She was probably angry
that you didn't get into SNU.
Everyone says your mom was
the Admissions Murderer.
How could you of all people
say that?
My mom went to help you.
That's why she died!
Your mom...
even killed Seol A to get you into
Cheong A Arts High School.
She would've done anything
to get you into SNU.
I'll beg you, Eun Byeol.
Please tell the truth.
That Ms. Jin took you.
You got into SNU,
so it doesn't matter to you!
I'm not here to argue about you
getting into SNU.
Give me a break.
You sound like I'm lying because
I want to go to SNU.
Are you that jealous that I got in?
You don't get into a college
because you're talented.
They know who will get
more financial support.
They can tell.
You witch.
Let go!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Hey! Ro Na! Stop it right now!
Have you lost your mind?
How could you attack a patient
in a hospital?
Get out before I call the police.
Are you trying
to disgrace your late mom?
I was a fool.
I never should've helped
someone like you.
If I hadn't,
my mom wouldn't have died.
If you do this,
I won't show you mercy.
I'll restore my mom's reputation,
and I'll get you out of SNU.
Whatever I do...
from now on is all your fault.
She still hasn't learned her lesson.
My baby. You must've been scared.
I'm okay.
Thank goodness I came.
Don't worry.
She's just like her mom.
But...
Do you really not remember anything?
What?
Ro Na's mom dragging you away
and trying to kill you.
No, I don't.
I found out from the news.
Really?
It's better to forget bad memories.
It's late. Go to sleep.
I came to tuck you in.
Wait a little while.
I'll erase all the bad memories,
my sweet baby.
We should love each other
and get along like we used to.
Hey.
What took you so long?
I said to hurry.
Give me the money.
I warned you...
that only I can call.
I had no choice. It was urgent.
Did you blow all the money
that Logan gave you?
I bottomed out today.
I started out well,
but I lost it all in the last hand.
This is the last time.
Do I look like someone
who runs errands like this?
What if someone sees me?
Didn't you know I was like this
when we joined forces?
You said you'd let me gamble
as much as I want for life.
I even fooled Logan
and came to Korea.
You shouldn't make me worry
about money.
Must I regret
betraying the rich boy...
and teaming up with you already?
(Su Ryeon)
Take it.
Su Ryeon searched your room.
I think she suspects you.
Hello?
Is something wrong?
Sorry for calling so late.
It's urgent.
I need you to go
to the police station right now.
The police station? Why?
They need you to give a statement
about Logan's death.
A witness statement?
Isn't the case closed already?
They found new evidence.
They found remnants of a bag
in the car that wasn't Logan's.
They found something suspicious
in the bag.
They say the killer may have been
someone else, not Dan Tae.
There's another killer?
I don't know the details.
You need to work with the police
on the investigation first.
Okay. I'll let you know
after I get back.
What happened?
Did you deceive me?
This was your plan
from the get-go, wasn't it?
What did Su Ryeon say?
That I'm about to be accused
of the murder.
What was in that bag?
Did you put in explosives
or something?
Don't be ridiculous.
You must've seen what was inside.
Were you trying to kill Logan
without telling me?
What are you talking about?
Then why are you nervous?
Dan Tae is the killer.
In other words, they'll find nothing
even if they investigate you.
If you're thinking of stabbing me
in the back,
I'll tell Su Ryeon everything.
That you knew Logan
was going to die that day.
You idiot.
Do you think she'll leave you alone?
We showed our cards already.
Watch yourself unless you want
to go back to the mental hospital.
Tell the police
only what you have to.
If you slip,
you and I both die.
Follow me.
You'd better not mess up.
When you were Na Ae Gyo,
I thought you were cool.
What do you mean?
To be honest, I almost fell for you.
You were proud, full of confidence,
and spoke your mind.
That wasn't me.
It was me pretending to be Ae Gyo.
From now on, you should
live like her, like Na Ae Gyo.
Don't stay stuck in the penthouse
just being a good mom.
I'm still full of questions,
but one thing is sure.
Who I must kill.
Can I do this?
Yoon Hee, help me.
I miss you.
Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee!
(6 months later)
Come and eat!
I'm coming.
Why is it just you?
Come and eat.
Yes, I'm here too.
Good.
What's your schedule for the day?
Class finishes at six,
then I have a lesson.
- Ro Na?
- I'm applying for an audition.
Again? What's the point
if you always apply?
You never reach the audition stage.
They don't care for you
because you're a killer's daughter.
Ms. Cheon and the media are doing
all they can to tear you down.
How will you ever pass an audition?
Still, I should keep trying.
It's so infuriating.
Why don't you just quit singing?
You're smart. It might be quicker
for you to get into med school.
Why should she quit?
You should learn from her.
You need this kind of tenacity
to become something eventually.
Eat up, Ro Na.
You're comparing us over breakfast?
I'm sick of it.
How do you act like
you might change but never do?
A person must be consistent.
Eat up quickly. I have to go out.
Why are you so busy these days?
You come home late too.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Don't be silly.
I'm sick of men now.
I got a job.
A job?
- Honey.
- Don't talk to me...
until you sign the divorce papers.
Jenny.
Honey.
Welcome.
Do we have the VIP room?
Yes, you do.
Ma Ri.
Why do you care so much
about your looks?
Are you separated
from your husband...
because you have a man?
Did you hear a mad dog bark?
A what?
My husband says...
Mr. Yoo's acting like
a poor bachelor.
You're not divorced
or amicably separated,
so why bunk with Ro Na...
when you have your own home?
Who's bunking with whom?
Ro Na lives alone,
so I just go over to cook for her.
You should cook for Mr. Yoo too
since you live across the hall.
He's the CEO
of Cheong A Constructions.
I feel sorry for him.
If you feel that bad for him,
you can live with him.
What?
Whether he's the CEO of Cheong A
Constructions or whatever,
you can take him in.
Did she really
fall out of love for him?
She loved him so much.
What happened?
The materials used to build
the Cheonsoo District apartments.
Could you please order them from us?
Please, Mr. Lee.
- Please, sir.
- Please sir.
It's not like I have any influence.
But you do.
You're CEO of Cheong A
Investment and Development.
I heard you're
the Cheong A heavyweight.
I'm no heavyweight.
I'm such a fair person.
I don't care
for shortcuts or favors.
I heard your son attends
Seoul National University.
How did you manage to raise
such a great son?
I'm so very jealous.
Isn't it easy to get into
Seoul National University nowadays?
But how did you hear about that too?
Darn it!
I'm not in rehab after an injury.
Get out.
- Mr. Oh.
- Yes?
Give it to me.
Come on.
Let's eat. It's on me.
The food there was nice.
Yes.
Secretary Cho,
make me a milk coffee.
What good food are you eating...
that your skin is so nicely oiled?
Don't be like that.
I have so much work to do
that I'm losing weight.
Look at me.
About Cheonsoo District.
We should get a famous
private school to move there.
So today,
after much work, I arranged a meet
with the Minister of Education.
Chairman Joo, back me up.
So what if you build
apartment complexes?
It's worth nothing
without a good school.
I'm in the middle of...
making a deal to move
a boys' and girls' high school.
Already? Then it's game over.
The moment that happens,
the housing prices will skyrocket.
Why don't we recruit
a private elementary school too?
Area One of Cheonsoo District
that we're trying to bid for.
Dohae Construction
seems to be showing interest.
It's Dohae again?
They've been getting on my nerves.
I heard they have a lobbyist
working for them.
I asked around, and I just
can't figure out who it is.
Don't mind them.
They're a new company
that can't keep up with us.
There's no way they can beat
the great Cheong A Constructions.
Whenever you speak
with such confidence,
Kyu Jin feels really uneasy.
What is this feeling?
You two look so beautiful.
You've been winning all contests,
and you're also famous for
being SNU's queen.
You must be familiar
with the praise...
that you are a born-to-be star...
who has both talent and beauty.
You flatter me.
I still need to learn and work hard.
My goal is not to harm
my mother's reputation.
I heard that Cheong A Arts Center,
the biggest in size in Asia,
is hosting the first audition
to find its resident musician?
Yes.
If you are selected as
Cheong A's resident musician,
not only will we host three concerts
for that person every week,
but provide any support needed...
for that person to grow into
an international musician.
The application will open today.
I will try my best to make it
the fairest audition...
where only the talent matters.
I'm here to apply.
Okay.
You're applying?
You didn't even get into college.
I don't think there's
a requirement on education.
If a vocalist who's supposed to make
the world's most beautiful sounds...
got to her current place
only by harming others,
aren't those the sounds
of an evil being?
You're the one to say.
My shoulders still have wounds...
from when you slammed them
with your trophies.
It'll be much quicker if you quit.
I see you still can't
acknowledge you lost.
It's not over yet
for who the best is.
No matter how hard you try to stop me,
I will never give up.
I swear I will step on Ha Eun Byeol
and become the best.
Then I will prove to the world...
that my skills are not fake.
(Application)
- Let's toast.
- Cheers!
Minister, in order to
bring the rent prices...
at Cheonsoo District to a level
even higher than those at Gangnam,
we really need to move
Gangnam's Eighth District.
We will provide for free...
33,000m of land
in the First District,
which is the richest area of all.
33,000m for free! Let's go!
I heard your daughter...
is in her prime for marriage.
She's in eighth grade.
I see. That's what I mean.
Soon she'll be in her
senior year in high school.
And soon it'll be time
for her to get married.
That's why we already prepared
everything for you...
with a huge apartment
in Cheonsoo District's best area...
so that you can win in advance.
It's the Royal Floor.
The chance to buy the place
is 1 in 3,000.
Jackpot!
You did your research.
I'm thoroughly impressed.
Let's have a drink!
- Cheers!
Live together, be happy together.
- Live together, be happy together.
Cheers!
Not bad.
Minister, have another drink.
Come right now.
I can't. I'm at a gathering.
You don't need to be there.
However,
you do need to be here.
You're keeping an eye on me?
Where are you right now?
Sorry I'm late.
Hello.
I'm honored to meet you like this.
Status report?
The worst.
I can't regenerate the skin.
Chances of survival?
Less than ten percent.
What have you done
in the past six months?
We don't have time. Hurry up!
I'm trying my best.
I'm the one who wants to save him
more than anyone else!
What on earth is your relationship
with this person?
Why is this person lying here?
It's been six months.
How much longer are you going
to stay hidden and give orders?
Show yourself.
Who...
are you?
You can meet me...
when the patient wakes up.
So bring him back to life.
Ha Yoon Chul.
(Seven months ago)
I'm going to go use the bathroom.
I'll wait at the parking lot.
What is this?
Joo Dan Tae got out of jail today.
He's after Logan.
Given that Secretary Cho
just bought a bomb,
today is the day.
So this will prove that Logan died?
Leave this in the car
when you get out.
Be careful.
Keep your promise that you'll give
me money to last me a lifetime.
I'm going to go smoke a cigarette.
I'm a bit nervous.
Sure. Go ahead.
Get Logan's body no matter what.
He needs to be kept alive.
Everyone will think Logan died.
Tell your boss...
to keep his promise.
(Secretary Do)
Logan.
Save Logan, no matter what.
I'm not expecting him to properly
function like a human being.
I just need him alive.
That's all.
That's why I got you out of jail.
(The Penthouse 3)
You must do better than me.
An audition? I'll win.
Accept me as your dad.
I can't do this anymore.
Let's break up.
I'm not a moron like you.
I'm not afraid of Joo Dan Tae at all.
- What will be your collateral?
- The penthouse.
You know why my mom died.
What's the truth of that day?
I have something urgent to tell you.
I'll save her no matter what.
The Dohae Construction lobbyist.
That's me.
I can kill Joo Dan Tae
and take off whenever I want.
You don't deserve to live.
I'll make sure
you can't do anything anymore.