[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 20]
I know.
you like Li Qingfeng.
From now on, I'll marry far away to the Northern Zhou.
I hope by doing this,
you can be with each other.
Your Highness,
I'm not that kind of person.
Li Qingfeng said,
love is a matter of two people.
I see it all now.
He likes you
and you only.
Time can wear everything away.
Time can also make one person
fall in love with another person.
Miss Zhao, you are a good girl.
Everyone can see your feelings
for Li Qingfeng.
So, you deserve it.
Actually,
I’m not as good as you think.
Now,
I should also confess to you
about the bookshelf that fell down
in the Liao's Mansion that day.
I did it on purpose.
If you blame me,
I'll have no complaints.
In fact, Qingfeng has already hinted at me.
I can understand you
in that situation.
This also shows
how much you love Li Qingfeng, right?
But I don’t want to be looked down upon by him.
Your Highness,
you are framing me for injustice.
I know.
I know it all.
But I...
You just worry about Li Qingfeng.
I just feel like my ending
is already a tragedy.
I don't want him to end up like me.
I want him to be happy.
You...
You heard it?
Li Qingfeng, don’t take this the wrong way.
That’s not what Her Highness means.
We were just making small talk.
Miss Zhao, you don't have to explain it for me.
Turns out in your eyes,
I, Li Qingfeng, am just an object.
If you like it, you keep it.
If you're tired of it, you just throw it to someone else.
Why do you have to say harsh words like that?
You gave me no choice.
Li Qingfeng,
what Her Highness said may be a bit inappropriate,
but she is a princess after all.
She‘s under more pressure
than any of us can imagine.
At this moment,
are you still mad at her?
I know how you both feel.
At this moment,
why can’t you two just let go of the misunderstanding
and talk about it?
Especially you, Li Qingfeng.
As a man, don't let me look down upon you.
I've had my say.
The rest is up to you.
Let's go over there and have a look.
Look how fun it is.
It seems to be on that street.
Let's go over there. Let's go.
[Tofu Workshop]
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
It was my fault.
♫I feel so safe♫
I was not generous enough.
♫My dreams are all about you♫
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
I can understand you.
♫Just want to meet you again♫
You‘re making me
look childish.
♫I am so lucky♫
♫You did not give up♫
You're indeed childish.
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
You're kind of ridiculous, too.
How could you give me
♫You'll show me the world♫
to Miss Zhao?
Miss Zhao is so nice.
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
If I'm gone,
she'll still be good enough for you.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
If you marry a woman I don't know,
I'm even more unconvinced.
♫Fly round and round♫
I'll marry no one
♫Fly into your arms♫
but you.
♫Ask your heart♫
♫Even if only a drop♫
Qingfeng.
Langyue.
♫A drop, a drop♫
What national righteousness?
♫A drop of love is left♫
What royal rights and responsibilities?
♫I would love to♫
I've really had enough of that.
To be honest,
I even envy Miss Liu and her lover.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
♫Fly round and round♫
At least in this world,
they have a place of their own.
♫Fly into your arms♫
Unlike us,
♫Ask your heart♫
we can only be heartbroken.
I also want to be with you forever.
♫Even if only a drop♫
If there is an afterlife,
♫A drop, a drop♫
I don't want to be born in the royal family.
♫A drop of love is left♫
I just want to
♫I would love to♫
be an ordinary woman
and be there for you.
But without you,
how am I gonna make it to the next life?
[North Gate]
Luo,
there’s one thing I don’t understand.
Please tell me.
Yesterday, I told you
I wanted to be with you forever.
I said I wanted to marry you, but you hesitated.
Today, why do you...
You don't have to worry about Master.
I‘ll make it clear to her.
I'm sure She‘ll agree with us.
I'm not worried that she won't agree with us.
I just feel like...
What?
Sir,
if the princess really has to marry to the Northern Zhou,
I will definitely go with her.
So, thank you for your kindness.
As long as you have this affection for me,
I'll have no regrets. I’m satisfied.
But I'm not satisfied.
I'm just not satisfied. I just don't want it to end there.
I‘m gonna marry you.
Sir.
If you take this bracelet off,
I’ll break it.
OK, I won’t take it off.
You go back to the palace first.
Niaoniao,
what are you doing?
Everyone is coming back to the House.
I'm just cleaning up.
How can you do this?
Just let me do it.
Why don't you go in and have a cup of tea?
Have a seat.
I’ll get you some tea.
Thank you, Boss Luo.
Niaoniao.
There's something I've been thinking about for a long time,
and I think it’s time to tell you.
Don't be nervous.
I...I’m not nervous.
Aren't you nervous?
No.
Then...Then I’ll say it.
What do you want to say?
Look, you're still nervous.
I'm not nervous.
Niaoniao.
If you want,
let's pick a good day to get married.
This...
It's too hot. The tea is too hot.
Niaoniao.
Theses days I've seen
what happened to Qingfeng and the officer,
and I've figured it out.
Since I like you,
I should be brave enough to take that step.
If you want,
I will be good to you in a lifetime.
If you don't want to,
it doesn't matter.
I‘ll wait for you.
It's not that I don't want to.
It's just...
Just what?
I just want to know
what you like about me.
I like
your fortitude and elegance.
If I have to use a flower to describe it,
it would be
plum blossom.
"Not angling for good looks,
you'd be content to let your integrity fill the universe."
You...You said I didn't have good looks?
I didn't mean that.
I...Let me use another verse.
You are...
"You are as beautiful as peach blossoms in March,
as pure as the chrysanthemum in September."
Both your appearance and temperament
are just like a fairy's,
not like those of the ordinary people.
I think you are just trying to cheer me up.
And those verses you said
were probably just memorized
as they were that night in the poem club.
No, I mean it.
Then I won't use verses.
I'll tell you
in the simplest and most understandable way.
You are the kindest, bravest,
and most admirable woman I've ever met.
Although you stand aloof from worldly success,
you have your own persistence.
This style is absolutely unique.
Am I really as good as you say?
Yes.
You are indeed brave and admirable,
Han Niaoniao.
This is...
I'm Han Zhongzheng.
Han Niaoniao is my daughter.
I...
Do you remember this painting?
I'll take it with me.
I want you to leave it here.
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
Even now,
you still go against me?
♫The moon hidden in the boundless night sky♫
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
♫You are the starry night sky♫
Here. Let's toast with water.
♫Every single word♫
After this drink,
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
I'll go back to the palace.
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
♫Not knowing why♫
♫Just let it pass by♫
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
Langyue.
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
Your Highness,
♫From dark night to dawn♫
♫Stars have sunk into the sea♫
♫And I only want to belong to you♫
Actually, when Niaoniao first came to Lin'an,
she had a hard time.
She worked as a maid in someone else's mansion.
A maid?
I can't believe the daughter of the richest man in Yangzhou
was reduced to being taken in.
Pathetic!
The richest man in Yangzhou?
You are...
Yes, it's me, Han.
I've heard your name many times.
Cut it out.
I‘m taking Niaoniao with me.
But...
But, you like her.
You don't want me to take her away.
To be honest, I was just thinking...
It's of no use.
I bring her back to Yangzhou this time
just to get married.
Uncle,
I like her from the bottom of my heart.
Stop.
Your heart?
How much can your heart be worth?
I will be good to Niaoniao.
What kind of life can you give her?
How about this?
I'll buy your heart.
Name your price.
Price?
Young man,
since you are a businessman,
you must know what I'm talking about.
Uncle,
Niaoniao doesn't want to go back to Yangzhou.
It's not up to her.
I'm her father. She's my daughter.
I raised her up.
She has to do whatever I tell her to.
You are her father.
You should care more about her happiness than anyone else.
No one can make her happier than I do.
How about this?
I give you 1,000 taels.
I won't say anything more. You don't have to either.
[Bank Note]
I have no patience to listen.
Uncle!
You're not stupid.
This is for the best.
Don't be ungrateful.
Don't make me angry.
Dad.
Go home.
Dad, what did you say to Boss Luo?
It’s none of your business. Go home.
Do you have to make me angry?
My lady, please.
Boss Luo!
Luo Ye, if you don't get out,
I'll be taken back to Yangzhou.
Luo Ye!
Niaoniao.
He‘s not coming out.
No one can resist the temptation of money.
How much you think he loves you. Go home.
[Thorough Survey of Curves and Lines]
I give you 1,000 taels.
I'll buy your heart.
[Wine]
Luo.
Qingfeng, you’re back.
Sit.
Sit down.
Come on, have a drink with me.
Come on.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I'm happy.
Come on.
Why are you happy?
Why am I happy?
Look.
Because of the letter of appointment from the Ministry of Works.
You don't know, do you?
Today His Majesty ordered
the Ministry of Works to start the construction of Fengjiang Tower in seven days.
The minister sent someone over this afternoon.
He asked our Wood Feather House to cooperate with the government,
as a civil craftsman team,
to extend Fengjiang Tower together.
I asked around.
It’s Her Highness’s instruction.
I think
Miss Zhao must have persuaded the princess.
Speaking of which,
Luo, I already knew.
Tell me
what happened.
I knew
I couldn't hide anything from you.
You and I are both men of misfortune.
What do you mean?
Niaoniao's father came from Yangzhou.
He took her back to Yangzhou to get married.
I can send someone
to find out what's going on with Miss Han.
We don’t know the inside story.
We’d better not act rashly.
We'll figure it out tomorrow
when Luo sobers up.
Li Qingfeng,
what did you and Wang Sheng do last night?
Why are you so listless in the morning?
Today is the day that Master returns to Wood Feather.
Can't you be more enthusiastic?
Not to mention them,
when we got a job in the past,
Boss Luo was always the most active.
But now he's not awake yet.
Who knows what unpresentable things these three men did
in the middle of the night.
That...That is too improper.
Why didn't they call me?
Good morning, everyone.
Your Highness.
Pass the courtesy.
And don’t call me Your Highness anymore.
Master. Luo.
Where are Boss Luo and Niaoniao?
Niaoniao's father came to the Wood Feather House
and took her back to Yangzhou.
Where is Boss Luo?
Did he go with them?
He‘s not awake yet
after drinking all night.
Luo Ye,
what a loser!
I'm telling the truth.
Brother,
you are really a loser.
Stop talking, sir.
Luo is like this now.
He is right.
I'm indeed a loser.
I...I...
Now that the princess is back,
let's not talk about private matters.
Let's just talk about work.
OK.
Luo,
bring out the draft.
The job this time is to build a new tower,
which is one of the three auxiliary towers.
I drew six drafts in total.
You can have a look.
This tower is called Sanjun Tower,
which is dedicated to the memory of Xiao's martyrs.
At that time, the tower will enshrine
all the heroic tablets with outstanding military achievements.
I am in full charge of this job.
It is not just my dream job.
It also represents responsibility and honor.
So we cannot afford to make any mistake.
Since you are back,
let's do our preliminary preparation work
here.
I've collected all your stuff.
It's all in this box.
So, as soon as I left,
you put away my stuff.
Exactly.
I'm just as heartless as you said.
So I want to keep your stuff
in the Wood Feather for a long time.
Your Highness, you might as well
stay here.
Qingfeng.
I don't know how to explain.
But about the marriage,
there is no turning back.
Then don't say it.
You're tired of talking. I'm tired of hearing it.
Why don't we just pretend that
nothing happened
and concentrate on doing the job well?
Qingfeng.
Langyue, trust me, will you?
Li Qingfeng.
What is it?
Boss Luo just left the House alone.
I'm afraid something might happen to him,
so I asked Meng Yuanxu to follow him.
But I think it would be better
if you could talk to him on this matter.
Is it about Niaoniao?
Yes.
Luo Ye
usually seems to
have nothing to worry about,
but this time is really different.
We didn't expect
Niaoniao to leave here and return to Yangzhou.
If Fengjiang Tower weren't so urgent,
we should
bring her back together.
Luo Ye has to do it himself.
Even without the job of Fengjiang Tower,
it doesn't make much sense
for us to go there.
So you mean...
I'll go find Luo Ye first.
By the way,
I asked Meng Yuanxu to leave marks along the way.
Follow the marks and you'll find them.
OK.
[Wood Feather House]
[Luo Ye]
This is the mark.
Mark?
[Luo Ye]
What mark?
What are you doing here?
Someone gave me money
and asked me to stand here with this.
You can go now.
No.
I took a tael of silver,
but I'm standing here for less than 15 minutes.
How can I leave?
The person who made you stand here
just wants me to see it.
Now I see it. You're free to go now.
Really?
I still can't leave.
Why?
I took their money.
If I leave now, I would have a guilty conscience.
I should at least stand for an hour.
In this way, I can feel at ease with the money.
Right.
Then keep standing.
Your Highness,
during the work,
are you going to live in the House or...?
I'll live in the House.
Because you are all here.
That's great.
[Luo Ye]
Who?
Li Qingfeng.
Why don't you make a sound?
Where's Luo Ye?
He's inside, worshipping the Buddha.
[Guangji Temple]
You go back first.
Are you sure you don't need me?
what can you do?
Are you looking down on me?
Fine.
There's nothing I can do.
I'll leave it to you.
[Guangji Temple]
But my advice is that
you should talk to him.
I‘m sure it will help.
Advice?
Sincere advice on life.
The two of them were in love
and were so sweet.
But at that very moment,
Han Niaoniao's father took her back,
which caused them to break up
and be separated.
It's so tragic.
Luo Ye is kind of my brother.
I can't bear to see him so sad.
What do you want to say?
[Guangji Temple]
Talk to Luo Ye,
there are other fish in the sea.
I know some nice girls
and I could set him up with.
I'm being kind.
My sincere advice.
[Main Hall]
Luo.
Qingfeng, you got here at a good time.
I drew a straw.
But I don't dare to read it myself. You read it for me.
[Main Hall]
What's wrong?
It's not accurate.
I'll read it myself.
There're rivers and mountains ahead.
Who knows
what's going to happen.
Let's get someone to explain what it means first.
No need.
I know the last two sentences.
No matter what you do, it's hard to get over it.
Bad things are going to happen.
It's the short straw.
[Main Hall]
[Tianxiang Building]
Qingfeng.
Do you know why I'm so familiar with this straw?
Before our Wood Feather House got hit hard,
I went to the Lingyin Temple.
That's what I got.
I didn't let you know that time.
But you saw what happened later.
We almost died.
What you want this time is marriage. It's different.
Since ancient times, it's for comfort.
Don't let it bother you.
I understand.
Luo,
I think you should go find Niaoniao back.
Find her?
Why should I?
She is the daughter of the richest man in Yangzhou.
What am I?
I'm just a half-dead shopkeeper.
Even if I meet her father in Yangzhou,
what can I say?
Am I supposed to take her back?
You are not
the Luo I know.
You said you got a straw for Wood Feather
just like this one.
Even if it's the short straw,
think about Wood Feather now.
What's the big deal?
When one door shuts, another opens.
Qingfeng.
I understand what you said.
But I really have no choice now.
If the Wood Feather House has no money, I can go get some.
If there's a shortage of manpower, I can go find someone.
But marriage is different.
Others don’t understand.
Don't you understand?
I know.
But I won't give up.
I'll do everything
to keep her by my side.
You have an idea?
I don't know
if this is a way.
But I really don't want to give up.
You too.
Think about it.
Why did Niaoniao come to Lin'an?
Because she didn’t want to accept her father’s arrangement.
[Tianxiang Building]
You told me last night
if it weren't for her father,
she would have said yes to your proposal.
Luo.
Niaoniao values love and friendship.
She must want you to appear in front of her now,
standing firmly and bravely in front of her.
Are you going to let her down?
[Tianxiang Building]
The first time I confessed to Niaoniao
was on the night of Zhongyuan Festival,
by the Le Lake.
The night was beautiful and the moon was beautiful.
But she's the most beautiful in my eyes.
Thank you, Qingfeng. I'll figure it out.
You need to get back.
The work is about to start.
I don't want to hold you up with my stuff.
I want to be alone.
[Tianxiang Building]
Master.
Tell me.
Master, I'm sorry.
Why do you apologize to me?
What did you do?
You know, I want to marry Luo.
I’m so happy
to see you two together.
This is what I want to tell you.
You always do things without thinking.
Since you’ve decided to marry Luo,
why don’t you know
what she is like?
Would it help
if you just tell her to stay?
But I really
don't want to lose Luo.
I’m already sad that you’re going to marry to the Northern Zhou.
Now Luo is going to the Northern Zhou with you.
I know.
Luo, as your maid,
should go with you.
But I just don't want to.
Don’t worry.
Luo will stay.
Luo has a miserable life.
She followed me from childhood,
and I treated her like my sister.
I shouldn't have taken her
to the Northern Zhou to suffer with me.
Now you two are in love.
I should let her stay.
From now on, take good care of her for me.
Don't let her get hurt.
Otherwise,
I won't forgive you even I'm in the Northern Zhou.
Do you hear me?
What's wrong?
Don't do this.
I‘m fine.
Master, this is unfair.
What is unfair?
You are so nice.
You are the best princess in the world.
You shouldn't have married to the Northern Zhou like this.
It's too good for that bastard prince.
I'm not happy. I'm very unhappy.
I want to kill that bastard prince.
Stop saying such silly things.
Don’t mention it again.
Don’t argue with Luo
or she'll think you’re pushing her.
I’ll find a way
to talk to Luo about this.
OK, I see.
Alright, don't do this.
I, your master, am not the kind of person to mess with.
Even in the Northern Zhou,
I will never let anyone bully me.
Have you forgotten
how I grew up in the palace?
No one can bully me
anywhere.
The work is the most important thing now.
This afternoon,
I'm going to the scene of Fengjiang Tower to prospect.
I need you to run an errand to the Ministry of Works.
Find Mr. Situ
and tell him to get someone to take us there.
OK. I’ll go now.
Is anything else you want me to do?
Comfort Luo for me.
Just tell her you won’t push her on this.
This will help her relax
and she doesn't have to think about it later at work.
I see. I'll go now.
Come on.
Sit down.
Miss Chen is a princess after all.
I'm really embarrassed to
have caused you so much trouble.
Cut the crap.
Sit.
Niaoniao is my good friend.
Tell me. What do you think?
I...
I‘m not sure.
Boss Luo.
Niaoniao must be waiting for you in Yangzhou
to bring her back.
You two seem to be separated,
but this is a test.
According to woman's intuition,
if you bring her back by yourself,
you will be happy together in the future.
On the contrary, you will regret it for the rest of your life.
Woman's intuition?
Woman's intuition is very efficacious.
You don't know, do you?
Don't hesitate. Be brave.
When you impress Niaoniao,
if Niaoniao's father is still stubborn,
you can come to me.
You?
Have you forgotten?
I'm the princess of Xiao.
You and Niaoniao are my best friends.
If you are in trouble,
how can I stand by and watch?
Come to me if you have any problems.
I'll go to His Majesty
and ask him to grant you a marriage.
I don’t believe
Niaoniao's father has the guts to disobey the edict.
You must be kidding.
I'm not joking.
But it still sounds like a joke.
I have no official position and no contribution.
How can I be granted by His Majesty?
You don't have it now
doesn't mean you won't have it.
You mean Fengjiang Tower?
When this thing gets done,
the Wood Feather craftsman team will surely make great contributions.
So, as long as you take the first step bravely,
there'll be a way to salvage.
If Niaoniao wants to,
I'll ask His Majesty to give an order,
then you will have nothing to worry about.
I'm very grateful for your kindness.
Then I'll go to Yangzhou right away.
No matter what,
I don’t want to have any regrets.
[Wood Feather House]
Boss Luo,
you must bring Niaoniao back.
Our Wood Feather House can't be without anyone.
OK, I will.
Luo Ye,
you are not my friend.
I talked to you for a long time, but you still hesitated.
Langyue said a few words and you made up your mind.
What did I say wrong?
Don't say that.
Your advice
is also very important.
You two are indispensable,
[Wood Feather House]
working very well together.
That's what you did at work,
and that's what you advise me to do now.
I really admire you both.
[Wood Feather House]
Where did you go?
What is this?
Take a look.
There're rivers and mountains ahead.
I know there'll be difficulties this time.
It’s all because of marriage.
Everything will be fine in the end.
The medium straw?
Last time you drew the straw in the Lingyin Temple.
Two years have passed.
This time was in the Guangji Temple.
Last time, you asked for business.
This time, you wanted marriage.
Of course it's different.
Look.
The short straw becomes the medium straw.
You didn't lie to me?
When did I lie to you?
Go to Yangzhou and get Niaoniao back.
After all, she is the supervisor of our Wood Feather.
We'll need her when we get started.
OK, I'll go now.
Quick.
You must bring Niaoniao back successfully.