LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 31
Thanks to Brother Liu,
Ting Nu came just in time.
No problem.
You...
You are lucky.
I almost broke my wings in order
to act out the show for you
to make them believe that you’re
caught by the golden demon.
Don’t worry, they won’t suspect you.
I wouldn’t have known how things will
end if Hao Chen had caught us this time.
Yu Si Feng, why are you here?
I didn’t fight but ran away
after casting spell of deceit.
They couldn’t get me then.
But Little Phoenix,
I make you suffer by
casting poison into your soul.
We had no choice in order to
make sure there’s no mistake.
By the way, Xuan Ji has a terrible senior.
He even tested you.
Luckily the poison
blocked any further test.
Also, we reached just in time,
so everything is fine.
We covered it up for you.
I’ve troubled you all.
Yi Huan, you won’t be frank
if it’s not for my medicine.
Lize Palace really kept the secret well.
I thought Rose Gold Bird tribe vanished
after the war a thousand years ago.
I’ve never thought they disguise as
cultivators and survive till now.
Our ancestors who survived surprisingly
discovered the Dragon Crystal Seal.
Thus, they thought of this way
to hide and protect themselves.
I guess the mask wore by disciples of
Lize Palace has the same function?
Brilliant. You surely are a demon
who have lived over 1,000 years
and even went to the heavens.
You even notice this.
So, you have to keep this secret.
Don’t worry, I won’t tell anyone.
But Si Feng,
were you worried that Xuan Ji might see
you so you ran out and almost got caught?
If you two are to stay together in
the future, will you keep hiding from her?
I don’t know
how to tell her.
You don’t need to open your mouth.
His identity will be revealed
once he opens his mouth.
How does he tell then?
Also, is the old guy Xuan Ji’s father?
You saw his attitude too.
The biggest crime
is the difference of identity for them.
In my opinion,
you just keep it to yourself first.
Si Feng, don’t think too much.
The most important thing now
is to recover well.
Don’t push yourself too much.
Hurry and sleep.
Thank you.
How is it? How is Si Feng?
Don’t worry, Si Feng has great fortune.
He also got helped from Ting Nu,
he has overcome it well.
Si Feng’s heart pulse has been revived.
But he fell asleep because of exhaustion.
Don’t worry, Si Feng will
recover after resting well.
Great.
Thank you, Ting Nu.
Father.
That demon cast poison into Si Feng’s
soul to drive him nuts without knowing
so he can harm him secretly.
What an evil trick!
Thanks to Sect Leader Chu
for sending Hao Chen
to restore flow of energy
in Si Feng’s body.
He’ll be in trouble if nobody noticed it.
I see. The demon is evil, I can’t believe
he escaped that we failed to kill him.
What a pity.
Ting Nu, can I see Si Feng now?
Hurry and go.
The room is too small for so many people.
You needn’t go and just let Si Feng rest.
Sect Leader Chu.
My friend from the demon clan
will only save people.
He saved your disciple today.
If you mean to make things hard for him,
you need to get over my dead body first.
I’m not an ungrateful person.
Thank you so much for helping out today.
From today onward, disciples under my sect
won’t trouble you unreasonably again.
But if you help the demons,
Shaoyang will fight for righteousness.
Our promise will be invalid.
He draws the line clearly.
Only the cultivators are righteous
but not the demon clan?
Yi Huan, stop shouting.
Little Phoenix, this will be hard.
Si Feng.
Do you know that
I’ve never been so scared like today?
Five of us went to Mount Buzhou.
But now only two of us come back.
I thought in an easy and simple way.
I even troubled you
to bleed so much and endure severe pain.
I didn’t have six senses back then.
I was envious of Ling Long
who will cry and feel pain.
But now only I know that
this feeling is horrible.
If I could choose, I hope I
was the one who got stabbed.
Fortunately,
you got through everything.
You are alright now.
Si Feng,
don’t you worry.
I’ll become strong.
I’ll protect you and everyone whom I love.
I won’t let anyone of
you get hurt anymore.
You all will work here from now on.
You’ll stay here too.
You’ll have to clean hard
although you’re cooking at Sky Hall.
What do you mean?
Aren’t we following Wu...
I mean North Superintendent?
You just came but wish for an easy life?
Just work hard!
Who would have known that
after coming to Sky Hall,
these incidents will happen?
Ruo Yu.
You stabbed Si Feng...
He is fine.
People from Lize Palace won’t die easily.
Don’t worry about him.
Do you really stay in order to survive?
Since I know you sneaked into
Sky Hall against your master’s wish,
I can’t do nothing as your brother.
What did you say?
That night, your master ordered you to
sneak into Sky Hall to get spirit keys.
I heard it all.
Do you really willing to
save Ling Long at all costs?
Alright, you didn’t disappoint me.
But it’s not only about
saving Ling Long,
I have a more important task to give you.
I want you to take this chance
and hide in Sky Hall.
Find the chance to get spirit keys
and bring it back to me.
I’m foolish. What should I do?
Sky Hall has always been
humiliating the cultivators.
You go to Sky Hall
and pretend to surrender,
show that you’re willing to work for them.
Only by this, you will have chance
to stay there and find spirit keys.
I know that you might
sacrifice your reputation,
but for the sake of our sect and people,
our sacrifice is nothing as a man.
This is also the only
way to save Ling Long, am I right?
I’ll forever remember your advice.
Your wish is my command.
Remember that this mission is dangerous.
I allow you to sacrifice
the righteous way at critical moment.
Or even sacrificing our own people.
Only then you can complete your mission.
I won’t let you down.
Sorry, I didn’t mean to eavesdrop.
I can’t let you go alone
since I know the truth.
I’ll come with you.
Two of us is better than
you struggling alone.
Actually, you don’t need to do so.
You’re from Lize Palace.
I’m afraid your master
will blame you if you do so.
I don’t mind.
Getting spirit keys is
good for mortal realm.
It’s not late to explain in the future.
As for stabbing Si Feng,
I’ll let him do the same next time.
No, Ruo Yu.
You are so loyal and helpful,
I shall bear all
the consequences and responsibilities.
Si Feng got injured because of me.
My second senior too.
Min Yan, don’t say that.
You’re forced to do so,
you kept him alive too.
Let’s rescue him
once we get the spirit keys.
You’re right.
Since we stay here,
there must be way to find
my second senior and the spirit keys.
Then, we shall bring
all of them out to my master.
Chu Xuan Ji’s power now is
far worse than what I’ve wanted.
It can’t help me revive the Star of Mosha.
If I wasn’t careless and let Wu Tong
took advantage at Mount Buzhou,
we could still help to revive God of War
the moment Chu Xuan Ji entered.
What a pity.
Please allow me to attack Mount Buzhou
and catch Wu Tong back alive
in order to bring you comfort.
Don’t ever do that.
Wu Tong is just a maniac who bites.
If he is irritated and destroys
the spirit key inside Dragon Seal,
all our hard work will be wasted.
Don’t worry.
He doesn’t have much time
left in Mount Buzhou.
I’ve got an idea
on how to deal with him.
You just need to get ready
to get Seven Stars Disc
from Dianjinggu Sect
and the last spirit key
during Flower Session.
Yes.
Please forgive me for being incompetent
and still can’t break through the poison
thus fail to sneak into Dianjinggu Sect.
We can only wait for Flower Session.
It’s still not too late.
Let’s make use of Flower Session
to create bigger problem and chaos.
This time, I must
revive the God of War.
Si Feng.
You’re awake, you...
Do you feel unwell? Let me call Ting Nu.
Don’t be panic.
I’m truly fine.
Does your wound hurt?
I’m really fine.
Why do you even cry?
Your red eyes make you look like a bunny.
No way.
Our Xuan Ji has become
so good in crying.
She can’t be having
Merman’s Tear in her mouth,
thus she keeps on crying, right?
Not at all.
Back then, I thought
crying is something fun.
But now only I know it
doesn’t feel good at all.
Si Feng.
It seems that I’ve known everything.
So this is the feeling of loving someone.
My heart will ache like this.
In the future,
don’t scare me anymore, okay?
Don’t leave me anymore, okay?
Xuan Ji.
I won’t leave you, it’s all fine.
I’ll accompany you forever
and ever.
I won’t leave you forever.
Si Feng.
What is this?
I had seen this on your body too.
Xuan Ji.
Actually, I... I got it.
Ting Nu gave you this to heal?
You’re right.
Xuan Ji.
Actually...
Xuan Ji, is Little Phoenix...
Should I leave first?
Si Feng is alive but his body needs rest.
Father, go back to Shaoyang
with Aunt Hong first.
It’s important to revive
Ling Long’s primordial spirit.
I wanted to talk about this with you all.
Hero Yu got injured because of Xuan Ji.
We should bring you back
to Shaoyang to recover.
Si Feng needs rest now,
he shouldn’t go anywhere.
It’s unfitting to bring him back
to Shaoyang nor Lize Palace.
Let me stay to take care of Si Feng then.
Father, Ling Long’s primordial spirit
is the most important now.
Hurry and go back.
Moreover, I heard from Aunt Hong
that the condition of
secret ground isn’t so good.
You needn’t worry about
the stability of secret ground.
As for the rest of you...
Sect Leader Chu, don’t worry about me.
Ling Long is more important.
Xuan Ji, you’re a grown-up now.
I won’t interfere your decision anymore.
But Flower Session which happens
once in four years is coming soon.
When Hero Yu gets better,
hurry and return to Shaoyang then.
Think thrice before taking action.
Also, remember that you and...
Your relationship with friend must
follow etiquettes, understand?
Father.
I know. Oh right, if Ling Long wakes up,
you must write letter to inform me.
Then only I can be at ease.
Please tell sister that we will return
as soon as Si Feng recovers.
Also, regarding Sixth Senior...
Father, you...
Don’t worry about Ling Long.
Also, there’s no decision
made regarding Min Yan.
He betrayed the sect.
It’s hard to tell
if he’s an enemy or friend.
Bring him back if he appears,
then only we will decide
in order to avoid confusion.
Everyone, I shall bid farewell here.
Si Feng.
Your father has finally left,
I was suffering all the time.
How is Yu’Er now?
My good girl.
Why are you avoiding me?
Do you think I am not good
enough and trouble you?
I thought you’re bullied by people
of Sky Hall because of me
and I have caused you troubles
that you don’t care about me anymore.
Silly girl.
Why would I dump you?
I know I wasn’t good enough back then
and made you feel wronged.
I wish to make up for you now.
I saved you is not to
control and chain you up.
I wish you can cultivate
your demonic core again
so that you can protect yourself
better in future.
Father, it’s my fault.
I’ll listen to you and be diligent.
By that time, not only I can protect
myself, but you too.
My good girl.
Oh, right!
Thanks to Uncle Si Feng
and Aunt Xuan Ji this time.
They saved you, hurry and thank them.
I’ll remember the great kindness of
Uncle Si Feng and Aunt Xuan Ji forever.
I’ll pray for you two
to get married, have children
and live happily forever.
Why does it sound off?
Yu’Er, I think you’ve
got your father’s genes.
Does it sound off? I think that’s not bad.
Since Yu’Er is cultivating demonic core,
I think she needs a safe and
spiritual place to stay focus.
What about going to our
merman’s place in Donghai?
That’s great!
We’ll get it done immediately.
Cultivating demonic core
should delay no more.
Ting Nu, I’ll hand Yu’Er to you then.
Sure, let’s go now.
Well, I witnessed Yu’Er
and Brother Liu reunited.
Our journey back from
Mount Buzhou is worth it then.
However,
I don’t think Sixth Senior
is a person like this.
He won’t betray the sect.
I trust Min Yan as well.
When my wound gets better,
we’ll find them in Mount Buzhou.
I have a feeling that there’s
reason behind Ruo Yu hurting me.
We must bring them back no matter what.
Si Feng.
I think my father’s words make sense too.
I must think thrice
before taking action in future.
I can’t let you take the risk with me.
I must be stronger.
Then I shall find Wu Tong
and kill all those demons.
Xuan Ji.
Do you really think that
all demons
are unforgivable?
I guess not.
Purple Fox is much more
better than Wu Tong.
But I must kill all demons who do evil.
Wu Tong’s side is guarding against us,
we have no idea where the spirit key is.
There’s no way to find
my second senior too.
We’ve looked over places like dark dungeon
and colosseum where they captured slaves.
I’m afraid your second senior
might be locked up individually.
Don’t worry, let’s find other ways.
Here! That’s great! Can you do it?
Take it! Do it again!
She is really good!
I didn’t expect Ling Long to be so good.
She is indeed good.
Give me my jianzi.
Min Yan.
What are you looking at?
Who allows you to look at me?
How dare you hide things?
This is for my future wife.
We are reasonable and grounded.
What hereditary treasure is this?
What did you say?
Do you recognize this dagger?
What hypnosis spell did you cast on me?
Min Yan!
Just keep this dagger
for your future wife!
All of you, beat him up!
Don’t go!
How is it?
Her primordial spirit has been revived.
Her pulse is stable and life is safe.
Don’t worry.
Great then.
Why hasn’t Ling Long awaken?
Extraction of primordial spirit
is forbidden.
It’s my first time using this.
I guess it takes some time.
Let’s observe a few days.
I shall go through the record again
to check if I’ve overlooked anything.
Sure.
I’ll ask Hong Luan to
send Xuan Ji a letter.
She must be worried.
Si Feng.
Ting Nu said you recover well
these two days.
You can walk after another two days.
I specially cooked fish porridge
for you to build up your body
so that you can recover fast.
What’s wrong with your face?
My face?
What’s wrong?
Try this first, I learned
from the aunt next door.
Try if it’s tasty.
Not bad, it’s very tasty.
Really? It’s my first time cooking this.
It’s almost perfect for the first time.
You must be talented.
Si Feng, are you being serious
to praise me this way?
I can’t bear to try such tasty porridge.
Try it for yourself then.
Why would I lie to you?
It’s really delicious.
I know that
my Si Feng will never lie to me.
Min Yan.
Are you sure that flower demon
is related to Ling Long?
Her technique while kicking the jianzi,
I actually amended it from Yaohua
sword moves and taught Ling Long.
It’s impossible to kick the exact
same way if she’s other people.
Moreover, she can
recognize my dagger too.
Is all this coincidence?
I heard there’s a sorcery in Beizhou which
extracts a person’s primordial spirit
and injects into another person’s body.
If Wu Tong is using this sorcery,
the lady that Xuan Ji brought
along wasn’t Ling Long then.
The primordial spirit of real Ling Long
is inside the flower demon.
I’m just saying, it might not be true.
No.
Your saying might be true.
Wu Tong is always cunning.
- Wu Tong, watch out!
- Min Yan.
We’re now under control.
You’re only inviting troubles
if you look for Wu Tong now.
We must carefully identify Wu Tong’s
flaw now in order to turn the table.
Our priority is to check if Ling Long’s
primordial spirit is inside flower demon.
These fragments from
Mirror of Origin might help us.
I’ll find a chance to test her.
Thank you for helping me to recover.
Master, how is the
secret ground lately?
The closer the two stars,
the weaker the barrier.
We can’t avoid this situation.
However, I can still maintain it.
So, don’t you worry about this.
You need to slowly clear off
the poison in your body.
Don’t rush it.
Yes, master.
This is the formation of truth
you asked for previously.
Any demons which turned into human,
as long as their skin gets in touch
with this formation for some time,
they can’t help but to
expose their original form.
Thank you, master.
Even the power of Love Flower
can’t heal your wound.
Unless your body has the energy
to oppose energy of the heavens.
I wonder if it’s because of the poison
or you’re actually demon.
Yu Si Feng.
I won’t end this matter easily.
You’ve sent Yu’Er safely?
Why are you back so hurriedly?
I was chased away.
Yu’Er said I nag too much
and disturb her cultivation.
But I can’t really
help her in cultivation.
Why haven’t we started eating yet?
Where are they?
Backyard.
I won’t push you anymore, come yourself.
Walk slowly, Si Feng.
Be careful of the door sill.
Do you feel better?
Don’t put pressure on your wound.
Tell me if you’re dizzy, alright?
I seem to be a little dizzy.
You seem dizzy?
Come here.
Do you feel better resting on me?
- I can’t bear no more.
- You can’t bear?
Don’t use your strength, come on.
Hug me tight, is it alright?
- Hug tighter.
- Tighter?
What about this?
Is it alright?
Si Feng.
Xuan Ji.
I was just kidding, I’m all good now.
Ting Nu said my condition will be
as good as the past after a few days.
We shall stroll around the altar then.
We’ll then catch some demons to
ask about situation inside Sky Hall.
We’ll also snatch some Black and White
Rings before entering Mount Buzhou, okay?
But I still feel I’m not
strong enough now.
Do you think I should find
one spirit beast too?
You and Silver Snake joined hands
are so much better than me alone.
If you’re destined to get skillful beast,
you will be like a flying tiger.
But you can’t rush this thing.
It’s all destined, so do it slowly.
Si Feng, let’s take a look outside.
This is...
Is it nice?
This is a way for blessings
taught by the aunt next door.
Hang the wind-bell on tree after
making a wish and it will come true.
I hope you will be safe in future
without injury and pain.
She also said we can write on the wind-bell
if there’s anything we’re
too shy to say it out,
then wind will tell that person.
But I have nothing
after thinking about it.
What about you?
I do have something to tell you.
But I can’t write it on the wind-bell.
Because this is actually a secret
I want to keep forever.
I don’t want others to see it.
So, I sealed the secret inside this.
Xuan Ji.
If you unlock this Lugong puzzle,
you can see it then.
Lugong puzzle?
Si Feng, it seems hard to
unlock this Lugong puzzle.
You kept the secret inside,
but want me to open it.
Do you actually want me to see it?
Forget about it if you don’t want to know.
No! Let me try.
Xuan Ji.
You will eventually
unlock and see it one day.
At this moment,
I’m being timid,
I’m greedy
that I can’t let go of this moment.
Si Feng kept his secret
inside Lugong puzzle.
He is cutting off all ways for Xuan Ji.
Won’t you stop him?
Why should I stop him?
- If so...
- Xuan Ji might be the way for Si Feng.
So, let’s not do something useless.
Don’t think of harming Xuan Ji.
How do you know if Xuan Ji
discovers Si Feng’s identity,
she won’t hurt him?
There are only two
consequences for this matter.
It’s either Xuan Ji accepts him
and his Loveless Curse is cured
that everyone is happy,
or they totally break up and
he will die from the poison.
Which would you choose?
Of course I’m choosing the first one.
That’s right.
Silver Snake,
Little Phoenix’s future depends
on Xuan Ji no matter what.
It doesn’t really have
anything to do with you.
So, don’t be obsessive.
I am not obsessive though.
What are you doing? What are you hiding?
- Show me your hand.
- It’s nothing.
What do you mean by nothing?
Let go of your hand.
- Don’t look at my thing.
- What is it? I want to see.
I like you, I only have you in my heart.
What is this?
What Mount Shaoyang?
How do I know you?
You saw what happened in Mount Shaoyang?
- What did you see?
- Don’t touch me!
What nonsense is this?
What is Bazhen cake?
Why do I have such weird memories?
Bazhen cake?
It’s really you.
- I’ve found you, Ling Long!
- Shut up!
I knew it’s your trick.
Just you wait.
I’ll surely tell Brother Wu Tong
so that he will teach you a lesson.
You!
- I’ve been waiting long.
- What do you want?
Tell me how to open
Wu Tong’s secret chamber?
- I know he told you everything.
- I really don’t know.
- Let me go!
- You won’t tell without suffering.
Hurry and go!
Be careful!
Little Six!
What did you call me?
Go and die!
Brother Wu Tong.
I didn’t expect your skill of stripping
the soul has improved so much.
Wolf, our lord has yet to agree.
You caused troubles.
If I’m unhappy
and destroy spirit keys, is it your fault?
Don’t forget that when you’re lost,
our lord saved you.
Gratitude?
You’re nobody to teach me!
Just you wait!
He’s surely fast at escaping.
Brother Wu Tong, you’re here finally.
I was so scared, luckily I was smart.
Yes, you’re so smart.
This guy is silly.
He has no skills but still stood out.
He put in effort to save you,
he has done a deed of merit.
You can follow me in future.
Go and clean your injury.
Brother Tong.
My master specially prepared
the Bazhen cake for Xuan Ji.
It’s an unique birthday cake.
If she isn’t Ling Long, there’s
no way she knows about it.
But why doesn’t she remember a thing?
If you say so, I have a wild guess.
Inside body of flower demon might have
half of Ling Long’s primordial spirit.
Thus, she has personality like Ling Long,
but doesn’t have Ling Long’s memory.
She can only see the past
through Mirror of Origin.
The lady Xuan Ji and Si Feng
brought along
was another half of
Ling Long’s primordial spirit.
I’m afraid this is true.
After so much hard work,
we’re still fooled by Wu Tong.
It’s hard to guard Wu Tong who is cunning.
But Ling Long has half of the primordial
spirit as protection, she is safe now.
We still have chance
as long as we’re in Sky Hall.
But we have no idea how to get Ling Long’s
primordial spirit back all in a sudden.
The flower demon must know something.
She has Ling Long’s personality.
If she’s willing to help...
But she doesn’t remember
a thing about Ling Long.
Wu Tong has great impact on her.
You understand her the best.
If you can’t bring her back,
then who else can make it?
Wolf came today. Although we
don’t know what happened in Sky Hall,
there’s a clue which is definitely right.
The spirit keys are hidden in
Wu Tong’s secret chamber.
I’m sure flower demon knows the secret.
It will be Wu Tong’s biggest flaw
if she’s willing to help us.
Zhong Min Yan!
How are you? Wu Tong doesn’t
want me to get closer to you.
So, I couldn’t thank you just now.
Take this medicine, it’s quite good.
Your wound is probably severe, I saw it.
I didn’t expect you to save me.
Of course I’ll save you.
Though you don’t remember
most of our things.
I don’t want to hear this. I want to
repay you since you saved me today.
Do you want to see your second senior?
You’re willing to bring me there?
You’re talking so much.
It’s all on you whether to follow me.
Second Senior.
His wound is infected.
He’s having fever.
That’s the medicine I gave you.
Second Senior.
You...
Second Senior, it’s all my fault.
I am so sorry.
But you must endure it.
I’ll surely rescue you.
I’ll beg Senior Heng Yang
after returning to Shaoyang.
I shall give you my arm by
using his attachment skill.
Silly you.
- Do you really think we can go out?
- Yes, we can!
Second Senior.
It has been some time here,
you can’t stay for long. Let’s go.
Alright.
I trust you.
We should go now.
- Food.
- What?
Please get him food.
My second senior is very weak now.
You all didn’t even
provide food these days.
It’s not me who care for him.
How would I know if he eats or not?
Take this.
This is my favorite glutinous rice cake.
Give it to him.
- Thank you.
- That’s not too bad.
But
your favorite isn’t glutinous rice cake.
It’s osmanthus cake.
Senior.