LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 40
I’ve told you enough.
Why don’t you show me
your sincerity as well?
I’ll tell you my goal after that.
So, what exactly do you want me to do?
Go to Demon Citadel
and save Wu Zhi Qi
with the power of the 12 Feathers.
Mortals and demons are enemies
because they’re equal in strength.
But if the demons grow much
stronger, no mortals would dare to
disobey us.
So, by that time,
that silly girl will be together
with you naturally.
Do you think I’m in the dark
because you didn’t tell me the truth?
After the Demon Citadel
was destroyed by the heavens,
it is filled with deadly anguish.
It is a death trap.
You just wanted to send me to my grave.
You have no right to talk about
Xuan Ji and I when you’re this selfish.
I’m doing this for your sake.
If you don’t help out the
demon clan, next time,
you’ll die by her sword
when she masters her powers.
It’ll be too late for you
to regret it by then.
Scram.
Think about it.
Seems like he’s getting
more and more ambitious.
Elder Luo, how’s the
situation in Lize Palace?
He forced everyone to join Sky Hall.
For those who disobey his
orders, he’ll either put them in cells
or execute them immediately.
Please pass this message to everyone.
Sky Hall is powerful now.
We need to compromise with them.
And save our strength.
We shouldn’t sacrifice
ourselves for nothing.
Now, I know what his next plan is.
Give me some time to think of a solution.
I will surely protect our clan.
Yes.
These four stupid chains!
Palace Lord, you’ve absorbed 80 souls.
It’s finally working after
absorbing so many souls.
Now, we just need another
19 souls to complete it.
You can absorb the God of War’s power
if you complete the Soul Furnace?
Are you interested as well?
The God of War is mighty.
I can’t absorb her powers
by using the Soul Furnace alone.
We need to set up a formation as well.
And I’m the only one who knows
how to set up that formation.
Only I can use
the God of War’s powers.
Ruo Yu,
you better don’t try anything funny.
I don’t dare to do so!
I’ve always been loyal to you, my lord.
I will never betray you.
Rise now.
Thank you, my lord.
Of course I will succeed.
I’ve planned this for over 1,000 years.
I’ve located the God of War
and had awaken her powers.
Everything is according to the plan.
We need Yuntian Loop and Chehai Hook
to unseal the Jade Cup.
But when we unseal the Jade Cup,
the immense pressure of Star of Mosha
will turn us into dust.
We’ll only be fine if we have
God of War’s power.
And only her powers can fight against
the Star of Mosha’s power.
I’m not reviving the Star of Mosha
for him to become our leader.
He can only obey me.
So, my lord,
you’ve planned for this all along.
But now, you need Yu Si Feng
to enter Demon Citadel.
I’m afraid he won’t do so.
Even I can’t enter Demon Citadel now.
Yu Si Feng is our only chance
because he has the 12 Feathers bloodline.
I wouldn’t have kept him alive
if it weren’t for that.
The chains trapping Wu Zhi Qi
will only show up when Fenru City’s gate
open on the 15th day of next month.
I’m sure he’ll agree before that.
Yes.
My lord, I have another favor
to ask of you.
I hope you can help me.
My sister is not feeling well lately.
Can I...
Do you think this is the time for that?
What you need to do now is to
monitor Chu Xuan Ji’s movement
so that I can acquire her powers.
- Yes.
- After you complete your task,
I will arrange for you two to reunite.
Yes.
Now, we need to think of a way
to deal with Chu Xuan Ji.
You two weren’t even here
when I was still in Lize Palace!
What’s going on?
Old Luo! It’s me, Liu Yi Huan!
Why have you returned?
Can’t I even pay my condolences
to the old palace lord?
These two scoundrels wouldn’t let me in!
I was an elder too, you know?
Old Luo, help me out.
Let him in.
- But the new palace lord said...
- No buts!
Old Luo, you have a short temper,
but you’re helping me out today.
What a rare sight.
I’ll treat you to a drink next time.
Si Feng is close with you.
I hope you can console him.
Where’s that chap?
He’s at the wake in our Clan Hall.
Today is the seventh day
after his passing.
It’s time for him to come out. Follow me.
It has been seven days.
It’s time for us to bury his coffin.
Wait! I haven’t pay my respects yet!
Palace Lord!
I’m here to pay my respects.
Why did you leave us like that?
I still have many things
left unsaid, you know?
Palace Lord!
I’m here to wail.
And I’m very shy.
You wait outside.
Hurry!
Will you cry for me if I can’t cry later?
Those who are outside can leave as well.
Palace Lord!
Brother Liu.
Are you here to pay your condolences?
Of course not. I’m here to find you.
I’m here to find you.
Purple Fox has a message for you.
Xuan Ji wants to meet you at Qingmu Town
by 7 a.m. tomorrow.
Xuan Ji?
She’s willing to meet me?
Why should I lie to you?
Both of you are suffering
because of each other.
Since you’re suffering, why don’t you
meet her and explain everything?
So, are you going or not?
Look at you.
You’ve been here the entire
day, staring at that stupid hairpin.
Fine then.
Stinky woman, if you miss Little Chef
that much, you should find him.
Honestly speaking, he’s a great cook.
I’m sure he’s not a bad guy.
Senior Xuan Ji.
A lady wearing a purple dress
wanted me to give you this lantern.
Thank you.
7 A.M., QINGMU TOWN
- Flying Snake.
- What are you doing?
Hey, do you want to try every food
around Shaoyang Peak?
Of course I do.
Okay. Do me a favor first.
It’s 7 a.m. already.
Why isn’t Xuan Ji here yet?
I’ve sent the lantern to Shaoyang Sect.
Xuan Ji will definitely come.
How could you be sure?
What if she changes her mind?
That’s possible as well.
You’re such a wet blanket.
Don’t speak. Just wait and see.
What’s with your face?
I learned how to cook this
from my neighbor.
This is my first time cooking it.
Si Feng, you must eat more.
So, this is how it feels like
to love someone.
Please don’t scare me anymore, okay?
Please don’t ever leave me.
Xuan Ji, I will stay by your side forever.
Forever.
Si Feng, you’re even jealous
of my spirit beast?
So what if I’m jealous?
I can be jealous of anyone.
Next time, I want a kiss as consolation
We shouldn’t see each other
in the first place.
If my father knows about this,
he’ll be disappointed in me.
Let’s speak like this.
I’m sorry.
I’ve always wanted to tell you the truth.
It must’ve been shocking for you.
Why did you hide it from me then?
Why didn’t you tell me the truth?
I’ve always wanted to
tell you my true identity.
But everything happened at the same time
before I got the chance to
tell you the truth.
I swear, this is the only
thing that I’ve hidden from you.
But that is
the most important thing to me.
Si Feng, what I
only care about is
the fact that the person I trust the most
had deceived me, you understand?
Xuan Ji,
I’m sorry.
I will never deceive you in the future.
Nor will I
hide anything else from you.
Let me ask you this.
How much did you know
about Yuan Lang’s scheme?
And did you participate in his scheme?
Yuan Lang?
Are you talking about
the Right Lieutenant?
Was he involved in this as well?
Yuan Lang is the vice palace lord
of Lize Palace.
He’s the leader of Sky Hall as well.
Purple Fox discovered that.
So, that’s the case.
It’s no wonder
he’s acting so mysteriously.
Yuan Lang wants to save Wu Zhi Qi
by using the spirit keys.
And he wants to revive the Star of Mosha.
Did you participate in his scheme?
I have never participated in his scheme.
We were on the same page
before Dianjinggu Sect
held the Flower Session.
I didn’t know Lize Palace was involved
in Sky Hall’s evil scheme.
I didn’t know about their plans.
I didn’t even know that
my master was my father.
I knew something was wrong
during the night before Flower Session.
My father was used by Vice Palace Lord.
I tried to trap them,
but in the end,
I still failed.
I know.
Everything I’m saying now
seems like an excuse to you.
But Xuan Ji,
can you believe in me?
I believe in you.
So,
can I see your face?
No!
Two of them finally have the chance
to see each other.
But why aren’t they hugging each other?
I don’t understand.
An old fox like you doesn’t know anything
about mortals.
This is the delight of life.
Staring at each other
with passionate eyes.
You’re jealous, aren’t you?
Little Phoenix is
an affectionate man indeed.
It’s tough being a mortal.
But he still insists on being one.
Wu Zhi Qi told me before
that being a mortal is great.
The mortal realm is prosperous,
filled with blue skies and white clouds.
Full of songs and dances,
filled with amazing events.
It’s a dazzling realm.
But I think that’s not important.
Si Feng.
I do believe in you.
But
that doesn’t mean
everything has been solved.
That time,
I witnessed my mother’s death personally!
She was burned to death by deadly anguish!
And your father was the murderer!
If you were in my shoes,
could you treat it as if
nothing has happened?
My father,
he did commit too many mistakes
due to his obsession.
And now,
he’s dead because of it.
But Xuan Ji, my father
didn’t murder your mother.
Yuan Lang, the vice palace lord,
murdered her.
Yuan Lang?
What did you say just now?
Say that again.
Yuan Lang admitted that himself.
I know I have no prove.
And Shaoyang Sect won’t believe me
without any prove.
You said your mother
was burned to death.
I think I know how to
investigate this matter now.
Xuan Ji, please give me some time.
I will get to the bottom of this.
And I’ll bring the true culprit to you.
By that time,
I will stand in front of you.
And you can punish me however you want
for my deceit.
I won’t punish you!
Si Feng, I don’t need you to do anything!
I just want you to leave Lize Palace
and stay with me!
I want you to return to Shaoyang Sect with
me so that my father can believe in you!
As for the true culprit, we
can just investigate it together!
Xuan Ji.
Now, I can’t just
do nothing about the situation.
Before my father passed away,
he told me to
protect the members of our clan
in Lize Palace.
Now, Yuan Lang is the new palace lord.
If I leave,
he’ll manipulate my clan members
and use them as killing machines.
My clan isn’t evil.
So,
I can’t just leave them behind.
Can you really change them?
What if, one day,
you become as evil as
the demons of Sky Hall?
If that does happen,
please kill me.
Kill you?
You want me to kill you?
Do you know this?
Every sect knows that
I’m the God of War now.
And they want me to lead them
to exterminate the demons.
Lize Palace is the first thing
on their mind!
Lize Palace and Sky Hall had killed
too many people in Dianjinggu Sect.
Their sins will never be undone!
I can’t,
and I won’t stop hunting Lize Palace
just because you say that
not all demons in Lize Palace are evil!
When my sword points toward Lize Palace,
when my Dingkun Sword points at your face,
what do you want me to do by then?
Are you going to fight me?
Xuan Ji.
I’m sorry.
I’ve made things difficult for you.
But can you
not sever our ties right away?
Please give me more time.
Let me drive Yuan Lang away
and take over Lize Palace.
After that, I will give
the sects an answer.
And I’ll bear the sins of Lize Palace.
I just hope that
you can wait for me.
Let me think about it.
I’ll give you an answer tomorrow.
Okay.
I’ll wait for your answer.
But Xuan Ji, remember this.
No matter what you choose,
you will never change in my heart.
Why did Xuan Ji run away while crying?
Did the deal go wrong?
Are you sure you’re a Rose Gold Bird?
You’re more like a crow.
Just shut up.
Master and the rest
had returned to Shaoyang Sect.
It’s bad for us to go there now.
Don’t worry about Xuan Ji.
I’m sure everyone will take care of her.
I’ll buy some noodles in front.
Why don’t you go to the fabric store
and see if there’s anything
you want to buy?
We’ll decorate our home together later.
Okay.
Take care. Please come again.
Miss, please have a look inside.
Goodbye.
Shopkeeper.
Miss, what kind of fabric
are you looking for?
Is there anything I can use
to make a bed sheet?
Yes.
Valley Master insisted on
sending us here to follow Shaoyang Sect.
He wants us to follow the God of War.
We left in a hurry. We don’t even
have time to pack our clothes.
Shopkeeper.
Hello, gentlemen.
Do you sell silk cloth here?
Of course we do.
But please wait a moment.
I need to give this to that lady.
Wait.
I think this fabric is quite good.
It’s suitable for us.
Wrap it up for us.
Sir, that lady had placed
an order before you.
I thought it was someone else.
So, it’s the young lady of Shaoyang Sect.
Wait.
I heard that she has been
kicked out of the sect.
What was the reason again?
- Shopkeeper.
- Miss.
Thank you, miss.
Didn’t you hear me?
This fabric is ours.
Step aside.
She’s scary, huh?
Why didn’t you act like this
while you were together with demons?
You only like demons?
Humans are not that bad, you know?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Look.
Don’t fight!
You thought you were a real young lady?
In our eyes, you’re worse than
a village girl.
Even village girls know how to
keep their chastity intact.
Shut up!
This is my mouth.
I can say anything I want.
Moreover, you had fooled around
with demons before.
Are you afraid people might tease you?
Are you tired of living?
Look who’s here.
It’s Zhong Min Yan,
the traitor of Shaoyang Sect.
Seems like you’re
the only guy in the world
who will fall for
a woman like Chu Ling Long.
Scram!
Let’s go.
Ling Long, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Ling Long!
Do you remember what I’ve said before?
You didn’t do anything wrong.
Don’t torture yourself
because of their words.
But in the end, I still hear their words.
I’m not the past me anymore.
I can’t hide from them.
In my eyes, you’re Chu Ling
Long, the person I love the most.
There’s no difference
between the past and the present you.
Ling Long, I’m beside you.
You don’t need to hide.
Do you know
what I dream of
every night?
It’s Wu Tong.
It’s like he was implanted in my brain!
I can’t avoid him!
There’s no place for me to hide!
Ling Long, that’s not you.
Don’t think about it anymore.
But the images I see
are so clear and vivid.
I can’t avoid him.
I can’t avoid him!
Ling Long, I’m here.
Don’t be afraid.
I will help you to forget him.
Ling Long.
I’m here.
Don’t be afraid.
I’m around.
Ling Long.
If you stay by my side, you’ll be
despised no matter where you go.
Unless I die,
I’ll never be able
to escape Wu Tong.
I’m sorry.
See you in my next life.
Ling Long.
Ling Long!
- What happened?
- Master.
Ling Long is missing.
- How did that happen?
- She was teased in town yesterday.
And she left without a word this morning.
Master, please help me find Ling Long.
Lead my men and search the area.
- Okay. All of you, follow me.
- Yes.
Sect Leader.
Your injuries haven’t healed yet.
You better rest.
Ling Long is a generous
and forgiving girl.
What exactly did she suffer?
How did this happen?
- Senior!
- Ling Long!
- Senior Ling Long!
- Senior!
Ling Long, where are you?
- Senior, where are you?
- Ling Long!
- Senior!
Where is Senior Ling Long?
In the past, she would hide in places
we couldn’t find when she was angry.
We never found her.
I’m such a fool.
- Senior!
Duanjin Sword,
I’ve embarrassed Shaoyang Sect.
I’ll leave you here
so that you can slay more demons
and atone for my sins.
- Ling Long!
- Let me go!
Can’t I even choose to end my life
over such a terrible fate?
Chu Ling Long!
I thought you were only willful.
But I didn’t expect you
to be this selfish!
Think about this carefully.
How did you manage to stay alive
after you were captured by Sky Hall?
I risked my life to save you.
Second Senior sacrificed his life for you.
Do you think you can die
when you feel like it?
Did you even ask me for my permission?
Don’t you think you’re letting down
our Second Senior?
You love to serve justice
ever since you were young.
But now, some other people
are committing misdeeds.
Why didn’t you go and punish them?
Why are you trying to punish us
with your death instead?
Are you trying to let your father,
Xuan Ji and I suffer forever?
- It’s not that.
- If you want to die, fine.
I’ll die as well.
I’ll die in front of you.
I’ll let you know how it feels like
to see your loved ones die before you.
No! Min Yan! No!
Min Yan!
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry!
Please don’t die.
Ling Long.
I will always stay by your side
no matter what happens to you.
Please don’t leave me behind.
You can’t just sacrifice our happiness
because of something that didn’t happen,
okay?
Okay.
She’s fine. She’s unconscious
because she was grieving too much.
She’ll be fine after a few days.
It’s all thanks to Min Yan.
It’s lucky that he found her in time.
If not, she would’ve...
We’ll let Xuan Ji accompany her.
Maybe she’ll feel better that way.
Where’s Xuan Ji?
This is a huge matter.
But Xuan Ji is not around at all.
Didn’t you tell her?
- Where’s Xuan Ji?
- Don’t touch me.
Can I say that I don’t know?
Tell me!
Qingmu Town.
I was actually frightened by a mortal.
Is Xuan Ji’s senior that scary
in the first place?
Little Phoenix is pitiful indeed.
His father just died and Xuan Ji
may become his enemy in the future.
The heavens are truly messing with him.
He’s the 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
I think he was influenced by sentiments
as he has been here for too long.
If he wants to be a demon,
he should learn from Wu Zhi Qi.
If I were Si Feng,
I would’ve eloped with Xuan Ji.
The survival of Lize Palace
has nothing to do with me.
It’s easy for you to say.
Let me ask you.
Si Feng chased after Xuan Ji
in his previous nine lives,
but did he ever complain about it?
This time, he just wanted her to
wait for a while, yet she’s unhappy.
She even wanted Si Feng to follow her back
and apologize to the other sects.
Being virtuous will cause him
his life, you know?
Let me ask you this then.
Did the Rose Gold Bird clan
kill Xuan Ji’s mother?
Did the Rose Gold Bird
hurt Xuan Ji’s father?
Did the Rose Gold Bird clan
slay many of their people?
If I were Xuan Ji, I would only be happy
if all of them were dead.
Now, she only wants Si Feng to follow her.
She’s very magnanimous.
She wants her to leave?
Tell me, where else can he go?
You said this yourself.
The vice palace lord is Yuan Lang,
the leader of Sky Hall.
Now that he has all four spirit keys,
the three realms will be in turmoil soon.
Yet you’re asking him to leave Lize Palace
and elope with Xuan Ji?
- What did you say?
- What?
Yuan Lang has obtained
all four spirit keys?
Yes.
The three realms will be in turmoil soon.
Let’s cherish our remaining days.
Yuan Lang is devious.
He’ll surely trick Wu Zhi Qi again.
I need to steal the spirit keys somehow.
- Senior?
- Why are you here alone?
You don’t need to tell me why.
You’re here to meet Yu Si Feng, right?
I just wanted to clarify things with him.
You saw his true form, the
12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird personally.
He had deceived you for so long,
yet you still wanted to
clarify things with him?
Senior.
Si Feng...
Although he’s a demon,
he has never hurt anyone.
I believe in him.
You knew that he’s a demon,
yet you’re still trying to defend him?
Xuan Ji, when will you stop
being so naive?
Do you think he’s really in the
dark about Lize Palace’s scheme?
- Si Feng is...
- Enough!
I didn’t expect you to not know
what’s good or evil.
You even ignored the basic rules
of being a cultivator!
And you came to meet that demon in secret.
Xuan Ji.
I’m too disappointed in you.
Fine.
I’ll sever your ties with him now.
Senior, I’m sorry for this.
Xuan Ji.
You actually attacked me
because of a demon.
Senior, I’m sorry.
I don’t want to do this.
Please don’t force me.
Fine.
Since you’ve brought out
your Ninth Heaven Fire,
there’s no way for me to defeat you.
Just forget it.
But I didn’t expect you
to use the God of War’s
power just to protect a demon.
Ling Long’s reputation was ruined
because of a demon.
And she almost committed suicide
because of it.
Yet you’re here, fighting against me
because of a demon.
Committed suicide?
What’s going on?
Is Ling Long okay? What exactly happened?
Although her life is not in danger,
her reputation was ruined.
I’m afraid the trauma in her heart
will never disappear.
Ling Long.
I’ll look for Ling Long right away.
Si Feng, wait for me.
Ling Long!
Xuan Ji.
Why are you so silly? Are you trying to
leave both Father and I behind?
I’m sorry.
How could you do such a silly thing
because of a villain like that?
What about Father and I?
Sixth Senior will be very sad, you know?
Xuan Ji, I’ve thought about it.
I won’t do silly things anymore.
I will stay alive and
take my revenge against Wu Tong.
I will make him pay for all
the humiliations I’ve faced.
I’ll avenge you.
I won’t let Wu Tong or
anyone from Sky Hall off.
And Si Feng as well.
Si Feng is with them.
You mustn’t show him mercy.
Ling Long, Si Feng has nothing to do
with Sky Hall.
Why didn’t he return with you
if he was innocent?
He...
It’s because he’s
busy with something.
Xuan Ji.
Don’t fall for his tricks again.
He’s just trying to acquire your trust.
He’s trying to find another chance.
No! Si Feng isn’t a person like that!
He told me that the only thing
he lied to me was his identity.
That’s the only thing he lied to me.
I believe in him.
Xuan Ji, he’s a demon.
Even if he’s not a part of Sky Hall,
you two won’t end well together.
I’m your sister. You should listen to me.
The people will forsake
those who affiliate
themselves with demons.
I’ve embarrassed Father and Shaoyang Sect.
You mustn’t disappoint Father anymore.
You’re the only one
he could depend on now.
You mustn’t disappoint him.
You mustn’t follow my steps.
I won’t go anywhere.
I’ll stay here and accompany you.
I’ll stay here. I won’t meet Si Feng.
If Si Feng did commit
those atrocious deeds,
I will never let him off.
But
if he’s innocent,
please give him
another chance, okay?