LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 9
You’re wearing this mask because of me.
But don’t worry, I’ll find a way to
remove the Loveless Mask for you.
I told you before. This was my decision.
Brother Liu, you don’t
need to blame yourself.
To become emotionless and focus on
my training is a good thing as well.
How is that a good thing?
Our training is hard enough by itself.
But now, you have to
force yourself to be emotionless as well.
That’ll make your life meaningless,
you know?
It’s not a good thing.
It’s fine. Don’t worry.
I’ll definitely find a solution for you.
By the way,
come out now.
Come out.
I’ll return you your spirit beast.
Ascending the Heavenly Realm
was tough indeed.
Silver Snake, you were naughty.
Thank you, Brother Liu.
Why are you thanking me?
Okay.
I’ll leave now.
Xuan Ji, are you done with your training?
Ling Long.
Isn’t this the bell Si Feng gave you?
I’m sure you kept in touch, right?
How is he doing?
Senior Hao Chen confiscated
everything I had when I went to
Xuyang Peak.
That’s why I didn’t contact him
for four years.
You didn’t contact him at all?
Xuan Ji, before Si Feng left,
he wanted you to contact him
once you woke up, you know?
Besides, even if he did
confiscate everything,
you could still write him letters.
Write letters?
I was busy with my training every day.
I never thought about that.
You’re too heartless.
Did you forget him already?
And you never contacted me as
well after you went to Xuyang Peak.
I would’ve severed my ties with you
if you weren’t my sister.
Ling Long, how could that be?
I missed you so much.
But I think it’s fine
if I keep you all in my heart.
Besides, sisters and our friends
will stay with us forever, right?
Initially, I wanted
to finish my training
as soon as possible so that
I could meet up with you sooner.
Same goes for Si Feng as well.
We made a promise.
We’ll train together once
I leave the mountain.
That’s why I didn’t contact him
for four years.
That doesn’t matter, right?
But Xuan Ji, you need to
maintain your relationships.
No one will wait at the same spot for you.
I thought you would’ve
learnt about other things
besides your training.
I didn’t expect you to still be
a blockhead in relationships.
Ling Long, will Si Feng be angry
because I didn’t contact him?
Will he ignore me?
About that, I
can’t say for sure.
I’m sure he won’t do that.
Si Feng must be very busy in Lize Palace.
He needs to train as well.
I’m sure he forgot about this
due to his busy schedule.
It’s fine. I’ll find him immediately
after we leave Mount Shaoyang.
And the four of us
can roam the world together.
I’m sure it would be fun.
Have some fruit wine.
Great wine.
Xuan Ji, I didn’t ask this before
because it was inconvenient.
Did you find any shards
when you went to Xuyang Peak?
It’s fine. Maybe we could find them
when we roam around.
Sixth Senior, I’ll stop finding them.
Senior Hao Chen told me that
everyone has a different purpose in life.
And I should treat it as such.
I should be protecting
the Mirror of Origin
instead of searching for them
in order to recover my six senses.
What if I become obsessed with it?
Is that so?
Did the strange power appear again
during your training?
That’s good. We won’t look for it then.
Oh right, Sixth Senior, I
have some good stuff for you.
There’s an immortal tree on Xuyang Peak.
Its fruit is delicious.
But it only bears fruit once
every five years.
That’s why I’ve saved some
for you, Ling Long, and Si Feng.
You little glutton.
You actually saved some for us?
Not bad at all. Seems like
my efforts were not in vain.
You’re unlike your sister at all.
I have no idea
what she’s thinking about.
- Min Yan!
- Ling Long...
Ling Long is going to dance
with a fellow male disciple!
Sixth Senior, what about this?
Xuan Ji, your senior doesn’t
like the drink and the fruit.
I’ll take them for myself.
I...
My lord, after the failure of
Shadow Demon in Shaoyang Sect,
we’ve planted spies in the four sects
successfully.
But, due to Shadow Demon’s failure,
and to avoid any further
suspicions, I think we should
stay in the shadows for now.
We should wait for the right time
to grab the spirit keys.
We still need to wait?
How long do I need to wait?
My lord, we...
Who’s there?
You didn’t manage to locate
the God of War and the Star of Mosha
these few years,
and you didn’t obtain
the spirit keys as well.
Wolf, aren’t you too merciful?
Isn’t that the reason
you got nothing done at all?
Wu Tong, do you think you have
the right to speak in this place?
Our lord is keeping you here
because he just wanted you to tell us
more about the Five Great Sects.
Just be a good dog.
When you’re a dog,
you shouldn’t just come out
and bark like this.
The Sky Hall only appreciates
capable people.
Those who got nothing done
should just keep quiet.
Wolf, what do you think?
I just didn’t want to reveal
our true strength too soon.
My lord, I just wanted
to avoid casualties
from dealing with the Five Great Sects.
The demon tribe has been
training in secret for 1,000 years.
Your strength is much greater
than the Five Great Sects.
If they aren’t willing to
cooperate with us,
it’s the best excuse for us
to execute them without mercy.
Why should we hide?
You’re just trying to get your revenge
against the humans who had driven you out.
Wu Tong, don’t try to manipulate
us due to your personal hatred.
It’s precisely because of that.
Only a human knows how to
force another human to submit.
To manipulate and destroy them.
My lord,
why don’t you give me this chance?
I’ll destroy the Five Great Sects
and obtain the spirit keys.
My lord, Wu Tong is just a dog
who has been driven out from its shelter.
We mustn’t trust him.
But this pathetic dog managed to find out
that the Xuanyuan Sect is lying to you.
- What?
- Someone!
You were misled by
Xuanyuan Sect’s spirit stone all along.
One of the spirit keys was actually
hidden inside the Destiny Pearl.
You didn’t know about that.
Tell us.
Yes!
The spirit key is hidden inside
the Destiny Pearl in our sect.
But only Sect Leader Zhu Shi knows about
the location of the Destiny Pearl.
Wolf, you chose the
wrong person to threaten.
Instead of threatening those
who are loyal to the sect,
isn’t it easier for you if you threaten
the weaklings in the sect?
Darn it.
My lord, please give me a chance.
Let me obtain the spirit keys for you.
We’ve been hiding for too long.
It’s time to create a scene so
that our prey would be attracted.
Wu Tong, from today onwards,
you’ll be the leader of
Mount Buzhou’s hideout.
The Five Great Sects
can’t reach Mount Buzhou.
You don’t need to fear anything.
You don’t need to fear
the Five Great Sects.
You can use any method
to obtain the spirit keys.
Yes, my lord.
The Sky Hall has been
in the shadows for too long.
It’s time for us to make an entrance.
Greetings, Master, Vice Palace Lord.
Si Feng, you’ve
mastered your skill.
I’m very relieved to hear that.
You were always the most talented.
As long as you aren’t distracted
and focus on your training,
I’m sure you’ll be the leader
of the Five Great Sects.
You’ll take over Lize Palace
sooner or later.
My lord, your effort wasn’t wasted.
It’s good that you forced him
to choose this mask.
Yu Si Feng,
you mustn’t disappoint your
master and repeat the same mistakes.
Let bygones be bygones.
Just forget about them.
I’m just reminding him.
Although the Loveless Mask
can render him emotionless
and stops him from having any feelings,
if he faces a situation where
he couldn’t control himself
and feels for someone,
a Loveless Curse will form
and he’ll be done for.
You only talk about useless things.
Si Feng, you do understand the
purpose of the Loveless Mask, right?
By getting rid of emotions, it will
save us from unnecessary trouble.
That’s good to hear.
And you must remember that
outsiders
are just like mirages.
Your only home is Lize Palace.
Yes, my lord...
I’m not finished yet.
All of you mustn’t risk
your lives for an illusion
that you cannot hold.
And create unnecessary trouble.
- Yes, master.
That’s enough.
Let’s return to the main point.
- Vice Palace Lord.
- Do you understand what to do?
Once you exit the palace tomorrow,
you should never break the rules.
I’ve received letters from Shaoyang Sect.
They stated that some demons
are causing trouble outside.
Coincidentally, you
will leave the palace soon.
Investigate the matter as well.
Those demons have
nothing to do with us.
They can’t reach Xiyang on either side.
If they want to create trouble
in Zhongyuan, just let them be.
Senior, you’re ignoring
everything except for our sect.
But you must respect
the other sect leaders as well.
Since we belong to
one of the Five Great Sects.
You make the shot.
Investigate the matter.
Yes.
Xuan Ji, you have
the Transmission Charm with you.
Do you know your task
when you leave the mountain?
- What’s my task?
- Silly Xuan Ji.
Senior Hao Chen wants you
to write letters to him.
But Senior Hao Chen,
we’ll be busy when we leave.
She’ll think it’s troublesome.
Or maybe she’ll forget about it.
Remember to write letters to me.
You’re pure and innocent.
You haven’t recovered your six senses.
The outside world is complex and chaotic.
I was reluctant to let you go,
but I have to abide by the rules.
If not...
So, after you leave, you need
to report to me every single detail.
Firstly, you can reflect on your progress.
Secondly, I can know
your progress as well.
Do you understand?
Yes, Senior Hao Chen.
You must be careful.
You two must remember this.
After you two leave the mountain,
you must deal with situations
according to your own capability.
You two mustn’t be reckless.
Xuan Ji, remember to listen to
your Sixth Senior.
Ling Long, you must
control your temper as well.
Father, I know that.
It’s the first time
you two are leaving here.
Your father is worried.
You must remember his words.
Yes, I’ll remember them. I’ll leave now.
You!
This child...
Father, Aunt Ying Hong, Senior Hao Chen,
don’t worry. We know what to do.
Master, Aunt Ying Hong, don’t worry.
I’ll take good care of them.
- Ling Long, wait for us!
- Ling Long!
Wait for me!
This is so beautiful!
We finally left the mountain!
This is too beautiful!
Senior Hao Chen, we
had another uneventful day.
Today, Sixth Senior ordered
a dish that was not tasty
at a restaurant on Mount Mengxi.
It’s not delicious?
Fine, we won’t order that tomorrow.
We can save some money as well.
This is great!
We’ll go to Xishu tomorrow.
There are many delicious food over there.
There are pork trotter jelly,
cold noodles, and peppered chicken.
You’re going to finish our money soon.
We can only depend on Si Feng
in Lize Palace later on.
We’ve been out for seven days.
But there are no demons to be seen.
I don’t feel like a hero at all.
Look at the letters Xuan Ji
wrote for Senior Hao Chen.
I’m so happy today.
I’ve eaten a lot today.
Okay, we’ve finished
our mission for today.
- Let’s go.
- Okay.
Senior Hao Chen, we
had another uneventful day.
Today, Sixth Senior ordered
a dish that was not tasty
at a restaurant on Mount Mengxi.
It’s lucky that the vegetables
were delicious.
I’m happy today.
Where are we? We should ask someone.
Excuse me.
Sorry for the interruption.
Judging by your attire,
I’m sure you are cultivators.
Do you know how long it will take
for us to reach Mount Shaoyang?
Mister, are you going to Mount Shaoyang
because there are demons around?
Yes.
We came from Wangxian Town.
Demons are wreaking havoc
in our town these days.
They cried in the middle of the night.
All of us were too afraid to go out.
This situation has lasted for
three months. This can’t continue on.
After that, a wandering priest
told us that
Shaoyang Sect is famous
for slaying demons.
That’s why we’re trying to
seek their help.
Wangxian Town?
We need to pass by there before
we reach Lize Palace and Xuanyuan Sect.
We can meet Si Feng
after we slay the demons.
This is great! We finally
have demons to slay!
Mister, we have decided
to slay the demons for you.
But...
You three are?
We’re members of the Shaoyang Sect.
This is our name tag.
Mister, please tell us more
about the demons.
We will try our best to help.
I think you are too young.
These two ladies look
very fresh and innocent.
I think you shouldn’t
sacrifice your lives for this.
I think we should seek for
your master’s help instead.
- Goodbye.
- Wait!
Mister, wait a minute.
We may look young, but we’re
famous in the pugilist world.
Especially this girl.
She may look weak and feeble,
but she can slay
dozens of demons at one go.
Dozens of demons?
- They’re pretty good.
- Sixth Senior,
since when could I slay dozens of demons?
You defeated Shadow Demon
and his clones, right?
That’s a different matter!
This is a rare chance.
We should grab hold of it.
I’m her senior.
As for her,
she’s not important.
Little Six!
We came down the mountain
in order to slay demons.
You don’t need to
travel far to seek help.
Since that’s the case, please help us out.
In Wangxian Town, there’s Mount Haiwan.
On that mountain, there’s a grass
called Zhuyu Grass.
And only our town has that grass.
But the strange thing is
it can’t be planted.
It can only grow on its own.
But three months ago,
some of our townsfolk went
to pick some Zhuyu Grass.
But all of them were
devoured by demons.
After that, some brave youngsters
went up the mountain as well.
But they never came back.
Mister, do you have any idea
what the demon looks like?
The demon always assaulted
people from the back.
That’s why nobody
has seen their true face.
I have a grandson
who only learnt how to speak recently.
Two days ago, he said
he saw a demon that cried.
It cries, it has two huge talons,
and it can fly as well.
But he’s just a child. I don’t think
we should treat this seriously.
It has wings,
and it cries as well?
Isn’t that scary?
Ling Long, look.
From the Demon Manual, a
demon who cries and has wings,
- it is a Quru Bird?
- Quru Bird?
But it didn’t state that the demon
likes to eat Zhuyu Grass.
Is it possible that someone is behind this
in order to obtain more provision?
Since that’s the case, we must act now.
Let’s check it out.
We must be cautious later on.
It’s just a Quru Bird.
Since it likes to eat, I’ll give it
a taste of my power.
I’m sure there are more than one of them.
We must be careful.
Even ten of them won’t scare me away.
It’s really desolate here.
Of course. There are demons
roaming around.
The Zhuyu Grass is pretty fragrant.
Ling Long, it’s such a waste
since Zhuyu Grass is delicious.
Xuan Ji, it’s dirty, you know?
Why are you eating it?
- Ling Long, it’s delicious. Try it.
- No way.
- Sixth Senior?
- I’ll skip this time.
Silly girl.
Ling Long, look.
The cuts are uneven.
I don’t think this is caused
by something sharp.
It looks like it was ripped.
You’re right.
- Look here.
- Seems like we’re facing a tough demon.
Little Six, why are you so timid?
- You’re afraid of this?
- You!
I smell a demon.
Watch out!
- It’s the Quru Bird!
- It has escaped!
Let’s chase after it!
What a strong demonic scent!
I smell that too.
It’s thick and disgusting.
It stinks!
It’s dark down there.
We don’t have a clear view.
- Xuan Ji!
- Ling Long, be careful!
Ling Long, are you okay?
I’m fine. You must be careful.
Little Six!
Ling Long!
Ling Long, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Be careful!
- Xuan Ji!
Si Feng?
Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji!
Xuan Ji!
Why are you bleeding?
I’m fine.
Silly girl, you’re not fine.
I’m Ruo Yu from Lize Palace.
Greetings.
Si Feng will return later, right?
Miss, Si Feng is...
We’re his friends. This is great.
I didn’t expect to see him here.
You said you were his friends?
That is bizarre.
What’s bizarre?
I heard that the members of
Lize Palace weren’t supposed
to make friends with outsiders, right?
But Si Feng is different from others.
- There are no exceptions.
- Si Feng is an exception.
Si Feng!
Did you capture it?
The Quru Bird fled because
it was frightened.
It fled?
It’s all because of you three.
- You!
- Save your breath.
Ruo Yu, let’s go.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, is this really you?
You got yourself a new mask.
I almost couldn’t recognize you.
I thought my skills would’ve been
better after four years.
I thought I could protect everyone.
But I didn’t expect you
to improve this much.
You saved me once again.
Quru Birds hunt in groups.
We need a tactic to hunt them down.
Next time, you
better prepare yourselves.
Don’t create trouble for other people.
Si Feng, my brother, long time no see.
Si Feng, it’s been four years
since we have met.
We wanted to find you in Lize Palace.
Let go! All of you,
stay away from Si Feng!
You’re rude! Who exactly are you?
That is none of your concern.
Please calm down.
She is Miss Lu Yan Ran
from Dianjinggu Sect.
She was separated from her friends.
That’s why she’s travelling with us.
- We...
- We’re not here to save you.
We prepared an ambush for the demons.
We were waiting for them
to return to their nest.
But you just came
and went all out on them.
And that messed up our plan.
How should we know you have a plan?
You speak as if this is our fault.
Wasn’t it your fault?
Si Feng, since we didn’t
manage to find their nest,
we should return to our inn and rest.
Sure! Where are you staying?
We can stay together.
And we can travel together afterwards.
We’re not going on the same path.
Miss Xuan Ji, first, we need to help
Miss Lu find her friends.
So, it’s inconvenient for us
to travel together.
Please forgive us.
Save your breath. Let’s go.
Si Feng, are you leaving us?
We missed you.
And we’ve finally met after so long.
Please don’t leave.
That’s right. Why are you leaving us?
Si Feng, are you angry
at us because Xuan Ji
didn’t contact you at all?
Yes. Ling Long said you
must’ve been waiting for my news.
Si Feng, I’m sorry. It’s my fault.
- But the Sound Bell...
- No.
I lost mine as well.
It’s an useless item.
That’s good. I knew it.
Si Feng, you were so busy.
There’s no need for us
to contact each other, right?
- Since we’ll meet anyway.
- I’m busy indeed.
I won’t waste any time here.
- Si Feng!
- Everyone, farewell for now.
- Xuan Ji!
- Xuan Ji, what’s wrong?
What’s going on?
Xuan Ji was poisoned.
Wait, Quru Birds aren’t poisonous.
Si Feng, seems like
Miss Xuan Ji has a serious injury.
We...
Are we going to leave them for real?
Si Feng, I heard that your sect
is an expert in neutralising poison.
Are you really going to ignore her?
Little Six, will Xuan Ji be fine?
But the Demon Manual stated
that Quru Birds aren’t poisonous.
How did this happen?
You’re right.
That’s why we suspect that
someone is manipulating them.
And the manipulator must’ve applied
poison on their talons.
We would’ve captured that demon
if it weren’t for someone.
But in the end? We’re stuck here
because of them.
Such bad luck.
What do you mean by that?
Si Feng is our old friend.
We will travel together sooner or later.
And we still have plenty of things
to catch up as well.
You can leave if you don’t want to stay.
You are thinking too much.
Si Feng has nothing to catch up
with you.
Didn’t you see that?
He ignored you just now.
- You!
- To me, you are here because the Quru Birds are too strong
and you wanted to seek Si Feng’s help
to defeat them.
- You!
- Some people are useless by themselves.
That’s why they want to seek help
from Lize Palace.
I...
What?
Stop it now.
Si Feng.
Si Feng, don’t leave.
Don’t leave me.
I had just neutralized the poison.
You better not move around.
Si Feng, I know you’re angry.
I was too dumb.
When I went to Xuyang Peak
for my training with Senior Hao Chen,
he confiscated the Sound Bell you gave me
because he didn’t want me
to be distracted.
And I didn’t think of other ways
I could use to contact people.
That’s why I didn’t write one letter
to Ling Long nor Sixth Senior.
Ling Long was very angry with me.
You don’t need to explain that to me.
It’s fine even if
we didn’t contact each other.
Si Feng, why are you
still trying to leave?
We wanted to find you
in Lize Palace initially.
Isn’t it a great thing when
we meet each other here?
Why are you still insisting on leaving?
Why must we stay together?
Because we made a promise.
The four of us are
going to travel together, right?
So childish.
Is that so?
But after that, I realized that
nothing is permanent in this world.
Same goes for a friend’s promise.
Si Feng.
I don’t understand.
- Initially...
- I did promise you
that I’ll find the Mirror of Origin
with you initially.
And I will keep my promise.
I obtained one shard by accident.
Here.
Si Feng, I didn’t mean that.
And, regarding the Mirror of Origin,
I don’t need it
anymore.
Senior Hao Chen said that
I will become obsessed
with desire and
greed if I search for it.
It’s not good for my training.
So, I promised Senior Hao Chen
that I won’t search for it anymore
after I leave the mountain.
But Si Feng, I still need to thank you.
So,
you don’t want to recover
your six senses anymore.
I was born without them.
I think it’s fine even if
I don’t recover them.
They don’t seem that important to me.
The current Chu Xuan Ji isn’t
that bad anyway, am I right?
The human heart is indecisive
and unstable.
I’ve witnessed it for myself.
Si Feng, what did you say?
Since it’s useless to you,
that means we don’t need to meet anymore.
Farewell.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, don’t leave us!
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji, why are you here?
Si Feng, did you neutralize the poison?
She can move after some rest.
You may leave after some time.
We’ll handle the Quru Birds. Let’s go.
- Wait, Si Feng.
- Si Feng.
What do you mean by this?
Aren’t we your companions?
That’s right. I thought we were going to
capture them together?
There’s no need for this many people.
It’s troublesome.
That’s not the point.
Si Feng, I thought
this is a happy occasion?
But why are you treating us
like the plague?
You’re trying to avoid us.
Si Feng, what’s wrong with you?
Si Feng, there’s no need for explanations.
Let’s go.
Si Feng!
What’s going on?
Why are they approaching us?
There are so many of them!
There are too many of them!
Set up the barrier!
Why are there so many Quru Birds?
Didn’t you say someone
was manipulating them?
They’re still not leaving
even after the barrier was set up.
I’m afraid they’re trying to trap us here.
You won’t be trapped
if you’re capable enough to break through.
Hero Zhong, you’re quite skilled.
But it’s hard when you have
two amateurs around.
Stop looking down on us!
You can leave if you’re that capable!
We’ll deal with the birds and the demon
once Xuan Ji recovers her strength.
Miss Lu, it’s fine.
We can escape by ourselves.
Silly girl, she’s not saying that
out of concern!
These Quru Birds
all came out of their nests.
And their talons were coated with poison.
It’s too risky to try and break through.
Si Feng, what do you think?
We’ll just destroy their nest then.
- Are you going to use that?
- We must deal with the mastermind first.
It’s better for us to
end this fast as well.
Si Feng, what are you doing?
He’s going to cast the secret spell
of Lize Palace, Soul Chaser.
It can detect the location
of the culprit behind this.
Inside the palace,
among the stars,
chase the cursed soul,
with the speed of the wind.
Search!
- Si Feng!
- Si Feng, are you okay?
To the west, there are ten caves.
Take the middle cave,
and you’ll reach a valley.
The demon manipulating
the birds is located there.
I’ve injured the demon
and he can’t move around.
You can go and capture him.
Si Feng, we’ll let them go
since they wish to capture it so badly.
Your breathing is a mess.
You need to recuperate.
- I’ll stay here and guard over you.
- No need.
That demon is quite powerful.
All of you should go.
- But what if something...
- Stop wasting time!
If the demon flees,
I’ll blame it all on you.
Be careful then.
Send us a signal if you’re in danger.
Let’s go.
- Si Feng, you...
- Xuan Ji, let’s go.
I...
Si Feng, are you okay?
Why are you here?
I’ve thought about it.
I can’t leave you alone here.
I’ll stay by your side
until you get better.
No need.
Si Feng, you mustn’t rush
the recovery process.
Don’t move. It’s dangerous for you
to activate your energy by force.
Si Feng, why is your breathing
getting more and more unstable?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Are you in pain?
Why are you sweating so much?
This won’t do. I need to
transfer some of my energy to you.
- But your mask...
- Don’t touch it!
- I want to help you.
- You’re helping me by not touching it.
I knew it. Si Feng was still angry at me
for not contacting him.
What should I do to appease him?
Oh right, what did Sixth
Senior do every time
he makes Ling Long angry?
Si Feng.
Why are you sweating so much?
You’ll catch a cold.
Here.
What are you doing?
Si Feng, I’m wiping away your sweat.
You’ll catch a cold like this.
I’m not trying to scold you,
but you’re not taking care of yourself.
You can’t do anything without me around.
My sweat is gone.
Si Feng, this dried fruit is very sweet.
I can’t even bear to eat it.
I kept it specially for you.
Try it.
Chu Xuan Ji, what exactly
are you trying to do?
I... I’m trying to
make you happy.
I’m trying to coax you.
Please don’t be angry anymore.
Please don’t hold it against me.
Si Feng.
Isn’t this funny?
Si Feng, please smile.
You’ll get younger when you smile.
Si Feng.
Chu Xuan Ji, that’s enough.
Isn’t this funny?
Never mind. I have another trick.
Si Feng, let me tell you a joke.
Listen closely.
Once, there was a phoenix
who tried to attain nirvana.
Guess what happened in the end?
Listen carefully.
It overheated!
Isn’t it funny?
Si Feng, isn’t that funny?
It’s funny, right?
Answer me.
It’s not funny?
I have another trick up my sleeve.
Si Feng, look.
I’ve hidden a treasure in one of my hand.
Take a guess. If you’re
correct, I’ll give you the treasure.
You think it’s this hand, right?
You’re wrong. There’s nothing inside.
Are you done?
Si Feng, don’t be angry.
Although you’re wrong, I hate
it when our Si Feng gets angry.
So, even though you’re wrong,
I’ll still give you the treasure.
Are they nice?
Sixth Senior used this trick
every time when Ling Long was angry,
and he succeeds every time.
I like Sixth Senior.
Min Yan?
You like Min Yan?
Chu Xuan Ji, listen carefully.
I’m not angry.
You can stop your silly acts.
Si Feng, you’re not angry?
Why are you acting like this then?
Why did you change so much?
You don’t want us
to be your friends anymore?
Do you hate me now?
The pupils of Lize Palace weren’t
supposed to have friends anyway.
There’s nothing for me to like or hate.
Four years are a long time.
It’s normal for people to grow and change.
There’s no need to dwell on the past.
No, you weren’t like this in the past.
We had plenty of things
to talk about in the past.
And many things we could share.
You taught me many things as well.
Si Feng, you even told me that
meeting me was the best thing
that had happened in your life.
Although I was asleep,
I did hear what you say.
I was rash then.
I never think before I speak.
You mustn’t hold it to your heart.
- It’s meaningless.
- It’s not.
The past you, and everything you had said,
all of them were meaningful to me.
I don’t want our relationship to change.
Si Feng, I don’t want to lose you.