LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 47
You can’t do this to me.
Demon Lord.
I did everything for you!
For the past 1,000 years, I’ve
stayed loyal and endured hardships
for your sake!
Is that so?
But why do I only see ambition
in you instead of loyalty?
I did everything for you.
For you to conquer the three realms!
That does make you sound useful to me.
In that case,
since I am still of some
use to you, release me.
Unfortunately, I am not the Star of Mosha.
I won’t be needing you anymore.
You’ve been doubting me, haven’t you?
Blame your ambition for
blinding you and making you hasty.
You deceived me.
You deceived me too!
How dare you say I deceived you?
Don’t fall for his tricks.
We are brothers.
Don’t you remember, Old Wu?
We traveled across the
three realms, drank together
and serenaded together.
For the past 1,000 years,
in order to save you,
I’ve put in so much
blood, sweat and tears.
You can’t betray me!
You betrayed me first!
Why did the heavens
arrest me 1,000 years ago?
You think I don’t know it was you?
It was the God of War!
It’s not me!
Are you still denying the truth?
Yuan Lang.
Who instigated King Asura 1,000 years ago
to attack the heavens?
And when the attempt failed,
who decided to protect himself
by securing a celestial position
and selling me out to the heavens?
Listen, Yuan Lang.
I’m here to avenge my 1,000-year grudge!
Wu Zhi Qi.
You’ve finally avenged yourself.
We were brothers.
Why did we end up like this?
The Soul Furnace is vicious.
If it were used on Xuan Ji,
it would be catastrophic.
This isn’t right.
Why has Yuan Lang become so weak today?
Stupid Monkey.
Stop making yourself
sound all high and mighty.
Oh no, I’ve forgotten.
Yuan Lang knows clone magic.
Look there!
They must be attacking Shaoyang Sect now!
- Let’s go.
- Little Fox.
You shouldn’t follow us,
Si Feng and I can handle this.
Protect yourself.
O Vice Palace Lord.
Yu Si Feng.
Wu Zhi Qi!
How dare you ensnare me!
Did something go wrong with the formation?
Even if I haven’t received
power from the God of War,
I must take the Jade Cup first.
Then, I’d still have another chance.
I’m going to take the Jade Cup.
You two stand guard.
Make sure nothing happens.
Yes, my lord.
So many years have passed.
Aren’t you giving up yet?
My body is deteriorating day by day.
I may not last much longer.
I need to come up with a way quickly
for Xuan Ji to destroy the Jade Cup.
The Jade Cup.
An asura?
Weren’t the Asuras
exterminated 1,000 years ago?
I am merely borrowing this body
to take the Jade Cup.
Anyone who blocks my way shall die!
Hand it over.
As long as I am here,
you shall not prevail!
When you took the Vermilion Bird Bottle,
I’ve already had an idea of who you are.
Not many people in
the three realms are capable
of taking the mythical treasures
in the heavens.
Unfortunately, with your current
strength, you cannot defeat me!
Senior Hao Chen.
I’ve brought you some
wine from my wedding.
Senior Hao Chen.
Wine? What wine?
Wu Tong?
Don’t you dare wreak havoc
in Shaoyang Sect!
Why are you wearing a wedding robe?
Who are you marrying?
Don’t you know whom I’m marrying?
I, Zhong Min Yan,
will only marry Ling Long.
Ling Long will only marry me!
Ling Long is mine.
No one can snatch her away from me!
She’s mine!
- Min Yan!
- Ling Long!
Min Yan!
Don’t give chase.
You’re injured.
Ruo Yu.
You’re really alive.
So, what Si Feng said was all true.
And I treated you as my best friend.
You don’t deserve it!
Yes.
It was me who tricked you
to steal the spirit keys
and set Si Feng up.
Also, I was the one
who injured Elder Chu Ying Hong.
It wasn’t Si Feng.
So...
So it was you who injured
Elder Chu Ying Hong.
Min Yan.
Yes, I have done all wrong and sinned.
That’s why I cannot see you die today.
Wu Tong is already half-demon,
you can’t defeat him.
I’ll go.
I won’t let him get near Ling Long.
Min Yan.
Ruo Yu.
Listen carefully.
I’ll get you for everything you’ve done.
Min Yan!
Min Yan, come back!
You’ve always meddled in my business.
I shall not spare you!
Leave him to me.
I sense demonic aura.
Dingkun Sword!
Someone is taking the Jade Cup!
Min Yan, you’re back.
What took you so long
at Hao Chen’s place?
What are you waiting for?
Remove my veil.
My dear Ling Long.
Are you so eager for me to unveil you?
Scram.
Scram off!
I was the one who unveiled you.
You are now my bride.
I’m bringing you back home.
Why are you still haunting me?
Put me down!
Scram!
Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- Wu Tong!
Let go of Ling Long!
Min Yan.
Min Yan!
Ling Long.
Zhong Min Yan.
Ling Long won’t follow me because of you.
As long as you’re dead,
Ling Long will be all mine!
No.
Don’t kill him. Min Yan!
Min Yan!
Let’s see how you can stop me now.
Dream on.
Don’t you ever take
Ling Long away from me!
Min Yan.
Let go of him.
You’d kill yourself like this.
Wu Tong.
Please let go of him.
I beg you.
I’ll follow you back.
Please let go of him.
Don’t hurt him anymore.
I beg you.
Ling Long, don’t beg him.
Ling Long.
To think you will follow me
back just for him.
Fine.
I’ll still kill him anyway
so you’ll give up on him!
No!
Min Yan.
- I’m sorry.
- I will be back to marry you.
Father.
Min Yan.
Min Yan, how are you?
Ling Long.
Don’t be scared.
I will always stay by your side.
Min Yan!
Min Yan, wake up!
It’s our wedding night.
You can’t leave me like this.
I won’t let you leave.
Don’t leave me like this.
Min Yan is seriously injured.
Take him to his room, now!
Min Yan.
Oh no. Someone is taking the Jade Cup.
This is bad.
Hao Chen is alone in the secret ground.
Si Feng.
This huge Asura is an undead spirit.
He is vulnerable to sunlight.
The golden light from
your Rose Gold Bird Wings
is similar to sunlight.
Kill him.
As a Rose Gold Bird yourself,
you shall die from
the power of your own clan.
It’s a perfect ending for you!
It’s finally over.
Yuan Lang.
I guess our 1,000-year grudge is settled.
Now that we’ve removed
this monster here,
you can finally explain
everything to Little Pretty.
I’ve been waiting
so long for this.
What? You still care about this guy?
He’s Xuan Ji’s senior, after all.
I didn’t know you’re so kind.
I’m not trying to be a saint.
But if I don’t save him,
Xuan Ji will blame me
for the rest of her life.
I don’t want to carry this sin.
Besides, if her senior testifies for me,
I can explain everything to Xuan Ji.
You punk.
That’s a clever plan.
Senior Hao Chen.
What’s going on?
Yu Si Feng.
Stop wasting your energy.
You are a good actor, Star of Mosha.
You’re trying to use this chance
to conquer the demons, right?
Regardless of your goals, do you
think what you’re doing is useful?
You’re just wasting your efforts.
What do you mean?
Senior Hao Chen!
Senior!
Xuan Ji is in this state because of you!
- Where are you?
- Since there’s no return,
let me lend your identity
as the Star of Mosha!
Sect Leader!
Senior!
You demon.
Even if you kill me,
you’ll never take the Jade Cup!
Senior!
You demon!
How dare you attack Hao Chen?
You people are an unreasonable bunch.
My brother was helping him.
Senior Hao Chen.
I’m here to kill the undead Asura spirit.
I’m here to save you.
Why are you maligning me
when you know this?
Yu Si Feng wants to take the Jade Cup.
I can’t let him get his way.
You trusted the wrong person.
Senior!
You’ll be fine.
I’ll heal your wounds now.
Xuan Ji, that’s not it.
Don’t waste your spiritual power.
Xuan Ji.
Why didn’t you listen to me?
Everything has gone so awry now.
You’ll be fine, Senior.
I’ll listen to you.
I’ll listen to you, Senior!
It’s too late.
Xuan Ji, that’s not what happened.
When I reached here, your
senior was already seriously injured.
I saw the undead spirit attacking
him, so I decided to strike.
The spirit was possessed
by Yuan Lang’s soul.
He was here to take the Jade Cup!
When I finally killed him,
your senior...
I wanted to save him!
Promise me.
Destroy the Jade Cup.
Don’t let the demons get their way.
Senior.
Promise me.
- Senior.
- Promise me.
I promise you.
I promise you, Senior.
Senior!
Sect Leader!
Senior.
Senior!
Yu Si Feng.
You killed my senior.
Xuan Ji, I didn’t kill him.
Trust me!
When I knew you’re a demon,
I chose to trust you.
When you trespassed upon
our secret ground,
I trusted you too.
Even when I knew
you’re the Star of Mosha,
I still hoped that you would change.
I trusted you time and again.
And now?
My loved ones are hurt because of you!
You injured Auntie Ying Hong.
You killed my master and my senior.
How can I still trust you?
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
I’m not the Star of Mosha.
I’ve never hurt anyone.
I came here today to kill Yuan Lang.
Now that Yuan Lang is no longer here,
no one can threaten the Jade Cup now.
I can tell you everything I’ve done.
Think about it.
If I did kill your loved ones,
why didn’t I run away?
Why did I stay here?
You think Hao Chen can stop me?
Shut up!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
What should I say to make you trust me?
Have we ever trusted each other?
Senior Hao Chen was right.
I shouldn’t have
searched for my six senses.
Had I not done so,
I wouldn’t feel so painful
as I face you now.
Yu Si Feng.
I regret meeting you.
Xuan Ji.
I regret taking the brunt
for you at Fuyu Island.
I regret loving you.
I regret everything
that happened between us.
I’d rather
not have anything to do with you, ever!
Si Feng!
Si Feng.
I finally understand
why my past nine lives ended so.
Chu Xuan Ji.
You are after all
a heartless woman.
If I don’t have a heart,
I won’t feel pain.
For the years to come
and even lives to come,
I don’t want to see you again.
Si Feng, stop messing around.
You’re dying!
God of War.
To think I treated you as a friend
for the past 1,000 years.
Has time dulled your wits?
You’re a bore.
A real bore!
Si Feng, let’s go.
Hao Chen.
Hao Chen!
Sect Leader!
- Sect Leader!
- Hao Chen!
Hao Chen!
Sect Leader!
Xuan Ji.
Do you really want
to practice martial arts?
Will you follow me to
Xuyang Peak for training?
Xuyang Peak?
You are born with the talent
of eradicating demons.
You are also destined
to guard the secret ground.
Senior.
What does it mean to guard
the secret ground?
It is a mission borne by us,
the disciples of Xuyang Peak.
Our task is to guard
the secret ground with our lives.
You are the God of War, nemesis of evil.
You shouldn’t have fallen for him.
You’re just misguided by mortal desires.
It was him who planted
the seed of pain in you.
That’s right.
I am the Star of
Mosha, Rahu Ketu.
You think I’m just here for the Jade Cup,
but I’m actually here
to kill the God of War.
Xuan Ji.
Have you forgotten about
your mother and your master’s deaths?
Elder Ying Hong’s injury?
Do you want to see him wreak
havoc or attack our brethren instead?
Yu Si Feng.
You broke your promise again.
Is there any shred of truth in your words?
He’s the one who should die.
Xuan Ji, don’t mind us!
Seize this chance
and kill the Star of Mosha!
Kill the sinful demons
in Lize Palace once and for all!
Why didn’t you listen to me?
Everything has gone so awry now.
Promise me.
Destroy the Jade Cup.
Don’t let the demons get their way.
I promise you.
I promise you, senior.
- Senior!
- Sect Leader!
Senior Hao Chen.
I’m sorry.
Everything started
because of the Jade Cup.
It’s all the cup’s fault.
I will destroy it.
IN MEMORY OF HAO YANG
Where are we?
We are at Fenru City’s
Path of Reincarnation.
You’re already dead.
Don’t jest, Brother Wu.
I say, you punk.
You didn’t even strike back when
that girl was about to kill you.
You’re a fool, aren’t you?
I’m probably the biggest fool
in the whole wide world.
In the end, it’s all wishful
thinking in my part.
So what’s your plan next?
Are you really ignoring her?
She said she regrets meeting me.
She regrets everything
that happened between us.
What else can I say?
Let’s go back to Lize Palace.
I have much work to do there.
Sure.
The divine weapon is wailing.
Something must be happening
to the soul of Star of Mosha.
It’s in danger.
The soul of Star of Mosha
is sealed inside the Jade Cup.
Who can touch the Jade Cup
and threaten the Star of Mosha?
The God of War.
Before he died, Hao Chen told
Xuan Ji to destroy the Jade Cup
and erase the soul of Star of Mosha.
If the soul of Star of Mosha
is so easily destroyed,
those from the heavens
would have struck a long time ago.
They wouldn’t have to wait till now.
Everything happens for a reason.
I think that shameless pact from heavens
must have done something disastrous
towards the soul of Star of Mosha.
That’s why the soul
is filled with hatred.
It’s indestructible.
Although Xuan Ji has
the power of the God of War,
I think that
even if she sacrifices herself,
she still can’t destroy it.
Guard!
Yu Si Feng, you stubborn demon.
How dare you trespass again?
Move.
I cannot hurt the innocent.
I want to save Xuan Ji!
Star of Mosha.
Today is the day you die.
Don’t you dare approach the Jade Cup!
Take him down!
Stop!
Listen, old man.
Xuan Ji can’t destroy
the soul of Star of Mosha.
Look at her!
Xuan Ji.
Why are you doing this to me?
I won’t let you off.
Xuan Ji looks awful now.
- What should we do?
- Why is this happening?
Hao Chen did say that
Xuan Ji is the only one who can
destroy the soul of Star of Mosha.
Yu Si Feng, you must
have done something!
I told you, he didn’t!
What? You don’t believe me?
If that stinky woman destroys
the soul of Star of Mosha,
she’ll die as well.
Hao Chen said she’s the only one
who can destroy the soul
not because she’s
the God of War, but because...
Because what? Tell us.
She’s the...
She’s the one sealed inside...
Even the gods are
forbidding me from speaking.
It’s okay.
I have a jade inscription
about the God of War.
Read it and you’ll know.
Can’t I let them read too?
You people from the heavens
just love being sneaky and mysterious.
Shut up, who do you think you are?
You have no right
to comment on our affairs.
If it weren’t for
Hao Chen’s interference...
Hao Chen?
How did Hao Chen know that Xuan Ji
is the only one who can destroy
the soul of Star of Mosha?
Xuan Ji!
Stop him!
Fool, you can’t beat him!
- Let me go.
- Don’t risk yourself!
I can’t afford to wait!
You can’t do anything, Si Feng!
Who is she? No one can battle him
other than she herself.
No, there must be another way.
I can’t let her die like this!
Flying Snake!
I know you have another solution.
Tell me!
The divine weapons.
It used to be a part
of the Star of Mosha.
You can absorb its powers
to battle the Jade Cup.
No, Si Feng, you’re not a demon.
You can’t absorb all the powers
in the divine weapons.
This ape has a point.
If you do that, the
weapons’ powers will kill you.
I have only one question,
what’s the procedure?
Tell me!
The Rose Gold Birds absorb energy
below the ribs, right?
Stab the divine weapons there.
Shut up, you stupid snake!
I won’t let you do this, Si Feng.
Brother Wu.
You promised me three favors.
I can’t let you die!
Brother Wu, I’m begging you!
Fine.
I can’t stop you if that’s what you wish.
Xuan Ji.
Oh no!
The soul of Star of Mosha is about
to gush out from the Jade Cup!
Flying Snake.
Please take care of Xuan Ji.
Si Feng, are you trying to kill yourself?
He’s using his wings
to reseal the Jade Cup.
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
I’m fine.
Flying Snake.
Don’t tell her what happened today.
Please.
From now on,
she is just a woman called Chu Xuan Ji.
Brother Wu.
Let’s go.
Very well, Si Feng.
The Star of Mosha
will bring calamity someday.
They must be still near, let’s go!
You’re an idiotic bunch!
Can’t you understand?
What are you after now?
It was Si Feng who saved Xuan Ji.
It was also Si Feng who resealed
the Jade Cup that you almost opened.
It was also Si Feng who killed Yuan Lang
so he won’t release the Star of
Mosha and destroy the three realms.
Right now, you’re still standing here,
and all is peaceful in the three realms.
And it was Si Feng the demon
who mended your mistakes.
If he is the Star of Mosha,
what can he get from this?
Can’t you think about it?
It’s over.
It’s all over.
You haven’t told me where my sister is.
How can you die like that?
I deceived the elders and our clansmen.
I no longer have spiritual power
to lead the Rose Gold Birds.
Elder Luo.
I shall leave this in your hands.
No, please don’t.
It is often said that we Rose Gold Birds
are violent and bloodthirsty.
But we want nothing
other than a peaceful life.
It’s just that our pact
with the demons still stand.
Of course we need
to follow through our promise.
Just now, you mentioned that
you are not the demon lord,
and you do not intend
to destroy the three realms,
so we do not have to fight for it.
This is a huge relief for all of us.
You are still the
12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird,
and you’ve been planning
the best for our clansmen,
seeking a safe sanctuary
for us to live in.
May I ask if there’s anyone else
who can lead the Rose Gold Birds?
You should keep the medallions.
Elder Luo.
- Actually, I...
- That’s enough.
Our clan still acknowledge you
as our leader.
Why are you still denying it?
Exactly, so please don’t worry.
I will manage the clan with
the other three elders
and await your return.
I shall take my leave.
I wanted to pass
this position to Elder Luo.
Brother Liu, why did you stop me?
If I didn’t stop you,
I’d have to see you
bang your head on the wall,
put a Loveless Curse on yourself
and pretend to be the Star of Mosha
until you’re half-dead.
Now, I even have to see you
pass all your duties to someone
and find a place to die alone.
Isn’t that what you’re thinking,
Little Phoenix?