LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 12
It’s gone.
Thank you for sparing me.
I’m leaving.
She’s still young and immature.
Thanks, Little Phoenix.
Yu Er!
- Let me go!
- Let you go?
Are you going to run away again
if I let you go?
Couldn’t you thank him
for saving your life?
What if you get caught by
the bad guys again?
That’s my problem!
You’re not willing to accept me.
And you kept avoiding me.
Why are you pretending
to be a good father now?
I don’t need one!
Let me go, you old fogey!
You didn’t care about me
when I was still alive.
Now that I’m dead,
you can’t stop bothering me.
Yu Er.
It’s my fault that I couldn’t be with you.
Now I can’t leave you alone.
From now on, I
won’t let you go again.
Let’s go.
A demon saved Elder Ling Shi?
Xuan Ji, did you make a mistake?
No. I’ve never come across
such a strong demonic aura.
Whether a demon
has caught Ling Shi or not,
we should head to Xuanyuan Sect
and inform Elder Zhu Shi of what he did.
Si Feng. Xuan Ji.
We’ll head to Xuanyuan Sect.
As for the rest,
wait for us in the town.
Min Yan.
I’ve said so.
You need to care about Xuan Ji’s feelings.
But I need to explain myself.
You should stay in the town
and give it a thought,
in case your insincere
words hurt others and yourself.
Ruo Yu. Yan Ran.
Take Min Yan to the town.
Don’t let him follow us.
Si Feng.
Min Yan, let’s go.
This is utter nonsense.
Wait for me!
Wait for me.
Ling Long.
Ling Long!
Does Ling Long have something on her mind?
She’s ignoring me.
Something is bothering her.
That’s why she’s acting that way.
What’s bothering her?
We’re here. Let’s get down now.
XUANYUAN
Please wait for a moment.
I’ll go inform of your arrival.
No one is training.
And the ground isn’t swept.
That’s so outrageous.
The censer has gone out of use.
It seems that they haven’t
burnt any incense for days.
Sect Leader is inviting you to go in.
Sect Leader.
You’ve travelled all the way here.
Why are you here?
Sect Leader can’t talk
because he’s caught a cold.
That’s why I’m asking on his behalf.
I came uninvited
for an urgent matter.
We went down the mountain for training.
While passing by Wangxian Town,
we saw someone controlled
the demon spirits to drink human blood,
and grow Jialuo blood fruits.
We investigated and found out
that it’s Elder Ling Shi’s doing.
As juniors, we dared not act recklessly.
We’re afraid it’d tarnish
Xuanyuan Sect’s reputation.
That’s why we came to inform
Sect Leader Zhu Shi of it.
Got it.
Our sect will see to it.
Don’t worry yourselves with it.
We almost got killed.
You don’t look concerned
at all, Elder Mo Shi.
I don’t need you
to teach me how to settle it.
Since the fellow elders have found out,
there’s nothing else to talk about.
We’re leaving.
No rush.
You came all the way.
I think you should stay for
a vegetarian meal.
All three of you went down
the mountain for training.
How many of you?
Six persons in total.
The other companions are waiting
in the town for our return.
We’re afraid we’d get into danger again.
That’s why we came up with a plan.
If we don’t go back by this evening,
those three persons will inform
the sect of our disappearance.
If so, I won’t make you stay.
Xuanyuan Sect will catch Ling Shi soonest.
We’ll give you an explanation.
Guys, see yourselves out.
Wait.
I might need your
help for something.
The wife of Lord of Fuyu Island
is having her birthday banquet soon.
My men are too busy to send her the gift.
Thus, I’d like you all
to send this gift to Lord Dong Fang.
- See the guests out.
- Wait.
It’s a gift to Fuyu Island.
And it has to do with the face of my sect.
Sect Leader isn’t feeling so well.
He might miss something out.
I’ll take a look at it
again for Sect Leader.
There’s not much time.
But you managed to remain courteous.
It seems that I was
worried for nothing.
If so,
please see yourselves out.
Xuanyuan Sect is so weird.
They made me feel uncomfortable.
Oh right, Si Feng.
Why did you say that
if we’re not back before dark,
those waiting in the town
would inform the sect of it?
I don’t remember we made that arrangement.
I found Xuanyuan
Sect strange too.
That’s why I said that.
Maybe I was worried for nothing.
XUANYUAN SECT
Please calm down,
my fellow divine messengers.
Sect Leader...
Sect Leader did so to get rid of
the suspicion of the five sects.
- That’s why he sent that gift.
- Yes.
I’ve checked on it.
There’s nothing wrong about it.
You need not worry,
my fellow divine messengers.
Sect Leader, you mustn’t do
such an unexpected thing again.
Hand over the spirit keys.
And Xuanyuan Sect will be saved.
Xuanyuan Sect has gone
for a thousand years.
Whether it can exist after that,
that depends on fate.
Instead of being controlled by demons
and existing on the brink of collapse,
it’d rather die an honourable death.
Do you stop your sect
from being honourable?
My fellow divine messengers.
Sect Leader is just being stubborn.
Perhaps he hasn’t figured out
your compliments to him.
Please allow me a few more days.
I promise that I’ll
persuade Sect Leader
to hand over the spirit keys.
I don’t have to remind you all.
The deadline is in three days.
You don’t have much time left.
- Sect Leader!
Go away.
Sect Leader, the poison
is going to attack your body.
Why can’t you stop being stubborn?
That’s right, Sect Leader.
Stop being stubborn.
Based on what those young people said,
Ling Shi’s method
isn’t going to work soon.
Today, another ten
Xuanyuan disciples have died.
Do you want all of our
disciples to be killed?
Yes, Sect Leader.
Xuanyuan Sect made a mistake.
We can’t make another one.
You’re back.
You’re hungry, aren’t you?
I’ve prepared us supper.
Let’s eat together.
I’m a bit tired. I’m going to bed first.
Ling Long.
Si Feng.
I have something to tell you.
It’s very important. I have to say it now.
Master. Green Feather
marks are on your wrist.
And the Loveless Curse
is now in your body.
I knew you’d find it out.
Don’t tell Xuan Ji about it.
Now isn’t the time to care about her!
I don’t care.
You can’t stay here anymore.
Let’s go. We’ll go back to Lizhe Palace.
And we won’t come back again, okay?
Then,
we’ll lock ourselves
in Lizhe Palace forever.
I’d rather die.
You won’t die.
It takes three attacks from Loveless Curse
for the blood to flow backwards.
If you don’t get hurt by love,
the curse won’t attack and you’ll be fine.
That’s right.
That’s why I think I can still manage it.
What are you worried about?
But Chu Xuan Ji is unreliable.
She doesn’t love you at all.
You shouldn’t have
fallen in love with her.
And you’re in a complicated
relationship with her.
She’ll get you killed, Master!
Silver Snake.
You’re getting unruly.
Please calm down, Master.
You’re fortunate enough
to cultivate yourself a human form.
And it’s not easy.
That’s why I let you pretend
to be a Dianjinggu disciple
and train with me.
You’re not here to control me.
You can’t restrain me
or meddle with my affairs.
Because I... I don’t
understand your decision.
I want you to stay alive, Master.
You’re right.
I should stay alive.
You’re my spirit beast.
Our six senses are connected.
Can you not feel how happy I am.
Get up.
Silver Snake.
Did you know?
The moment I put on the Loveless Mask,
I thought I’d never
be happy again.
I was scared that
the curse would take my life.
That it would control me.
But now I’m very happy and carefree.
I was presumptuous enough
to make this decision.
I let myself fall in love with her.
All this
is my decision.
No matter what happens in
the future, I’ll bear all the cost.
And I won’t regret.
Do you understand now?
I do.
But you’ll die eventually.
I don’t want you to die, Master.
I don’t want!
Stop being so dramatic.
Nobody is dying here.
Silver Snake.
We used to go up
the heavenly realm together.
Can you be more polite to me?
If your hand slips and
you accidentally kill me,
you master is dead meat.
Brother Liu.
You haven’t gotten rid of
the bad habit of eavesdropping.
If it hadn’t been for
my eavesdropping habit,
I wouldn’t found out your lifeline.
Lifeline?
What lifeline?
Of course it’s a lifeline that breaks
your master’s Loveless Curse.
You’re kidding me, Brother Liu.
There’s no way to break it.
Little Phoenix.
You’re very lucky indeed.
On the day I sneaked into
Lizhe Palace to visit you,
I eavesdropped on the conversation between
the palace lord and the vice palace lord.
And I found out that there’s
a secret chamber in Lizhe Palace.
And there’s a dossier
in that secret chamber.
And the dossier records
the solution to Loveless Curse.
What’s the solution?
I’ll do whatever it takes
to break the curse for Master.
Well, it has nothing
to do with you.
The only person who can
save your master is Chu Xuan Ji.
Chu Xuan Ji?
We all know that when
the curse starts working,
one’s blood will flow backwards and die
if he gets hurt by love for thrice.
And the mask will turn into a crying face.
It’s impossible for one
to not get hurt by love.
Thus, this curse became a death curse.
And that’s the reason why
there’s a lifeline.
If the one you love
treats you with all her heart
and is loyal to you, she
can take off your mask.
And the mask will
turn into a smiling face.
Why so?
I’ve never heard of
this solution to Loveless Curse.
Well...
Because only the two palace lords
can enter the secret chamber.
Naturally, they don’t believe
there are loyal partners in the world.
That’s why they’ve never brought it up.
That’s normal.
I’m bring her here to
take off my master’s mask.
Here’s the main point.
They have to love each other.
- They have to love each other?
- Thus, I’m reminding you.
You’d better not act recklessly.
There’s only one chance
to take the mask off.
No second chance.
Little Phoenix.
Your life depends on
whether you can make Chu Xuan Ji
fall in love with all her heart.
Thank you, Brother Liu.
For giving me a solution.
I really appreciate it.
- Don’t mention it.
- But you do know that
Xuan Ji has someone else in her heart.
I’ve fallen deeply in love with her.
It has nothing to do with her.
I can’t force her
for my own sake.
Look at yourself.
You’ve never troubled others.
You’re a man who
endures everything alone.
But when it comes to love,
you’ve got to listen to me.
You need to be aggressive
when courting a lady.
I Have come across many women.
I think Chu Xuan Ji is a confused
girl who’s ignorant of love.
She seems to know nothing about love.
Therefore, you need not
take small fights seriously.
I have faith in our Little Phoenix.
It’s not as hard as you think it is.
I, Zhong Min Yan,
only care about Chu Ling Long.
I’m not apologising.
You feel the same way about me.
Why don’t you admit it?
Can we stop lying to ourselves?
Brother Liu. You said Ling Long and
Sixth Senior fought because of me.
Why so?
Don’t you see that your silly
sister and that silly Zhong Min Yan
like each other?
But Ling Long and
Sixth Senior fight all the time.
I thought she didn’t like him at all.
Isn’t it great if they like each other?
But Brother Liu, why do they fight
even though they like each other?
All three of us live happily together.
Isn’t that great?
What’s so great about it?
Can you see that
Ling Long has lost her appetite
because she’s very upset that
Zhong Min Yan likes both of you.
That’s impossible.
Ling Long is very generous.
I enjoy eating drumsticks. So does she.
We share our drumsticks all the time.
Sharing is caring.
Are you ignorant or pretending to be so?
There are many things in this world
that can’t be shared
Especially one’s loved one.
That can’t be shared.
Who said so?
Ling Long and I like Father.
And she’s not mad about it.
Little Xuan Ji.
Humans are very greedy.
There are many kinds of likes.
You like drumsticks.
And I like drinks.
You like your father.
And I like Little Phoenix.
Yet, someone will make you
forget about all these likes.
You still don’t get it?
Let me put it this way.
If you were to travel alone
to a desert island
and stay there forever,
you could take someone along
to keep you company.
That’s the one whom
you wouldn’t share with others.
Would you abandon Ling Long
and stay on the desert island
with Min Yan forever?
That means he’s not the one.
The one and the only.
Someone who can’t be shared.
Ling Long seems to treat
Min Yan differently.
And Min Yan seems to treat
Ling Long differently.
Did I really make a mistake?
Fill her bowl.
Si Feng said vegetables
help you grow taller.
Ling Long.
What happened yesterday
between you and Sixth Senior?
We...
- Here.
- Leave me be.
I can’t do it.
Why did you say it out loud?
How embarrassing.
What’s so embarrassing about it?
All these years,
whenever I see you,
I feel like catching a glimpse of
you and talking to you more often.
I feel happy even when we’re bantering.
Today, I’d like to make
things clear in front of you all.
I like you.
I’ve said so. If you
let Xuan Ji down, I’ll kill you.
Go ahead and kill me then.
I’d tell the same thing to anyone.
There’s nothing between me and Xuan Ji.
- You...
- I only have you in my heart.
You shut up! You...
Ling Long.
Sixth Senior is telling the truth.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I promised Mother that I’ll protect you.
No one can bully you.
No one is bullying me.
I’ve made a mistake.
I thought I liked Sixth Senior.
Actually, it’s all a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
You told me that
one feels like seeing
the person she likes every day.
When I was locked inside the Mingxia Cave,
I just recovered my sense of taste
and Sixth Senior sent me
good foods every day.
That’s why I feel like
seeing him all the time.
I thought I liked him.
But I found out that
I was just craving for foods.
I then thought about it.
Sixth Senior didn’t make those foods.
They’re prepared by the cook in our sect.
Does that mean I like the cook?
Xuan Ji.
Is this the reason why you...
Yes! I just found out yesterday
that the like between you and Sixth Senior
is a unique one which can’t be shared.
I’m different. There are
many people whom I like.
Thus, Ling Long, I’m returning
this dagger to its owner.
Don’t ever fight again, okay?
Here, sit down and eat your food.
No.
If you don’t like each other,
why did you hug each other on that day?
Zhong Min Yan, you still wanted to
take advantage of my sister!
- I...
- Ling Long!
That’s not what happened.
Do you still remember the incident
where Gudiao was killed at Mount Lutai?
Actually, I killed it.
Xuan Ji.
Sixth Senior, you need not
keep this secret of mine anymore.
I killed Aoyin at Mount Haiwan
with the blue light,
which isn’t the Yang Jue Skill.
It’s a kind of strange power
which I know nothing about.
It made me lose my consciousness.
I don’t remember what happened afterwards.
Sixth Senior saw it.
He’s afraid I’d be seen as a freak.
That’s why he kept this secret.
We’re wondering if it has anything
to do with the Mirror of Origin?
We thought of destroying that mirror
so that these weird things
wouldn’t happen again.
On that day, we tried to
destroy the mirror at the inn.
But that spell bounced back.
We hugged because of the spell.
Why was it so strange?
It’s...
The misunderstanding has been resolved!
It’s a good thing!
But Xuan Ji, do you
have any symptoms?
- Are you feeling not well?
- No.
I’m fine without that blue light.
I didn’t want to make you worried.
That’s why I kept it from you all.
But now, I was
left with no choice.
Do you believe me now?
You tried to show off
even though you’re not skilled.
Also, why did you hide it from me?
Did you think I’d hurt Xuan Ji
or spread a rumour?
I was wrong, my dear.
I regret for making such a grave mistake.
Forgive me and I’ll do anything for you.
And I’d like to gift
this dagger to you.
Look.
Your name is actually
engraved on it.
LING LONG
It’s all a misunderstanding.
I’ve always wanted to marry a lady.
- She is...
- Shut up!
I’m not accepting it.
I haven’t forgiven you for
causing such a big misunderstanding.
- Ling Long, don’t go!
- Ling Long!
- Isn’t the misunderstanding resolved?
Why are you still fighting, Ling Long?
Girl.
They’re not fighting.
That’s called flirting.
I’m jealous.
Although you usually seem confused,
you act decisively at crucial moments.
Not bad.
Thus, I think that impulsive
warrior isn’t suitable for you.
But it’s okay.
We have another model.
You’re suitable for a man who’s
gentle, determined, polite,
charismatic, and ambitious.
Brother Liu, what are you talking about?
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
The best fish has always been with you.
Turn around and you can see that
he’s always protected you!
Why has everyone left?
Some dishes aren’t served yet.
Ruo Yu.
Forget about what I just said.
- Brother Liu.
- I...
Why did the spell bounce back?
It’s all your doing, wasn’t it?
Master.
I thought Chu Xuan Ji liked Zhong Min Yan.
And I was worried about your mask.
I just wanted you to leave her soonest.
That’s why...
That’s why I...
It took you a lot of effort
to transform into a human.
You don’t focus on cultivating yourself.
And you can’t stop scheming.
It seems that you want to
turn back into a snake forever.
No. I admit it’s my fault.
Do you?
Remember.
If you ever do such a thing
again, I’ll teach you a good lesson.
Master, I’m okay if she can
break your Loveless Curse.
If she can’t, I
won’t let her go.
I was trying to matchmake for you.
Why did you run away?
Were you shy?
Let’s go, I’ll matchmake for you again.
Brother Liu.
Surely Xuan Ji feels troubled
about what just happened.
Let’s not make her feel more upset.
Little Phoenix.
You remain a gentleman
at this critical moment.
Xuan Ji is like a blank paper.
You’ll draw whatever you want.
Think about it.
Her sixth senior sent her a meal.
And she thought she liked him.
You have many chances to
make her surrender herself to you.
It depends on whether
you will seize the opportunity.
I’m anxious seeing you this way.
You and Xuan Ji are just two stiffs.
If it keeps going this way, you’ll
remain two stiffs after a hundred year.
Let’s do it this way.
You will walk to her
and be a fortune teller.
"Miss."
"According to your Five Elements,
you’re in need of a man."
"What do you think about me?"
This trick is not good enough.
Fine.
Let’s have a more straightforward one.
You’ll choose a moonless and windy night.
Brother Liu.
Just keep these
tricks for yourself.
Fine.
Little Phoenix.
Take it.
Don’t say I didn’t help you.
Thank you, Si Feng.
For the long walk.
Back when I was in
Shaoyang, I was really silly.
The seniors and juniors always bullied me.
But whenever I was upset,
only Ling Long and Sixth Senior
would cheer me up.
They’ve been fighting these past two days.
I’m actually worried about it.
I was truly silly back then.
I always imposed my feelings upon others.
Now that you understand it, that
means you’re not ridiculously silly.
Xuan Ji.
What’s wrong?
Don’t cry.
Got you!
Did you forget that I can’t cry?
It’s the Merman’s Tear.
Why were you panicking?
I see.
You’re making fun of me, aren’t you?
It’s because when Second Senior
was rejected by Senior Duan Min,
he cried so hard.
His nose ran. And his tears kept falling.
That’s why I think
this is where I should cry.
But I can’t do it.
That’s why I pretended to cry.
I think your second senior
made that up to save his face.
Tears are a precious thing.
Even if you pretend to cry, you
can’t simply let your tears flow.
Get it?
I find that embarrassing too.
I really want to be like everyone else.
That’s why I made such a joke.
I need to stop being confused.
When I was young, my mother taught me
to write the names of
important people on a notebook.
Look.
FATHER, MOTHER, SIXTH SENIOR, SISTER
SENIOR HAO CHEN, YU SI FENG
You wrote
my name too.
Of course I did, Si Feng.
You’re very important.
But Brother Liu said that
it’s unique to like someone.
And it can’t be shared.
But I find all of these people important.
And I like them all.
Can’t I?
She sees no difference between
kinship, friendship, and relationship.
She really knows nothing about them.
Actually, there’s no need to
distinguish them from each other.
They’re all feelings which
come from one’s heart.
You’ll figure it out eventually.
But I don’t think I will.
You do know that I’m lack of six senses.
My heart can’t feel them.
That’s too bad.
I envy those who know
what they’re thinking.
They know what they want.
And there’s me who’s always confused.
Si Feng.
That fragment of Mirror of
Origin, do you still keep it?
Yes, I do.
Do you
want to keep looking for your six senses?
I...
I do.
I want to find out my thoughts.
But I’m scared.
I don’t wish to misunderstand others.
But
I promised Senior Hao Chen that
I’ll stop looking for the six senses.
Also, what if everyone else gets
hurt by my strange memory and power?
Si Feng.
What should I do?
If You don’t know your
heart, you can’t feel for others.
You won’t know how to protect them.
And you won’t know
how not to hurt them, right?
Your senior wants you
to do good and fight evil.
But it’s not easy to tell good from evil.
If you’re confused, you
can’t tell good from evil.
You said you’re scared
of that strange power.
But it’s when we’re in danger
that the power is unleashed.
I guess it’s not
some demon trick.
It’s your secret weapon.
Some proper guidance will
even turn it into your booster.
Besides, I’m with you.
No matter what
happens, I’ll protect you.
Si Feng.
Are you staying?
You’re not training
separately again, are you?
Didn’t you make
me eat the Truth Pill?
I’ve confided myself
to you.
I knew you wouldn’t leave us.
Xuan Ji.
Are you ready?
Xuan Ji. Xuan Ji!
Si Feng.
I...
I saw that general killing people again.
And this time it’s more lifelike.
But... But who is she?
Why is she always on my mind?
Don’t worry. A fragment
can’t prove anything.
When all the fragments are
found, we’ll know the truth.
There’s demonic aura.
Why can’t I feel it?
Si Feng.
Is this the smell of flowers?
Xuan Ji.
You’ve recovered your sense of smell.
This smells so nice.
There are many smells in this world.
Everything has its smell.
And there are many interesting ones.
Come with me.
- This is a peach blossom forest.
- It’s so beautiful!
Peach blossoms smell so nice!
No wonder... No wonder Ling
Long’s room is always full of flowers.
Si Feng.
Does each flower have its own smell?
Each of them smells different.
Sometimes its smell is
memorable than its appearance.
You can’t distinguish
their colours for now.
But you can differentiate them
based on their smells.
Si Feng, what do you smell like?
I smell like nothing.
No, you smell good.
But it doesn’t smell like
a flower or a food.
But
it’s a familiar smell.
Xuan Ji.
I
Would like you to
know that I... I...
Si Feng, there are too many flowers here.
My nose has gotten uncomfortable
from all this smell.
It’s very uncomfortable.
It’s okay.
We have plenty of time.
There will be chances to experience it.
- Let’s go there.
- Sure.
KELAI TAVERN
Take this.
Teach me how to cook tonight.
Sure.
Senior Hao Chen.
It’s been a while since
I last wrote my thoughts.
Because many things have happened lately.
But I’ve figured out several things.
I think Si Feng’s right.
One should know what he’s thinking.
And don’t be confused.
No way.
If I write that,
Senior Hao Chen will know that
I’m still looking for the mirror.
I’d better not tell him.
Forget about it. Anyway, it’s no big deal.
Si Feng?
Are they edible?
What a sumptuous feast.
We can’t afford it.
What’s that good smell?
There are so many nice dishes here.
Why don’t you dig in?
We...
It’s delicious!
- Brother Liu will buy us this meal.
- Min Yan.
- He’ll pay for it. I want to eat it too.
- Ling Long.
Ruo Yu, join us.
You...
Does it taste good?
Does it taste delicious?
Why don’t you say something?
Does it taste good?