LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 26
After that, Wu Zhi Qi locked
me in that grape garden.
He kept playing tricks on me.
And I tried to escape every day.
But I always failed.
So, it became a routine.
I would run and
he would catch me.
Then, we unknowingly spent
a few hundred years together.
Pretty lady, how old are you?
Do you have a husband?
That macaque is good in everything.
But he has a bad habit.
- How about a drink together?
- He loves pretty ladies.
- I have everything.
- He always
- left me behind for a pretty lady.
- I have drinks and food.
Stop washing the clothes.
This is very heavy.
- Let me help you with it.
- Thank you.
So, I cultivated myself for 500
years to be able to take human form.
I want to let him know that
the most beautiful lady
is right beside him.
Wu Zhi Qi.
Wake up.
Wake up and see who I am.
Pretty lady, how old are you?
Do you have a husband?
What do you mean by pretty lady?
It’s me, the little fox.
Can’t you recognize me?
Little fox?
You are that little fox?
You really are that little fox.
Where is your fur?
Where’s your tail, little fox?
- You...
- You like pretty ladies, right?
So, I turned into a pretty lady.
How is it? Am I beautiful?
You gave me a fright, little fox.
I...
You look better before this.
You’re so furry and cute.
And you warm me up when I hug you.
Can you turn back into a fox?
You stupid monkey, you made me so mad.
Just like that, I spent
500 years with him.
I finally appeared in front of him
in the form of a beautiful lady.
But before I could make that
macaque fall in love with me,
he left.
Back then, Asura was leading demon clan
to wage war against the heavens.
He has a friend named Yuan Lang.
He invited him to become
the Left Lieutenant of the demon clan.
This macaque is a very loyal friend.
I couldn’t stop him.
He was so impressive back then.
I heard that they were winning.
But suddenly, the Star of Mosha
was killed by the God of War.
And the demon clan was defeated.
From then on, the demon clan
was exiled from Mount Buzhou and
they were dispersed into the human realm.
And Wu Zhi Qi was captured
by the heavens and is chained
at the bottom of Fenru City under
Mount Buzhou with Dimension Chain.
It has been 1000 years.
It is my fault.
If only I could
stop him back then.
So, I have to save him.
I never thought that you are
a sentimental person.
But Wu Zhi Qi has never
given you any promise.
And you’ve loved him for 1000 years.
Is it worth it?
I don’t care if it’s worth it or not.
I love him. So, this is what I want to do.
I’m happy with my decision.
I think it’s great to be
so decisive in love.
It’s way better than the relationship
between that Lord Dong Fang and
his wife.
Why do you need to hesitate
when you like someone?
As long as I can save Wu Zhi Qi,
I’m willing to do anything.
Si Feng.
I never thought that demons can love
as deep and true as this Purple Fox too.
Demons are like humans too.
They are living beings in this world.
And they have real feelings too.
I’ve never thought about it before.
I thought that Purple Fox
is just a frivolous demon.
I never thought that she’ll be so loyal.
I even like her a little bit now.
Yes.
She took the Mirror of Origin
because she wanted to relive
the moments between her and Wu Zhi Qi.
I want to look at the female
general in that Mirror of Origin too.
What is her story?
And how is she related to me?
You and your Senior Hao Chen
are already destined to be together.
He has been pursuing you for 1000 years.
Maybe the person in the mirror is him.
Si Feng.
Can I say that you
are acting jealous now?
You are quite a fast learner for things
that I didn’t teach you.
Your father has never
wanted us to be together.
Now that you’ve ran away with me,
he might be
putting me on a search warrant tomorrow.
He won’t.
Although my father is
a little bit old-fashioned,
I know that he dotes on me.
As long as it’s not a demon,
he will be able to accept anyone.
Don’t worry, I’ll convince him.
Hey, we’ve been walking for so
long. What’s wrong with your nose?
You couldn’t even smell him.
Can you really find him?
Ting Nu’s smell disappeared
around here last time.
It’s the same this time.
You old woman,
don’t play any tricks on us.
I’m not playing tricks on you.
Are you dumb?
If I can smell him myself,
why do I have to ask for your help?
How can we find Ting Nu then?
Brother Liu has a celestial eye, right?
If we can find Brother Liu,
we’ll be able to find Ting Nu.
Yes. We just need to find Brother Liu.
Purple Fox, you can’t smell Ting
Nu but, can you smell Brother Liu?
I don’t know him.
How do I know how he smells like?
Little Phoenix.
Take this.
Don’t say that I didn’t help you.
I have something that
Brother Liu left for me.
What is it? Show me.
You can’t look at this.
- Why not? Show me.
- No.
Why not? I showed you my book last time.
Why can’t you show me yours?
- Show me.
- No means no.
Why not? Show me.
Don’t tell me that you are reading
that kind of book.
Nonsense.
What kind of book is that?
Stop it.
Stop fooling around.
We should find Brother Liu now.
Smell this.
Find out where he is.
Let’s split up and find him now. Let’s go.
Show me.
Show me. Si Feng!
Don’t tell me that the one
we are looking for is here.
Where does this handsome man come from?
Come, play with me.
It’s painful.
Hurry up and let’s go.
This is Qingyang City.
How do you know that Brother Liu is here?
My nose has never failed me.
Except when someone purposely
covered up the smell like Ting Nu.
We are here.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Come on. Come in.
Don’t be shy.
Just treat this like your own home.
Little Phoenix, as the saying
goes, people meet out of fate.
Come, have a seat.
More like out of money, right?
If it wasn’t because we need your help,
I wouldn’t admit that I know you just now.
You paid for me.
So, you are my master now.
Come, Master. Have a seat.
It’s fine. I want to stand.
Brother Liu, why are you at Qingyang?
Have you found Yu’Er?
Well, Yu’Er?
Half a month ago,
Yu’Er brought me to Sky Hall’s hideout.
She said that she wants to
stay in Sky Hall.
It was chaotic back then,
I couldn’t convince her to leave with me.
I saw her leaving with
the people from Sky Hall.
And I didn’t have the chance
to tell you about it.
That Yu’Er is really naughty.
How can she spend time
with demons from Sky Hall?
I really can’t do anything about her.
Forget it. I don’t care anymore.
Who is this beautiful lady in purple?
God is really treating me well.
I even met this beautiful fox lady
who is 1000 years old.
How is it? Is my hand nice, you scoundrel?
You are indeed an old fox demon.
How dare you say that I’m old.
We are all friends. Be kind to him.
Brother Liu.
We are here this time
to ask for your help.
I have a friend named Ting Nu.
He went missing.
We couldn’t find him or smell him.
Can you help us find him?
You want to find someone? It’s easy.
Great. Brother Liu,
let’s not waste any time then.
Open your celestial eye now
to help us look for Ting Nu.
Now?
At first, it’s not a problem to help you
find him with my celestial eye.
But unfortunately, I just opened
my celestial eye two days ago.
You know that
if I open the celestial eye again
within such a short time,
it’ll be adverse to my health.
You opened the celestial eye?
Then, we won’t be able to save
Ting Nu now.
Calm down. Although
I can’t open my celestial eye,
I can still feel a faint trace of him.
How about you stay at my house
for two days first?
I’ll find a way in two days.
There must be a way.
We’ll have to trouble you then.
It’s no trouble.
Yu’Er!
Such a bright young lady.
It’ll be a pity if she dies.
Old Fogey! Save me!
I can’t take it anymore!
Don’t hurt her! Yu’Er!
Don’t touch her.
What do you want?
I need you to do something for me.
This is the Mirror of Origin.
Bring this mirror to Chu Xuan Ji.
Let her look into this
mirror to remember her past
so that she can awaken
her God of War’s power.
Xuan Ji?
You want me to
betray my own friend?
Impossible.
Fine.
Yu’Er!
Old Fogey, save me!
Fine, I promise you. Stop!
Stop!
You should’ve agreed earlier.
I’m just asking you to jolt her memories,
not to kill her.
Think about it. Our lord wants to
reawaken the God of War.
But I heard that God of War was the one
who killed Star of Mosha back then.
Who can win? Our lord or the God of War?
You are a lunatic.
I really don’t know what
Sky Hall is plotting.
Little Phoenix cherishes Xuan Ji so much.
If Little Phoenix and Xuan
Ji are hurt because of me,
it’ll be such an unfaithful thing to do.
I can’t do that.
Just like what the lord has expected.
They’ve asked you to help save the merman.
Now, everything is ready.
It’ll be up to you next.
Yu’Er! How’s Yu’Er?
Don’t worry. The North Superintendent
knows that you’ll miss your daughter.
So, he sent me to give you this.
After your mission is done,
you’ll be able to see your daughter.
Maybe it’s not a bad thing to reawaken
the God of War’s memories.
She’ll have to know the truth
sooner or later.
I’m sorry, Little Phoenix.
Why aren’t you letting us sleep?
You better have
something important to say.
Of course I have
Let me tell you.
I tried everything I can
and used up all of my power
to finally be able to feel
where that merman is.
This is the Fire Desert?
We can only reach the entrance of
Mount Buzhou through this Fire Desert.
But it’ll be hard to fly with sword within
a few miles around Mount Buzhou.
It’s fine. We can just walk there.
Mount Buzhou has a complicated terrain.
A gale will blow through here every night.
We won’t be able to travel in it.
It’s late already.
How about we stay at an inn first?
We can travel first thing
in the morning tomorrow.
Don’t worry, Sect Leader.
Hao Chen already said that
the entrance of Mount Buzhou
will only be opened at certain time.
Even if they reach here before us,
they won’t be able to go in now.
Okay.
Let’s find an inn first then.
- Ting Nu is locked up here?
- There’s a demon guarding the door.
It’s fine. Later,
we can climb over the wall.
We can save him without alerting anyone.
Wait.
This doesn’t feel right.
What place is this?
We don’t know who our opponents are
or what they want.
It’s not wise to just
rush in.
I’ve lived for 1000 years
without fearing anything.
If you are afraid, I can go in myself.
We’ll save Ting Nu for sure.
But we have to be careful.
Be careful then.
Let’s split up and search the place.
Let’s go.
- I smell Dang Kang.
- Dang Kang?
What is Dang Kang?
Ting Nu’s spirit beast.
Dang Kang.
Don’t just purr. Tell us something useful.
Where is your master?
Bring us to him.
It said that Ting Nu
is trapped by the demon here.
It just managed to break the barrier
and came out to ask for help.
Come here, little guy.
Si Feng, you can communicate with it?
You can understand it?
I learned some beast language before.
If you want to learn,
I can teach you in the future.
- What did he say?
- He said that
Ting Nu is locked inside a secret room.
It wants to bring us to him.
Let’s go.
There are so many rooms here.
How long will it take?
We are here to rescue him.
We can’t rush it.
We haven’t checked this room, right?
Let’s go in.
Okay.
Let’s go.
This doesn’t look like a place
to hold someone in.
Maybe there’s a mechanism in here.
Let’s look for it.
What is this?
They are trying to lock us in.
This is a Restrictive Formation.
We won’t be able to get out now.
This is bad. Si Feng and the others are
in danger. We’ve to find a way to get out.
Mirror of Origin?
What happened to Ting Nu?
Ting Nu’s heart’s blood is used
to build this formation.
This will kill him.
Let’s try to break this formation first.
You stupid fox. Why aren’t you here yet?
Si Feng.
Are we inside the Mirror of Origin now?
I think so.
Why will we be in the Mirror of Origin?
Where is the Purple Fox?
King Bailing, this is bad!
The life pillar of God of War
is flickering again.
I’m afraid that Chu Xuan Ji
has entered the Mirror of Origin.
She just left me for a few days.
But she has already
run into the Mirror of Origin?
This is not as simple as it looks.
You are the God of War, right?
She’s the one I keep on
seeing in my dream.
Do you mean that female general?
Xuan Ji.
She looks exactly like you.
She looks like she has a
lot of secrets in her heart.
What does she want to tell me?
Where is she now?
No matter it’s about Xuan Ji
or the Mirror of Origin,
this is a matter of the human realm.
The heavens can’t interfere with
the matters of human realm.
I can’t find out where she is.
I can’t stay here for long. Goodbye.
Deity Binding Spell?
King Bailing!
I used my energy to cast this spell.
If you break this spell forcefully,
you’ll break my spirit.
Then, you’ll be committing
a grave crime, Si Ming.
Just this once.
Tell me where Xuan Ji is.
Why do you have to do this, King Bailing?
The key memories of the God of War
have already been wiped away
by you from her life pillar, right?
Even if she enters the Mirror of Origin,
she’ll just see some fragmented memories.
Even if she awakens, she won’t
be able to remember the past.
In this life, I can’t
let her be anymore.
King Bailing, everyone
has their own destiny.
No matter how much
you want to save God of War,
we can’t go against the laws of God.
By the way, it’s considered
prying into the prophecy if mortals
go into the Mirror of Origin.
When they do that, there’ll be lightning.
There will be lightning?
Smart.
If you think along this line, you
might be able to find Chu Xuan Ji.
If you can seek her out yourself,
it’ll be by your own effort.
I didn’t say anything.
Go back to Siming Hall at once.
If things go wrong with her life pillar,
seal it up even if you have to
deplete your power to do that.
We can’t let her power awaken yet.
Go now.
If you fail me, I won’t forgive you.
Yes, King Bailing.
What place is this?
This is...
Could it be that this is the heavens?
You can fight well, right?
Come, fight me.
I don’t want to fight you.
Are you afraid of me?
If you can’t even defeat me,
how can King Bailing send you
to lead the army against Asura?
You are not stronger or better than I am.
King Bailing’s order.
Nobody is allowed
to disturb the God of War.
Don’t mind him.
God of War, I’m here
to issue a military order
on behalf of King Bailing.
Say it.
King Asura has led his right and
left lieutenants with 12 Dark Knights
to attack the shore of Life and Death Sea.
You are to go into battle at once.
King Bailing thinks that this is
our best chance to kill King Asura
and defeat the army of the demon clan.
King Bailing said that he’ll
await your triumphant return.
After defeating the demon clan’s army,
the war will end, right?
After that,
does it mean that
I don’t have to fight anymore?
Well...
Let’s go.
Can you stop creating troubles for me?
King Asura?
The demon clan’s army?
Could it be that this is
the war between the heavens
and demon realm 1000 years ago?
I think so.
You can see the past
through the Mirror of Origin.
This happened in the heavens
1000 years ago.
I think it’s related to you.
But 1000 years ago,
who is she?
They call her the God of War.
Could it be that
she’s the legendary God of War
who defeated the demon clan’s army
and destroyed King Asura?
Xuan Ji.
She looks like you and
often appears in your dream.
She is
probably you in the past.
Really?
In the past, I’m not a devil
who killed without batting an eye
but a God of War from the heavens?
Look.
You always thought
so badly about yourself.
Do you understand now?
She’s an outstanding person.
She stayed here?
It’s too cold and desolate.
That is Dingkun Sword.
Yes.
It’s Dingkun Sword.
No wonder you are the
only one who can awaken it.
It’s Ting Nu.
He told me that he was once
a medic in the heavens.
He was punished and sent down to
the human realm because of something.
God of War.
You haven’t fully recovered yet and
you are leading the battle again?
Do you want me to tell
King Bailing about it
so that you can sit out
for this battle this time?
My injuries are nothing.
The demon clan’s army
is gathering their forces.
If I don’t go, nobody else can fight them.
No need to worry King Bailing
because of this.
The most worrisome thing for a medic is
patient who doesn’t take care of herself.
After this battle,
I’m afraid that you’ll add
new injuries to your old ones
until I won’t be able
to treat your wounds.
I’ll try to get injured less.
Don’t worry about me.
This is not what I meant.
Take care.
How can the Jade Emperor
break his promise?
You Asuras are cold-blooded killers.
Today... Today, I’m going
to kill you just like how
I killed Rahu Ketu.
You are the God of War
of the heavens?
You are the one who killed Star of Mosha?
This is such a joke.
What’s wrong?
What does King Asura mean?
Why can’t I see anything?
What does he mean by such a joke?
Calm down, Xuan Ji.
Let’s go through the fog.
God of War.
You are so vicious.
What’s wrong?
The mirror already let us in.
Why won’t it show us the rest?
This is indeed strange.
As if something has covered it up.
Why did you lie to me?
Why?
- I’m just sword for you to kill with!
- Xuan Ji.
- Why did you do this to me?
- What’s wrong?
Why do I feel so upset
when I hear her voice?
In the past, I thought that
we are two entities.
She and I are different.
But now, I can clearly feel
her anger and helplessness.
But I don’t know what happened.
Why can’t I see anything?
When I read an ancient scroll
regarding the Mirror of Origin,
someone mentioned that
if a person’s past is sealed,
it’ll affect the Mirror of Origin.
Looks like your past has been sealed up.
That’s why you can
only see fragments of it.
It has been 1000 years.
Why do they still want to seal it?
Why? Why does the heavens
want to wipe away my pass?
Xuan Ji!
Don’t be obsessed with it. You might
get lost within these memory fragments.
Wu Zhi Qi, how dare you stole
the Yuntian Loop and Chehai Hook?
God of War,
I want you to arrest Wu Zhi Qi.
I want to eradicate demon clan
from the three realms.
Wu Zhi Qi, surrender now.
Return the Yuntian Loop and Chehai Hook
to the heavens.
Do they belong to the heavens?
You killed Star of Mosha
and took away his things.
I’m just getting his things back for him!
God of War, King Asura
asked me to send you a message.
God of War, I was killed by you.
I kept my last breath
to give you a present.
Take a good look at
what secret does King Bailing
hide in his celestial hall.
You brought this upon yourself!
Why is it gone again?
What happened?
Why won’t it show me?
Bailing, come out!
Are you trying to revolt?
How long are you going to
keep lying to me?
Bailing looks so familiar.
You lied to me and made
me into this God of War.
I trusted you so much.
How could you
and the whole heavens
use me like this?
How dare you!
God of War, you are disobedient and revolt
against your superior. It’s unforgivable!
What did I do wrong?
You are the one who was wrong.
I want to see the Jade Emperor!
Or else, I’ll destroy the entire heavens.
No matter how courageous you are,
you can’t just charge into celestial hall
and scream at King Bailing!
I can guard the heavens.
And I can destroy it.
How dare you! Arrest her!
Bailing!
You have to give me an explanation today!
Bailing.
I won’t forgive you.
I will kill you.
I’ll kill all of you
and avenge myself!
Jade Emperor!
Why won’t you come out and talk to me?
Is the heavens full of cowards?
You want to see me?
What did I do wrong?
You are the one who did wrong.
You used me
and turned me into
the heavens’ murder weapon.
You used me to kill people
whom I shouldn’t kill.
You made me do something evil and vicious.
And in the end,
I am the one who did wrong?
This is not fair.
This is not fair!
Let her go!
You hate me for betraying you
and lying to you.
So, you want to seek revenge
from the heavens?
I will uphold justice
even if it’ll cost me my life
or bring me to hell forever.
Please forgive her!
I’ll send you down to the human realm
to go through ten reincarnations
to get rid of your resentment.
As for how it’ll turn out,
it’ll all depend on you.
Why?
Why do I have to be punished?
I didn’t do anything wrong.
Why? Why did you
seal up all of my memories?
Why won’t you tell me anything?
Xuan Ji, look at me.
Pull yourself together. You are not
God of War, you are Chu Xuan Ji!
They are still waiting for us outside.
Don’t be dragged into it anymore.
I have to get to the bottom of this.
I have to get to the bottom of this!
Xuan Ji!
Xuan Ji?
Why am I here too?
This is the memory of my trial.
Could it be that
Xuan Ji was in a trial with me?
It’s done now.
With the injury on your ankle,
you shouldn’t have forced yourself
to dance.
If you can’t recover well,
I’m afraid that you can’t even
walk properly in the future.
I never thought about the future.
And I don’t believe that
there is sincerity in this world.
I won’t leave with you.
I’ll only wait for one person
to come and get me.
Lan Yue, Mister Qiao is here to
bring you back to Qiao Residence.
Pack your things.
See?
I knew that he would come.
You said that
you don’t believe in sincerity.
But you believe in him.
Do you know
what kind of man Mister Qiao is?
I know what kind of a person he is.
And I never said that
I’ll trust his sincerity.
I don’t trust anybody.
I trust only myself.
I remember now.
No.
Xuan Ji.
Don’t go, Xuan Ji!