LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 50
Where’s the Black Feather?
What’s going on?
Did someone take it?
Impossible, no one knows I was here.
Wu Zhi Qi may have destroyed this place,
but the demonic aura is still strong.
Perhaps it has already been consumed.
He deserved it, I guess.
Silver Snake, what’s wrong?
Here, cover your nose.
The demonic aura here
is still too much for you.
Let’s leave now,
I’ll search the feather for you.
This place is so big.
We won’t be able to search
everywhere in a day or two.
I’m staying here to search for it.
Fine, but promise me this.
You must not stay here long.
You must leave here every seven minutes.
After all, you need to stay alive
to meet Si Feng, right?
Flying Snake, ask them.
Hello, sorry for disturbing.
- Have you seen him before?
- No.
Flying Snake.
Do you see a black crow tailing us?
What crow? Can we eat it?
You...
Where is the God of War now?
Your Highness.
The God of War is in the mortal world,
searching for the
Rose Gold Bird, Yu Si Feng.
She’s still entangled with that demon.
Looks like I have
no more need to keep her.
Pass my order.
All celestial soldiers and knights
shall bring the God of War
and her associates here
once they are seen.
Rebels will be prosecuted!
Do not spare Flying Snake as well.
Your Highness.
As far as I’m concerned,
Flying Snake was forcibly
captured by the God of War.
He didn’t want to do this.
He was forced.
Please investigate this.
I shall hear no more.
Four Mythical Beasts.
Proceed to the mortal world now
to arrest the God of War
and her associates.
Yes, Your Highness.
We’ve been searching for ages,
and still no trace of him.
If it weren’t for us trying
not to alarm the heavens,
I’d have summoned the Lord of Earth
and get our answers.
Wu Zhi Qi gave us the Perfect Fruit
so we can mask our presence.
Will the heavens
really give us trouble?
What’s with you and your curiosity?
Why so many questions?
But when I was destroying
the Jade Cup in the secret ground,
I think I heard the Star of Mosha
talking with King Bailing.
I think King Bailing must
have done something wrong.
Don’t spout nonsense.
Out of all the deities,
I respect King Bailing the most.
Anyway, Wu Zhi Qi
gave you the Perfect Fruit,
so the heavens won’t find you.
Stop thinking so much.
When I find Si Feng,
let’s live in seclusion.
No mortal or deity will ever find us.
There’s a village there.
I’m hungry.
Let’s buy something to eat.
- Hot buns!
- Fresh desserts!
Want a bun, sir?
Delicious desserts on sale!
Hot buns!
Want some desserts, sir?
Please take a look.
Money, now.
Choose whatever you like, sir.
Where’s the money?
All your food binging has made us broke.
What now, then?
Listen up.
I can’t afford to go hungry.
Go figure.
DEMON SLAYERS NEEDED IN INN
Successful demon slayers
will be rewarded handsomely.
Looks like it’s time to earn some money.
Sir, do you know where this inn is?
Miss, don’t risk your life.
That inn has been closed
for about a week now.
Anyone who tried to kill
the demon has never returned.
You look young and frail.
You sure you’re up for it?
Just tell me where the inn is.
DEMON SLAYERS NEEDED
Didn’t you see the notice?
We’re not open for business.
I’m here to kill the demon.
Kill the demon?
Stop joking.
You think it’s a game?
Go away.
I said, we’re here to kill the demon.
Let’s go in and see.
Ah Lan, what are you doing?
Didn’t I tell you not to open the door?
Hello, we saw your notice.
We’re here to kill the demon.
You?
Can you?
Don’t worry, we’ve killed
many on our way here.
Let us try, and you’ll see.
Anyway, you can pay us
after we kill the demon.
If you can really kill the demon,
we’ll appreciate it very much.
Boss, didn’t we agree to wait
for Mister Yi to kill the demon?
He’s foraging for herbs
at the mountains now.
Can’t you wait for him?
Mister Yi’s
whereabouts are mysterious.
Who knows when he’ll be back?
Besides, we can’t just close our inn
while waiting for him to come back.
We’ve been closed for business
for so many days.
We’re going broke at this rate.
But I’ve already left a memo
for Mister Yi.
He’ll help us when he’s back.
That’s enough.
I know you’re anticipating his return.
But no one knows if that
mysterious man will ever turn up.
Why don’t we let the masters here
take a look first?
Didn’t you say the inn is closed?
Why is there a room still alight?
Hush, that’s the room with the demon.
Whenever the sun sets every day,
you can see candlelight from the room.
You can even hear someone cry
when you get near.
I didn’t know better back then,
so I let our guests stay there.
Then, every guest who had
stayed in the room all disappeared.
Only then did I know
there’s something fishy inside.
Actually, we have a resident
demon slayer here named Mister Yi.
But only a few has ever
managed to contact him.
That’s why we put up that notice
to hire a demon slayer.
Boss, Mister Yi
will be back someday.
Let’s not risk this young lady’s life.
Miss, please don’t risk your life there.
It does reek of demons there.
And pretty strong, too.
Looks like it’s highly trained.
Flying Snake.
Do you even need me
to handle that puny demon?
Who’s that, Ah Xiang, Ah Ling, Ah Lan!
Come, serve me tea.
I’m feeling so thirsty now.
What’s with you?
You haven’t even done anything yet.
It’ll be done before your tea goes cold.
Aren’t you following her?
Tea, please, hurry up.
You...
The lights are out, they’re out!
Is she doing fine?
Oh dear, that young lady
is going to get killed!
Please take a look!
Is my tea done?
Faster!
Did that demon eat the young lady?
We still don’t know who’s eating whom.
I’m starving.
Miss, are you okay?
Here you go.
A weasel spirit.
Weasel?
It said you splashed it
with hot oil three months ago.
That’s why it’s back for revenge.
But we can’t spare it
since it killed so many people.
Three months ago, I did see
an animal eating our chickens,
so I splashed hot oil on it.
So this is it.
You two look so young,
but you’re rather formidable.
Thank you so much.
Ma’am, do you want the weasel’s carcass?
No, no.
You like eating this, don’t you?
You can grill it.
If you don’t mind, please
stay here for the night.
Of course we don’t.
Here, help me grill this.
By the way, ma’am,
I have a favor to ask.
You’ve been staying here
for so many years.
Have you seen anyone like this?
Well, let me see.
He does look familiar.
Really?
But I’ve had so many guests in my inn.
I can’t really remember.
Si Feng.
Where are you?
I say, Liu Yi Huan is dubious.
We’ve already searched all over
the southern region for a whole year,
but there’s still no sign of him.
Could it be that he doesn’t
want you to find Si Feng,
so he pointed us to the wrong direction?
No.
That’s not how Brother Liu is.
Perhaps for the past year,
Si Feng has been migrating around.
Fine.
Anyway, we’re about to reach
the southernmost region.
So where should we go next?
I heard Si Feng say that
the Rose Gold Birds
used to live in the west.
Let’s head west tomorrow.
Mister Yi.
You’re finally here.
I saw your memo.
Well?
Did someone slay the demon?
Yes.
But it’s just a random girl from nowhere.
We’re still unsure about her skills.
Why don’t you take a look,
Mister Yi?
No need.
The demon is gone.
Now that you’re finally here,
I can’t make you come for nothing.
Why don’t you stay here for dinner?
No need.
Mister Yi!
Flying Snake.
Let’s buy some rations for our journey.
What do you want to eat?
Anything delicious will do.
It’s Sanqing tea.
Sanqing tea? What’s that?
It’s made from morning dew,
pine nuts and Buddha’s hands.
Si Feng drinks that every day.
Si Feng is here!
Si Feng!
Si Feng, Si Feng!
Who are you?
I just flew up to get a good view.
I think you’re mistaken.
Si Feng isn’t here.
Impossible, I’m sure I saw Si Feng.
I can’t be wrong.
I’m not leaving.
I’m staying here to look for Si Feng.
Masters.
Can you pay a visit to Huangdi Town?
Our livestock has been dying mysteriously.
I’m afraid it’s the work of the demons.
We’ll go there in a few days’ time.
How much money do you need?
Forget about money.
We just want to look for someone.
Please ask the townsfolk
if they have seen this man.
I’ll ask them.
Masters, please take a look at my place.
I think it’s haunted.
What’s with you?
I thought you’d ask Mister Yi
for help when it comes to demons.
Why are you asking them for help?
Have you forgotten
all about Mister Yi?
We’d love to ask him for help too,
but he’s so mysterious and elusive.
Whenever we need his help,
we can only leave a letter
in the town’s mailbox,
and we still won’t get any news from him.
We just couldn’t find him.
That’s right.
We can’t help it.
When are you two leaving?
You’ve been here for over a month.
Aren’t you looking for someone?
You should get moving.
What’s wrong?
Do you think that we’re
stealing your crush’s business?
You’re just a bunch of amateurs.
When Mister Yi is back,
you’ll go out of business.
Ah Lan, don’t argue with our guests.
My osmanthus wine is about to mature.
Go give a jar to Mister Yi.
Sure.
You look so happy at
the mention of Mister Yi.
Your crush only appears
once in a blue moon.
Is he a nutcase like they say?
None of your business.
He’s a fine example of a man.
He’s principled, stern and capable.
Besides, he may be cold towards everyone,
but maybe not so towards his wife.
He’s my type.
Does he have a wife?
No, but he will get one soon.
Are you talking about yourself?
Actually, he does fancy me a bit.
I fancy him too.
If he’s willing to marry me,
of course I’ll be his wife.
I can even marry him tomorrow.
That’s why I’m making this clear.
Don’t you take advantage
of Mister Yi.
Otherwise, I won’t let you off.
She said she won’t let us off.
This girl...
Sorry for making you witness a farce.
How is that a farce?
I’m envious of her, in fact.
Si Feng.
What color is this?
It’s a light-blue hydrangea.
So this is blue.
How pretty.
I love blue the most.
So you’ve decided to like blue.
I’ve always liked it.
What are you doing here?
Ah Lan, here’s a question.
Is that the road to
Old Li’s house in Huangdi Town?
Why should I tell you?
Fine, you don’t have to tell me.
I’ll just follow you.
I know you’re looking for Mister Yi.
It’s that way, just follow the path down.
Does Mister Yi live nearby?
Why are you looking for his house?
You know we’ve been searching for someone.
I want to see if Mister Yi
might know anything.
No need, he hates strangers.
Besides, all he does
is foraging for herbs.
He doesn’t like socializing.
He won’t know
the person you’re looking for.
You should go now.
Move!
Mister Yi.
I’ve brought you some wine.
No rewards come without merit.
How can I take your wine for free?
What merit? I don’t care.
I just want to give you some wine.
Take it back.
No.
You’ve taught me so much about
medicine and spells.
I’ve never paid you.
Take this wine as payment, please?
Mister Yi, listen.
Lately, there are two
wandering cultivators in town.
They’re annoying.
They just won’t leave now,
and everyone’s been
seeking their help instead of yours.
They’re stealing your business.
You should show them a thing or two.
Let them know you came here first.
Since someone is doing my business,
that saves me a lot of trouble.
What if you go out of business?
It’s fine.
I’m satisfied with a simple life.
Let them be.
It’s true that you can
fend for yourself now,
but what if you have
a family in the future?
It’s fine, though.
Even if you don’t have a penny
to your name, I’ll take care of you.
Mister Yi!
I’ve finally found you.
Uncle, what brought you here?
I’ve heard you mention about this place.
This is my uncle.
He lives at the neighboring
Huanglong Town.
Mister Yi, our town is in trouble.
I’m here to ask for your help.
This is what happened.
Lately, every wedding in town
will become a funeral the day after.
Newlyweds have been dying
from mysterious circumstances.
I wonder what demon
has been targeting newlyweds.
Last night, another couple died.
Now, my son is over 30 years
old, and he’s finally found a wife,
but we have to delay his wedding.
If he doesn’t get married soon,
the bride’s family is going to cancel it.
That’s why we’re asking for
your help, Mister Yi.
Please slay the demon
for us, Mister Yi.
There are two new demon slayers
in Xigu Town lately.
Since they’re a man and a woman,
they can act as the newlyweds.
They’re more suitable for this job.
You should look for them.
It’s not that I don’t trust them,
but we’ve hired many
demon slayers and monks,
and they’re all kidnapped
by the demon too.
None of them have returned yet.
The demon is too strong.
Mister Yi, take me along.
We can act as newlyweds too.
Since you’ve been teaching me,
I can help you too.
No, this demon is too vicious.
You’re no match for him.
That demon is so strong, and
those cultivators are just amateurs.
If we let them go,
they might just die.
That’s right, Mister Yi.
Please help us.
Our town’s prospective couples
are all counting on you.
If that’s the case, I shall go there.
Sir, hold the wedding as planned.
Ah Lan, sorry to bother you.
I need you to act as my bride tomorrow.
It’s not a bother.
I don’t mind even if it’s for real.
I have nothing valuable on me.
Please take this
to buy a pair of wedding attire.
You can use the rest for the banquet.
He approached me instead of someone else.
And he gave me such
a huge luminous pearl.
That means he does fancy me, right?
Once we go through the ceremony,
I’ll get my uncle to propose for real.
I’m sure Mister Yi won’t reject.
Ah Lan!
Aren’t you going to serve the guests?
What are you grinning at?
Boss, I’m marrying Mister Yi!
What nonsense is that?
It’s true, I’m going to be
his bride tomorrow.
By then, I’ll be the envy of the town.
I don’t think you’re sick.
Miss Ah Lan, here are your wedding robes.
- Put them here.
- Sure.
Boss, I’m taking two-day off.
I’m going to get married.
I won’t be back for the next two days.
Please keep this luminous pearl for me.
Mister Yi gave me this
as a token of our love.
I’m going to get married.
Ah Lan!
What’s wrong with that stupid girl?
What now?
No one has seen Si Feng.
I say, you must be mistaken.
I’m sure he wasn’t Si Feng.
Impossible, I can’t be wrong.
He is Si Feng.
Miss Chu.
I know you’re knowledgeable.
Can you help me and see
if this thing is worth much?
How much money can I get from it?
Isn’t this a luminous pearl
from Lize Palace?
Look carefully.
I’ve seen this before.
I saw it on Si Feng.
Ma’am, where did you get this?
Mister Yi gave Ah Lan this
as a token of their love.
- Well, is it worth much?
- Mister Yi?
Or was Ah Lan scammed?
Where are they?
Ah Lan was rambling about
marrying Mister Yi.
I don’t know what’s going on too.
I heard that man is sickly.
I don’t know what she sees in him too.
Here comes the couple!
Bow to the heaven and earth.
Si Feng.
We’ve finally found him here.
What a surprise.
Bow to your elders.
Bow down.
Bow to each other.
I sense demons.
What are you doing here?
We saw a demon here,
so we were worried and came.
You mindless wench.
Did we ask for your help?
Do you know you’ve ruined my wedding?
So, you’re Mister Yi.
Why are you looking for Mister Yi?
Si Feng.
We’ve finally found you
after searching everywhere.
Thank goodness you’re here.
Otherwise, we’d still be searching.
You’ve lost weight.
No wonder you look
different from the portrait.
Is there anything you need, miss?
What are you talking about?
Who is Si Feng?
Mister Yi, do you know them?
I have never met them.
I’m afraid you’re mistaken.
Little Phoenix.
She’s Xuan Ji!
Should I know this name?
Si Feng, you...
Don’t you remember me?
I came late, after all.
Have you eaten the Heartless Pill
and forgot all about us?
Then...
Look at this.
This...
You made this lock puzzle.
I’ve read your note inside.
I know you didn’t mean
to hide the truth from me.
I was wrong to blame you.
And this bell.
We contacted each other
with this, Si Feng.
Si Feng, look.
Don’t you remember?
Don’t you remember one single bit?
Si Feng.
If my guess is correct,
you’re the new demon slayers, are you not?
I don’t know why you’re
showing me these knick-knacks
while rambling nonsense on my wedding.
I’m sure you can see
I’m getting married tonight.
I’d like to request you two
to not interfere in our ceremony.
If we had any history, miss,
I’d like to tell you this.
All is in the past.
I hope you will not take them to heart.
If you wish to stay for the banquet...
Auntie, please take them to their seats.
If you don’t,
please leave.
Si Feng, you’re crazy!
You’ve been through so many
hardships for this stinky woman.
How can you forget her?
And you’re marrying another woman now.
Are you done yet?
I know you want to make a quick buck here.
That’s fine.
But if you disturb
our wedding because of this,
don’t you think you’re too mean?
What do you know?
How long have you known him?
He’s known stinky woman
for ten lives, and you?
Ten lives?
More like ten lice.
What are you talking about?
I don’t care what you say.
I only care about this life.
In this life,
Mister Yi belongs to me.
Right?
Uncle, the auspicious hour
is coming, right?
That’s right, you should go now.
Don’t miss the auspicious hour.
Yes, go now.
Fine, Si Feng.
Let’s fight,
and you’ll remember everything!
Stop that, Flying Snake.
Actually,
if you’ve really taken the Heartless Pill,
at least you will be safe.
I wanted to find you
to stay by your side
and ask for your forgiveness.
But...
If you have found someone
you love, and you’re happy now,
then I’m satisfied.
Yes.
I am happy now.
We’re running out of time.
Please exchange your gifts now,
dear newlyweds.
So, Si Feng.
There are so many colors in this world.
Which color looks best?
It’s red.
That’s because a girl looks the prettiest
when she wears her red bridal robe.
You just have to know that
only those who anticipate for love
can remove this mask.
You have removed it.
I know
you and me
are in the same wavelength now.
When we leave here,
we’ll return to Lize Palace.
We’ll get wedded in front of my master.
Enter the bridal chamber.
Stinky woman!
I thought the worst scenario
was him forgetting you.
No, listen to me.
We’ve finally found him
after going through so much.
We can’t let this rest!
Stinky woman.
Stinky woman, say something!
This is it. I’m going to knock him out
and bring him here!
Let’s see if he’d still forget you!
Say, you’re the God of War after all.
Can’t you show him what you’re made of?
Who cares, you can just kidnap him first!
I was wrong.
I hurt him again and again.
I thought that no matter
what I do, wherever I am,
Si Feng would never leave me.
He would always be there, right behind me.
But I was late.
He already has a new life.
And I’m not included in it.
He has taken the Heartless Pill,
so he’s free from the Loveless Curse now.
At least he’s forgotten about
the hurtful things I’ve done to him.
That’s good too.
Brother Liu was right.
That’s the best ending for him.
Stinky woman.
Are you out of your mind?
I came late.
Have you eaten the Heartless Pill
and forgot all about us?
You made this lock puzzle.
I’ve read your note inside.
I know you didn’t mean
to hide the truth from me.
I was wrong to blame you.
And this bell.
We contacted each other
with this, Si Feng.
Si Feng, look.
If my guess is correct,
you’re the new demon slayers, are you not?
I don’t know why you’re
showing me these knick-knacks
while rambling nonsense on my wedding.
If we had any history, miss,
I’d like to tell you this.
All is in the past.
I hope you will not take them to heart.
I’ve hurt Xuan Ji so deeply.
Is she upset too?
Xuan Ji.
This is the only thing I can do.
Mister Yi.
Mister Yi!
Or...
Should I call you Si Feng?
Just call me Mister Yi.
They’re your past acquaintances, right?
Yes.
Then why did you lie to them
that you’re getting married?
I have some history
that I do not wish to recall or repeat.
That’s why I wanted them
to take my hint and leave.
It has to do with Ms Xuan Ji, right?
Was she your significant other?
I do not wish to talk about it.
I’m sorry.
I should be the one apologize.
I dragged you into the mess just now.
Thank you for cooperating with me.
It’s fine, Mister Yi.
I’m glad to help you.
Even if...
I have to help you
forever, I don’t mind.
Your hands are cold.
Are you fine?
I’m fine.
All stinky woman did the entire day
was crying and starving herself.
I’m famished too.
Why are there only leftovers here?
This family must be a bunch of misers.
Can’t they prepare something
better for a wedding?
A wedding?
At least they should have
something better for the newlyweds.
To the bridal chamber!
Yu Si Feng isn’t asleep yet.
I think I shouldn’t peek
on their wedding night.
Mister Yi.
Why don’t I sleep outside?
It’s cold outside, and you’re frail.
You’ll catch a cold.
Since we’re putting up an act,
we have to make it look real.
Don’t worry, this demon targets newlyweds.
I’m sure he holds a deep grudge
towards newlyweds.
Local tradition dictates
three days of wedding celebration.
I’m sure the demon will be back
within three days.
If you sleep outside, it’ll be
bad if the demon finds us out.
You should spend the night here.
Then, why don’t I sleep on the floor?
You can take the bed.
No need. Rest early.
So, Yu Si Feng,
you’re not really married.
You’re playing me and stinky woman
around like two fools.
- Really? Si Feng’s not married?
- That’s right.
Who’d sleep separately
on their wedding night?
One sleeps on the bed,
and the other on the floor.
They’re treating
each other like strangers.
They’ve fooled us!
I think they’re setting
a trap up for some demon.
I’m going to find him.
For what? Steal his business?
- I...
- Please don’t embarrass us, will you?
But what if he did take the pill,
forget about me
and marry that girl for real?
If you ask me,
something fishy is going on.
Think about it,
a lady approaches him and cries.
Even if he doesn’t know her,
he would’ve asked something.
But he didn’t, isn’t that weird?
Well, let me test him,
and we’ll know.
Ah Lan, stay here.
Don’t go anywhere.
This is bad, we followed
the demon all the way here,
but that demon is too strong!
He even kidnapped Xuan Ji!
- Where did they go?
- Over there.
She’s the God of War.
What kind of demon can kidnap her?
Haven’t you forgotten about her?
Why do you remember
that she’s the God of War?
Stinky woman, come out.
Little Phoenix didn’t take
the Heartless Pill after all.
He’s never forgotten about you.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, don’t go.
Do you think this is fun?
I’ve been searching for ages,
and I’ve finally found you.
Since you wouldn’t
acknowledge me, I had to do this.
Don’t be angry.
Come on, stinky woman went through
a lot just to search for you.
You two can talk it
out or even fight it out.
Settle your scores once and for all.
Stop hiding around.
I’ve been looking for you
for the past year.
No one knows where you went.
It was Brother Liu
who said you’re in the south.
Why must you search for me?
Ting Nu told me about the Loveless Curse.
If you didn’t take the Heartless
Pill, then how is your health now?
Does it hurt?
I’m fine now.
As long as you don’t show yourself to me,
I won’t die.
Si Feng, I know I was wrong.
You can do anything to me,
but don’t leave me without a word.
Xuan Ji.
I’ve never been angry at you.
The past is all but history to me.
I don’t believe that.
If you don’t care about me,
what does the hydrangeas
in front of your house mean?
Hydrangeas are common in Xigu Town.
If that confuses you,
I shall pull them out.
Si Feng, I do know I was wrong.
I’ve done you wrong.
I regret not trusting you.
I was a fool, so please don’t go.
If you do feel regret,
please do me a favor.
Tell me, I can do anything for you.
Stay away from me as far as possible.
Mister Yi, help!
Ah Lan!
Si Feng!
That’s a lot of bridal gowns.
This must be the demon’s nest.
While killing demons is your clan’s
duty, you can’t kill the innocent.
I didn’t mean it.
I couldn’t see clearly.