LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 15
Let me see your Destiny Pearl.
Don’t try to have any ideas about it.
I know something’s inside it.
The spirit key of Xuanyuan
Sect is hidden in that pearl.
I’ve been looking it for a long time.
Just give it to me.
The spirit key is very important.
We can’t let a demon like you hold it.
I’m different from the demons in Sky Hall.
I’m just trying to save Wu Zhi Qi
with the spirit key.
I can give you the spirit key,
but only on one condition.
What condition?
You’re the only person who knows
how to cast spell in Mount Gao.
I’m sure the others have no idea
about the Mirror of Origin.
I think the mirror shard is in your hand.
You can use the mirror shard
to exchange for your spirit key.
Mirror of Origin?
I’ve never heard of it.
Mount Gao is a huge place.
You can look for
the mirror shard yourself.
- I don’t know anything.
- You’re lying.
I saw it.
- Xuan Ji!
- Ling Long!
Xuan Ji, are you okay?
Why did you come up here?
It’s dangerous, you know?
Didn’t I ask you to wait for us
down below?
Someone would’ve become
the wife of a bandit chief
if I didn’t come and rescue her.
By the way, you said you didn’t know
about the Mirror of Origin, right?
How do you explain the mirror
inside your Maze Formation?
Dumb girl! Keep quiet!
So what if that’s the mirror shard?
I’ll take both the spirit
keys and the mirror shard.
You!
Sky Hall?
Are they all dead?
They...
You demons! You will pay for this!
Kill them!
Weren’t you amazing just now?
Burn them with your Samadhi Fire then!
I... I can’t use it right now.
So, you’re just an amateur.
I can see colours now.
- Wu Tong?
- What a busy scene.
- Long time no see.
- Wu Tong?
All the people I’m looking for
are actually here?
Wu Tong, why are you here?
What?
You didn’t expect me to be alive, right?
Sorry to disappoint you.
I’m quite tough.
I told you before.
I’ll drill a hole in you
if I see you again.
There’s more than one hole in my body.
Come on.
My arms are always open for you.
Wu Tong, it’s been a long time.
I didn’t expect you to join
the demons in Sky Hall.
I was forced to a dead end
by your so-called righteous sects.
I was almost dead.
Only the demons gave me a place to hide.
Why can’t I join them?
But, I have to
thank you for this.
If not, I wouldn’t be the
glorious person I am right now.
You’re welcome.
You deserved everything
due to your evil deeds.
You don’t need to find excuses
and blame others for your mistakes.
It’s been so many years,
but I didn’t expect
Lize Palace and Shaoyang Sect
to still be in a good relationship.
This is so interesting.
You became a lackey of Sky Hall.
You felt proud even though
you were just their lackey.
Isn’t that more interesting?
All of you, listen up.
I will make those who had
insulted me pay thousandfold.
If you don’t want to end up
like the old guys in Xuanyuan Sect,
you better give me the spirit key.
Xuanyuan Sect?
Don’t tell me you’ve...
It’s a pity that you didn’t
get to witness it for yourself.
Your Sect Leader Zhu Shi, he
was killed by his own disciples.
I made them kill him
in exchange for the antidote.
You didn’t see how
hardworking they were
in order to obtain the antidote.
You!
This is just the start.
Just wait and see.
I’ll reduce all your righteous sects
into ashes.
In order to appease my hatred!
Take them down! Leave none of them alive!
Bring them and retreat! Cover me!
What are you trying to do?
Protect the spirit key! Go now!
Run!
- Stand down!
- Who is this?
Who exactly are you?
Why are you always appearing in my dream?
You think you’re great after
you’ve slain many Asuras?
Even the Jade Emperor
can’t save you now!
What did I do wrong?
You were in the wrong!
Dingkun Sword!
- Ling Long.
- Little Six.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
Over there.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, please wake up!
Si Feng, you...
Si Feng!
Si Feng, are you okay?
This...
Si Feng!
Si Feng, are you awake?
You’re finally awake!
Xuan Ji?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Don’t worry, I’m fine.
The water flushed us into this valley.
That’s why Wu Tong
wasn’t able to pursue us.
That’s good.
Don’t move.
I’m applying medicine for you.
I’ve dressed up all your
wounds except for this area.
Don’t worry. I’ve checked your body.
There are no other wounds.
Xuan Ji,
did you see anything else
besides my wounds?
What do you mean?
Listen, I need to dress
up this wound for you.
That way, you’ll heal faster.
Chu Xuan Ji,
why do you always remove
a man’s clothes without any care?
You’re a lady.
It’s impolite for you to do so.
I...
But, when you did the same thing
four years ago,
you said we mustn’t be shy
when it comes to applying medicine.
Remove your clothes now.
- What exactly are you trying to do?
- I want to help you.
No need.
I don’t need your help.
I’ll do it myself.
I’ll inspect my wounds over there.
Si Feng, I told you not to move.
Your wounds won’t be able to heal
if you move around.
My mask!
Where’s my mask?
Your mask?
You were bleeding underneath your mask.
I thought you were seriously injured.
I removed the mask because I was anxious.
You removed it?
Did you really remove it?
Si Feng, did I do something wrong again?
I’m so dumb.
I forgot about the rules of your sect.
I shouldn’t remove your mask like that.
Don’t worry.
It’s outside. I’ll get it back for you.
Xuan Ji!
I...
Si Feng, what’s wrong?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I’m just happy.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, what’s wrong?
Are your wounds hurting again?
Sit down now. Slowly.
Come.
Si Feng,
are you okay?
I’m so happy right now.
Do you know?
I was worried that
you couldn’t remove the mask.
I thought
I would have to wait for a long time.
Si Feng, you’re not angry?
You wouldn’t even let me touch
your mask in the past, you know?
- But this time...
- Silly girl.
You knew it all along, didn’t you?
I didn’t mean what I said.
I wished you would look at it
and touch it.
I hoped you would remove the mask.
I originally thought
that this great fortune
would not embrace me this soon.
Why is removing the mask sometimes good
and sometimes bad to Lize Palace?
I don’t understand.
Silly girl.
It’s complicated.
You just need to know that
only the person whom
the holder treasures the most
can remove the mask.
If that person can remove it,
the mask will become a smiling mask.
It becomes a blessing.
And it’s a good thing.
But if that person can’t remove it,
it’ll be a sad story.
And it’ll become a crying mask.
Until... Until what?
That’s not important.
The important thing is
you’ve removed the mask.
I know.
I know we’re thinking the same thing.
We’ll return to Lize Palace
once we leave this place.
We’ll meet my master together
and give him an explanation.
Will your master punish you again?
I need to return to Lize Palace
and give an explanation no matter what.
Only then,
Only then I can account for you.
After that,
we’ll be together forever.
Together forever with you?
Si Feng,
why did your face change colour?
Are you blushing?
I’m not.
You are.
- You are. Look.
- I’m not.
- You’re blushing.
Look at your blushing face.
This is great!
I can be with you forever!
Si Feng, you’re the best!
- Look!
- Stop it.
You’re blushing!
I’m not.
Xuan Ji, you said you
can see colours now.
Tell me then. What colour did you see?
Red colour.
You can see colours now?
I saw your face turning red.
Look, it’s still red.
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji, stop it.
Xuan Ji, can you identify
other colours besides red?
Ling Long said the wedding dress is red.
And eyebrows are black, am I right?
Yes.
Si Feng, are your eyebrows same
as what was written in the book?
Are they as black as ink?
You’re right. They’re black.
What’s the colour of your lips then?
They’re red as well.
But why are our lips and the
wedding dress different in colour?
Both of them are red.
The wedding dress is bright red in colour.
It’s dazzling.
Our lips are pinkish red in colour.
They’re gentle and elegant.
There are so many
different hues to a colour?
Si Feng, what colour
is the land then?
The land is yellow in colour.
Si Feng, there are so many colours
in the world.
Which colour is the best?
Red.
Because women look best when
they wear a red wedding dress.
Si Feng, did I do the right
thing by removing your mask?
Of course.
Since I did something right,
shouldn’t you grant me a request?
No problem.
I’ll change your dressing for you then.
It must be painful.
It does.
That’s why you need to
dress up your wounds.
You won’t be in pain after that.
Tell me if it’s too painful.
Yan Ran, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Your mask...
It fell by itself.
I have nothing to do with it.
Don’t blame me for this.
You should try and patch it together.
Never mind.
The mask has been broken.
It won’t return to its original state.
I will return and accept my punishment.
I wonder how Si Feng
and the rest are doing?
We shouldn’t waste any time.
Let’s go.
- Did you discover anything?
- No.
Stop wasting time here.
Our leader asked us to search
from the top to the bottom.
We must find those cultivators.
- And obtain the spirit key.
- Yes.
Let’s go.
I wonder if Xuan Ji and the rest are safe?
You have the Sound Bell with you, right?
Try and see if you can contact them.
You’re right.
Xuan Ji, can you hear me?
Ling Long.
How are you doing?
I’m with Min Yan. We’re fine.
Where are you?
We’ll look for you.
No need. Don’t come and find us.
Si Feng and I are
in the bottom of a valley.
The undercurrent took us
to an unknown location.
You don’t need to find us.
You should leave Mount Gao now.
How could I just leave without you?
Moreover, I don’t know the location of
Ruo Yu and Yan Ran.
We don’t know where we are,
but we’re safe.
We’ll find a way out later.
It’s dangerous for you to stay there.
You should report to Fuyu Island.
Ruo Yu and Yan Ran should be fine.
We’ll try to contact them
after we leave this place.
Okay. You be careful then.
The spirit key is hidden inside
the Destiny Pearl in Xuan Ji’s hand.
You should rush back to Fuyu Island
and hand it over to the elders there.
See you on Fuyu Island.
It’s good that they’re fine.
I didn’t expect the Destiny Pearl
to attract demons from Sky Hall.
And I didn’t expect Wu Tong
to be one of them as well.
I’m afraid Xuanyuan Sect is gone now.
If it weren’t for Mount Gao’s
complex structure,
we would’ve been gone as well.
Sky Hall is far more stronger
than we thought.
If our sects don’t work together
against them,
they’ll become a big threat.
Si Feng, are your wounds hurting again?
You were severely wounded.
You need some food to recover.
Wait for me. I’ll find you some food.
Be careful.
Don’t worry. I have no problem
finding food.
Chu Xuan Ji has the spirit key indeed.
We’ve surrounded the entire mountain,
but we couldn’t find anyone.
I was thinking that you
might be hiding here.
I was right.
Wu Tong, you gave
up on being a human.
You became the lackey of demons instead.
You wretch!
Take them down!
Ling Long!
Wretch, you’re
finally in my hands!
You pervert! Let me go!
You’re still as stubborn as ever.
Where’s Chu Xuan Ji?
Min Yan!
- Despicable!
- I’m despicable?
The Five Great Sects are despicable
for trying to hunt me down!
I still have debts to settle
with the Five Great Sects.
As long as you’re in my hand,
I’m sure your sister will show up.
Kill him.
Let go of me!
Ling Long!
Strange.
Is this a barrier?
I can’t cast any spells.
I can’t leave as well.
The Four Sacred Beasts are here
to report the current situation.
King Bailing is not here.
Just leave the report here.
It’s Flying Snake again.
It can’t stop creating trouble.
This is too much!
King Bailing only wanted
you to keep watch over me
so that I would not create trouble.
But now, I have something to do
in the human realm!
Our king said that
if you leave this place,
you’ll wreak havoc down below.
That’s why you won’t be able to leave.
It’s glowing.
It’s glowing!
Look, it’s glowing!
You know what this is, right?
When the God of War was punished,
her sword was sent to the human realm too.
Her Dingkun Sword is hard to control.
King Bailing had no choice
but to seal it away.
And he gave the medallion to me.
That’s why I became Lord Flying Snake.
Someone is trying to take
the Dingkun Sword!
Let me leave and check that out!
My lord, you’re the guardian of
Dingkun Sword. This is not a joke.
- Please stop joking around.
- Glow!
Glow now!
Hurry up and glow!
Lord Flying Snake, if you do this again,
I’ll call for Lord Green Dragon.
Fine. I won’t argue with you.
I’ll go back to sleep.
Listen, I’m not doing this because
I’m afraid of that Green Dragon.
Xuan Ji!
- Si Feng!
- Are you okay?
The lightning is trying to strike me!
Let’s go in!
Why would it try to strike you?
I don’t know. Seems like
there’s a barrier around it.
We’re isolated from the outside world.
We can’t cast any spell.
Look, there are
no other living beings here.
And we can’t leave as well.
Actually, we don’t need to worry.
We need to be here
for a few days no matter what.
It’s the same with or without the barrier.
Think about it. We came out of the pool.
I’ll see if we can leave using the
same route after my wounds healed.
We still need to be here for a few days?
It’s lucky that I’m smart.
I’ve gathered many fruits.
We will starve to death without them.
Xuan Ji, you’re the best.
I’ll wash them for you.
Is it nice?
It is.
You should eat more then.
It’s delicious.
It’s that good?
Si Feng, this is very bitter.
It’s not nice at all.
Apricot kernels are bitter naturally.
I’m afraid your tummy has to
suffer for a few days.
That will be the saddest thing in life.
I figured you would be hungry
in the mountains.
I brought a bun.
You should eat this.
This will be so delicious.
Si Feng, you should have some as well.
No thanks.
I only eat the buns from Yongfang Court.
You’re being particular
even when we’re in this situation?
I’ll rather be particular
than to compromise.
If I must choose,
I would choose wild fruits over
buns that are not from Yongfang Court.
Do you know what I feel like eating now?
Osmanthus cake with lotus seed
from Liufengzhai.
It’s sweet, delicious, and fragrant.
This is the cake.
Delicious.
This will be the most delicious
Peach Chicken from my house then.
The Eight Treasure Duck
from Guangyun Court.
Roasted deer.
The beef noodles in Kelaiju Inn
are great as well.
With so many delicious dishes,
and with some Drunken
Dragon from Liuxianlou, cheers.
- This is so delicious!
- Eat this then.
I won’t eat that. I’ll leave it for you.
I’ll eat this.
Si Feng.
Cover yourself.
Let’s sleep together.
You’re really testing me all the time.
I’m not a saint.
Do you know how happy
I was when I knew that
you could remove my mask?
If you continue this,
I won’t be able to stand it anymore.
I know now.
I know you can pass your message
to other people with this.
Is this the thing you use to
contact Chu Xuan Ji?
Seems like it is.
How do you use this?
Ask Chu Xuan Ji to hand over
the spirit key right now.
No way.
Wretch, how dare you reject me!
You’re in my hands.
If you don’t follow my orders,
I have more than a thousand ways
to deal with you.
I will let you suffer so much
that you wish you were dead.
I will make you suffer
until you follow my orders.
Do you want to try it now?
You better listen to me right now.
I hate lackeys like you the most!
I hate it even more when
I’m threatened by a lackey!
You’ll never get the spirit key!
Young Lady, you’re
overestimating yourself.
The Sky Hall has countless demons inside.
Do you think I can only obtain the
spirit key by holding you as a hostage?
I’m just teasing you.
It’s more interesting
when you don’t listen to me.
We’ve been missing our marks lately.
- What should we do?
- This mustn’t continue on.
- Let’s walk around.
- Yes.
Why is there a person here?
- Let’s have a look.
- Let’s go!
So beautiful!
Si Feng,
what colour is this?
The hydrangea is blue.
This is blue?
It’s nice.
My favourite colour is blue!
You have decided to like the colour blue?
I like it since I was young.
I’ll bring it with me and I’ll show it
to Ling Long and Sixth Senior.
Xuan Ji, let’s check if
there’s an exit over there.
- Okay.
- Let’s go.
This is strange.
We were washed ashore by the same pool.
But now, we can’t even touch the water.
We’ve been stuck here for some days.
We couldn’t contact Ling Long
and Min Yan as well.
What should we do?
We should try and seek another exit.
I think something is hidden in here.
That’ll explain the barrier.
I’m sure the barrier has a weakness.
Xuan Ji, where’s my mask?
The mask? Didn’t you say
you don’t need it anymore?
We still need to find it?
I need to bring it back in order
to give my master an explanation.
Maybe, it could even help us out.
The mask is made from the bark
of the Undying Tree.
It’s filled with spiritual energy.
Maybe it can help us
break through the barrier.
Si Feng,
didn’t you say the mask will become
a smiling mask after it was removed?
Why is it crying?