LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 14
You are still fine after inhaling
my Love Smoke?
You are a woman?
You disguised as a man to trick me.
Mount Gao will never spare a woman!
Don’t hurt her.
Interesting.
I never thought that
both of you are a couple.
I hate couples the most in my life.
Okay. I won’t kill her.
Let’s play a game.
I’m going to inhale all
the Yang energy dry out of your lover.
I’ll make him into my slave completely.
Then, he’ll forget about you completely.
As for you, you can only
think and long for him.
But you’ll never see him again forever.
How about that?
Let go of me!
Si Feng!
Let me in!
Where were they taken too?
We can’t find them anywhere.
They are not in any danger, right?
Enough. Stop nagging.
You are making my head hurts.
I’m worried about them.
Unlike you. You are not worried at all.
But right now, the most important thing
for them is their safety.
- I can’t wait like this any longer.
- What can you do then?
Xuan Ji.
Ling Long.
I can hear you. How are you now?
- Have you met Goddess Gao?
- We’ve met her.
But Si Feng and Sixth Senior
have been captured.
What?
That Goddess Gao is actually
a thousand-year-old fox demon.
She feeds on the energy of the human
to increase her power.
She already noticed us earlier on and
deliberately tricked us to Mount Gao.
Moreover, Si Feng and the others
are under the influence of Love Smoke.
I don’t know where they are now.
I know that Si Feng will be in trouble
when he’s with you.
Let me ask you. Si Feng has been captured.
What about you? Why didn’t you save them?
Don’t vent out your anger on my sister.
I’m trapped too.
But don’t worry.
I’ll definitely save them.
Xuan Ji, tell me. Where are you now?
I’m not sure.
But I remember that the fox’s
palace is between two mountains.
And there’s a stream in the middle.
Stream? Isn’t that a stream?
Xuan Ji, we got it.
We’ll go and save you now, okay?
Be careful.
You too.
Let’s go.
Ling Long.
Ling Long!
This fox demon is really bad.
Why does she love tying things up?
She even tied this stone monkey up.
You filthy demon, don’t think of
seducing me and killing me.
Killing you?
I can’t bear to do that.
Isn’t it a pity to lose someone
as handsome as you are?
Are you just going to let us stare
on the ceiling?
You are such a killjoy.
Since you’re so
impatient, how about...
This mask is such an eyesore.
Why can’t I take it off?
Could it be that
this is the Loveless Mask?
You know about it?
I have lived for a thousand years.
Of course I know about it.
I never thought that you are such
an infatuated guy.
You are a thousand years old demon.
Do you still think that you are
a young and beautiful lady?
You’re really shameless.
Who are you calling old?
If you say this kind of
nonsense again, I’ll eat you!
All of you better don’t make me mad.
So what if we make you mad?
You flirtatious and shameless fox.
You’ll be sent to Fenru City
to suffer when you die.
And you’ll never be allowed
to become a deity.
Are you trying to scare me?
Let me tell you.
I’m eager to enter Fenru City.
Good.
Since you want to do it the hard way,
I’ll let you have a taste of my power.
Brother Ruo Yu.
Yan Ran?
Ling Long.
Ling Long, you are not angry
at me anymore, right?
Why will I be angry at you?
I like you so much.
Really?
- Who is it?
- Xuan Ji, it’s me.
You are that merman?
My name is Ting Nu.
Xuan Ji, long time no see.
I never thought that I’ll see you here.
Has your wound healed? Why are you here?
Long story.
Let’s talk about you first.
Why are you here?
I was caught by that fox demon.
This purple fox is too stubborn.
She wouldn’t listen to me.
Are you saying that she caught you
to help her increase her power too?
She caught me for another purpose.
Actually, Purple Fox is doing something
that is out of her capability.
Do you really can’t remember anything?
Never mind.
I used to be a medic
from the heavenly realm.
I was sent to earth because
I was involved in an incident.
She wants to know about an event that
happened in heavenly realm 1000 years ago.
So, she caught me.
She thought that everyone who had been
in the heavenly realm will know about it.
How would an unimportant official
like me know about that incident?
But Purple Fox wouldn’t believe me.
So, she kept me here.
So, you were once a deity
from the heavenly realm.
What does the heavenly realm look like?
Is it beautiful?
There’s a lotus pond
in the heavenly realm.
There were once a beautiful general,
a goddess of war.
And she would talk to the Rose Gold Bird
every day by the pond.
It was the most beautiful scene
that I’ve ever seen.
Although heavenly realm is beautiful,
there are disputes between deities too.
Let’s not talk about it anymore.
By the way, just now, you said that
your seniors have been
taken away by Purple Fox.
I don’t know what is that
fox doing to my seniors now.
I have to find her and defeat her.
- And then, I’ll save everyone.
- Xuan Ji.
If you want to defeat Purple Fox,
you have to find her real body.
Her real body?
She is 1000 years old. She is now
separated from her fox body.
She is taking the form of a deity now.
Mortals will not be able to defeat her.
No wonder I couldn’t score a hit on her.
Where is her real body then?
Bring me with you. I can help you.
But...
- This...
- I’ll be fine.
Although I can’t walk
on land, I have a solution.
Look.
But the Purple Fox has concealed
this place with spell.
Our tribe has zero attack power.
So, I couldn’t break the barrier here.
But it should not be hard for you.
Si Feng.
We haven’t seen each other for four years.
I missed you a lot.
I’m very happy that you are cursed with
the Loveless Mask because of me.
Actually, I fell in love
with you on first sight.
Xuan Ji.
I think it’s just around here.
Where is it?
What should we do?
So much time has passed.
If we can’t find it,
Si Feng and the others will be in trouble.
Xuan Ji, calm down.
Although Purple Fox’s real body is in
slumber, its six senses are still opened.
Every living thing has a sound
that they hate the most.
Let’s give it a try.
And make it come to us.
It’s indeed here.
I’m going to catch it now.
Xuan Ji. Don’t be rash.
Purple Fox is not an evil demon.
Don’t kill her.
But she took my friends.
How can I let her go?
Threaten her with her true body
and she’ll release your friends.
No. She did something bad.
I have to kill her.
You are still the same.
What do you mean?
It’s not easy for others
to take the form of a human.
Actually, she has never
hurt anyone before.
She just took the wrong turn
because she was too anxious.
Spare her.
She has never hurt someone?
I don’t believe it.
Look. She just trapped you just now.
She didn’t hurt you.
Besides, you have the true body
of Purple Fox now.
Spare her first.
If you really find out that she’s
doing evil, you can kill her then.
But if so, how am I going to
save Si Feng and the others?
If you trust me, leave
this matter to me.
Our tribe has psychic power.
I can use her real body to let you
communicate with her for a while
in order to save your seniors.
Si Feng.
Are you going to do anything
that I ask?
Si Feng!
Who is it?
My true body.
- Who are you? How dare you! Brat.
- Let Si Feng go!
How dare you threaten me.
Xuan Ji, show some mercy!
Xuan Ji.
Are you okay?
Min Yan.
Ling Long.
Si Feng?
- Are you okay, Ruo Yu?
- I’m fine.
Si Feng.
Are you okay?
That demon fox didn’t
do anything to you, right?
Cut the nonsense.
This is bad.
That demon fox said that
she likes you the most just now.
Disciples of Lize Palace are not allowed
to be intimate with women, right?
Did she mark you? Hurry up and check.
Zhong Min Yan, let me tell you.
Don’t ever tell Xuan Ji about this.
Of course I won’t.
You can’t tell Ling Long too.
Or else, my reputation will be ruined.
- It’s a deal then.
- You’ll be single forever if you break it.
I will not tell anybody about this.
Si Feng, what do you mean
by don’t tell Xuan Ji about it?
- Don’t tell me that the one you saw is...
- Cut the nonsense.
We have to leave now.
The fox is probably coming back soon.
Let’s go.
What kind of a place is this?
I remember that
we came from this direction.
Let’s go there and take a look.
Why are we back
at the starting point again?
That evil fox.
We must have fallen into
her maze formation or what.
Fox demons are good in
hallucination spells.
This is probably a spell of deceit.
Why is there a drawing here
out of the blue?
This is fishy.
Maybe there’s a secret mechanism here.
Don’t simply touch it.
There’s a formation on this drawing.
If you simply touch it,
it’ll be dangerous.
I didn’t even realise that.
Do you know how to
break this formation then?
If my guess is right,
this must be the eye of the formation.
I found it.
Amazing, Si Feng.
Now I know why the disciples of
Lize Palace have to wear mask.
If someone as handsome and
as amazing as you travel the world,
all the girls will follow you
like bees to honey.
Now is not the time to joke around.
This palace is full of danger. I wonder if
Xuan Ji has gone out safely or not.
If she has gone out, she will be
with Yan Ran and Ling Long now.
And they’ll wait for us in Zhongli City.
That’s for the best.
If she would just leave like that,
she wouldn’t be Chu Xuan Ji.
I’m sure that she’s just
around here, trying to save us.
Let’s go.
I never thought that
you’ll be so weak in this life.
This is bad.
You must have angered
the Purple Fox when you did that.
She must be on her way here.
Go now. Or else, you’ll be in danger!
No. I can’t leave Si Feng
and the others behind.
- I have to save them.
- Xuan Ji, leave now.
She is 1000 years old.
She has gone through the 36 Trials.
Mortal fire is useless against her.
It’ll be too late if you don’t leave now.
No, I have to save Si Feng and the others.
Today, it’ll be either her or us
who will die here.
Xuan Ji, why do you have to be so extreme?
She has never killed anyone before.
Spare her life.
How is that possible?
She almost killed Si Feng just now.
What about the people in Zhongli City?
She’ll take four men every year, right?
Where are they?
You are right.
I killed all of them.
What can you do to me? Avenge them?
By the way, I’ve already
killed your lover-in-mask too.
Lover-in-mask?
No. Impossible.
- Si Feng will be fine.
- How is it impossible?
Who am I? Killing a mortal human
is easy for me.
Your lover is called Si Feng?
He’s really infatuated with you.
He kept calling your name before he died.
Si Feng will not die.
You are just spouting nonsense!
Purple Fox.
Stop saying nonsense out of anger.
So what if I’m mad?
Brat. Come and seek
your revenge if you can.
By the way, I forgot to tell you that
Si Feng has already become a dry corpse.
The other two have died
a horrible death too.
No!
It’s not easy for us to meet again.
It’s not easy to make him come
to the human world to train with me.
We promised to be together.
How dare you hurt him!
So what if I had hurt him?
You are just a powerless little girl.
If you don’t want to die, get out now!
Fine.
Then, you can try dying too.
The Samadhi Fire?
Don’t come near me.
I didn’t kill anyone.
I’ve never killed anyone before.
I didn’t kill your friends!
Don’t come near me!
Ting Nu, save me!
Xuan Ji, stop. She is telling the truth!
Xuan Ji!
Xuan Ji.
Don’t do this.
You’ll hurt yourself.
Si Feng. She...
Just now, she said that she killed you.
So, I was furious.
- Are you okay?
- I’m fine.
I...
What did I do just now?
Just now,
you almost hurt this fox
demon with Samadhi Fire.
Samadhi Fire?
But... But I’ve never
learnt about Samadhi Fire.
Can’t you walk faster? How can you
save them if you are so weak?
What’s the point of walking fast? We
should think about where the entrance is.
Hurry up.
Since she is a 1000-year-old fox demon,
these must be
her children and grandchildren.
We’ll find the entrance if we follow them.
Of course. They are all foxes.
Let’s go.
Let go of me.
Look.
Your friends are fine.
Not a scratch on them.
- Let me go.
- Shut up.
Since everyone is fine,
please forgive her this time.
You are that merman four years ago.
Yes.
I am Ting Nu.
It’s you.
Why are you defending this fox demon
who harmed others?
- I didn’t harm anyone.
- You didn’t?
- Why are you pretending as a goddess then?
- None of your business.
If you don’t tell the truth,
I’ll grill you with the Samadhi Fire.
Purple Fox, it has already come to this.
Stop being so stubborn.
Explain it to them.
She caught those people
to feed on their energy.
But in order not to kill them,
she just fed on them a little bit.
Really?
If it wasn’t because
I have to save someone and guard
the Dimension Chain under this Mount Gao,
I wouldn’t suck on others’ energy
to increase my power.
This is so disgusting.
What is a Dimension Chain?
And who are you saving?
In this world, who else
will I wait 1000 years for
and make me do everything I can
to save him?
Could it be that he’s your lover?
It has been 1000 years.
That stupid monkey has already been
chained for 1000 years.
If it wasn’t to save him,
I wouldn’t be like this now.
Why are you torturing yourself like this?
Wu Zhi Qi has never said that
he loves you.
This is just a one-sided love.
When did he say that he doesn’t love me?
Just you watch, when I save him,
he’ll have no choice but to
repay me with himself.
What evil did Wu Zhi Qi do?
Why is he chained?
You are the one who do evil.
Wu Zhi Qi is the freest
and easy man in the world,
He was just tricked to become
the Left Lieutenant of the demon clan.
Then, he got implicated and
was chained by the Dimension Chain.
The demon clan?
Left Lieutenant?
He sounds powerful.
Why can’t he break a chain
even after 1000 years?
You are just a mortal.
What do you know?
This Dimension Chain
is a steel chain made out of
the essence from Mount Gao and
the other three mountains.
There are four of them.
They go straight to
the bottom of Fenru City.
And Wu Zhi Qi is chained there.
This is one of it.
These four chains are extremely tough.
Even the sharpest weapon
will not be able to break them.
But if no one can break it,
why do you have to guard it?
Tell us now.
This Dimension Chain
is bound together by a lock.
And there are four spirit keys
guarded by the major sects in this world.
Seven Star Disc from Dianjinggu.
Destiny Pearl from Xuanyuan Sect.
Moon Blade from Fuyu Island.
Dragon Seal from Lize Palace.
The four spirit keys are hidden inside
four mythological objects of the sects.
If you can gather all four spirit keys,
you’ll be able to unlock Dimension Chain
and I can save Wu Zhi Qi.
Spirit keys?
Ting Nu mentioned about spirit keys
four years ago as well.
What are spirit keys?
All of you are cultivators.
But you don’t even know about this?
How ignorant.
A few thousand years ago, heavenly realm
gave a mission to the major sects here.
They are to use four mythological objects
to guard these spirit keys.
Don’t blame me for not
warning you about this.
The demons of Sky Hall
are looking for these keys as well.
They are not as kind as me.
They are vicious.
Sky Hall?
It’s them again.
Ting Nu, when we saved you four years ago,
you were chased by
the demons of Sky Hall too, right?
They chased after me to find out
how to unlock the Dimension Chain.
And I had no choice
but to tell them about
the locations of the spirit keys.
XUANYUAN
It’s morning and nobody is training
or cleaning the garden.
- This is really unbelievable.
- The incense ash is cold to the touch.
Looks like it has been a few days
since someone lit an incense here
I have a favour to ask from
the three of you.
Give this present to Lord Dong Fang.
Are the demons of Sky Hall
looking for the spirit keys
to save Wu Zhi Qi?
They are not that kind.
They want to save Wu Zhi Qi
because they want to ask for his help
to wake the Star of Mosha.
What is the Star of Mosha?
Why is this the first time
I’ve heard about any of these?
Ignorant humans. You know nothing.
All of you are so narrow-minded.
You won’t understand.
Star of Mosha was the strongest fighter
of Asuras from the demon realm.
It has the power to destroy a world.
A few thousand years ago, king of
Asuras sent Star of Mosha as general
to wage war against the heavenly realm.
In the end, the Star of Mosha
was killed by the God of War.
And that was the fall of the demon realm.
No matter how powerful Star of Mosha is,
he has already been defeated, right?
What’s so scary about it?
But there’s a rumour saying that
the soul of Star of Mosha
cannot be destroyed.
So, it was just sealed by the God of War.
And that his spirit has been reborn after
going through the Path of Reincarnation.
And the demon clans who still
hold a grudge built the Sky Hall.
They want to break the seal to
wake the Star of Mosha.
They’ll cause chaos to the world.
If that’s the case, it’s bad.
Other major sects
still think that Sky Hall
is just made up of
a bunch of lowly demons.
I never thought that they are so powerful.
If that’s the case, I have to go back
and tell my father about it.
You just want to do it now?
The demons of Sky Hall have already
infiltrated all the major sects.
And you just realised it now.
- Don’t you think that it’s too late?
- What did you say?
Sky Hall has been running amuck
for a long time.
Do you think that catching me
is a huge achievement?
What is it? Are you going to bring me back
to get compliments from your father?
- I...
- Cut the nonsense.
Don’t think that you are innocent
just because you told us about Sky Hall.
You said that you didn’t hurt anyone.
Where are you keeping those
whom you caught from Zhongli City?
Those people are living very well
at the backyard of Tianji Pavilion.
If you don’t believe
me, I’ll show you.
Slow down.
Let’s go.
Oh my goodness.
Weren’t we here just now?
Why are we back at the same place?
I told you to turn right just now.
But you wouldn’t listen.
We are back because
I listened to you by turning right.
- We are back because I listened to you.
- You...
This Goddess Gao
is really cunning.
Lu Yan Ran!
You are no help at all.
Why did you activate the trap?
I had to use so much energy to save you.
- So painful.
- Why did you save me? I could have...
Forget it. I don’t want to fight.
Let’s find a way out first.
This drawing must be the drawing
of that demon, Goddess Gao.
She depicts herself like a deity.
So narcissistic.
We are more beautiful, right?
Look. The suction was so strong just now.
But this rush cushion didn’t move at all.
Could it be that this is the mechanism?
Goddess Gao is so narcissistic.
And there’s a solid rush cushion here.
Maybe someone need to kneel before her.
Kneel before her?
How about you kneel before her then?
- Why can’t you kneel? You do it.
- I...
I knew it.
What is this?
Mirror...
- Origin...
- Mirror of Origin.
This is the mirror that
Xuan Ji is looking for?
It must be it. After I bring it back,
Xuan Ji will be able to recover
all of her six senses.
Why can’t I take it?
Forget it.
We won’t be able to take it.
Let’s look for Si Feng first.
I don’t know if he’s in danger or not.
Fine. We’ll save them first and then
come back for the mirror.
The poison inside me
will be activated today.
Is this the end for the
whole Xuanyuan Sect then?
The cave of a monster is like this?
Shouldn’t it be filled
with blood and skeletons?
You watched too many fictions.
Will you be able to stay in
that kind of place?
- Goddess Gao is here!
- Where is she?
There she is!
- Goddess Gao is here!
- Hurry up, Goddess Gao is here!
- Goddess Gao!
- You are here!
All of you are from Zhongli City.
Nobody is holding you hostage now.
Go home.
Why should we leave?
We are chosen by Goddess Gao.
We are blessed.
That’s right.
We are so happy to listen while she
teaches us about cultivation every day.
- That’s right.
- Look.
I didn’t force them to stay.
Since they look up upon you as a deity,
why don’t you ask them to go back?
Listen to me.
I’ve completed my cultivation now.
I have to go back to the heavenly realm.
You can go back now.
If we are fated to meet, I’ll
summon you back here again.
Take care of yourself, Goddess Gao.
I’ve already released them.
Shouldn’t you release me too?
Let me tell you.
I have to gather the spirit keys
before the Sky Hall can.
I have to save Wu Zhi Qi so
that they won’t be able to use him.
And then, those sects of yours
will be safe too.
Why should we believe you?
How can Wu Zhi Qi wake that Star of Mosha
who is sealed by God of War?
I think you are just boasting about it.
I already told you everything I know.
I have nothing else to say
if you don’t believe me.
I just know that mortals like you
are not a match for Sky Hall at all.
If you want to save him,
why did you catch Elder Ling Shi?
What do you want?
None of your business.
For the spirit key, right?
Goddess Gao.
- Goddess Gao, he tried to escape.
- You can go back first.
Okay.
Don’t try to escape.
We’ll bring you back to
Xuanyuan now to be punished.
No. You can take everyone else away.
But not Elder Ling Shi.
I caught him
because I want to know the location
of Xuanyuan’s spirit key.
You demons.
I won’t let you get the spirit key.
Destiny Pearl?
Why is the Destiny Pearl with you?
I think Sect Leader Zhu Shi
slipped it in when he asked us
to bring a birthday present
to the Madam of Fuyu Island.
How fortunate.
How fortunate that it doesn’t
fall into the hands of demons.
But it’s too bad that Xuanyuan
Sect is probably doomed now.
What happened to Xuanyuan Sect?
We brought this upon ourselves.
We brought this upon ourselves!
I was greedy for power
and wanted to restore
the reputation of Xuanyuan Sect.
So, I fell into the trap of Sky Hall.
Kunyin Pill is a fatal poison.
As soon as you stop taking
it, you’ll be poisoned to death.
Sky Hall wanted to use this way
to threaten Xuanyuan Sect
to get the spirit key?
When we wouldn’t do that,
they forced us with the pill.
They gave us a deadline.
So, I could only do my research
about Kunyin Pill in secret.
You controlled the demon spirit
to collect the Bloody Jialuo Fruit
in order to make this pill?
I already know that I can use
Zhuyu Grass and Bloody Jialuo Fruit
to make this Kunyin Pill.
But I don’t know why I failed
every time although I was so close.
Aren’t you ashamed to ask that
after killing so many innocents?
As long as I can save my sect,
what’s wrong with killing some people?
But if you do that,
- how are you different from a demon?
- You...
- You’ve failed as a cultivator.
Are Shaoyang Sect and Lize Palace
feeling so proud of themselves now?
Sky Hall will not give up.
It’ll be you next.
You’ll be next.
- What should we do now?
- Let’s go to Fuyu Island.
It’s the Madam’s birthday.
Every sect will go there.
We can inform them to send help
to Xuanyuan Sect.
But I’m not sure if we can make it or not.