LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 1
Since the reordering of Chaos void,
the heavenly realm has ruled over
the mortal and demon realms.
It’s the head of the three realms.
Yet, more than a thousand years
ago, King Asura became ambitious
and rejected the authority
of heavenly realm.
He finally formed the demon ally
and started wars across borders.
The heavenly realm thought
it’s nothing to be afraid of.
Unexpectedly, King Asura
had an extremely powerful general,
Star of Mosha, Rahu Ketu,
who defeated the heavenly army.
The fellow gods were forced
to retreat to Heavenly Gate.
The Jade Emperor was shocked.
He and King Bailing dispatched
a lot of soldiers to fight the enemy.
But they lost.
The heavenly realm was in danger
and the Asuras was about to
turn the three realms upside down.
It’s at this moment that
something shocking happened.
Star of Mosha disappeared
before the final great war.
At the same time, a saviour
appeared at the heavenly realm.
God of War.
Her invincibility
got rid of all the Asuras.
Without Star of Mosha, the demon realm
was no longer powerful.
It’s totally defeated.
The surviving demons are
scattered all over the world.
Rumour has it that
the death of Star of Mosha
was plotted by God of War.
His soul is sealed inside
a mythological object called Jade Cup.
It’s hidden in an ancient secret area.
And his primordial spirit
was lost in the chaos.
ONE THOUSAND YEARS LATER
However, things change with time.
The universe changes every thousand years.
After a thousand years of rest,
the separated primordial spirit
is gradually regaining its vitality
and waiting for the reunion.
And the demon realm is
eagerly waiting for its revival.
It seems that everything isn’t over yet.
If Star of Mosha returns with
the grievance he’s been accumulated,
the world will be destroyed.
My lord!
Elder of Constellation.
Were you talking about these two stars?
Yes, my lord.
After Star of Mosha, Rahu Ketu died,
two stars have appeared
faraway in the sky.
They’re Rahu Star and Ketu Star.
For the past thousand years,
they’re located at the south
and north respectively.
They had nothing to do with each other.
But today,
these two stars are suddenly
getting closer to one another.
It seems that...
What?
It seems that they’re trying to reunite.
Does it mean he’s
really waking up?
My lord.
That lost primordial spirit
of Star of Mosha
has appeared in the Fenru City.
My men has looked into it.
Half of that primordial spirit
will go to the mortal realm for
a tribulation via the channel of karma.
You deities have done wrong and
been stripped of the immortal forms.
You’re here in the Fenru City
and it’s a chance for you to
reshape your immortal qualities.
Be obedient and head to the mortal realm.
When you successfully
get through the tribulations,
you’ll have the chance to
return to the heavenly realm.
Consider yourselves lucky!
Hurry up!
Drink this Water of Forgetting.
We don’t have all day.
I’m not drinking it!
I don’t want to leave the heavenly realm!
I only stole a flat peach.
- I’m not going to the mortal realm!
- There’s nothing to remember.
It’s just a boring life.
Forget it.
It’s good to forget it.
There’s one more thing, my lord.
As far as I know, God
of War and Star of Mosha
are entering the mortal realm
together for tribulations.
Both of them will be born on the same day,
in the same month and year.
It’s very interesting.
My lord.
Both of them are
destined to be enemies.
Will it ruin our plan of
reviving the demon realm?
No.
God of War used the Divine Weapon
of Star of Mosha to seal his soul.
We need both God of War and
Divine Weapon to save Star of Mosha.
I want both of those kids.
Go look into it quickly.
Find out where God of War
and Star of Mosha will be born.
Yes.
Madam, push!
Yes!
Push again, Madam!
We’re almost there.
Take a deep breath.
Madam.
Madam, take a deep breath!
Push!
- Push, Madam!
- It’s been more than two hours.
Why hasn’t this second child come out yet?
Almost there, madam! Push again!
Is it a difficult labour?
Who are you, demon?
How dare you break into
the forbidden ground of Fenru City!
Don’t delay it,
open the channel of karma now!
Get in now!
Madam.
It’s out.
It’s coming out, madam!
It’s out, madam!
It’s out!
SIXTEEN YEARS LATER
No one thought
madam would give birth to a dead baby
after ten months of pregnancy.
Sect Leader didn’t want to upset her.
Thus, he buried that child on that night.
No one saw what happened
at that midnight coming.
Ghost!
What happened?
Why was there a child crying?
The butler ordered to dig out
the grave of Second Lady.
Guess what happened!
Senior!
That child came back to life!
Our little junior took a long time
to take her first breath.
You’re all the disciples of other uncles.
You didn’t know.
Our little junior was born
without the six senses.
- Senior.
- What?
What are the six senses?
I’ll tell you what they are.
Sight.
Sound.
Smell.
Taste.
And she’s born without
touch and thought too.
She is, to put it politely, heartless.
To put it otherwise,
she’s a good-for-nothing.
Little Junior is now sixteen.
But she hasn’t even mastered
the first level of Shaoyang mantra.
- Really?
- You’re exaggerating.
Fine. You don’t believe me?
I’ll show it to you all today. Let’s go.
Sure, let’s go check it out.
Look at her hand!
She really doesn’t feel pain.
Do you believe me now?
Yes, we do now.
Second Senior.
Is this yours?
Yes.
- Are you alright?
- I’m alright.
Second Senior. If you want to fool me,
you’ve got to be creative about it.
Are you all scared of this?
Yes.
You can’t feel.
Of course you’re not scared of it.
Xuan Ji!
- Xuan Ji!
- Ling Long!
Come, let me take a look at your hand.
It’s all red.
- I’m alright.
- Chen Min Jue!
You!
If you ever bully my sister again,
I’ll ask Father to teach
you a good lesson!
And you! Are you looking for trouble?
My good Junior Ling Long. Don’t get mad.
It’s just a joke.
Enough.
Ling Long, don’t take it seriously.
I don’t know what pain is anyway.
And I don’t even know how to get mad.
You see, I told you that Little Junior
wouldn’t mind it.
I’m telling you.
If you ever dare bully my sister again,
I’ll ask Master to flog your bottom!
Enough.
Stop fighting.
- Little Six.
- Yes?
- Whose side are you on?
- I...
Ling Long, did you forget why
Aunt Ying Hong ask us to come here?
I almost forgot about it.
- Xuan Ji, I’ve got some good news for you.
- Go ahead.
Aunt Hong asked us to serve the sects
during the Flower Picking Session.
- Let’s go down the mountain now.
- Ling Long.
This isn’t a good news.
Can I not go? I want to take a nap here.
- I don’t want to join it.
- No way!
- I’m not joining it!
- Spare me!
- No way!
The five great sects will gather
for the Flower Picking Session.
The aces from the other four sects
are coming too.
We can go check out
those handsome men first.
Let’s go.
You’re acting improperly.
And you’re trying to influence Xuan Ji.
What are you talking about?
I’m already sixteen.
Aunt Hong said
I can look at whoever I like.
Xuan Ji will turn sixteen this year.
We can look at whoever we want.
Let’s go, Xuan Ji.
I...
To test it with
such a powerful demon wolf.
Isn’t it a bit too risky?
Si Feng.
That’s why you’re my descendant.
Only Yu Si Feng passed this set of test.
As of the remaining disciples...
Please spare us, Palace Lord!
Lize Palace doesn’t take in
good-for-nothings.
Let’s do it the old way then.
Get rid of their skills and
chase them out of here.
Please spare us, Palace Lord!
Enough!
You said Si Feng can’t be
the first disciple of Lize Palace
because he’s still young.
But he’s so gifted.
If not he, then who?
When Si Feng wins the
Shaoyang’s Flower Session, I will
grant him the Gold Feather Medallion
and let him take over the Lize Palace.
Since you’ve made up your
mind, we shall obey you.
We’re leaving for the Mount Shaoyang
for Flower Session in a few days.
For many of you, it’ll be
your first time leaving the palace.
I’m reminding you.
What is the first rule
of leaving the palace?
Never take off our masks
in front of outsiders!
I’m glad that you remember it.
You know very well the
consequences of breaking the rule.
Yes!
Si Feng, let’s see who
gets to Shaoyang first.
My lord.
Is there still no news?
We lost God of War and Star of Mosha
at Fenru City sixteen years ago.
And you haven’t found anything since then!
Please don’t get mad, my lord.
I’ve just found out the whereabouts of
Yuntian Loop and Chehai Hook.
But...
But it’s not easy to get hold of them.
My lord.
It has to do with Wu Zhi Qi.
Since they’re with my old
friend, I should meet up with him.
I’ll try my best to sneak our men
into the five sects.
The quadrennial Flower Session
will be held in Shaoyang.
If those two kids are among the crowd,
their unusual powers will be shown
before everyone. And they can’t hide them.
Star of Mosha and God of War
entered the channel on the fourth of
4th month, between 9 to 11 at night.
That’s when they’re born.
Remember.
Don’t miss out any child
who’s born between 9 to 11 at night.
Yes.
SHAOYANG
My fellow seniors from Xuanyuan Sect,
you’ll be staying at Tianzi Pavilion.
Please.
Show the seniors the way.
Yes.
Xuan Ji!
Pull yourself up!
We’re the representatives of Shaoyang.
You can’t embarrass Father.
Yes.
Do you really not want to stay here?
Forget about it, go ahead.
You wouldn’t even
know if you catch a cold.
These are the dog blood for the sacrifice.
Take them home.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Open your eyes and look at it.
Even if you don’t know me,
surely you recognise the sword
made by Dianqinggu Sect.
- You can’t enter without a plaque.
- Stop fighting!
You can talk to me.
Who are you?
I’m the Shaoyang sect leader’s
daughter, Chu Ling Long.
Am I important enough to talk to you?
Ling Long.
This Dianqinggu sect member
insists on entering without a plaque.
You’ll go in only when the elder
of your sect confirms your identity.
- Next.
- What if I insist on going in?
I’m sorry.
You can’t enter without a plaque.
You rude lass.
Are you messing with me?
Fine, look at this.
Ling Long!
I’m alright.
Now that I’ve shown you the plaque,
can I enter now?
You think you can brush me off
with your trivial kungfu?
Any one of our sect members can beat you.
Don’t waste your time
trying to get into it!
Do you think you’re
able to stop me?
How impolite you are!
Don’t come close to my sister!
Xuan Ji!
You said anyone can beat me.
Does it include this lass?
Fine, I’m curious to know
how powerful Shaoyang Sect is!
Xuan Ji!
- Let go of my sister! Xuan Ji!
- What do we do?
Let go of me! Xuan Ji!
Pull out your sword.
What for?
I don’t want to fight with you.
Pull out your sword
or I’ll let go my hand.
Don’t let go!
I don’t know how to use a sword.
I’ll fall down if you let go.
Are you kidding me?
Didn’t you brag about yourself?
How dare Shaoyang Sect call itself
powerful with a good-for-nothing like you.
I’ll show you what being powerful means.
Aren’t you scared?
Cry if you’re scared.
Cry and call yourself a good-for-nothing.
And I’ll let you down.
I was born without the ability to cry.
Have you had enough fun yet?
If so, let me go. I’m sleepy.
Fine, since you refuse to bow down to me,
let’s play a more exciting game.
What do I do? I’ll die for sure if I fall.
And Father will call me
an embarrassment again.
What are you doing?
Your clothes are dirty.
I’ll clean it for you.
Don’t touch me!
Senior, are you here
for the Flower Session?
I’m the disciple of Shaoyang Sect.
But I don’t know how I ended up here.
Could you send me back?
Send me back.
When I get back, I’ll wash off
this dog blood for you.
No need.
What do you want?
Why do you talk like this?
Boring.
Wait a second.
Senior.
I really don’t know how I ended up here.
And I don’t know how to fly.
I can’t go back there.
Walk back then.
No!
It’s too tiring!
I’ve never met such
a lazy cultivator like you.
Where is my sister? Say it!
I don’t know where she fell!
She’s so stupid that
she can’t even stand on a sword.
You are stupid! You’ve lost my sister!
How could you talk like this?
- Have you found Xuan Ji?
- Not yet.
We have yet to search
that dense forest of Shengyun Valley.
Its terrain is complicated.
Sometimes there are demons lurking there.
We’re short-handed and need more people.
I’ll go tell Father now.
- Nothing can happen to her.
- Ling Long.
Xuan Ji!
Are you alright?
This kind and powerful senior saved me.
Great! You must be
a senior from Lize Palace.
You look like gentleman,
unlike that man who is a bully!
Thank you, Brother.
I’d like to enter.
May I register now?
Lize Palace, Yu Si Feng.
I’m quite curious.
You disciples of Lize Palace
wear your masks all the time.
What are you hiding behind them?
What?
Want to fight with me?
Bring it on!
I’m not interested in it.
Everyone is waiting to enter
the Shaoyang Sect.
I see, a little stammer
has saved a little idiot.
That’s very interesting!
I heard that the disciples of
Lize Palace rarely meet women.
You carried this little idiot
all the way back here.
How did it feel like?
Wu Tong, are you
looking for trouble again?
- I’ll your mouth apart!
- No!
- What are you doing?
- Let go of me!
- You...
- What’s going on?
What are you arguing about?
- Aunt.
Master.
I accidentally lost the plaque.
While waiting to enter the Shaoyang Sect,
I’ve pulled a prank on the juniors.
I’m afraid they’re not happy about it.
What prank? You call that a prank?
- You...
- Wu Tong.
You shouldn’t have done so.
Apologise to the daughters
of Sect Leader Chu.
Yes. I was wrong, Master.
Juniors, I apologise.
I didn’t ask you to apologise!
We’re all the disciples of five sects.
We’re all brothers and sisters.
I hope we can help
each other in the future.
You’re right, Elder Chu.
Come with me now.
Yes.
Aunt, how could we
let them go just like that?
Did you know how he bullied Sister?
Thanks to Yu Si Feng
from Lize Palace. He...
He’s left?
Xuan Ji. Did you know? That Yu Si Feng
is the most promising disciple
in Lize Palace.
But their palace rule is to
put on their masks every day.
We don’t know what they look like.
But I bet he’s definitely good-looking.
- Good-looking?
- Yes.
I bet he’s definitely ugly-looking.
Why would he wear his mask all the time?
You’re just being jealous.
What a coincidence!
- What?
- Look.
Yu Si Feng and I
were born in the same year and month,
and on the same day.
It’s true.
Walk back then.
No!
It’s too tiring!
Chu Xuan Ji.
You’re just a lazybones
who sleeps all day!
And you don’t do what you should do!
You’re already sixteen.
But you can’t even summon a sword.
If word gets out, Shaoyang
Sect will be shamed!
Mother!
- Why are you crying?
- Mother!
If you’re watching us from down there,
look at how Father is scolding Xuan Ji!
You’ll be very upset for sure!
You...
Mother said
she just wanted Xuan Ji
to live a steady life.
She didn’t expect her
to be skilled in martial arts.
Did you forget about that?
Xuan Ji is acting this way because
she’s born without the six senses.
She didn’t ask for it.
Who could understand her pain?
Alright, Ling Long.
Mother!
If you insist on punishing Xuan
Ji, I’ll keep crying to Mother!
Okay, forget about it. Stop crying.
There’s a reason why she’s dull.
But it can’t be an excuse
for you to be a lazybones.
Let’s do this.
You have ten days
to master the first
Yaohua sword moves.
If you don’t work hard and
master it, I’ll teach you a lesson.
Okay.
I knew it’d work.
Father can’t do anything about us
whenever I cry to Mother.
But Ling Long, this
is indeed useful.
This is the most important weapon.
It works not only on Father.
If your future lover dotes on you,
he can’t do anything about you
when you cry.
Is that so?
But I don’t have this.
I think tears are the most precious
thing in the world, aren’t they?
When you got mad today,
did your eyes feel tingly
that you felt like crying?
I did feel quite angry.
But I thought I didn’t need to
take them seriously.
As long as you’re happy.
Instead of taking them seriously,
I’d rather go take a nap.
Then do you...
Little Six.
Are you here to send us the birthday cake?
I’m the sender.
But Master was the one
who asked to prepare it.
This is Bazhen cake.
And it’s made from eight ingredients.
It’s true that Father is fierce.
But he dotes on us.
Let’s eat now.
Xuan Ji.
It’s so delicious.
Xuan Ji, it’s such a shame
that you can’t taste it.
Can you not bring that up?
It’s okay if I can’t taste it.
As long as Ling Long
enjoys eating it, I’m happy.
Our Xuan Ji is such a good girl.
But Father isn’t satisfied with her.
Jeez!
Today is that
little stammer’s birthday too!
Si Feng?
Si Feng!
Is Si Feng around?
- Si Feng!
- Someone is looking for you.
Why are you looking for me?
Little Stammer, you forgot your plaque.
I came to return it to you.
Anything else?
- Oh yeah, Little Stammer.
- I’m not Little Stammer.
Then why do you
stumble over three words?
None of your business.
You can stumble over two words too.
Just leave if there’s nothing else.
Here’s the thing, miss.
Si Feng has always stayed in Lize Palace.
And he’s new to Zhongyuan.
He’s not so fluent in Zhongyuan language.
I hope you don’t mind.
I’ll leave you two to it.
I see.
I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Chu Xuan Ji.
Thank you for saving and
sending me back to Shaoyang.
You’re the first best friend
I made outside Shaoyang.
Today is our birthday.
Therefore, I’ve brought you
a birthday cake.
We share the same birthday.
Ling Long said fate brought us together.
What fate?
Stop talking nonsense.
We’re not friends.
And I never eat birthday cakes.
I’ve finally found a peach tree.
And there’s morning dew.
Where’s Xuan Ji? Master asked me
to teach her Yaohua sword moves.
Why is she nowhere to be seen?
She must be taking a nap somewhere.
It’s wrong to steal bird eggs.
Get it?
It’s you again.
It’s you, Little Stammer.
Why is it always you?
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to knock over your tea.
There’s a mountain spring.
I’ll go fetch you some water.
- Wait for me.
- No need.
Peach dew.
Buddha’s hand.
Pine nut.
They make triple purity drink.
A cup a day helps one’s cultivation.
I’m not drinking if it’s not peach dew.
Why are you being so particular?
It’s just tea. Is there any difference?
I’ve never met
a lazybones like you.
And you know nothing.
And you’re poor at spell casting.
No wonder you get bullied.
You’re useless.
You...
I’m useless.
But I didn’t mean to knock over your tea.
I saw a bad snake which
tried to steal bird eggs.
I wanted to catch it.
And I accidentally...
It’s that bad snake again!
Let go! Let go of it!
This is my spirit beast.
I’m sorry. I didn’t mean to pinch it.
Is it dead?
Tell me.
Why
did you pinch it?
Because it came to me.
I thought it’d bite me for sure.
Don’t mimic the way I talk.
What do we do then?
Should I let my father have a look at it?
He might be able to save it.
Silver Snake!
Where are you, Silver Snake?
Why is your spirit beast so disobedient?
My father’s shows itself
at once when we call it.
It’s still young and immature.
Don’t talk bad about it.
I feel it’s being attracted by something.
This peach forest is strange indeed.
We’ve been looking for Silver Snake.
But it’s nowhere to be found.
There...
There’s something wrong
about this peach forest.
Little Stammer.
Do you feel hot?
I... I don’t.
Don’t you?
Little Stammer.
We’re of the same age.
But why are you so knowledgeable?
Stop talking.
This formation is difficult.
Why are we here on the lake surface?
Little Stammer, are you alright?
This isn’t a lake surface.
There’s a barrier here.
Barrier?
It’s really a barrier.
I know why there’s
a peach formation out there.
This is the secret ground
of Shaoyang Sect.
How did we end up here?
How do we get in?
I don’t know. Shaoyang Sect disciple
aren’t allowed to come near here.
I want to enter it.
No way!
This is the forbidden ground
of Shaoyang Sect.
Without Father’s permission,
you can’t set foot in it.
Are you alright, Little Stammer?
How do we open it?
I don’t know.
We shouldn’t be here.
- Let’s go now.
- We’re running out of time!
I’m connected to my spirit animal.
Silver Snake has
been attracted into it.
If I don’t save it,
it’ll be in danger!
Open it!
Let’s head back and ask for help.
- What do you think?
- We’re running out of time!
I...
I can do nothing about it.
I’m so poor at spell casting.
This is the most ancient barrier
set by the most powerful elder
in our sect.
There’s no way I can open it.
Watch it.
It’s open.
How did I open it?
- Open it!
- No way!
If my father finds out, I’m dead meat.
Chu Xuan Ji!
Silver Snake is dying!
I...
We’ll come out after saving Silver Snake.
Your father won’t find out about it.
Won’t he? I’ll...
Okay. You helped me once.
I’ll help you this once.
There’s something powerful in there.
Don’t come in no matter what.
Okay. Hurry up.
Silver Snake.
Silver Snake!
Little Stammer!
Don’t you bully Little Stammer!
Don’t hit Little Stammer! Let go of him!
Shut up!
- Why did you come in here?
- I’m here to save you, Little Stammer.
Run!
Are you alright, Little Stammer?
This is Candle Dragon.
It’s very powerful.
You can’t save me.
Run!
Is it powerful? Let’s run together then!
Little Stammer!
Are you alright, Little Stammer?
You’re bleeding.
Little Stammer.
You’re alright.
Thank God you’re okay.
Little Stammer.
Thank God you’ve woken up.
My... My mask.
It’s missing!
Your face was bleeding.
That’s why I took your mask off.
- Where’s the mask?
- The mask is over there.