LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 16
Xuan Ji, did you remove my mask?
Yes.
If the person you love
only has eyes for you,
the person will be able to
remove the mask.
And the mask will
turn into a smiling mask.
What’s going on?
The Mark of Green Feather
hasn’t disappeared.
And I still have
the Loveless Curse within me.
Si Feng, what’s wrong?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
It’s nothing.
Don’t worry.
The mask has been removed.
It’s not important whether
it’s smiling or not.
What’s more important now is
that we should leave this place.
Let’s go.
Let’s go and see the staff
you talked about.
I...
Let’s go. Why are you standing there?
Let’s go.
Si Feng, it’s this staff.
When I touched it last time,
it struck me with lightning.
This barrier is formed according
to the Eight Trigrams.
I think the staff is
the eye of the formation.
I’ll see if I can break the formation
from the top.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, are you okay?
Let go of Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji, don’t go over there!
Si Feng, I want to save you!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji, let go of it!
Such impudence!
You never learn your lesson!
Xuan Ji!
I’m not in the wrong!
What did I do wrong?
You were in the wrong!
It’s you!
Dingkun Sword!
Si Feng.
The barrier surrounding
Dingkun Sword is broken.
God of War,
I’ve finally found you.
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
Si Feng?
- Why are you hurt?
- I’m fine.
What just happened?
What happened?
The earth was trembling just now.
This is not a staff. It’s a divine sword.
I saw the general calling its name
within the Mirror of Origin.
Its name was
Dingkun Sword.
What’s going on?
Seems like the barrier was
used to seal away the sword.
But you broke the seal by accident.
And you became
the owner of the divine sword.
The sword is immensely powerful.
Seems like it doesn’t
belong to the human realm.
Maybe it’s connected
to you somehow.
Every time when I obtain
a shard of the Mirror of Origin,
I’ll see a vision of
a general dressed in armour.
But this time, when I held
the sword in my hand,
I saw her face clearly.
She looked just like me.
I always thought this was only a dream.
But now, it seems different
from what I expected.
I feel familiar holding
the sword in my hand.
And, I felt like her experiences
were my own experiences.
It seems that she suffered injustice.
Si Feng, what exactly is going on?
Who’s that general?
Why does she look just like me?
And why does she keep
appearing in my mind?
I don’t know what’s going on.
Xuan Ji, don’t be afraid.
No matter what happens,
you’ll always be Chu Xuan Ji.
But,
Ting Nu said
I am me, yet I am not.
Who exactly am I?
Since the Mirror of
Origin shows all origins,
maybe those visions
were you in your past life.
Maybe
your lack of six senses have something
to do with your past life as well.
Xuan Ji, don’t worry.
Everything will be explained
once we collect all the shards.
Believe me.
Si Feng!
Si Feng?
Where’s your mask?
It came down by chance.
Congratulations.
So, we have to congratulate someone
when their mask is removed?
Ruo Yu, I need to
congratulate you as well.
My mask is different from Si Feng’s.
- Si Feng is...
- This is not the time.
We need to leave.
Xuan Ji, go and check if
there are any demons around here.
We’ll travel to Fuyu Island later.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Si Feng, I lost my mask.
I need to return to Lize Palace
and receive my punishment.
I’m afraid I can’t accompany
you anymore.
It’s lucky that
your mask wasn’t destroyed.
You just lost it.
And you don’t have a person you fancy.
If you return and apologise,
maybe you’ll be able to avoid
the 13 Punishments.
Take care.
Master.
Silver Snake, I need you
to do something for me.
You’re not a human.
You can sneak into Sky Hall and
find out about the location of the shards.
You mustn’t act rashly
if you find out anything.
Just return and report to me.
Master, are you still trying to help
Chu Xuan Ji find the Mirror of Origin?
I’m not going. I’m your spirit beast.
I’ll follow you wherever you go.
Besides, you may
hide the truth from others,
but you can’t hide it from me.
Master, Chu Xuan Ji removed your mask,
but she didn’t dispel the curse.
What’s going on?
This won’t happen if
she has you in her heart.
I don’t know what went wrong,
but the Loveless Curse hasn’t
acted up yet. No need to fear.
Why are you lying to yourself?
If she hurts your heart,
the Loveless Curse will trigger.
When the feather mark from your wrist
disappears and travels to your chest,
it’ll be too late by then.
- Master!
- Why are you cursing me?
I’m your master.
If I die, you’ll be homeless.
- Master...
- Don’t worry.
This is my body. I know my body the best.
And I think this has something to do
with her lack of six senses.
I asked you to find the shards
because of my own interest.
I have no choice. She’s the one
who put the curse on you.
Master, if she dares to hurt you,
- I won’t forgive her.
- Silver Snake,
I don’t like the way you speak.
Fine.
I’ll go.
Be careful.
Greetings, King Bailing.
Didn’t I ask you not to
look for me in the human realm?
Did something happen
in the heavenly realm?
It’s not that.
A moment in the heavenly realm
is a few decades in the human realm.
About your visit to the human realm,
no one in the heavenly realm
knows about it yet.
Of course, it’s because
I was great at hiding things.
Why are you here then?
My king, I’m writing this book
called "Tales of the Three Realms".
But I had obtained no new materials
ever since you came down here.
I’ve put it aside for decades.
But today, there are
some changes happening.
I’m here to ask about
your thoughts on them.
So that my story
would be more interesting.
What changes?
I forgot that you can’t use your power
once you’re in the human realm.
That’s why you’re in the dark.
She... She escaped
your grasp again.
And she managed to unseal
the Dingkun Sword again.
After such a long time, you
managed to find Dingkun Sword again.
Seems like it’s fate.
This is my script.
My king, do you want to read it?
My king, you were the one
who brought up the God of War.
And she became famous
in the heavenly realm.
I was thinking that if you two
became an item,
everyone would be envious.
It’s a pity that both you and her
are too calm and collected.
I was anxious.
That’s why I made the decision to
make the story between you and her
the most important chapter
in "Tales of the Three Realms".
But before I wrote my story,
the God of War was punished
and sent to the human realm.
You’re awake?
Who are you?
I’m King Bailing.
Who am I?
You’re my God of War.
I saved you.
I gave you life.
Your entire life belongs to me.
You will fight for the heavenly realm.
God of War!
I won.
I told you before.
I trust you the most.
God of War!
My king!
God of War?
I’m too late.
I’ve been guarding the
Dingkun Sword for 1,000 years.
Yet she just took it away just like that.
She didn’t even stay here
to fight with me.
She’s despicable! This won’t do.
I need to find her.
I need to fight her to my heart’s content.
Who are you?
This stench is so familiar.
Green Dragon, let me go.
I have business to attend to.
Someone removed the Dingkun Sword
used by God of War.
Green Dragon,
let’s talk over this.
Guarding the Dingkun Sword
is my responsibility.
I need to retrieve it.
No need for that.
King Bailing has a message for you.
No one is to ever ask about or
involve themselves with the God of War.
You don’t have to go.
But why?
How dare you question
King Bailing’s order?
Green Dragon, let go of me.
You!
That was close.
It’s lucky that you marked yourself
with the Mark of Concealment.
Even immortals can’t see you.
If not, trouble would arise
if that Flying Snake saw you.
I’ve expected
Flying Snake to create trouble.
That’s why I locked him up.
I didn’t expect him to
sneak to the human realm.
That’s right.
Flying Snake doesn’t even know
the God of War.
But he’s stubborn in pursuing
Does he think he can pursue
the God of War?
Does he think he’s you?
He’s overestimating himself.
I didn’t come down to pursue her.
I’m here for the three realms.
The king descended into
the human realm for the God of War.
If you write nonsense like that,
I’ll burn your book.
I mean for the three realms.
My king, it’s a pity.
You’ve done so much just to come here.
But the God of War still
managed to retrieve Dingkun Sword.
Dingkun Sword is an evil sword.
The God of War had slain
countless demons using it.
It’s filled with anguish.
Seems like your wish
will not be granted again.
My king, God of War will
face another trial today.
So what?
She has failed the previous nine trials.
Today is the tenth trial.
If she fails again, she’ll never
return to the heavenly realm.
I’ve received another news as well.
Some demons are trying to
locate the God of War.
You failed every trial you had faced.
Why can’t you just get over yourself?
My king, you’re the ruler of our realm.
How could you ignore everything
and descend into the human realm?
If I ignore the God of War any
longer, she’ll become a demon.
I knew it.
My king, you cherish her so much.
It’s impossible for you to ignore her.
You still have her in your heart.
This is too touching.
No, I must write this down in my book.
I’m not concerned about her.
I’m just concerned about the three realms.
As long as her hatred doesn’t overflow
and she leads her life in peace,
the three realms will be saved
from another disaster.
And I can guide her
to become an immortal again.
So that she can return here.
But, my king,
this...
Immortals mustn’t interfere
with human affairs.
If you descend into the human realm,
Jade Emperor will find out.
And he’ll blame you.
That’s why I’m here
at the Altar of Banishment.
To hide your tracks,
you’re skipping the Path of Reincarnation.
You’re trying to become a human by force.
My king, you’re the ruler
of the heavenly realm!
You’ll be punished by Nature’s law
if you do so.
Not only will you suffer tremendous pain,
you can’t use any of your powers as well.
And it’ll be hard for you
to practise any spells as a human.
How are you going to protect yourself?
I don’t care even if I have to
use ten years in the human realm
to change her destiny.
If I want to do
it, I will do it.
My king.
My king!
Your skills have improved tremendously.
I’m very relieved.
Master, it’s all thanks to your guidance.
If you didn’t help me when
I was seriously injured
and take me as your disciple, I
wouldn’t have accomplished this.
I told you before.
If I want to do
it, I will do it.
No matter what happens, I’ll lead
her back to the heavenly realm.
My lady, how’s it going?
Let me out.
You can’t stand it anymore?
I told you before.
There are many things
scarier than death itself.
Now, you can only choose
the path I gave you.
You can either stay here and suffer,
or kneel down and beg me.
In your dreams.
Great.
I knew it.
You’re more interesting than the others.
You’ve been trying to go against me
ever since we met.
And you tried to offend me
in every way possible.
I knew you were different from them.
Of course you won’t submit.
The young lady from Shaoyang Sect
is precious and proud, right?
I still have many things waiting for you.
I will definitely kill you.
What did you say?
Say it louder.
I will definitely kill you.
I will definitely kill you!
Let go!
You lunatic!
How dare you bite me
when you’re in this situation!
I’m liking you more and more.
Don’t touch me! I’m going to search
for Dingkun Sword.
- I promise I won’t do anything else.
- You’re just trying to fight!
Stop fooling around! Stay put.
Old Guy?
Old Guy.
You’re acting weird.
Lord Flying Snake, I saw you two
fighting just now.
I wanted to stop the fight,
but you know I’m timid.
My skills are limited
and I’m afraid to take a beating.
That’s why I didn’t go and help.
- My lord!
- Stop it.
What is this?
It’s...
Tales of the Three Realms, Lord
Snake and his beloved Phoenix.
My lord, you should return it to me.
What is this?
He, Flying Snake,
is the handsome king of fighter
in the heavenly realm.
A fateful encounter has reduced
his tough demeanour into gentleness.
And he was willing to ignore
everything else.
He, Green Dragon, is
the charming immortal.
A fateful encounter
has caused him to have difficulties
choosing between love and friendship.
It’s all because of Ling Qin
of the phoenix tribe.
She was elegant and gorgeous.
She was a true beauty.
Hold it right there.
Why do I feel disgusted?
The handsome king of
fighter, I’m sure that’s me.
Yes.
The charming immortal,
are you talking about him?
But who’s Ling Qin?
Ling Qin inherits her skill
from Lord Xuan Huo.
She’s a relative of Lord Phoenix.
She’s young and talented.
She became the leader of 28 stars
when she first ascended to this realm.
She’s amazing.
I heard of her before.
But I heard that she stays
in the Southern Star Palace
and she rarely goes out.
How is she connected to us?
Lord Flying Snake,
seems like you were too busy
to remember this.
Don’t you remember?
You saved a sparrow once.
That sparrow is Ling Qin.
She couldn’t forget you.
But Lord Green Dragon couldn’t forget her.
Please don’t think that my stories
were all made up. I have evidences.
Just now, it seemed like you two
fought for no reason.
But in reality, it’s because of love.
Wait.
You’re saying it’s a one-sided love on
my part, and I even lost to Flying Snake?
- No.
- Change it!
My lord!
Si Ming, I think your
story was well-written.
Keep up the good work.
Sure.
Pian Pian, Yu Ning, please
plead with Master on my behalf.
We did nothing wrong.
We don’t know what’s going on.
But why is he chasing us off the island?
Senior, calm down.
We’ll try to understand
the reason behind his rage.
And we’ll plead with him after that.
Thank you.
Everyone, calm down.
We should return for now.
- Let’s go.
I’m Yu Si Feng.
This is Chu Xuan Ji from Shaoyang Sect.
We need to meet Lord Dong Fang.
Please notify him for us.
I’m Pian Pian.
This is Yu Ning.
If you two want to enter the island,
you two can follow us.
Please.
Senior Hao Chen.
I didn’t write my reflections lately.
Please don’t be angry.
But I have good news.
I have mended my relationship
with Si Feng.
I think that is the most exciting news.
Si Feng changed his plans
and followed us on our journey.
Si Feng’s skills have
improved tremendously.
He knows a lot as well.
It’s lucky that he’s with us
on our adventures.
Senior, you don’t need to worry.
I forgot to tell you this. Min Yan
and Ling Long had patched up as well.
They like each other.
It’s not me.
I made a huge joke out of myself.
It’s lucky that Si Feng was around.
I managed to understand
these things under his help.
Si Feng is amazing.
He helped us a lot on our journey.
Yu Si Feng.
Senior Hao Chen, this is
the most important news.
Please pass this message to Father.
We suspect that Xuanyuan Sect
was harmed by the Sky Hall.
Sect Leader Zhu Shi handed
the Destiny Pearl to me.
After that, we were ambushed by them
and got separated.
Si Feng and I are trying to
enter Fuyu Island right now.
Ling Long and Sixth Senior
should be on the island now.
Before Sect Leader Ling Shi passed away,
he said the Sky Hall
had taken control of Xuanyuan Sect.
Wu Tong said that as well.
But we haven’t confirmed that
for ourselves.
That explains it.
Although the Xuanyuan Sect
is getting weaker and weaker,
it is still one of the Five Great Sects.
There’s no way Sky Hall can destroy
a sect like that without alerting others.
I think Sect Leader Ling Shi
must’ve consumed too much demon pills
for him to utter something like that.
I know our words have no weight.
You may not believe in us,
but Sect Leader wouldn’t have
given us the Destiny Pearl
if he had a choice.
The Destiny Pearl?
Uncle Dong Fang, this is the Destiny Pearl
Sect Leader Zhu Shi gave me.
It is the Destiny Pearl indeed.
This is the sacred item of Xuanyuan Sect.
Seems like we need to investigate this.
Xuan Ji, can I hold on
to the Destiny Pearl for now?
Of course you can, Uncle Dong Fang.
The Sky Hall wanted this pearl
because of the spirit key.
They want to revive the Star of Mosha.
Star of Mosha?
I don’t know what it is either.
But I heard that it has the power
to dominate the three realms.
Dominate the three realms?
What a joke.
The Star of Mosha was vanquished
1,000 years ago.
How could they revive it?
If they could revive the Star of Mosha,
I could revive the immortal, Pan Gu.
My lord, the Sky Hall is
harbouring such ambition indeed.
And they’re trying to execute
their plans now.
Xuanyuan Sect is just a start.
I’m afraid they would
go after Lize Palace,
Dianjinggu Sect, Shaoyang
Sect, or even Fuyu Island.
They can come then!
I’m not afraid of them!
Relay my orders!
Activate the Sword Formation!
I want to see if the demons
can penetrate my formation!
My lord,
Madam’s birthday will arrive soon.
All the other sects will be here as well.
If we activate the formation,
everyone will panic.
Moreover, we still need to
investigate the Xuanyuan Sect.
Just activate the formation! No excuses!
How dare the Sky Hall
try to create trouble!
I’ll vanquish all of them!
- Uncle Dong Fang, wait...
- What?
Youngsters have no right
to interfere with this!
It’s late now.
Ask someone to clean up their rooms
and bring them to rest.
Uncle Dong Fang, can you
ask someone to escort us off the island?
- I’ll look for Ling Long and Sixth Senior.
- Of course not!
The Sky Hall is looking for you.
It’s not safe for you outside!
Xuan Ji, it’s fine.
Don’t worry. I’ll send someone
to Mount Gao
in order to find Ling Long and Min Yan.
- But I want to go there...
- Such impudence!
I have the same rank as your father!
How dare you disobey me!
I can’t bear the responsibility if
something happens to you, you know?
I’m sorry. I’m tired.
You should rest now.
I’ll set up a feast for you tonight.
Xuan Ji, you don’t need to worry.
We will find Ling Long and Min Yan.
Go now.
The houses here are empty.
They’re fully-furnished as well.
Just pick a house you like.
Just tell me if you need anything else.
My master
is not acting like his usual self.
You must’ve been shocked.
It’s fine.
Did Lord Dong Fang go somewhere
or encounter something strange?
It’s been half a year since
my master left the island.
Besides his normal training,
he’ll accompany his wife
and do some gardening.
There’s nothing strange going on.
So, Madam Dong Fang is responsible
for the beautiful scenery on this island.
It’s such a wonder.
Where does she come from?
She came from Mount Zitong.
After that, my master...
My master has activated the Sword Trap.
You need his permission
if you want to leave the island.
So that you wouldn’t be hurt by the trap.
Si Feng, Uncle Dong Fang
was acting strange.
I can’t get through him at all.
We can’t find Ling Long and Sixth Senior
since he has locked us in.
Calm down.
Lord Dong Fang has sent someone
to search for them.
Ling Long and Min Yan are chivalrous.
Maybe they were delayed because
they were helping others out.
But Lord Dong Fang is strangely anxious.
Something’s wrong.
Seems like he was bewitched.
- Bewitched?
- I’m not too sure either.
But there are red rashes on his arm.
And it gives out a sweet scent.
Those were the same symptoms
I saw in someone who was bewitched.
Regarding the truth, we’ll
find out in the feast tonight.
He activated the Sword Formation.
Everyone is panicking.
Just forget about all the joyous occasion.
Steward Ouyang, our
lord is acting strange lately.
What do you think?
I’m just a steward.
It’s better for me
not to ask questions like these.
But it’s good for us
to act more cautiously.
It’s hard to say. Maybe Sky Hall
would invade the island.
If they dare to come, they
will die under the Sword Trap.
Today, you two get to try
the special Flower Wine in Fuyu Island.
They’re freshly brewed.
It’s the best time to try them.
Go and find out where Madam is.
Yes.
How’s the taste?
It’s fragrant and sweet.
It’s delicious.
Youngsters have no worries indeed.
That’s why you can taste the wine.
If we have too many troubles on our mind,
we can’t taste the wine.
My lord, I’m impressed.
You’re an expert in wine tasting.
I brought some special wine
from Lize Palace as well.
My lord, please try it.
Bring it to me.
Why doesn’t it taste like wine?
It tastes like water.
- Because...
- Seems like I’m late.
Dear!
QIYU HALL
My dear, you’re here.
- My dear.
- Greetings, Madam.
Is she the daughter of Sect Leader Chu?
Yes.
She’s such a beauty now.
So, he’s the favourite
disciple of Lize Palace?
It’s rare for me to see a disciple
of Lize Palace without his mask.
This is very rare indeed.
Qing Rong, did you drink again?
What? Can’t I drink?
Of course you can.
Did you drink by yourself
or did you drink with someone else?
Why should I tell you?
Come, my dear.
What wine is this?
This is the wine Hero Yu
brought from Lize Palace.
Why don’t you try it?
How’s the taste?
Although it’s bland,
it has a delicate scent.
It’s much better than the wine
in Fuyu Island.
Good! You can drink more if you like it.
I heard that Xuanyuan Sect was in trouble.
Although Xuanyuan Sect
is one of the Five Great Sects,
it’s corrupted inside.
They deserved everything.
Qing Rong, that’s enough.
You should drink less.
It’s not suitable for
you to say that, right?
Xuan Ji, Hero Yu,
don’t just sit over there.
Enjoy the food and wine as well.